[Music]
n
a
[Music]
n
oh
hi long time no
see look at
that it's already my
birthday on the East Coast countdown's
over
everybody just kidding we're going to
count down until it's my birthday in CST
and then MST and then PST and we're
going to probably stop there yeah hi
hello how we
doing hello
again did we watch V oh my
goodness oh my goodness she's so
cute she's so cute she's so precious my
my goodness she fell so many
times she fell so many times it must
have been so
painful the things that she's she's
willing to
do for such a wonderful 3D Live u b boo
u u
[Music]
u so much happening so much this week my
brain's going to
explode by the end of this weekend I
think I'm going to take a 24-hour
nap just so much excitement like a
toddler take them to the water park and
they're out for 3
days you don't even have to wait no
never mind you still have to feed them
you still have to take care of them I'm
I'm thinking of something else I think
I'm thinking of a sloth I'm sorry not a
toddler a sloth you take the sloth to
the water park and then they can rest
for 3
Days m
anyways it is
not that time yet we are not past the
weekend we are in the middle of it right
now and that means uh we're doing stuff
wait what I'm sorry I really have to
cough and I'm trying so hard not to but
I can't think of my words very well as I
physically try to restrain
myself to keep myself from coughing
perhaps I should just cough so that I
can make sentences that makes sense and
use my
words pardon
me no background
music it was just very quiet for some
reason so quiet perhaps I was scared of
it being too loud for all of
you oh I should have never said
anything too loud it isn't you have you
have dials you have a mouse you can
click button
it's not stop it you're going to confuse
me you're confusing the M stop confusing
the M stop tormenting m
[Music]
m okay I did it I coughed I can think a
little tiny bit better now this is the
part of the weekend the part of the
marathon if we can call it that not at
this point but this is the part of the
day where I do the tot Marti but it's a
special one because I'm going to draw my
guests instead of receiving gifts I'm
giving
gifts I also do not think enough people
will show up to fill an entire 3 hours
so I'm going to be stalling a lot I also
do not have designated times for
everyone who gave a heads up that they
would join so it's going to be a bit of
a mess honestly I would be fine with
multiple people joining at once if they
really want to I don't really know how
to set up a Quee here but I think I know
who the first person is going to be
because she asked but I'm so sorry I'm
keeping her waiting
but but before that here let me say some
things first thing do you guys like my
[Music]
hair it's new is I did it
today you do oh yeah you were there oh
yeah you were there when I did
it thank you I'm glad you like it um
okay second thing I have a 3D Live my
first birthday 3D Live First full 3d
live I had my 3D showcase that was a
showcase where I talked and did skits
did some singing I think about half of
it was singing maybe but tomorrow it is
dedicated to
performances which do not include skits
I suppose it's it's for
singing more singing so that's why I
feel like it's my first actual live cuz
I feel well I know some members they
have 3D lives but they're not totally
focused on
singing they got lots of stuff going on
in there anyways more
tomorrow
yeah exciting stuff I think that's all I
have to say and I really hope I set this
up properly I haven't used this method
of drawing in a long
time I also I thought I got an
optimal method for putting icons but now
now that I think about it I don't think
it is it's probably going to be even
more difficult but it's okay it's okay
like I said we have about 2 hours and 40
minutes so we got to fill that time with
with
nonsense all right here is the
Box hold on where did I just here and
here's my pencil
okay here's that and does it work oh it
does not work yet hold on a second hold
on a second it's a box no I'm not no
we're drawing inside the box outside the
box is
tomorrow right now I'm drawing Inside
the Box do I have to put this here I
think I do
okay modest moose is me
apparently can I change my
name what I don't think I can I don't
know how to that's okay do not
fret do not fret we know who this modest
moose is and it is
me it
works yes I'm going to have guess I'm
going to either they're either going to
say I can draw whatever I want or
they're going to ask me to draw
something in particular but if they ask
for something in particular I will most
likely need a reference
[Music]
Tada can you
see
okay all good and I will only draw as
long as whoever joins me is in the
call there's a challenge there wait
where's my
ponytail forgot about it
I have to get used to the lay of this
program
[Music]
again okay let me double check that
everything is set up properly hold
on hold on hold on let's see okay icons
check but I have to edit them I set it
up so I edit it in Photoshop no clue how
that's going to go okay Discord thing I
think that's set up too we will find out
how it looks in a second okay
uh we have music we have
um this is Discord audio okay we have
Discord audio okay we have I think we
have everything okie dokie I shall
[Music]
now I didn't ask for this but I'm
keeping this thank
you oh wait oh wait wait wa she's
thinking I had okay okay I'm going to go
oh she's waiting for me oh my goodness
is this one of the is this the first
tosu where they're waiting for me in the
VC before I I even join I'm Coming For
You
K well I'm
Deen hello oh hello oh hello oh hello
hello oh hi oh hi oh hi you oh hi hi I'm
so sorry you're the test subject
everybody can you hear
her test test
I am the test subject she is the test
subject my little experiment
hello experiment on me too quiet she's
too quiet I me oh louder louder louder I
wonder if it's hold on I'll just okay
may you please speak please I am
speaking Kitty hello happy birthday hi
let's go oh hi oh hi oh hi oh hi oh hi
oh yes are you away from home right now
yes yes yes indeed I am good morning
it's so sometimes weird to talk to you
when it's this late for
me yeah normally at this time yeah I
wouldn't want to be awake at this time
if I was in Austria but now it's fine I
completely
understand at this point nearly 3 years
in I'm also reaching the point where if
stuff is
too late or too early for
me I it's unlikely I can do it now I
bring myself to do it it messes you
up yeah I agree I'm I'm amazed like the
the new girls they're staying up like to
who knows what time it is for them like
3: 4 a.m. for just collab of their
Senpai they're like so so committed to
being awake whenever they're needed but
yeah couldn't be me yeah it he used to
be easier for me I used to be able to do
it and then just go about my day and
then sleep again at night but if it's a
day where I have to wake up like or if
the thing I need to attend is at 3:00
a.m. 4:00 a.m. 5 like 5:00 a.m. is the
worst no 4:00 a.m. I'm sorry 4:00 a.m.
is the absolute worst mhm that's like
for 3:00 a.m. you can stay up but 4:00
a.m. do you really want to stay up until
4: a.m. because then it's going to take
longer maybe it ends at 5 a.m. ex you
stay up till then and then when it's
over it's like 600 or 7 a.m. mhm then
what are you left yeah yeah you're left
with being sleep oh it's okay they'll
adjust to us we're we're done
adjusting we're done with that oh dear
are you going to put up like uh I just
want to check if you're not forgetting
it because you seem a little bit
stressed out do you want to put up a
picture of the caller or I want to do oh
see you were kind enough to send me a
beautiful picture of yourself I was just
going to do Twitter icons but because
you sent me that I'm going to use it
hold on actually that was going to be
the reference but you can put it up as
the collar picture too wait hold on my
bra I'm going to use your icon and I'm
going to draw the reference okay I'm
going to do that yeah that sounds good
okay okay that's okay you were think you
were thinking even more ahead that's
even further make it easier for you have
things ready yes I definitely need a
reference I realize I hope people come
prepared with what they want okay I take
your okay I'm going to do this I'm going
to do this as fast as I possibly can
okay yeah take your time
time you know I feel like I'm I'm I I've
done this before I feel like I'm sitting
in like you know one of those places
like on a chair where people one one
person will draw you like a character
chair this is how it feels yeah like the
on the street where they
make no yeah yeah sometimes crazy most
of the time they make you look crazy
sometimes sometimes can be pretty cute
too yes today will be cute right
whatever you want do you want cute yeah
yeah cute please I I love your cursed
things but today please throw me cute
okay I'm going to do my best here can
they see oh I don't think they can see
hold on I only have so many monitors oh
this was not this wasn't planned very
well okay okay wait let me maybe do this
it's okay chill chill M don't dress
thank you take your time I'm at complete
now
brief I have DMS what are people saying
to me it's okay it's okay all right I
can put you here don't talk to her now
talk to me
instead hi hi it works okay we're
drawing inside the box I like that joke
by the way today we're drawing Inside
the Box tomorrow
we're you'll see why did you why did you
call it that will we find out you will
find out okay yes we'll find
it's not I like that I promise it's not
that
deep but the box is not that deep yeah
oh so it's a very shallow box yes oh
quite shallow interesting how many
people can you fit into a shallow box
then maybe they have to lie down if it's
shallow have you ever ordered a um a TV
oh a TV yeah yeah that's how sh out the
box is yeah that's that's the type of
box it is oh so a big p
books yeah basically it's
sure nice okay interesting I'm I'm
interested if that's that's going to be
like a gimmick or
[Music]
something oh cof somebody said coffin oh
my God are you putting people in coffins
are you are you on theing them
um cofin not not or not today and not
tomorrow can you like notify me ahead of
time when the day is when you on the
live us um so I can make plans and plan
around it yes because you asked so far
in advance I can yes thank you oh so it
will be pretty far in the future okay
okay that's that's good to know so I
still have a few days can okay how do I
do this sorry your hair I love it but
how do I cute already look at this I
hope it actually looks like you yeah
just might it really fluffy you know
like fluffy hair from the 80s or 70s
yeah I forgot what the style is called
I think it's making a
comeback there's a name to the style to
the hairstyle or to the like the really
fluffy high volume yeah yeah is there a
name for it there is I there's like a
process I don't know what it's called oh
perming you hear I think isn't perming
more like I should really share my
screen shouldn't I sorry oh I I'm
watching an on YouTube it's fine I think
perming really good curls it but I could
be wrong yeah
is that what it is a
blowout I yeah I think so okay blowout
watching you know the friends and
Seinfeld I think they they have like a
messy blow like a messy blowout yeah
yeah yeah yeah it's super cute but you
know more than the hair I'm more
interested in like this type of workout
clothing coming
back is it oh my gosh I
can't what are they called what are your
the yes that's what it is but like
really high cut leotards and then tights
like shiny tights underneath no not
necessarily shiny they're not all shiny
but I chose mine to be shiny so I'm glad
you did the coloring is very
pleasing thank you I'm very sorry but
I'm I'm only going to draw this much of
you oh what no booty do you want or crot
I could do like a separate like on the
side no that's fine that's fine that's
fine this is fine don't worry oh shoot I
forgot how to deselect
here how do I
deselect I don't know what you're even
using I'm on
magma oh no idea what that is I forgot I
pay a monthly subscription for what is
the thing I'm supposed to do somebody
look up the book do you have a
booklet do I just tutorial book is there
a edit desect I found it okay okay oh
you it I got it you know I've been kind
of fantasizing that um because this
outfit has been making its rounds and I
feel like it would be really great to
see every possible member ideally every
holot toi member wearing their own color
variation of this what do you think I
would love to see not that you would
draw it now but you could you could draw
yourselfbe not now
but perhap I don't think I'm good enough
at Anatomy I'm appreciating Anatomy but
I'm not good at Anatomy myself
especially now I'm very out of practice
what happened to this brush what the
heck I know if I ever saw you draw non
chibi uh probably
not probably not it's been a
bit I don't have a reference I don't
have a butt
reference oh are you are trying to booty
now I'm trying I don't remember what
butts look
like I don't know what the back looks
like I don't know what like where's the
hip is it there like
well the back is basically just you know
high cut leotard from the back this is
like a very tight one also I need to
clothe it hold on yes tight quickly now
before YouTube sees what have I done
what have I done why won't it let me
clothe it hello hello oh it doesn't have
to be clothed but it's
YouTube this is
educational no this is fine is a process
I believe in the process you know why is
this it's it's a really tight butt it's
like somebody
flexing yeah no good oh very good need
to be bigger very nice oh yes yeah yeah
yeah yeah you get it you get it go there
we go okay okay bigger thighs too I
think yes press four on those thighs you
know I don't know if you saw my 3D
stream that I did with this but this
outfit I do have a toggle to make the F
bigger I did not see that I did see
parts of
it I actually it was already made bigger
throughout the whole stream but I have
one more toggle to make it even bigger
than
that sorry I'm confused is my why are
people saying four is that the toggle ah
no the four press four is the Chimera uh
meme uh B on Chima like when you press
four on your keyboard while watching the
music video yeah yeah it and everybody
was like amazed and discombobulated by
it I remember oh my goodness I just
don't remember was four I really should
yeah probably it all goes back to press
four it all comes back press four here
I'm sorry I would love to spend more
time on this but I'm going
to just use this sketch and clean it up
a little bit and then I'm going to give
it a little bit of color and I'm just
going to yes give me color just going to
leave that butt there speaking of color
Yes would you like if you were to wear
basically the same outfit as me what do
you think your color combination would
be cuz my tights are a bright pink and
the leotard is like white with some
patterns and then the top is light
blueish what do you think your color
combination would be I need to look up
fan artists need to look up pictures I
mean pink isn't like one of your I'm
thinking like my main colors like for my
normal outfit but they don't have to be
but I guess they could it could be teal
it could
be would better than
brown yeah no I think because you know
if we're only looking at hoto Tony I
think there wouldn't be any yellow
necessarily so you could take yellow
instead of brown oh I think yellow would
be more fun it be neon oops a
combination of teal and yellow and maybe
maybe a touch of berry
red
ooh
yeah okay artists looking forward to the
result
can't oh wait super right that's
actually damn it right she is
ah well I mean you don't you know the
combination of course some can overlap
like my blue would probably overlap a
little bit with waya I've already seen
fan out of waya in uh the same outfit
basically only So Many
Colors visible to the human eye only
yeah yeah yeah it's the combination that
matters very
cute
W you've been doing so much with all
your birthday streams mumes no I tried
but I had to cancel one oh my
voice it's and you have the the outside
the box live concert got to be careful m
I wish to not lose my
voice I don't want to I don't think
anybody wants you to lose your voice mes
I've never fully lost my voice before
I've just sounded disgusting which is
the main thing I don't want I've lost my
voice fully before yeah I remember or
like you were close to it at least I
like I think like two times actually
already during my time in whole life I
think it happened like twice yeah at
this point thanks thankfully I used to
never get
then you joined Hol live no it's this
just because yeah normally I stay inside
to stream and all that but the that like
the moments when I do go outside because
of working from inside the whole time
the moment I go outside it hits me like
every sickness always hits me the rest
and everything from traveling and just U
touching objects that are not at home
like my my immune system is just messed
up that would make sense I feel like I
don't get a lot of people get sick when
they go to Japan I did get a minor like
a little cold when I was there for my uh
3D but there's been other instances
where everyone's sick and then I don't
get sick
but I just get I don't know I have
constant postnasal drip
a yes you have to H you know like how
some times you see people uh maybe it's
only in shows or in anime but with like
tissues stuck in your nose permanently
oh gosh that I here do I can't breathe
through my nose no you have to breathe
through your mouth then but at least
it's soaking up all the dripping from
your nose oh it doesn't drip it doesn't
drip out of my nose it drips down the
back of my throat ah and then you get
fum yeah yeah yeah constantly I have so
many fum problems too
do you spit it
out nope no no I'm drink that just makes
it worse I drink water I feel like if
you it just it will never like really
like go away though if you just don't
spit it out there's too
much yeah but then that's why you have
to spit it out it's okay I'll just like
is it pretty fake M does it taste salty
or or more like disgusting
I don't have any right now I just feel
it dripping down my throat you you
trying to figure out the flavor right
now e no it just tastes like
flum
M well there's different flavors of
flum oh like if like I feel like if it's
an issue with like your stomach acid it
would be
sour probably like a sour taste in your
mouth yeah like for example if I cry and
then my nose gets like runny and then I
if if I were to suck it up and then it
goes down my throat uh and if I then try
to spit that out that it's kind of like
salty because that's like just I don't
know snot kind of legum but if it's
sickness kind of fum it has
different texture and flavor and and
that's I I definitely want to get that
out um yeah because that's that's yeah
um what a conversation
boogers m I used to have like when I
when it was really bad when I was really
sick but I was still streaming uh I had
a fum cup and I was like spitting into
it during the stream several times maybe
that's what I need a fum cup yeah get it
out get it out my chat was excited
whenever I spit out my flum back in the
day appreciated it no I'm going to mute
every time this is the first honestly it
was disgusting too
okay it's not as okay
it's so
cute Tada I'm wait can you add my Hoops
my Hoops can you just add my Hoops oh
you have hoops let me see yeah what
color are they are they gold gold okay
okay fin huge gold hoops okay let me see
if I can do it
um wait why did the opacity go down
hello bring it up bring it up bring
those Hoops why is it like this wait is
this the opacity is full though what the
heck
what the this program is
weird oh no oh maybe the smaller it is
that's
weird you can make it relatively
thick cute nice those Hoops are giving
me the 70s 80s Vibes yeah oh I can't get
this
one I tried okay thank you MSY and of
course happy
birthday bir yeah happy birthday how old
are you
now like
[Music]
9,000 somewhere around somewhere around
9 somewhere between 9,000 and 10,000 or
over 9,000 it's over 9,000
yeah wait did you is was your age and
you de stream was it like nothing
basically I'm as old as
civilization whichever is the very very
first civilization which who knows if
that's truly been
fully figured out civilization is 9,000
years old roughly there's like there are
different guesses it's at least I think
like 6,000 is like the
guaranteed but then there's like but but
you have to consider that aliens came
here 9,000 years ago to establish the
first first civilization where did you
hear that from the aliens I suppose yeah
well from yeah History Channels Ancient
Aliens a trueth right I have to looked
at okay thank you for educating me I
will continue to educate myself on this
topic yes you should it's important to
know where all these where all these
people came from the lizard people there
is an episode on those if you if you
want to learn more really on Discovery
Channel yeah there's a on the lizard
people is that what I have
yeah look at reptilians Ancient
Aliens reptilians ancient oh it's it's
it's oh dear okay I will I will take
this very seriously okay and I will
watch it tonight okay you should okay
take notes thank you for drawing me
momies thank you for joining me thank
you good luck with all the other
drawings oh gosh I will not take as much
time as I took on yours but thank you
you're
welcome bye happy
birthday
[Music]
byebye
H we got one okay I can't spend that
much time on all of them we got one
though okay now I'm going to see if this
works that's too small okay hold
on that's still too small let me let me
just do
this okay I think this this is good
good
okay
[Music]
T maybe I should get rid of this butt I
feel like I'm not supposed to have that
I feel like this isn't allowed this
doesn't look like this looks like a
muscular butt an Olympian's butt I
haven't even been watching the Olympics
oops let me see oop that's not what I
wanted merge I say merge
merge and oopsie oh delete okay say
byebye byebye to
[Music]
butt do I really have to get a flum cup
I don't want to I don't want to get a
flam
cup let's see oh de oh
my oh my gosh there's so many people but
they're all in different voice chats
they're filling up every voice chat
oh dear wait am I supposed to select
somebody I ah see this is why we set up
times oh a child approaches
hello
hi I should I should probably let the
others join in first though I was
thinking of going to their voice chat
and like do you want to go in
first it's okay it's okay you're here
you're here hello hi
sh hi happy birthday thank you sh oh my
goodness see yeah it's nice to see you
talk about fle and FL flavored stuff do
you have FL also I want to draw you
something do you have any requests
what's up um no just just draw whatever
makes you happy you can draw me as poop
if you want and I will accept it I need
to look at a picture of you one second I
need okay okay to find one also I'm
going to get your I'm right under your
bed so you can just check there my bed's
not here but it's okay I have the
Internet it's okay oh Whose Bed am I in
then would you have
fun huh fun would what what do you have
FL oh right now no oh that's do you want
me to no I think it's great that you
don't I can't imagine okay Dar no FL for
me no FL for you I
currently I'm going to use my phone to
look up a reference there's too many
things on my monitors oh it's okay it's
okay okie dokie where my pen I'm going
to draw it how are you sh how are you
after your 3D
deut oh thank you thank you I saw your
comments I love your song Choices I I
keep saying it but they were just really
fitting for you and your oh you think so
oh thank you thank you I my favorite one
was the uh the abnormal dancing girl I
believe or abnormality I don't remember
the names but that's okay it's a I think
it's the the third one yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh okay CU like it's all rock like
and it's like yeah I'm going to be
abnormal and and you are in the best way
possible oh I thank you how do I make
you how do I cap your eyes are crazy I
don't know how to capture them oh it's
okay it's okay you can take like a
camera or or maybe some like a jar to
capture them with I could I have some
sharp
instruments oh by the way congrats on
the the new accessories and all that
stuff thank you I sorry you to like you
do like yeah I'm
edgy she's pretty I yeah my I get scary
I become
abnormal no but you're so beautiful like
that so you I'm going to make you shs
thank you
bakaa I'm making you I feel like I'm not
supposed to say like what my inspiration
in drawing you is right now yeah but
there is something and I don't know why
I feel like I'm going to draw everybody
this way oh what's the inspiration here
it's based on a
cartoon oh that doesn't really narrow it
down but thanks it's based on a cartoon
from the '90s
it's not it's not movement is
it I need to look up a reference of the
cartoon is it it's not moving
right
no okay oh that's how it looks okay I
got I got
this guess she ain't moving right now oh
power puff
maybe okay now it is sure or no it's
what uh I no I thought what uh
what oh oh what what what what
what that's a better idea
no oh I
see this is wait I'm sorry I don't know
what you
are it's okay I don't know what I me
there wait this is easier oh this is
great okay oh that's really cute
yeah oh it'd be so cute if we all had
like a 3D Powerpuff Girl for thinking
about
it this is unrelated but this is
unrelated to what I'm drawing right now
but but the person I think who does like
the a no he doesn't say ah the City of
Townsville no the City of Townsville you
know that the narrator yeah I'm pretty
sure it's the guy that uh places
SpongeBob
what he does oh my gosh I he's the miror
too oh I'm pretty sure holy crap man
he's been in the VA business for a long
long time yeah have you seen Adventure
Time I have yeah yeah he's Ice
King oh oh I like his story oh wow wait
so SpongeBob and Ice King are
technically the same person they
are oh that's kind of nuts isn't it once
you hear it you can never listen to it
the same oh it's kind of like a Jake the
dog being the dude from Futurama
yeah yeah yeah yeah wait wait y he was
the the robot from Futurama yeah I
forgot his name because I never fully
watched Bender Bender I never fully
watch Futurama because it scarred me as
a kid it was one of those shows where I
F the channel thought I was just
watching a child's cartoon and then
suddenly some guys I think it's the main
guy like fries his uh hands were bitten
off I was like that
children's cartoon what the heck oh man
as a kid I was watching like really bad
stuff like South
Park how kid how how much of a kid
though um enough to I probably shouldn't
have watch par maybe I don't know I used
to be scared I don't know my parents
didn't seem to mind though I was okay
one of my siblings we had like these
like a shared desk for
homework yeah
but they would watch South Park at the
desk and I was really scared of it
because they kept saying bad words and I
was like we can't you can't they can't
say that you can't say the no no word
yeah so it scared me and I just be like
trying to study and anticipating a curse
word a you're such a good girl Ms I was
I was like terrified of
cursing aw and when
all the time oh not now I don't it
doesn't scare me
anymore okay okay but when I got to
middle school and that's when like
everyone just starts curing for no
reason I was like oh my God I have to
learn I have to be cool so then I
started watching Family Guy thinking it
would make me cool so I watched Family
Guy like the first season or something
and I was like okay now if anybody asks
me about an adult show I can talk about
Family Guy I'll be ready and no one ever
asked
oh oh you weren't ready for the the
interview at the time huh yeah like what
adult show do you watch I
got I was ready but no one asked I
remember watching Family Guy too and
stuff on uh Adult Swim like uh aquatine
Hunger Force I think Robot Chicken yeah
when it became oh yeah wait did what did
it do it was like Cartoon Network then
it became tsunami and then it became
adult oh yeah yeah
anime or was tsunami just one day a week
I could never keep track I think uh I
think they alternated cuz tsunami died
for a bit and then it became Adult Swim
and then they would try to squeeze in
anime every now and then I thought the
guy from tsunami was like based on
Halo oh that's funny actually he had a
lot of forms still he used to be like a
cheapy dude and then he became muscular
yeah they made him like cool like if you
want to even call him that
he was like no they did they did make
him cool I know he he had like the the
whole really cool robot voice he became
muscular he like whoa what happened to
you my chippy F dude perhaps it was just
so many people were made fun of watching
anime they're like no we need a cool guy
representing tsunami what happened we
need the Halo Chief dude uhoh what
happen what I do what's up oh I I lost
you for a second but you're back now
okay oh it's okay I was never gone in
the first place Ms you weren't I just
accidentally made you
invisible oh it's okay it's okay this is
really messy I I I don't have it in me
to be
clean oh no it's okay I think it looks
cute tada this is you yeah this is this
is you if you were a chibi on
tsunami witness
me
Tada nice it's you
I was made with spice trauma and
everything not so good for you I have
one more question before what's up
before you leave me did you ever watch
Cow and
Chicken I
did I remember
that who wait which guy the sausage guy
I think he might just be the oh holy
crap the red right yeah he's a sausage
he was he was kind of freaking DIY were
you uh were you scared by Him from
Powerpuff
Girls is him the red one yeah yeah yeah
the devil one yeah he was creepy too he
was I was scared of I wasn't scared of
him but I was like
uh oh man I just thought he was like he
was a cool villain oh yeah yeah he had
that really weird high pitch like kind
of a Reverb or something to his voice
too it was place man him was cool
I liked his heels he had heels right oh
yeah he did he stomped on everyone yeah
yeah
yeah did he
have Oh no you're F oh you're talking
about his pin right pin he has pin yeah
yeah I remember he did have pctures he
looked really freaky like funky actually
kind like a
butterfly I don't know thinking about it
I'm not
sure well happy birthday I've stole the
spot I shouldn't ask first so I'll go
now it's okay I just didn't organize
this veryable thank you for coming by no
you're fine you're perfectly fine
bye-bye happy birthday byebye thank
you oh I'm so sorry I should have
organized this better my bad what is
this T can
this okay get rid of this oh no no don't
get rid the Hat no get rid of this oh I
made this on the computer
oh okay wait I lost Kiara dang it it's
okay we have screenshots
[Music]
okay hey
hello
hello hello I was wondering when I
should come in I'm sorry this is not
organized well and you're all in
different VCS no it's F I'm just
confused I'm like wish I should
communicate with them hello s hello
happy birthday
thank you I'm grabbing your I what is
your icon right now don't worry I I came
prepared so oh I just I'll send you all
the stuff the icons oh boy the Twitter
icon is so I got your Twitter
icon that's all I prepared what's the
story oh
this yeah that one yeah yeah I okay got
it got it I hope you don't mind is that
what you want me to
draw no I was wondering oh you can draw
me since we were at like um what is it
called since she already was drawn as
like Powerpuff Girls no she wasn't she's
just drawn as a as a chibi from
tsunami oh okay I thought she was drawn
us no she's not drawn no she's just
she's just
there oh oh oh oh yeah oh yeah obviously
yeah um the yeah it's just my art style
oh yeah yeah yeah it's obviously just
your art style yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah no wonder it's so
unique yeah I've I've never seen it
before in my life never me neither I
just came up with it yeah never never
yeah
yeah what what would you like can you
draw me inside a cardboard box in a
cardboard box yeah okay cuz you do me a
favor and send me a a picture of you I
need to look at your hair okay okay I
got the I got the easiest one for you e
mom this one's super
easy oh that is
easy all right in a cardboard
box okay why is this
not what I don't what am I doing wrong
hello oh there we go oh oh okay all
right is this working oh it's working
okay okay okay okay are you using magma
I
am ooh in a cardboard box in a cardboard
box please all right while you're
drawing can I make some
gases some gases for your yes some
guesses for your 3D life oh sure yeah
yeah yeah
um since I'm a secret agent and all I
kind of want to make guesses and then
you can say yes no or maybe okay all
right okay let me analyze this logo oh
the oh the meaning behind it yeah the
meaning behind it I'm going to guess
what's going to happen what's going to
appear all right all
right
okay
um starting from
outside okay I can see ribbons on the
o uhhuh um ribbons usually they're
always in front of like a store and then
you cut the ribbon it symbolizes new
like new business new openings New
Beginnings oh my gosh wait are you going
to reveal my most top secret business
plans right now yes but you can say yes
no or maybe okay okay okay okay so it
symbolizes something new you'll be
showing something new yes no maybe um um
I mean I
uh may
maybe maybe
okay the next is like youu youu is short
for you so will there be a nanashi m in
the 3D live
I probably guessed it right I knew it I
knew it I knew there was going to be a
Nashi in the Life maybe maybe I haven't
decided
yet okay so the box it has like an
hourglass shape
sdx so hourglass is where you turn back
time so it has something to do about
like time
warping
no no dang it okay
[Music]
um there's like a crown on top of the
letter i which means you'll be you'll be
ruling over something or someone or
maybe you'll be ruling over the
civilians something about
dominating the the stage no what is that
why did you draw me as a cat I didn't
what what makes you think I drew you as
a
cat I mean there was it's there's a
there's there's cat ears that but your
outfit has cat
ears headphones those are those are
headphones mes yeah I made them it looks
cute though here I'll make them blue
just to make it even more thank you you
added colors I'm so honored now it's a
bit more obvious here I mean she
already's just black and white so I mean
she she
is she's originally black and white you
know the last time um I don't know if
Chad knows about this but whenever me
and M meet we always talk about like
animals and a bunch of like conspiracy
oh yeah we
did we do what did we talk did we talk
about bears was that what it was last
time we talked a lot about like I think
like Bears wolves and like a lot of
lions even oh
yeah yeah apex
predators apex predators indeed and
we're like speculating of why they act
the
done analyzing animal behavior we are so
qualified because we're both we're both
animals you're both apex
predators not me what you're not a human
I am I am a human but that's yeah you're
you're an
animal a homo sapien because humans are
animals yeah I get you uhhuh we can be
worse than animals sometimes we
are
animal an animal I am animal
animal animality animal animal anomaly
anom anom anomaly animal anomy animal an
anal animal animaly animal anomaly that
knows about Anatomy an
[Music]
an
yes thank you very much for the
beautiful drawing you're welcome yeah
let me Center this a bit
better I want to screenshot it hold on
feel free do we
I'll screenshot it after the modest
moose is gone okay here we go
boing got
it got it thank you you're welcome Happy
Birthday M thank you thank you for
stopping by thank you I love you and
your new
accessories you thank you love you
byebye byebye I'll treasure this forever
you better thank
[Music]
you hello oh hi moose is this the modest
moose wait isn't that's not
you I thought it was honestly coming a
little bit I thought you were possessing
me happy
birthday thank
you fun your new hair is super
cute it look fluffy the
accessories they are I feel use them for
ASMR the little puff balls I've been
wanting to ask you I do not know where
to find the the like ear cleaning
I just buy it on Amazon am I looking it
up
incorrectly I just searched for like
Japanese ear pick oh fluffy ear pick I
maybe I didn't put Japanese in it is
that what I have to do probably a and it
it's like going to be like way more
expensive like if you buy it in Japan at
the 71 it's like like 70 cents I looked
for them in Amazon I went to donkey I
mean to be fair donkey like I get kind
of claustrophobic pretty fast it's over
stimulating if I look for something like
there's somebody that's like trying to
go down the same you know row and I'm
like oh I don't want to be awkward and
like brush them so I'm just going to I'm
just going to leave
yes I can I can draw you
something will you draw me my cat's
snail yes
with pleas I would love a drawing of
snails did you see what I sent you yes
and I wanted to I have this okay M sent
me a picture of a black cat next to a
black cat plushy and I have the exact
same black cat plushies so I wanted to
recreate this picture and send it to you
I have it I have it oh are you waiting
for like to like get it posed and ready
yeah yeah I see I need I need to
recreate the photo if I ever see black
cat merchandise that's really cute and
it has like these giant eyes I'm like I
have to send it
yes and my mom is the same she always
always buys me black cat merch see
that's the good thing about having
something you're like that you love like
especially animal like if there's an
animal you really love it's so easy for
people to get you gifts and you'll love
every single one yes I wish to fill my
house with black cats real or
otherwise will snail ever get a brother
or
sister I I've been thinking about it I'm
just nervous cuz I I I'm worried that he
wants to be an only Kitty but that's how
I feel with animal I really want a cat
or another animal but I'm like what if
she doesn't want that how do I know what
she wants I know I wish we could ask
them yeah be like would you would you
want a friend do you want a
buddy I feel like most animals they
don't know what they want so they might
at first seem to not want you know
another friend but then right I think
they can
adjust yeah I think about it like well
what about when I'm streaming and snail
gets lonely what if snail had another
black cat an identical black cat as a as
a snuggle buddy
right I okay I learned cuz I left animal
with a new sitter kind of like sort of
recently and the sitter has an
animal and I know when I'm around anal
gets really possessive and starts to act
really weird but apparently while I was
gone animal was totally chill and really
liked the animal and when I went to pick
her up she became a total female do
dog I I see what you're saying yeah
she's like a like a yandere to you she
is she got so upset she doesn't want she
doesn't want you to interact with any
other animals that's that's really it I
think that's also why she seems to like
cats a lot because we'll like be on a
walk and we'll see cats and she's really
chill and really patient with them and
they'll make eye contact she'll just
watch them if they come up to her she'll
sniff them and they'll be like what the
heck are you doing you weirdo why are
you sniffing my
butt but if she makes eye contact with
the wrong
animal she just gets very upset and I
don't know what it is like it's not
every animal it's like every like one in
10 h H it's like they look at her wrong
and she gets really
angry I mean that's like understandable
right sometimes people look at me wrong
and I don't like them for no reason
you
I oh this is bad I shouldn't say
this maybe I
will let it out it's your birthday you
can do no wrong today I it I uh
no no it's okay it makes cuz I genuinely
feel really bad I feel really bad about
it it's more so like if if people do a
certain thing I don't dislike them but I
definitely don't want to be near them
anymore oh I mean everybody has pet
peeves but I feel so bad because I feel
like sometimes the thing could be a
result like a health problem maybe I I
don't I don't know
I understand yeah I have I have pet
peeves too sometimes even like like my
family my friends people that I love
sometimes will like do a pet peeve of
mine and I'll be like oh that's annoying
to me but I love you so I'm I'm I'm
going to I'm not going to say anything
I'm just going
to I can't anymore uhhuh yeah it builds
up it's okay it's out of L wa I'm going
to give him his his eyeballs or his his
yellow eyes yeah yeah
yeah I really love black cats because so
many of them look very
similar like more than other cats like I
feel like black cats look really similar
to each
other so anytime I see a black cat I'm
like oh my gosh it's snail I do the same
thing I go oh my gosh it's snail why
that's what I want I don't know my dream
is to have like five black cats and I
can tell them apart but nobody else
can yeah this is special special bond
special connection it's not even by how
they look it's by how their
personalities you can tell them Point
yes just instantly actually this is like
a recurring nightmare that I have
sometimes I have a nightmare and I've
had this even before I had snail when I
was little with my other cats I would
have a nightmare that like an identical
cat like a doppelganger cat is in my
house and I don't know which one is the
real one and I'm like panicking because
I'm like I need to figure out which one
is my cat that's I mean huh in reality I
could just keep both but do you ever
have okay see I consider these bad
dreams where in a dream I get another
pet and then I wake up and the Pet's not
real and then I'm sad oh yes
yeah yes those are my what my nightmares
are like
M it's a sign maybe maybe you should get
another pet maybe we both should I think
the most recent was like an orange cat I
had an orange cat in my dream and I woke
up and I didn't have an orange cat it's
a sign it's a sign to go get an orange
cat I'm waiting for an orange cat to
appear at my doorstep yes that's what
I'm saying have you seen okay I don't
know if you've seen on on Reddit there's
like the cat distribution system I've
seen on other platforms but the cat
distribution system when is it my turn
yeah that's what I'm saying when is it
my turn I'm waiting I'm waiting I'm
ready I told you I had it actually I
think my term my term my turn came and
went and it was the wrong time because I
did find a little black cat
yeah but I couldn't keep her so I gave
her to a a family friend it was their
time it was their yeah I distribute I
was just the middleman you were you were
the middleman yeah so it wasn't really
okay it wasn't really my turn I was just
involved our turns will come I believe I
believe
too thank you for this drawing it's
adorable you're welcome a snail snail is
perfect I forgot to put your icon I need
to remember to do that Twitter Twitter
fauna Twitter I'm here she's here in
spirit this is this is Siri's fun and I
do this and then I do this and and then
suddenly oh wait no suddenly
Tada oh my goodness here I
am hi hi thank you for coming
thank you for being
[Laughter]
born oh stop okay okay I'll let you go
happy birthday good luck tomorrow you're
going to kill
it thank you I'll see you yeah see you
later bye-bye
byebye
byee all right I wish I could drag her
I'm just going to go to her before any
wait I don't know should I go to her to
the next person yeah okay thank goodness
ana anaaa
ana hello happy birthday thank you oh
Anya I saw you waiting for so
long I'm sorry yeah I would for like um
nearly an hour I'm so sorry this I
didn't organize this at all this year
that means you are loved by a lot of
people it's proed by us coming to your
tattoo I'm going to go past past
midnight at this
point Thank you thank you thank you Ana
I'm going to draw you something dra what
you're drawing I just drew uh faa's cat
snail and I'm going to draw something
yeah I'm looking at it right now really
cute
thank you oh do I actually have an idea
do you know do you know chawa do you
know chawa can you draw me in a chawa
style CH hold on I'm going to I'm going
to I'm going to s a picture okay it
sounds
familiar I think she'll like it I think
she'll like it hold
on it's my birthday in CST
[Music]
huz let me see let me see
I've been so obsessed this yes okay this
is what I thought it was yeah yeah this
this is really popular it's been really
popular lately how do I make you I
actually have one of these I have like I
got it in Goa yeah I have a little gacha
one it's like the middle one
sleeping oh I'm so jealous he's cute oh
why can't this work oh here we go how
would I make this into you hold on I
have to make it can be
anything you don't need to be you don't
you don't have to try so hard it's just
me let me see let me see I try for you
wait what animal what animal do you want
to
be um that's a good question wait so the
the theme is animals hold on it can be I
we well I guess it doesn't have to be I
could try to make you a person looking
like this okay um no no no can I can I
be a frog then a frog yeah okay I have
to restart would you love me if I was a
frog I would you still love me I saw a
dead Toad on the side of the road the
other day and got really upset it was
like not even it wasn't even you know
run over it was just on its back intact
dead kind of
deflated
from yeah
that's like what happened to you you me
it across like it it wasn't well maybe I
wasn't looking enough yeah you know what
I feel bad for loving I should I
shouldn't have love no it's okay it's
okay to
laugh okay how else do we get through it
how do we get I don't remember how to
draw frogs here we go this is going to
be you as a frog this a little silly
frog is okay let me see
what that's that's cute actually I can't
wait for you treaty
to treaty life I mean treaty life
yeah yeah sorry I was I was watching
People's that's okay I also get mixed up
I'm like I'm having my showcase tomorrow
wa it was a showcase all along oh my
goodness showcase part two yeah I
remember I remember us talking about you
know I remember you talking about W to
do uh birthday to your life like last
year I'm glad it's a reality now I'm
glad it's three yeah oh my goodness they
so much
planning there's so much how do I make
this
you hold on I need to see more pictures
of um just add just add you know um the
yellow parts of my hair I guess oh wait
hold on like the
little wait oh I know I have to do I'll
give you your little just add the banana
parts of my hair the banana you have an
you and the and
this yes oh should I give you your full
B I love
it okay I love it yes my little my
little yellow bangs okay oh that's cute
too all right let me give it a little
bit of color I didn't think I draw so
many cute things today oh my goodness
and also sent
yeah what the mean uh oh are you okay
yes I just always have cancel to karoke
you're can you Koke cuz your voice yeah
I'm preserving it Ms yeah I just always
have okay we're having this conversation
again let's go I always have postnasal
slim so there's always gunk in my
throat and it makes me cough and not
able to sing sometimes or I can sing
it's just a sounds really
bad
uh yeah and have happens sometimes yeah
it's like a constant issue for me and
the doctors are like not very helpful
but hopefully soon they'll be helpful
hopefully soon I can wait if you're
rescheduling your Koke I can't wait to I
yeah I'm going reschedule that one yeah
yay it's
you it's me as a oh my God it
me that was let me screenshot it yeah
let me let me screenshot this get it get
it get
it okay I think I got it got it we also
need to play OverWatch
again I my most recent streams I've been
playing it a lot earlier but not usually
stream which is like super super early
for ID so I need to play it
later oh yeah I know I I know you're
playing it today but it was like so
early it was super early I didn't expect
any ID to make it but I need to schedule
an ID friendly time yeah I'm so sad but
it's okay you play you play OverWatch
every day so no I don't I don't
play
every I know cuz like cuz like my
impression of you have has been
overridden by OverWatch oh that's not
good I see I see OverWatch I I think of
you no over I think of M no because if
you feel that way other people must feel
that way
too oh gosh it's okay you're a
pro no and I'm a baby you think at this
hope I hope I'm not too much of a burden
and we play OverWatch next time you're
not you're not it's the only burden I
feel playing overwatches when I play by
myself
no yeah no you're good at the game no
maybe one day if I play enough no you're
good and maybe a little bit too addicted
but it's okay I still love you either
way thank you that's that's thank you
thank you for having me thank you for
being so patient of so I SAR we need to
talk more about you know Higurashi and
falo yeah yeah yes oh I I I can tell you
a story if I remember uh-huh uh-huh yes
not not right now but it's a I can't
talk about stre but I'll I'll tell you
I'll tell you I'll tell you I'll tell
I'll tell you yeah tell me tell me after
the stream it's okay thank
you and then we can have Boomer Boomer
talk together Boomer I'm a
boomer I'm I'm pretty sure I'm pretty
sure you're one of my people you know po
Boomers oh vocal Boomer yes yeah FAL
Boomers yeah you're one of us you you me
and I we need to have a I can sense it
have a
talk yeah I can sense it you're one of
us one of
us yes thank you Ms for having me and
happy birthday I can't wait for the for
your 3D Live not showas
live thank you thank you thank you moms
bye-bye bye-bye let's play OverWatch let
ribit
ribbit oh no oh oh
yes oh
yes oh yes I
say oh
yes please say something please talk to
me talk to me what is it is my breath
what is it wait wait wait wait wait can
you hear me can you hear me hi yes hello
hi hi hi M happy almost
birthday thank you is this the phone
voice
narissa yeah I'm sorry I'm I'm in a bit
of a situation so I have to join on my
phone I hope that's okay I really wanted
to call that's okay I appreciate you
calling despite being in a situation are
you okay yeah no no no everything's
great okay H but I was like H how are
you m May are you having a good day so
far I
am I've been doing stuff and I'm doing
stuff right now and I'm going to
continue doing things
later yeah you're making cute cute art
of everyone it's so adorable yeah I'm
surprised it's yeah would you like
something uh sure um what what would you
like to draw of me I I don't know I'm
kind of in a a art
block um hm I I everyone always calls me
a wet cat so do you want to make me a
wet cat why do they call you a wet
cat um because that's the energy I give
off in life you know huh I can I can
make you a wet
cat okay let's do that turn make make me
a wet cat
okay I'm just going to draw a cat that's
I guess the your
color yeah a black cat with like blue
strands of hair just like soing wet
that's
me okay is there anything specific you
want for your birthday this year I
want I want people to watch my 3D
live I am so excited to see your 3D
live I can't I can't
wait I'm EXC I'm excited to see your 3D
debut or
showcase yeah now all of all of advents
have been a blast so far yeah I the
quality my goodness I I know I'm like oh
oh God I hope I hope mine's okay I'll do
my best I believe so I believe you
yeah just it it'll be cute I'll I'll do
my best it cute I have I have fun plans
for it so yeah I I won't ask you
questions here and now because I don't
want I I can't tell you anything yeah
you can't give anything away but I
believe it m sounds sounds
believable yeah you have have fun
plans yes I have fun plans with it so I
you
tell keep keep your eyes open for it
okay they're not going to
close at all yes
that's going to be me when I'm watching
your 3D Live just eyes open the whole
time no blanking absolutely
not good that is the way to to
watch this is you if you were a wet cat
I don't really get why are you a white
cat um Just Energy I don't like I
understand but like I don't you know I I
think it's because I have this pathetic
Vibe like
what I don't know I don't know that's
just what they say they're like you're
like wet you're so pathetic
what it's not like oh you're grumpy
sometimes which I don't feel like you
are but no it's not cuz I'm grumpy it's
cuz I'm pathetic apparently what have
you
done nothing I don't I literally don't
think I've done anything I feel like I
shouldn't have drawn this now I should
not be encouraging the what
no I literally when people draw me as a
wet cat I literally retweet it like I
think it's so
funny wet cats are funny in themselves
like look look at this guy they're cute
I love wet cats I'm like I feel so bad
for them it's okay they they got to get
their baths every once in a while I
don't know why you're so squished though
can I fix
you it's okay that's when the liquefy
Tool comes into play I wish there's a
liquefy tool on this website I'm using a
brow browser thing oh so I can draw
today let's see and you're
blue yeah not that black and blue do you
want to be a oh is this wait I need to
look a picture of you hold on color
matching
time like oh I don't remember what you
look like I do I know you have blue
Accents in your hair but do I like if
feel like how do I do this hold on I
have no no idea that's why I leave it to
you you're the genius literal Queen
let's
see maybe this isn't the best brush
cheese but we're doing it okay it's fine
who cares and I'm going to give you ooh
I can make you like a you know an OC s
Like a Warrior C oh God my cat Sona yes
your cat
Sona your cat Sona which falls under a
being a
persona I'm getting I can't believe it
my Persona my cat Sona
mhm let's see I'm going to give
you um this is not a very good not a
very good designed one I don't know to
do
wait you just got to give me some hair
some like blue hair in the back yeah
make your like chin area blue like this
is
blue give me like a blue spot on my ey
so I'm going to give you a pink
nose cuz you're cute like that and then
oh yeah your eyes okay they're kind of
yeah okay your eyes my eyes are also
pink yeah yeah yeah all right and
then oh your
horn should he's just grumpy you know
the cat ears replace them so if anything
you should just take a chunk out of the
left ear oh oh my gosh you're so right
and that's even like a gives you more
yeah so the ear okay oh wait no sorry
her your left her right yes oh wait yes
I get it I get it I get how things work
[Music]
okay wait yeah no you're doing it right
I can't talk I'm directionally
challenged no it's okay it's okay I I
got you I got you all
right um she's a baby I'll give you a
blow a blow what oh wait BL blow I think
that's what blue is in German is that
what CeCe said did I remember that
correctly oh I have no idea I wonder if
I did did her Germans stick with
me
okay I give you
towel yes okay make it like baby pink or
something I don't know baby pink okay
okay yes cuz you're a girl okay mhm cuz
I'm cute I'm just cute like that
yeah here we
go look at that it looks just like me
it's like uncanny like really captured
my likeness I don't see
it it's
perfect make I'm like meow meow
meow you're
wet wait I'm wet I'm stopping wet I need
help I need a
assistance didn't do this right wait oh
there we go
okay it's you you're a queen I literally
love you so much you have no idea I was
thinking about you today and I was like
God I miss m Miss hope she's doing well
she's doing how's narissa doing nissa's
doing good that's good Nissa gets to eat
nice food every day so it's
perfect m is jealous of
um well I'll just have to take you out
to eat sometime you will I don't want to
cook any more food I've been cooking
food trying not to eat
out you're being so healthy that's like
healthy girl behavior I'm trying I'm
doing my best
here that's all we can do sometimes you
know this is you well it's me thank you
for having me and letting me stop by it
was nice to hear your voice I hope you
have a happy birthday and I'm looking
forward to your live thank you thank you
thank you thank
you okay I'll let you get to the next
guest goodbye for now bye bye bye okay
bye by bye I love you bye
R before anybody dare enter I have to go
to an idol
meeting I must go I hope they I hope
they know I'll tell
them I don't meeting I want s
back okay okay okay I don't meeting I
don't meeting idle meeting idle meeting
idle meeting this is great this is
taking up more time than I thought it
would I thought I'd just be sitting in
silence for like 2
hours this isn't great I much to talk
about okay I'll be right back I'll be
right back I'll be right back I'll be
right back wait did you I see something
did you see did you see something I
didn't see okay okay I'll be right back
I'll be right back okay okay okay okay
be be
[Music]
okay I
returned someone's waiting for me do I
make them wait longer no it's
okay oh
hi hi hey oh my hi my gosh it's
like it's like I just heard your voice
like you're playing
OverWatch V up OverWatch actually
five that's that's okay my I'm I that's
that's okay I appreciate the offer
overwat okay no I I can't multitask that
well my
apologies I'm adding you to the to this
thingy hold on whoa why does it do that
wait your Twitter icon is crazy how does
it do that large no it's just crazy like
it's a circle but then when I copy it
there's more outside the circle oh
really yeah I didn't even know that see
it's like for Advent they have theirs
where it's just white outside but they
prepped justices I guess to be to have
more when that you copy and paste huh
thank you sta
CH that's crazy when you click on my
icon it's just a circle and then you C
who I just tried it that that is insane
yeah wild would you like
a I would love a
drawing what would you
like what's the most cursed meme you
know um off the top of my oh that looks
pretty cursed right now o um the most
cursed meme I know probably something I
wouldn't be allowed to draw
do you know the slug like live slug
reaction I don't shall I look it up let
me send this to you yeah you can look it
up I can send it to you why slug
reaction can you draw me as that it's a
song that it's a picture of a oh
apparently there's a song too oh I did
not I didn't know it was a song okay
what you see the image wait I was
sending you
something where are
you this was also this is what appeared
on my Google
results I see maybe I have seen this
before you want to be this I want to be
that how do I even make you into
this um probably hair and then the poate
coming out from the middle okay let's
see what I can accomplish with this
given time and my
ability to draw
excited so this is what you think I look
like this is appar which you think you
look like I that's some confidence you
have yeah I think I look like that I
wish I was that confident thinking I
look better than I
did yeah yeah I have a really big head
and I'm kind of vain
if they off with this
phone
watch I don't know where to go from here
wait these are two far apart they're
supposed to be
closer let's see all right once you draw
the eyes it's kind of damn I look good
yeah you do I was just kidding you do
look is good yeah I look like this on
every given day I feel like it's easier
to draw Attractive people than it is to
draw an attractive people and this has
been pretty simple so I didn't mean to
do what I just did but it it seems it's
been pretty simple so far which really
really goes to show how attractive it is
how attractive you
[Music]
are if you have to K assign yourself
with a meme what meme would you K
yourself with shoot you're asking some
intense questions I can't get
philosophical when that's not with like
other things in it like it has to like
the only thing that can be there is
just you look like you know what you
look
like you look get messed up version of
Turbo from that
movie the snail movie
yeah this is no the Beautiful version of
Turbo Turbo after the movie you know
well what's messed up is that you look a
lot better than him despite him having
such a high budget oh
yeah yeah I think you drawing it shows
that I've had unlimited budget yes I'm
willing to put in
more because you're worth
it okay so what meme are
you you know try to get away from this
do you know though okay I can think of
one off the top of my head where it's
uh it's not just a single like there's
not an
individual subject there's multiple you
know the one with the owls there's like
four owls and they're all doing
different things and there's the one
that's like eating like voring a
[Music]
mouse I'm going to Google owl boring
Mouse me I I don't think you should do
that I think instead I'll do this for
you
hold on okay thank you before I get some
gore before you get some stuff you can't
believe exists um I'll eating mouse
meme what' you
find that's awful oh my
God that's
insane oh dear is this
it oh oh
wait hold on okay I have to send you to
Reddit
[Music]
okay oh this one they're all me they're
all Me Maybe you know I'm not even the
ones I'm not the one Ving the mouse I'm
the one that's next to him that's just
just yapping yeah that's me you're like
yeah and like and then just eating the
rat alive
this is a good meme to kign yourself to
i' like to think it's already
dead it would be a little sad if it
wasn't it would
be it' be pretty rough that's fine that
rat died to um old age and yeah they
just found it mhm it would want to go
that
way yeah be you know useful in death
kind of how like people are organ donors
yeah yeah exact that's what I was
thinking yeah it signed up to
be owl
food
yeah am I drawing you correctly yeah I
really like the folds going
[Laughter]
on I'm glad you like
them it looks really
good wait this should be in a museum
you think
so yeah do you have an
exhibition that's what it's called right
I hope I an
[Music]
exhibit yeah do you have an exhibit
somewhere I've been waiting for a museum
to reach out and offer me one I'm going
to email um MMA and I'm going to send
this photo and your stream and I'm going
to write a very very long worded email I
feel like with the with the drawings I
make I feel like the Smithsonian should
take me or the right Museum I'll I'll
email them don't worry I'm going to be
like there's a very special birthday
girl with very beautiful art of a very
beautiful slide and if you don't hang
this up I will stand in front of your
Museum and make you regret it
I will change the trajectory of your
life
by doing things no one wants me to
do by saying you saying the museum none
of the the paintings are
real yeah everyone who goes in there
yeah that's a that's a counterfeit
that's a counter it's not a real
painting yeah they didn't even ask the
artist permission yeah they traced it
actually they
traced they traced everything in this
Museum mhm all traced and
yeah even the abstract art that looks
like
this the abstract art was traced too
that Circle traced
yes what what do you think this is so
abstract it looks like an animal to me
what animal do you see this is kind of
like you
know what's that I see a horse
okay okay well write write that down
wolf write that down write that down
it's like a personality test um what do
you see the person who drew it well
there's multiple things you can be
seeing it's just what you see determines
your mental
sanity what would you say my mental
sanity is based off of the answer I just
gave do you really want this out in the
public yes these are private records are
you sure yes I need you to Psycho
analyze me so bad girl you
wild a woof
woof you got a wolf living inside you
just one though not two just one wolf
not two just one I don't even get two
wolf I have a wolf in the slug inside of
me you are the slug and there's a wolf
howling trying to get out oh
wait hold
on sorry you don't get color but you get
you get a wolf inside you
yay the wolf inside of me Bow Wow it
says let me
out it looks really
good wow thank you we should play that
wolf game we
should okay it has a name
Wolf Quest I'm sorry sorry I'm so sorry
give it give it the respected deserve we
should play Wolf Quest and I'm going to
put it somewhere in my calendar and I
will just send you a Google invite okay
yes please please send me a Google
invite and I'll if I am able to the only
thing that would make me not able to is
not being physically in my home with a
computer okay I'll make multiple Google
invites and I'll just send like 10 of
them just to see what happens all right
just to see how many I say yes
to okay sounds
good this has been a very productive
Birthday to happy birthday
for happy
[Music]
birthday yay happy birthday M
Senai I am happy we got to play
OverWatch and set up a Wolf Quest collab
and and I got I'm happy I got to look at
this beautiful snail with so many
wrinkles me too I'm happy about the same
things okay I want to know one more
thing you're happy
about oh oh what am i h I'm happy that
I'm having a 3D live tomorrow at 8:00
p.m. PS or 12:00 p.m. jst or other times
in different time zones
yeah I don't know any other time zones
either um yeah that's all I
know 1100 p.m. EST uh 10 p.m.
CST and 700 p.m. Hawaii time I think is
it what is Hawaii time I don't know
Hawaii 1 hour
[Music]
before Hawaii time well currently it is
7:50 in Hawaii oh it was really off it's
not 7 pm. Hawaii time everyone I was
lying it's I lied to you two no almost 3
hours earlier than
that PSP minus
3 that
is
um 500 p.m. Hawaii time
everyone yeah be there or this slug will
we'll find you do things to you yeah
it's like that thing where it's like you
get $1 million but you have to like stay
away from a snail the like the rest of
your life the moment it touches you it
kills you and it's always going for you
that's what this slug is going to do
that's a
thing I think it's like a thought
experiment or what or like a question
where it's like oh you get $10 million
of this or that a slug yeah this is the
slug that chases you and if it touches
you you die I
see okay I should stop I know there's
other people waiting to talk to the
beautiful birthday girl but any go see
the 3d concert tomorrow 3D
birday thank you for having
me
bye byebye
[Music]
well got nothing to say
huh you good bird you good bird are you
are you are you are you I feel like you
asking me is just you
projecting goodbye doing good are you
are you asking cuz you want me to ask
you are you good
I heard your your laughter and I was
concerned for a second oh dang it see I
was about to my goal was to laugh and
then time it perfectly so that by the
time someone joined I stopped but then I
saw you and I just stared and I was like
did she hear that did she hear me hey I
did you're just okay oh we have a new
Twitter icon when did this
happen oh yeah reacon I changed it oh
dear hello hi hi hello hi happy birthday
thank you it's my oh yeah it's my
birthday in Japan yeah it is your
birthday happy
birthday how you how you been how you
doing I'm okay Bae I'm okay it's good
yeah it's good it's okay B ooh do you
want a
drawing yeah what do you want please
what do you want what do you want
anything no you have to be
specific I want me freaking on a glacier
of ice looking out into the Wilderness
because there Wilderness and ice on the
same time and I want my hands on my hips
and my thigh is as thick as tree trunks
because I just came back from training
how about that
okay thanks ma'am let's see I'm going to
do it from a bird's eye view or no from
an airplane an airplane's
view thanks man sorry I was going to
call in a little bit earlier but then
there's a lot of
people yeah that and also um I went
through it I discovered something very
interesting it was like a you know like
when you come across the situation where
you just can't help but watch and you
just could can't stop watching like a
car accident like a train wreck like
rubber necking yeah
yeah but like it's just it there's no
danger
involved okay what were you
watching I was observing another member
over
sleeping
stream it's so fun I get why people get
I I understand why people have so much
fun when I over sleep now oh my God just
it's like the
anticipation it really is I felt like
was it was like a crowd event we were
like cheering we were counting down the
minutes it was
great sorry does it inspire you to over
sleep
no let's see this is the snow and then
it becomes like oh dear what did I do
okay wait hold on how did gles work it's
like the snow and then these are the
mountains and wait is that bird's eye
view no it's not bird's eye view anymore
it's landcap view I changed my mind okay
okay okay I realized I don't know how to
draw from a bird's eye view or an
airplane view can't fly that high oh I
see okay are you
excited water because and then or no is
there water no no there's like land and
then there's okay so there's like some
land or something well if it's a
receding gler if this is a receding
Glacier then maybe there's some like
sediment left around here and then
there's water at some point and then
this is you on the
glacier all right I'm waiting because
your stream has lag
oh I see that's me okay I was like are
those like mountains or my pigtails I
can't
tell does it that's your that's your
your
ears like I'm on the yeah okay okay
that's you I see thanks man accurate
size I'm so
[Music]
excited for
tomorrow
yeah oh yeah I'm so excited are you
going to are you going to show up
you going to show I'm busy man you're
not going to show up for
work busy tomorrow
bro you're
busy you're busy working for
me oh wait that's
tomorrow I think so is it I might be
wrong sheit it might not be oh let me
know is it this
year yeah
[Music]
is it
tomorrow I'm too busy over
sleeping oh okay oh then that can be
part of the live I guess we'll have a
time where like we're counting down you
waking up
[Music]
M oh yeah you have cheese cheese yeah
sorry you want you want your hands on
your hips yes I want my hands on my hips
and my legs far apart thighs thick as
tree
trunks what the why do I have a pine
cone sticking out of my oh wait never
mind I changed my mind about some things
is that
a I don't what that is maybe I should
actually make this all go further down
like this oh dear I miss why did you
give me a why did you give me a pine
cone where is where are you seeing this
pine cone
check I gave you cheese are are you not
happy with that type of cheese do you
want no what's under the
cheese what's in between my legs why do
you have a p those are legs I'm not done
yet wait what I'm not done
yet that's the beginning of your
torso huh you asked for thick
thighs I'm so confused wait those are my
feet right oh those are my oh those are
my
hands
oh oh I'm sorry I'm sorry that's okay I
thought that was with my feet
oh how do I make these look more
muscular they're not
there yeah there we
go yeah that's you breathing out the
cold and the altitude sickness on top
perfect of the
glacier
perfect yeah feel I feel like I haven't
spoken to you on stream in so
long yeah it's hard for me to keep count
because like we talk but then when was
it on stream was it not since you were
here I think
so it's been 2 months holy moly get busy
that's crazy busy stuff to do
no it was um Zeta
stream remember worker it was Z stream
yes I remember yes yes yes yes okay that
wasn't that and then we had Doom as well
I forgot about that oh yeah I joined you
for Doom oh my goodness it wasn't that
long ago it wasn't that long ago it's
fine I'm drinking so much water these
days me too it's good for you it's good
for you you
surprisingly
surprisingly no because like you know
how like whenever you ask for like
Health advice the first P thing people
always say is you need to drink more
water drink more water drink more water
you need to and then you just kind of
like well does it really make that much
of a difference and I'm here to yes it
does it really does oh no the advice I
was given works oh no oh no oh no it's
it's really good I'm I'm like less
bloated which I'm like wow what yeah
that's what water does oh my God thank
you
water I guess water is pretty good it's
also summer though I can't imagine
drinking this much water in
Winter got to keep your place super
[Music]
hot maybe I don't know sweat it out
g g Gul gulp Gul G I also feel like it's
very helpful to have like a Tumblr like
something to drink out of instead of
just a cup oh a tum that kind of Tumblr
yes yes
mhm not someone tumbling I see
no not a tumbler no no no
[Laughter]
[Music]
tumbler a tumble a tumble a t tum sounds
a tum sounds tum a Tumblr a tum Tumblr
Tumblr
Tumblr Tumblr
Tumblr cute pigtails by the way thank
you so
cute we kind of match a little bit yeah
we have like you have longer pigtails
but you have like the puffy on the out
you know yeah I do yeah yeah yeah it's
instant hair I'm reaching I just want to
feel connected to you
a
cute C than
[Music]
cute are you nervous for
tomorrow yeah I told you about my dream
oh
yeah I shouldn't I told chat too I
shouldn't have oh you know the entire
the entire time they're going to be
going it's too loud it's too loud it's
not going to be too loud it's too loud
they're going to scream it's too loud my
comment section highest voted voted
comment it was too loud M
no you're going to be fine people going
to love
it people are going to love
anything as long as you
show up no they should have
standards um I'm a smack you how dare
you have standard please how dare you
insult Nashi m in front of me I'm how
dare you I'm not I feel like it's an
insult to like everything I
do even if I do it
badly you could never do it badly it's
you this is insulting
[Laughter]
what I can never win guys I can't I can
I I'll tell you how to win M you say
nobody's perfect and if there's
something you got to work on just work
at it and I'm sure you'll get
there nobody's perfect M and if there
are things that you got to work on I
forgot the rest
you can just leave it
[Laughter]
there I appreciate
that appreciate it you're welcome thank
you you're welcome thank you I had a
real really weird ass stream last night
as
well I literally woke up and I was conf
you know when you wake up in confusion
yes I haven't had one of those dreams in
a while but I woke up I was so confused
F you say that because sometimes I when
I wake you up you always look
confused
[Laughter]
[Music]
really really
yes oh
no when I look at you I see myself
I'm sure I'm sure I look confused when I
wake up too but my favorite thing is
when I see you fall in asleep and like
you're still holding your phone cuz you
were watching a
video oh
yeah yeah and I'm like I wonder if she's
awake I hear her watching a video and
they're like Bae Bae no she's gone I'm
gone I will say something that adds to
you probably thinking I'm confused when
I wake up is the sound that I make when
I wake
up it's your face and it's your it's the
noise that you
make you don't you definitely don't look
how you do
[Laughter]
[Music]
here oh dear man oy I hate
you away like a like a little mouse that
you are oh it's okay we are on a time
limit we are but we are and I should
have thought this I should have given a
limit I should have thought this real
every like there's people that you were
worried no one was going to show up I
was worry I don't enough people would
show up to spill 3 hours but since it's
not like oh 5 minutes per
person no yeah well happy birthday I'm
really excited for tomorrow and and and
everyone's going to love it do your best
I hope it's not too loud thank you yeah
to lat back bye
bye I should check my DMs real quick
hold
[Music]
on hi hi happy
birthday happy birthday mov thank you I
just saw your
drawing yes I I'm and I draw I draw mate
too yes I'm going I send you I'm going
to share it oh you drew me
too yes oh wait oh I I need I need
oh I I need to put the color that's okay
wait I think it that's okay I think it
can work hold on can I paste it let me
see yes yes yes yes let me see copy
image allow first time I draw I told I
need a present for you and I drove a
tant but I thought uh I I I forgot it I
forgot to draw M so I draw M too it's
okay I love seeing
tarant so it's still a gift it's my mom
mov mom
m mom
yeah m
m can you see my
stream wait oh M eat M now
yeah nice it's oh wait it's oh it looks
like so
cute yay I've never seen such cute hat
all right I'm so
happy
yeah for you birthday Pleasant thank you
I happy birthday thank you I will make
you a present a drawing really yeah yeah
what do you want yay I go fast fast
drawing fast drawing yeah fast very very
fast very far first okay oh fast fast
fast I I like I I want to see the tal
something okay because I really like
your talant okay let me what can I do uh
um I'm going to make okay okay I think I
know what to do hold on okay I need to
look at a picture of of the
baby baby okay the baby
I I pick pick okay okay I think I can do
this okay
okay I I I did not make this but I just
found this
look oh I can't share it
no no wait I want to share it with
you here oh shoot the baby the baby the
baby can you see see I can see
W it's so cute so
cute cute baby okay I I can draw okay
um this oh is it not
working oh oh oh oh okay I got
it okay okay hot baby
hot okay baby hot
baby
terama I'm going to draw her making her
first spider
web spider her first web her um like
spider web here I I draw it spider we
like
the the
web make Mak sense ah W yeah yeah you
see okay I'm going to I'm going to make
it so
she uh it's okay okay for YouTube Okay
no Okay for YouTube okay yeah no
demonetization okay for B that's okay
it's okay no ban no ban it's okay it's
okay it's Mo my channel exactly
it's okay all right you have and this
one and then oh uhoh it's dying that's
okay this one and the
foot C Food yeah okay and
this oh no I lost it's okay it's okay
okay do the foot oh no that's not how I
don't know how to draw foot okay I have
to think okay this is what if fo looks
like
okay okay and then
um this is the
body
body and
then she's making a
web do oh making a web yeah she's making
web now making
[Music]
web
T the we
[Music]
so she can catch bugs to give
you yes she can eat it yeah she's going
to
hunt for you she going to hunt eat oh
box yeah and then she she got another
spider
oh she did it ta
dead oh my God it's upside
down it upside
down I thought sorry I thought you you
you did it no not on
purpose on purpose it was accident it
was it was accident okay
Tada T I did it yay thank
you thank you hat so cute
thank you for drawing pict oh okay I'll
take picture take picture yeah yes yes
oh I forgot I forgot oh no no no no no I
forgot uh I forgot two of her legs her
legs Al okay you have a life tomorrow I
do yeah my first you can do
it thank you
me best thank
[Music]
you thank you for coming and thank you
for the
drawings they're so cute thank
you thank you for drawing too you're
welcome and
I'm I'm
always T always I I'll watch I'll watch
your life oh thank you thank you I'm
nervous thank you thank you you nervous
yeah you can do
it I do it for you you can do it for
hot for and for
everyone yeah and hot thank you yay yeah
he thank you hot okay my m bye
bye-bye bye-bye by bye bye bye
[Laughter]
bye-bye
yay those drawings are so
cute I to C hold on
[Music]
oh
my who who's next who
approaches why I muted cuz it was
gross it wasn't cute Hello that's cute
hello it's been
5,000
years for this call I'm so sorry I've
seen you there for like an
hour Ollie's there
too oh my gosh okay if I ever do a Totum
mati again everybody gets a designated
time I understand now why no it was good
it was good I was I was I was eating my
lunch you that what you eat scra the P
from a oh yummy yummy yummy
anyways I uh I heard it was someone's uh
birthday perhaps it might be I don't
know do you know do you know what it
[Music]
is
possibly it it might be
mine you maybe I don't know I don't know
things sometimes but
maybe that's me yeah yeah wait you're
Nashi M I'm Nashi
M oh oh my goodness happy happy birthday
thank you oh my oh
my
[Laughter]
why I forgot where I was going with
why I you know for when I was when I was
just sitting I was like okay how do I
how do I start off this this uh entire
conversation I had different um
different uh options I came up with but
I forgot oh my goodness you forgot
because it was it's me and I forget it's
it's the Nashi moving effect it is the
closer I get the the faster I forget
yeah when the time comes brain empty
brain very empty but have you been I'm
okay I'm nervous about my life and I'm
and I I'm I'm just I'm just here I'm
just chilling my my official birthdays
in like 20 minutes well not official the
countdown ceases in 20 no my math my
math in 40
minutes oh my goodness it's so soon but
it's it's tomorrow right yeah tomorrow
it's tomorrow tomorrow tomorrow
tomorrow I can never I can never
replicate yeah it's like if you try you
just can't but if you just oh my gosh
this I feel like if I could voice crack
on command like I should probably be
doing you know
not just talk proper voice yeah know if
how was that great I think I can I can
crack my voice like but without speaking
like without saying words like H wait
was that it like hey how are you those
are words but that's not the right type
of cracking that's more just like yeah I
don't know what that is it just comes
and goes the natural voice crack is hard
mhm if only we were if only we were boys
going through puberty then it'd be easy
if oh yeah it's just natural to yeah I'm
so excited we have to work for it thank
you sorry that's me coughing do you want
to
dry I mean I mean sure sure I I would
love a dry what would you
like um um H um did you draw me a uh uh
a taco d a cured Taco d a cursed
takachi I can
try I'm going off a memory I don't
remember exact like I think I remember
how they look
but very cursed do oh my goodness your
Strokes so confident
dirty I don't know about
that oh I looks lovely it looks like the
back of my
head you have eyes on the back of your
head
now are they little flaps is this the
right place for their flaps or is it
more like this yeah yeah yeah
is it I mean I can look it
up let me I'm going to look up vtra he
looks like a cow
now they
move
CI uh oops wrong thing uh let me see
tack
Dy oh it could be either wait oh they go
up or down it's pretty flexible yeah
yeah say okay okay I give the
[Music]
Halo I can feel it a
masterpiece it's just getting there
we're getting in there do they have
noses I mean they're
good they're they're pretty uh pretty
flexible in terms of a features on the
face all
right okay
[Music]
okay I love it oh my goodness you like
it oh they have a color
shirt
yeah here I'll give it a little bit of
color just just a little bit
you know what this is kind of like it's
like
when
um it's like the American carttoon
version of yeah there's a specific
cartoon I had in
mind that's where the mouth came from
well actually a lot of cartoons use like
a very similar style of this like this
type of
mouth the big eyes with like a tiny
pupils too yeah like imagine this taco
and like an anime and they'd be uh
they've seen something but like in an
American cartoon style just a normal guy
yeah this is just a normal
Tuesday legally distinct it is I mean I
don't know what this is based on it's
this just there's a lot of cartoons that
kind of kind of look like this fun yeah
yeah yeah and I did this
okay all
right taada
I'm
glad is there is there some people in
the chat that's going just like me for
real have I
captured like like have you ever seen
videos where people are like I'm want to
draw a random person and I'll keep doing
this until like somebody you know
replies to the video showing that I drew
them sort of thing oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah that's what I've done here
oh my goodness I can't believe you just
like you just you just showed the real
form of the takachi in the world I did I
whoever this looks like you're the
chosen one The Chosen
One the
P like like from Hunger
Games yeah yeah yeah the Hunger Games
yeah man this one really looks like it's
about to win the
[Music]
H who could harm that I know the hunger
gam but he does look kind of
hungry he he'll do well he looks very
friendly oh yeah like you know my I've
always love like your
drawing have
you it's just so
good it's just like it's it's like one
thing being good at drawing you know
anime girl and there's another Talent of
like just being able to capture like
magical
moments that makes me so happy I will
forever remember you telling me this
anytime I feel bad about my drawing I
think but en likes it
I love it I love it I'm I'm going to put
it on my small little fridge I have here
oh thank you oh I'm so happy this is
this is going out the fridge
yeah will you sign it next time yes I
will thank you thank you even here my
family
a imagine how much this will be worth in
300 years oh my goodness even has your
signature
amazing can you imagine like like
Millennia later someone's just going to
like maybe unearth
this from from from the from the fossil
they going to be like what is this
strange looking figure is this what the
humans look like back in the day I
should put this on a
USB just leave it leave it
yeah that's so good but oh man I don't
want to take too much time cuz I I think
Olli is also I some of I I don't know
who's waiting next oh
Ollie yeah but but happy happy birthday
I hope you have a wonderful wonderful
year wonderful today wonderful food
happy things and do your best tomorrow
thank thank
you all right goodbye bye bye thank
[Music]
you come Ollie Oli come here oh olly oh
oh olly patient little olly oh
olly I don't know if I should go to her
because well she's muted it probably is
fine if I go to her
or do I let her come to me how do these
things
work well hopefully she hasn't just been
staring at Discord for like two hours
she probably's doing other stuff
too should I jump scare
her
okay let's see if she's
home oh
wait hold on ah Oops I messed it up
pardon me
hello H hello Ollie oh my God is this
the Nim who's having her birthday today
it is Ollie oh dear Ollie thank you for
waiting for so long you precious theing
you no it's my pleasure I'm sorry that I
can come this morning that's okay so bad
no Ollie it was so early I was shocked
any he would respond
I I thought I would be able to make it I
even had my uh alarm up but I just
couldn't wake up Ollie I so bad Ollie I
would have
honestly hear me out I may have lost
respect for you if you woke up that
early to play OverWatch 2o listen it's
not about the OverWatch I want to play
with you I I just want to carry you you
want to carry me I I I feel like you
know uh can can I call myself out real
quick okay last time you had a to Koke
you wasn't there and then I wasn't there
during the OverWatch and I feel so bad I
feel immense guilt I feel like I owe you
so much because you're always so sweet
and you're always going through so much
just for me and I'm not giving you the
same
thing I do not want you to wake up and
be super tired to play OverWatch it's
not like a t you'd have to get up go to
your computer open that cursed game and
play
it well maybe next time next time we for
sure time no I was I told who was it
that I told Ana I told Anya I well she
cuz she was also like oh you're were
playing OverWatch the most recent
streams I've done of it are like early
kind of not like early in the morning
for me but earlier than when I usually
stream so which is really early for
everyone in ID so I just I just need to
plan better I need to plan a late night
slash normal hour OverWatch but it's
okay I I saw that you played with like
the girly so it looked really fun yeah
no we we can play don't worry I play
this game I play it we can play it this
[Music]
game would you like a drawing
Allie I I I would love a drawing what
would you like
um can you draw me but as a gun as a gun
as a
gun like pew pew mhm oh gosh these are
like the things I'm worst at drawing but
I can try for you or we could try
something else I can no I'll try for you
I'll try for you I'll do it for you I'll
try for you hold on hold on Guna why did
I look up gun ol I know there's not
there's not one that already exists is
there
okay all right
okay okay yeah man you you are you okay
are like do your hands hurt they don't
no it's been mostly just chatting no I
haven't actually drawn that much it's
been mostly talking and silly doodling
oh thank God because I was like yo 10
people she's been drawing for 10 people
I would have been dead they're just
Doodles there nothing I used to draw for
so long for such a long period of
time this is this is fine let me make
sure wait why is it not changing uh-oh
hello wait a
minute why why is this why is this curs
Taco Dai not going away on the
screen it's not leaving what the heck
wait he he isn't leaving what it's
staying there we go there we go okay
okay okay did I do it what is wrong do I
have too many layers is that the problem
I'm sorry Ollie but give me a it's
mine what what the heck is going on did
my apple pen die what is
happening you're fine you're fine I
think no no no stress no stress is
here it says my Apple pen isn't dead but
why is it not letting
me I I I'm going to refresh the page and
hope that fixes it
okay are you
snacking yeah I'm I'm eating lunch what
you eat
eating I'm eating eggs um beef jerky
sausages hash BS and pancakes oh my gosh
breakfast yeah breast for lunch for
lunch yeah no you can have breakfast
anytime you so
please well I'm jealous that sounds good
have you eaten I made a little bit of
food but I'm going to make more later
probably I did guns work
what is it wait is it your um birthday
yet like it's a countdown right yeah
it's going to be well it is my birthday
in multiple places but the last
countdown well I might countdown till
Alaska the Alaskan time thingy but 30
minutes will be my birthday
PST mhm but not in Hawaii it's not my
birthday in Hawaii for like another 3
and 1 half hours
but I don't think I don't think we're
going to get that
far let's see okay this goes like this
I'm so bad at drawing things that aren't
alive like what the heck this is too
complicated hold on I'm just going to
make you a bit simpler I mean it's also
it's also one of the reasons why like a
lot of people go like okay listen I can
draw I'll take commissions but no Mech
please yeah no Mech no old people that's
like a common one
they don't want to draw
wrinkles yeah drawing old people is
actually so hard it is that's why they
say they won't draw old people it's not
cuz they don't like old people it's just
they don't know how to draw them exactly
they're a whole other thing to tackle oh
my goodness I don't know how to draw a
gun at see I'm just I'm so confused does
this look like a gun it's okay because
it's an odified gun so it doesn't have
to look real this doesn't look like a
gun I think my issue too is like I just
am so used to drawing things that are
like moving in fluid but when I think
gun I'm like oh but it's so like I need
to think shapes but I'm not this is a
this would be a good time to like do an
art lesson like oh it's just made of
shapes like here's another shape but
it's too much shape and then then but
this is here this
is this is the
[Music]
hand no stress by the
way it's okay um do you have like a
favorite thing that you like to
draw not
really
like not the
moment do
you um uh I like drawing boobs to this
oh like a body part that I like the most
to draw yeah or anything that you like
to draw like maybe eyes maybe I draw
probably I've drawn eyes the most but I
need to work on Anatomy I feel like if I
were good at Anatomy I would like
drawing and coloring bellies the
most
uh at least coloring yeah yeah like you
know what I
mean there can be really nice rendering
for them you kind of look like Thomas
the Tank Engine right now I'm going to
make you a Thomas the Tank Engine gun
you you can turn me into a train I don't
mind I don't know if how that I I don't
know I think I'm going to run into the
same issue there
honestly let's see okay oh okay here's
another uh art question yes how do you
feel about line
art
I I really admire people that do super
clean thick like gpen line art it's
something I never was really able to
do or you know what program I think is
best for doing line art still
what paint tool
sigh honestly you're that is so real
right that is real I remember when I
first got into digital art I was Wasing
uh like speed paints and stuff and a lot
of people use pain to side but I didn't
know how to get it and I just was using
like a parents computer that had
Photoshop and I was like I can't get the
I can't get the brushes to be as crisp
and look as
nice and then I learned oh it's it's
sigh and then I I used it for a very
long
time oh I might it's actually cool how
you first draw in the
Photoshop it looked so
blurry cuz the brush I didn't downlo
download custom brushes M it was it did
not look
good I first use uh Ms
paint I don't know how to make you into
a gun can I make you into a is that
possible yeah sure or you can turn me
into any other non living thing because
you know I'm basically
[Music]
[Laughter]
dead
a you'll never be dead not in my
heart M let me see if I can make you
into a train I don't I think this is
even more complicated to be honest but
I'll try or a car or a car I might be
overthinking this but wow it looks like
these trains are wearing
turtlenecks cuz they have like the black
around them yeah yeah yeah it's like a
turtleneck that is so cute here and then
you got a little light I guess and then
you got these things I'm so bad at
shapes all right shapes all right and
then body but oh thank goodness your
your buns kind of cover them all
right all right and we got this the body
the train
body here oh is this the steam trains
yeah yeah yeah oh that's that's so
fitting there you
go wow this is where the smoke comes out
choo choo
wait choo
choo here your
wheels I am Ollie the steam
[Music]
engine oh my God I looks so cute
what okay
um I just I remove some of this that's
your okay okay okay
okay I'll make this a bit bit more I
don't know what I was doing here oh oh I
see what that is okay that's part your
butt okay T you're a train choo Cho I'm
a
train
y
yippy thank you I will treasure this let
me let me screenshot it real quick
what's your favorite number what's your
favorite number
13 okay it's a bit hidden but it says 13
here there you go that's your
number
yeah taada oh wait free commission I can
get rid of this hold on wait why is it
like this stop doing okay there we go
all right
ta it's so cute thank you L you're
welcome I hope you have a lovely rest of
your uh naat birthday thank
you yeah so um so you know uh I know we
don't talk a lot but I hold you really
close to my
heart I care for you a lot and you're
really really
talented I'm wishing you the best of
luck for tomorrow by way you can do
it thank you ol I can't wait for to Al
thank you H I love you you precious you
precious little thing you I I truly
meant that no
you thank you
H thank you I'm going going to take my
leaf now byebye
[Music]
byebye yum that's me eating my
feelings because I have so many I have
to swallow them
okay whom is next whom hoop hoop hoop
hoer Let's see we have two options here
but one of them is deafened but she's
there is somebody deafened but she is
hanging out with the other person who
isn't
[Music]
deafened wait what is this who named it
that wait how did how did this how does
Discord work now why is this channel
called waiting for
hello hello
hi I didn't know if I could jump in the
car I was waiting oh don't worry I was
waiting to pounce too but you beat me
cuz you're a
panther yeah I'm a dial yeah yeah yeah
hello
hello thank you for
coming thank you not yet but almost
almost yeah in Japan yes more minut yeah
yeah yeah I I'm going to grab your oh
shoot I didn't I oh there we go okay I'm
grabbing your Twitter picture and I'm
going to put you in here and okay I put
I put you here
and would you like a
drawing yes I'd love drawing what would
you like oops what would you like oh my
God anything is fine I I don't know I
need guidance I need guidance okay okay
you know what would you like to draw my
my smoth mascot I can send you their
reference yeah I can send you their
reference very quickly yes please yeah
yeah yeah I'm going to do it let me give
me a moment okay okay how's it going
how's your day are you having fun I
am yeah are you being spoiled by
everyone yeah everyone's being super
nice to me for some reason of
course you're a very nice person you
deserve to be treat them very good
everybody's nice here a
I'm looking for my ah my my my my my oh
good oh good I can also Google
it no I have a proper a proper reference
sheet yeah I found it there you go let
me see there you go let me see let me
see perfect oh my
goodness okay okay okay I got this can
people see it all right thank you so
much I'm so excited to see it I'll will
do my best I don't know you're very good
at dra I don't know about that you're
look at you you you are crazy good I
love to watch I love to watch you like I
only really maybe it's just the timing
but when I see you draw so far it's only
really been when you're sketching but
even that is so satisfying to me a thank
you so much you know I
usually I usually like to sketch on my
own because um I get stressed out uh on
the sketching face I don't if that's the
same for you oh I do too if it's a
serious draw that's why I never draw
seriously yeah it's like I gu stress out
when when I have to sketch so I prefer
to do that on my own and then I I like
the render face on yeah see I'm really
bad at rendering because the way I am is
like I never I used to be able to finish
drawings but I just can't anymore if I
started drawing I just want to move on
to the next I give I have a limited like
a like a time limit in my head for some
reason so I never finish to be honest
that's quite how I feel sometimes is
because after a while you get tired of
the of what are you doing right yeah
like like throwing the same thing for
more than two three days it kind it's
kind of tiring and then you don't like
it anymore that's why I feel like I put
a timer on my head as well isn't it
crazy there's people that spend like
months years on the same artwork I my
limit is literally 2 hours I can't oh no
it's really
short unfortunately no I don't I usually
don't spend more than two three days on
the same thing because if I spend more
than three days I just drop it I
literally I literally like remove from
my folder I put in the bean yeah I don't
like it I do that too for used to my
little YP te holder yeah that
just hasn't seen the light of day in so
long it's so full
right yeah I'm going to make
dra I'm going to make you're doing so
good I'm going to make him a a feral
form a do you know what I mean yes it's
crazy good no he's don't worry don't
worry about it don't worry about
it his body his body I'm getting a
little
what do I make him do oh I'm going to
make M BR out
[Music]
actually it's like he's
posing yeah so cute
[Music]
fig so I said CH oh my gosh my I okay no
you say right perfect but I saying the
Pokemon
on
accident which one was it
Dratini oh Dratini yeah oopsy true oh
which one is your favorite Pokemon my
favorite Pokemon including
legendaries yeah everyone okay my
favorite Pokemon is Latios including
legendary cute oh my God it's so nice
that just is great yeah the movie is the
movie is so good this why yeah yeah my
my favorite is also legendary if you
consider that a legendary is
giri oh gir yeah yeah yeah that's a cute
one too I love giri so much it's very
pretty it's the cute there's like
different categories of legendary it's
like super small and cute or super super
ominous
and I don't I feel like they have a
different name I remember is there a
name for the typ yeah like Myster I
don't remember it was like Musical
musical tree Pokmons yeah I don't
remember how to
draw oh
dear it's okay you can draw potatoes
fine he's a bean he's a yeah I like a
bean here I'm going to cheat I'm going
to make him
floating in a donut fine he's in a
[Laughter]
donut he's he's in a donut it's so cute
wait he's maybe too Bean too bit too
much Bean okay it it's okay it's okay
it's okay it's perfect all right he's
been eating hot dogs
yeah
body too many too many hot dogs this
summer too many too many hot dogs yeah
do you like do you like hot dogs in the
summer yeah they can be good but I don't
I have one in a while I don't have a
grill and I don't feel like they're good
any other
way yeah yeah I feel
that limited I did buy one like a month
ago oh oh why you know I don't think I
ever got a proper hot dog in my whole
life because you know
Mony no never never I don't think so
you have to get a good one I got like
one
from
7 but it's not a good one wait 7eleven
where uh in Japan oh okay cuz yeah even
in America in 7eleven that's not the
type I would recommend oh yeah it's I
feel like it's a similar one they have
like the warm hot dogs in the in the
fing you got to you got to go to a
baseball game just to
get this looks so weird uh just to get a
hot
dog I want to try never never been to a
baseball match before either it's been
years for me I don't remember how to
draw oh
dear oh no it's okay A it can be
difficult like I heard that sometime the
more easy something is like is to throw
that the more difficult you know that
like the same concept as drawing Kirby
you know Kirby is so hard to draw even
if it's a just a bow right that actually
makes sense because since there's like
less detail I guess I don't know how to
explain it but you're you have to put
everything in the right position yeah
yeah your uh what's the word yeah the oh
my gosh what's the word what's the
word the dimen yep that's it the
proportions have to be super accurate
yeah oh that makes
sense oh I feel like this is too L here
now make it a little a little taller
maybe I don't know I'm just going to I'm
going to just go with it okay
oh I also I have a question for do you
like what's your favorite kind of T not
cake to get on your birthday my favorite
cake yeah what's your favorite cake my
favorite cake is Strawberry Short Cake
in Japan oh oh yeah it's good it's so
good but um I also I I'm always good
with the normal vanilla cake with if
this like it has not too much icing and
a lot of sprinkles but not the Bey
sprinkles has to be like the stick
sprinkles you know oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah got it
mhm I think my favorite is feel like
it's cheesecake do you consider
cheesecake as a cake I do yeah yeah it's
a type of cake yeah what kind of
cheesecake
cheesecake uh so if I really have to
pick one I like salted caramel
cheesecake o m I love salted caramel
yeah I love saled caramel ice
cream yumy
yummy
yummy I didn't get cake this year maybe
after my liveo go get myself a cake you
should you should get yourself a even
like one of the small ones just to
celebrate yeah I think I will I always
tell other people on their birthdays I'm
like did you get your cake you got cake
yeah it's not really your birthday if
you don't have cakes you're not going to
get any older if you don't eat your cake
[Music]
I'll get some a
donut have you this is very random have
you ever tried doing 3D sculpting
before Oh my God I actually did I used
finger was like VRA zbrush okay softw I
was going to ask if you've used blender
because yes have you have you ever used
the I did a bit the famous blender donut
tutorial
oh yeah yeah yeah
did I was just thinking about
it wait you did you did a little bit of
3D before I did like a class really
briefly a really long time
ago and um I remember I did it on my
laptop and my laptop could not handle it
and it was supposed to be graded but I
wasn't even able to finish my donut
because my my laptop was
overheating oh no I had to turn it in
unfinished oh no they just expected me
to have a full chunky computer that
could handle it yeah 3D is very heavy
for for laptops especially for laptop
down I remember I kind of had the same
problem that's why I never really got
into 3D because my computer was a potato
PC back in the days uh but I would
really really wanted to learn because
the main reason I wanted to learn 3D is
because I wanted to print uh you know
Pokemon figurine
or
yeah
cute I you know I saw so many cool
things doing with the 3D print and I
wanted to learn myself but I never
really got into it yeah it because of my
PC was too bad I also tried tried using
even like flash animation and it would
make my computer so slow and back then I
had more patience but after a certain
point I couldn't I couldn't handle it
anymore
a where should the tail be maybe this
way no where should his Tail's just in
the water be inside inside the donut
just in just inside the donut is okay
it's deep in the he's deeping the the
the tail into the water
okay ta
here is a quickly dtin am I missing any
important details so pretty it's perfect
I'm going to just thank you so much I'm
just going to do actual blushy and
then and then I will be done oops no not
like this like this perfect
[Music]
yeah I tried oh he's off to the side
though I made made
a quick
attempt it's a perfect thank you so
much I love it thank you for dropping by
of course my pleasure thank you for
having
me and happy birthday soon yeah five
minutes 5 minutes in 5 minutes the
countdown is technically over oh my god
let's
go year
M happy birthday thank
you thank
you byebye everyone byebye bye bye
byebye let's see hold on wait let me uh
wait let me real quick uh de
okay there are still people waiting but
shoot what what do I do I feel like I
shouldn't be in a call during The Final
Countdown but they're waiting I feel
really bad um
I'm going to I'm going to send a message
hold on hold on hold
[Music]
on I can't hide I can't die fast
enough did you sne
did
somebody sound like a I heard
that oh
dear we got 4 minutes should I count it
down I don't think I can I think it will
take me 5 minutes exactly to set up are
you
good animal hold on a second sheot hold
on hold on
[Music]
oh she was dreaming she was dreaming
that's why she was making weird
noises she was
streaming Okie doie they that wait it's
it's okay it's okay this is 3 minutes
there also this is the first instance
I've seen where people waiting are
speaking to each other they have each
other it's
okay it's okay for
out
anyways oh wait that's not where that is
it's here this goes good
here well
everybody it's almost time is it it's
almost time
PST but it's not it won't be time yet
Alaska or
Hawaii yeah they have each other so cute
I wonder what they're talking
[Music]
about It's the final countdown 2 minutes
what do I do within those two minutes
I'm so used to having somebody talking
to me and carrying a conversation I
forgotten how to do it on my
own I know what to do I'll ask the chat
questions and hopefully see their
response do you guys have a favorite
creation so far today a favorite doodle
[Music]
show my 3D did you guys know I have a 3D
live tomorrow almost
today if you're in
PST go oh wow quite the
variety lots of different
[Music]
answers sometimes I have this like
mindset when I draw where like I'm I
know I'm putting too much into it but
but I want it to look better than it
can't be but sometimes just not not
trying so hard is what makes it look
better sometimes then it's embarrassing
if you do try hard and it looks really
bad I I cannot believe I was worried
about there being empty space just
people have been talking to me for so
long yes I won't do this again where
people are waiting like this I will
definitely set it up so that it's
designated time with a time limit
it makes sense now it makes perfect
sense why people do that oh where where
are we with the time the countdown hold
on can I see the
second two three four five that's not a
countdown dang it wait three two
one it's my birthday in PST
wow wow wow n PST it's my birthday
that means my 3D Live is is on the same
day as my oh gosh it's it's my birthday
[Music]
and I waited for this day for so
long I've waited for so
long the day is upon us I just need one
more one more night worth of sleep and
by that I mean like another 3 hours of
sleep and then I'll wake up and then
I'll be up during the day and then I'll
be prepping for the 3D live and then
I'll have the 3D
live oh my goodness I'm so so nervous
about I'm so nervous and I'm so excited
about it I'm so nervous but I'm so
excited about
it the whole thing I mean it's the whole
thing how do I say this it's for me I do
it because I want to do it you know it's
been the biggest thing I've been
planning that's on my mind it's been
like that for months and months it's at
the Forefront of my mind because I want
to do it and because it's for me but
it's also so very much for all of you so
I really really hope I do an okay job
and that you guys like it when the time
comes because it's not well what's for
me is making it so that you guys okay
how do I say you guys liking it that's
for me it's and for you it being for you
is for me you get
it do you get you get what I'm trying to
say
[Music]
here I think go go okay and I don't I
don't think it's going to be too
loud I I I don't think it's going to be
too loud I hope it's not too loud
did I have any other complaints in my
dream what are the other complaints that
I
had oh I think the other complaint I had
would spoil would spoil what I'm
doing oh I hope it's not too quiet
either I hope that it's just right
[Music]
do you
guys I wonder if you guys will have any
guesses have any hunches as to what I'll
do what will I
sing I'm going to sing a
lot M more than my 3D showcase that's
for sure
[Music]
K but asked my
birthday should I get a cake should I
get what kind of cake should I get
[Music]
after you know it's rough buying cakes
for just one person because I want more
than one piece of cake it's like they
either just sell one piece of cake or a
full cake I can't eat a full cake but I
can definitely eat more than one piece
of cake over a few days I guess I could
buy multiple pieces of cake cake that's
probably the that is the solution to buy
multiple pieces of cake I fixed it
cupcakes cupcakes that's not the same I
I do like cupcakes though cupcakes
though I I I do not eat the uh
icing I always take the icing off not
always often I take half of the icing
off I don't know they're they're fine I
could bake my own I won't have time
tomorrow to bake my own cake never mind
I should have planned this ahead I
should have done that yesterday
okay my
goodness I'm out of
water okay I'm going to I'm going to get
more water I think I'm going to get a
tiny little snack and I won't be too
long because I have lovely people
waiting to talk to me but they're it
seems they're talking to each other so
that's
good that's good I don't want to you
know interrupt them they might not be
done talking to each other
so so so
so okie dokie everybody I will be right
back and then we will continue I think
there's just two more I think unless
other people do decide to show up
but shall see I be right back hold on
I'm going to do this I go here one
second one second one second oh wait
I'll leave you with a drawing what
drawing do you want me to leave you with
which one am I most proud
[Music]
of I I lost the Kiara
one as long as there's a
screenshot the taco or the
SL where is
it wait that's ba oh oh my
gosh is this it no that wait that what
there you go
I think that might be a little too a
little too out of context here no I'll
leave you
with oh my goodness let me scroll let me
scroll I'll leave you
with oh I have to do it
here all
right perfect okie dokie I'll be right
back I'll be right back I'll be right
back be right back
[Music]
oh
hi I'm
back Okie
[Music]
okay shall we see who wants to come
first will he will he even
notice are they talking to each
other I can add them I should
probably I notice
ah Mommy happy birthday
Iris Iris hris Iris
Iris making us wait for eternity huh you
popular girl I'm so sorry there's no
time liit I didn't think this thre very
well I was thinking oh this will be
easier on everybody am I just say I just
show no you're so right though it truth
to it oh Iris
hey how are you I'm doing all right how
are
you just a little just a little bit here
I'm going to get your your picture here
oh you're so cute oh my
goodness yeah travel R looks very cute
let me wait let me uh oh shoot I'm
running out of space I have to make this
bigger give
me Irish do you want a
drawing yes please what would you like
oh that's a hard one I have two I was
thinking CU I know you you're you're
asking everyone what they want so like I
was thinking either I want uh I want to
see Iris as a dude or um I want to see
ekim and
gyus wait is that not the same thing no
it's not it's not the same thing no gyus
is the stick figure
oh guys is a stick finger I was so lost
leading either that or or gender
B okay do you
have a specific eiman in
mind specific eiman in mind can you
guess kind an
inspiration an inspiration um like is
there any eeken you look at and you go
gosh I wish I could be just like him oh
well I mean you know there is um one
character that I think you also know
that oh oh yeah I know
know maybe not mention the name just in
case okay okay okay okay I just
inspiration could come from that maybe
perhaps so all right I know exactly what
features to focus on yes you can read my
mind right I think so okay let me get
rid of this Taco
Dai that taco Dai is C what what's going
on with that taco Dai barely fits the
shirt what I don't know you
just it's just just tell fit is it's
just a bit tight fitting that's
all that's all I wonder what if we're
not thinking of the same the same if
we're not thinking of the same then I
will think that that's the type of eimen
that you think of mum oh okay well I'm
thinking I'm trying to think of the one
that you're thinking of why is this not
working yes read my mind M I'm screaming
at you in my mind right now okay I'm I'm
listening I'm I'm taking the scream okay
I have to refresh the page one
second it w let me draw Hello There we
go okay okay let's see all right wait I
need a picture of you too hold on
Iris yes oh are you drawing are you
drawing gender band Iris then doing wait
wait wait wait where are you at you
don't watch yourself as an Ean no no no
no no no no yes I did yes I was s either
it was just the two options I was just
wondering which one you were going for
okay you are going to be eim and
Iris yay okay okay okay okay all right
how do I do this um all right Dorito
Dorito I just realized that the go XLR
when you like key down your voice
there's like a there's a gender
button yeah wait can I let me see I
didn't noticed it was gender it's not
very good though it just makes you sound
like a chipmunk really let me
try
uh it doesn't really do anything did you
press the FX button yeah I did I did see
it's like you had helium yeah it goes up
like this it doesn't really go down when
I go down it just kind of goes down like
this this is the lowest I can go just
sound like I'm congested or something it
does sound like you have a cold that's a
believable voice you could do yeah oh my
most believable like dude voice has to
be like I think I end up would have to
use the pitch the pitch down even that
one I don't
know uh
oh you're you're a dude
alien you're an alien guy the guy from
what's going on I don't know it doesn't
it sounds so robotic why does it sound
so robotic I've noticed that too I don't
know why it sounds like that maybe
there's more you have to address but I
have had the same thing
before yeah so are you nervous for
tomorrow
I I am are you nervous
tomorrow you're not as nervous as you
though for
tomorrow sorry I'm thinking you how do
you draw
ears I don't know how do you draw ears
don't you just like I mean I guess
technically oh but iris's ears are
pointy oh you're right they are pointy
oh my goodness they are they are lady oh
sh I lost please tell me I didn't lose
that okay thank goodness I would never
able to make such a perfect chin again
okay okay okay I think I think you're
getting exactly what I'm thinking of
though okay Neato you're going to look
like an elf for a little bit yeah all
right all right all right and I do this
and
then why why do you want to be an Ean or
I guess you you don't want me why do you
want me to draw one I wanted to see you
what how what kind of eeken I've never
seen you draw an eimen before I I don't
think I have drawn one before I don't
know how to draw
guys I feel like girls are just easier
to draw I think so too I don't know
they're more fun to draw it's like cuter
poses and yeah I feel like you have to
be more discreet with yeah dud just wear
pants yeah that's boring I know right
and sometimes I'm so glad I didn't I
wasn't born as a dude that only wors
pants
right I say as I well I wear skirts too
I I I dress very like easily yeah I'm
just a lazy dresser in
[Music]
general it's like girls have so much
stuff they can do they can wear makeup
they can short they can get their nails
done yeah they can get their nails done
I do now cuz of you
pretty
regularly really really pretty regularly
yeah well I should be more regular
because I let them grow out way too long
and then I'm embarrassed to go get them
done again cuz they'll see how long
they've grown out and be like have you
have you been walking around like this
you should be ashamed I feel it feel
them judging me it's it's hard to go
regularly right like it is sometimes
you're too busy and it adds up yeah it's
not cheapy yeah so they're have been
times where I go and I'm like just take
them off please and then I then I just
don't have anything for a little bit but
only thing is you have to pay them to
also take them off to that's it too but
I mean it's a cal as much as You' pay
for them to do something else all right
yeah I've been taking like whenever
someone asks me like oh I want to get my
nails done when they come to Japan I
take them to the same place that you
know uh we've all been to yeah yeah and
they're they they always recognize me oh
you brought a different a different girl
along dang you have so many friends yeah
but then they never come
back they're like wait what are you
doing with them no no they know that
they're they know that they don't live
in Japan they know that there are people
that are not from Japan you have so many
overseas friends that you bring along
I'm like yes thank you for your business
oh my God the neck is so long this is
not what you
wanted no no no it's perfect perfect
long necks are definitely a trait of
beauty you know they are like a swan
like elongated necks yeah yeah like
totally not a not yeah like a swan
that's what it's based on because of
that not based on anything else mhm yeah
not based on anything this is my Pure
Imagination of what you would look like
as an E I don't know how to draw
clothes that makes me think man thank
God I was born a girl I don't have a
neck this long this is no this is just
the
the just just the special ones have a
neck this long ah it's just I'm special
am I special to you m yeah of course you
are of course taada all right I'll give
you your hetero
chromia yes color in my eyes the okay I
feel like I should do your hair too
just a little bit just a little bit Yeah
okay I'll I'll go really fast if I just
have to color match can I do it can I do
it can I do it okay okay
um it doesn't have to be exact this is
beautiful this is what we're rolling
with all
right I don't know I don't think I've
ever
seen an eaman with this hair color
you're truly special yes I know that's
true I really don't think I've seen one
with magent magenta hair I feel like
there should be if you like if you play
like games like Idol eim idol Rhythm
games and stuff they have like a million
different dudes so like there has to be
like a different color for every single
one of them I haven't been exposed
enough I'm just thinking of like or in
high school scho I feel like it's just
like you know when it comes to anime
characters one of the most distinct
features to differentiate anime
characters is their hair color yeah like
that's how you know who the protagonist
is and the first shot is shown they
faces in yeah they all have the same
face cuz it's the same art style usually
right and you just have to depend on the
hair color color and how big the alog is
yeah man I love your alog I wish I had
an Al like that ask for one in your next
outfit are you going to become are you
going to become Emo with me I want to
become some of emo yeah
dip dipp to
what's a dip what's dip a toe dip a toe
into the emo oh that's em yeah no I will
definitely I will plunge my whole foot
in emo you oh my goodness oh what if
it's scorching hot in there the emo what
the emo bath it's okay emo Emo's I don't
think emo would be scorching hot right
it's more
like yeah you know like ice cold
well this is this I like your pig
tails I always wonder people say
pigtails but isn't this supposed to be
like twin I guess I think those are
pigtails but like I think I heard you
talking to Bae about like oh I like your
pigtails too but I was like isn't Ba's
like hair more like you're right Tails
oh wait no no no I meant uh
her her new outfit oh that one oh yeah
yeah that's pigtails M no well she has I
would call those those are twin I don't
know what is it
I think it's like pigtails I feel like
are the ones that like hang
lower is my personal opinion yeah cuz
these yeah and twin tails are like
higher up huh is at least that's what I
think okay are the is the difference but
I don't know it might be different for
people who I don't know I trust you I
trust your guest trust my guess yes my
opinion is absolute thank you m that is
beautiful you're welc keep that as my
Roger I'm I'm glad you like
it the neck is so
long that's the best part yeah it is the
best part so much neck you know you can
you can probably you know um wrap his
whole face around you yeah it's like a
snake yeah like a snake yeah that is
definitely an e feature all righty then
I don't want to keep the last last
people waiting so all right happy
birthday M thank you thank you for the E
eus you're welcome it looks exactly like
what I imagined by the way the E
character oh perfect oh I'm so glad to
hear that mhm you Dro beautifully okay
what are you drawing right now I'm
drawing him wrapping his neck around
somebody that is that is longer than I
thought but
yeah thank you you're welcome now I
don't have to leave it to my imagination
I see it right in front of
me thank you for dropping by see you
tomorrow see you tomorrow yeah
[Music]
byebye t I might just get rid of that
real
quick oh no that's as far as I can
undo that's okay
that's all right okie dokie do we just
have one person
left or should I say two persons left
hello
B one person one person I di there's
only one person in
Discord it throws me off happy birthday
thank you thank
you thank you
thank would you to like a
drawing a drawing a drawing yeah oh
actually it will be a scary as last time
no
not not like last time it's your your
birthday m s but it's actually another
birthday coming up really soon what uh
it's a p's
birthday it's perel's birthday soon yeah
but you can forget about it but yeah
it's your birthday yeah are you sure are
you so you guys are sacrificing your
drawing for pedal
petal is that what you're saying you
want do you want me to draw pedal I
guess he's really nasty though but he's
nasty so round I don't even know if he
this is big enough for
him yeah you know what they say when
you're faced with nastiness you just you
know be kind in return we we tried that
he
tried he has yeah he has I don't
know angry he has a really really long
tongue yeah NY he looks so round but it
just it comes out nowhere it just
continues is the is the tongue round too
or is it like oddly sharp it's long it's
long I have to see this but if it's too
scary if it's too nasty I could just you
know draw my own idea of it if you if we
don't want to use your imagination okay
all right I'm going to do that you're
right he is so
nasty what he says horrible things
don't wear anything uh what anything
white like I am right now anything I
just remember how he's behaving when it
was whole
summer yeah what did this m do what did
he do talking about girlo unspeakable
yeah what but it's your birthday it's
okay we don't have to talk about nasty
stuff no we're so excited for your
birthday thank you yeah oh I hear you
sing so much and
dance so many people are going to oh my
gosh everybody's talking about it which
means they're going to watch
all thank you that oh don't
worry don't don't worry you do amazing M
so fun thank you I'm so excited for your
3DS I feel like I've been I've been
waiting so long no don't wait don't okay
it's okay okay I won't wait we did we
did our best we're going to do our best
practice has been difficult it has been
long yeah I bet I I heard some of what
you were planning just a a little bit
and just from what I heard I was amazed
we been working like dogs you know you
have been oh I'm so
[Music]
excited well we get to enjoy your
concert tomorrow and then I guess maybe
you get to check out our deew I I shall
it'll get be here before you know it I
know yeah it's oh sorry I'm trying to
still so much
practice how do I draw his wings sorry
he's so nasty I'm I'm not used to
drawing such nasty things Nast he's so
nasty he's hard to draw too he is
there's just so much to capture how do I
capture just how nasty he is yeah
like e he's not round enough it's not
nasty
enough yeah he's so round sometimes you
know it's just like the canvas just kind
of breaks yeah yeah I know I'm trying my
best to contain contain it right now
hold on don't worry the tongue is coming
I haven't forgot about it well that
means that his wings need to be a little
bit I got this I got don't worry do not
to worry girls I got this stand back I'm
not worried it's p he won't hurt you
anymore so so he's just nasty it's not
that he's powerful or or is
he he's he's the great
palalo that's how he refers to himself
the
parino yeah the Great parino
what yeah what is this guy involved in
he says he's our Mentor Tau he taught us
some stuff the demon you don't have to
worry about that cuz he's just a pet
okay he's just a pet okay did he get Dem
pet not tougher than I no okay okay all
right that's good to know so if I push
his buttons I can just hide behind you
guys and you'll protect
me yeah yeah okay perfect yeah all right
tongue here's the tongue hold on yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah just like that just
like that he's so nasty he wraps it
around
himself he could I've never seen it
happen but he could oh my
gosh I can see it it's like a knit
sweater cuz he's too nasty to ever be
hugged so he so he has to hug himself he
has to hug himself hug PE have why would
you hug something so ni he helped us out
when we in the cell wi
Wi-Fi presents I could never give him a
hug so no that's good what's this could
could it really be that he would do this
in my
imagination that he would got very
confused that he would offer a flower oh
a flower flower a flower to somebody
that would be like him he could pick
some somebody these flowers a the
flowers was R the G he picked their oh
my
gosh I I see it now wait Let Me Wait no
that's not round enough I'm going to
make him very
[Laughter]
round oh no the thing is those really
like him I don't know why maybe it's
because P's been stealing flowers and
giving it to the
wolin that could very well be it you
know my friend my floating paper bag
friend there was a time where he would
sell tickets to my humans without
permission and they were not real
tickets to anything oh wow validated
tickets unvalidated invalidated tickets
so you really just got to keep an eye on
them yeah they Sil but P's been sort of
missing recently yeah you know from
morning generally the muffins they keep
an eye out and give us per sightings
wait you don't recently you don't keep
him in a
box no he's just going around what he
sound a little bit you mean so he could
show up to my door after I made this
depiction of him and I guess that's
that's true waiting for you yeah we
haven't seen him for a little while it's
been almost a week yeah what do you do
what like you know how if you see a bear
you're either supposed to like run or
play dead or something what do you do if
you see a perro that is not so happy
with you pudding pudding him pudding
pudding oh pudding oh my gosh it's so
simple what a simple creature okay okay
yeah okay just in case it's like I'm
putting salt like a salt circle around
me put little puddings outside the door
I
offer pudding I off I don't remember
what pudding looks like exactly but
here's some pudding yeah pudding here
you go C just in case to keep him at Bay
is that what Ping looks like probably
isn't yeah yeah or is it more like goopy
goopy well maybe it's m s hand made
pudding no my attempt at pudding yeah
have you made pudding before I have not
have you oh it's actually pretty easy I
you know what I've watched before I
think I've watched other people make
pudding like on YouTube I used to it's
of fun you just take gelatin and like
vanilla or I don't know I I have no clue
do do you do you what do you do for like
pudding it's like eggs and milk and
vanilla extract and then you have to se
it so you make sure that's really really
smooth and then you put the mixture into
like little cups and then put them into
water bath and then I put them in the
oven with the microwave oh I'm thinking
of jello that's what I'm thinking
of I see I see like fla I see
okay oh sounds yummy so yummy I miss
Japanese pudding a recently we haven't
found any good pudding oh you guys you
guys have like higher taste than I do I
just go to the comen I'm content well
actually it's very sweet it's super
super sweet it's too sweet yeah that's a
good point the comini one has been too
sweet I don't know I had one once in
Japan that I was given and it was just
the right amount of sweetness I've I no
clue what it was though maybe one day
maybe like a special department store
one probably oh yeah one of those fancy
stores that you have to know to to be in
a no you got to go to the
basement the basement has all the good
puddings it's so of weird that it's the
basement huh it is suspicious you look
at a department store and it's like
bottom to like the two basement floors
is like yeah
treats right
it's
yum yeah but there's so many things to
choose from we always feel
like never mind never mind yeah it's
overwhelming for sure especially when
there's like more than an option so for
me when I have gone to those I just go
to the ones where like they only have
two flavors of something so it's easier
to
choose this or that yeah this one or
that one and you know maybe one it like
really sticks out so easy it's like I'm
just I only have one
option
yeah well I think you're safe from ped
for now for now now for now he looks so
cute does
he kind of like a big yarn ball oh it
does like got into some trouble got into
some trouble yeah you could really make
a sweater out of that
tongue it's cute figh
oh thank you thank you thank you happy
birthday happy
birthday sometime yes please we have to
find a
game all we keep doing is
call no it's hard to find game maybe or
we can be creative can do something even
more creative than a
game yeah I'll use my I'll try to use my
brain I'll try to remember it's just
sometimes time goes by so fast like you
guys have been here you've been here for
a year it's crazy
yeah I don't even know right it feels
like just the other day we were saying
hajim together I know that was a year
ago right what the heck that's
crazy y oh that's so weird I know right
it's very
scary yeah I don't like
someh time exist
yeah crazy stuff yeah crazy
indeed but do
you yeah we be cheer you thank you thank
you and I will cheer you
back on on back for your 3D debut keep
keep strugging along keep working
hard thank
[Music]
you happy birthday happy
birthday b b
[Music]
bye-bye bow
bow oh goodness gracious everybody I
think they are the last the last
visitors I don't have anybody else
waiting right now so maybe some people
couldn't make it anymore but some people
who didn't uh who didn't initially say
they could make it showed up so more
people than I expected oh my gosh I
didn't put them on the screen wait hold
on
B oh I got to remember to do
things interesting has all of Advent has
the same icons they had since they
joined how long did how long did it take
me to change mine for the first
time oh
my let's see I think it took at least a
year for me to change my YouTube icon
that's like a
bit cie dropped by did she oh was she in
chat
wait Callie did send a message she's in
a little bit of a
pickle that's okay though I appreciate
just anybody saying they would try to
make
it oh I missed it what did she say what
she said happy oh Callie thank you
wherever you are Callie whatever
whatever pi pickle juice you're
in thank you thank
[Music]
you oh my goodness it's so late
everybody I should go to bed so should
all of
you man this day went
by I'm still a little tilted I wasn't
able to do everything I wanted to do but
we'll make it up and we'll have a day
full of song tomorrow
yeah yeah yeah
yeah thank you everybody this has been a
day of streaming it is now my birthday
in all of Na except some parts of Alaska
and
Hawaii and Canada
maybe in the Arctic I don't know how
does Canada look again
oh wait no not here not here not here
not here not
here oh it goes a little over oh I don't
know
actually it's not real I know but what
does it look like if it were real what
time zone what time zones would it
cover anyways thank
you thank you everyone for hanging out
today for watching we played OverWatch
we showed new accessories we almost did
a karaoke and we watched bi Boo live and
then we did this I can't believe it's
been how long have I been here oh this
one okay this has been 3 and a half
hours this day hasn't felt as long as it
was I don't feel like I've been
streaming since the time I started just
cuz OverWatch you know it just goes by
it's so simple so easy to stream
[Music]
anyways please if you can and if you
want to come watch my 3D live
[Music]
tomorrow I I think I'm going to be happy
with how it goes I hope so if everything
goes according to plan I think I will be
happy and I hope you guys will be too
and I hope it's not too loud and
[Music]
yeah tomorrow 8:00 p.m. or today 8:00
p.m.
PST
tomorrow uh 12:00 p.m.
jst yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm so excited I
can't believe it's happening my chair's
making
[Music]
noises did you guys enjoy today was it
okay did it go by super fast were you
glued to your screens
I know I was my eyes feel really weird
this is the longest I've been in front
of a screen for a while cuz even in
between in between my well no that's not
true I I did take animal out I was
looking at my phone though was not
completely in the
moment went by fast it was fun I'm happy
to
hear I wish I didn't have a
cough I wish I didn't have these issues
use but it is what it is right now and I
think it still went okay to well yeah
it's okay it's okay make up
karaoke Another
Time 3D live tomorrow here I'll make it
even bigger hold on where is
it oh
oh it's me outside the
Box yay I'm looking forward to seeing
you all there those who can make it I
know it's a kind of difficult time if
you are
in if you're in Asia and in of course
Europe EU if you're in
Africa but you're in South America
or North America or Central America you
should be a well I don't know you you'll
have your lives you'll do your own thing
but yeah I know in Asia it's a Monday I
saw people respond cuz I asked on
Twitter I said he like are you going to
be there and I saw people especially in
Japan say I have work I have
work that's okay I hope you're able to
watch after work and that you enjoy it
it will be there waiting for you after
your hard day
[Music]
I'm oh
Antarctica Antarctica what are you doing
using the limited Wi-Fi and data that is
there to watch my I'm just kidding it's
probably not it's probably pretty good
there they have research facilities and
everything it's probably not that bad
they probably need
[Music]
anyways anyways
anyways I go do you guys want me to
direct you to the
3di do you need help getting there it's
not for another how many hours oh math
I'm not going to bother right now I'd
say 12 plus oh no it's almost 1 okay so
like 11 plus like 19
[Music]
hours you guys are like the kindergarten
kid who always gets lost so the teacher
has to like put like hold his hand or
something
[Music]
but it's not me that will be holding
your hand it's YouTube the YouTube
direct will hold your hand and take
you all
right thank you all for today I hope you
have
fun time for
bed time for bed time time to not be
able to sleep because you have a 3D live
tomorrow oh the is here okay
all righty I'll see you
guys tomorrow oh oh oh last thing sorry
last thing I'm going to do a member
stream after the 3D live so I will set
up that waiting room once I make the
thumbnail I just realized I don't have
the thumbnail ready once I do that I
think I'll do
that I think I'll have to do that
tomorrow I don't think I can get myself
to do that right no I should no I'll do
it tomorrow I'll do it
tomorrow like eight hours before the
live how about
that or no I should probably alert I'll
do it tonight I should alert members
that it's happening okay okay we got
this figured out all right all
right all right I'll see you tomorrow
goodbye
bye that's not how
[Music]