kick it again
hello hello I know I know it's me again
I'm sorry but wait don't leave just yet
I have important things to show you yes
yes yes I am using this
um 10th day of the Holo Ian Advent
calendar oh my God it's only two weeks
left until Christmas
um for something special that concerns
oh all of the whole live English members
and maybe also the fans of the old love
English members
oh yes yes yes so
could it possibly be hmm
[Music]
you may already know if you're watching
this video late and you you're coming
from Twitter or so but let's just act as
if this is the first time you hear about
it anyway it's
[Music]
kind of Austria recently so I'm gonna go
and get changed really quick before I
make this announcement
you know we don't want this Phoenix to
be frozen to
um
sadness
um so you guys are thinking what could
it be what could it be are you guys
thinking you should be thinking think
think think
have you made up your mind
um
are you ready
to guess
three two one guess
wrong maybe it was right
I'm feeling way Cozier now oh yes
yes announcement is
Hollow
Hollow language
sweaters
hello happy English Christmas 2022 I'm a
Christmas sweater get your hands on new
Christmas merch from Whole Life English
at by Olivia's available from Amazon
that's right yes there's a black version
and there is a gray version of one I'm
wearing right now but I can also wear
the don't look
behind
behind the batter whoa
well let me move myself over here
yes so
um this is actually not the only special
thing that we're doing for Christmas or
holiday season so I want you guys to
stay tuned but a little bit early in
time so you get it for Christmas perhaps
or you can get one of your whole life
friends
um this for Christmas or you can ask
your mommy to get you this for Christmas
and the ugly Christmas sweaters are here
to protect you from the cold cold cold
weather unless you're in Australia or
New Zealand or whatever but then you can
get it now and then wear it in summer I
guess which is winter for you but anyway
all of us drawn by Olive views
on I I think it's not really an ugly
Christmas sweater but that was kind of
the theme you know yeah yeah you see it
cute on the top row we have Memphis on
the bottom row we have
Council race is that yeah that's how you
say it counselverse
cozy 10 out of 10 will wear every day
until Christmas and on Christmas yeah
this is really great because normally
our merchandise
um are like birthday merchandise and
anniversary merchandisers
um as you may know
you know pre-order and then you have to
wait half a year if not longer to get it
but the fact that it's on Amazon makes
it way easier check on Amazon look for a
live production
um it may not be available in every
country but for example for me Austria
uses German uh Amazon so you guys gotta
check check and maybe get a friend for
help if it's really not available but it
should be available in a lot of places
and it will come right away to your
doorsteps to make your holiday season a
little bit Cozier and with that being
said I will show the Japanese version as
well
there you go
yes but yes L with that being said
that's all I have for you today tomorrow
we'll be back to normal Advent calendar
videos I hope you guys have been
enjoying them
with I'm like really excited because
they've been going really well and and I
think it's something really nice to look
forward to every uh every day yeah yeah
yeah but as I said uh this is not the
only thing that we have for you guys for
Christmas season so stay tuned and yeah
happy holidays
is and bye bye
cozy
cozy my cats are gonna love this black
sweater they're gonna put their hairs
all over it you
[Music]