[Music]
n
oh
[Music]
a
n
H is it playing the
[Music]
music HHH there we go something was
missing
no what's the weird noise I can see oh
well okay here is the music
KY hello I've been preparing a lot for
this stream and I may have also spent a
lot of money on it h i wonder how much
it was we can maybe figure out at the
end although no it's uh prices I all
wrote down are all per per liter per
kilo Etc um but I have a bill still no B
GM
are you
sure are you are
you you do oh my [\h__\h] god which
stupid chicken one guide
me you confused the [\h__\h] out of
me okay my God who was that who was it
write it down I need to I want I want on
my desk later the
name ah
okay very confusing it's very low oh
there you go make it a bit louder for
you how about how about
now how about now it shouldn't be too
loud we have to get started because I'm
scared I don't know how long the cam the
the batteries of the
camera work I know I said I wanted to
figure it out for next time but I didn't
find the actual camera charging cable um
so it's still connected by USB which in
app works but who knows for how long so
um there were times where it worked
pretty long and there were times where
it didn't work so long uh but if I think
in theory the stream itself shouldn't
take too
long
um
Ma
let me show you the
[Music]
camera
yay my gloves today I cut them up yes
because I might need to feel some things
maybe and it's it's embarrassing though
cuz I don't do my nails I don't do my
nails fingers are really not pretty um
yeah okay look at it judge it blah blah
blah just
don't I I talked about this with
management because I saw a few
colleagues streaming without gloves at
all and I was like so what's the what's
the current actual rule on this and so
there's no real rule but you know like
as long as there's no like what you know
things that
would that you that don't that shouldn't
be there you know what I mean then then
it's okay but on my fingers it's fine I
have nothing on my
fingers so yeah
um and and generally it's preferred to
wear gloves but if you have to then I
guess do it so my in between solution is
this yeah okay eh no no I don't mean
rings I mean like birth marks or
whatever okay and so so this today's
stream is basically I will be uh do I
want to oh wait I want to turn this
around I will be testing certain
products that I prepared
beforehand um that are like the same
product but then one version of it is
cheap and the other one is an expensive
version
as expensive as I could find it and as
cheap as I could find
[Music]
it um I I went I got help with um like
disguising the thing so I don't
recognize them and with uh packaging
them in weird ways so they're they're
not recognizable anymore I did pretty
much all of the shopping because I only
trust myself but um but uh I don't know
I just needed the control over it but
like then we packaged things differently
first of all what I want to start off
with
is green tea and I'm going to make it um
see so my friend for example did this
and and one is marked with an X and uh I
have in like a
spoilered text form on Discord I have
the information which one is the
expensive one okay so and some of some
of others just have it on the on the
back of the mug by the way I have these
I have the I have washed them for a few
times and I I think I shouldn't have
washed them so so hot because the color
is is uh fading which is so sad but oh
well we'll start with green tea so that
I can drink it um there will
be one green tea that is per 20 bags in
a box almost a yearo and the most
expensive I could find I could have
probably found more expensive ones in an
actual tea shop but I didn't want to go
that far it was annoying uh the other
one is
$439 by the way US dollars is pretty
much roughly the same so so you can just
imagine the USD sign instead of the Euro
H actually expensive though yeah I guess
so but I think it can still get more
expensive so let me pour some water with
my beautiful
retro I just cooked some water let's
make some tea this will be good for my
throat as
well and
then I generally don't take um
don't take the the time it needs
to
um do their thing that
seriously um but while
it's while it's doing its thing we're
going to test other things I
guess my camera is doing weird
things okay there we go so we're going
to set this aside actually I guess cuz
I'm n and you have to I don't know 3
minutes maybe also also it's too cold
too hot anyway I can't drink it after 3
minutes so we're going to set it aside I
guess put that aside what would be smart
to test first um ah I forgot to bring
one thing
ah can you wait for me like for a tiny
tiny amount of
[Music]
time
okay okay okay I got it I got it I got
it I got it I got it I got it I got
it everything okay over
here
let's
Okay I needed some accessories for a
certain test we're going to start
with we're going to start with
honey the reason why is because then I
can afterwards put the put it into the
tea
okay the honey difference is actually
insane it hurt my wallet a bit to buy
this one so the cheap one is per
kilogram the actual thing didn't cost as
much of course but the only real way to
um differentiate the prices properly I
thought is going by kilogram liter price
Etc so the cheap one is this and the
expensive one
is 10 times the price
111 why because one of this is
apparently Manuka honey and I never had
Manuka honey so I don't really know what
it's supposed to taste like the color is
obviously very different
already uh I know I know manuk honey is
expensive I never had it before I don't
know why it's so
expensive but what it
is Mea honey yeah I I don't like eating
honey just like that but I will do it
for this uh
opportunity I
mean first of all the texture is like I
don't know normal it it looks
actually
uh I don't want it on my on my hand but
oh it looks pretty I don't know how to
explain but it looks like there's a lot
of stuff in there also it was sitting on
the spoons for a while and this one is
definitely thicker cuz it just stays on
the spoon I don't know if that speaks
for being
expensive um but okay let's do a little
a little taste test I'm not going to do
the whole spoon
uh oh
oh
wow it's it's kind of grainy oh it's
very sweet
it has a strong smell let me smell it
actually it smells like normal honey to
me like any other honey I mean okay I
know that like there's like more bit
like dark bitter Honeys and then there's
the sweeter Honeys which are uh the
other one should be like a flower
honey I don't know it's very
creamy creamy and grainy sweet strong
wrong
[Music]
flavor thank you
Jo thanks made a m it does taste like
high quality okay you can see I really
only took tiny
nibbles let me try this one oh dear wait
actually that texture is kind of special
[Music]
looking I don't know it's not it's hard
to tell oh maybe now do you see it's
like really um it's really GL it's
another finger oh [\h__\h] okay I'll take it
from my finger um what's glat as smooth
and yeah smooth it's really
smooth it's very yellow let me try the
smell M for the smell I need the whole
thing I guess the texture really looks
very new to
me
oh oh okay the smell is interesting I I
don't know how to describe it though let
me give take a t taste
test
who what is
this it's almost got to
be that Manuka honey I think not because
it tastes like worth the
money but it tastes
different one
more I'm not even sure if this is
[Music]
honey oh wait I said I would put it in
the green tea but actually I have to
test the green tea on its own without
the honey H I think I don't know I
wouldn't say it tastes expensive
it doesn't even quite taste like
honey which is why I think this is the
Manuka honey
so I'll go for that the other one tastes
more familiar cuz it just tastes like
any any uh oopsie why did I do
that any other flower honey you know
what I mean just normal normal honey why
are they together there you go I say
this is the that one this is that
one understand okay what which one is
it
it I was
wrong I
was
[Music]
it
really I
mean I do think this one tasted kind of
better wait has anybody ever had hanuka
honey
[Music]
before the
run the runny honey the runny honey
being cheap makes sense so apparently
it's the other way
around this
[Music]
okay the bright yellow is filled refined
sugar to get the price done
uh I've never had your honey but I can
tell just by the way they look which
one's cheap and which one's expensive oh
just by how it looked on you it was the
more expensive
one I guess not being too runny is a
sign for and not too runny and not too
smooth is a sign for being expensive
[\h__\h] I only F because it was like so
different and special that it's going to
be this
one the bottom one looks way more
natural it this this is worth all that
money let let me try it
[Music]
again it does it does seem like almost
too good to be
cheap
M yeah
okay okay okay I admit the feat I want
to check the bill again later to make
sure and take the check the
container
[Music]
but yeah okay for now for now we admit
the feat or I admit the feat
okay okay
M
next what is
[Music]
this what do you feel think this
is
oh oh interesting already the texture is
very I mean texture but like the the the
finess it's parmesan so the thing with
Parmesan is for me personally I um in my
world parmesan is expensive and um I
don't buy it because it's too expensive
but there I I think for my impression if
you want uh parmesan but don't want to
spend so much money you buy um what's it
called again there's uh the the other
one that's not so
expensive I I call both paresan
though uh P Grana padana and paragano
there's those two wouldn't you agree
with me that Grana padana I mean it's a
great cheese on its own but it's kind of
like the cheap version of a pan to me so
that's what I'm trying to do here
because I couldn't even find a cheap
parmesan there is no cheap parmesan so
uh we are comparing palano against
padana or so yeah you
know basically my logic so one the cheap
one is 1 15 the expensive one is
33 just by looking at it this one has
like it's like way finer than they're
both like shredded I guess I bought
shredded versions of them and this one
came out already with like like little
little
little constellations of cheese which
makes me
think simply that already is a sign for
it being cheaper but who knows yeah
clumps like why is it clumping if it's
expensive I don't know then okay let me
smell this
one
cheese that is cheese let me smell this
oh that's also cheese
[Music]
okay there it's kind of different but I
wouldn't know how to say what's
different okay let me try
um it smells like more familiar I
think let me try
um
a I don't think I ever have like this
kind of cheese on its own I only
sprinkle it over
things it it has
a a faint hint of feet
[Music]
mhm that's all I can say it's kind of FY
mhm this one seems almost milder in
smell
[Music]
oh milder and
taste I don't taste
feet
shouldn't parmesan like the real deal be
more stronger in taste be more aromatic
probably he probably ready okay one
second
e this is definitely weaker in taste
milder milder uh in taste and uh smell
but this one smells more familiar maybe
it's just the smell of feet that is
familiar or tastes more familiar I don't
know I guess
I'll I but I still had my argument with
the
[Music]
clumps shush shush shush and the clump
argument is it
important I wonder by the way have you
noticed this is the first time reveal of
the night version of The Girls Room I
forgot to tell
[Music]
you also it it felt like this one
because they were out like for an hour
like this this one dried up more than
this one
did is that good or bad like generally
it's bad but does that mean it's more
expensive or cheap
[Music]
keep I'll
say I'll
say I don't want to be like influenced
by the chat so I'll
[Music]
say I'll actually say the mind one is
the expensive
one I hope I'm Bri cuz my first thought
was the more stronger one should be the
expensive one but I'm actually going to
say the other way around and keep it
like
this okay that's what you're guessing
too okay for this one I think I have it
under the bowl let's
[Music]
see no this was the expensive one and
okay okay but it makes sense cuz like
for normally you would want more more
value for the money so if you get more
flavor for the money then that that's
worth it then that that that's okay that
makes sense and I guess you could see
the the non clumping as a sign of
cheapness too because it's just that
capable of clumping because they took
all the wait what makes the cheese Clump
maybe uh humidity or whatever I don't
know maybe they drained it all out and
that's why it's also faster to get dry
I'm
coping
Okay
g i once again got it
wrong Mama M okay I am not a cheese
expert for real though like I never
really consumed cheese um unless I
sprinkle a little bit on top of you know
on top of uh pasta now here comes the
tea The Comeback of the
[Music]
tea the color seems to be darker on this
one but again I don't know if that's
supposed to indicate anything we're
going back to the tea so we have I am
I'm zooming for this which is probably a
good
thing where's my tea here we had the
expensive one
at440 and the cheap one at under a Euro
wow so um
um again I I I appreciate you guys
sharing your opinions but I feel like I
shouldn't let myself be SED it should be
my own opinion my own stupid uh prone to
fail opinion let me
smell
oh smells
Japanese actually really gave me this
like Japanese tea smell which I guess
it's just great tea but no for real it
reminded me of
Japan this
one
oh this
one trying so hard to breathe so
[Music]
hard I don't know they smell the same I
guess
I don't know I
don't I don't okay let me drink the the
lighter colored
one my
nose I need to blow out it still seems
very
hot my
aspa is this ready to
drink oh I'm getting a headache I'm
feeling
dizzy wait oh
God I'm
dizzy it's too much too much air
exchange mild
taste tastes like
Japan which is a good thing
it's
[Music]
warming
refreshing
soothing it's
Japan now this one let me drink some
water clear my taste pack
palette here we
go it's not very pleasant it's not very
pleasant the other one is way more
pleasant I don't know how to describe
the reason but it's just it's it's not
as welcoming and it's not as friendly
and it's not as pleasant
[Music]
so I'm going to say she although you
know good taste doesn't always equal the
price but still I got to go with this
this is the only thing I would yeah I
can attach it to you
know the the Japan one shall be the
expensive
one uh okay here we
go ah the one of the x is the expensive
one
a let's go
woohoo I got it I got
it this
really it it's a it's a budget tea like
you know here we have several brands
that show you they're like the budget
brand of the supermarket that they're
selling it at and I can
tell I can
tell so it's a tea but it's not not a
friendly tea it doesn't want you to
really enjoy
it it's just a tea for the sake of being
a tea while this is literally
Japan all right since we tasted the
honey already I can put the honey in my
teeth now
right so wait the the let's put the
expensive one in the expensive
tea and the cheap one
Ew with the fascinating texture goes
into that one I like to always have some
honey in my tea because um it gives it a
little bit more sweetness while also
helping out my throat you
know two birds with one
stone but I wish I would just stop
killing birds with stones like it's so
brutal like why would you do that take
the bags out well
okay okay
freaking freaking tea back seaters man I
don't
know
okay taking it
[Music]
out let's have some tea if you're what
was it if it's spicy sip some tea says
waya from Whole Life Indonesia second
generation it's still stuck on there
because it's is so
rich
wow
M wow that is now Japan plus
Manuka M thank you for the Super Chat
all right let's put the teas aside
what's the tee tell me the tea give me
the
tea um as a as a little side uh
advertisement or like intermission
let me
Flex
[Music]
this you yeah okay most of you don't
know who it is unless you're
Japanese any Japanese person knows who
this is I'm telling you it's
t t
song yeah so a while ago I you know I I
love um like he okay okay start from the
top he used to be in a band Japanese
band he used to be the singer uh called
shaan Q then later on he became like the
producer uh the creator of hello project
a huge Idol uh company which produces a
lot of idol groups the most popular one
back in the day was morning musima they
created my favorite one B cobal smileage
cute buo
Etc um it's also the origin of Suzuki
idy the one that you guys know from the
daddy
ddy he scouted her when she was like I
don't know seven eight something like
that and then joined his
company yeah the cute girl so uh I
actually
uh I forgot why but they knew I was a
fan
and then they asked me to write a
comment about my
favorite uh uh hello project songs and
it made it into the book I haven't found
it
yet but supposedly it made it into the
book and you know here are all like
comments from people and because I did
that I got a a signed copy my first ever
signature and these are all
SM love them these are all like from
like the songs that he wrote like all of
this are songs you wrote all of this all
of
this yeah
wow it's it's
incredible he he wrote so many songs in
his
lifetime he can't sing anymore though
because um he has has had had has had
has uh cancer so he he lost his voice
which is incredibly sad but if you look
at the book you know how much he's done
throughout his whole life it's
incredible
had Aura gets me she gets
me okay next up you may have been
wondering what this
[Music]
is um
the this is a cut up mtart ball m b I
cut off Mort
balls yes I did um it's a typical
Austrian
souvenir
uh cuz mte was B born and raised in
Austria and uh at some point I don't
know when they made a little chocolate
ball that is supposed to represent in I
don't know how but
um there's actually like several
companies who create these there's some
cheaper ones there's some better ones
more expensive ones there's some that
they consider to be the real
one I would say though that there's at
least like two companies that are like
the favorite the legit ones that
austrians know this this if you want to
get mad balls get these ones Mo kouan by
the way um but like foreigners tourists
would probably just buy whatever they
see the cheap ones are actually packaged
kind of like like in an obvious way like
hey these are mot balls so buy us in
like a big bag so you get more for your
money um and you spend less money so I
feel like the cheaper ones are more
often purchased
um what are they though they are usually
like you can already see some variation
I generally don't eat them because I
hate them but I know generally it's like
a I think a dark chocolate layer inside
there's usually some nut cream uh and
the most important thing is the maripan
I can see it the green thing in the
middle greenish thing is the
maripan um which in Austrian
Confections they and cakes and so on is
quite popular to be used I see some here
as well at the bottom here there's also
maripan yeah I I I hate Maran this is
why I don't like M
balls yeah um so the
prices are the expensive one per
kilogram
$34.90 and the cheap one still expensive
because more balls are just expensive
per
kilogram there might be even cheaper
ones and there might be even more
expensive ones but yeah
[Music]
um by looking at it you would probably
assume and I would assume that this is
the expensive one just because it has
more it's melting on me just because it
has more like variations more
layers wo
it used to be a full Ball by the way we
cut it in
[Music]
half I can't really get anything from
that but yeah this one
is maybe you know simple is best who
knows it h it has
like some marabon at the bottom some
darker something in the middle and
around that I don't know something
creamy just looks cheaper already I
guess but no not necessarily right let's
try this
one oh actually no the more I look at it
no the whole thing is maripan I think
the more I look at
it oh yeah it smells like a lot of
maripan okay here we go
[Music]
M oh oh there is another layer of
something there do you see
it oh [\h__\h] in
Focus
yeah oh actually it's pretty good maybe
maybe over the years I changed my mind
on
March it's not my favorite thing but H
definitely the
ratio of chocolate to
maripom is very
unbalanced lots of lots of Maron in
there
M oh my mom just wrote to me cuz she
knows I don't like
maripan she's like oh poor
girl
well let's taste a few bit more of the
chocolate if I can get something out of
[Music]
that
okay okay let me drink some water I
don't know what to say I can't tell cuz
I never eat them I buy them as souvenirs
all the time and give them to girls in
Japan and
[Music]
ID but I figured if I like them then if
I don't like them then chances are high
that they don't like them so nowadays I
mostly give them sacer
cakes let's try this one all right it's
melting on me wow
uh
oh
wow
oh wow this must be the expensive
one there's so many layers of
flavors so many interesting tastes to
experience
[Music]
m
I think they yeah the noua is really
strong
too the maripan is not
overwhelming more flavors doesn't mean
better for me it currently does cuz it's
more interesting more
more do I like it more than the first
[Music]
one about the
same but it's just it's just more
interesting it's
it's it's hard to say but I could see
how just as I said in the beginning how
Simplicity may not mean that it's the
cheap one because sometimes keeping it
simple is just also a sign of
Elegance you know what I
[Music]
mean
but also the layering in this one looked
so clean and pretty that it and and it
definitely also means more
ingredients so for that I must give the
expensive ones are these and the cheap
on are
these do you understand my reasoning I
could see both being
expensive but I I'll go with the
reasoning about you know just different
layers being pretty and it just looks
visually appealing when you cut it up
when you bite into it and stuff like
that okay mozard balls I think it's
under the
yeah this one was the cheap
one oh it's hard to
tell but okay then my other reasoning
makes more sense too just it's elegant
when there's not too much you
know ah [\h__\h] M
balls God damn it all right I'm losing
[Music]
this ah the the thing is by the way one
reason why it was cut
up these balls um they're uh the
expensive one isn't even a proper ball
the bottom is actually kind of flat um
so we had to cut it a little bit my
friend cut it so when I wasn't looking
um so that I wouldn't tell and it worked
it seemingly worked because I didn't
really you know notice
anymore um she doesn't have expensive
taste
well
well yeah I guess I
don't it look great even then even when
we say this is cheap it's still
expensive right like you guys would
still agree it's still like expensive as
a product on its own
[Music]
yeah okay
um hm
[Music]
M I have a few more products uh oh okay
okay this one's
[Music]
interesting can you tell
difference it's
water it is sparkling water I originally
I was thinking of buying um the most
expensive Still Water I could find and
then compare it to tap water but I
couldn't even find any thing remotely
expensive in terms of Still
Water so um I found within the Sparkling
Waters I found some more expensive
ones um so the cheap
one which came in a huge bottle uh in a
1 lit or 1.5 L bottle then usually in in
big versions they're also cheaper right
um is 0.19 versus the
expensive
5.84 water don't know which one is which
but um one big reason why this is
expensive I can already
tell uh you guys but I still think even
without it would be probably up there
cuz it's just uh conceited water
is because it's the boss water that
comes in a glass bottle right which is
like already like so luxurious and like
thinking so highly of itself so um
hopefully I'm hoping that to me the
cheap water tastes
better just for the sake of dissing
boss but I do want the container I will
use it who buys boss if not for the
bottle that you get right yeah so uh the
ones in a Pikachu look in a Pikachu
cup Pikachu which is why it's yellow
inside and one is in a um ater
Risa
two buug there you go all right they're
both sparkling and we didn't put that
much in there
because does it smell the same cuz I
don't even like sparkling water but at
this point it might have lost its
sparkliness because uh it's in the open
for 1
hour okay um also there's a cat hair in
this one I
think yeah I can only see the shadow of
[Music]
it oh I think I got it yeah okay so
let me drink let me take a big
sip
oh I like it it has a some kind of
sweetness to it and there it's still
sparkling I don't know if this is how
how much sparkly it should
be um but it's like a a tingling
sparkliness
H
okay
M okay this one is not really sweet
tasting and the the tinglin of the
sparkliness is a little bit like already
on the painful side like nightmare side
I remember like having a nightmare when
I was a young child uh Babble bubble
child no not Babble Babble but young
child uh where I had really high fever
like seriously concerningly high and I
uh when I was sleeping I felt like uh
you know when you have like um aluminum
foil
ball uh and then you roll it on your
skin that's how this feels and that's
how my dreams were feeling
like it it's like so long ago but that
stayed in my brain so strongly because
of that feeling of the aluminum
foil yeah so this reminds me of my
nightmares and this
doesn't so but the fact that this
probably over this one hour kept More
sparkliness Than This One did unless it
already came unless one of them already
came with less strong
sparkliness um then that's another story
but let's assume they're pretty much
both very sparkly and this this one lost
more and this one had did
M I wouldn't mind calling the Voss water
uh nightmare
water
so wait let me take another
[Music]
sit
uhhuh wait now suddenly this is more
tingling I think it's better
though
it The Taste is Al don't
[Music]
know it's definitely different but this
this tastes more like how Austrian
sparkling water would taste like cuz I
feel like the boss water is not from
Austria right um this tastes more
typically Austrian sparkling
water it's so so weird like unexplicable
but we need to know which one's wobbler
good good
good this one is that good or bad that's
actually bad
right wobbliness is bad in my on in my
books
which one's better I can't really say
they're both like just
water I would really say that any of
them are like more expensive tasting
this is a little bit more like sweet
though
and uh this is more
boring um but I wouldn't say that one of
them tastes
luxurious I'm going to say
nightmare water and the cheap one be cuz
I also felt like it tastes more like
Austrian
water okay did did we have it underneath
yeah oh I'm right I'm right I'm right
yeah I was right I was
right let's
go
[Music]
nightmare water versus Austrian water I
I think if my austan friends compare
austan water with other sparkling water
I feel like Dave would understand there
there's this like Austrian sparkling
water
[Music]
taste where is boss
from can someone
Google
I don't want to this and if it's from um
no way no no way I'm sorry I love
Norway such a refined palette oh thank
you so
much but um as I said I feel like most
of the price comes from the glass
bottle um but as I said just the fact
that you're making your sparkling water
with a glass bottle is like so like oh
my God who do you think you are like
chill out come
on even without it would definitely be
more expensive cuz this is also um a
budget a cheap um brand of water but I
like it I like
it sorry no
way oh maybe they agree who knows
okay this is fun are you guys enjoying
this I hope my camera doesn't die cuz
this is a lot of
fun
[Music]
um um okay
okay which
one which one should I do
next
um let's go with
this don't worry I will not not drink it
this is olive
oil olive oil
this and this
is
shocking
shocking absolutely insane price olive
oil generally tends to be expensive
right the cheap one is per ler 9 32 uh
sense but by the way in case any anyone
just came in and didn't hear my
explanation in the beginning Euros are
like you can pretty much just exchange
the Euro sign with a US dollar sign it's
like roughly the same um this is like
the cheap one that I could
find
mhm but the expensive one I found a lot
of expensive ones but the there was one
that absolutely took the
[Music]
top
yeah
yeah I I felt bad buying it but it came
in like a smaller container than the
others and um afterwards I noticed
something written on the bottle first of
all the bottle looked very sleek and
fancy doesn't look like olive oil but
but one thing that confused me and made
me think maybe this is why it's so
expensive it did say I only noticed this
afterwards after buying it but it did
say
all uh revenue from the olive oil uh
sales goes to
charity child
charity and I don't know if I'm reading
it correctly but it says
[Music]
all maybe that's why they raked up the
price so high but it also comes with a
really like nice bottle and everything
like they must cover at least the
production cost and all that I don't
know how much really goes to charity but
there's like this whole product line
that goes to charity and it has like a
little like seal and everything probably
profit you know Pro it must be it must
be but for this this as I'm not going to
drink it like this I brought some bread
some white
bread I couldn't find a
baguette but a seml an
Austrian
beautiful seml will be just fine this is
what you call a seml and the actually in
fact in Germany you don't really find
this this shape is typically Austrian
semmer
and yeah it's a Kaa Sumer I love my
suers inside there are white fluffy
[Music]
bread oh it still has a a great crunch
to it look normally I would cut it in
the middle and put some like condiments
and and cold cuts in there yeah yeah
yeah of course Germany has a too but
this is our bread okay
Ka this this this pattern is ours
okay yeah we have it too yeah okay chill
chill chill ch ch I said I said you
don't find it that much like you have it
sure but you know it's our thing so I
shall taste test it with
[Music]
bread okay M just by the color I think
this one's a bit more yellow you guys
might see it also as brighter because
the light is kind of more on that
one um maybe I should smell it
first
w
wo
wo decently wo but I think I think this
one was more
wo
oh I want to drink
it
okay how much should I dunk it in like
it's dripping
already it's good
[Music]
right
wow it's so good it's so good
oh
okay all right oh my God I never like I
know people genuinely just eat bread and
oil like this I I don't do it and I
think I did it once in an airplane cuz
all they gave me was oil and
bread but yeah maybe I should do it more
often holy [\h__\h] with a good quality
olive oil d
okay here we
go
I I think this one's a bit more oh quite
quite a bit more
bitter oh oh yeah oh oh yeah oh yeah
definit oh definitely
bitter which is a sign of bitter
oil not of cheap oil
but wait let me try one
[Music]
more wow is this
healthy bitter is not good right not
necessarily unless you really want bit
of oil I don't know
why oh why it's kind of buttery
wo this is special holy [\h__\h] okay I'm
glad I bought it actually now was
regretting it like okay I'll do it for
the stream but
[Music]
M
wow that's fascinating that's actually
fascinating I didn't think I would taste
much of a difference but actually I
guess I should have expected it because
people do say that you guys even said oh
olive oil expensive ol olive oil is
worth it I will keep it the way it is
right
now
go this one's bitter the r side is
bitter this one just the smell already
threw me
away threw me
away is that English is that what you
would
say um okay I think it's under the let
me
[Music]
check
yeah ah that was I not okay wait I would
say maybe not not worth the money but
since they're also donating to charity
then I can't say it's worth the money by
the way the packaging is really
interesting I don't have it with me
right now I'm too lazy to get it so um
wow I will uh either pour the rest back
or eat the rest with um the bread I
guess
sheesh that's amazing that's
amazing
M refined your
stab just stab you
[Laughter]
stab yeah nicer bottle like not even it
wasn't even glass bottle it's um it
almost looks like a spray can but it
didn't have a spray o uh top
thingy okay uh foodwise I think we're
done with the
food there's something that I have that
I'm not sure how to test it
um I have an
[Music]
idea what is the W
doing what is the W doing I'm trying to
make this
dirty
um if I smash it but I want to melt
it but it's not doing what I wanted to
do
H
well dishwashing
soap no not quiet not
quiet oh oh oh this one's maybe
better
this will
do
probably maybe I don't know I really
don't know how to test this I don't know
what I was
thinking so um the next
thing
ooh how do you F this
is I'm going to put it here I know it's
very very shiny
uh don't worry I won't get my face too
close it's a
toothpaste
toothpaste so I'm not sure how to test
this
but um we're going to don't worry we're
going to switch away from the spoons in
a
moment cuz I have like
these these toothbrushes that are
bamboo
toothbrushes
biodegradable I had like a whole package
of them I don't know why and I never use
them cuz I have my electronic one um but
this is the perfect way of using them
great presentation one thing that you
can probably see is this ones I mean
okay they've been out for an hour but
this one's so much smoother and shiny
and liquidy while this looks almost like
like a dried up but if I touch it oh my
God I love the
texture it's like it's cute um but that
might be because it's drying up I I I
wouldn't say that it was like this from
the GetGo let me put this
whoop let me put this up here
t
uh yeah that's it looks smooth as
[\h__\h] oh let me let me smell it
oh it smells very freshening and like it
will make your teeth
clean like it should and
then
okay it's nice scoop this one oh God oh
God oh God it's falling
over
okay interesting I feel I feel like this
one's kind of like
basic
smell but this one's like a little bit
more like it almost smells tasty like it
would be tasty should I put it in my
mouth but like it's not like I can show
you the
result I I'll taste a little bit though
what do I do then what what do I spit it
out like what do I do ew I I don't I
don't know if I want to taste it I guess
I'll spit it
[Music]
out
tingly I don't know what to say about
[Music]
this mhm okay
um how do I get rid of this taste in my
mouth now cuz like too baced
taste it it just stays in your mouth
full a while it's hard to get rid of it
let me take some of the bread and the
oil but before let me gargo well not
gargo but I didn't put that much in
but drink some water and then more of
this
okay it's it's coming back to me
no okay wait let's let's taste Let's
test this
out wait we need some we need a little
bit of water I
[Music]
guess we're
brushing uh
[Music]
uh it's barely getting the dirt off
here
what M use the sparkling
water
ew it's it's I don't [\h__\h] know I
don't [\h__\h] know how to tudge
this
um I think I I think this is the
expensive one you don't even know the
prices yet by the way
right I'm just going to
say um so the expensive one there's Al a
huge price difference here actually
expensive one is almost 10 cheap one is
like one and a half year almost yeah um
I think just by the by the texture it's
very
different like this
looks like I don't know this just looks
special that's why I think it's the
expensive
one e meow I didn't hear meow that's
just me probably I didn't hear one if I
didn't hear one then you shouldn't be
hearing
one it's a it's one I'll tell you one of
them is an
elx H
elmex elx I think that's what it was
called like a really good one and the
other one uh was uh a cheap as [\h__\h] uh
other one I forgot the
[Music]
names yeah and then it was elx yeah now
it's to me it sounds now like a movie
theater uh a version of watching the
movie
um I'm just going to say even though I
didn't taste test the other one I'm just
going to say this is the cheap one and
the other one uh this one's the
expensive one this one's a cheap
one how do I find out
[\h__\h] I took it off the spoons do you
guys remember on which
spoon
the um the this one
was you guys remember was it the one
with the tape or the one without the
[Music]
tape
uh there's no X it's just uh one with
tape and one without
tape I think it was the one with the
nice texture being on the tape the
spoons oh yeah wait oh yeah yeah yeah I
think uh this one was the non nice one
and this one that went off completely as
a whole is the probably the the nice
one okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
I will I'm I'm going to bring the
toothpaste over cuz I don't [\h__\h]
believe
it I don't believe
it no no no no no no no no no don't
monkey monkey no no no no bunkers
[Music]
[\h__\h]
okay
so here we
go in case you're interested this was
the olive oil have you ever seen olive
oil sold like that I
haven't
Oh see it says child
foundation and what it says
here no one's entire profits are donated
to children in need your purchase gives
them access to Education and
Training
wow wow bioorganic origin Greece classic
early
Harvest it's a beauty product it's legit
profit yeah well to be expected it's
fancy fancy as [\h__\h] I don't think they
have it overseas the
brand but okay uh let me check
my my my
purchases okay
so this is the cheap one this is the
expensive one I said I think the smooth
thick one is the expensive one
[Music]
let's
see okay I think it depends on how they
dry cuz right now they look pretty
similar but I think this is the one that
turned out smooth it just really dried
out after an
hour it does look more more
like the one that became pretty I think
okay you can't really tell we'll have to
wait for it maybe it will dry out nicer
later because
[Music]
uh we we'll we'll see we'll see we'll
wait for this one to show its results
later on cuz I'm confused now in the
meantime our next test we're going into
Beauty products I have uh two two beauty
products T these were originally in
other
containers actually one of them um I
didn't want to buy expensive perfumes
because uh they are [\h__\h]
expensive and so I what the the other I
bought a different beauty product and
then I got a te I got a tester from a
Chanel uh perfume and I was like oh this
is perfect I can use this so I bought a
cheap perfume um and I filled them both
into like this is not the these are I
don't know which one is which but it's
not the original tester but I had two
other testers from something else and we
filled them into these testers tester
containers one is cheap as [\h__\h] one is
not
um let's
see
[Music]
cheap one
is uh
943 per 100
milliliters you can go even cheaper but
this was like pretty cheap the expensive
one is 167 you can go even more
expensive too uh you can definitely go
more expensive but this is a nice price
difference isn't it I have no no idea
which one is
which so we're just going to judge by
the smell but the scent if it's if it
smells
luxurious okay there I'm going to start
with this one
um okay I'll put it on my I'll put it on
my glove
here wow
[Music]
oh more I need more I think I need
more I really don't really use perfumes
if anything I use like body sprays or
so so it's hard to
explain it doesn't have a very mature
and
like
um it's not it has a young scent if
anything and I don't know let let me try
the other
one
[Music]
mhm
I smell the
alcohol this this one's
[Music]
different it's weak it's very weak in in
in
Scent it almost smells like catus
wouldn't that be so funny if this is the
Chanel
one
okay my left arm smells more like a
lady and my right arm smells confused
like I may have got I may have hugged
smoothie right after her toilet Break
um it's Saker it's it's more like
honestly both could be expensive both
could be
cheap but the the right one is already
fading the the right one is like this
one right now my right arm yeah so I'll
say expensive
here
cheap here right yeah that was that was
this this was the first
one this is what I'm going
to this is what I'm going to
do okay oh my
Sony right
arm's I will forever lose my Chanel
perms okay let's [\h__\h] go uh oh yeah I
I the way of finding this out is by
unpacking it because I do remember the
color of the
perfume okay I'll will first blindly
blindly unpack
it um if it's if it's
expensive uh oh D this is really well
packaged uh if it's expensive
then the color should be green greenish
if it's the Chanel one I don't want to
look I know want to look I know want to
look it this should be green in my
opinion wait I can't find all the
openings uh well let's just open
here oh it's green it's hard to tell cuz
when I do it like this you don't see it
but when I do it like this and I look
underneath it's green it's green it's
it's green it's green the catf face is
the
cheap wait let me let me confirm by by I
know I might want to make sure it's not
like I mixed it up is this the strong
one
[Music]
right yeah it's it's nice it's quite
nice it's now it gave me a hint of
citrus and this one was the was the
weird one
right yeah yeah yeah yeah this is weird
this this also immediately gives you in
the first second cuz I'm very sensitive
to alcohol this in the first moment gave
me like immediately like an alcohol
punch in my
face a really slight one a slight punch
a a a
touch soel perss
saved okay okay okay okay interesting
not this is I didn't buy a full perfume
so all is good I didn't spend a lot of
money on this this is a free tester that
came with it but what did it come with
it did come with an actual Chanel
product I don't even want to look too
much at it I feel like I should be blind
testing this
[Music]
um um um uh cuz I have looked at the
cheap
one uh a little bit um I don't want to
be
too I don't want to look too too much at
it wait where are
the here uh the cheap one per piece 2
2.75 from Essence a really cheap makeup
brand the expensive
one it hurts me to buy this I usually
buy pretty cheap makeup or like for my
Foundation at least I have like a
mid-range
Foundation this is I've never spent so
much money on one shitty makeup item and
it's a [\h__\h] lipstick like I I don't
think this is reasonable at all okay it
hurts me it it hurt me so much buying
it but Chanel lipsticks are said to be
good so hopefully I'll get my money's
worth why is it in tful so that I don't
see the packaging duh cuz the packaging
would make it very obvious okay um I
think we're going to do color test test
and like see how well it stays as well I
I could do it on my fingers so I could
try a little bit n this is easier to see
I'll do it here
okay okay number one there I tried to
get his clothes I asked a somebody who
worked there I asked them to give me uh
one of the Chanel lipsticks that uh are
is the closest In Color to like the
cheaper
one do swatches I never do swatches I'm
not a beauty YouTuber but
so these are the closest I could I could
get one is definitely more orange but I
don't even remember but just by the
shape I don't I don't want to think
about it okay so let's try it out oh do
you see
this oh it's so
soft it does it
smell a little bit
[Music]
maybe oh no not quite there not quite
there camera there we
go wow
wow I don't know what to say it doesn't
look like 50 bucks let me smudge
it very
smudgeable very
smudgeable I don't know if that's
good shouldn't be so
smudgeable I think for me personally I
would like it to
be that's not quite sure like at least
in the beginning when you app apply it
then maybe it's okay to be smudgeable
but then it soon should become UNS
smudgeable doeses that look cheap to you
guys
oh
oh sorry you weren't looking
but the application
[Music]
it feels um it feels like this one is
way harder like the whatever like what
the I don't know the the the texture I
don't [\h__\h] know it's it's hard it's
more stiff and this one's smoother more
gentle
and the color like this one's a bit more
matte and the other one's a bit more
shiny but I mean there are matte
lipsticks and there shiny lipsticks but
let's try to smudge it oh it's way more
difficult to smudge it but I would
actually say that makes it a bit cheap
in this case cuz it feels cheap it feels
a bit
cheap it in this
case this is way more like Smooth than
buttery these are beautiful colors
though both are
beautiful I like orange tones though
this has a orange
hint
M it well when you smudge it it it kind
of gives you the same like amount of
color still and both are very high
pigmented I would
say I would
say I would say that the the the one
that was smoother is the expensive one
can I smell wait did I smell
both
[Music]
okay this this one uh the the one that
was less orange and
harder
it it
smells it
smells like children's makeup or like
these pens that are
scented
um which is a nice a a cute tropical
cute Berry smell but it's a sign of
cheapness like it's children's makeup
for sure so yeah I would say this and
this and they for yeah it it it aligns
with everything else I
said
so beautiful hands no my hands are like
[\h__\h] like ew don't
even really will I be right or will I be
wrong we will tell by the
[Music]
packaging I want to look I don't want to
look I don't want to look I
[Music]
want I think I'm right oh yeah that's
Chanel
baby that is [\h__\h]
Chanel that is so
Chanel because I know that the other
pack packaging was uh
um uh silver yeah with a shitty pink
plastic leg okay it's
more more fancy this was uh Essence in
case you're curious girls in the house
uh can we see
[Music]
it
[\h__\h] so bad at this that Hydra matte uh
407 coral Coral coral Coral competence I
have to find the Caps later and then
this one is freaking Chanel it doesn't
say which one on on this packaging but
probably on the cap Chanel my first
Chanel
lipstick I will never make such a pro
just
again but for now it's nice to have I
think I I try to not look too much at it
because I thought it was kind of a
giveaway but I did think that even the
shape um wait okay this one's kind of
messed up already because of the
aluminum foil but I think even the shape
looks cheap maybe you guys if you don't
have experience with this but I think
the shape looks
cheap of the of the top
um it looks nice and clean but it looks
cheap and the the shape of the
application is a teardrop and I I I just
think that that's like just generally
just too sharp yeah and and this makes
more sense to apply to your lips I don't
know I'm trying to I'm trying to make
sense of
this but nice nice I got it right okay
it started really badly today I have one
last piece I
unless I forgot something but I have one
more uh yeah let me let me let me
uh I should have probably done this
before the lipsticks cuz now my hands
are
dirty um actually no they're here I can
just pull them over
probably such a mess
again I
sure um okay my last
experiment are bed
sheets I have made a mistake when
purchasing them these ones I purchased
over Amazon they're both like pretty
much 100% cotton I think the the the
cheap one probably has like a 5%
non-cotton part of it um but it's mostly
cotton and
I um the problem is the cheap one was
about  15 I don't I didn't check the
Bill anymore but it was something like
that uh it's a it's for a big bed that's
why I was thinking I might want to use
it myself but that's why they start
pretty expensive already uh
180 x 200 bed so big big double
bed and I'm not going to lie in it no
I'm going to touch it the expensive one
is
50o and the problem is I accidentally
bought two
I I wouldn't have minded buying two of
the cheaper one but I actually bought
two of the expensive
one stupid so I spent 100 bucks on the
bed
sheet made it even more expensive I
didn't unpack the second one so I'm
hoping to send back at least the second
one yeah
um trying to make a bit more space for
myself also get rid of
[Music]
this wa my my
headphones okay okay
okay okay so
[Music]
uh sheet number
one
sheet number
[Music]
two all
right they look the same
mostly I can already tell that this
one is less
wrinkled um more like IR
already um let's see this one is just
wait let me get one layer this is all
double the lipstick it's okay this I'm
not returning these ones don't
worry okay
M this one's softer but only probably
because it's
um thinner it's also like less uh this
one's more SE through can you see the
quality already looks better on this one
doesn't
it
let's look at the the seams
here the seams look cleaner and higher
quality on this one yeah this is like
this is the
50 I don't even have to think too much
about it I think the quality is pretty
visible but both is supposedly like
pretty much the cheaper one is I think
like maybe 5% less cotton
how about the
stretchiness oh my God the fabric is
just so much more pretty oh my
God I can't
even I can't
even both will be messed up by my cats
scratched up and all that so I don't
know if it's worth buying an expensive
one in my household but yeah this one's
way smoother okay we'll keep it like
this this is pretty
OB that's pretty obvious if you don't
have cats if you don't have anything
that can mess up the sheet
then you should probably you could
invest in an expensive one but if you
have animals and stuff then I would just
keep on buying cheap ones like I I don't
want to spend too much on bed
sheets yeah so so let's see uh for the
bed sheets the one of the tape is okay
no there we
go I just checked the notes from My
Friends the one where the tape is on is
the expensive one and there it is
yay buer is about to destroy this yay
she's going to rip out the FR unless
maybe maybe the Frets are more resilient
in this
one yay
y
woohoo nice so what's the end result did
did I get a tie actually in the
end that would be funny I got more
correct than wrong probably a really
close call though I won oh 6 to three oh
it started so bad by the way look at my
cute cup my cute water
cup it's the cutest [\h__\h] ever
I showed this off
before I bought it
inima is not the only place where you
can buy them though this is the cutest
[\h__\h]
ever so cute like if you turn it around
you see them oh look at the
paws ah the toothpaste ah wait we're not
done we're not
done cuz we didn't like really did you
decide if my thing was correct do you
guys
[Music]
remember it doesn't quite look like the
that one
yet
but this was the the one that I think is
expensive but color-wise color-wise it's
closer to this one I think this one's
more like bluish you know what I
mean so and I said that this would be
the cheap one and this the expensive one
right so I think I was right the the
notes from my friend just confused me I
think or the all the spoons I got the
spoons mixed up maybe well got to watch
the VA actually and see if the one with
the tape was actually the one with the
elmex
taste test no [\h__\h] that I tasted one did
I taste the expensive one or the cheap
one I don't even remember that
anymore yay 7 to free
woo by the way do you want to see my
terrible Nails I always get like my
nails like especially the Thum
nails they are like cut on the side you
want to see I I cut it I cut the part
where it's like going in inside because
I always get like uh caught in like
friends in my hair but this just
happened this just happened can you
see I had to cut it all off so it's
really short cuz I always I always I
always get these like rips rip rip and
tear it's hard to see
Hello water fum
whatever I always have that at least on
one finger at a
time my other I just cut my nails but
these are relatively long but they're no
no special shape
either cuz I just I just don't care
about my nails I wanted to get my nails
done with
Goa when we were in Jaan but we didn't
get to do
it oh maybe next time me and
if we go to Japan again we got to we got
to we got to get our nails done but it's
just such an annoying thing because like
the the there's such cute nails that you
can get but then it's usually like the
the acrylic nails and then well you have
to go there again for them to take it
off you can't just you can't really just
you don't get get rid of it yourself but
anyway did you like the stream idea I I
think it worked great it was um it was
really fun for
me to uh do this and and I I like these
creative ideas and I like anything that
I can do with my hand cam I need more
things to do with my hand
cam 10 out of 10 10 out of 10 10 out of
woo thank you yeah yeah cleaning up is
going to be a little bit BL but I it's
not going to be too
bad thank you there were a lot of
interesting Revelations like the tea I
didn't think the tea would be that
different I thought that would be pretty
similar but it was surprisingly
different and
the the oil was insane
actually are you an olive oil convert
now I would definitely like um be happy
about getting served oil with
bread in like a restaurant or
[Music]
so that was really
interesting new stream snack bed with
oil
yeah
[Music]
the tea doesn't even look like yeah it
was so dark wasn't it that's that's
true yeah it was like green tea is
supposed to be more transparent and and
light color that's
true unbelievably believable I should do
that again too I was planning on it but
then time time just slips out of my
hands hey the cam everybody can we get
an Applause for the camera for not dying
on me today
yay thank you
camera thank you I charged it fully
before the stream fun for the stream
thank you than love love I
uh I I did
spend a little bit of money money I I I
will try my best to get my money's worth
out of this
lipstick it's quite nice I
[Music]
guess I'll sendas SP if you flip us
[Applause]
up [\h__\h] you I don't like doing that
[Music]
oh
I'm look I'm flipping myself off maybe I
am maybe I
am
nah I feel like uh middle finger
flipping someone off is just so stupid
and childish and like man it's just a
hand like are you really trying to
insult me with a hand I mean I guess if
someone flips me off I would feel
insulted but like is that really
something that we should feel insulted
by it's just a hand and and stupid as
childish
H I haven't I haven't shown someone the
middle finger since like maybe
Junior High School like first or second
grade cuz it just seems so immature to
me cuz like even if I do it at someone
that that I'm angry at like it's not
going to it's not going to change
anything it's not going to like get me
any like like you know it's not going to
make anything
better it's all about the message yeah
you want to let it out in some way but
like it it only makes if anything if
they see it it only makes things worse
if they don't see it it doesn't get me
anywhere
so
[Music]
like you use it when someone honks it
you oh yeah well I guess in a car you
don't really have much else to like do
because they won't hear you if you say
something so you got to show
something okay yeah for car situations
it's probably
different okay okay okay okay guys uh
while I'm still here I'm going to read
some super chats I guess might as well
let me turn off the
[Music]
camera
if you're going to go and sleep or
whatever or do something else thank you
for
watching and uh mic switch
why what did it switch
to that was surreal with the
switch
is this
my oh
no
[Music]
ah no it should be the good
one is it was it using the camera mic
until
[Music]
now
uh why did you not tell me that what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] you thought it was
intentional
you m m
Mia I wonder what it sounded like did I
sound very
[Music]
different the change sounded
professional well okay that changed
it it sounded very bright sounded fine
just different sound was okay okay well
it is a it is a good camera so I would
hope the microphone isn't too
[Music]
bad that's why it was a little bit
echoey to you
[Music]
guys a that's also why you heard a meow
and I didn't cuz I had my headphones on
that were probably blocking a little bit
of the sound that was coming from
outside cuz I I still heard myself the
whole time with the proper microphone in
my
ears I had the feedback from my proper
intended
microphone wow it would you guys say
this lowered the quality of the
stream was it uncomfortable to listen
[Music]
to
No
okay
okay all right then do you want to look
at the the
room my
the the dark
room here let me also show you uh
without Wawa this is the dark
[Music]
version yeah
nighttime the difference is quite
nice and like little things like the
stars are on and also the toast light is
turned on in the background of the where
the bed is the aquarium with froggy waa
is actually
um uh more lit up
now oopsie
yeah oh yeah why is frogging while one
up moving is she supposed to be moving I
think she's supposed to be moving or is
she no in in here she never moves does
she and did you notice by the way that
the picture is like mirrored in the
mirror the chicken picture here over
there wow pretty
cool pants on bed what's on legs don't
question
it thank you well thank you for the for
the red super chat and thank you for
renewing your membership
yay okay let me bring chat
back taada
all right I think I only have to read
the ones from today do
[Music]
I also do you like the pose from the
thumbnail I gave chy a reference of what
I
wanted and he created it perfectly
look with a big butt over there
I'm so glad um cuz I I would never be
able to create this on my own thank God
thank you chy for helping this is the
full pose in case you want it
guys take
it and the money the money wasn't like I
I was going to put like normal money on
my hands but chy put like some pickle
pickles pickles on my
hand
funny okay so what was the answer about
the super
chats was it only the ones from
[Music]
today I didn't know you were testing
cake on the
stream oh ff16 also
okay by the way tomorrow we're playing
GTA again it's been a little while since
the last GTA
stream uh we're playing Gay Tony
[Music]
again wonder how far will get and only
the last one right um I think the last
FF
[Music]
stream
okay uh
[Music]
thumnail let me put a little text I
guess
reading super
chats
now
okay now everybody knows what's up then
we can start C Dan py Dan Jacob 47 Dan
studio thanks for the
pinky FP yes I don't hate chicken thank
you is this a reference to what n so
sad that was such a huge shock to me
man you don't even understand ah there
she
is it's
like how could
you like her argument was well that's
okay cuz you're not a chicken but no I I
know that I'm very aware of that I
wasn't like in pain because I thought it
was against me but chickens are like
defining my whole life right now you
guys are like a huge part of my life and
if narissa doesn't like you then I don't
know how
to go on with my life with
her but she does mean that she doesn't
like eating chicken right but she likes
she probably likes chickens themselves
eles life in its life form I
think
so
yeah that would be cannibalism well
cannibalism pretty normal in
[Music]
kfp it's probably fine I guess it's fine
it's
fine
thank you Studio Rob thank you soon alen
thank you for the red super chat kiaa it
was my birthday last week and also three
year anniversary of the rabbit hole Yeah
long time and three years of kfp this
week it's honestly feels surreal and on
how long it's been just wanted to send
you all the love in the world and thank
you for being you
Alita you've been around for so long too
I know I know thank you so much and
happy belated
birthday yay oh there you are in your
shining new armor
now how was your birthday did you have a
good time did you feel
celebrated oh that's a nice cake emoji
with candles
what what
happy birthday it was really good and
relaxing oh did you do something
relaxing rather than something exciting
like partying maybe you went to treat
yourself treat yourself that's how I
want to like I want to and was you
spending a lot of my birthdays reading a
book in front of a fireplace
[Music]
fireplace at this time of the
year you already have a the fireplace
turned
on is it already that cold where you
are I mean it's getting cold over here
too
but yeah already right I watched this
video that reminds me I watched this
video um where some guy I think in New
York you guys maybe saw it too some guy
in New York like looks across um the
street and sees a building of window
like no curtains and sees a fire in the
window calls the um the firefighters
they go there with like free fire trucks
through New York
going really loudly and then they go
there and it turns out she just had that
like fire place chill relaxing sounds
music video not music video video uh
running on her big TV smart
TV and from the distance where the guy
was at it really looked like a fire like
a pretty decent fire so he was concerned
that there was a pretty big fire in that
apartment yeah it's a you log video 4K
too
powerful and then they even included in
that report they even included like an
interview with the lady who was living
there and with the guy who reported it
and um they even talked with each other
and and the lady was like yeah I I I
think what I learned from this is really
that I need curtains
[Laughter]
uh and the guy who was like everybody
was chill about it I wonder if anybody
was charged for this but everybody was
chill about it and and
yeah everything was okay in the
end I hope they became friends
apparently now they wave at each other
when they see each other in the
window isn't that titty yeah no one was
harmed or cool so Alita was yours a real
fireplace or a smart TV you log
[Laughter]
fireplace a real one would be nicer for
sure a real one quite toasty
wow damn your own
fireplace damn cuz like I I can't have a
fireplace here fireplaces are nice for
sure but then you got to take care of of
getting wood cutting wood maybe and I I
think it's a bit expensive too
so real 4K that's like
400k if you look at it with your own
eyes you can get a gas one yeah but you
know it just looks nicer if it's like a
typical one like an old school one
that's built into the wall you know now
that leads up with a
chimney
oh yeah oh my God if the whole winter
will be nice with a fireplace it sounds
like you didn't have one before well
then enjoy it and enjoy the following
years of your life as much as you can
cherish every day and hopefully I can
spend some more time with
you thank you so much for the support
all these years it's been incredibly
long if you think about
it kind of unbelievable and it's also
unbelievable that you're still here but
I really appreciate it thank you m rine
thanks for the pinky you can use deadly
Embrace on big enemies when they stagger
bar when their stagger bar is at half oh
yeah I learned this you will hear ding
audio Q using it then pulls the big
enemy down for an opening for One Big
combo this makes deadly embrace one of
the best skills all game yeah I try to I
try to do it I think I've I've got it
down yeah I got it down thank you for
telling
[Music]
me I think I think I'm doing pretty well
now with Final Fantasy combat so all is
good it's definitely a cool cool
thing and yeah got to switch around all
the time which is a bit annoying but
right now I only have two I'm guessing
I'm getting more later on and then it
will be even more annoying let's go
let's
[Music]
go I'm guessing I'll get like four
total cuz that's just a magical number
with these kind of things and no maximum
three equipped oh so maybe I'll get more
but I can equip only free okay that's
good that's that's just one more then I
can I
can
chill not too much then
okay GD D Jim Tracy D hi
or lunchbox looking for the
toacy thank
you thank you thank you thank you guys
oh thank you
actually you guys are in super chats and
need Super I see that you like oh please
take a good long vacation and this and
that and um yesterday me and the
Mysterious
person we sat down and we booked the
hotel uh and then I was going to book
the flights but uh I realized I my card
was somehow not working I don't know why
apparently limit but I wouldn't say I
have such a low limit uh was kind of
weird but uh we're we're booking it part
of it is already booked so it's
happening it's really happening I'm so
excited so excited and I'm not going to
the same place I was kind of like
originally even considering it but the
same place that I was at last year with
waya um
was
incredibly expensive holy [\h__\h] now in
cuz now the time where where we're going
this time is actual High season for the
males the actual season when you're
supposed to go there so there will be no
freaking uh typhoons all the
time this is peak season but somehow
this hotel that I was at last time was
now even considering peak season
unreasonably expensive um Monsoon time I
felt it was definitely also a
typhoon so even more Koreans on
honeymoon possibly
yeah let's hope the weather won't be too
hot it was already freaking hot and
blazing back then I think whenever it
wasn't
raining I think I just remember the sun
being blazing I don't know if it was
really that hot was it did I say it was
hot it's definitely hot all
year but this time there won't won't be
rain so yeah got to be very careful got
to got to put sunscreen on all the time
several times a day M oh yeah I want
those sunscreens from the US again oh
well I know someone I know a way to get
the the American sunscreens again until
the
moldes
um oh
uh yeah cuz those were like damn so good
I want that one
again huh must be an ID member then no
that makes no
sense no but like realizing that it's
really happening that I'm really going
again I'm so excited cuz I I think I'm
burned out right now like wow M I'm
trying my best and I I want to do these
fun ideas that I have and I want to
stream but I feel burnt out I think and
just generally uh mentally not really
good but I have to Galu a bit more and
then and then and then we can do it and
so I was planning um you know we're
going to do like pretty much a week
almost a week pretty much a week of
males and then when when I come back to
Austria I'm going to do one more week of
just
like ignoring the
internet hopefully I can uh going to try
to also do no no work at all during this
time no in total that's two weeks of
vacation with one week being really
really detox and away from the internet
I think that's going to be fine cuz one
week I may still be on the internet but
I be in the males I won't be spending
that much time on the internet we'll
just be streaming and you know a little
bit of Twitter and this and that and and
and we'll we'll have fun it will be
super relaxing on its own take free no I
can't uh I can't I don't want to maybe
another extra week afterwards after a
month or two separately but not not in
one go not in one go cuz like
then then I'll be gone for too long and
I would feel like uh
that's not good that's not good I can't
be gone for so long I have to
stream cuz otherwise
otherwise I don't know it just feels
wrong
yeah but I think it'll be enough for me
to you know otherwise I'm going to get
[\h__\h] nervous
like I can't do this anymore I need to
go back on the internet and I'm going to
lose my [\h__\h] mind that's not good
either that's not
good you know we don't want me to lose
my mind during my
vacation
right but I'm so excited for this so I I
I I can I can gum I I can gum but until
the vacation
yeah I think so I'll do it
[Music]
yeah R now visiting me but that will
only be like the time that we spend
together will be really
short so it's not going to take up much
time as it's just like 2 days or
[Music]
so that's fine I see her in Japan and so
on every now and then so you know and
I'll go to I'll go to Bali in
2024 I don't know if waya will go to
Bali at the same time but I'll offer it
to
her so where was I black FR D recall 87
AG d unknown thanks for the pinky please
don't ever feel pressured by us Ki you
already always give us more than enough
amazing content all the time even if you
stream less than usual it's still so
much content so please take more short
and long breaks whenever you feel like
it after three years of gambu
nonstop it definitely you know feels
like
limit has been
reached in some ways
uh getting to a dangerous point but it's
also things that like even if I take a
vacation it won't fix the problems that
I have right now that make me
unhappy uh with my job right now so I
don't know I don't know if it's really
going to help but at least it might help
with the burnout and I don't
know
no
yeah just time to not think about
[Music]
it thank you guys thank you thank
you thank you love you guys thank you
thank you
sh m
thank
you h m and golden Dan miffin danash Pig
TB Dan missani danash 77 Dan oh I got
the new bill I got the new updated bill
for the motion capture suit since you
mention
it it's better than
before so before I think I said like
seven
1,000 right no 16 it was
16,000 so now with the fixes it looks
already much better only a bargain of
13,770
Euros I think it was Euros right yeah
what a
deal what a
deal uh wow so
God well now it's only going to make it
in time so I've been like working on
this for like two
months um I hope they send it soon and I
hope it arrives soon but the whole like
getting this organized took so long Mama
Mia um
but yeah I want to use it for last sleep
talking
MV uh and kind of uu told
me I should like buy the latest should
send if I want to release it at the end
of
November which I have to uh by the
latest release it at the end of November
for it to make sense for me for reasons
um then I have to to give him my
recorded
motion early November he said at the
latest the earlier the better
but
so if they send it out
now could still be fine they said like
it takes like two weeks but I don't know
if they realize that I am also in
Europe cuz the the maker of the suit is
also in
Europe so it might not even be 2 weeks
who
knows it shouldn't take that
long maybe for overseas it would take
that long but it's just within
Europe yeah so when it arrives I have to
like record my motion but I still have
to learn the Coro for for sleep
talking it's really
difficult don't under esate lazy DHL oh
I hope they don't send it with DHL but
if it's within Europe they can't charge
me taxes so it's
okay then it's
okay oh I just found the cap for my
Chanel lipstick oh wow what an
interesting
mechanism
oh
okay highly looks sh Mex mechanism
mechanism on
the cap how the inside goes inside it's
like you push it in and and you know it
locks itself in you know what I mean
then you have to push
inside you know what you know what I
mean it's I can't explain
it it's nice
though
no it's not a
robot childproof I wouldn't say it's
childproof no but it's
fancy I I I I would show you on the
camera but in order to turn it on again
I have to do like something complicated
and I don't want to do
it um where was I where was I I yeah oh
seven s d the professor ke D CR at d j d
Domin D Steven Long D
Mo check Chanel D certainly thanks for
Pinky here's my little contribution for
you Moab suit looking forward to the to
seeing holan's best dancer with her full
power I'm not the best dancer but thank
you uh by the way Blind Guardian the
BART song I'm sure you like it but feel
free to try to prove me wrong what what
is that
what is
that what is that some
[Music]
OST
oh what is
this just some why why are you showing
this to
me seems kind of random why
why why certainly
why Feels So
Random oh it's a song about Lord of the
Rings yeah it's a metal band so that's
why it's even more random like what
you've downloaded the Rings themed
albums okay okay you said you like B
music
oh
wait it's probably not what I meant but
let me let me
try
oh Good Start Good
Start yeah good
start Good
Start oh still no metal Vibe which is
good
uhhuh I feel like it's going to hit me
with the metal in a
moment or does it stay like
this let me
skip oh this song actually stays like
this okay okay okay okay I skipped
through and it it stays like
this well it's
beautiful
that is
beautiful all good it passed the
test getting hit with metal HTS yeah
Bonk still kind of random but I guess
yeah I said I like this kind of like Bly
music
yeah that's that's that's it that's it
thank
you Unity chat thank
game 8 910 d h d m eight than for the
pinky can you tell this game was made by
an MMO team of an actual DMC combat
director oh great job today T you really
improved can do the side quest off
stream if you feel like it there's also
a lore NPC in the Hideway
oh
a
[Music]
I don't think I could tell cuz I didn't
play DMC and it didn't feel like it was
made by an MMO team but I know they made
an MMO I mean I guess it could be a
different team with vin Square Enix
but don't hold hold it's mostly the ff14
team
interesting well I can't really judge
the DMC thing though so no idea but yeah
I will I will do it that way with the
side quest I mean I don't know if I
think like I'm falling behind and like
levels or whatever money then I might do
some side quests off stream but
generally I'm just not going to do them
at
all for now do you guys think I'll fall
behind in any
way
no no probably not never ever
no not
really
okay
good thank
you than soon D star thanks for the red
chat Hi boss not sure if you remember me
but about a year and a half ago I had to
change careers and my SK of course I
remember you Del what the [\h__\h] I
remember you like it was yesterday my
schedule completely changed I always
woke up when the stream was ending but
now I changed my schedule to my normal
time again and I can watch your streams
every day no
y no W now now it was cut off there
let's go dstar is back dstar is back
dstar is back woo woo woo welcome back
I'm happy to hear
that H you're here right now let's go oh
let's [\h__\h] go did you change it for
me did you change your schedule for
me did you do it for
me just say
yes you you did actually oh my God you
love me I love you we love each
other welcome back
finally it was about time you came
[Music]
back oh it's so nice that's great I'm
happy thank you welcome back Des I hope
you can see all my streams now h k also
with a red Super Chat thank you wow
just remember tento that whenever you're
feeling down tell yourself to sick him
tole not this time I read this
already get give them all you got boy
sck too get them that'll help over here
they're boy not this time give them all
you got boy sck tle get him don't
help M WS boy why did yeah why did you
not not you missed out on that one
coronor you're missing out on my wounds
boy I guess that's not really like
positively
[Music]
supportive maybe it's not yeah
supportive
[Music]
enough oh the keyboard well yeah that's
just how these keyboards
are thank you
Conor I I feel very amused by this Super
Chat thank you even the second
time
Mis well doesn't make me feel
better check your channel
d r Moonlight thanks for the pinky hey K
today is Mother's Day in Argentina so
happy Mother's Day don't worry I did
congratulate my mother so it's all D
that said have a nice week I catch up
with that with the week and now oh mean
what I streamed on
weekend thank you thank you soon and
Happy Mother's day
indeed thank you so much what but I
thought I was your real mommy what you
better say sorry Mommy to me now what
the
[Music]
[\h__\h] very confusing
this very
[Music]
confusing I just
realized my sniffing
sounds when I was like sniffing things
were way louder and intense in my in my
ears because I was monitoring the
microphone that I was sniffing
into and you guys probably didn't hear
it that much at
all or did
you cuz I was definitely not sniffing
into the camera
microphone you heard it
[Music]
properly but not as good as you could
have let me hear sniff for
you the olive
oil strong
sniff
[Music]
did it sound like this if not then I'm
disappointed let me eat some more of
that before the bread
goes like too too
hard what a good Oil
Man incredible
who [\h__\h]
yeah [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah such a good
oil and it
even helps the
children
[Music]
wow Mama
me Good Karma oil
M ah thank you Ash I'm happy to hear
that welcome to the live
stream I'm just eating but I need to
make use of the
oil n nom for
charity the bread is also really good
yeah it's just Austrian bad bread is
[\h__\h] amazing even the cheap
[Music]
ones like we have some discount
supermarkets that are like generally
just really cheap
overall but even those they have like
fresh bread sections and they're
insane they're so good like what the
hell they're not like wow they shouldn't
be that
[Music]
good
M our bread is so good
man mhm little I think they even have
little over
[Music]
se but like little is like a budget
discount supermarket here but their
bread is
[Music]
incredible great
bread mhm but Lea is from Germany but we
have it here
too is it's just
[Music]
Aly unless I'm mixing things up right
now I would think that Len overseas may
not have the same bread section though
so don't
think you can
[Music]
compare
m
M yeah this bread is perfect because
it's crunchy on the outside but not too
crunchy that everything falls apart and
soft on the
inside okay
um carp thank you for the red super chat
with free waa heart emojis than sh
carpet carpet absurd
Carpenters thank you I hope you're on my
side of that battle of that debate I
hope you
are sharing my
opinion you better
be thank you for the red super
chat on my side of the carpet
my carpet carpet absur I call you carpet
absum now not carpet absum from now on
okay you're not even here so you can't
say no but you know that's how it is now
I'll quickly read the TG tgw super chats
by the way in case you didn't know guys
today I
released the simple MV of of the great
wandera um and I know I
know I also wish I could have done full
budget great mvs for all the songs but
you know this is how it
is um they're simple they're literally
just there to show people who like did
not see that I have an album the
songs uh again give another chance to
people who haven't noticed I have an
album and
um
[Music]
yeah it's a great song right yeah Mama
loone I requested um uh cuz like the
plan was way early on already that I
would have uh 3D mvs for those two songs
and then for these other free songs I
would have simple mvs so I request
tested from Mama loon uh like I don't
know a couple months ago three artworks
one per song I was going to request more
but it was uh Mone was quite busy with
other things so it was just one but uh I
gave her like
some uh Inspirations like other photos
of outfits and artworks of
outfits what I wanted it to look like
and like yeah then she created these
beautiful artworks they're going to be
in the booklet as
well but they were yeah they were
supposed to be uh mainly for the music
videos just to have something there and
also for the
booklets but yeah
I there's one more yeah for
retrospective they've been done for a
while
now and they look pretty nice booklet
yeah for the physical
version of the
CD uh I had them include into the design
the artworks CU I was like well I got
them made might as well include them in
the booklet to make it look
noise yes yes
yes it will it looks pretty
cool that way there's like some nice
visuals in between the lyric pages
[Music]
I thought it was
quite quite
genius CD Japan still has some physical
wa
CDs huh for pre-order I thought the
pre-order time was
over it for
real okay if somebody do still want want
it the check out city of Japan seven in
stock they
say or maybe maybe seven people canel
their pre-order is that
possible I wonder how that
happens well if you guys want one more
you can try it
out okay so there were a few super chats
for this so let me read them Jacob 47 py
Dom Eden x
z zip D Lord EV d py d Jim Tracy D GD
thank you for the red super chat amazing
MV kudos to you and your team thank you
it's it's really meant to be simple cuz
budget
Reasons I'm already spending way more
than I
should but I'm glad you guys liked it
even if it was simple thank you thank
you thank you thank you
soon for the big support I really
appreciate
it I am a beep thank you soon J than you
soon TR than soon Evans L thanks for the
pinky keep up the banging effort thank
you I'm
trying I'll do my best space waterfall
dang soon yeah sci-fi
waah
[Music]
thank
you than you
soon no I say it because I know like a
lot of you guys' favorite songs were not
the ones that are getting the high
budget MBS but this was the plan since
the beginning and I I can't change it
now when the artwork is already done for
those songs since like 2 months ago I
can't change the plan now and in the end
I still agree that with myself that the
the k- poppy
songs like I I I will only do a 3D MV
for a song that I feel like is
incredibly dancable because that it
makes sense like using 3D for it yeah
could have still done something else for
the other songs but uh it was just not
not making sense for me to do that when
I have you know I don't have a freaking
label behind me like cie
so I'm paying for all this myself every
every there was no budget for any
visuals like I am paying everything out
of my pocket in terms of like
illustrations and music video editing
everything is all completely on
me it's a bit different from when I do
singles like there's different you know
ways of how things are being done
compared to um singles versus albums so
you know this is just I'm just doing
like more than one 3D MV just for my own
satisfaction
[Laughter]
anyway originally I should have probably
just like done one but I'm committing to
two which is already more than I should
be doing
so yeah you know that's how it
is
is your new sound dancable it
is it is um I don't have a Coro for it
yet and I think there's still time we
have like a really really really simple
music video in 3D just to get the like a
little bit of the vibe across but it's
really simple cuz it was really
rushed um if if if it gets to the point
like if I get another uh
round uh further then I hope they give
me the chance to make a new one cuz I
don't want to use the one that we have
now um what I found interesting when I
look at like last year's Germany
applicants the ones in the
preliminaries um they all had really
really way less than us oh really they
all had really uh expensive looking
music videos so I wonder if EUR Vision
Germany the Ard which is behind it I
think if they pay for the music videos
for the
preliminary
um bands and musicians that they have
cuz I I can't imagine that all these
artists A lot of them like mostly
Indies who are probably not even under a
label that they could really pay for
such expensive looking music videos on
their own I would think once they get
into the preliminaries that that they
pay for it for them to have something
nice to present and that everyone's like
on a on same level so that it's not
unfair if one person has a shitty music
video people are not going to like vote
for it as much you know I don't think
they want to put them on the same
quality level so I can imagine they
would pay for it but I can't find any
information about it if they pay for it
but if they do then I want this little
like you know it's not really a music
video but this little video that I made
for the song I want it to be redone and
going to put some high budget into a new
one but who knows if I get in the next
round I really doubt it I'm being very
realistic about it I really really doubt
it e n I don't think it matters to not
live in Germany that's why they have
otherwise is like you know they would
put up a rule and I'm pretty close to
Germany anyway I speak German it would
be weird if I don't don't even speak
German that is not even my biggest uh
negative point about
me I think the biggest negative point is
just being a vtuber but at the same time
it's a it's a positive point because
that makes me
interesting that makes me interesting
and unique okay
H we'll see I don't know if I even get
an answer if they don't take
me or if I just get
ignored I wonder I it would be helpful
if they tell me like hey sorry you're
not in next round so that I can just
stop waiting for an
answer
I hope
so please I hate when you submit
something to something and you don't get
a notice of wherever you made it or
not you only get the notice if you made
it like I hate
that that is so like wasting my time too
waiting for an answer and not like
applying to anything else if it's like a
job thing or so yeah the limb
the limbo I hate
it but thankfully I didn't have that
with whole life cuz I got an a reply
immediately
immediately like hey you're in the next
round let's have an
interview I'm like let's [\h__\h]
go nowadays I hear it's not that quick
anymore cuz like there's way more appli
ations and you
know they may take a long time to look
at your application in the first
place it's not the process is not that
fast
anymore yeah for us it was pretty
fast things happened fast and they found
what they wanted fast I
guess yeah yeah H where was I
oh yeah space waterfall D I think I read
them all now okay so that was the the
the great
wander super chats I'm going to read the
ones from today quickly I kind of want
to keep this stream short because you
know it's nice to have a few short ones
up on my channel so that people can be
like hey this one's short you know what
I'll try this like you know
newcomers people who don't watch me
regularly or at all and they're like uh
okay let's check out this channel uh
wait all of these are eight hours what
the [\h__\h] wait this one's three hours
I'll try this one you
know so let's not make it too long uh
hopefully how many super chats did I get
from the stream is it too
much is it going to take too much time
no should be fine
probably
let me wait one
[Music]
second you're freezing outside only
wearing a hoodie go inside what are you
doing what are you
doing don't freeze chicken
that's not
good I guess when you go inside I'll
I'll I'll I'll I'll have an idea how to
warm you up I'll throw you straight into
the fryer you'll feel super warm really
quickly all the pain will be gone
instantly come here come
here still your wrapping to the pinky T
to it oh my God thank you always my
so sweet of you thank you so
much the shadow under my chin really
bothers me it doesn't even move with the
chin it's certainly a
bug sorry getting
distracted I'm nice and warm inside my K
omocat hoodie that's what you're wearing
right now let's
go let's go
cat thank
[Music]
you 5:00 shadow wait is that like isn't
that like a term
for a a certain state of a
beard yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh I get it I get
it
is it when is that how it gets when you
shave in the morning and then at 5:00
it's already back at that point what the
[\h__\h] is that
fast I mean maybe not for everybody for
a lot of people shes that's so annoying
what like wait for 24 hours
please end of the day for men who shave
daily if you have pale skin and dark
facial
there
[Music]
there naita mini I don't even know about
this change I don't even know that that
was
missing what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay I wrote to jenma she's sleeping I
think but thank you I pointed it out
immediately before I forget
it thank you for taking not of
it oh
nice [\h__\h] yeah Pro riding a landan cable
in your Villa during your stay [\h__\h]
yeah got a got a reply from the
hotel that was like the one request um
we're going to work during our stay in
the Mal
Dives so um um we need a good internet
connection can we please have a cable
instead of a
Wi-Fi this is so weird like people only
really B the males if they're going for
honeymoon or just like a real vacation
like nobody goes there and then
continues to
work they must be like how workaholic
are these people why are they working in
in on the [\h__\h]
males yeah well don't worry it's not
really it's it's
fine it's
different they don't know that we're
going to be streaming
though just that we're going to be
working they wouldn't get it yeah they
don't get it they don't
[Music]
understand
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
the Phantom
Sky thanks for the
pinky uh I'm an armored chicken now
which means today is October 17th 2023
the three year anniversary of my first
Lord of the Rings SW long really good
luck with guessing today thank you
what three years ago we watched our
first Lo the Rings watch long
what hey man ma with the
lore I was there for that thank you I
see it on your
armor time for another
one I'm always up for watching it but I
I feel like we already watched it
twice we I should be watching something
else with you guys at least like
privately I I can watch it again but
like with you guys I should watch
something
else no
no maybe with someone else who hasn't
seen it yet as a collab watch long I
wouldn't mind
[Music]
joining no I want to see something new
no cuz like Lo of the is also such a
long commitment cuz if I watch one then
I have to watch all
three and they're long movies even
without
extended such a commitment
guys Jo W thanks for the pinky here's a
little something to half cover your
expensive honey thank you what the [\h__\h]
like I don't know if the honey was worth
it like yeah it tasted great but in the
end I'm just mixing it into my
tea and then it's not really noticeable
I guess for for the Manuka honey maybe
I'll try actually eating it in a way
that the honey is the main component
like on on a butter bread I guess
normally I wouldn't do that cuz I'm not
that much into
honey yeah well I I'll try I'll give it
a try tomorrow in the morning
maybe
yeah yeah Manuka Honey is probably too
expensive to be mixed into tea
[Music]
man why the [\h__\h] is let me let me read
up on why Manuka honey why is manuka
honey so
expensive Manuka Honey is expensive
because it is rare it is only produced
in certain regions of New Zealand and
Australia oh mate bloody hell mate so
expensive additionally it is more
expensive to produce because sometimes
bees need to be moved to these regions
and there's a short FL flowering window
of about about 4 to 6 weeks per
[Music]
year
I I think oh maybe one thing I could use
it for is like don't you I feel like
some home DIY homemade beauty masks um I
heard that you can use honey maybe using
Manuka honey for Dad would be quite nice
I don't
know I don't know can you you believe
it could use on Vanilla Ice what never
heard of combining ice with
[Music]
honey I mean I still feel like it's not
reasonable man AA honey is different
from standard honey and is sometimes
touted for its health
[Music]
benefits Manuka Honey is known to have
anti antibacterial and
antimicrobial
properties yeah just like normal honey
though
[Music]
no unlike regular honey Manuka Honey
contains methyl gly oxil glyoxal
a powerful antibacterial compound the
MGO is Created from the conversion of d
diydrone a compound found in the nectar
of Manuka flowers oh those are flowers
Manuka flowers that's where it comes
from the more mdo that Manuka Honey has
the more expensive it is because it has
more poent antibacterial properties the
potency of Manuka Honey is indicated by
its um F rating which stands for Unique
Manuka Factor
[Music]
oh oh therapeutic great Manuka Honey
which can be used more for wound care
than eating must have a minimum rating
of umf 10
[Music]
plus because manuga honey is such a
valuable commodity the industry has also
been roted with crime in 2016 the
guardian reported about High thefts
vandalism and bee poisonings that were
happening in the Manuka Honey industry
as beekeepers battle against each
other there's
drama
shees while Manuka Honey may have many
health benefits it's production process
has the same ethical and environmental
concerns as normal honey fortunately
there are vegan honey Alternatives
available that aren't produced by
[Music]
bees company lach
uhuh the
[Music]
bees War
honey drama in the Manuka Honey
Community spill the
tea spill it and extract the Manuka
honey that I put into my tea cuz that's
a waste apparently I guess I don't
know now you want an anime
[Music]
yeah there's varying prices too the mine
was expensive was the most expensive
honey I could
[Music]
find I'm sure there's documentaries
about Manuka
honey I am certain
uh where was I here space
waterfall dead pan Sanchez
kand oh from
Norway wait Norway was the one uh with
the Manuka honey no no that's New
Zealand what what what was the thing of
Norway the ah the V water the V
water
water that was the
one you C Mike D thank you for the pinky
looks like you and your wallet have been
through quite a bit for the stream
really fun idea for the stream no thank
you K it's fine I just hope that I can
send back the the one uh not blanket
the bed bed sheet the problem is
generally I'm just too lazy to send
things back that I have from Amazon so I
just end up keeping
them like the process of putting it in a
box and bringing it to the post office
also like my printer doesn't even work
so how am I going to print out that
thing that they want you to print out
like so many
obstacles
a is it really worth it for definitely
not I mean not worth buying it but worth
sending it back yeah
probably you don't need a printer for
some find a printer that's even like one
more step how annoying you can use a QR
C code by
now it can I let the post office do it
at the post office you can show your
phone thing that they can print it is
that like where are you from Ender Taco
maybe that's a regional like maybe they
don't do that
[Music]
here I just bring it to the drop off it
has to be in the product box but not
prepped for
shipping that sounds convenient I don't
know if it's this convenient here I'll
I'll look it up you can just return with
only a QR code and let the post office
do it what do you mean only a QR code in
the Box though right and they'll they'll
do the labeling
[Music]
then
huh uh I don't know about Amazon drop
off stores I don't I don't I haven't
heard of
that you show them at the post office
and then oh okay okay okay that makes it
easier cuz [\h__\h] my printer why did why
did I ever buy a printer should have
just bought a scanner and that's
it man I gave my printer no reason to
malfunction it just was working and then
5 weeks later or so when I didn't use it
for 5 weeks I use it again suddenly it's
not
working it has no reason to not be
working [\h__\h] that
printer ah at least the scanning
function still works
[Music]
no [\h__\h] printers
man Amazon does have returnal yeah of
course well I know about returning being
possible HP is being sued for that like
currently for real
funny oh okay I'll check it out I
actually have one more thing to return
at the moment but I don't know if it's
not already too late at this
[Music]
point well there's copy shops everywhere
but like just going to one just for that
seems just stupidly annoying to
me just for printing out one thing
and no if it works that way I'll just
bring it to the post office then thank
you thank you guys I didn't know about
that that's actually really helpful
information r 9,000 than hild than oh my
God the stream is almost three hours
James Jackson donate blood and
watch David
L you should the gameer cre D and Chief
and Lee
[Music]
h no the salon also very good but the
olive oil makes it even better K thank
you
D the bird place of takanasi Kiara also
obligatory come to
Thailand hopefully one
day looking for the top Dan soon every
another call thanks for the red chat fun
for the stream also fingers reveal yeah
my my fingers don't look so nice they
they look they're so weirdly shaped
they're so so bulky in the middle they
don't look so nice just simply by having
longer more feminine like fake nails
they would already look so much nicer
just by default just by putting on some
sticky nails or whatever I should have
done
that my nails my fingers are just so
like what are these
sausages I'm ashamed I'm
ashamed don't look at my fingers
but it was so much nicer touching like
if I do cooking streams in the future I
think I'll do it like that because then
you know just feels kind of weird with
gloves all the time cuz also I get cat
hairs on a glove and then I can't wash
my hands and CU it's gloves
and
yeah no no I'm ashamed guys don't look
at my hands but thank you every another
cold t d soon love D for the rest of CH
thank you you're welcome I I don't want
to flip you off but I hope you felt
satisfied I even did the little the
little wheel it up wheel it down
thingy Sky D soon delar soon rer thanks
for the red chat thanks for the fun
stream T you always come up with such
UniQue Ideas ah you have no idea you
know
um a while ago the M stream I was
talking about this stream idea and I
said wait I actually had one more and I
was going to tell you guys about it and
then I forgot about it the moment I was
going to say it and then I was like well
[\h__\h] I I really want this to come back
to me and then last night I woke up
sometime in the middle of the night and
I uh some for some reason the idea came
back to
me and I was like wait should I was like
half asleep so I was like should I write
this down but that will wake me up if I
do that let me just say it to myself in
my brain 10 times this idea and then I
will remember it usually that works but
I forgot about it again the second
idea forgot about
it I forgot about it again it came back
to me once for a short time and then I
fell asleep again and then it was gone
again but if I trusted myself to
remember it cuz I told myself like this
is the idea this is the
idea regretting
spaghetti maybe it will come to me again
next time I'll write it down even if
it's in the middle of my deep
[Music]
sleep
voice
[Music]
record yeah I hope I hope I'll
remember they are cute stop are you like
in the past is this still about my
fingers how far are you behind with the
[Music]
stream thank you rer mAh
I appreciate that I I really try my best
to like come up with some nice funny
interesting original ideas every once in
a while for my streams and I think
that's like my
specialty my
specialty um yeah you know I try
to you know come up with some cool ideas
for my streams yeah
yeah
yeah I hope it reaches more people thank
you for watching today deeply D Nathan
cotton thanks for the red CH thank you
for fix fingers and Camera mic for my
second membership anniversary I'm I
become reborn Jin ah you even said it
here camera mic
[\h__\h] was this after I found out cuz like
[\h__\h] why was it on the
camera I feel so so so [\h__\h]
so failured man such a
failure
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] please ber me in German
[Music]
by
talking in Austrian
dialect
dude
[Music]
man Nathan M thank you and
congratulations on being reborn thank
you so much for being part of the
membership supporting me every month
every day dun you're the best thank you
for all your
love I give you love back as much as I
can Bruce Dan for the pinky haven't
spent two birthdays with you but somehow
my sentence in the unic room is still
ongoing but anyway my birthday was in
September can I get a py PTY from my
birthday that passed thanks C how are
you still in the usual room what did I
what did you do what did
how long of a sentence did I give you 5
years I think I I'm ready to Pardon you
delstar I mean I can imagine you did
something but I should probably pardon
you or or you just don't want to
go what
happened he did something really
bad he was rebelling I guess
[Music]
huh sometimes yeah there were some times
where I didn't specify it
probably [\h__\h] rebelling well delar
what's your statement are you planning
to Rebel anytime again
soon answer
honestly or
else fry waa not until I'm out well then
you're
staying happy birthday though
yay hope birthdays are fun in the usual
room you're staying there forever you
little [\h__\h]
Cruz d space waterful d Matrix free BC
D motion thank you D oh you finished
[Music]
it motion I'm not going to answer your
your question cuz I answered this
question already 5 million times have
you not been
listening my
[Music]
God
it's been 3 years no even recently I
talked about
it maybe it wasn't Japanese cuz it was
like toward super simpai I'm not sure
but you should know my reason for why I
like xilia 2 so much it's so obvious
when you play it it's so obvious why
what was the one thing that cilia did
differently cilia 2 to all the other
tell off games huh think about
it
think just
pink that's the
reason it had a cat no no
no [\h__\h] I didn't think you were the
type of person to bring me on a [\h__\h]
palm tree in German we say to BR me of
the
P you bringing me up a palm tree that's
how angry you make
me apparently when you're angry you go
up a palm
[Music]
tree driving me up a wall yeah something
like that
[Laughter]
is your cat cuter than
tutu
yeah
yeah yeah she's pretty cute too pretty
darn cute but she still has the being
tiny baby
bonus and my cats are grown up and
they're
still I would say
cuter at least chunky wonky her
behavior is the cutest like what the
[\h__\h] like oh my God like what what's
wrong with her like that's how cute she
is like my
God she's so
cute Bob Dyan thanks for the red chat
hey yo hi T it was my birthday yesterday
I'd be really happy if you sing Happy
Birthday to me but don't force yourself
if you don't feel like it of course so
really happy when I can catch a stream
even partially temp my Divine comei oh
[Music]
yeah how do you sing
it Jo aniversary something like
[Music]
that
uh is that all you sing in
French happy birthday
song
Let give me random French phrases in the
chat guys
happy
birthday to you let's go
[Music]
join
mer get we we pee hon
Hong my friendch
chicken I love the way
you
[Music]
go happy birday to you happy birthday in
your
shoe happy birthday in your pants to
happy birthday to
[Music]
you whatever that
means and
P
what I wonder what I'm saying happy
birthday to you happy birthday in your
shoes happy birthday in your pants too
happy birthday to
[Music]
you all these years you've been waiting
for your service to be
ending and all you free time go to me
thank you so much happy bir oh that's it
oh [\h__\h] uh
well that's lame that's a bad we're
standing I hate it but thank you what
the [\h__\h] did I say anything bad I hope
not I was just reading off chat
bour bour Mami
maon no let's not say that let's not say
that
[Music]
I didn't say anything about your mom or
a war right
right well you seem to be happy so seems
to be no issue there pardon my
French
uh it's okay it's like your seventh
language no it's my non-existent
language
but [\h__\h] loud
[Music]
bgm yeah wow wow wow thank you uh so
much
for the support and I learned new French
I'm actually surprised it doesn't even
sound so familiar to
me I've never heard that before Jo
annivers why does it sound so unfamiliar
to me how how
[Music]
come pretty good
pronunciation you you a joyous
oh it does sound like joyous now that
you say it
right thank you so much Bob Dylan thank
you I hope your birthday is
wonderful for Pinky actually T speaking
of Lord of the Rings seems like that
return of Mora game comes out next
week was that the good one like
something we're looking forward to the
opening cinematic also comes out today
voiced by gimle himself John R Davis oh
my
God what kind of game was that like in
terms of like s like like how is it
strategy or what what is it is the dwarf
one Builder Survival
game
Co-op online or couch
Co survival crafting game
in survival crafting
game I'll have to watch some gam playay
or like
[Music]
yeah E I wonder I wonder if the co-op is
fun if it's if it would be collab wor
if is it like Minecraft Arc and rust too
really
[\h__\h]
collab Coop survival crafting I wonder
if she would like it I mean I know she
she liked all lot of the Rings but if
she would like this kind of
[Music]
game got to find out about the collab
potential let me let me let me Google it
right now uh what was it Lords of Moria
minds of Moria what was it Moria Moria
game 2023 game
[Music]
play Return to Maria okay I'll watch
this video 13 minutes of exclusive game
playay I'll watch this and see if it's
worth
it which publisher is that
anyway Moria
[Music]
copia
of course we're skipping Golem game of
course we
[Music]
are are you Italian no I'm
Austrian oh my God fre hours what the
[\h__\h] satisf iction for the pinky thank
you so much Sam K's hands looking mighty
holdable sorry for my l Hold the B hold
the
B
thank you that what a what a
compliment than very sweet D and and Bob
Dyan D I'm going to end it now thanks
for watching and Jo
in looks a lot like Fable man I love
Fable bye-bye enj in tomorrow GTA GTA
GTA GTA GTA
[Applause]
GTA
[Music]