[Music]
all right Duncan get to work
those floors aren't gonna wash
themselves you know what's that pouty
face for you should be grateful for that
fabulous party we just Brew
one dead by the way
you weren't exactly invited to you know
not a bad thing to have a little extra
company though I'm packing up the
leftover cookies but if you want any
extra let me know
yeah I figured as much here you go
you can't eat those until you're done
cleaning okay I'm putting you to work
hey are we cooking something else I
didn't plan on making more food but now
that you mention it
[Music]
that a chicken
me not again
whoops Jimmy's in the oven
ah we were making such progress too but
I guess chickens are just drawn to the
oven by Nature ever consider just
letting him cook
oh
me
he's a valuable employee of kfp right
sorry
there you go all better
now we can focus on making Callie's
house Sparkle yep just gotta focus on
oh
it's snowing I've been waiting for a
winter wonderland in Tokyo oh
so much for cleaning huh
but this is a big event you guys we
can't miss an opportunity to make a
snowman
well there she goes
when Kiara sets her mind to something
there's no stopping her huh
[Music]
foreign