I'm In Too Deep did I lose my
way oh no no way no way ain't got a
choice don't look
away where do you want to go I don't
know breakr listen up cuz it's here some
advice you could tell by now temperature
is crazy off that wall and that should
scare me they go ahead and do it what
you waiting for I feel like I'm melting
for the heat H I am turning back let's
go I don't even know what to do with
this mess going round and round well
life is the only way you make of it
don't know what to do just take a chance
committing fou
play Hello convince myself I'm doing all
right but you know nah I won't pretend
the lie that I tell myself so I'll
survive who who are you talking to
Flames burn me up down into my core and
every part of my being doubts the past
and the present and my dreams I just
hear your voice I can't be sure why or
when I'm alive tearing it down to just
what I want one day I just the light it
will lead me back looking back I'm ready
to admit it was all me who destroyed
everything I am you're not
you wish I stay now CLE keeping me
captive I want
it I'll save if I can