​​​ ​Hey there, rowdy kids of Graffiti Kindergarten!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's today's drawing time. Gather round!​ ​​
​​​ ​​​ ​​
​​​ ​Mommy!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not your mom. I'm your teacher.​ ​​
​​​ ​Before we start, kids, go ahead​ ​​
​​ ​and introduce yourselves!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi! My name is Shirakami Fubuki!​ ​​
​​​ ​1st Gen & GAMERS​ ​​
​​ ​Shirakami Fubuki​ ​​
​​​ ​Good!​ ​​
​​​ ​I will draw lots of cute drawings!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm looking forward to it!​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive Indonesia​ ​​
​​ ​Airani Iofifteen​ ​​
​​​ ​Mish A! I will draw a lot today,​ ​​
​​​ ​Cute.​ ​​
​​​ ​so please give me a flower stamp then.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you did well enough.​ ​​
​​ ​You need to earn it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, right.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay. I'm Iopi, by the way. Hello.​ ​​
​​​ ​Next is Reine-chan! That's one sexy look.​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive Indonesia​ ​​
​​ ​Pavolia Reine​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi! I may not look like a baby,​ ​​
​​ ​but I weally am. Gonna draw lots.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can't wait to get started!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good to hear!​ ​​
​​​ ​C-Can you talk, Kiara-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​(She's introducing herself)​ ​​
​​​ ​Seems like she can't, so I guess we'll​ ​​
​​ ​record her part some other day.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait! Hold it!​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive English -Myth-​ ​​
​​ ​Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Takanashi Kiwawa from hololive English.​ ​​
​​ ​Call me Kiwawa.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, Kiwawa-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Draw a moai sculpture!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now, I'll give you a couple of words,​ ​​
​​​ ​and you'll draw each one​ ​​
​​ ​without looking at the picture.​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't wanna!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you didn't get your drawing quite right,​ ​​
​​​ ​your friends have to reveal​ ​​
​​ ​an embarrassing story of yours​ ​​
​​​ ​that you've been trying to​ ​​
​​ ​keep a secret until now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh no!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's part of your broader education!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this how you educate children in Japan?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't wanna become a grown-up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Grown-ups are scary!​ ​​
​​​ ​Graffiti Kindergarten!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's the first word! Ta-da!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Panda"?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start by drawing a panda face!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure thing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Miss!​ ​​
​​​ ​How much time do we have?​ ​​
​​​ ​Try to get it done asap. You'll understand​ ​​
​​ ​why when you grow up.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can we change the colors?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sure, you can do that!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are there any colors to change...?​ ​​
​​ ​But sure, go ahead.​ ​​
​​​ ​You can just stick to black and white, no?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey! Shh! No giving out hints!​ ​​
​​ ​Understood?​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaaat?​ ​​
​​​ ​What kind of idiot would do that?​ ​​
​​​ ​This kid just said "idiot."​ ​​
​​​ ​How is it looking? Are you done?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's first see what the correct answer is.​ ​​
​​​ ​So yes, this is what a panda looks like.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​What a cutie.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's start with Fubuki-chan's drawing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Show us.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh, that's cute!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is Mr. Panda.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's cute, but... I see you didn't color it in.​ ​​
​​​ ​In he back...​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, you didn't!​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't know which parts are black​ ​​
​​ ​and which are white.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you tried to cover up your ignorance.​ ​​
​​​ ​Also, that neck has quite the presence.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's almost human-like, even.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's beefy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's look at Iofi-chan's drawing next.​ ​​
​​ ​Here it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, this one's pretty cute too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pink pandas totally exist!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why are you all adding your own faces...?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow, you're right. She did it too.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here is Reine-chan's.​ ​​
​​​ ​This Mr. Panda is very strong​ ​​
​​ ​and goes to the gym every day.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a bodybuilder panda!​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh? These look so similar.​ ​​
​​​ ​Muscle!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Gym Panda! Muscle!​ ​​
​​​ ​Finally, let's look at Kiara-chan's drawing!​ ​​
​​​ ​Please don't...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a raccoon! A raccoon!​ ​​
​​​ ​This isn't quite...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's not a raccoon! It's a panda!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's the odd one out​ ​​
​​ ​compared to the others.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on! Mine's​ ​​
​​ ​eating bamboo and everything!​ ​​
​​​ ​And now to decide​ ​​
​​ ​which ones are wrong. Well...​ ​​
​​​ ​One of them has ears that are​ ​​
​​ ​quite a bit too pointy for a panda,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I'm afraid it's yours, Kiara-chan.​ ​​
​​​ ​But I worked so hard on this!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, Kiara-chan, looks like it's​ ​​
​​ ​time to expose one of your secrets.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's your own fault! It's your own fault!​ ​​
​​​ ​So, do any of you have​ ​​
​​ ​a secret of hers to share?​ ​​
​​​ ​Me! Me! Me! Me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh? Fubuki-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Miss! Kiara-chan had ramen the other day,​ ​​
​​​ ​and it took her a whole hour to finish it!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​One hour?!​ ​​
​​​ ​A whole hour?!​ ​​
​​​ ​What's wrong with that?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's so slow, Kiwawa!​ ​​
​​​ ​The noodles will get soggy.​ ​​
​​​ ​They'll get soggy, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​They also get longer, and there's nothing​ ​​
​​ ​wrong with more noodle, is there?​ ​​
​​​ ​Why did it take you that long, I wonder?​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't slurp up ramen noodles, so instead​ ​​
​​​ ​I figured out a different way to enjoy them.​ ​​
​​​ ​A different way, I see.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's the spoon, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​The soup spoon, yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​I first put some noodles in,​ ​​
​​​ ​then top it with corn and green onions​ ​​
​​ ​and other trimmings.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then I blow on it because I have​ ​​
​​ ​a sensitive tongue, and finally I eat it.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is one long explanation.​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't get any toppings in your mouth​ ​​
​​ ​when you slurp up the noodles, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​But if you pile it all up on a spoon,​ ​​
​​ ​you get to enjoy everything at once.​ ​​
​​​ ​It actually tastes better that way!​ ​​
​​​ ​W-Wouldn't you end up​ ​​
​​ ​with soggy noodles, though?​ ​​
​​​ ​I just told you I get to​ ​​
​​ ​eat more noodles that way!​ ​​
​​​ ​Graffiti Kindergarten!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's your next word!​ ​​
​​​ ​Draw a pteranodon!​ ​​
​​​ ​A what now?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's draw a pteranodon.​ ​​
​​​ ​A pteranodon?​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you know what that is?​ ​​
​​​ ​Going from a panda straight to a​ ​​
​​ ​pteranodon is a bit much, Miss.​ ​​
​​​ ​Before we look at your drawings,​ ​​
​​ ​let's check the correct answer, okay?​ ​​
​​​ ​You all got it, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm sure you've all seen this​ ​​
​​ ​in a game somewhere.​ ​​
​​​ ​I got it! I got it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Me too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Did all of you really know this?​ ​​
​​​ ​Aren't you a bit​ ​​
​​ ​too smart for kindergartners?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's reveal all your drawings in one go.​ ​​
​​ ​Here they are!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?! Why did everyone else get it right?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh dear, this is bad.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiara-chan,​ ​​
​​ ​is this an attempt at a joke, maybe?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, it's not! I swear!​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't know what a pterano-something was,​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, you didn't know.​ ​​
​​​ ​so I drew a N*tella-don instead.​ ​​
​​​ ​N*tella-don...?​ ​​
​​​ ​N*tella's this delicious,​ ​​
​​ ​chocolate-like thing...​ ​​
​​​ ​A N*tella bowl?​ ​​
​​​ ​N*tella on rice? That exists?!​ ​​
​​​ ​N*tella-don!​ ​​
​​​ ​It doesn't, but I might try one now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry, Kiara-chan, but this doesn't count!​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, yeah, there's no way.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's your own fault! It's your own fault!​ ​​
​​​ ​Does anyone else have an embarrassing​ ​​
​​ ​story about Kiara-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​Me! Me! Me! Meee!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh! Reine-chan!​ ​​
​​​ ​There was this time Kiara-san​ ​​
​​​ ​called over a friend for one single thing:​ ​​
​​​ ​to turn on her computer​ ​​
​​ ​because she couldn't do it herself!​ ​​
​​​ ​I had a stream that day,​ ​​
​​ ​but my computer wouldn't boot up.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aah, that's bad.​ ​​
​​​ ​So I tried pressing the power button harder,​ ​​
​​​ ​but again, nothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​I did that for ten more minutes,​ ​​
​​ ​but it wouldn't budge!​ ​​
​​​ ​I was like,​ ​​
​​ ​"Oh no, I have a stream coming up,​ ​​
​​​ ​and my PC is broken!"​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh no!​ ​​
​​​ ​So I ended up calling a friend​ ​​
​​ ​who knows stuff about computers.​ ​​
​​​ ​They said​ ​​
​​ ​"All right, let me see what happens,"​ ​​
​​​ ​and pressed the button,​ ​​
​​ ​and the PC turned on just like that.​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​Have some sympathy, will you?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be spilling your tea in the next rounds!​ ​​
​​​ ​Graffiti Kindergarten!​ ​​
​​​ ​Here is the next word.​ ​​
​​​ ​Draw a bulldozer!​ ​​
​​​ ​A bulldozer?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't remember what the front looks like.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can you draw it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course we can!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bulldozer!​ ​​
​​​ ​Can we leave out the color?​ ​​
​​​ ​Color it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Fiiine.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's first check the correct answer!​ ​​
​​ ​Here it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, this is what a bulldozer looks like.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cool.​ ​​
​​​ ​Beeg!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yellow!​ ​​
​​​ ​Now let's see what you made of it.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's this? One of these has a rather​ ​​
​​ ​round thing in front of it.​ ​​
​​​ ​More specifically Reine-chan's.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's the Road Roller!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right, it's the "WRYYY!" thing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Looks like Reine-chan's the odd one out.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're out!​ ​​
​​​ ​Reine, you're out!​ ​​
​​ ​Time for a spanking!​ ​​
​​​ ​Spanking...​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a different show.​ ​​
​​​ ​Meanwhile, Iofi-chan's bulldozer has​ ​​
​​ ​an angry face for some reason.​ ​​
​​​ ​I saw a movie with bulldozers once,​ ​​
​​ ​and they all had eyes, Miss.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, that's why!​ ​​
​​​ ​But real bulldozers don't have eyes,​ ​​
​​ ​so you're also out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Out!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's your own fault! It's your own fault!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's expose a juicy secret of yours.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's exposure time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Does anyone know an​ ​​
​​ ​embarrassing story about Iofi-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​I've got one! Yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, so you do!​ ​​
​​​ ​Then please share it with the class.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​There was this time​ ​​
​​ ​during one of her streams​ ​​
​​​ ​when she referred to​ ​​
​​ ​a ring as a cincin (PP)!​ ​​
​​​ ​Disqualified!​ ​​
​​​ ​What?!​ ​​
​​​ ​"Peepee"?!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's just what we call​ ​​
​​ ​rings in Indonesian. "Cincin."​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep! That's the word we use!​ ​​
​​​ ​The most embarrassing instance​ ​​
​​ ​of this was when I was in Japan.​ ​​
​​​ ​When you went to Japan?​ ​​
​​​ ​You've got those anime merch stores, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​I was looking around in one,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I said "Oh, they have rings​ ​​
​​ ​as merch" in Indonesian,​ ​​
​​​ ​but it sounded like​ ​​
​​ ​"Oh, they have peepee merch."​ ​​
​​​ ​The other people in the store​ ​​
​​​ ​gave me some weird looks after that.​ ​​
​​​ ​I see... But it's just a ring, right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah...​ ​​
​​​ ​If that's the case,​ ​​
​​​ ​I can say that Mio gave me​ ​​
​​ ​a cincin last year.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is going on the official channel,​ ​​
​​ ​so I think it's time to stop.​ ​​
​​​ ​Cincin.​ ​​
​​​ ​One moment please​ ​​
​​​ ​So, does anyone know an​ ​​
​​ ​embarrassing story about Reine-san?​ ​​
​​​ ​I do! I do! I do!​ ​​
​​​ ​This was when we were​ ​​
​​ ​staying in the Maldives.​ ​​
​​​ ​I woke up in the night​ ​​
​​​ ​because she was touching me all over!​ ​​
​​​ ​Touching you?!​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't do it on purpose!​ ​​
​​​ ​It wasn't intentional?​ ​​
​​​ ​Really now?​ ​​
​​​ ​I was sleeping with my back turned to her,​ ​​
​​​ ​when I suddenly felt​ ​​
​​ ​her fingers brush up my back.​ ​​
​​​ ​She was stroking your back?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah! She was stroking me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Why did you do that, Reine-chan?​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean...​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know! I was asleep!​ ​​
​​​ ​But I wub her, so I didn't actually mind!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yaaay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Such a sweet baby.​ ​​
​​​ ​You can touch me more if you want.​ ​​
​​​ ​She gave you permission.​ ​​
​​​ ​"Touch her sweet pey-pey"...​ ​​
​​​ ​Touching her pey-pey?​ ​​
​​ ​What does that mean?​ ​​
​​​ ​Pey-pey is p—​ ​​
​​​ ​One moment please​ ​​
​​​ ​Those were all the words for today,​ ​​
​​​ ​but there's someone in the class​ ​​
​​ ​we haven't heard a story about yet...​ ​​
​​​ ​I have something to​ ​​
​​ ​spill about Fubuki-senpai.​ ​​
​​​ ​You do? Then please do share!​ ​​
​​​ ​Tell us!​ ​​
​​​ ​A long time ago, Fubuki-senpai...​ ​​
​​​ ​cut up a wild boar.​ ​​
​​​ ​She... cut it up?​ ​​
​​​ ​How so?​ ​​
​​​ ​Japanese is too hard for me,​ ​​
​​ ​so please tell them yourself.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well... Way back when I was a little kid,​ ​​
​​​ ​my grandpa accidentally​ ​​
​​​ ​ran over a wild boar.​ ​​
​​​ ​Boars often roam about​ ​​
​​ ​in the sticks, you see.​ ​​
​​​ ​Grandpa then brought the dead boar home​ ​​
​​​ ​and turned it into meat.​ ​​
​​​ ​You ate it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep! We did!​ ​​
​​​ ​And it was delicious.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, it was?​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you cut it up yourself?​ ​​
​​​ ​I just helped a little bit.​ ​​
​​​ ​Still, that's impressive.​ ​​
​​​ ​It was pretty gross, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well then, thank you for all your​ ​​
​​ ​fun and wacky stories.​ ​​
​​​ ​Subscribe to the hololive official​ ​​
​​ ​& our guests' channels!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm never coming back here.​ ​​
​​ ​You don't respect my privacy.​ ​​
​​​ ​No no, it's not like that!​ ​​
​​ ​It's for your own good.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's scary here.​ ​​
​​​ ​It is.​ ​​