​​​ ​Takanashi Kiara - DO U​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: Takanashi Kiara​ ​​
​​ ​Produced: KIRA​ ​​
​​​ ​Written: monii, Johnny​ ​​
​​ ​Lyrics: monii, KIRA​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooh​ ​​
​​​ ​Choreography: Kianna​ ​​
​​ ​Video: Kanauru​ ​​
​​​ ​Logo: Spiritsnare​ ​​
​​ ​Special thanks: Priichu!​ ​​
​​​ ​(K-I-R-A)​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't wanna stop it yet​ ​​
​​​ ​(Ooh-wah)​ ​​
​​​ ​Playin' Russian Roulette​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah boy as soon as I saw you I knew it​ ​​
​​​ ​Baby it's you, oh ya, now​ ​​
​​​ ​(Yeah)​ ​​
​​​ ​Got me love drunk I'm knocked down, down, down​ ​​
​​​ ​There's somethin' special about you​ ​​
​​​ ​(Uh-huh)​ ​​
​​​ ​When I see you I know it's true​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh ya, now​ ​​
​​​ ​Gotta getta ya, oh ya, now, now, now​ ​​
​​​ ​If it ain't you baby then I'm done​ ​​
​​​ ​(Yeah yeah oh girl, you know it!)​ ​​
​​​ ​I just can't resist you​ ​​
​​​ ​Your eyes are like a spell that I can't break through​ ​​
​​​ ​And that should scare me​ ​​
​​​ ​But I don't know baby​ ​​
​​​ ​You're captivating me​ ​​
​​​ ​And in the end you'll let me go​ ​​
​​​ ​That's just what we do...​ ​​
​​​ ​Love, Hate​ ​​
​​​ ​All the same​ ​​
​​​ ​If you know​ ​​
​​​ ​Play the game​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm all locked up-up inside​ ​​
​​​ ​No I can't fight the feeling and I won't try​ ​​
​​​ ​Love, Hate​ ​​
​​​ ​All the same​ ​​
​​​ ​If you know​ ​​
​​​ ​Play the game​ ​​
​​​ ​Baby you decide​ ​​
​​​ ​If you want me then shout it out right now!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Love is just a game​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't complain, I do the same, Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​DO U? DO U? Say​ ​​
​​​ ​You do feel the same​ ​​
​​​ ​Spark me like a flame​ ​​
​​​ ​I know I'll never be the same, Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​DO U? DO U?​ ​​
​​​ ​In the end love's just all a game​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't ever let yourself fall in​ ​​
​​​ ​(Yeah)​ ​​
​​​ ​You got it?​ ​​
​​​ ​(Uh)​ ​​
​​​ ​'Cause love's just like a toxin​ ​​
​​​ ​(Uh-Uh)​ ​​
​​​ ​The way pain is so common​ ​​
​​​ ​Your problem, I can't solve it!​ ​​
​​​ ​(Nope)​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm just a fool in love​ ​​
​​​ ​Know that this more than a crush​ ​​
​​​ ​(Ahh~)​ ​​
​​​ ​So you can't save me​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm in too deep​ ​​
​​​ ​And I love the rush, yeah​ ​​
​​​ ​I just can't resist you​ ​​
​​​ ​Your eyes are like a spell that I can't break through​ ​​
​​​ ​And that should scare me​ ​​
​​​ ​But I don't know baby​ ​​
​​​ ​You're captivating me​ ​​
​​​ ​And in the end you'll let me go​ ​​
​​​ ​That's just what we do...​ ​​
​​​ ​Love, Hate​ ​​
​​​ ​All the same​ ​​
​​​ ​If you know​ ​​
​​​ ​Play the game​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm all locked up-up inside​ ​​
​​​ ​No I can't fight the feeling and I won't try​ ​​
​​​ ​Love, Hate​ ​​
​​​ ​All the same​ ​​
​​​ ​If you know​ ​​
​​​ ​Play the game​ ​​
​​​ ​Baby you decide​ ​​
​​​ ​If you want me then shout it out right now!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Love is just a game​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't complain, I do the same, Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​DO U? DO U? Say​ ​​
​​​ ​You do feel the same​ ​​
​​​ ​Spark me like a flame​ ​​
​​​ ​I know I'll never be the same, Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​DO U? DO U?​ ​​
​​​ ​In the end love's just all a game​ ​​
​​​ ​(K-I-A-R-A!!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Got me breathless, oh yeah​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm by you night and day​ ​​
​​​ ​How can somethin' so wrong​ ​​
​​​ ​Be makin' me feel so right?​ ​​
​​​ ​Breakin' me down, down​ ​​
​​​ ​Pick me up just like you do​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm always coming back to you...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Love is just a game​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't complain, I do the same, Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​DO U? DO U? Say​ ​​
​​​ ​You do feel the same​ ​​
​​​ ​Spark me like a flame​ ​​
​​​ ​I know I'll never be the same, Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​DO U? DO U?​ ​​
​​​ ​In the end love's just all a game​ ​​
​​​ ​Love is just a game we play​ ​​
​​​ ​(Ooh woah)​ ​​
​​​ ​Love, Hate, Trust then Betray​ ​​
​​​ ​(Yeah)​ ​​
​​​ ​DO U? DO U? Say​ ​​
​​​ ​You do feel the same​ ​​
​​​ ​(La-La-Love me, too!!!)​ ​​
​​​ ​Love is just a game we play​ ​​
​​​ ​Love, Hate, Trust then Betray​ ​​
​​​ ​DO U? DO U?​ ​​
​​​ ​In the end love's just all a game...​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh Uh!​ ​​