foreign
[Music]
thank you
hello
[Music]
how is audio everyone how is audios
please let us know audio is good how
about you
why do the awkward potions look the same
as the water bottles because it's
awkward
[Music]
because I can't tell
exactly
oh God
um hi good a good message I am
officially in
um my like mess up base so at least now
I can come through don't ever
[Music]
love you I'll come back
I just left you oh wait you're getting
both yeah I have some extra bows they're
not very good though but don't worry
they'll become good I mean I think we
can buy some Enchantment
books
oh yeah you don't have the infinity ones
in your shop fauna yeah I don't have
infinity or wait where is uh funnest
town on your PVC right yeah okay I'll
see if I can it was that like at 1100
minus 200 it was that yes I'm too scared
to bring my elytra today so
I'm walking oh wait hold on I can use my
basement I forgot did it work
on a flashlight can I fix my oh I tried
FFF sometime
[Music]
anytime oh okay okay I'll do that
another time
is wrong to confirm can fix anything oh
I don't need Kyla to do it for me
oh are you dying no no no no I'm just
I'm just panicking a lot but um I think
I'm fine what am I missing to make a
potion of healing I'm just making fancy
water bottles what am I doing wrong
see to see this book over here yeah it
may have some uh uh oh my God
recipes it's my recipe book oh oh okay
but how do you make it oh what you need
you need you need sparkling melons for
healing potions what about a region how
do you know I
one
say hello yes tears I think was it oh oh
yeah I think it is gas tears
the thing I'm not sure if I have any
more
that sounds like nine
I'm okay oh that sounds like dead yeah
okay what the [\h__\h]
okay you must die I I'm because I'm in a
never I'm in another oh remember we're
gold yeah because I was so far away to
look for a cave to fight in for like 40
minutes then then I lost my I was out of
fireworks and then I had to find my way
back and I was in the middle of nowhere
and now I am traversing in the Never
back to home I am safe more or less I
just forgot I was in the Never
really I never found a cave though so
we'll find one together
so we can probably find it on like in
like a desert I think outside I
suggested I it would probably be okay I
think a cave would be easier but Laguna
said she has some caves true
wasn't it yeah wait did I say that why
would I say that a good bit now I don't
have the proof because I logged out
before but but but proof right here I
said a cave
um yeah
wait can't we make a cave to stick down
and like dig more you know make a big
hole Yeah just take a big hole digging
streets
basically no holes underground yeah
exactly yeah I made myself like a whole
huge hole and then I just came out in
the water
oh okay but I mean that is generally I
think a good option though
wait what
I am now back home where is everybody
I'm at home I'm playing with the alchemy
table if we couldn't do it I'm watching
her play with the Alchemy team pestering
fauna actually I look if I have more
arrows for I have a bunch of gear at my
snowy Village if we want to be there
I got some arrows as well I don't know
how many we need though I made like a
bunch of health potions too
um
hold on I feel like I I know I use the
bottlemelons making my potions sorry you
can share my questions but what am I
gonna do with this 64 Splash bottles now
oh my what do I do yeah I'll take some
I'll take you home
[Music]
but what do they do wait maybe maybe
wait wait I have a lot of gold maybe I
can make more spices
can you make spicy ones yeah
[Music]
yeah how
um
it's a business secret don't want anyone
else to get the idea
um excuse me
music is uh off off limits man
man what about it
Tom why is the second floor off limits
it has my precious
my precious my breakfast
hold on let me let me go make some
melons shiny melons
[Music]
um where is where is a melon
do you think oh I have some melons here
okay okay
golden carrots give some extra HP too
though don't they yeah
it's like hunger
yeah they increase your saturation which
is good
melon sees okay gotta have some I have
some sparkling melons for you wait where
are you guys sparkling
your makeup
fauna I have the Wither Skeleton skulls
right yes okay okay
um
she'll cry over shark has where if you
have coin
not sure if I have Soul Sand
Olson
Leo do we need salsa yeah
so I have one so Monday what am I doing
I should have more somewhere you're
talking
to bed what what did you do
nothing they're like nighttime cookie or
something without reading the Bedtime
Stories I'm not
okay do you have awkward potions
I mean splash water bottles
supposed to make awkward potions first I
think I missed his step
so you just have 64.
wait what it's just like water balloon
wait wait wait oh this is made of water
balloons that's actually
another good business idea I guess it's
good if uh someone's on fire but I have
one awkward splash potion what happened
to the rest of them
[Music]
make the base
okay I will try to find fauna now maybe
we should sleep present nighttime
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
everything's so messy I'm sorry guys my
house is a little loud
is everybody sleeping why not sleeping
going to sleep spend time
they're in my pockets good luck
I came back is it too early no
perfect
[Music]
Minecraft splash water bottle
splash water bottle why
why
oh gosh I have to I have to mute the
game again I turn it back on after that
is this the villagers
I saw a clip of you hating them
I just don't like this they make
they are yeah very very openly splash
potions why splash potions and water why
what I say Splat potion of water why not
what did I do
so many tend to make things awkward and
then how do you make them in the other
word you want you use the what the the
ward the little red house
neither what yes Another War that's how
I made them into Monday mundane
well there were forced yeah to make it
into awkward potions and then you add in
the melons
no okay now I have one wait is it like a
game of chance no
it is not do you have awkward potions
now I just made one from mundane
[Music]
maybe maybe we don't need potions so
much I've made 45
45 right we can use the water balloon
I'm sure it will help what if what if
someone catches a fire you know you
gotta use the water balloons you know
yeah I'll be bound to happen yes you
think you'll be healed you will be
healed
well we need a Healer in the group that
it's that easy
who's gonna be in charge of healing huh
wait that's not how Minecraft Works wait
there is no healing character what
why is there no healing staff or so in
Minecraft
let me cook America
I can throw potions on people right the
splash ones that's what I'm making it
feels everyone I think it's fauna this
way I think fun is probably the Spy PPP
okay
this is a
he's doing it she's doing the chat is it
possible to mend my things over there
still
yes
wait you can use
for fast amending I wanted to mend my
Elijah but I don't have to do it right
now you know girl there's two who came
to me stands right fast can you take me
to the oh wow
okay don't say I want to go
you're doing great though you're doing
great
okay
we
what does mundane do
I don't think
I raised it to the max
um hello it gives you encouragement
[Music]
there we go
you made it
[Music]
don't worry about it
I'm walking though
I think I think she's good it wasn't
even
a bag sorry
hey is this guy like immune to anything
specific
[Music]
um well I have swords then he's weak to
for everyone
excellent I have one backup sword for
myself
and an ax oops
[Music]
yes please okay let's set things on fire
again we may becoming a Firebird I
apparently the Wither is weak to Smite I
do have a sword
never you've never used this machine
before it's their first time seeing it
because every time Kyla said oh don't
worry and then she came back and I never
questioned her will you you want to mend
it right yeah does it have mending on it
yeah then you just have to wear it and
then go smack the fish
gently the fish oh
[Applause]
that's what man does it makes it when
you get XP it will heal it
I'm going in there upstairs enough
oh use that use the sword in here though
I have good intentions
oh oh it's fine you could have left it
there oh it's back in the box now okay
oh this is the newest model it is
[Music]
all right
yeah
look this is an invisibility potion
watch this ready oh
my God where'd you go
where'd you go back
[Music]
sounds good
in the basement I mean
[Music]
wait what it I'm gonna guess
negative 1 100 and and no I
[Music]
describe the terrain oh hello
okay I follow you Sonia well you know
it's on this cake
oh
on this cake
now no not that big
what is this where's she hiding that
oh my God
I'm too scared to know where that goes
here wait I found a man
[Music]
we can wait for her we can wait for him
all right okay
oh I need to do something after we go to
FFF
um
[Music]
um it teleports the fish from the
guardian Farm or from the monument up
there
oh
[Music]
it's gone
I don't know portals that mind broke you
yes ah good to know but it wasn't my
fault I built it correctly the server
plug-in was outdated yeah yeah fun I
keep on telling yourself that
[Music]
but you don't need bread
just take the golden carrots they're
better okay wait where are we meeting in
the fish tomorrow
only if you need anything from the fish
farm maybe can you show everyone else to
wear the house is
wait I'm running out of rockets does
anybody have anybody have rockets that
they could lend oh so you have to Kiara
you have to like jump up and then close
the trap door right there oh yeah yeah
it's been a while thank you and there's
a sword you can use in here
oh
there's an extra bow in one of the
chests at the house maybe my black
coffee is better news with good on what
um
how do I wait when something doesn't
happen
oh
no this
is half man half mending
anything yeah it's okay I want to amend
my pickaxe though I
puppies
uh okay I have to have one in my hand
right
[Music]
this time all right
my cards in here
mommy
oh well this is fine I can enjoy my
fries
rise it's not working are you using the
sword
I'm using my own mending sword
they're hurting because there's a
sweeping Edge on it
oh
does your sword have sweeping Edge
no she used the fish sword okay fish
sword fish sword
[Music]
oh yeah okay that's faster that's it I'm
walking
here is fish sword back thank you I'm
camping
think I'm good um okay
[Music]
I think I think Watson really needs a
little bit of a maintenance
yeah oops we can go back
it is like almost three years old now
it doesn't need a little bit
[Music]
um
I'm beating her
[Music]
this is
taking too long
the room till my my mom gets home wait
wanna you should be the one okay I'll
drive I don't know where I am
okay
[Music]
I'll hit your head where's
do you see that no no oh I can imagine
over there you did not awkwardly splash
or did you maybe you did you're just
like a wasp flying around I can't
believe
did you did you drink that potion
what potion of course slash potion
fake monster in the sky
hello this is almost turned out it's so
cute all of a sudden there's lamps it
wasn't like this back in the day
wait lamb swear like that's the entrance
of the Railway oh yeah they changed them
I was shocked too
what is this there's berries planted
here
would that have been
rainy and Mumbai oh bird gravy hey bird
gravy we can try to sleep oh did you
read that
the message and just kick these guys out
oh wait can I sleep get out of my bed I
think there's beds up there I remember
there's two beds upstairs
I'm in one of them
I don't see anyone here oh wait wait
where where are you
Shack
all right mommy is
the coordinates are 1100 minus 200.
there's like a building with a Red Roof
is that one
[Music]
mine I Got One Singular 1100 minus 200.
okay no no this way
[Laughter]
what
[Music]
holy moly you're so much
is this west side door opening race
door
no I'm still salty
this is the last okay now even we're in
front of the same door I see houses
[Music]
a weapon a weapon a weapon yeah a weapon
indeed training yes please it just has
like half a
half thing but I think I think will be
fun used to be dead oh you revived it
wow wait can I take from the shulker box
there's a bow here
wait 30 day free trials wait wait wait
is this a paid subscription
well
you gonna be a free trial no which my
version is there another one wait you
take our credit card once my Smite is
gonna be really strong against the
weather so even if you have another
sword I would recommend using this one
let me look strong against him
did they go into your Instagram
automatically renew but you can cancel
it before then if you remember I think
fauna picked up arrows oh
I think it's a new inventory maybe I got
I got them I got them oh this is
everyone
in the house oh in the big house in the
house
in the big house
it's got Red Roof wait should I take
this bow or no I'll keep this one
because I see their names because Kiara
gave it to me
um I should take okay 30-day trial
without you're not asking for my credit
card before right and you're not going
to charge you have to right put on your
credit card and it will automatically
charge you when the trial is down but
you can cancel anytime you can just give
me a call
[Music]
I'll do that later okay
um that must be
in there huh where are you Inna it's
cool though where are you
come inside let me just light up a match
ing it
you
should we bring back up armor phone yeah
come in come in because I have one set
for myself but should we have like
backup armor in case we die and lose it
I mean I don't know how we would lose
the armor we can bring that and put it
in chest
I mean there's not gonna be like I don't
know did the withers explosions delete
items he explodes yeah
oh raw chicken oh no mama oh
[Music]
yeah
switch switch
I'm gonna take this because it's here
okay yeah everyone can take a set of
armor it's bothering me
what I want oh I see
oh okay
oh well
how do we take the armor from here
click it
I took two pairs of pants sorry yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah absolutely move
those to you
[Music]
oops
translate number 47 by Karen Carr no
cute what does it says
[Music]
wait did everybody grab their helmet
I think oh I have one with name oh oh
wait is this is cute they have names
actually mean by someone else
one more try
oh yeah who the [\h__\h] is
now yeah yeah you see that dirt yeah
yeah let's see this dirt I'm gonna take
this dirt that dirt let's eat it
this is fun do it I'll give you a dollar
do it oh
all right all right I'm gonna eat it
okay okay
everybody watch um um hold on hold on
I already watched
oh wait
can can you hit me once I'm not hungry
enough
wait tell me again
the harder
what are you doing wait no I'll I'll
just hit you
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay I'm
gonna eat this I'm gonna eat this dirt
okay okay
so everyone should take at least one
stack of golden carrots and that's the
food you should eat because there were
stores your saturation better
so it's like how that how hungry you are
it keeps you full longer you can
restores your health better so you don't
know the Wither effect it's the one that
makes your hearts go black and you take
damage and you can't see your health so
oh yeah just try to eat always like
always constantly eat your carrots okay
okay
more than one yeah
okay what about I need to get out my
potions
[Music]
I'll just start with this and someone
doesn't have their smiled sword everyone
should have one Smite sword you should
use that one
so your items might get blown up by the
withers so you can just leave your items
here and just use the
Smite sword probably did you throw a
string at me or what item would I use I
guess I should leave my fishing rod do
you have a seven attackers I only have a
armor stand yeah it'll be good against
the Wither nice extra damage from it
yeah probably leave your Elijah just in
case
I need one more for what um I need to
make a bow to repair my bow oh
wait I have a bowl
do you wanna know
but isn't it like a like an unenchanted
one yeah oh this is power Five Below in
here if you want to use that instead of
no one use my own ball
um I'm very good at hydrating so I'm
going to go to an idol meeting I'll be
right back okay I'm ready I'm ready
ready so you yeah oh one level I am also
ready
hi ladies
hi I need one level
I'm gonna trade with villagers Maybe
there's some emeralds
though I don't remember
[Music]
what do you want oh
oh
my God
I think Yoshi music has to be the most
empty-headed music I've ever heard
I am I want UFC music too
what's in here
in the basement
do you have some MRI that would be my
training Emporium where everyone works
willingly and happily
of course
unlike phoenixden
Phoenix
well everybody works indeed happily
truthfully happily there uh-huh it's not
a lie
down
see he's so happy he just needs to spin
all day long why does he not let me go
down
yeah he heard you insulting his his
co-workers
are we going to do something about this
guy punch him in the nose don't punch
him don't punch him he's got a buddy
right here
oh that's right well I'll just we'll
just Bonk him in the nose he will win
four against one five how many ones yeah
what do you see outside
he's got buddies well I got buddies
like you I'm I cannot
that's a pit bull he probably can fit
through the door even he's too big big
boy I see you and shiny
oh no I brought chicken I'm going to die
huh
okay oh wait the window is open
what are we going
oh yeah are we are you almost ready
I'm ready oops I'm ready ready ready
ready
yes am I ready
okay wait wait these are shared sound
effects huh I guess I'll just oh our
Lantern
Sheraton oh we should bring beds
[Music]
oh yeah I should probably bring some we
want buddy
big old head full of iron nothing else
alloy looking
knife okay what was I doing oh yeah
yes do you have the app
I don't know what is the app oh
it's copyright
dictionary.com there's all of them on
the PC wait I don't know if I do that
one oh I was doing them on the PC no I
do them on my phone because I'm lazy I
think the phone would be better because
I can do it when I'm busy yeah yeah I'm
really bad I had a great one today
does everyone have a bag
it's actually a red bed I mean yes you
have it in here no wait I have no I'm
gonna bring your bed upstairs not from
upstairs does anyone need an extra bed
I need a bed wait do we bring one do we
blow up
we need to everyone in their inventory
yes okay I require a bed please thank
you sorry there's one bed in here thank
you sorry I'm annoying I'm sorry I'm
sorry sorry oh no me I'll borrow this
bowl
it's a bad couple
and I have
can I see yeah
here's another bed
one you got a cookie that doesn't have
any nutritional value we have a
sleepover before we go we have like one
big situation values
we pushing our beds together before
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's so bad at everything we should wear
matches
[Music]
without it wasn't even on purpose but we
just so happened to have the same
pajamas that's cute
did somebody take my bed
what color is yeah I did here you go
wait
yes thank you
okay can we do a checklist yeah yeah
card you have the three wither skulls I
have them in my never in my inner chest
yes okay you have to bring them yes okay
I'm just keeping them there for safety I
was gonna bring another and the chance
to just place it wherever we do it um
true true that's a good idea does
everyone have a bed yes yes does
everyone have at least one stack of
golden carrots yes
does everyone have at least three totems
of undying yes yes
I'll take one more okay yes keep it in
your off hand at all times yeah everyone
have a Smite five sword yeah yes
everyone have a bow
with arrows yes yes yes okay I think
that's a good don't send
oh okay okay let's go again where do we
go though we don't have a location yeah
we should go very far away desert
or came I think cave is slightly easier
but I think we could handle a desert too
are we bringing elytra's or are we
walking down
there
[Music]
away from home what about source
so we should probably go through the
nether
okay I mean yeah we can take one of
those exits wherever it leads us
I tried my exit but there's like so much
Messa around it I feel bad for doing it
that's true
where would be a good place
was chatting
The bunkeroni's Underground King
oh that is an idea
just just joke
[Music]
for protection not for fighting in
um
area somewhere where I lost my Ikea fish
but that has like it was pretty big I'm
right here I'm not sure where that
actually wasn't the resource server
actually back in the day so good I don't
jump
[Music]
um
let's do a backflip no do we um
ready
[Music]
nice
don't even
[Laughter]
think where do we go
um we can go to a desert maybe
I still don't see why we can't dig a
hole we can let's just take the cheese
Strat like I think it'll be really easy
oh yeah it looked really easy yeah okay
so we're gonna run around like chickens
with our heads I don't think we should
choose it I mean we don't need all of
this stuff do we have okay
women don't scare my viewers please with
your statements oh did you know that
grotesque did you
[Music]
no no what would you know what I say I
have to confirm with Google because I
forgot the exact amount of time that a
chicken will keep running with its head
off oh
is that why there's the face or phrase
all running around like a headless
chicken yeah
where are we walking we should probably
walk why not both oh
it's a long way oh hello creature
creature
you get here oh oh oh there's more rails
here what where does it go oh there's
quite a few what how many I go left or
right that's why I am
be free be free be free
did you kill it it's gone no it's on the
rainbow how far we go
just to use the nether portal this is
where the bunkeronians yeah
what
there's rails to it
yes
I I I just missed you I missed you you
couldn't shoot me in the head for that
that's good man oh I'm craving your
attention he has my full attention my
popcorn there's no need to shoot me in
the head okay
[Music]
yeah
never mind when do we get off yes what
what were you saying are you smell the
butternut I don't know if you want to
know is it about the chicken it's about
oh yeah
about a certain chicken a certain
chicken named Mike apparently I lived
for 18 months after his head had been
cut off
what
what apparently what I don't know what
does it mean by live yeah
what was
what on Earth
is it like the opposite of dead inside
is it like a rose right inside but then
outside
I'm just gonna live forever
but this is a chicken
that's true like
um
it was determined that ax had missed the
jugular vein and a clot had prevented
Mike from bleeding to death although
most of his head
[Music]
he's gone what was the chicken's name
Mike wait no bye I'm bad
I was Googling stuff are we did you guys
run off but when I should have gotten
off I
got I stopped I have to it probably got
pushed back yeah
Google I was learning about mine
we really need someone like Muma and our
team otherwise it will be over too fast
yeah
we need those pictures
caught AFK in 4k
[Music]
bringing another card with her oh okay
I'm all right where are we going this
way
oh don't look at the Endings by the way
don't look at what oh
is it up or down down down
I almost looked that down
[Music]
remember I closed the door behind you
oh
oh yes I still have foxes this is
crony's Bunker yeah oh I've never been
here before out of respect
oh this is like a sauna but actually
this is snow this used to be my room oh
it was full snakes
[Music]
they're all gone oh there's a point on
here why one of them ended up in the
room we're gonna go through this portal
okay foxes sound like chickens
I guess foxes say book book but we need
like a golden helmet it'll be fine I
have nothing bold I have something going
you have your heart
oh that was so cold
[Music]
okay
oh I remember this place I helped I
think
this brings about many memories ages ago
when I actually I told her to play
Minecraft totem works on its own if you
have it in one of your hands
ideally The Shield hand I I've heard I
don't have a shield it's fine we need
those okay okay okay just keep a totem
in that hand yeah just eat all the time
okay always eat carrots always eat
carrots okay
I eat Berry for now though you know
these potions would be a lot better if
you could stack them yeah yeah it's kind
of bad you can't
why am I fat I'm faster oh I wasn't
running but
you can run
[Music]
oh flying cat
cute
yeah
good how is that really go back
endlessly
um
I was thinking it was a person making a
cat noise and thinking we're saying how
cute to a person again
you really is a cat it's like a cat
that's not something
it's a it's a cat voice actor you know
look
yeah the guest
oh there's a cat yeah have you heard the
slowed down voice of Yoshi speaking of
no no no no like some dude going Yoshi
and I just set it up really fast or
whatever
[Music]
the Yoshi kick today because I'm I've
had Yoshi music
besides me
[Music]
and I was told it was what you expected
it to be and I expect it to be a minions
I forgot
are they still here
oh they're still here
no we lost you guys because you ran so
fast actually
behind you but I sprinted I'm tired
I eat my cookies
I'll see you guys in the moment I'll be
right there okay
are we going to where the weather is I
don't know he will be wherever we went
into this running oh
what happens if you're nice to the
Wither is he nice to you no he gives you
a kiss
he will give you a rose romantic Rose
are you supposed am I supposed to do it
there's a zombie
wait was that a Wither that beat me up
if you don't have to fight Legend this
one is nice
did you wait for me yeah oh yeah why are
you so sweet I'm not gonna leave you
behind I actually got jump scared let's
see your face
thank you oh they're going here I think
this one let me check
I'll see
oh wait maybe not this you're wasting
arrows
y
oh yeah this
one's good chicken and cow
s
anyone know that show
the chicken couch yeah
very cursed shell like the sausage man
is that the claymation show
Mr meteor cursed puppets
um
so we might want to sleep outside not
inside
you here
yep look through the portal
okay were they were they puppets and not
claiming oh wait they were pugs go to
sleep
again I think I forgot that it was um oh
my gosh I've I'm gonna look up a picture
is that for some reason
the Mr meene show I think
wait a minute my hand's meaty me is this
oh oops Yeah
we can leave our beds here oh no I just
picked it up we're gonna put it back
down inside your spawn I put it down a
bunny
wait don't leave me I'm looking up
things
[Music]
okay
did you do that everyone ready yes
wait not the rabbit again
[Music]
oh creeper oh man
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum powder
um
[Music]
so many creepers
wait there's not a parent like careful
there's a creeper over there oh there's
a lot of creepers oh there's another
creeper yeah which one it is
someone's been here there's even an
Ender Chest here noise whoa what
happened to you
oh
yeah Withers
this is a nice open area for me yeah we
should go a little further how do you
get the birds
[Music]
he's green oh they want a cracker silly
cookies
I think they patched it they used to
your parents could eat cookies but
parrots can't eat chocolate in real life
so they had to take it out make sense I
thought I had my Legend oh is that
Jungle by all over there
okay
um
[Music]
we all here don't worry we're not
running away fauna yes this will be a
good experience for you
[Music]
maybe there could be a cave
no wrangling necessary or wrangling
ourselves
[Music]
I'm wrangling with myself
oh
that's the
wrangling and mangling is this
and wrangling we can mangle the winner
together and go
are we still looking for a cave just one
big open space
it was okay
it was okay my cave doesn't it came out
of the block or something I don't know
how big it is but there was a cave
wait what's the Strat here because we're
in a wide open space
um so he could fly yeah so he might like
we can like fly away and
oh
I'm gonna choose it's absolutely not the
same one but they could be close holy
cow it's halfway to Halloween wait wait
wait what was that
what was the Austria
red white it's red red wait look it's
red white red there
[Music]
[Laughter]
you and your your knowledge is
hmm
I have about his
I'll be honest I just
[Music]
didn't
eat here
we could hide him here probably
Gerudo Valley's playing yeah I think
Gary do I get weird are you sure again
[Music]
where is everyone
waiting
would be the one to get lost in that
movie or so
hey if I'm not doing like things I'm I'm
I I'm good
the light
[Music]
where is she
um
130 minus 8 300. go to the top and look
down do you see Mesa
I see Mesa I'm still on the sand I see
you stop moving stop
stop
hello there you are hello I remember
where the beds are you have such good
memories
oh this bunny should get out of here
this is dangerous
I feel bad yeah for real for real yeah
in the open why not should we go to
Party holes
emergency hidey hole oh that's all right
I gotta get good out here
is it
an emergency uh I have no blocks to get
up oh yeah
good broad blocks naturally
I can place my end just somewhere there
seems to be a big hole down there I'm
kind of scared oh yeah maybe we should
place the under chest in this hole that
way it doesn't get exploded don't you
think that we
should have brought our beds a little
closer well he's he might wander is the
thing
you can try again
so I don't want him to blow up our beds
[Music]
that would be bad yes
I don't know maybe it's too far
I think it's that far no to walk back
um
yeah that is a that is a good option
what's the shortcut to putting is there
a shortcut to putting something quickly
in your right hand
um from your toolbar FF
okay nice we could if this game against
the feds and then we could like bury
them
[Music]
it's not that very momentum
I didn't realize how I said it
I mean
she's all exactly
Berry the best
I guess it should be fine I guess
I think he'll be okay I think it's fine
you guys could dig up some which is
[Music]
oh okay closer
finding here
I'm sure we'll be fine oh my God
Rabbit Man
don't want it too far too far you get
lost whoa there's a nice big ass cave
over here and we're just gonna ignore it
here how big is it here never ignore it
it's a huge oh if you want to find the
one that doesn't win right there it's
it's almost too big where are the ashes
yeah the odd some girls are seeing it
did I see it water
[Music]
people
toilet paper toilet paper
I mean
I'm just gonna Flex my bow skills
bet you can't hit a moving Target oh
I didn't say I was the target wow oh wow
very fast
[Music]
I'm getting real low getting dark oh
I have I have my light sticks
[Music]
I almost killed myself
excuse me I don't wanna do you wanna no
I don't wanna no it's Gonna Fill my
[Music]
particle
it's really the error of my ways is this
the twerking rabbit it is it's the dumpy
rabbit oh yeah
[Music]
I forgot where you guys are or is that
you that's you
I I literally
[Laughter]
hit sorry I didn't even do that I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
as a family no we were camping right now
[Music]
but I can't sleep bedtime you need some
melatonini
can we tell all these stories before we
sleep
back in my day
in Minecraft I had a dream about hell
last night
it was so good everyone fell asleep and
woke up in the morning
okay we should put the beds um
should we put the beds in the cave
okay no no follow me there's like behind
you there I'm playing horse race steam
currently it's really good music
weather
where was it epic soundtrack yeah wow
battle music careful
I I forgot where it was
it was this way it was by the cactine
which one the flashlight is here
why do you remember better than me
bigger brain the candles
that's just because you have a bigger
hand go down I was gonna say have you
seen the size of it
oh yeah that was it
[Music]
and we could also find the weather here
but I guess not
[Music]
oh yeah see it's it it's huge
has nice shade too so we don't get
sunburn nice
but I probably have already gotten a
sunburn
oh yeah
the only thing is maybe hard too
get out of the cave
can make okay we can at least put our
beds here yeah it should be safe right
yeah but it's not that enclosed is the
thing
[Music]
digging a hole for the beds okay
bye-bye cave I will explore you one day
surely wait wait
I'm getting huge stroke
okay
water bottles like that sorry put out of
the class it's my fault that you're
getting a heat stroke
here oh chest question yeah although
it's sand here maybe like right here
it's unsanitary
oh
[Music]
nobody uses our board
oh
oh thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
I got lanterns I can put some nice
lanterns down here
um I'm just a little worried like if the
if it blows up the beds that would be
really bad so like oh yeah dude maybe we
should dig it a little deeper
we gotta go deeper
because then we'll respawn like back at
spawn and that one unfortunately that's
very far
laughs
that's good yeah oh should be good
I don't think he can fit in here did you
know that they reverse engineered Roman
concrete
[Music]
I told my chapters they found out that
there's a lime inside of it and lime is
like a self-hit it was like when it when
it got wet lime would expand and
self-heal the concrete because like how
did this live for so many billion years
it's pretty cool
lime it's also like the new cars have
you seen the new car grills lime if you
pour water on it it self heals the
scratches we live in a crazy it is crazy
times
it will dissolve with acid rain no lime
I guess I didn't have that but
okay
is that cool inside yeah very important
extremely important touch the bed that's
the bench depends oh wait only one bed I
have milk I have only one is fine lots
of beds lots of beds beds beds beds
[Music]
I think I touched it I'm gonna do a
double chicken just to be safe
wait actually I don't know if I don't
trust my touch touch touch okay I touch
I'll do it one more time as well just in
case oh now you're making me questions
are you sure you touched the best are
you sure did you really touch it maybe
you should touch it again you can never
be sure
if you don't oh there's something left
do you touch the pillow when my channel
right after I saved the game did you
save the game Kiowa but maybe you should
save the game I just saved I just saved
honestly you cannot receive enough when
you're working on something you know
it's trying
videos I'm scared this is a lot of
anticipation right now I can't get in
that looks so nice Oh
I thought it was nice huh very nice I
think this has to be one one Higher yeah
I don't know
nice beautiful
all right all right
I feel like we should fill this in
because there's a giant falling Pit of
Doom where's the under chest yeah right
here but we could go like over here and
spawn oh [\h__\h] anyway
foreign
[Music]
how does this happen what's gonna happen
I didn't Google or study before he has
two phases the first one he flies around
and shoots explosions at you so hit him
with your bow and eat as many carrots as
you can he's gonna give you the Wither
effect so you won't be able to see your
health you're always going to be losing
hell so just eat as much as you can
and then he'll have a second phase where
he goes to the ground and spawns
skeletons and that's when you want to
hit him with the Smite sword
and you should die fast and just keep
eating and try not to die
would you say that orange shoots then
one each then one shoots then one each
is a is a good way to go or should it be
like
I should have waited one huge one we
should eat oh should I use do it should
we spell or the potions or like
yeah I have some pretty
people I didn't bring any so maybe it's
okay I'm strong
on my own
I believe in the potion chest outside
[Music]
oh okay
I might have exploded if you put it
outside
there will be a lot of explosions that
is true the boom booms and he can
destroy items with his explosions so oh
oh don't worry
Kelly
scaling skello skill the tone okay this
is fine I'm sure this is fine run around
run around shoot run around
shoot eat shoot oh okay okay are there
any more dangerous holes
bottom a little further away probably
like over there yeah
oh flat round area here he'll probably
like move around quite a bit though so
okay right here seems like a good place
to be able to see
okay there's another massive cave over
here oh my God is this the same one
[Laughter]
she's doing it she's doing it are you
doing it oh yeah there's everyone ready
just on top right little stubbies three
on top
one
of my face should we sleep first or no
no more no more why are we Sleeping Sun
is kind of exciting it's fine my bow is
ready I'm gonna get the first shot
doing it
it's kind of small wait he's does he he
doesn't take damage yet does he him yeah
[Music]
right I think
running away
[Music]
why are you running
movies
[Music]
oh I got him
come on guys
I'm
way too far away
I need a hint compilation
he's he's on that strong noon
he sucks look he sucks
I'm missing I'm missing things
is
Flash oh gosh he's almost half pounds
[Music]
I don't know I'm still running though
nice nice Nina you're ready for a
marathon I'm so scary
I hit him
[Music]
[Applause]
is that it is that was weird that was
pretty easy
that was it we did it
[Music]
yeah
the Stars the superstar
that was blame I want another one no it
took so long to get the skulls though oh
yeah that was way more difficult
[Music]
all right
looks like a tree star yeah I deserve it
I did the most work I'm just kidding
yeah how many gold medals do you have I
have gold
there's Golds no
I'll try to make a joke
[Music]
I have gold defense I have gold healing
and I have gold
um where's the Platinum wait so I made
all these potions with nothing yeah
who wants to stop
[Music]
who shot me
let's go for the next let's go let's go
yeah the morning is terrifying nothing's
terrifying with this team of
professional Killers
now oh watch out for the creeper
who am I saying that too
time for bed
[Music]
we only have we're missing the bed all
right
it's like Tetris down here
um
square meters square square feet
that's mine
I went into I don't feel like I should
hold sorry another star or maybe I
should because I feel like uh maybe
Ivana is the most responsible here
because Kiara's idea though so she
should maybe maybe Kiara should hold the
nether star oh yeah and here too oh we
have to take a picture anyway yeah
oh yes sorry
no we can take a photo and somebody can
draw a really bad Ms paint one and like
him in the background or something oh
yeah
[Music]
this dude almost looks like him
close enough
is that a zombie
yeah lizard zombies
in front of our cave how about that yeah
we could build a little like like this
oh you still have more salsa
we can pretend
oh yeah I was like oh yeah we're about
to summon it right now
we need to find skulls yeah you can
always summon another if you have kids I
want somebody's trying to help too oh
you know what if you stand behind on a
block behind you could look like the
head babe
wait I have I have two
[Music]
yeah
look
[Music]
that's the ID wither
Kyla who's got Kyla's name
I have no head at all even even at home
and my base
yeah it's okay so I might take a take a
while to get it but
we can't we can't we can't put one
remember because it's like
there's one oh yeah
summons though
but then I can't take the picture where
I want some is Kyla
she is the final boss
uh yeah be better if someone yeah hello
uh um
[Music]
can you stand next to Google
I got space
that was a good shot okay and cheese
[Music]
F2
yeah wait I want to take one more
wait can we all squeeze in here you can
squeeze in there oh hold on
I can do two rows there we go can we get
the sorority squats
yeah cute
cute thank you
[Music]
or more
everyone say cheese
[Music]
I'm good
and now and now don't forget the heads
I don't know what man I mean we can we
can rage something
we carry the
uh I don't know we can talk about our
deepest darkest fears
it's you Mommy
oh
should we go make a beacon
what's up you can do you shoot the light
up in the sky yeah it makes the bacon
Megan do we have made it do we know
where we want the beacon no
yeah I do not care at all where it goes
I'll stole it my eyes
can you imagine if it actually like
summons something can we put three of
them did you get it no no I did I did I
did I did oh thank you
let me know when you don't need the
chest anymore the under chest
is someone a gold star
that should go into the end of chest
yeah yeah
okay okay
[Music]
I think it should go wherever fauna
wants it she's the most active out of
all of us I think
but yeah we can discuss that maybe in
our Minecraft Discord
uh for real though like what I mean I
guess I should be happy that it ended
early because it's like half past one
a.m here
we are efficient as a team yeah exactly
but for real then let's next do the
warden that's so difficult it's really
difficult that girl is going in her
basement yeah how did she do that how
did she bring him to her basement like I
don't know
[Music]
I want to fight the warden
the other day
okay I could help you guys fight the war
yeah
okay woman yeah
where are you yeah
thank you
yeah the warden isn't meant to be fight
but I think with our strong ass team I
feel feel like we're perfect we're a
good match for it hell yeah
we have to first set off
[Music]
um we should oh my God have you girls
noticed how in the Japanese server they
all like their their guilds now they're
they have guilts we should yeah fighting
Guild too well they have guilt what do
we call it
um are we killed are we construction or
fighting or both we're we're fighting at
least fighting we're just gonna be the
party tree
[Music]
Phoenix
Sunset oh it could be strong
it's for what what's that
I don't know
but you have to separate it
Channel
a shark shark attack tackle owl nature
Kiana I'm the only one with the name
shark owl what'd you say
taco owl nature shark tacos
yeah I guess we're the stunks wait which
one am I oh
owl this dog
well this song sounds like something
oh yeah we're making stonks with our
with the quests that we fulfill in our
Guild it's true we have the economy
behind us like look at our fancy gear we
have so much stuff wow
we're gonna make even more stunks I did
like I do like stonks wait if we make it
wait when we move to make a guild base
oh good good idea yeah should we make it
in the new server because I haven't
built anything yes yes yes
oh should we uh I mean if we're gonna do
something big we might want to do it
another time if we want to make
something small we could do it now I
mean we can at least like claim a ground
or something okay because it's breaking
ground
we should probably sleep okay oh yeah
yeah thanks
claim a ground for free free real estate
sauce hi
seal it up lies lies
I can trust no let me sleep outside oh
wow you cut it off here can we make a
Guild Art out there
a gold one
oh yes oh yeah yeah who's out here
disturbing the peace
am I the enemy I don't know oh never
mind
bring your bed coming
[Music]
okay I'm coming upstairs I'm putting it
down okay
he's ready for you okay thank you
thank you room service how long was the
weather her life like three minutes
that's so sad I don't think my bgm even
looped once
I mean he's gonna look epic he has an
epic bgm and I don't think it even got
to finish I was just like one of those
people who are like on their jogs with
their their earbuds in with like Luffy
playing except there's like the world is
burning and exploding around them
they're just chilling when the world's
ending and you have to listen to One
Last Song but I'm just listening to some
loafy
and
[Music]
um
what does Wi-Fi stand for
wireless internet is fun interesting
Wireless
[Music]
why why
it doesn't stand for anything
come from Wireless
apparently it's wireless fidelity Wi-Fi
what is wireless wait we what's we in
what does it mean why why why
I'm fine why not fine
[Music]
infidelity is that when someone cheats
on someone
[Music]
well it could be an Infidel yeah that's
the word I think of
Infidel it just means a traitor right
which is also someone who practices
infidelity the enemy
um
the wireless briefly is the opposite of
that movie hmm
what
we got tickets
[Music]
I'll be back no that's not quite it it's
in the forest right so that weird ones
[Music]
over here it looks like a spine
where's everyone
um
look up look up
what
look up where's the door down from the
tower though
Woods
and the ones
the second time I'm
[Music]
coming for you
you've deserted your sense of direction
where is she I do not want the horse now
ah now you're on the phone it's not very
deep in the forest
very deep I'm going up oh is that the
tower the big red Tower yeah oh no
I can't find I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine
oh I see your name I see you guys
okay I'm here hello
hello
it's right here oh
sure it is right here well
oh is that the Mark is oh
[Music]
wow
oh yeah oh
oh he doesn't care about no gold that
guy is nice that was too dead inside to
know or want anything material in this
world man
[Music]
oh man
no chicken
can't
yeah
are we just naming animals we know now
what am I I'm thinking of something but
it's not
I don't know never mind nothing no it
said something but I can't tell you so
it's not nothing it's not nothing it's
something cat dog
no that's not that's a that's a great
thing to think about but that's not what
I'm thinking about it looks kind of
scary
what kind of shark are you in shark form
because I watched the shark tier list I
just want to know in one hammer how
Frank you are I'm a seven shark salmon
no but yes it is a thing it's a thing it
wasn't in the tearless so it probably
isn't really relevant is it no it sounds
like whoever made
people about sharks who made the stair
list here
therapist level
can I send you the videos they're so
good they just chose generic ones
because they don't know anything they
just go hold
sharks
specialty of a salmon shark what does a
salmon shark do uh no they look like
tiny gray ones they look really angry
but they're really small you can pick
them up with your hands and stuff they
don't do much
they might I'm not sure do they eat
salmon
I don't know
homes but I don't know is
more of a salmon then
[Music]
it sounds like a shark
what if it's just like a salmon and then
it goes like
I want to be a shark so it's a salmon
shark no he's he's shark I promise you
it's a shark
probably called a salmon shark because
they eat salmon maybe or they're small
like a snacks
salmon what color but which side which
salmon oh I walked into a wall it's
smelling cute
foreign
that's all I have I have no other
information about this
[Music]
so how how do you not know what else you
want to know how much life expectancy
it looks like it's the size of a salmon
oh I don't know your suspects I want to
know you are my stats your stealth your
intelligence your your stamina your HP
your defense I don't know at all you've
been playing too much of that jrpg game
[Music]
oh baby yes that was an emblem of flames
or whatever it's called friends at a
house that's on fire part 300 I want to
is there three of them
I had 90 hours of gameplay in that time
lord
990 hours yeah 90 hours of reading the
longest game you girls ever played game
with the most hours
um
[Music]
I know
wait you guys wanted to fight more right
yeah
[Music]
pretty jelly
um slinkies
okay nice cleanup okay
clean it up somebody said fauna's DOTA
for sure
it is
okay okay
maybe like Sims 2
I don't know if I would even count these
kind of like endless going games though
I mean like something that I can end at
what point do you count like MMOs to you
know like play time on them
they also don't count in that manner
around me
Servo
I'm so excited
[Music]
everybody has seen the new Sarah by now
right or you know yeah hasn't maybe I
have yeah okay okay that's where I found
the hoarding you know
oh did you just walk into oh sorry
wait well that means what type of owl
are you
uh are you a snowy owl
change my my type of owl if I'm if I'm
stupid I'm bar now uh-huh what the barn
owls are cute they're screechy though
and annoying yes you fit yeah and
they're stupid oh you're not screechy
though or wait or annoying you're
neither you're neither you're neither of
those things
berries
if you like the warden wouldn't kill us
but berries would
have the berry bushes the bear bushes
will definitely kill me one day
[Music]
I don't know where the portals are
except beer is it a mythological
creature yeah no I mean no it's
experience Kieran I'm kidding I've never
oh
drink they make mini drinks
yeah like everything I drink in Japan
was clearing brand it's so good it feels
like royalty
I'm not but was it really tea
what would it be otherwise I'm lost I'll
come back hi loss how are you was I'm
not lost
I'm not lost
let's shoot an arrow for you here you go
I
owned it
it's not lost you know
understandable me
feel the water
never find
oh there she is so you
hello
yellow is over there she's gone
so about hitting those moving cars
are you stood in front of it you still
you
you have no gun safety your gun safety
skills are
[Music]
I have sword safety but I'm gonna throw
it out the window oh I fell I'll forgive
you this stuff
it's like it's like
moments
rejecting
you're part of this guilt now you have
things to do no there's some suspicious
things going on in this in in here no
there's there's there there's you know
teams and those suspicious why are you
stuttering it's team building
that kid
I don't want to say something
yes say something that makes us all come
together again we can't lose think
[Music]
so I work together everybody
let's go oh it could be something else
before the words I've been playing too
many across words this is getting
dangerous what are you thinking of
inspiration
tears oh is there any place that we
should have it close to for like the
sake of what about the tree guilt it
doesn't get us over here right
oh maybe we can cozy up next yeah
but in the challenge the other guild
this is so pretty
yeah
bless you bless you and we have
something to claim the ground with let's
see torches are a sign or so I don't
I've had some Mesa biome yeah
[Music]
where's the kill that did me
the blue building is a guild
the blue building yeah this is over here
looks so cool
it's pointed directly cool too I want to
help Ah that's like
soda Senpai gills
oh my gosh I don't know if we should
build it next to here because
it's not
comparison might be
better
that's one of them sure
where should we go though
you building on the ocean
oh God
[Music]
no problem
okay
I feel like there's there's a lot of
land taken over here though
let's go west
yeah
where's West this way
right now
okay okay
[Music]
there's a lot of pandas
wait when did they put pandas in this
game oh a while ago a long time ago
actually what they came with the jungles
right what what maybe it's still going
west
be careful when there's a baby around
what only a panda baby if you find one
with a panda baby you want to stay away
where where are you guys heading to
we're going west where are you West
we're at the near the U-Haul the blue oh
the frames they just dropped all of a
sudden you're rare
we passed we passed the pandas yeah we
passed the pandas
yeah you passed them
there's like pandas pretty good
are you guys still at the pan
nearly went past the Pioneers pandas
only a little bit
another portal
what
past the surface one what is all this
stuff the beetle are you past no not
past the beetle why where are they
oh frog
is a different Panda place
can you come pick me up
wait I don't think we were going west
what is that noise what is that noise
it's beautiful
[Music]
water bottle yeah
that's coming out of your mouth
doing that
well I am a frog partially so you know
that's the other pen the spot okay I see
someone pick me up
um
building no we saw the Canyons
if you look at the big pecora building
like when you would stand in front of it
go right the Big Pig but like be further
away from it well it was not it was I'm
going I see you
um yeah we were going south I think oh
there there you are what the other
skeletons I was about to take out my bow
you went South
yeah or we can build over by because I
think fauna and my Trident we're kind of
close together we could build over there
yeah I was talking about the ocean
oh yeah I saw your thing and I was like
shocked that you built something it
looked really good
thing yeah wait what does that mean
like it looks
like finished but I guess then I went
inside and I saw it really wasn't
finished and then I was like okay that's
good
[Music]
my eyes are
um
go back to the go back I see the pandas
that you saw
the portal
are we gonna make a giant light up sign
another portal that you guys are not
talking about with our anagram in it
what I'll come find you
the coordinates I don't I've never been
in this area so I don't know what you
mean when you say like the blue Guild
and stuff
um well we went back to him
[Music]
what are you near the motherboard
I can go near the nether portal here I'm
just gonna go
Are You Gonna Save here
okay I've been I'm near the pandas okay
we're almost there or I'm almost there I
think I see you okay
scary
this is
this okay one yeah that's a hotel
it's a hotel it's like a hotel I found a
hotel yeah with an ally inside
wait who's m
M me remember
okay sorry I've mixed them all up some
of those like first letter names some of
them are
owl and shark and
[Music]
um
where is everybody now
[Music]
they were like yeah you're allergic to
everything
especially everything in nature
I was only scared if I was gonna be
allergic to cats but I wasn't so I was
like okay this is yeah it matters this
is the one I was worried about I was
like this is okay this is all that I
want to know thank you thank you goodbye
here this is a good spot something oh
in here
how to claim it
uh make like a like a square with our I
have some rocks red sand yeah pretty
free normal Sam should we ride like a
big en or something oh okay
or a big
big stunk you know who could try
I can't wait can we make it into the
shape of a turnip turn up our icon well
it's just a temporary right now Crossing
reference
wait we don't like piss off them now
uh here's some signs that we could use
noise
I'll take them
where are we putting it here
thank you I found this whole area if we
want to make like a big building
so from
I just
uh
uh Guild
wait sorry
oh wait it won't work with sand
I'm writing an S oh stunk
I'm writing an s from that side wait if
this is wrong yeah I guess it's like
easier to see
and now I can't collapse do you want to
use these blocks wait no they might be
easier
you want some orange terracotta
is done
oh stocks there it is that's an s
who wants to do the T
everybody's looking at this
oh my goodness wow
[Music]
yeah you might run out of blocks
oh you can do it oh I'm doing the oh
it's not enough room for your tea oh I
don't think so oh you tell me the
cameraman
hello
sorry
your tea can go in between there yeah
noise
so oh it's a very short tea
nice guys oh it looks
it looks so small I'm impressed like
we're in sync well wow beautiful
um
it's definitely readable
oh
you can just write stop
[Laughter]
though I also what to do and I was like
surely you will notice about it oh no
yeah
STC
oh
[Music]
this is Santa I can't
if you wanted to be a pee yeah
should they be an N yeah no no
[Music]
okay okay
things done okay we're not as soon as I
thought we were and we have to work on
that one
[Music]
wonderful okay I guess it works out that
works it's a clear message to anyone can
I make an exclamation mark then here
wait okay
[Music]
stop
in the name of the law
oh
what what does it mean wait make it even
mean get rid of all this shrubbery
nice nice mummy beautiful
I wonder if someone's gonna be like but
why
not you will say why you must be
eventually it will all make sense
we will surely we will build something
here right now
the next three months we will make
something here yes
okay that's a good reason for me to play
Minecraft again
for something like that
a whole bunch of stuff around it that's
useful
and maybe okay we can also like
eventually the first thing we should be
doing is like make everything around it
a little bit flat so we can have a
building oh Planet you heard the lady
flatten it up
at all just like the area where we're
building our lives
we have a robot here
robot robot robot went bad do we have
Guild rolls
is there a sign up sheet for the guild
rolls should I be the dog
I think we already have a shark
instead
we could have an owl too they can carry
letters
can I be the owl
I want to be in Saddle water
can I be okay so we got the ocean we got
the sky where's the ground one
the Phoenix
but I'm in the sky too
[Music]
and Kane walks on land it's true she's
the earthbender
roommate can be understood
is it a goat cute little
[\h__\h] cute little rodent cute actually
are they rodents
cute little
carnivorous
I Wanna Be I want I want to be the
ambassador for international Affairs oh
yeah it says good good yeah okay between
ID and Japan guilds Etc okay that will
be my role wait do we need to write this
down
I have no sign
I can be uh I have a book
Aesthetics
Ambassador I'm not very good at
designing buildings though
I'll be blueprints
I don't know wait what are Guild rolls
anyway I can be the one that turns on
everybody I can be the support Google
may please no
wait
uh and the I'm the consultant of many
affairs
yes
what kind of building do you want to do
you want something like natural or like
futuristic or modern you know
minimalistic fantasy like what kind of
theme are we going for here I've seen so
far a lot of like RPG fantasy style
Builds on the server so you want
something modern minimalistic huh
um no actually I like the fantasy okay
but which style of fantasy are we going
for are we going for like uh uh you know
like a classic in town look or do you
want more like uh a special area kind of
thing like uh in the forest kind of
building with like oh mushrooms or or
mushrooms sounds cute that would be cute
or like a castle or or you know
Gothic Castle or like a normal Castle or
I like wood
like one no yeah what do you guys
even though it's kind of like cute and
little hot like like the hobbits kind of
design
yeah
can we have a hobbit
um
like maybe that might be a little
difficult but we can make it happen yeah
your your roof is already a dome you're
not allowed to make it oh yeah Taco Dome
actually I'm proud of that though let's
make it Shire Hove it Shire Hove at home
[Music]
Lord of the Rings with everybody but
yeah you know kiwawa and Kuda already be
watching it I don't know about mermaid
Inna have you girls watched it in
theaters oh
awesome is the only one who hasn't
really watched it at all
right now
oh but then it's about time I know
Florida rings
oh I want to listen to that soundtrack
now but have you guys watched the Six
Star Wars movie back to back oh
I've never seen one never seen the Stars
[Music]
that's a good recently I have watched
um two Star Wars movies in my members
and I've stopped watching them because I
I refuse to watch anymore wait which
ones did you watch which one did I the
first like the the first ones that got
released the first two ones okay you
didn't like them
um
the Rings
do you like sci-fi or no yeah
uh my anime uh Alien are you a Jalen oh
alien is good well
depends which but I did I didn't enjoy
the news
I need to watch Avatar the blue one okay
I was like not The Last Airbender
I just said
[Music]
I don't know where I put my bed
she goes
good morning did we just leave our beds
here might as well yeah we can do that
okay so we have our stop sign we have
some of our roll stops
I don't know if we could change it it's
whatever you want to be uh-huh
what's a stoat
[Music]
yeah yeah it's like a little vicious
weasel yeah
okay well then that was uh way easier
than expected but we finally did it I
mean it's a warm-up you know for the
awards yeah
I'm excited for that
[Music]
let's see my house if you go in my
basement you can hear him oh did you see
the whispering's castle no it's actually
quite nearby here you go
is it really or am I getting
yeah like a cross over there do you see
see what okay
I see a big tree
so did they just like build it on top of
it isn't that cronies the warden built
it oh the word
oh my God
[Music]
okay all right
who's that
oh
[Music]
um
where may I put my guild resignation
you can't it's written and it's sealed
inside we have a contact for further
inquiry now you can't back out
you'll have to come before the council
before you remove yourself from the
guild That's the Law we're in front of
two of them yeah
and I say
no we say what do we say
why don't we we say stop we say you're
trapped here forever and you have to
listen to all the soundboard and two
noises
[Music]
okay I guess I have no choice on y'all
oh
[Music]
I am content
yeah me too I live here now and from the
stop sign that's all we need to lift
these beds
we wrapped it up today yeah let's wrap
it up
for us
[Music]
dogs stunk stunk stunk killed the Wither
like it was uh oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
and I learned what the Wither was yeah
and there you go and yeah more
experience in my life yeah yeah yeah
maybe the weather was the friend we met
along the way oh
but we killed him the song we met along
the way yeah
[Music]
the stonks
nice yeah okay okay
and and in strong we say Alfreda scene
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]