[Music]
can you gather some flowers for me oh
yeah I have some I'll give you some I do
not know what is happening but I have
just entered this realm and there's
people
[Laughter]
here what are you guys doing in our
base um oh we were looking at the art I
was doing an art tour yeah we were
looking at the art oh I see over here
just allowed in
uh yeah we opened the door this one is
called enemies to lovers I I what do you
think how does it make you
feel how does it make you feel what do
you think when you look at this can't
believe you guys are inside of
our cin Jonathan don't you remember that
I'm an honorary member of the blue
Cerulean Guild and I Lally own every
land so suppose that is true you have
not shown loyal here towards the queen
who is our
Queen T gambert
what that's not even her name I will
believe you to it excuse me I do
actually not remember the name excuse me
can you explain now happen I want my
money back not even not even know the
name of our Queen I must I must fit the
the memories I do not know know why they
are so strangely placed one second I did
not expect to be we did I did not know
we had a guest
today I was not ready to see these
guests I suppose this is good enough
calling me enough here we go oh man
Excuse me yes a stretch it is a bit of a
stretch one
second can't believe her only betray I
was not I was not prepared I was not
prepared for
this build
something here we
[Music]
go hello hello voice is in my head how
are things
now how are things doing now we are
going to have a happier don't hurt your
horse it's okay I'll die oh no there you
go I'm the I'm
huz good day to all I hope you are all
enjoying a very pleasant day wonderful
day uh my Amber coin mate we just have
many how you doing conversations
happening around us but you how are you
feeling today I must do a little
fiddling with my with my mind
settings there we go well what are your
plans for this lovely day
I think got thank you Gundam for the
support your message of support huzzah
huzzah good day huzzah thank you Sonic
Jerry for the message of support huzzah
another adventure with my Noble KN
Jonathan will the P get to him or will
he be able to move on from his
lost is his
Pearl it is something that we
must we will have to confront it one of
these days thank you YY for the red
message of support stay strong Jonathan
G I will I will remain strong for I am a
knight thank you yummy for your message
of support good tomorrow sir Jonathan
May thou Have A Grand Day yes may every
voice in here have a grand of the grand
this day huzzah huzzah huzzah
okay I believe I am ready to engage in
conversation with anyone who stands in
front of me I was was not I was not
quite ready I just did not assume that
they would be here they were just here
they are here so suddenly the door is
closed how did they get in how did they
get in what how did they get into our
home very
strange they broke
in how strange how very very strange
strange they would just break into a
night's home like
this
goodness yes we'll need double the doors
in
[Music]
security what has happened oh
no what is wrong with Princess koseki
vu's moai statue
[Music]
the corruption is spreading even farther
than we've
thought
goodness
goodness what are these
things it's quite terrifying
what we have fought
off see she's no longer in pain what is
this the
sand the corruption spreads
how
terrifying all right let me place this
down what is this what block is this
sand is fine it is
okay there we
go what am I looking at
Sandstone people in the distance I do
not have Sandstone
currently construction of the queen has
been going well we have
finished one side look is she not
beautiful her backside still needs some
work and this side is almost
complete she's looking quite
beautiful thank you
[Music]
Queen Eternal
amander I've never seen such a [\h__\h]
who is this Jonathan it is my queen Tam
Gander Queen is that different from your
Pearl yes it is very different from my
Pearl
well my
Pearl yes they are two different
people shouldn't you make one of your
pearls
um mayhaps mayhaps I should I just it
may take some time do you like the
statue of the queen though I don't know
if it looks like her it looks just like
her I've never seen her are you Queen
yes she is a queen she has treated me
with such Grace and
kindness well I'm glad for you thank you
thank you Moco I appreciate
it I I about you well how has things
been since um everything has happened to
you
I'm trying to learn how to cook you're
trying to I see you have potato salad in
your hands we need to prepare for it
what are you preparing for the final
battle the final you have word of a
final final thing happening The King The
King The King he is it is quite
terrifying well I I have word that do
you remember the person who was chasing
you down and calling you a criminal okay
there was many people including yourself
well do you remember who started it
all NOA it seems that she is
dead what she has died the Witch Is Dead
the witch she she's a
witch she's a witch it seems she has
died do you feel any anything towards
that she kissed me my goodness she
kissed kissed you and you feel sad that
she kissed you or that she was dead
she's dead someone who kissed me is now
dead my goodness oh my I why why did she
die she died
yesterday because of a misunderstanding
I do not know she was in the way yes
there
is yes T
Shakira oh sorry am I intruding I I no
you are not
intruding you come Feast your eyes on
the queen Tam
Gander she looks marvelous today as
every day as always she is quite
beautiful
very what
happened she died from a
misunderstanding yes it well do do
you is Tam Gander alive still Tam gander
is alive she's on an
expedition she will return once the
Expedition is over and she will come
back to this Kingdom and Rule and take
her rightful place as
Queen a
queen yes no this is our Queen she's Our
Queen all of our Queens she's the queen
of this entire Kingdom she's married to
the king a king then what about Queen
n what Melody Queen who
n
[Music]
l no she is a queen of another land she
is not a queen of Le
bestl Tam gander is the queen of Le
bestl of these lands this is true this
is true yes yes this is
[Music]
confusing like that well have you seen
any statues of this other queen that you
talking about I I have seen the the
crown Crown the crown thr the thr
yes but if she were a queen wouldn't
there be statues of
her this is the only statue I can see
yes this is the only statue in the lands
and is of our Queen T Tam
Gander therefore she is the queen but
I'm the Royal puppy you are the Royal
puppy of Evergreen I
assume Evergreen yeah that is where
Queen Mario
rules I should go check with her yes go
go with haste clear up this
misconception she seems to be a little
confused but she's got the spirit she
has she the heart is within her good day
to you good day lady Shakir fellow yes
uh sorry that I was a little off
yesterday I was going through a bit but
I am much I am more chipper today I am
uh I am ready to take on this new day
and you are more chipper indeed
yes yes I am feeling much better what
has caused
your sadness yesterday
ah it just seems that my time if you won
the the Arena Battle wouldn't that make
you very very
delighted I was quite joyous that I won
the Arena Battle but there was just an
aching in my heart because of someone
someone who is no longer with us any
longer
oh an aching in your heart has she has
she stabbed you in your heart no she's
gone oh
hello hello fluffy one it is the queen
Tam Gander this is
amazing it is the queen Our Queen
beloved Tam
Gander Tam Gander yes yes I'm taking a
gander at yes Tam Gander you are
gandering upon Tam Gander
wow I think can use some flowers Queen's
feet oh yes she should she deserves
flowers I will get flowers for her I
will gather flowers appreciate the
flower she will beautiful she will get a
few flowers wow I'm going to go check my
chest oh yes oh we
have
well well so what you have not been
stabbed in your heart are you okay I am
fine it was more of a emotional blow oh
to have lost someone I considered so
dearly as you can see yes oh so yes I I
see I see how it is well I hope those
wounds heal faster thank you lady
Shakira I I appreciate it your kindness
knows no bounds perhaps when our Queen
returns she shall give you
the the power the strength to move on as
you so desperately need I am just
holding on until the day that the queen
returns and I know I know then that it
would have been all worth fighting
for I certainly agree with that yes well
so I was uh wondering about what we have
discussed yes uh yesterday regarding
the the princess princess have you
noticed come come with me yes
oh do you see
this oh terrifying oh no yes it once
spewed water but now it seems to spew
blood or I do not know what this is it
is quite terrifying yes what has
transpired here I do not know but it
seems there is a corruption plaguing
these lands and it stems from The
Princess indeed yesterday it surely did
not look like this yes it did not now
but is happened to it it was quite
terrifying is she is she the call of
this I believe that she is I believe
that she is the root of all the
corruption I do not know how to approach
it though I I trust in you because of
your loyalty to Queen Tam Gander yes yes
but you can trust me and it seems that
Miss ninoa has some information
regarding her
H but she she's not around she's not
around it seems there are people there's
people on their way
hello
hello who is that we have brought
someone with
us
[Music]
terrifying such a beautiful voice killed
me Shakira and for that you must pay my
hey do not hurt her back ghost back
gathan she has killed me and my child
what is that you lady narissa Raven coft
yes you look so much more her voice does
soundar yes it is very familiar we so
[Music]
transparent well well I have an idea
isn't there what is your idea in lady
Shakira's memories in her dungeon is
there not a way for you to be
revived I am unsure I is there a way I
am a phoenix indeed
and if you are truly not a witch I may
be able to give you one of my Phoenix
feathers to Rive
you and never never turn but didn't you
kill her no she did kill me but if she
wants to make this right I will accept
it sense Flames have chosen her as a
Target but I personally from my heart
and my soul want to offer her Phoenix
Feather to revive her once again how
Grand all right Phoenix feathers must be
very valuable yes they are all right why
I must however uh go pick one out of my
hair first so oh she must she must her
plumage fly then fly Phoenix I shall
return uh in I will try my best it takes
a little moment because it's very
painful to pick it out of my hair
painful you have so kind to do that
sacrifice I me it might take uh a few
minutes longer I will I will hurry I
will hurry
away go for a few more minutes yes you
prepared the ritual I have I have been
reading some books and scriptures from
the the larger Library we will
I will see it right that you do not have
to look like this any
longer thank you it pains me to see you
this way it not
talk my
goodness I have found something though
quite troubling that I thought I must
report yes yeahuh it has to do with the
King and Le Estelle as a whole what what
is it I have realized today as I have
been a ghost I have decided that I
should use it to
uh investigate Le Estell and as I have
been investigating I have found that a
lot of buildings are completely empty I
haveed back already are you ready to
receive the Phoenix's blessing yeah in
about uh 40 seconds uh you can start
doing it now but make it take that long
okay can you come here yes yes my name
is Jonathan jonath just Jon Jonathan
sorry do you have do you have a don't
don't follow us she wants to speak to me
privately yes privately I kind like you
like this like a chicken feather what do
you mean like that she's beautiful she
deserves a body B I may I may have one I
I just I might I just need to combine it
with my Phoenix yes yes yes I do have
one you are in
luck you are in luck so you can become
like that as well I thank you I thank
you gratefully maybe but why would you
wear me I thought we wear thank you
betray I never betrayed you it's a
misunderstanding my
[Music]
queen hello Jonathan hi
Gordon one
moment I need to still
uh put my
finish yes I very excited to see
this me me as well I'm quite I'm quite
curious yeah well you must accept the
trade
request wonderful here is the blue and
turquoise colors look for to it that
will give you another chance in life
this is a chicken feather it is a blue
and turquoise colored
Phoenix oh wonderful colored Phoenix FEA
yes turquo it is very blue and turquoise
and and shiny
feather very sh except this gas lighting
look it is white what what no it's blue
and turquoise it's going to work
Jonathan Jonathan you are watch out you
are in the fire the Phoenix better is it
because she sees the world in a
monochrome way well I shall use Poss go
for it Phoenix
power what is this it takes a few
seconds it takes a few seconds sometimes
what the you are slowly regaining your
life get out of there what is wrong with
you there's a in the is not working I
was expecting do you know what that is
corruption on a person it takes a few
seconds patience for Life who did this
hello everybody what is going on we are
attempting to revive this ghost do you
see her trying to the ghost trying to
save the ghost you save the ghost yes
you not quite ready for oh yes I wanted
this as well I wanted her to be saved so
that I could use her to my
advantage your advantage what what is it
that must be done to save her why did
you say like that where did the ghost go
I am not sure she just
disappear loser said what loser said
what well you know what her plan is
now
interesting I need your I need I need to
talk to
yes what what you need to speak to me
about you got to come do you know how to
un invisible can you open the door
please I need to show you something
can't you just lockpick your way in like
you did oh you are back yes she's it did
not work I think we will need to perform
the ritual the ritual well the ritual is
a long and grueling one are you sure you
are ready to go through such trials and
tribulations yes it is indeed yes it is
actually a very very long and
complicated ritual in order to get your
life and body and soul back into one you
see for you see I will do anything your
body is currently being held inside the
depths of of a of a prison of the sewer
system yes the sewer system we must get
your body once we have found your body
we must bring your soul which is you
right now and your body to the Temple of
the Phoenix and you must get the last
hit on the statue in order to combine
your body and
soul all right yes all right yes yeah
but you must you must get you must get
Shakira's blessing because it is through
her blessing that she allows you to use
such resurrection and Revival purposes
the one who killed me I am sure I am
sure that you can get it I'm sure you
can receive her blessing it seems she
wanted to try but mayhaps if H if you
receive her blessing and get the last
hit on on the the statue you will become
whole
again yes I see I see this a very
complicated process this is the best you
could come up with it is a very long and
arduous trials and tribulations but I
believe in thee I will come with you on
your quest we will go through it
together
H well why don't you get my body body
and then we can go and do yes you know I
will seek your body I will find it seek
my body I will find your body call me
once you have found my body yes yes I
will
yes you can ride horses while
you while you how how do you do that my
goodness don't worry about it call me
once you have found my body yes I will
call you once I found your body to
what to what um conclusion have you
come sorry I was just so taken aback by
her horse riding skills we need to take
her body back and then you got to give
her a blessing so she can merge the soul
and body together in a ritual that
Jonathan will perform yes you you must
give her your blessing and and heart and
and then we will go to your your temple
and she will get the last hit on the
Statue and then her her body and soul
will combine and she'll be one again
yeah yes I suppose that is indeed how
it's done I just forgot about it yes so
the long the long ritual yes the long
ritual yeah it is necessary for the
impatient uh Souls out there yes all
right well I must find Body regaining
her body mhm we I will find her body it
must be in the sewer system somewhere oh
I will find it in the sewer find it yes
we will find it yeah has somebody
brought her body in the sewers it seems
as if someone has brought her body down
there to rot in the cave but we will
find it it is no matter that's why there
was a smell such a bad smell in this yes
the bad smell is because yes her body is
rotting in the waters very disrespectful
I cannot believe this and then you may
come along with us because it is your
temple and you know the ways and then we
will watch her as she fights against the
final statue and okay her body will
become one yes oh oh yes interesting yes
that sounds like a
plan yes yes shall we shall we proceed
oh but did you want to tell me something
Mario yeah I have something to do first
excuse me excuse us Shakira I I I need a
moment oh okay can you open the door you
you're not just going to lockpick your
way in like you did earlier you can just
gently open the door for me I just just
I just feel as if you have lockpick your
way in earlier no no no it was already
open I see well thank you come with me
so I was talking to a certain Cecilia
night uh today yes and we were admiring
the beautiful art pieces in your uh
house and at some point we saw this and
we were like wait a second do actually
remind me something what does it remind
you of I started to connect the dots and
I finally realized the probably the the
second
Queen was in love with me all along the
second Queen and so I
decided to propose her I want to marry
you are going to propose to Queen Tam
Gander yes but
first I be Al be
honest I need your approval my why do
you need my
approval because I cannot do this
without your support I realize how loyal
you are to Tam Gander and
so before of that I need your
blessing before I
shall propose to the Queen T
Gander myself and send a p I will send a
p a pijun my proposal out prepare it and
I see well yeah but I cannot do that
without your oh I will not she's back
are you a good news your
body the phoenix feather has revived
some of my life force I'm still dead
though oh so you are no long oh I can
pass through you ah you are a ghost oh
my goodness I cannot touch you oh you
are so cold when I passed through you
yes but I was hearing you uh dear Queen
Mario and I will support you you your
efforts are to marry Queen Tam Gander
correct thank you yes that's that's my
ultimate goal today let me continue
telling you of what I have found yes uh
gathan and and queen Mario as I went
into the castle I believe that the king
is a farce I have come to the conclusion
that stains are lest who actually
decided to defect you know who has magic
yeah the king who summoned us here to
lestel in the first place goodness I
have found out that the King has
transformed all of the past liest who
have rebelled against him in Chains
themselves hence why there is a stained
King it was the person who was trying to
overthrow and usurp his throne because
he was not kind he has summoned us and
locked all the currently bestin here so
they may not see the treachery that has
been performed
on their fellow uh Town's people you see
my goodness he has wiped their memories
as they have wiped
ours
not that does add up my goodness I have
heard it really
does so that's
that's that's what it was going all
along I never trust the king I told you
I never liked him me neither something
is always felt off we have to save Queen
Queen Tam Gander and the only way to do
that is to have her marry Queen Mario
only the two of them together can take
down the king as he is
now indeed
so I know you are a loyal Knight but
will we have your support in this
endeavor will you give me your
blessing did you see
that no you not see
that no
you did not see that it was the
princess the
princess is it the princess she was just
there she was just it it must have been
a trick of the light yes
mayhaps uh I must report one more
finding to you
both in the castle I have found two
bewitch Le best who were unable to speak
in complete sentences but together they
had one coherent message which was land
of faded Destiny echoed or and or again
break the chains and it will flee Back
to Where it All
Began I see this very troubling this is
a very
troubling I do not know the problem with
this entire situation is that they will
not get married in
time we can I Believe in Us even if they
have to get married after the king is
overthrown I think we can see success we
can just send a pigeon and the queen
will send a pigeon back you will need to
go through a ceremony for the marriage
no worries like we can wites yeah we
have the witness we don't need a mar an
actual we can we can do the marriage
another time this is an emergency
situation an emergency situation an
emergency I should send my Pon as soon
as possible so Jon G would you give me
your blessing for this I do not believe
that my word holds such wait but you may
send a pigeon and it is up to the queen
to
respond thank you not my place you are
Jonathan yes thank you Jonathan is to
the queen yes so is send your carrier
pigeon Queen Mario we must make case on
this matter I will do right now and
Jonathan J
I always liked you even though you
hidden me for a long while I always
thought you were very um I see her what
is she doing princess oh my God she's
doing it it was it was not a trick of
the light it is her what is the princess
doing make way to
her what is my daddy doing open the
door where did she
go prin Princess Princess where are you
where did the princess
[Music]
go where is she do you see her I do not
see her any longer is she hiding in the
moai
Statue I do not think so
princess she's not in
here my
goodness
goodness I am also scared for this
Kingdom there is some treachery of foot
where is my daughter I will need to I
miss
her well I shall eat
something well if I could speak so
princess Co beu if I could speak so
candidly to you are you speaking to the
princess
currently she hung up on me come with me
where we cannot be heard please please
this is an important matter believe that
no one comes here often up here I
believe so too I've discovered it myself
yesterday
yes we will not be heard up here speak
here not heard nor Disturbed must tell
you something where yes wait before I
tell you where does Your Allegiance lie
nurse of Raven
coft uh how do you mean my allegiance
you wish only for the good of the
kingdom yes and you of course I only
want the good of the Kingdom no ill will
towards Queen Tam Gander and you
recognize that she is Queen of course I
recognize that she is Queen Sam Gander
just like us is a hero who had her
memory stolen from her but she is
married to the king nonetheless making
her the true ruler and you have been
working very hard and tirelessly to
obtain all this
information yes so that we may protect
the queen because I do not think the
King has her best interests in
mind I must tell you something
yes it
is I believe that the princess is
corrupted no there's no way how do you
think that happened the stain on her
head I believe that it has possessed her
mind and the corruption has taken
root I have a feeling you know with what
I found out about the King today and him
turning the liest who rebelled against
him into stains do you think that now
that koseki beu and queen Mario are
trying to com for the throne that he may
also be trying to turn them into STS
just as he has done with his rival King
mayhaps mayhaps that is what is going
on I think so and I'm scared I am also
very frightened but I do not know how to
combat this it seems that she's very
very good at lies it must be the stain
on her head I have tried to convince
some people yes but she has easily
tricked them when confronted and that is
why when speaking to her you must not
you must always doubt her words
always I understand thank you for this
warning Jonathan with a G I know that
the princess is still there deep down
and that she does not mean to cause so
much harm that she is still there and
that we can save her but right now she
is no longer princess koseki bishu but
UNC corrupted she is
corrupt my heart breaks to find out this
news but with it we shall be stronger
together yes we'll be strong so well
what shall we do try to save the
princess if possible but if not then we
will simply do what we can yes we will
do our best and that as long as we make
it with our lives in the end of the day
it will be all that we could have
done of course the best is all or our
best is all that we can do so we must do
it yes together but we cannot do
anything until you have your body back
so I will I will retrieve it and we will
go revive you mayhaps yes mayhaps it
seems that I might have my body back
enough for now mayhaps the feather will
continue to work its magic yes yes maybe
I do not want to trouble you with with
such a grand quest of the ritual I see
let let me call upon Shakira to produce
another feather maybe you need another
feather may maybe you might be right yes
or maybe if you want to speedrun the The
Volcano dungeon together yes we will
just do the last part of the ritual
since it seems my body in a way is
retrieved yes we will speedrun it let
let let us do it now we'll speedrun it
now let me call not wait any longer the
Phoenix oh I'm on a phone call excuse me
good luck with your endeavors I shall
support it when you need me dear
Shakira yes it
seems that we have obtained narissa
Raven Craft's body it seems that your
feather has done enough that her body
has returned but we must combine her
body and soul so we are going to make
way to the temple if you would like to
meet us my feather has worked after all
after your FEA has worked yes yes it did
work I have told her so and she has
still doubt at me well then we shall
retrieve her soul we will combine the
souls shall we meet at the temple using
our warp Stone oh that is a great idea I
shall be there immediately yes I will
see you there farewell there the
[Music]
well
yes yes supposed we arrived it is wow
what wonderful technology to be able to
warp us such a way yes wonderful the the
the the technology here is quite
wonderful ful in general a Shakira can
turn a regular chicken feather into that
of a phoenix feather with her power it
must be her Magics it is quite aaz do
you think do you think oh she is here oh
wonderful you have already your body yes
thank you is delightful to see yes
converting the chicken feather into a
phoenix feather has proven to be quite
very very effective but only halfway now
we must speedrun a let's go let's
go
[Music]
huzzah this is important it is important
for our journey
onwards please join the party call yes I
will join the the telepathic link yes
here we go telepathic link here we
are let us go the Shakira dungeon
again
yes oh have you found this way be
careful it's quite a dangerous you do
not want to fall is no problem I'm sorry
I built it this way my family just had a
lot of fun with it yes it is quite
problem meticulously planned it is
wonderful thank you a lot of work went
to it Generations Wonder Generations I
can I can tell I can see ooh have your
family Ames in the past built similar
things I do not remember yes oh you do
not remember your family no un have any
memories oh that is yes it is very very
sad oh
goodness I have fallen I am
disgraced will I fallen
again please get the
checkpoint I have fallen
too no we can't all be falling we must
do we must speed run
it the fate of the kingdom it rest upon
it oh while while you were gone
Shakira yes nura ravencraft has apprised
me of some very interesting
information oops what might that be it
seems as she has come to the same
conclusion as us it
that the King made The Edge May oh yes
the king may be a
stain oh he may be possessed wait the
king yeah he creates the stains he has
the stain King and he has corrupted our
princess our dear princess
mhm oh no not again yes I do not know
what we shall do but I have seen such
things in the past it is up to us to
stop it terrible fate it is a very
terrible fate
a terrible fate indeed I felt like I saw
her today close to her Temple already a
little while ago and then she
disappeared quickly almost as if some
kind of dark magic was possessing her
she was fering in and out yes she was
doing
that weird what is she what is she up to
what is the the evil evil possession in
her doing to her this is yes what indeed
it is quite corrupting our
oh our lands yes have you not seen the
Cerulean that is the biggest
tell the Cerulean the Cerulean plot it
has begun there did you see the forest
the corrupted Forest the corrupted
Forest indeed the corrupted Forest quite
terrible it is something I have only
seen in my nightmares before wait the
corrupted Forest where oh did you not
see it next to the statue of the
queen I did actually it is a new
addition right yes it is like the
corruption is spreading into the kingdom
it is very very terrifying I have
noticed it is crying blood yes it is
crying very very dangerous
tears it is
quite horrifying we must we must get
your body with great haste before your
power something terrible terrible happen
happens I will get this for you my
queen for Queen Tim
Gander we are doing this for you Queen
TW Queen
Tander
yeah
forward um I
I um I'm sorry uh the wrong button no
it's correct button I believe
oh yes we must die before we can
progress the gimmick of this is the life
of a phoenix I will take this L bear the
well all right me too for me it is just
another day in my life another day
another Revival another day of
rebirth Loop endless
loop I'm tired of it sometimes I wish to
just die no no we need
you you are all that holds us together
death is not
allowed you will rise
again I shall I shall at this very
moment I am at the end are you
ready yes at the end of this part at
least where are you we went up the
ladder
yes all right I shall follow I can smell
your scent yes I'm slowly dying
ah am also
dying that might be a malfunction in the
castle that my family has built I
apologize your family built a lot of
traps in your
Castle yes it's quite inconsiderate they
were possibly quite
sadistic I would say
so very very sadistic but I would say I
have not inherited those from them
well that is good to know it is good to
know anything I am I am more on the
masochistic side I believe oh thank you
for not building a torture chamber for
us to go
through I'm glad to
hear
oh for me it is more like a fun chamber
but oh no that that felt good it did it
did it feel good now it is just almost
like a massage I have opened the pathway
we are almost there to the end thank you
you quite fast gathan you are inde
working together
yes a little pain is necessary if it is
for the
kingdom yes no no gain as they say my
family I have received the next
checkpoint thank you
fairest Raven ah I will fall I will go
to the checkpoint
no it is okay we have made it
fellow we will live we drawn to the
orange juices the orange lava I will go
to the top side one and I will I will
get it yes you will speedrun the
Maze yes I will speedrun the Maze
above oh there's already one light
activated you grow so so fast at this
it's as if you have visited my family's
Castle several times in the past yes yes
multiple times S I am
quite familiar the familiar with your
family sadistic ways oh it's almost as
if it has been treated as a kind of
tourist attraction these days almost I
mean it is quite a nice place to hang
out it is a nice
place but it's it is not just a
playground for people as you know it is
also there to serve greater causes such
as Revival of souls or combination of
Soul bodies I'm going to attempt
revelation
it was too early it was too
early
no I jumped from the wrong wrong
spot be careful my dears it's a very
very dangerous in here very D
underestimate the Phoenix
Flames they can cause great
harm why am I not I'm Not Afraid yes we
must do this we must let's conquer our
fears I'm not afraid of fire I should
just go this way
what yo what yo it is okay yo
what my thing that I've been using to
get over that isn't working is no longer
working I don't know why I'm pretty sure
that's not watch this
Revelation what no there's another
hole
help I'm not sure how to assist you when
you are so far from my hands my
goodness what what a terrifying place
this area again I I have
forgotten
ah no what going on you fall down
too um I just wanted to make sure you're
okay it seems like you were not yeah yes
I'm fine now it is it is all right it is
all
right I I quite enjoyed the
uh the onen yeah well as long as you are
in this uh the night bad building you
can revive forever endlessly as the
Phoenix powers are imminent thank
goodness otherwise I fear that we would
have long been dead already Revelation
why did my Revelation not work what why
did my Revelation not work ah oh there
is great
pain I think perhaps your Revelation is
connected with your heart and as your
heart is broken your Revelation grows
weaker no no that is not true it is not
true it is okay it is okay to accept the
truth no it's not true do not believe it
do not believe that happened to my
double jump the heart has great effects
to our
powers I will grow stronger I just need
to I just need some time to grow
stronger have you yet to activate the
next checkpoint no I fell because my
Revelation had failed
me you must you must try to also
help go as I said I am masochistic I
also enjoy uh seeing myself suffer so I
want to make this as long as possible I
see I see I see watch this it will work
now
Revelation I have done it I have done
itar I love this no don't make it faster
make it slower look at
you my soul will be revived I can feel
it I can feel it as well let us go we
still in the same place we are going to
the next area oh yeah I forgot about
this part I
falling what what a masochistic place it
seems my body is out of balance because
I have given away a
feather now I cannot fly properly
anymore sounds I need to get used to
this
imbalance
yes thank you for getting the
checkpoint yes great you're quite
welcome I see it I see the statue we are
getting
closer your body will soon become one
with its
Soul oh my my mother my mother is close
I can feel her anger oh no your
mother she wants to ah curse us with the
Flames no but I will I will tell her to
do the
opposite
gracefully all right here we go a
blessing I am going we got this with
great haste oh
wonderful thank you mother she is
mothering mother is
mothering oh I you've gotten
it oh is it this
[Music]
way you orange and you are so talented
in these challenges perhaps you have it
is for the queen for the queen can I
skip in yes get the queen I've gotten it
I received it please meet me at the
checkpoint on my way
yes Maiden you are incredible thank you
mother sir Jonathan
mother we must let her get the last hit
it is the only way please mother have
mercy on us please do not be angry we
only want we only your powers for
reval to join the soul and body of ah I
am on fire it hurts but it doesn't hurt
as badly as yesterday it is
okay you become stronger I am stronger
now
I presume we must uh after all prove
ourselves uh worthy of the
Revival
yes she it
says so we shall help her with
that all right I am on it but I shall
give you the last hit of course yes
thank you fair
Maiden mother I sorry I'm here as well
sorry Mom
me sorry all right I will the rest to
you right yes it has become a little bit
dangerous get the last hit is the only
way on you go we have done it we have
completed it we have done it do you feel
it do you feel it do you it
[Music]
alive oh you are warm to touch again in
you are finally whole huzzah
you for saving me yes it is no problem
what a glorious day a joyful day yes all
right now we must find princess beu and
help her yes perhaps perhaps I will go
to Le Castle I will too I will warp to
lesto Castle me too all right we must
find princess
beu all
right is she is she
around is she around her perhaps join
our party call okay sorry she's not even
in our party oh
oh we have revived her hello fluffy one
it is good to see
you a pleasure to see you today I'm
sorry I'm not I'm not in the party we
have just revived Miss Nissa
ravencraft how do I make a shield a
shield seems you may need some iron and
and some uh I will make one for you guys
it's no problem yes let me see if I have
any I have iron I have iron you have
some
iron all right at the
smome my cat Jonathan you are quite the
kind Knight Jonathan it's Jonathan
Jonathan yes it is Jonathan kiss I will
go get it I will go get it
they are kissing cute what is it like
this oh I do not have the iron in my
inventory did you did you get your body
back yes did oh my god really three one
for me as well no longer
dead let's
go yes I am alive but now we must search
for princess beu cuz we are quite
worried about her my do oh here you go I
will trade
you take this Shield yes thank you would
you take care of my problem fluffy one
oh thank you I will return in the party
call but I no it is everything oh your
inventory is full you have too many
things in your
pockets I will trade you of a shield
okay thank
you yes yes a shield for you what else
isarb there you yes huzzah bow B with
thank you okay okay is there any way to
make it extra strong feel this is the
only Shield okay I feel like I might
break it I will do my best as there we
go thank you fluffy one
B it wow M it is looking for the
princess oh yes
a party call still let me join the party
call destroy
hello what is going on oh to the gardens
to the gardens the gardens we must stop
her which Gardens the garden right by
the build area you guys passed it see
look I do not think I do not believe
destroyed the
Gard starvation will come usop
what is she doing do you remember me
what is
happening oh no oh no she's out of
control oh nice food thanks oh um I must
I know that it is a very treacherous
thing but I must be a away for a moment
need to talk about this one one
second one second
[Music]
I am sorry vo is in my head it seems as
if I was pulled away
momentarily by another voice in my head
a voice in my head had called for
me all
right oh
goodness seems there's
[Music]
made the land
starve May the land
starve quite
[Music]
terrifying it is so very
terrifying oh
[Music]
goodness seems as if
things are really ramping
up
but what is a high
score it's so
bloody it does seem as if they were oh
what a nice
what a nice little
cart I do remember that there are talks
of games there are games in
town I believe that there is a game
in let me
see where is the Cerulean Guild is over
here there's a game there and there's a
game over here
[Music]
another game let me find
it is it over
[Music]
here let me
see why is the land
starving I do not know is it this one oh
what what game is
this game will start in front of you
there will be basket and chickens will
fall from above basket will
move oh you must
capture even a night needs um a little
break even a knight needs a break once
in a
while how do you move the basket oh I
see oh we must capture the
chickens what a joyous wonderful
glorious
day how beautiful chicken
capturing a glowing chicken huzzah with
a speed boost and another
one that is a lot of chickens what
happens to the chickens that do not get
caught
[Music]
what happens to them another glowing
chicken and here and this glowing
chicken so many chickens are
[Music]
around oh no I have let that glowing
chicken
fall there's a glowing chicken here I
have caught it you see wow what a what a
joyous Glorious
Day a chicken catching
[Music]
day a wonderful diversion from all the
Terrors that are happening
currently huzzah
huzzah what is the other game that they
are playing at The Scarlet Guild
where is
it it is over this
way it
seems oh
is isn't the night of Evergreen in The
Scarlet Guild mayhaps I should give her
the book to put into to the
[Music]
library oh you guys are playing games
how do you play this
game uh we shall show you once this
round is over dear Knight the
distraction why does fra sounds like she
is crying she's distracting me she
sounds like she's really going through
it she's distracting me is she okay what
is going on she's distracting me is she
is she okay I think she's I think she's
fine yeah I think it's just oh I see
you're distracting her maybe oh she
sounds like she's on the verge of tears
too distracted I mean it's a very
tilting game it is a very tilting game
distrac she's distracting she going to
cry yeah maybe you can push a little bit
more I'm already
[Music]
crying do not fret Freda your time will
be your time will be soon by the way
Nana
yeah she I'm fretting I'm fretting I'm
fretting I'm oh it's nice to meet you n
moo I'm fting so so much right now there
is too much to fret about oh the all oh
goodness oh goodness oh how I oh how I
fret oh dear do not cry you are almost
there you are so
close damn it are you
okay it is nice to meet you n moo hello
it's is nice to meet you is here what is
the name of that who distracts me oh yes
my name is Jonathan
G hello Jonathan G thank you it's a
pleasure to meet
you just if you say so J G yes would you
like to join us in our battle I would
love to see your your game how do you
play yeah you should read the rules just
the
rules mhm it's 3 seconds to m
it oh well I will just guess let us
go
okay have you all signed up yes should I
press start I pressed
start May the mostest win wait where I
see with a ghee oh yes the damage on the
farming lands has been greater than
expected greater than expected yes but
Nissa is currently on it um what are you
currently doing I am playing a a mini
game
currently a mini game how delightful on
these sad trying times you talking to
where is it um at the Amber Hall
Guild Amber Hall Guild yes
M maybe I shall join yes you should come
join dang it if I find it let me try to
find it we would be delighted to have
you
okay I see I
see I do not remember these
colors perhaps like
this mayhaps it is like
this how you doing it I do not know how
are you doing I am doing something doing
oh I am not doing very well quickly yes
I also forget very
quickly what a what a Troublesome game a
very Troublesome game indeed
very triggering you would say so is that
what you
believe I
believe I see I
see why would this Guild create such a
place for pattern
recognization to become a little bit
more intelligent with time I think
training your mind's eye time is that
what you guys do at um such a place yeah
we always want to be on our smartest you
know where was strive to I
understand I see I see well I do have a
book I would like to donate Oops I did
not mean to place it
there if you would allow me after this
blend it
out yes of course again to many
distractions too many distractions so
what distractions were there did you not
hear the green on
what no I was just answering to her she
was bling the entire time I was on the
phone we were too far apart yes we were
too far
apart oh I am getting another phone
call yes I confused it seems you haven't
spoken in oh sorry not the it is the
Scarlet wand Guild the red ones very Sor
you out I'll you out what shape is it
it's a very pointy hat I don't know if G
Jonathan I am
ready ready Jonathan yes I am ready okay
yes it is the red Guild um it is a
building by the arena I believe I
believe that is near the arena the arena
okay yes I shall find it I will see you
soon disappear I will not disappear
veryy
well well how was your day green one
uh so far I've only played this I got a
lottery ticket from moo uh Nana and
that's about it that is it yeah I
haven't really done anything nothing
else oh wait I got a cake for the
princess oh a cake huzzah well huz I'm
sure she would be
delighted what's why did you say it like
that like what I did not say it any
which
[Music]
way okay we have to we can't let her win
uh n this
is what what is this oh it is a game we
are playing a game a game is a what game
yes you should play as well what is
happening I'm not sure I understand it
seems to be a pattern recognition game
yes it seems we're playing a pattern
recognition game what are you whispering
to yourself
about what what is going what is going
on may I ask I was I was trying to focus
and talking to myself to hyp psych psych
myself up oh I seem to have stumbled
oops clicked on the wrong one yes
mysterious very mysterious paying
attention Okay okay okay she's s what
what are you whispering to yourself
about trying to psych myself up you are
doing a splendid job at psyching
yourself up Fair night ah I seem to have
fumbled a shame it is a
shame what is what is wrong
what I ha
you I hate you oh goodness goodness I
wasn't talking to you oh I was talking
you speak because I'm so disappointed in
my I see I see well well you should you
click on this person you speak to this
person and then you press you let him
know that you would like to join the
game pardon me Jonathan G yes n pardon
me I have opened a new establishment
called Nana 11 and we offer the juiciest
of of berries and the highest quality of
of of meat and we also have a lottery
it's free to enter I would love to enter
your lottery oh dear would you like to
enter the lottery first 20 people who
enter
win oh what have I won am I one of the
first well you don't you don't know if
you've won yet oh I would like to enter
recommend her Services all right you I
will give you a ticket hold on I'm
pulling it out of my pocket they very
have to go to
the I am looking forward to
it here is your ticket thank
you wow what a glorious ticket our
tickets 100 coin prize tickets yay in
only 31 minutes won't the lottery be
pulled it will in 31 minutes wonderful
huzzah
huz be sure to meet me at the na 11
where I will announce the winners I will
be there with great haste in 30 minutes
will you be here playing this game in
the
meantime no I think that it's rigged
oh why here this game is rigged oh I
want to give it a try sometimes you
don't have the color that you think you
have and sometimes you don't scroll
enough or sometimes you scroll too much
oh and it is not your it is not your
fault it is the fault of the
gameid want and sometimes they I know
we're not perfect none of us are perfect
it's okay it is okay but just but just
be aware that sometimes also it says
that the are in one spot but and then
they move them somewhere else so it
tricks you making you think you just
have really bad memory I see what oh
there is treachery a foot in this Guild
in these Guild Halls that you are part
of Trey M honest mistakes human eror oh
a human error I see yes we ar robot well
you should try one more time I will not
be entering I will be allowing um Miss
Shakira to enter so I would like to see
you guys I will stay quiet I promise one
more time yes one more time no you
should play as well I you should play as
well I would like to see you one more
time you do not want to play against
lady
Shakira I would love to play against
lady Shaka
Shakira yes well I am a beginner in this
game I I I I I'm not sure yet of how to
play it but is everyone ready I will
play with anybody you shall go I'm ready
ready to be distracted and to be rigged
no I'm not rigged to
experience other other world other rig
yes yes yes how terrible maybe you
should submit a complaint are these not
your guil
leaders no I will put a note and let
them know that it's out of order and
needs to be yes yes yeah maybe we should
do one more try so we can like really
test if it's out of order or what's the
problem you know you
should yes okay okay whoever did the
first one has to start the game it was
oh oh oopsie oh begin okay
begin May the best memory okay
Queen like
so oh
easy so you have been playing this for
30 minutes green
one yes yes I Happ been and you would
say that your memory is quite this is
fun good this is delightful uh
no no not think it is fun but I saw but
this is delightful I saw that you but I
saw that you had gotten the high
score yeah but then you beat me I did
not beat you I did not beat your high
score yes no oh yes I did not beat your
high score I do not remember okay well
then maybe I like maybe I have maybe you
are yes maybe you do have the greatest
of memories so slow at this oh thank you
for Fletching me like that yes any I
have a book I would like to donate to
your
library okay I'll take it in a bit thank
you agree what did you put in your cake
today C oh a strawberry strawberry oh
for the princess IET the princess do you
think she will take it like now it is
rigged I don't know she's been kind of
weird to be honest she has been a little
strange and she did like this really
weird thing and like vanished into th
quite weird it has been a little strange
you do not sense that something is
different no I have not forgotten with
her I definitely know something's
different but I don't know what and no
one's talking like told me what's wrong
and everyone's confused as I am
apparently yes it is quite very
confusing if you could you have some
information you could share with me
maybe at the library in a bit yes in the
library in a bit in the fart Library I
assume
yeah yeah The Great Library
yes we will have to the greatest library
of them all that was Rigg see that was
Rigg it was rigged it was rigged look it
seems you have a new high score had me
press it where it was
not what a terrible do you think that is
the green one rigging it she seems to be
beating
everyone no because you beat me earlier
why are you C against me Jonathan what
oh I am not I am not I was just a
thought it was a thought in my head
again again again again again again go
again again it is certainly rigged
because I have failed yes does seem to
be that way you can play this time
Jonathan I'll watch my turn it would not
be again again again again did you enter
Miss chakira let's play two games at
once two game what other game shall we
be
playing the quiet
game what oh the quiet game the game a
very hard game what does the loser what
does the loser have to
do I punishment why does there need to
be a punishment wait why but why yes but
you are not even playing in this game
you're not playing in this round and
then you are not even you are going to
enforce a punishment when you're not
even played I thought I I have to be
quiet as well okay I won't be quiet okay
ready
ready are you have you signed up Shakira
signed up
yes participate in the quiet game we are
going to participate in the quiet game
am I not allowed to speak I guess we are
not allowed to speak it seems that n
does not want us speaking for some
reason do you hear me from here I will
not do you hear her n Mo do you hear
them are we playing the quiet oh we are
failing at the quiet game I did not mean
to was one 2 3 2 1 2 3 3 2 1 2
3 do you hear
them do you hear them n in my head
is
Unforgettable what what is that song six
I mean Jonathan
12 what is what 6 * 12 well beautiful
pattern in the land of Le bestl we are
not taught
algebra Jonathan tell me what happened
where's what's with the princess what no
you cannot just ask that in the middle
of the fields are you mad where she is a
fun game I
don't I do not have to answer that I do
not have to answer sorry my bad I don't
I didn't I didn't know I was stepping on
a mine there sorry Jonathan how did the
how did the Revival of narissa the ghost
go it went fine remember this it went
okay wait what do you sound Su it was
successful it was successful it was fine
it was a f family we have revived her
Jonathan I'm sorry did I I didn't mean
to step on any toes I was seriously
asking I was just curious It's just okay
I understand you had good intentions it
it just so fine it's nothing the Revival
went well it went perfectly well it was
fantastic and wonderful yes that's good
yes thank you that's good I didn't I
didn't like that sadness in your voice
so I I uh maybe we should change the
topic uh shall we how shall we change
the topic um how has your your little
statue gone for Tam Gander oh it is
going wonderfully the the statue of the
queen is going much better oh not bad
this was the one true game that
had the game has been fixed oh it is no
longer rigged it is no longer rigged no
longer rigged Perhaps it is not and this
was the game that determined who had the
absolute best
memory I wasn't even playing this a
little bit un sounds you are getting
compa when the green one is not
participating I sense a pattern oh my
goodness there may be a pattern in a
pattern wait we must to test it one more
time we should have the green one yes
you guys should play again and see if
the green one is the problem oh no I
have played enough you have played you
do not want to play any longer I have
played enough what about the the voes in
my head are growing tired oh I see well
they have very little stamina it seems
let's it seems so they're quite
weak seems so well Shakira there is
another game at the Cerulean cup Guild
you catch chickens in a basket you may
have more fun playing that yes oh that
sounds fun chickens I see chickens in
the basket oh it seems the game has
begun however oh are you guys this one I
will watch we are playing again there
there's not been a single one that I've
watched I've had to participate in them
all n
n her name is n today Jonathan yes
okay such a single name today did did
everyone
join Jonathan did you join I'm get yes I
did join meow okay I'm
starting I'm
you Jo the red I heard of your plans I
heard of your plans and I did not want
to join any longer about to end this one
but there's game
that Jonathan I heard of your
collusions red red red red green red
yellow blue it is red and a yellow and a
blue red red yellow red red yellow red
blue blue green it is a blue at the
third one three four blue red red yellow
red red red 55 11 red green blue red red
green and blue and red Alabama Alaska
Arizona Arkansas
Califoria my goodness um red blue green
11 12 13 sodi Salt table salt may have
table salt table salt pepper pepper egg
meat red meat red dye 40 50 70 80 red 40
meat
50 yellow ban banana green blue spinach
green egg can still do it blue blue H
green h green ham blue ham green ham
green eggs yellow ham bloody red ham
bloody bloody red ham do my bloody anded
very bloody red and bloody and yellow
and green and red you forgot the red you
forgot the red over there you forgot the
red one you forgot the blue one the blue
one is up there try the yellow try the
yellow there is the
yellow have you checked the red check
the red check the red oh you've gotten
it oh we're helping there is a yellow
there is a red yellow red red yellow
yellow is here yellow is here and then
blue is here and yellow and green and we
going to lose 40 40 you will lose you
will
lose it is rigged it is rigged it is
riged it is rigged it is because of the
green one I believe it is the green one
it is the green one it's the green one
that just rigging it we have decided
always wins yes how come the green one
always wins it is rigged it is because
she is paying them off last time
Jonathan joined it is because she is
paying them she is paying them off she's
paying this game keeper no no hold on
hold on let me step in here I think it's
an honest mistake I think she's doing
something unintentionally she doesn't
know what and she's just as confused as
we are just as scared as we are confused
she is very confused and scared it's
kind of strange to be honest I wonder
what's going on oh how terrifying should
not play this game should we go to the
chicken
game should okay let's just go to the
chicken game everyone should go to the
chicken game it at the ceran guild I it
buy the Amber
dare yes Tred though oh your head you
have a very large hat M matching horses
matching horses matching horses you are
matching those horses are matching I
will I will I will I will I as well I as
well I have
[Music]
many almost I too will match I too will
match I will also match
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
do you have this polka dot this one does
not have the this is an imposter po oh
goodness oh
goodness oh you how much now how much
now still incorrect no how how about now
huzzah there we goah go we are matching
horses hes at all yes yes all right I do
not know where it is
I I could be lying I could be lying I do
not know where it is you
[Music]
could he I will know the it is by the
Amber coin Guild it's next to the Amber
coin
Guild oh she is is she
okay where is it my horse is a little
sick your horse is very loud please do
not make S conscious your horse sounds
very good it is this way I found it I
found
[Music]
it here it
is oh it seems someone is already
playing the chicken catching
game
Chicken
hello are you catching the chickens yeah
I'm cturing the chickens she capturing
chickens very good very good very good
for helping out it is cute oh wonderful
does this distract you yeah oh yes is it
distracting stay it's fine what about
now what if I it makes it difficult I
see is okay very interesting can you
catch me catch me in the
basket yeah I want to be I don't know if
you want that I think these are for
dinner they are for dinner it is
over you know oh she disappeared so
quickly okay everybody click ready join
the game oh we can play together I think
so oh how many people can join player is
already enjoying the game is it only two
people I think it's can two people okay
were you able to join then I'll leave my
spot to someone else go for
it
uh I have joined the game did you join
as well well you should start
now wait wait who joined I have join I
don't know who else has joined do you
want to play anal how many how many
people can join mayhaps two join and
it's okay you do and then I'll we'll do
the
[Music]
next it seems she's a little bit
preoccupied join another player is
already it seems only one player can
play oh hello Raven
C fast hello can I interest you start
here it is complet I tell him that you
would like to start sounds like f the
first 20 people to take a ticket will
win but I cannot tell you whether you
are one of the first 20 okay you will
find out work to go for certain chickens
maybe some of them you no I my eyes are
very focused on the
chickens the most important Target
wonderful yes the wonderful chicken targ
moves the bucket
from right to left in amazing display of
skill and a wonderful display of skill
my's trying to distract her but she's
not succeeding it is impossible to get
them all but I will try my best to take
you all under my wing Shakira is focused
come here into my safe warm fluffy wings
I wonder what she's going to do with the
chickens surely ra them me and some will
die for me and die for
you
terrifying for Honor for Honor f f what
fuckus how has it gone fuckus that was
really good yes she
should Sal it's okay we can exchange it
this way would you like a lottery you
have made the lter
board
huz I want to play
again I see I will be sending them over
to you now everyone been serving me what
the hell no I've already play Oh talk oh
mhm oh I want to be can we meet by oh I
see let's go because it's not possible
[Music]
let's just go to the planes fluffy one
very
well she she bowed down to her yes I
have not to her she's a wonderful
person oh they don't allow me to buy
tickets anymore so they are at
the Cerulean Guild if you would like a
free ticket from nanu yes you at you at
the wrong wrong space
[Music]
we have cut in the
book hello yes into the
library take a seat a seat oh may I may
I give you my
donation my donation oh for the book for
the thingy yes for the library if you
may put it on the shelves if you could
mayhaps put this book on the
shelves of course thank you thank you is
it okay if I read it um yes go ahead it
is a book to be read by all in the
library can I read it can I read it out
loud I will be yes I will be the
audience
happily why is why are you a why are you
a ghost again oh I I now after turning
into a ghost I found out I have the
power to turn invisible oh it seems that
your soul is still in between the two
because you
have really scary it's quite scary it's
so terrifying it is terrifying my
[Music]
goodness I'm not allowed up
there to me you f
Beast oh goodness okay I'll I'll look
away it's okay I'll read your book while
looking away oh I will a night's T I
[Music]
will I
can not listen to it
now I cannot I
cannot I am not
ready
oh is that is that a
horse I am not quite ready to listen to
such a
tale we still have to build our statue
of the
queen it
is it is much too painful to hear that
tale though it is it is just a story I
do not know why it hurts
so we may listen to it another time
mayhaps mayhaps we we shall listen to it
another time um what am I oh yes yes her
hair her hair it is very important that
we finish her hair and we have some
concrete yes yes yes
yes although
if I
could speak so candidly to you voices in
mine
head although I am feeling a little
better today after I have slept it off
if one could even sleep through such
feelings even though I feeling a little
better it
still still
hurts and I'm afraid that that
feeling makes me a little a little
weak especially am I allowed am I
allowed to feel this way when there is
so much more happening in the
kingdoms there's such terrible things
happening in the kingdom and here I am
thinking about something so
silly when when the princess is
corrupted and and the king is
potentially the one that is spawning all
the stains and I am just here being sad
over a silly little
tail how strange it is the knight's duty
to stand
strong to
be a good person so that all may look up
to
him to inspire others so that I may make
the queen proud
so I do feel as if it is a
little is is wrong of me I feel as if it
is wrong of me to feel such a way when
there's so much more
happening or all it was was just a story
of a person who is
regaining their their rightful memories
oh yes
dearest Jonathan yes I must say that was
a wonderful story oh thank you I I found
it I found found it where did you find
it oh it was just a collection that I
previously owned I wanted to donate my
story um to the to the library so that
all may read it your story yes because
I've owned it it is just a oh you owned
it yes it is a book that I've owned in
the past so I believe that it is time to
let it go so so that it may Inspire
others to read it and um you know it was
oh thank you I think I understand that
you're saying that you found it but if
per chance you wrote it I must say you
have a true gift for writing thank you
and I feel like you should put your
emotions to the paper and per chance
this is your calling to be a writer
writing to be a writer to weave stories
mayhaps I will fill the library with
with books oh if I were to have written
it of
course which you didn't yes I did not
but I I will let you know if I have any
books to donate to the library thank you
very much yes I have a question yes what
is your question very unrelated if you
wanted something in this world like an
item of an item what would it be an item
that I would want in this world yeah
like say a cake or berries
or um a sword I don't not to want for
much mayhaps
[Music]
H I suppose I would like a milkshake to
remind me of when the queen had
purchased us all some food and it is a
very fond memory in my heart so mayhaps
a milkshake a
milkshake okay thank you very much for
letting me know if I can ever repay you
for your wonderful gift I will do so
maybe I'll prepare something on my end
as well than I appreciate it uh now I
shall go and play the chicken game oh
have fun with the chicken game thank you
thank you take care dear KN what is
goodbye
farewell what is this will you marry me
what is happening
I
see I see what is going on
goodness there is much happening there
seems that there is much happening
currently Jonathan oh yes what do you
think
about my message it is very bold it is a
very bold message was it good enough yes
I think she will love it
that's good yes I hope so
too yeah she she will surely love such a
thing it is wonderful and
beautiful thank you yes will you be
sending the the sketch through carrier
pigeon I did already I said the pigeon
already on the sky you know where other
pigeons fly how
wonderful oh yeah you can see it too is
on the K right now yes I see it well I
hope your words reach her for the sake
of this Kingdom I hope so too yes well
are you going to build her ass now yes I
will be building
her I have to finish her it is a
disgrace to leave her in such a
way very pretty oh thank you I've worked
very hard on this statue of the queen I
believe you thank
you once I finish her I hope everyone
can look up and remember all the good
that she has done for
us yeah yes well I must I must refer to
my blueprints where is my
[Music]
blueprint oh
no seems as if I have
[Music]
I will return we will
return one
second it seems as if I
[Music]
have I need to obtain my blueprints real
quick it is very important that I do
otherwise I will not be able to build so
easily without my blueprints
what is a blueprint we must get my
blueprints blueprints are very very
important a blueprint is
necessary there one second I am
obtaining my
blueprint recall the blueprint if I do
not have the blueprint How will I know
where to place all the blocks I spent
many a Time crafting the
blueprint so that I may
build it on the plot of land
easily especially because we have you
know a not Unlimited Supply of blocks
and I will have to craft them so it is
very important that I have sketched it
out before I build
it so here we
go I've
returned make sure that this is here
[Music]
all
right
yes let me
see then I will show you all the queen
in a just a moment in a
moment have to make sure that this is
set up
yes it is not a recipe it is a blueprint
for it is just a fine piece of
architecture blueprints have existed for
many a days many a
time where is it here we go we'll have
to change how this looks
stretches
this like
so here we go all
right let us build with
haste let me
see it seems that the next
step is her hair the l oh yes the
lottery how can I forget about the
lottery
don't have to be here right now still
get your prize money but but I just
wanted everybody together because I'm
lonely hello I am here for the lottery
oh is everybody here except the single
person who refused a ticket they refuse
a ticket a free ticket why would they
refuse a free ticket refed a ticket my
goodness after the TR happened to her
sister sister sister hi sister wait a
minute I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I you
two just look very similar I got I they
do not look similar assumed they look
very different from one another they
look nothing alike yeah yeah one is pink
one is blue that's not true they look so
much they look as alike as you look
pregnant
what what room are you in do I look are
you are you perhaps not pregnant Zach
would assume male pregnancy am I even
able I do apologize am I even able to
get pregnant I shouldn't
have your business partner you have to
stop stop insulting your am I even able
to be male pregnant try not to try not
to stop pregnant am I backwards
backwards what do you think does it feel
like I and I am just revealing it to you
I have a hunch you have a hunch Jonathan
G am I icept nothing a Miss I'm pregnant
am
I is anyone a doctor do we have a
doctor CIA are you sure you another
doctor too huh is there a doctor I do I
did take I did take a a First Aid Course
once I do make yeah is that good enough
is that good enough I suppose the
lottery oh yes what about the lottery
seem good at all I guess but
Lottery see is more important ly and if
you were in fact pregnant you would
really need the prize money wouldn't you
I suppose I would given that your wife
seems to be out of the picture now yeah
you would be raising it alone the child
huh I suppose I would be raising the
child alone what happened to her oh how
sad oh she is not of this world any
longer
she died are you sure about that yes she
is no longer with
us she
died new is no longer she is no longer
with us but she's not dead is she she is
she dead the the version I knew is no
longer here with
us she's long God if you believe so I
would not put all my eggs in one
basket she is part of my
I do not know you as somebody who gives
up so easily oh love see well don't give
up we got Nara back from
the this is just a small small
difficulty I think you deserve it too
honest deserve a second chance well if I
am pregnant then we will need the
lockery money money money alert money
alert alert money alert arrived the
money has arrived oopsie wait oh shoot
hold
on oh oh she snuck in wait lety that's
fine that's fine you can hang out you're
so
patient cuz you're so patient all righty
all righty everybody I will now be
announcing the winners but please be
please have even more patience I have to
go en count
yes Okie
doie first winner of the lottery
is you whose name I did not
get GRE you who is
Green
Oh
Cecilia oh
Cecilia by the green one the green one I
go I can go by the green one I like the
green one but there's another green one
so it gets kind of
confusing we call her the other well
just whoever is present is the green one
and whoever
is the other I I win but yes you win I
win you you win 100 coin wrong thing
congratulations wow congratulations on
your 100 coin what is going why is
this oh yes that's what I want this is
what I want I thought it was trying to
make me call somebody I will accept the
friend
request you get 100
coins 100 coin
[Music]
coins for you
what
at winner is the Lady of the oranges
yipp huzar Yi huzar indeed you win 100
coins 100
Surprise a
feeling I hope win for you I think today
we're all winners yes next the next
winner is this Nana 11 Mar next winner
is
Mario yeah there's so many
winners there's so many winners in this
n 11 March you get 100 coins thank you
not sure why you need it since you were
the queen but I'm just happy you my
lottery
uh roal Team
extra sometimes it is required that you
donate a por of
your more powerful they need all the
money huzzah the next winner is Jonathan
G thank goodness great day what's a
wonderful
[Music]
day just got to keep your chin up yes I
will thank you for giving me A New
Perspective nanu
wow wonderful glorious 100 coin
huzzah huzzah huzzah next
winner is or I believe would have
been narissa the ravening
cross she is not here right now we did
that she can pick up her earnings
tomorrow which will do money on theor
SLE on the mar
the but that's okay we have now the
final winner of today Mo of the
co because you bought five
tickets you
get you could buy more
tickets
this I have 20 tickets and get
everything
no you could not have five was we all I
see how
wonderful graduations everybody you have
all won the lottery what a glorious
day's addicted as long as this is the
only Lottery she's going to because then
she will not lose any a beautiful
beautiful day today we are all
[Music]
winners one point by the way everyone
that the 11 is better than
oh no good everybody won this
is anything family run a family own star
should destroy
F destroy
destroy want to share
the to
destroy I will give you my
winnings this the
wi would like to share winnings I have
been sharing for you oh thank you those
are the
winnings you're Jonathan of the G yes I
don't may I speak to you on the side for
one brief moment of
course good job good job I am just like
you deeply concerned about what will
come of your baby If
there really is a baby it seems am I
pregnant you might be in do you not
think that she is I think I think you're
pregnant well in case that you are
pregnant and then in in the case that
you are you were to be raising the child
alone if your beloved wife is not coming
back to you I shall just uh of course
platonically offer my assistance to you
in raising your child of course if you
may be in need of any assistance I will
keep that in mind thank you for your
kind and generous off Shakira you are so
kind and wonderful yes since we also
support the same
Queen yes of
course I am of child if I am random
suddenly male pregnant I will turn to
you I feel as I will need someone to to
lean
on up because I have a good feeling
about your
wife your
pregnany than thank you thank you thank
you I do have something unfortunate to
mention oh yes that I think we should
all keep in mind and mentally prepare
for H the chances of a male surviving
male
pregnancy is extremely slim oh
goodness why what should I do how you
know this are you a
doctor no but I read I read books what
kind of books the library your on your
Kindle close see what is the
Kindle well anything that's written on
paper must be true
yes there's no wrong things written on
paper that is true that is
true the library that you that
you of course is there anything we can
do to help her him through the male
pregnancy there is very little there's
maybe some healing items maybe potions
anything you can try but I we can do our
best to help but I think it's very
important that we just prepare in case
Jonathan G I see does not make it
Jonathan G just now that we became
friends no I don't believe it I think we
can still make it if I am to die
Miss Shakira if you would yes see to it
that my child is raised with their head
on right oh but I could also just uh
bring you to the temple and revive you
oh that is true she can revive me it's
fine we have done it today we can we
done we can do it again that's true oh
simple well that's easy then oh okay
thank you for your concern anamu she
will take me to the resurrection Temple
and I will live again there may be many
things to be negative about like the
corruption that is spreading but this is
not something we have to be sulking
about don't worry we should be more
worried about the corruption of the land
there's something wrong with her the
princess jewelry beu that has been
acting very strange as of late oh yeah
I'm going to kill her what what you're
not going to kill my princess you would
kill her now not right now you going to
fight me first to kill her I'm sorry
kill wasn't the best word kill wasn't
the best word I do apologize use a
different word maybe if she were to be
killed uh and then revived by the
Phoenix fire she could be cleansed
automatically oh I'm going to make sure
that she is a good girl and doesn't do
anything bad yes yes she is my daugh I
will protect her all cost I'm sorry we
will not let you you kill her for no
reason we need a good reason kill's a
good reason I'm Sor what the reason
she's killing all of us by killing our
crops and we are resulting in Salvation
do you want us to die for one princess
where's the proof is she bringing Upon A
F the proof is in theing yes it does
seem so
was the
proof narissa has rebuilt all the crops
for us we literally have seen it with
our own eyes when she was destroying
them I ask for to the gardens let us
check the gardens they they rebuilt it
they rebuilt
it built them already it will not become
a proof oh it seems that the fluffy one
is conveni planting the Gard I don't see
any proof that the princess has done
anything so far has re it I have helped
her H oh hello thank you for your
kindness fluffy one in replanting the
gardens yes the gardens you attending to
the gardens you are so wonderful taking
so St oh I'm making see oh it was Nissa
thank you narissa Raven coft tending to
the
gardens but but how can okay so she's
been destroying the crops what if it's
just a simple prank why would you kill
her for that what what's going on that
does not sound like a good prank to me I
trust in you because there is empathy in
your heart fluffy one but it seems that
the princess is corrupt okay I I'll be
honest with you guys I mean the princess
the princess is my daughter and I've
never seen her acting that weird this
morning MH like I I I don't know there
was something extremely wrong with her
today and I couldn't stop her
I that's a good point yeah I've also
noticed her being very strange but I
feel like murder is very ex extreme can
we maybe have a trial can we have a
trial it seems that not a wishes to kill
the princess I got to get my carrots oh
okay therey will she does not want to be
involved in this the murder is quite
Tous for a fair say
she um I I will ask well I would like to
ask maybe we could have a set a court
date for tomorrow court date h would you
guys be okay with that Justice rules it
would be for justice I don't know if I
can go for justice a corrupted evil
mind I have seen the evils that have
happened well on this land well we can
we can we can talk to her and see if
she's responsive and then we can have
her have a trial I'm sorry but she out
of control it okay can I can I be honest
with you h it seems like something is
corrupting her from inside and Nissa
Raven coft the the she told me that
there is something about the king that
is going extremely wrong like a
corruption from from the kingdom itself
really so yeah and and yeah Shakira was
with me when she was talking about it
and like apparently the king is
corrupting the lies and the the lies um
transform into to the uh stains that we
see outside the kingdom and so I'm being
called sorry one second was
calling who's calling oh we are at the
gardens we are currently at the gardens
Naru oh I
see also if you needed any about the
plot that you started wanting to kill
the
princess you said kill you
said what you said true it's
true here we have to explain her about
what Nisa told us before okay then okay
yeah also the princess has uh uh that
true the princess has used the community
notice boards to uh write a cursed
corrupted message to us what do you want
to do with the queen true I've seen it
I've witnessed
it it was in a cursed language that was
really hard to decipher it was and if
you notice it is the same the same font
that plagues her her lands have you seen
the the notices on her her Forest the
corrupted Forest exactly it's like at
the Blue uh there's like water one must
be blind if one were not to notice that
it is a garden or purposefully ignoring
it it's like on on the side of of the
giant circular building and then
there I see
[Music]
well I did not want to tell it she's
corrupted too front of them but remember
what Miss ninoa said is that there is a
golden yes
hello
what are you looking for someone okay
never mind well n I'm is
confused okay are you sure she also
confused oh yes she is very
I see she has made her way hello okay so
tell us about this
corruption well first of all all these
lands were cleared by her destroyed by
her I saw her literally doing it and
then Nissa has rebuilt it and she has
then spoken to us in her cursed language
telling us that we must all die also if
we go to her statue it is now bleeding
with deadly blood and then
can this it has also been cursed and
corrupted she might just have a tummy
ache think it is a tummy ache I do not
believe so it might be a t a tummy ache
who's calling it seems more an aching of
the Soul
hello I do not want to say this in front
of her but it seems that she is she has
a few screws loose I do not know if we
can trust her she keep changing her mind
for some reason but I do want trust her
cuz she's part of the scallet
want I see and she gave us money earlier
with a with a with a lottery you know is
full of kindness but I do not know if
she is in the right of mind maybe I am
not pregnant maybe she's just making
things up yeah I don't think you can I
can I can I put my hand on your tummy
yes go ahead okay I know of a technique
to find out whether you are pregnant or
not oh what is it what technique well I
have suggested it to nursa before but
she did not want to try it however if
you um pee on red sand if it turns green
you are pregnant if it stays red you are
not
oh how do you know about this what is
this how do okay well there's some red
sand at
the I don't remember IED my in my
backpack oh you have red sand oh maybe
we could try that yes only if you want I
suppose we will have to will you give me
privacy when I do it happened while I of
course they're trying to figure out if
she's actually if he's actually pregnant
oh
oh that is quite a bit of red sand yeah
in case you want to um confirm it 42
times oh yes well sure I will be back if
you may give me some
privacy where am I to even do such a
[Music]
thing my
goodness oh I did not mean to spin
this let us see
[Music]
we do not want
to how shall we
build shall I do it in the
forest Let's us just make it seems as a
simple
already shh I'm trying to listen what is
happening what is going
on what would an ouse look like it would
be very very
small like mayhaps are you pregnant oh I
have not done it yet I am building a
place in which I can are you pregnant I
I've not I've not built it yet I'm I'm
building an
ouse oh
yes that will indeed be necessary it
will be
necessary it will be necessary I do not
know how large to build this
though I think 3x3 is fine a 3X3 out
house maybe perhaps like this unless
you're visiting the out housee with
other people I think this size should be
yes I think this looks pretty nice it
will be it would just be a very crude
ouse currently
because yes I am on my lands
cool oh thank you it it will be a very
humble out
house um is there to be a door yes there
will do not do not watch me please there
will be a
door you can't tell me not to watch why
would you want to watch me I like to
watch everything can you add a window we
are very old servant no I cannot but
it's going to get so stinky if you don't
add a window
that is true that is just how medieval
outes are yeah just it's it's going to
be
terrible he need some ventilation
let's in Medieval ages where did my
default ax go seems I have lost my axe I
will just punch this out
stinky but it's isn't this there is
there is is being aired
out where where I don't see oh I see yes
yes so there's a hole upstairs at the
very top at the tippy
top
sufficient let me
see what do I want apart as
my
safe what else do we need in an out
house well this is of utmost importance
so just just the just the door have
privacy oh
yes there's the ventilation and
ventilation you will is that the is that
the first out house in the whole Kingdom
for I suppose this is the first out
house in the entire Kingdom then
everybody must use it all right can you
give us all access to it yes but not
right now I am currently using it all
right good luck with the um peeing why
are you sticking your head
inside who is trying someone is
attempting to stick their head inside of
my door what what color is the head
sorry sorry oh yes one second let
[Music]
me one one second one second before I
you are making me nervous let me too
nervous to PE is it let
me San huh yes you should drink more
fluence I will I will to hydrate hydrate
Lots if you want to pee 42 times
I am now going to be peeing on the the
the the sand yes okay okay let us know
if it turns
[Music]
green if you need something let us
know I heard
water oh that must have been it seems
that it is red it is just red red still
it is red still can you try again show
us show us show us oh you get out of get
out of I thought it was on the floor try
again try again make
sure okay I will be PE once
more oh I hear the juice is glowing wow
you're really good at doing that on
command huh no it it was it was red you
must hyd you must have hydrated well yes
I was very very hydrated maybe all GL
things are free we have found out that
you are not pregnant yes it seems that I
am not pregnant well I would AG do you
want your red s back I humbly apologize
for my
assumption in case your your wife one
day gets pregnant I see I see thank you
I do it was because not because of your
stomach but because of your glowing
complexion I do apologize for the for
the mistake thank it is fine maybe
because of that uh big juicy looking hat
oh thank you my very very juicy hat that
surely looks like you hiding a baby in
there but it is empty I
think SC Scarlet W member I have a
question yes can you come with
me
yes
yes did you just give
giggle this is how I sound and I'm happy
oh oh okay sorry um okay
[Music]
you see what I see no one trust anyone
no EL watches
me Jonathan are you obsessed a beautiful
Forest this isn't a forest it's a garden
Beau Forest wow what's a beautiful
Forest Jonathan the man you should try
fixing your own issues before putting
your nose in the ones of others what a
wonderful wonderful Forest it's is so
green and
Luscious it really isn't you do not
believe
that I'm trying to get a get a magical
stone to work and I need a I need a
Scarlet wand member in order to help me
with it oh an ally well it says an ally
but it has to be someone I trust and
that's kid it it is luscious I just was
trying to be I was just trying to be
special oh yes thank you you you are
quite special I was just really
embarrassed that I didn't think of the
word lusious before you I'm sorry oh
it's fine it I think you are very
special in your own ways nanu you you
are wonderful and a fantastic business
owner and you have created a wonderful
March that has brought so much joy in
the Kingdom everyone was happy today all
thanks to you thank you I think you are
quite wonderful and you deserve the
absolute best in somebody who will love
you for the rest of your days I believe
in you thank you nanu that is very very
kind of you to say your words have
touched my heart far greater than Poss
so sorry for so sorry for any pain that
that it is fine follows you no do not do
not lift your head up high please miss
nanu I believe that you will find yes I
will pled my allegiance to you because I
sense a kindness in you and if you ever
would need help please call for me and I
will I will use my sword for you in your
name oh oh thank you yes and I would do
the same for you oh thank you dearest
nanu I also have some hot friends if you
want to oh if you want me to get no it
is okay I I yes I do not need no I am
just looking for some companionship
through friends and allies oh I can
provide that yes huzzah huzzah what a
grand dayah huz
friendship ho friendship ho
huz thank you dearest
anamu you're welcome you are so
kind and those are you yes I will see
you again I what what is this see want
for me where'd she
go oh dear oh hello we were just
celebrating friendship oh wonderful
friendship very wonderful veryy well
mayhaps you should give Cecilia a
ring perhaps I shall yes you have gosh
you give such good advice yes I will see
you soon goodbye for now farewell for
now there are kind souls in the kingdom
and that is why I cannot just let the
sadness plague me because there are good
Souls out there we'll put this here for
now I believe
that we are going to need need
to at least make a little bit of
progress on the
queen though the pregnancy mention
didn't have me quite frightened for a
split second even if I knew that there
were no way it could be possible I was
scared imagine me bringing a child into
this world a child that would not know
their other
parent how how
terrifying I said it was quite scary and
then if I were to bring a child into
this realm would I even be able to
provide that child with everything that
it
deserves I am not that good of a man you
know I do not know if I can provide the
child the life that it deserves so I am
very very relieved to know that it was
just a Gest it was a Gest that she was
mistaken
that way we are able to I'm I at least
do not bring a child into this realm in
which you
know it does not have both of its
parents to love and protect it and
cherish it oh I'm getting a phone
call yes hello hello I would like to
inquire where might you currently be I
am next to the stat of Queen Tam Gander
oh wonderful that is my favorite place
to be yes it is my favorite place as
well I will find you yes I will be
waiting oh I see
you
hello dear Jonathan M I have something
to give to you oh yes what is
it well I'm about to depart uh for the
day and we might not see each other for
a long time but um I I just had a a
really Joy ful time with you um you seem
to be of the same mind I enjoyed your
company as well Shakira I was just um I
wish you the best of luck with regaining
your happiness and thank all that I just
I just oh a a flower thank you of the
highest order I will place it here with
the queen for she would also enjoy your
loyalty how glorious and
beautiful yes for the queen of course
that was meant for the queen oh but I
know that you had given it to me but I
thought I would share your loving flower
because it's a beauty that should be
shared with everyone oh no no it was uh
I just because I don't have the rights
to build on this land so I just oh yes
yes for the queen I enjoyed spending
time with you today too and I know that
yesterday was a little rough with you
being accused of so many things but I
have seen through it that you are pure
and kind of
Soul thank you yes it means more than
anything to me to hear that from you
thank you for joining me today I will
miss you dearly but I know we will meet
again I know it too in our quest for the
queen for the queen wherever we will be
together in our quest for the queen yes
for the queen she's the one that brings
us together queen and I thank her for it
thank you thank you miss queen Tam
Gander Tim
tender thank you thank you
Shakira to have found an ally in you it
means if oh yes to the queen yes yes I
love you dear queen or have for saving
us I love you yes farewell farewell I
will miss
you I waved to her
well I am happy that we were able to
create a friendship after all of oh
another phone
call yes hello hello Jonathan G are you
uh doing something uh of importance
right now no I am just building the
queen did you need something oh do you
would would you like to play a game of
memory oh I suppose we shall play a game
of
memory because ellia you won and I will
I wish to oh I no longer wish to play a
game of memory veryy well why
[Music]
not let's us
see
huh yes but why oh I I am just so tired
and I must build this statue of the
queen you don't want to play
memory why do you wish to play memory
because it was so much fun to play oh
you were just having so much fun it is
not because you wish to have a win over
me I mean do you play to lose or do you
play to win I we are playing for fun yes
yeah yeah yeah I mean I have fun no
matter if I win or lose but you know I
can want to win while still having fun
regardless but it's okay if you don't
want to it's fine I just saw did you do
the M me
what what who who did that did what no
there's like a
giant there's like a text floating in
the sky oh it is it was Queen
Mario oh oh
she is asking to marry Queen Tam
Gander oh yes
yes okay okay well well if you do not
wish to play I respect your decision
well
mayhaps we can play one game if that
would so please
you yeah it would please
you yeah yes of course I will meet you
at at the guild I love games fa well
I will see you
soon it seems as if I do not know I have
I have a feeling that Miss Cecilia of
Evergreen wants to
win it seems that she was quite unhappy
that she did not get a win on this
gracious day mayhaps we should H what
the heck J we will
oh I did not know if she wants to join
but no I think it would distress her she
was quite
distressed
okay we will try but I think we need to
allow the night to win or she will not
let us down
hello
Cecilia ohello Jen I am here I have
joined the game
pie
yes good luck to you yes yes good luck
to you as well yes good luck good luck
oh I must start we have
started
mhm I did not know you were such a
enjoyer of the game of memory
I it's fun but it is quite hard I think
it's quite hard it is quite hard yes but
you have proven that you are very Adept
at memory
gaming I did not mean to place that
there but you beat me on your first or
second try yes but it took a second try
to beat you it but because you are quite
good you are very good at this
game you think I'm good at this game yes
you are very very good at this I lost
game how did you lose we are so early
into the game but I messed up I pressed
I I'm I'm choking do not falter do not
falter do not falter you are very very
good at this game of
memory I'm also choking as as you have
said the wrong yes yes oh do not worry
what a Jonathan you wouldn't lose on
purpose right you would never do that no
I would never lose on purpose I would
see to it that I have given you a
rightful
challenge okay I trust you I would not
lose on
purpose why would I do such a
thing I don't know it's just I feel like
sometimes the kindness in your heart is
uh seems to be very strong and you put
others in front of
yourself uh and it makes you suffer but
also you know it's like a level that
might uh
oh I hurt you in the long run is that
what you think I would not sometimes I
would not do such a thing I am trying my
very very hardest right now Cecilia of
really Evergreen yes promise you
wouldn't lie right I would not lie I am
doing my utmost currently and you are
just ooh you are so good you have Ved
me oh oh oh no oh good oh goodness
[Music]
why do you okay why do you sound so
afraid Let's us play again let's play
again let's just play again but let's no
let's take a moment let's take a moment
why do you sound so afraid I am not
afraid I just things aren't
afraid I was just so shocked that I had
won cuz your memory is so good ah it is
because I was distracting you it was let
us play again but I will also play the
silent game this
time oh you don't have to I should not
no you can't talk I I should
speak yeah if you want to if so you so
wish are you ready oh yes I am
ready
okay I don't like that they take away
our hats in this I feel like up yes why
would they take our hats away yes why
would they undress us why would your
guild do such a thing to
us M maybe it's like safety reasons so
people don't cheat maybe someone you
know oh has a piece of and paper someone
cheat at this with their hat and Cape
maybe with like a piece of paper stolen
uh hidden between everything that is
true that is
true so
Jonathan what do you oops wrong one what
do you think about the princess what are
we going to do with the
princess I think that there is something
going on with the princess and it is our
duty but to to find out how to what what
we should do but do you really think we
have to kill her no I believe killing
her is only The Last Resort it is the
last thing we should
do right yes yeah that's what I'm
thinking it would be quite terrible keep
going down on the stairs like yes yes
[Music]
oh it's not looking good no no you you
are so you are very good at this game
what how did but you were winning what
happened oh I am just so foolish and
stupid what suddenly happened that's so
OD oh oh I am now I am now so back we
are now back in the game it seems that
if I just had a momentary lapse in my
memory of course you see it happens to
everyone it happens to everyone
yes it it does it does happen to
everyone okay I am only
human I make
mistakes oh you human what's with a tail
then nothing there is nothing with the
tail but why do you have a tail if
you're
human I am just a knight
but it's okay it's okay to lose yes yes
it was because I am sorry it is because
I am such a loud mouth are you sure that
we should not be silent can take this
win Jonathan what you can take the wi oh
yes I have W this time
huzzah huzzah huzzah what a glorious
day well I think we should not kill the
princess I feel like there's still a lot
of mystery surrounding her and I feel
like we should either give her a fair
trial or try to heal her somehow do you
have an idea how we could heal her do
you have any
plans I have a few ideas mayhaps she
must consume something that will allow
her to be pure of mind like a cake a
cake what is that what you built for her
what you've
baked I made a cake for her yeah you
you've made a cake for her yeah actually
I'm working h no nothing yes I made a
cake for her you are working what I made
a strawberry cake because that's her
favorite oh do you believe that a
strawberry cake will be enough to to
cure her no actually no I don't think so
because I don't know what's wrong with
her because I haven't like I've seen her
a couple of times she was a bit weird
but I haven't seen her do anything evil
you know everyone's saying she's doing
evil stuff but I haven't actually seen
it I'm not saying she isn't I'm just
saying I haven't seen her do it I see I
see that is a fair point it is hard to
believe something that you Haven
experien yes I've been worried a little
bit you know how there's been two queens
right the rightful Queen Tam Gander and
then the queen of Evergreen Mario so
there were two factions and then the
king the king's faction I guess and I
feel like something is weird because why
did the princess suddenly become a
Target to such you know to so much
hatred she's part of your guilt is she
not I care for her deeply and I wish for
her to be alive I do not want us to all
fight her but I cannot deny that she is
corrupt and it's not her fault it is a
stain a stain has poisoned her mind so
we must we must cure her of the stain
that poisoned her mind
okay well then riddle me that you know
how the king you know how the king
called us all here against our will
yes and then we had to fight in four out
of five dungeons in order to destroy
stains but not in a single one was there
a stain there was a stain in the
sewers yeah I said four out of five I
mean a four out of five and
then he puts a lottery shopping thing
and one of the hats that you can get
from it is a
stain that is true why would the king do
such a
thing I just do you distrust the king I
do distrust the king but I'm scared of
voicing it because everyone else seems
to trust the king
well we should not speak of it inide of
your guild halls with oh that's true
yeah let's go somewhere else the game
master standing right there
[Music]
okay okay so there's two options right
either it's a plushy then the question
is like isn't a plushy something that
you would make from something that you
are a fan of that is true I'm telling me
the liian and the King are fans of
stains then why would they option the
other option is it's a real stain and
the stain has has corrupted our princess
I do think that is my princess a stain
on her head that has corrupted her and
the corruption you think it's a real
stain it must be real it has to
be it has to be real think about it when
did the corruption start exactly 4 days
after Tam Gander has been gone where is
she what did the king do to her you
think that the King has her and that she
is not actually on an
expedition I haven't seen any proof of
her being on sad Expedition she left me
a note in her
handwriting what did the note say it
said that she would be going on an
expedition I cannot say where because
I'm am afraid of voicing such things but
she is on an expedition and she says
that she will see me again
soon soon don't you think soon has
already passed well I believe that at an
expedition of isn't she the strongest
Queen it does such a que cross the ocean
the wat days it's been days though yes
but she has to it has only been what 3
days 4 days since she's left I believe
feel like since she cared about the
Kingdom so much for her to just up and
go and leave her post she did not know
that this would happen no she left it in
my hands so it is up to me it's up to
me it's up to you it is up to me should
we I think we have to investigate the
king I do believe in that though I do
not the one thing that I have faith in
in this entire kingdom is to queen Tam
Gander I will never lose loyalty to her
but I do believe I do believe that the
king is not who he says he is he is well
I think maybe the king I think the king
took the queen and is hiding her away
somewhere well if he has done that then
come with me all
[Music]
right please show me the way to the
castle um I will attempt
to cannot believe she told me to come
with her she doesn't even know the
way she got lost so quickly is it this
way your foot sister
this is the
castle that's do seem she was going the
complete opposite direction let us
[Music]
see yes we will see I suppose
oh yes we must be very guards hello
hello dear guard hello guards good
day now follow me
guards guards pleasant day hello hello
dear guards yes good day
guards
now what do you
think it's hidden
here my
goodness a cell don't you think that's
kind of
suspicious and when you look through
doesn't that look like a cell with like
very very small cell that's not Humane
it is not
Humane evidence number one your first
piece of evidence ABS terrible living
conditions for their prisoners yes now
why are you pulling your horse out and
she is
gone I'm getting a phone
call it's me oh it's just oh oh I see I
see I see
I just thought this would be easier oh
yes
hello hello okay evidence number two
evidence number
two this is quite a winding staircase
this takes a while
yes why are you taking your horse out
inside of the Kingdom inside of Palace
cuz it's faster not rid me
this what what is this what's this lead
this must be a secret hallway there must
be something hidden here what is the
color of these this is the exactly the
same color as the stage do you not see
do you not see the sze in front of you I
see I
see I three I will not be doing that I
will be right behind you okay I guess
I'll walk fine it is rude do you do you
not
think okay okay you're right
yes yes
yes now stand with me I am standing what
do you see in front of you dear Knight
The King and two
guards okay what is behind the
king his
[Music]
throne but why why is there only one
Throne what about his Queen why has he
not built a throne in her absence for
her is true he may be he may be keeping
Queen Tam Gander
captive what shall we
do I think I I think I think I haven't
thought that far I
see you did not think very far you only
have what do you mean I thought pretty
far but it is a hard thing to say you
know it's a hard thing to bring up to
people and be like o the king might be
doing something cuz that is treacherous
well so actually I have signs in front
of you I have had this conversation
earlier in the day with another member
of the Scarlet wand oh with whom with
one miss Nissa
ravencroft oh really she thinks the king
is evil yes she spoke to me and she
conveyed to me all of the things because
you know when she was a ghost she was
able to wander around the halls going
unseen and unnoticed and she discovered
many things and she believes that she
see she thinks that the king is the host
of the stains he she believes that the
king is the one spawning the stains and
that he's SCE of it all yes just look at
him standing there while we go to war
for him hiding Our Queen from us yes we
must rid of him so that the queen Tam
Gander may take her rightful place on
the thr when she comes back when she
comes back we will color the throne in
the Blue Blood of the king why is for
the queen blood blue cuz he's a noble
and it's you call it Blue Blood because
the queen is blue so then it would fit
her very well it fits aesthetically
thematically yes yes yeah yes the color
blue okay well shall let
us wait for now cuz cuz I don't think we
can do anything just the two of us and
then tomorrow we shall discuss this with
the others yes I believe that you would
benefit greatly from speaking to narissa
ravencroft especially seeing as she is
in your
guild yeah I didn't get the chance to
talk to her much today because I was a
little bit scared of her being a ghost
I'm going to be quite honest with you
yes it was quite spooky every time she
spoke when she was a ghost it was very
oo yes don't REM you oh you are scared
of ghost I am so s I'm sorry it was
quite terrifi I forgot about the fact
that I was scared of ghost for the first
20 minutes when I attacked but suddenly
it hits me and I remember yes you
remember that you were scared of ghost a
terrifying it was quite terrifying scar
of ghost yes so but she's Alive Now
worry not we have revived her oh thank
God yeah I hope she doesn't use her
magical power too often I think it's
very scary it is quite scary for now I
think we should look into figuring out
how we can heal viu and uh put Tam
Gander on the Throne yes um and oh my
God I almost fell down and he would have
known get R he would have known well we
could have said it's like a parkour you
know oh yes we are just playing Parkour
in the in the Kingdom we're training
we're training this is a training AR we
are ding our spren to prepare for what
is to come
yes how
joyous oh well thank you for listening
to me um and may I say it's been a it's
been it's been it's been an honor
for you to beat me in the memory game
and you should Stand by Your Victory oh
it's okay you don't have to but you are
you have to do everything for very wise
as well you are the one who holds the
highest score so it is only that you you
would win for now oh for now but I shall
train hard and I will I shall keep the
high score hopefully maybe yes huzzah
huzzah well I will not to sleep all
right you will be
you'll be tucking in
oh what very well I thought I heard a
noise but it was nothing was just random
R the ghost it must have been it must
have
been goodness let's
go we will make we will make haste ah
your horse in the palace holes get out
of
here oh oh no mayhaps the stairs did she
just jump did you jump where did she go
oh I will take the
stairs I will take the
stairs no I have one more piece of
evidence oh yes yes what is
it why is there one lies all alone in
this giant Hall talk to him who do you
see
oh sorry I'm a little frazzled
oh I remember there is another there's
another leeston who completes the
sentence I remember that narissa Raven
craftt oh really has spoken of this okay
let me take let me take a Let Me Take A
Memory cap of
this and go to the other one Nissa
ravencraft had relayed to me earlier if
only she could relay it to me again and
through carrier pigeon because I do not
actually remember word for word what it
was dearest nerissa Raven cross of you
are listening to me she finished the
message yes she had finished the message
but we can find it here too if she does
not send word through carrier pigeon
because I have very rudely forgotten the
complete full sentence mayhaps we can
find it do you do you remember the gist
no it had it had oh wait I have received
carrier pigeon wait let's us go outside
so I must capture the carrier pigeon we
must go outside for the carrier
pigeon these stairs are so winding these
stairs are so very winding I will jump
now where where's the door how do we get
out of here is that the way
out oh here's the second one oh you can
I will I will get the carrier
pigeon
guards just good seeing
you okay I'm behind you wow so pretty
that's a grand Castle so what did she
say it
says oh thank you thank you dear
pigeon she sent word it says land of
faded Destiny echoed over and over again
break the chains and it will flee Back
to Where it All
Began say it again land of fed
Destiny echoed over and over again
break the chains and it will flee Back
to Where it All
Began land of f
Destiny yes can you send it to me I will
the carer pict yes I will send through
carrier pigeon come here come here my
dearest sweet carrier pigeon
[Music]
yes I have oh cool cool got it I got it
how wonderful land of fated Destiny
fated Destiny F
Des enigmatic over and over again break
the chains that it will flee back to
where it all began to Where it All Began
where did it all
begin maybe the land of fed Destiny is
where we
from what are the chains over and over
again something chaining us keeping us
here these lands Back to Where it All
Began in that white room I have vague
memories of a white
room a white room really where yes a
white room ah I not know where that room
a weird and that has led us into seeing
something yes it was very strange what
if the stains have also been summoned
here just like we have what what if we
have to free the stains for them to go
back home it's a it's a wild it's a wild
guess but maybe maybe very very wild
guess maybe we have to break the chains
for them as well so they can go home
maybe that's all they
want well it seems as if we cannot do
much today with just a two of us I think
we need a detective for this a detective
yes I know a detective
well yeah yes oh Amelia Watson yes one
dear Amelia Watson I will send a carrier
pigeon her way and ask if she would so
kindly assist us in investigating okay
such things well for now I will I think
we both need rest well I need rest I
don't know what you're going to do for
now I will need some rest um yes but
thank you thank you for thank you thank
you for trusting me of course I and uh
we might have our differences but at
least for now our goals align for now we
are allies and I will entrust my sword
to you we are allies for now for now
farewell farewell sleep well thank you I
hope I wish you a peaceful Slumber as
well thank you
farewell seems as if there is many
things happening in this Kingdom
that we are not there's just so many
questions why were we brought here for
what reason what is this
why is this just randomly
[Music]
here so many secrets are
about and we are not any closer in
solving
them is that what is
that does that lead to
somewhere is that a hall to some
place as
dearest nurse of
ravencraft explored that area can I
reach there the question is if I can't
even reach
there let us
see let us go upstairs guards good day
good day to you this is not the correct
way this kingdom is Palace is very large
wait what is this does this
lead oh so so many doors that lead into
nothing how curious how very very
curious that so many doors just lead
into nothing
[Music]
constantly let us
see it was upstairs but I do not know if
we can reach
it where would it even be there's a dead
end stairs downwards
is this it I believe this is it let me
let me eat up to prepare for this path
[Music]
downwards
yes I wonder if this does lead anywhere
or if it will lead to nothing oh it's
nothing it's nothing
why why a path here that will not let
you
enter what is this you are not allowed
in further there is nothing
else darn darn at
[Music]
all a sham yes voice is in my head I can
hear Nissa Raven crop's voice I think
back to what she has told us
today my
chickens it is just perhaps it is a
sham we will be inconspicuous us as we
leave farewell guards your hallway is
very
amazing I do hate the way that it winds
oh hello hello guards good day to you no
I did nothing it
nothing farewell farewell it is good a
good day it was good seeing you oh wrong
way
[Music]
on to here well oh I getting a phone
call hello yes fluffy
one Jonathan yes
yes Jonathan hello good day you hear me
I hear you do you hear me dearest fluffy
one hello you answered me yes I've
answered I would always why don't I hear
you do you not hear me my chickens your
chickens what happened to my chickens
what happened to your chicken my
chickens have disappeared what chickens
where are they Don where are your
chickens do you hear me fluffy one where
are you Jonathan's asleep where do do
you hear
me oh do you hear me I don't hear you oh
no why do you not hear me is it me
no is it is it my fault it's my fault
you what happened to my chickens what
happened to your chickens
they're G where where where are you last
one where are you at the building where
you gone like I I'm here I'm here do you
hear me do you hear me I can't hear Don
thing can you hear me you hear Don thing
yeah you can I can hear you what what is
going on you Donan what is happening
that's so strange hello hello where's
ask her for me where are her chickens
what has happened to her where are your
chickens what happened to you Jonathan
now yes hello I still can't hear
Jonathan what is happening I can't hear
Jonathan what is going on dad Jonathan
oh my tiets come here come here come
here I'm coming
too right over here where where they
were right here
mhm and last chicken is gone your
chickens were here they were here I
loved them and there were so many of
them and now they are gone they're all
gone every last one was it the curse of
the land you did build it quite near
close to potatoes to the to the
corruption maybe they left no they were
very happy they were so
they maybe you should like put something
here on the on the wood so they don't
leave anymore because maybe they just
left I don't think they flew away they
were very happy I love this think they
flew away for they flew away fly oh yes
chicken cannot
fly jum over here my
goodness yeah big cat you didn't eat
them right okay what why would you H
them on me it's not me it's not me I
love them it's not me you oh my goodness
eat a chicken she ate your chicken I
didn't I I do not think she would eat
your chickens she is living on bread for
the past few days I promise ling a bread
are you
sure
yeah know your chickens
though very sad I I know what happened I
love them she left chicken you know what
I can give you more eggs come with me
can you a well I hope wish them the
best but what if it was the curse that
took the
chickens one of the curse ate her
chickens it's very terrifying a
terrifying
thought what is happening over
here the Crypt well
H we we must
finish some construction of the queen
well we have one side of her head ah
thank you Queen thank you fair
Queen what are we building yes we have
made a little bit of progress today I
would
say
yes we have made quite a bit of progress
let me see I will finish your backside
[Music]
I have a memory in my head I see I see
it I see the Queen's cloak that she once
had a beautiful magnificent blue
cloak I will capture
her in such a way what
what yes her wonderful
cloak why does everyone keeps speaking
of
her
backside classy was out the cloak the
cloak is what made her made her so
wonderful well not only the cloak it was
not only the cloak but she was so
elegant in
it I am referring to
my to we must always refer to my
blueprints I have a few things I want to
do I do not know if I will get to them
to show you
but I want to write a letter to the
queen I would like to write a letter to
the queen just to see if she's all right
and I would also like I would
need I would need to write a letter to
one
Amelia
Watson
yes it does seem as
if something very dangerous is going on
here and I must put
aside
everything to write a letter and ask her
to help investigate what has been going
on what is this this is wrong it's here
yes so I will write a letter to the
queen tonight and I will be writing a
letter to one miss Amelia Watson to ask
for her assistance in the investigation
of the
king let me see 1 2 1 2 3 4 5 1 2 3 4 5
yes
[Music]
I
cannot let my past our past affect your
decision we'll be strong together won't
we dear voices in my
head it is fine I have friends they have
been very kind to me today
and it makes me feel as if perhaps I am
not alone
so it will be okay worry not worry
not it is of the utmost importance
though that we send a message to the
both of them
both about the
king and then I just want
to ask the queen if she is all right and
then we will at least know that she is
not being kept in the prison
right and I don't know I guess the
selfish side of me would just like to
ask the queen if if she is all right so
I know that what I am fighting for is
worth it and that I have not made
everything
up it is it is a little selfish that is
my little selfish request is that I
would like I would just like to hear
from her I think her words will give me
great strength if I am able to hear from
the
queen and I will have the strength to
keep on fighting oh it is the fluffy
one not that she saw me it's
okay put this here that's not the right
color and like
this oh thank you voice in my head red
voice in my head taggard worry not
Jonathan Queen Tam will surely always be
there for you when you need it most
thank you I appreciate the words the
kind words of
support it is 1 2 3 4 One 2 3 4 and then
two all the way
up like
[Music]
this so let us finish the Queen's
backside and then I will write my
letters and probably
call it call it a
day all right we will need more of
[Music]
these and then I will probably
continue in the dark of the night in the
darkest of nights I I will continue and
I will finish the building of the queen
so that everyone may see her in her full
Glory tomorrow but I will finish her
backside right now and we will add the
finishing touches so that everyone may
see it tomorrow yes worry
not I will see to it that this statue is
to completion oh thank you for the
kindest of
[Music]
gifts like so
no take this
away and then it seems like
this
oh
miss there a
ravencraft like like
so yes yes
all right and then we go up
here we leave that
there and we will need a blue to
complete
this ah but she is coming along quite
[Music]
well she has a gaping hole on her side
but she's almost
[Music]
done I have feeling quite
good this construction has brought me
quite a bit of
[Music]
purpose I'm happy that even though the
queen is not around to give me
instruction that the queen is
still here with me in some
way it's like
[Music]
this be rid of
this oh
farewell two
three and then be like this one
two
one one two three four 5 1 2 3 4
5 huzzah we just need to make some blue
concrete and then we'll finish her hands
she will be mostly done just the
finishing
touches let's place this
here and let us place this
[Music]
here do I have any we have gray
concrete where's the blue dye I do have
blue dye on me nope that is a gift from
The Fluffy one blue dye
where is
it let me see some
gravel and some oh are we all out of
sand I place it in the back where are we
out of
sand oh goodness we will need to get
more
sand does seem as if we were out of sand
all right
let me make way I am making way in the
chest I Am So Blind we do have sand we
are running
no
hello did I disconnect for a brief
moment did anyone see that sorry I do
not know what happened hello hello we
have returned my
memory just faded for the briefest of
moments very strange I hope it does not
happen to
[Music]
again we've disappeared for the briefest
of moment but we are back it is
okay continue our building
[Music]
here like
so seems as if she is engaging in the
Box
boxes all right then this this
here this
here
huzzah we will finish her hands
now put this
away great
concrete put these away we have any
light gray
are we out of light gray concrete no we
have some still some light gray concrete
powder oh we have so many think I made
too many on
accident we might
need some more light
gray concrete No Gray concrete here we
[Music]
go not
that oh I did not get the sand
need the sand gravel sand gray dye I am
blind put this
back all
right a symmetry in the
cloak oh no
goodness 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
what did I
do oh goodness gracious what is
[Music]
this place this
here she is better now she is better
now wrong one
[Music]
placees and grab
these she is acquiring quite a bit of
hat let me see
all right you will
[Music]
place like
so and then this
[Music]
side
screaming
then like like
[Music]
here and then where's the white did I
grab the
[Music]
white what is going on oh hi
hello it is good to see everyone
voices in my dear
head we are currently making progress on
finishing the queen and then I will be
writing some letters to send off tonight
before I B everyone a
do let seem may have
[Music]
mayhaps like
this not mean to place that there or
maybe C be
[Music]
there like this
goodness hello
everyone voices in my head that are
growing louder and
louder I wish everyone well
today on this fine fine day
[Music]
huzzah huzzah the queen is mostly
done there are some finishing touches
but she has she is
complete she's mostly
complete Queen saved
me OU
ououou eat what are you doing going in
the corrupted lands it said to go in no
do not you'll be
corrupted huh you'll be corrupted if you
stand in here for too long I thought I
thought it was yours no it is not my
sign it seems they have corrupted my
sign
too oh goodness oh terrifying here come
take a bath in the Queen's Fountain and
and you will be does have to do with the
queen what no it has nothing to do with
the queen k here take a dip it will
cleanse you cleanse yourself with the
water the holy
water yes drowning no you're not
drowning you're just taking a little dip
I'm stuck do you feel
better I suppose I was sort of drowning
and stuck but now I'm okay yes you're
okay because the queen is here to
protect us feet water no it is her holy
water it is the holy water holy water
not it is the holy water yes it is her
holy water
yes of course
princess
careful princess
careful be very careful oh narissa
ravencraft what are you doing
here we're not oh that was
frightening trest she's not speaking
either she is following princess be
[Music]
you no back back off fuzzy one I want to
be fashionable no fuzzy one no fuzzy one
fuzzy one no fuzzy one back fion I'm
never partaken in
[Music]
fashion hell Jan I must I must tell you
something are you are you hello can you
hear me can you hear me please please
tell me you can hear me please tell me
you can hear me hello you might be in
trouble no no I'm in trouble I'm in
really trouble are you in trouble where
are you I will save you do you hear me
do you hear
me oh no oh goodness I thought if I
was Jonathan I can't I can't speak to
you right now I'm being
chased okay farewell it's it's too late
for her it's too late for her I
will I will have
to I don't have to send word I have to
send word quickly with
haste where is
it how does one
obtain what is it again
we'll write two
letters it is important that we write
two letters today very very important
here is this here is this put this away
I am done with this for now we are done
with building for now
[Music]
currently I think we have everything we
need
[Music]
I will not we will
not I will not speak to them we must
send a word
quickly I will have to call upon all the
Allies I possibly
have let me see it seems as if oh this
she's following me I
cannot
oh I
must we must we must away we must
away yes an ink sack farewell
farewell Let's us go let's us
go we'll make way
[Music]
it does seem as if she
is through the power no she will not
capture
me why can I not do this on a
[Music]
horse yes
all
right I must check how to make a book
[Music]
again she will not find me here it will
take her a while to find me just like
this and then mayap something like
this all right
H she will not find me if I
go good thing we were given the power to
breathe
underwater otherwise this would be very
very terrifying
[Music]
yes there is no way she will find us
here it
will let me
see first of all we must
[Music]
write we will write the most important
message
dear Amia
Watson there is treachery a foot in our
kingdom of
lesto the corruption has
spread it has taken over our lands our
lands our
princess our
companions if you could you could
please if I could please
H what do I ask what should we
ask I could ask you to
investigate
the what does it say oh they are
receiving more
hats please be well
I
[Music]
fear I'm not careful
no I cannot write that what do I fear I
already I've lost so much already I
cannot lose the
kingdom please be safe and
well trust no one not even I
or I do not know what will happen in the
coming
days if I will
be
me
[Music]
yes
start with the
palace farewell
I will not seems she wants to give me I
will not you will
not and then a message to the
queen dearest
Queen hello well I do not want to I do
not want to raise any
alarms not want to alarm her
please do
[Music]
not no cannot I
cannot dearest
Queen I hope you are
well and having a good time on on your
Expedition I will not lie I miss you
dearly but the kingdom is
well and it misses you
too do not want to worry her
I'm
afraid there is a little bit of
trouble
Brewing
but I will do my best as your night to
ensure that the lands remain
peaceful awaiting your return
[Music]
I
afraid that I may not be
around when you
return to may not be around to celebrate
your
arrival so to celebrate to celebrate
turn but know that I have have not
strayed
once it will just be a small
trip it
will it will just be a small trip once
this is all
over I will return When I
can I hope you can greet me with a
smile always loyal Jonathan G I'm
getting a phone call Jonathan can you
hear me can you hear me can I hear you
Jonathan are you able to hear me now you
weren't speaking are you sure you're do
you hear me do you hear me hello
Jonathan where are you do you hear me
can you hear me can you hear me I can't
hear you no I'm near for right now
though I will I will make my way towards
you I on the
way I'm in trouble you are in trouble
seconds are gone again no your chickens
I know you cannot hear me I hope you can
hear
me I'm going to attempt is my
[Music]
volume I don't hear can you hear me can
you hear me I can hear Jonathan near me
can you hear Jonathan's near me but but
you cannot hear me
now that's it a pretty
place please in my head
we will place this here for
now
me
letters
yes we'll leave it
here we must make way
I hope she is
safe oh can you hear me are you able to
hear me huzzah what is wrong my my
chickens are gone your chickens are gone
they're
gone yeah what happened to them no I
said the the fence was it big enough I
don't think so cuz I kept on chicking on
them and they all good they were always
so happy were you they had many EDG were
you given a hat by anyone for chance
recently I was only given a hat by you
very far ago will will you promise me
dearest will you promise me yes my
dearest fluffy one please please do not
accept any hat from anyone else okay i w
i yes you promise you swear to me you
will not accept a hat yes okay I'll get
my hats on my own yes I have to we are
we are not safe I think I know what is
happening to your
chickens what do you mean they're not
just flying away I do not think they're
flying I think someone is getting rid of
them I think it is the corruption the
corruption how can I keep them safe
supposed to look like they I do not know
if you'll be able to keep them safe
mayhaps you should set up a trap you
should live yes
maybe I'm not that kind of person I
don't know how to make
trout it seems
maybe tomorrow tomorrow I will help you
create a trap and we can see if any
trusted allies but you must promise you
will not accept any hats from anyone no
hats no hats no hats I promise I had to
tell you something too the
one the one that people say that you
look very similar to Mo moo is it yes I
know that you have you are a little you
are close with one another yes we've
gotten closer to yes you've got closer
yes but you cannot trust her I fear as
if she may be corrupt she Mak be cry
yes why I don't know I don't know if I
can believe you
Donathan well you may not believe me but
I hope you think of my words when
something if you feel in danger remember
my words if you ever feel like you are
in danger remember what I've told you
okay be careful with Princess KIU and
Nissa Raven craftt be careful around
them yes okay careful okay I will
Marissa was just asking me about hats oh
do not accept a hat from her do not do
not okay I won't I won yes she didn't
have the hats I wanted anyways yes yes
yes I see I see
okay be careful I just I believe someone
is doing something to your to your
dearest chickens
okay yes uh let's pick you out the trap
for now I guess I'll just not have any
chickens I will help you with your trap
tomorrow I promise I promise you yes we
will find who is doing this farewell
farewell farewell bow bth bow
bth something very terrible is happening
in these lands I do not know
what queen do you see what is happening
I will send my carrier pigeons with
great
haste I see is
it I suppose that Marissa ravencroft
will just have to speak with me in her
own voice
tomorrow I will need to hear from her I
do not know who to trust there's just so
much going on why was she with why was
she with the princess koseki beu in such
a terrible
terrible
time goodness goodness my
goodness she is
back oh
well let me
see conathan
yes narissa Raven
craft I'm not suspicious I know I seem
suspicious but I could talk because my
my U my my family was in my room oh I
see I see all right I understand I'm
sorry I was I was monitoring her
monitoring her why were you trading
people uh because I was trying to get
hats and I got so many freaking
construction things but I have two Amber
or one one Amber coin no two amber coin
hats and two two tall pointy hats like I
have for the Scarlet yeah except I only
got those ones oh I spent 20,000 coin
20,000 coins and I didn't I only got a
crazy amount of coin it's not fair I'm
so angry I see what were you trading um
Moco if I may ask uh I gave her uh 16
construction boxes oh and then I tried
to give 15 more or 16 to fuaa but she
didn't want them so I offered her a hat
instead and she also said said she
didn't want them she want the Hat I see
yeah I just want the Hat oh okay so you
didn't come across
any stains did you you did not no I did
I did see that Moko accepted a trade
from uh princess beu and gave her gave
her a stain hat I think my
goodness but uh I did not get a stain
hat you were just simply monitoring
princess I actually wanted one of your
hats cuz I thought it would look cool on
me yes it would look very cool on you if
you were to have a hat of empathy yeah
but I didn't get a hat of empathy
no I believe you you keep trying you
will get it you will get it I don't want
to spend the rest of my money I like
being rich oh I see yes you are the
richest in the land I don't know about
anymore with only 30,000 coin I believe
you are still the richest in the
land well you are so kind I hope I can
maintain that I'll try to stop spending
money yes yes well I see that I just
wanted I wanted to clear it up since I I
caused a problem oh it's it is fine I
it's my fault for assuming such things
it was just you are so silent when you
are following the princess it's it's
understandable I was trying to figure
out what she was up to ah I see do you
know you happen to know where she had
gone has left uh I it it seems like she
is doing the same thing I am but I don't
know what her motive is oh but she is
doing it evily and you were just doing
cuz you had extra hats I was doing it
because I wanted extra hats oh I only
have this one hat and I wanted all of
them and I thought surely I'll be able
to do it very easily and I was incorrect
I see I see well yeah it looks like she
is also I hear I hear voices in the
land she is not to be
trusted she got two right after each
other that's not freaking fair it is not
fa there it's just corruption that is
allowing
her but yes I was simply I was simply
following her so that is my report is
she she's she's up to some dastardly
plan surely well do you do you know what
happened to the fluffy ones
chickens no but I noticed it was weird
before I had to leave for a bit I I I
saw the chickens and they were all
intact and then I returned or rather I I
saw and it seemed like they had all
disappeared and I'm not quite sure what
has occurred my
goodness I do believe that it is a
corruption I do think so too it was
right next to them and it seems like
it's only expanding I
am trying to set a trap will you help me
tomorrow so that we may find out who's
doing such an evil thing yes of course
we need more allies
in we need all the help you can rely on
Scarlet wand we are too smart to fall to
the foul plans of Princess beu and the
stains and the
King just the king I will be sending
letter to Amelia Watson in attempt for
her detective
skills I believe and we will get to the
bottom of this one way or
another yes well I shall leave you to it
then thank you dear best of luck Nur
Raven Jonathan thank you Jonathan thank
you Jonathan thank you thank you goodbye
farewell
we need a
detective seems that I'm safe
to catch my
letters let me get my letters so that I
may send them through pigeon through
carrier
pigeon I must be careful it seems the
princess was near this
area see her I see her in the the
distance
our letters are still
here I will write to them at
[Music]
once and we will send them
off
yes well let me
well dear voice is in my head there is
much to do today there is much to do
so I must be off to confront these
things there is much to do but let me
thank the voices the dear voices in my
head before I
go thank you for being here for me
through so much there is so much going
on H is
this all right
today two days messages thank you
assassin for your for your thoughts your
n Reco storyline has been the highlight
of my week you're so much fun to watch
thank you I am glad that my perception
my my mind's
eyes so entertaining even though I am
going through so many uh trials and
tribulations
thank you Casey for the thoughts sir
Jonathan please hear my report aain
entered the city earlier this day lady
bloodflame and the owl looking one both
witnessed this
event what a report it seems I will have
to speak to them in another time yes we
will have to
speak thank you Karen for the the
thoughts I salute you sir Jonathan G
huzzah huzzah to you
thank you tiger for your thoughts
Jonathan G truly
is I'm not safe here we must go to the
coast the coast is
safe
[Music]
yes thank you for the red thoughts
I kneel before the goat the goat what is
the goat the mountain
goat thank you NE matric for the
thoughts huzzah for Jonathan G and for
Queen Tam Gander yes for the queen
huzzah thank you mind of the quill for
your thoughts I shall support you
through this endeavor to build a
beautiful mage of the true Queen sir
Jonathan G please continue to protect
this land huzzah huzzah I will probably
be online very very late hopefully that
hopefully no one else is in the Kingdom
that is um projecting their thoughts
because I will be very head off as I am
thinking of what is going on and
hopefully I can truly finish the the
queen statue with some a little a little
more embellishments but she is pretty
much 90% done and if I am to leave her
like this I would be satisfied I would
be
satisfied thank you s for your thoughts
have you heard of The High Elves what do
you mean by that what do you mean thank
you black friction for your thoughts kfp
love you Jonathan thank you for being
such an amazing lad hope you have fun
with my ooshi and all the girls huzzah
huzzah I do truly very appreciate lady
Shakira and all that she has done what a
wonderful wonderful woman
woman thank you R Ru for your thoughts a
toast to Jonathan G champion of
tournaments humble night of the realm
and soon restore of lost souls huzzah I
do not know if I will be the restorer of
lost souls one can only hope one can
only
wish thank you for your thoughts kanano
another addition to the tales of noral
sir Jonathan huzzah thank you weasel for
your thoughts sir Jonathan the real and
all the lands
huzzah thank you kuira for your thoughts
per chance your memor of Jonathan G is
overwritten like a pearl would Jonathan
be willing to create a final Journal it
could be both a recollection of memories
and a memo for your past self
mayhaps I do hope to write a little
before or the journey
tomorrow before everything is to happen
I hope to have some alone time in which
I am able to mayhaps write a final
journal and hopefully I can write a last
journal before
anything terrible were to happen that is
my wish and I hope that I am able to do
it I will probably be in the Kingdom a
little earlier than usual tomorrow to
make sure that
we are all you know everything
is ready that we are ready to take on
the next
day we will have to make sure that there
are no no Loose Ends before this the day
this
battle thank you sidescroller for your
thoughts oh Jonathan G Body and heart
fortunate Agony thy scars thy pain or
evidence of thy true feelings let none
deny thy Pure Heart thy heroism thank
you huzzah huzzah thank you fret for
your thoughts even the most stward night
will falter when the heavens fall we
might only be voices but we stand with
you and your voices are everything they
give me so much strength to continue to
look onward
tah thank you playable for your thought
she may not be the mother but she's the
mother that stepped
up oh but I am no I I remember I am not
pregnant but thank you thank you for
your thoughts oh what a relief I was
quite
I was very terrified of bringing a child
into this world especially knowing that
I would have to go through the trials
and tribulations that Nur ravencraft
went
through very very relieved to hear that
I am not actually male
pregnant and then I would have to raise
the child all by my
lonesome and it would have never known
another what a terrible
fate thank you Ritu for your thoughts
that must be a modified artifact there
are many witches in in this Kingdom sir
Jonathan there are we must remain over
Vigilant we do not know when something
will strike something will
happen thank you tin for your thoughts
sir Jonathan I'm glad that you do not
have to go through the Pains of child
birth thank you thank you I was very
very terrified I am ever so grateful
thank you rtin for your thoughts Cham
Gander forever I am going down with that
ship we are thank you friend for your
thoughts I do not know who you're
speaking I love you Jonathan Oh My Heart
Belongs to another thank you Sonic Jerry
for your thoughts we will all be strong
together sir Jonathan huzzah
huzzah thank you corano for your
thoughts once again and we will fight by
your side huz thank you ELO for your
thoughts I believe it approprate to call
this brave knight as sir Jonathan with a
G as Brave knighter name was Sir huzzah
I would gladly accept such a title thank
you Juna for your thoughts stay strong
sir Jonathan G thank you mry for your
thoughts be gone which nope we have
cleared the misunderstanding it seems as
if she was just hexed for the moment and
she could not speak because otherwise we
would have heard other voices and that
would have been very very
bad yes yes
yes thank you re for your thoughts Raa
is vu's Mother and Tam agreed to marry
her I don't have a good feeling yes but
it does seem that Mario does know
that princess koseki beu is
corrupted I can only hope that she will
fight on the right side of
Justice For Justice thank you red voice
tager thanks for the stream Jonathan I
hope that you enjoyed seeing things for
my
eye thank you Chachi for your thoughts
thank you for being our humble night
it is a pleasure just a pleasure thank
you hunky dunk for your thoughts
Jonathan G need to send a chat because
you have been so entertaining to me this
week keep up the good work I am glad you
are enjoying from enjoying seeing things
from my eyes mine eyes thank you saber R
for your thoughts thank you for the
stream thank you for coming thank you
John EG for your thoughts I think we may
be related I hope all is well cousin
huzzah oh a fellow John huzzah to you
but I am Jonathan with a g at the
front thank you Sonic Jerry once again
for your thoughts thank you for this
wonderful stream sir Jonathan
huzzah what was
that oh no it may be too late it may be
too late for too many people it is very
terrifying it's so terrifying I have to
send the letters with
haste thank you atog for your thoughts
thank you for another eventful night
Jonathan the princess Must Be Stopped
only one thank you zian for your
thoughts there nights you carry this
Castle Your Grace out shines even the
moon good Tiding to safe travels safe
travels to you as well huzzah and thank
you timu for your thought
we will be there to witness your
legendary journey to the very end please
stay alive sir Jonathan the humblest H
haah to you as well and I'm sorry I
cannot Lo loow on for your thoughts H
thank you for your thoughts well I will
be seeing you
all it is very important that I send
these messages you understand right you
surely understand the weight of these
actions so I will see you in the
tomorrow please take care and
be careful there are things happening
that we do not even know that we do not
understand and I can only hope that
tomorrow will be a better day and there
will be peace in the lands farewell
voices take care of yourselves
[Music]