[Music]
he l
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
he
[Applause]
[Music]
n
sorry oopsie
K I'm so
confused K Kitty ah oh
I put the local time back on the
screen it's been a while since I had
that I'm so confused guys I was
looking for some snacks that I thought
existed uh but I couldn't find them I
was pretty sure I had some
cookies and now I can't find them where
are my cookies who's stole my cookies
not healthy snacks no no
no who stole my cookies they're not
dream
[Music]
cookies I I think we might survive
without them but there's no
guarantee no I I I I I I I I ate the
same cookies previously but then I
bought a new package recently
and I'm pretty sure they should be
around but I looked everywhere now and I
can't find the
cookies and that is very sad a sad day
for no
cookies you think I ate them all I
wonder who could have eaten them well
realistically only me
but I want to blame the
Takis chunky won meowing in the distance
hi hi
baby what did you take my cookies did
you take them did you take them not to
eat them but to annoy
me I will catch you come
here you can't just go under my desk
like
that I need you
sorry sorry sorry sorry I had to catch
chunky wonky when she was zooming
oopsie yeah um me and Chunky wonky we
had an awkward moment today but um we're
doing
well how you guys doing where did the
1980s Fitness lady go she she's she's
she she needs to dress appropriately for
the Wild West
I mean it's not is it even the West is
it probably more like the central the
wild
Central right Las Vegas is kind of more
in the middle
right gosh it's
hot why is it
hot oh
[\h__\h] West it is west coast oh okay but
it's not on the ocean
right let me connect my my
[Music]
fan okay do we have it Dyson
yes Dyson
power I don't know this room this room
is just really really hot all the
time okay guys we're gonna play some New
Vegas
today and I was going
to
continue with the main
story only I had AC you it's going to
continue with the main story
but [\h__\h]
but uh maybe sorry it's like chaos
everywhere holy
[\h__\h]
um continue gambling no no no no no no
no we're just maybe maybe we'll check
out a vault just one for today maybe one
Vault a day
keeps the leion
away
possibly okay I think I think I I'm near
Vault
21 TW
21 whatever is new buy is nice 21 and 34
good okay okay I'm just outside of it
it's on the Strip oh is it the one that
got like made into the
hotel cuz that's then that's not an
active Vault right
can we see active
vaults is there active
Vault there's no active
Vault
what the define active active is
depend you mean that there's like
maybe they all f we're already past this
is there not a single Vault that
like still continues to this
day well that kind of changes it I
thought we could see active
vaults oh that's so sad everyone left
the
vaults really what the [\h__\h] I'm late to
the party I'm always late to the
party huh a
well I can't believe it I can't believe
it okay
well I'll have to think about
that is this too loud
guys is this too loud for
you I mean most the time we won't have
any bgm
anyway uh I'm so sorry that this is how
I play the game I want to play it
safe me happy
[Music]
birthday H oh [\h__\h] Japanese
keyboard I'll turn it down a little bit
I don't
know and then Cal calibrate
myself okay should be
good
o m where are we uh ah hello why am I
crouching okay why am I slow why am
I okay H uh what's happening why do I
have to
press uh shift to be
faster oh caps lock oh
[\h__\h]
ah okay it's undone
okay yeah this is like the NCR I
remember let me see what what are we
what have we been up
to we have a few quests this is like
this was like for later you guys will
tell me when I should be doing this
right like when we first got it you guys
said don't do it
yet I can do it
now
[Music]
oh work for the Crimson
Caravan I don't know if I'm interested I
don't really know if this is interesting
wal is right there if you want to take a
peek
okay where
this no way it's this is it and the like
entrance is kind of lame no that's just
a workshop
okay uh to my right
okay Vault Vault usually they have big
ass doors
no
h oh it's still yeah right it's a hotel
okay Hotel this Vault ah Vault 21
Hotel what
where's this
this that's a gift job can we can we get
into the hotel for the oh you're wearing
the
suit all right that's at least
something hi I'm Sarah Sarah win welcome
to the finest Vault hotel in the whole
world can't even pronounce your own last
name girl what happened to you huh who
whoa whoa who he y I stopped moving
apparently as well that's of course
wonderful here
uh a vault Hotel was it like this before
the war no silly of course it wasn't
always a hotel I grew up in it I love it
my favorite place in the world not that
I grew up in okay okay I never left this
place come to think of it but it is the
most special Vault
ever okay what's so special about this
Vault My Vault is pure New Vegas
everyone has a chance and Lady Luck
Smiles if you play your odds right okay
it was like that before we had a gamble
Vault smart ways to help people get
along all arguments and fights got
solved gaming [\h__\h] this I swear to God
always not working rently if you
like what did you just say I was
screaming I didn't hear you over my own
screaming what did she say if I want to
go inside what did she ask
me
kak if I would like a tour oh [\h__\h] yeah
R Daddyo let's do it it better not be
dangerous all right please follow me
we'll head into the Vault right away is
this free I'm getting a tour for free
this shouldn't be
free Vault
tour oh man this seems
cheap is it even real huh is this even
real or is this a tourist
scam this bunker protects the entrance
to the Vault solid Stone outside and
thick Steel on the inside M thick Steel
eh what you want to talk to me good to
see you again yeah I'm right behind
you continue the tour
please
what okay see you
soon oh okay there she
goes D these people probably don't have
many tours going on huh not many people
around here asking for tours I might be
the first one in like months
huh whoa it's
real hey yeah what come
on do the
tour mhm so far it does indeed look like
a like a
tour H like a
vault don't know if it looks like a tour
above us there's a control center for
this level of the Vault life support
systems why you talking to the
dog why you talking to the dog does he
look smarter than me just because his
brain is on the outside rooms although
it is no longer symmetrical after Mr
House thre us out she should address me
not my dog
man hello yeah
hello
oh oh wa is it really a gambling
B oh I hear voices is this a bug sound
bug cuz I don't see any
people or am I going insane
already say
something don't act like you're saying
something and don't say anything this is
the main game here we settled the big
disputes among the vaults levels chosen
Representatives gambled against each
other here the winner earned the right
to settle the dispute as wished by the
collective so they they did gamble about
any kind of like decisions and stuff
like that that is I I I can see how that
is a [\h__\h] to clean later but well worth
it I can see how that is a a a
a a
experiment if people can figure out
problems oh there's chess is that chest
Yeah by gambling and
gaming this the
baby
baby baby
oh baby wait did baby write something or
is it just
we oh yeah it's going we we we give it
some milk oh did the baby hear me my my
calls for
it
a I'm so happy to see the baby some
people maybe don't understand but that's
okay the the baby is a meme an old meme
at
kfp the dead baby
lives a
a stop talking to my dog he's not
listening especially cuz you're not
saying anything don't confuse my
dog a where are the people Sarah what
happened to the people how did this
each side of the Vault had one but the
other is filled with concrete now okay W
it up I'll see you soon that wraps it up
what about the history of why this
failed this looks like
fun why did it
fail I guess she can still tell me when
I go back up and ask her some questions
maybe
h o
oh
oh I mean this looks not very
comfortable but uh it works if it works
it works go away the beds look
okay can I can I will I get in trouble
if
I do something
here oh history of Vault
21 attribute to to Mr House opening to a
new world Paradise of
equality VA 21 has a story unlike any
other nuclear fallout shelter you are
about to learn why it is common
knowledge that some vaults were built
and organized with motives that went
beyond their function as safeguards of
our last great hope the hope that
Humanity would survive even the worst
catastrophe imaginable nuclear war Vault
21 was one of these experimental vaults
in the spirit of Las Vegas our vault was
built and organized around gambling
sasuga everything you will see here
follows the idea that humans can coexist
and organize their lives based on the
principle that skill is the only factor
that should tip the blind balance held
by Lady
Luck H we embodied the perfect
equilibrium between self-reliance and
social equality each level of Vault 21
was symmetrical and transparent each
room looked exactly like the next and
every gambling place was built in plain
sight so that no person would have
advantage over another thanks to this
quarrels in our society were soled from
an equal starting ground the best one
just like our American Dream promised so
long ago I wouldn't say the best wins
when it comes to gambling that's just
the luckiest
wins after 200 years of living in
harmony we finally awoke to the nature
of the outside world when Mr House in
his able wisdom resurrect oh okay so
it's not a failure it's more like they
were just uh freed by Mr House when he
thought it's time to open it up but I'd
like to find out more about that
decision that the
timing ah maybe it's this one 7 years
ago Mr House rebuilt and organized the
great city of New Vegas vault 21 rests
in the middle of the strip and it was
inevitable that it would become part of
the city's bright
future yeah it's like the first couple
of people who started Living there I
guess Mr House contact our community and
offered us to participate in the
Resurgence of New
Vegas kind of forced out but it seems
like they were happy to do it most VA 21
ah never mind
immediately uh yeah the refused the
offer life was comfortable safe and
fruitful we had grown so accustomed to
the benefits of our isolated society
that we could not conceive leaving it
behind for an unknown future teetering
on our precarious
balance they are addicted to gambling
but don't worry guys you can gamble
outside
too this place is like Vault and there
show it's like a lot of vaults in New
Vegas they're Mysteries yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah I get it I get
it they challenged on Mr House's behalf
each of the Vault levels Representatives
that supported continuing our isolation
according to the custom a game would be
set up where the winner would decide the
course of the community's future a game
of blackjack was scheduled and held in
this very level of all 21 after many
hours of grilling struggle Mr House's
supporters won in an extremely risky and
Fateful Gambit they've decided to open
up the doors to the outside
world H black check it's always black
check the rest upheld our system and
remained true to their promise to abide
by the Victor's decision H after almost
200 years without Vault 21's Halls we
released the seals of the ancient doors
we opened to a new world but so 7 years
ago they left the Vault that's not that
long
ago but was that what does that mean
after almost 200 years
without that sounds like they've been
out for 200 years I thought it was seven
years
with in ah oh I can't
read 200 years in the vault and then
seven years since they've been
out my brain auto corrected that bad
brain bad
brain
okay Mr house with the help of the
families had transformed the most
unharmed ruins of Las Vegas into a
paradise it resembled the city that we
remembered thanks to stories and items
that our forefathers told and secured in
Vault 21 after the cataclysm we were a
struck and caues at once slowly we left
the confines of the Vault and settled
within New Vegas adding aiding it in its
reconstruction Vault 21 a giant complex
of functioning Machinery became a great
source of materials which with which to
rebuild bu New
[Music]
Vegas but wouldn't it have been wouldn't
it have been fine to just open the doors
and let them go outside and like work or
whatever outside of the Vault but then
you can still have them continue living
in their quarters like why waste this
space to leave it empty when there's so
much like you know
why would why would he not want that get
it
that's I don't understand Raiders
usually attack well but then it's in the
middle of New Vegas so it wouldn't have
mattered a hotel
now uh I guess okay so you can stay in
one of these vaults as a hotel okay cuz
right now because I got a tour I kind of
thought it's like always
empty okay
now it's a hotel okay well I mean
but yeah I guess okay I I think um the
fact that it's a vault Hotel makes it
very
attractive maybe maybe does it though
for me it does but for if I think about
a character in this world who was not a
vault dweller and is looking is looking
for a hotel judging by how what opinions
people had about vault dwellers in the
show I mean surely not everything can be
projected onto the game but how people
thought about vault wellers in the show
I feel like they would not be very eager
like they wouldn't really care to stay
specifically in a in a vault Hotel
rather than a normal
Hotel it's very cheap to stay
here uh is like novelty yeah but like
would people even want to stay here
oh well cuz it doesn't look like they
have much
business um Mr House stripped the Vault
and filled its empty husk with concrete
only leaving behind part of the vault's
top level uh this section is where you
now find hospice and where the warmth of
our ancient home remains alive for all
to enjoy you shouldn't have filled it
with concrete what if what if another
nuclear war starts and you could have
actually used this Vault what the [\h__\h]
this section is where you now find
hospit
and we have come to recognize the wisdom
of Mr House in forging a new and bright
of future for all generations of New
Vegas inhabitants without his leadership
the barren Wasteland would have remained
uncivilized uncivilized Savage and
brutal for all time sound like they like
them him we sincerely hope that you join
us in celebrating the glory of New Vegas
and the memory of Vault 21's
Legacy well that was a nice read
tasar nothing in there
okay oh oh who left their stuff
here
ooh psycho
psycle oh wait the cigarettes are still
oh was that my car Karma oh [\h__\h]
okay forgot about the
karma I forgot about it is there
anything else interesting inside of the
vault is this the
exit oh that goes lower oh not really ah
oh that's the concrete
oh is that where the
opposing people's dead bodies were
buried huh huh huh Mr
house huh tell me about it Mr House why
did you fill it up with concrete why did
you have to do that
H is that how you how you took care of
all the refusing parties who didn't want
to go
outside for sure that's what he did ah
oh
damn
it I can't I can't turn it I [\h__\h]
can't turn it this mouse is
ridiculous oh look what I found worth it
worth coming in
here botle cap botle cap la bottle
cap
M nice yay oh yeah 2,000 caps ooh
Sarah's terminal Sarah is the lady from
above
right y what's
happening she's typing something where
where am I typing oh okay let's go ah we
haven't done this in a while uh
okay uh I I I think I remember how this
works there's a lot of
BW forc houses boo back bottle borrow
let's let's start
with bottle one of the six probably the
be m
then ah here we go again man or it could
be the e or the O but no that it
wouldn't be forged Barbed could no could
not be Barbed could it be basted no
could not be basted could it be bored
no anything with more than one letter
matching can't be it what about warrant
warrant could be it cuz it has only the
e oh
two out of six
correct e uh
maybe
Bary no can't be
it what do you think it
is yeah the brackets mhm I can still do
one more
[Music]
right do you think it's
Barbed B
ah two Barb no then it would be three no
four even or even more one two that
would be four correct if it was barbed
wouldn't it be four out of six
correct one two three
four ah
yeah it's the position and ah it's the
position and the
leather h
ah h
a but still would then it would be for
right
[Music]
bottle War warrant let me find a similar
Barney no that it would be also four
thanks for the oh was that was that baby
again baby baby baby baby
baby I could be forgees forgees then the
correct one in Bottle would have been
the O Cy forges oh let's
go first try baby we Val reset what is
this stuff what what's hidden in
here NY NY Sarah Vine's
mail
messages interesting hi little sis how
are you holding up I miss you so much
Sarah this place makes me want to run
back to our home every single day I just
had to ride you so that I could feel a
bit warmer the warehouse cold air weighs
on me as heavily as the concrete that Mr
House dumped in our vault damped be his
soul yeah I imagine that you did not
expect that Outburst from your cool bro
but I am reaching the end of the
corridor here emptiness is my muse doubt
is my only mistress every that once
inspired my art slowly drifts back into
the nothingness into an unfathomable
void where neither I find light nor its
Radiance searches for the spring of my
soul B don't I sound pathetic I do not
wish to worry you little sis I just wish
that I could be there with you right now
perhaps once I find my strength again
once I finish the latest suggestion from
Mr house I'll Venture into the strip and
visit you my thoughts are with you
hot-headed Ro
Roadster interesting it's imply buying a
lot of things but I I don't have all the
details it's like he's stuck somewhere
working doing some weird job for Mr
house and he's not not enjoying it not
having a good time philosophy students
be
like he what he's just next door a come
on sounds like he's like stuck and impr
prison somewhere I don't
know Dear Miss wi this is Charlene tan
writing to say thank you for the great
experience we had at your hotel I can't
wait to tell to my inner circle as you
recall my husband Biff is a very
respected and influential man in our
wealthy community Miss shot ingrit
danger and Lady Bon will soon come for
tea to our estate and I will direct them
your way they will love the quaint and
rustic feel of your cramped underground
hole
TR even bib still talks about his new
favorite ranging Garb the lever from My
Vault 21 suit contains the scent of
unwashed Ages he says to all of our
visitors but he won't let them try it on
for one minute dear with most sincerity
Mrs tan so M tan it doesn't mean he got
like a souvenir suit he's wearing
it scent
mail what's shaking my C bro you'll be
happy to know that our vault is packed
and coasting along eh is
she is she lying even with those
legionaires bad news we still get plenty
of NCR squares down here they are all
chirpy and don't appear to mind that
Caesar is cruising for bruising all over
the place maybe the NCR is stronger than
we thought uhhuh don't know do you think
we can trust them over Mr house that is
a discussion I would like to
have no they just didn't want to add too
many
NPCs there are people in the vault where
it's just
me I still feel all clutched over what
he did to our home I mean yeah it is
good that we got to keep part of our
vault but I can't shake the thought that
one of these days he'll just push me out
into the open once he does not need us
anymore I tell you we should have never
accepted his challenge that Sher cheated
us I'm sure anyway you've heard all of
that before and I just wanted to bring
you a smile cheer up buttercup I miss
you h
seems
like oh
maybe maybe the people who actually were
supporting Mr House were
like
infiltrating people who were placed
there by Mr house just like in the vault
in the show where there's obviously a
group of people who are controlling
everything
uh just to
continue have it go their way yeah yeah
I don't know could be I don't
know the house always wins the game says
so I'm
cooking The House Always Wins he won the
Vault fair and square in a wager
everything there is decided be a
gambling
but what if there was cheating involved
ah chuckster cheated us she's sure about
it
h very
interesting very
interesting ooh level 75 to open her
[Music]
locker
toaster so she still seems to be living
in this room
where is the exit by the
way uh I feel like this way yeah hold
let me check here it looks interesting
too
oh
noodles I could take them with me for
food but karma karma is a [\h__\h] K's a
[\h__\h] I should have known
better JoJo
siwa a don't know where to go ah here's
here's the excident I think what was
this can I
people no it's people people being on
its own
[Music]
oh oh wait this is not the exit but
that's that's fine where is
it it goes down
again I'll just explore a bit more until
I find my way
out so the other Vault you guys are
recommending is it
uh like this kind of like not in terms
of the the challenge the mission but
like is it
empty or are there
enemies not as clean it's abandon okay
cool I want to see that that sounds like
we can find some stuff in there [\h__\h] I'm
so
lost Michael where's where's
haikui mayi haikui where you at help me
help
me m
where is my Kye
mey I I remember this like we came in I
think
[Music]
from
oh oh found it thank you haty
cie yes haty cie saved my life once
[Music]
again oh mhm okay let's talk Sarah good
to see you again tell me
more I want to ask you some questions
all
[Music]
right what does Mr House have to do with
VA 21 Mr house has everything to do with
Vault 21 he tried to get us out before
he filled it with concrete M I almost
went eight so we convinced him okay
Sheldon and I right we convinced him to
leave the top level mostly intact oh so
it wasn't even his idea then to keep the
top level and make it into a
hotel why did he fill the Vault with
concrete I don't know maybe he didn't
want anybody sneaking around down there
My Vault runs deep and wide it's filled
with corridors and rooms that go far
what gives him the right to screw us
with the Royal shaft anyway so he saved
New Vegas woohoo now scram and let us
going on with our lives
sheesh mhm
I
see you R the place yeah and you got to
dig what I did with it looking as good
as it should
almost do you miss the old days in the
vault it was bustling with activity we
all knew each other so well you see the
Vault kept us all even it's all Symmetry
and windows down there we solved any
crawls through gambling Lady Luck cast
no eyeballs you know so nobody shafted
anyone else
yeah I miss those
days do you know doc Mitchell who is
that again Mitch you mean mle but I
hadn't thought about that name in a long
time I was just a child and he had a big
mole in his rear bumper you understand
kids and all that everyone knows about
each other in a vault there's no other
way the one that saved my life in the
very beginning I mean Mitch is doing
well do you get a lot of business sure
the place is packed usually huh we get
loads of NCR cubes these days a stray
Brahman Baron once in a while and
recently Circle couples shining big
rocks on their fingers oh damn okay well
then thanks was uh somewhat interesting
and actually was interesting to read the
emails
done you said next door
in here I guess damn slots are
robbery but this is Michel
Angelo where's
Sheldon Sheldon
sh why is so
empty Shel
done why so spooky
Sheldon
Sheldon are you alive or were you
squashed by one of these machines oh one
person okay okay
okay where is she here hello
Kate you going to talk to me or what hi
what can I do for uh what's this place
you saw our front sign didn't you this
is where all the beautiful signs of the
oh you make signs it all comes from
Michelangelo's imagination we do a
little work here and there too sure but
real fake name right who is Michelangelo
he's the reason the strip shines like a
star at night Mike's imagined and built
every sign billboard and light you see
around
here where is he check out the back of
the shop he's usually working
there okay
bye
bye not maybe they can make my dog
Shine the brain's already shining maybe
they can make him I don't know some kind
of cute
armor
Michelangelo M Michael Michael Michel
where you at where's the back
can I go through here
no he was back there
huh that's just
her
where I can upgrade my pit boy what
here right I'll find him
there's a door in this
room the door next to hey yo a
what blind
Joel oh he's
sleeping Michael is that his Vol
[Music]
no cute nice room you got
there oh no he is his W suit oh hello I
am Michelangelo how can I how can I wait
are you here to deliver more billboard
requests no no no please tell me you're
not a messenger on behalf of Mr House
not yet
oh why would I say
this I don't want to say that why are
you so jittery about Mr house because
spending myself to the edge of artistic
Oblivion for Mr House sums up my
existence since I had to leave Vault 21
that's why he's so pissed
[Music]
off what's the problem it's this place
my inspiration es and I don't know how
to stop it I can't feel the warmth
[Music]
anymore oh man what are we going to do
about that
huh why don't you pack up and return to
Vault 21 wouldn't that be great no Mr
House filled it with concrete only a few
rooms and Halls remain my sister was
able to turn them into
Hotel you seem to dread hearing about Mr
H's requests what is the problem now
really kind of know what the problem is
you lived in 121 tell me about that most
people
don't understand what it means to grow
up in a vault its corridors its
walls radiate a warmth that
feels safe honest okay but here
everything is huge and
threatening so empty that I think one of
these days I'll just I don't really see
much difference between your vault in
this place except for this place being a
little bit more rundown but at least
you're not like in danger of becoming
claustrophobic in here as the the
ceiling is pretty tall and all
that what's wrong with this place I feel
haunted by something terrible working in
such a huge Workshop often makes me
shiver okay so he want to feel
claustrophobic what's the opposite of
claustrophobia can you feel scared by
big big open places I guess
so so is this fear of the outside world
draining your inspiration yes I think so
but keep quiet about it without
inspiration I'm as good as a tumble weed
drifting in the barren
Wasteland oh you really believed I
wasn't working for Mr House Chum well no
what
what why what's my end goal if I say
this I don't really see a point in lying
to him and scaring
him try
it I don't want to be a
jerk you can fail the first
one it's funny okay
I should have known that Mr House
wouldn't have sent just
anybody anything I might offer to well
encourage description yeah upgrading my
pit
boy have you have you seen the cost of
pliers duct tape and saws lately 300
caps free I can scam him for free on
caps nah don't worry I I nah I can get
money in the in the with Blackjack nah I
was just kidding you were really
okay for a moment I thought you were
going to tighten my screws like everyone
else around here it's
St why does it still offer me this I
don't
want I got I go oh wait yeah yeah that's
almost what you guys
said maybe you were thinking of
agoraphobia H yes you are right I need
something to bring back my inspiration
oh any ideas oh oh wait that wasn't bad
just because it wasn't enough medicine
actually was no problem
still several years of psycho anal
analysis and a few thousand caps will
fix you I know this guy in freest side
really good at trapping nation grow up
pair and go out into the real world to
find your
inspiration I could escort you into the
Wasteland it's not so bad
[Music]
oh no thank you for the offer but I
think I really can't go to see
wait a minute I know I don't have to
necessarily be there to see
it you're not making this easy screw
hand over the Caps or drop dead no what
do you mean yes yes that's it I have a
camera it is old but it should work
perhaps you could bring me images of
inspiring
landmarks I hate it when you have to
take pictures in games of whatever I
actually hate that
H Mikey photography is a risky why do I
keep on trying to scam him this is going
to cost you a
lot you know I'm tired of this I think
I'll just beat you senseless instead wow
wow what's wrong with me what's wrong
with
me no I'll help you I've always wanted
to see the dinosaur and it's therometer
sign at
Novak then there's the famous bison
Steve sign the McCaron Airfield and the
Helios One power station signs are of
much interest to my work like the sunset
sasparilla headquarters bottle
mhm let's see walk half the world or
rough you up right now Mikey you lose or
Mickey nah I love these answers though I
love them but it makes no
sense uh but if I do this what do I get
in return is that how you get the pit
boy upgrade
and there's so many options to beat him
up I he'll just give me
caps all of those are places I got to go
anyway
okay there is no P boy upgrade I really
can't thank you enough for this please
get me all the pictures I'll compensate
you accordingly you better oh and if you
need more camera film then just come
back and I'll get it for you again thank
you
H what if I just sell the film and come
back and get more and sell it
again no the dinosaur I can already do
right well okay we can do this like on
the
side now what if we really going to
focus on let me look at the quests again
we
have the pictures now we have convince
the Boomers to Aid you in the upcoming
battle I uh we wanted to talk to the
Boomers
maybe tell yes man that you've decided
to ignore white glub Society make
contact with observe the murders at
their Casino
but these
things do you do this if you want to go
independent or do you do them in any
case bug an access point to the Lucky 38
Data Network for the followers of ah
this
this you can get them to join any side
oh oh okay
uh okay there's a few conflicting
answers but
H omerta activities does this this one
kind of goes a little bit hand in hand
with this one
I don't know maybe we just do this one
just a side quest no I don't know I
don't know what to do what should we do
guys I don't know what to do I'm already
it's already ready already too
much
Boomers do NCR quest which ones are the
NCR quests or do you mean I should go
get some
ah the Boomer one is okay convince the
Boomers to Aid you in the upcoming
battle the
Boomers okay where are
they there is one
Arrow oh I think I see a du
sign is that the
Boomers no it's the T
something I'll go there
anyway the
tops Lucky 38 so this one will have to
put some bugs in
eventually I've been married for 17
years she where did I
go this is the Gamora H
okay hey yo isn't this already the exit
of the
strip are
they where are they
okay they're really [\h__\h]
far all
right
uh this
way yeah okay we're outside in the
Wasteland
yay yay
yay yay go to Camp mcaren
first oh thank you for the Super Chat
Arigato
goas don't know what camp you're talking
about H go back in first what what
McCaron
what what are you talking
about the
airport what do I want to do I don't
[\h__\h] know with this
game I need
to be guided what is this the airport I
don't
know you don't need to
go thanks for the membership
gift
H oh what even more membership gifts
thank you C is
there more
members let's
go welcome you have no choice but to
join the
kfp and I will use your help to
join maybe the
NCR maybe the
NCR maybe just because I've
been you know positively influenced by
them for a while now
NCR weak it might not be the most
interesting choice
yeah maybe uh maybe
um
oh maybe the most interesting choice is
like Mr house or
independent in terms of what
sounds what what do you hiding what what
are you
dog what are you do
what what the [\h__\h]
dog those are just some
cows why would you attack the
cows e
e bloodthirsty
yeah uh were they free Roman did they
have no owner because this is
like all locked
up killer cows they're hostile here
would they have attacked us really I've
never been attacked by a cow in this
game
before
Brahman
BR did I miss my exit no
[Music]
H some can explode no
way you're kidding what is
this this electricity
stuff
ammo oh someone's Shack El Shack Els
like the elder
man oh it's actually I fought these
doors were all like
locked not
accessible o abine kid L ebb
gun it sells quite
well is that
good a un
gun is it good though
how do I want to take all these things
man I'm going to be
so packed
again
oh didn't even know what I was picking
up
nice oh NCR you support the
NCR missile have no weight oh oh okay h
danger
Boomers oh oh are you going to shoot me
no right you're chill you're chilling
whoa there pal you better slow down or
you'll get blown up like the rest of the
idiots who thought they'd scaven in Muma
territory o now that I've got your
attention might you be interested in a
little information it'll cost you but
it's well worth the investment
what kind of
information you can tell me or you can
tell the underside of my boot whoa
simmer down I'll tell you I'm a gambler
and a scout that was easy I've made some
cash from gambling and some cash from
reclaiming Goods that are no longer
being used now do you want my help or
not I I don't know do I need it what's
going on past those
signs oh lordy lordy you haven't heard
of the Boomers no I what rock have you
been living under there a bunch of
artillery slinging grenade Loba jobs
camping out in Nellis wander into their
territory and you're as good as minc
meat is there a way to get past there is
a way and I'll tell you for a little wag
no I'm not paying you no okay well let's
hear it well I know the secret to get
past if you give me the Caps I'll tell
you the secret is C if you make it back
alive I'll double your money oh
[Music]
time to quick save I can't can I not
while talking to
him
but definitely before going
in what if he's dead when I come
back who's going to pay me when I
survive but he
dies okay here you go that page has the
details but it's all in the timing As
you move from building to building I'll
be here watching so I'll know if you've
made it to the gate or not remember
there's 600 caps in it if you make
it well even if it wasn't for the Caps I
would prefer to make it
[Music]
so let
safe yeah I got a
note uh this one the key to avoiding the
artillery is to move from building to
building up the Northwest side of town
toward the front gate stick to the High
cover in the northeast corner n this is
too much
info why Northwest and the Northeast now
I don't know which one of the two
buildings that make a be line for the
gate the Boomers won't shoot at their
own people so stick to the fence until
you make it to the gate also I know
there's an old train tunnel that enters
the area from the south but no one has
ever come back out of there to say that
it is
safe just YOLO and
Sprint go to the corners of the
buildings okay from house to house
Northwest nor
on oh sorry uh okay left side these are
supposed
to what
I I I
what what the [\h__\h] whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa it's not cool that's not cool what
the [\h__\h] man what
[Music]
man stresses me out I'm too old for this
which is exactly why I should be a
boomer oh
man what how do what did I do
wrong
why run
this Arrow over
there run for it h scammer oh you you
mean the all the corner [\h__\h] that was
[\h__\h] I I it I it I it I it I it I it
I it I don't know where I'm going I
Abit I don't get it I don't
understand I don't
understand do we have turbo probably
yeah I'm wondering about the tunnel but
H
uh use a stealth Boy
oh yeah we can we can do that
too but it
doesn't self Bo or
Turbo tunnel's really out of the way
just hug the left
wall without the the turbo you think
that will work let's do turbo let's go
am I
faster I don't feel
faster I'm going faster what it already
wore off
no but so far nothing has been shot oh
everything else is slowmo
ah well let's oh oh here we go oh here
we oh I'm not hit yet oh I'm hit I'm hit
I'm hit Dam
[Laughter]
it
bro I'm dying here I'm dying here my St
packs
sayona doy doy doy
oh are we through are we
through oh I think maybe we're through
but what what now I'm kind of in front
of a
fence are they going to hit me if I'm by
the
fence hug fence okay hug hug hug I am a
hugger I generally am a hugger I dreamed
about hugging GAA last night actually
having good dreams for on
man you know what happened in my dream
it was actually so sweet we were like
together somewhere and the manager told
us that we're going to Japan no first
they told GAA that she's going to Japan
for something for a job you know
whatever and and then uh like she got
really happy and all that but then they
told me that I'm also going and then GAA
started
crying because she was so happy that
we'll be together and I'm like oh it's
okay yeah we're going together just like
with a Hol of Summer last year and then
we hugged and she was crying or crying
she was crying really hard man she was
so happy about going with me going on
the trip with me it was
TI it felt good to hug her even in my
[Music]
dream yeah kind of wanted to tell her
right there don't you move how the hell
did you survive that bombardment I don't
even know I died once but I'm a phoenix
so that's basically how I survive
anything
uh I didn't run through all that arity
to hear your stupid question yeah are
you even human some kind of mutant I'm
human now and I'll blow you to
pieces I I didn't come here to attack
you then just just stay where you are
Raquel will be here any second ra I'll
take this from here Rael I'm Rael Master
at Arms for the Nellis Homeland mother
Pearl our have twin sister by
chance I think I've seen your twin
sister
before uh what What's a Master at Arms I
oversee the security of the Nell's
Homeland from the coordination of its
defense to the training and fitness of
its
population so the fact that we're having
this conversation means you failed
uh are you going to confiscate my
weapons confiscate your weapons
certainly not personal Armament is the
foundation of social trust and
responsibility oh you're that kind of
American all right lead the way follow
close and mind your behavior mind your
step welcome child your sweet time
getting here didn't you I've been
waiting a good five years for an
outsider to come along and visit oh
really
oh she's an ex vter huh tell me which
Vault oh I like your
necklace you didn't exactly roll out of
red carpet those hoers of ours aren't
just for entertainment child thir
explosive ordinance is what keeps the
Savages at a distance except you there's
something special about you child and it
was the howitzers that gave you a chance
to show
it how might I be your
assistance oh so many ways small ones to
begin with so we can get used to what
it's like to have a Sav Outsider around
excuse me what you say should that go
well it maybe you can help in big ways
too we'll have Savvy
Outsider how can we trust each other if
you're going to be keeping secrets you
have to keep in mind that you're our
first contact with the outside world
since I was barely a woman savior
seclusion has kept us safe but the world
around us is changing neon lights in the
distance patrolling robots
soldiers my youngers think our guns can
keep out the world but I think we need
to let it in just a little or become its
victim you're that little bit of the
world child welcome to
Nellis okay okay
um okay
a good time to stop by for we're
swimming in problems my youngers can
tell you all about it Rael could use
help the bug problem du has wounded he's
tending to zumers and Boomers and loyal
and Jack might be looking for help with
some
repairs or you could just go see Pete at
the Museum and hear the story of our
people yeah all you have to do there is
listen a should I stay a while and
listen you like don't help I leave it up
to you but but I hope you'll show my
youngers that not every Outsider needs
to be blown up uhuh what your step
sister I'll show them something oh you
look like a
Zoomer actually it's so cute how they
decorated fabuliz their
outfits activate
toilet I drank it e for me do you mean
it no no it's too much well okay but
it's too much I went on my knees thank
you thank you what I I I wish I had
something to give you I wait what what
about punching that's the gift that
keeps on giving what I can work on your
punching with you if you like show you
how to counter like a scribe what she
but she reacted to the dress now what
what
why
why uh okay teach me all right put him
up what are we going to let's see what
you got punch each other now in here no
okay okay black screen okay was very
delayed very random I thought that I
went on my knees to drink out of the
toilet and she was like oh for me like
as if I was proposing to her she thought
I was going to take out a ring to
propose to her or
something that's the only explanation
that I can give you
that was so Random I don't understand I
didn't think I was act like activating
the toilet meant drinking out of it
[\h__\h]
disgusting you've learned to scribe
counter special move to use this
technique initiate a standard attack
immediately after your character blocks
oh that's never going to happen I don't
even use my fists but thanks girl thanks
I'm glad you figured out the dress
thing come
okay so uh what did they give me several
markers
uh
yeah
yeah seems like
it so I probably have to do this in
order to do this maybe help the Boomers
around nellas
Boomers wait is there Vault here
too I
wonder yeah hi ah hi kids oh Zoomers H
what's up what what are you
wearing this doesn't look like clothes
for a
child interesting
Boomer teacher you're interrupting class
Outsider doesn't seem like you weren't
doing anything bye H like what's what am
I interrupting I see nothing on on the
chalkboard
cute hi yeah you do your thing I thought
I could help you in here never
mind never mind what about in here
Nellis medical
station I know mother was letting you
wander Nellis as you please Outsider but
I have patience to tend
to I'm looking for ways to make myself
useful I have three patients here who
were Gravely injured fighting those
giant ants in the generator building a
few days ago I've stabilized their
wounds but they're in bad shape do you
have medical training uh not enough
sadly I assume the ants T tibular
tibular nastas pierce the patient
anterior tracks
well I don't know actually I suppose
it's possible you should take a look me
trying to fake sounding smart and him
trying to fake as if that that he
understood that injured boomer this
man's lag is lag is seriously damaged
and will require amputation and proper
treatment will kill
him medicine 50 or higher
yeah can I not help them medicine 60 or
higher I don't even have I don't have
like how much do I
have you can do
it
really this one's 40 or higher could try
wait no
don't you have 30 gamble you have 30 but
can raise to 40 but does it even mean
anything if I just help one person
and the ma the the the magazine I'm
guessing I don't have it with me I have
a
cookbook science + 10 explosion plus 10
I can blow up their
legs sneak plus
10 I guess the other stuff is
in Novak or
so I can help them
later watch
your the bombardment was so hard my
whole internet broke on
what that's crazy it reached
you let's see if we can do something
else do we have to do all of
this in here now let's boom resume
H hi hi
Pete you going to talk to you you're the
outsider mother Pearl sent word that
you'd be stopping by you must be eager
to hear the story of our
people do you know anything about your
people you're so young what do you know
HH I like to know all about you people
though wonderful I'm sure you've noticed
the mirror on the wall of this Hut yeah
shall I tell you what it all means yeah
it means explosion right excellent
imagine you're the first Outsider to
ever hear our
tale but are you telling me it was kind
of written like imagine you are the
first
Outsider but he said it like I should
imagine it and it's not true everyone
had guns but the overseer wouldn't let
us explode anything not even a hand
grenade mhm the overseer
wait so this is when you left the Vault
why did you leave the Vault tell me
about
that or
continue don't just stand
there move
on what happened
then you don't remember your
lines bro he's
broken uh
oh there's a magazine
[Music]
here what about this one is this also
for a
skill how do I get this boy out of here
so I can steal these
things let me get out I'm back
in are you broken still
how's it going tell me
[Music]
huh does this mean that if I steal
something you're not going to do
anything
either don't save over the bug forever
no
what about this
one just go back
here I'll fix
him I'll fix him don't worry guys we can
fix
him that little boy it's it's too early
for him to be bugged for a the rest of
his life he still has so much so much to
accomplish in this
lifetime so many more people to tell
stories you're the
outsider
excellent okay here we
go I'm
listening Bring It
On ages ago long before I was born we
lived Underground
everyone had guns but the overseer
wouldn't let us explode anything not
even a
hand and then I think he really forgot
all his lines I don't think I can fix
[Laughter]
him
um give him time yeah
okay giving him some time he's he's
try to push
him okay that that might work ages okay
long before I was born we lived
underground everyone had guns but the
let us explod that's the same line not
even a hand that's the same line there
we oh there we go we left and wandered
the Wast they were Savages with knives
we blew them up with frag mines and
grenades burn them with flamethrowers
wow it was neat but there was a downside
every 43.6 Savages we killed we lost one
of our own we need nice math we needed
Nellis
yeah here we have prospered in multi
here our might guns destroy look at me
might try to harm us before they can
even reach our gates are you smiling so
smart why you I'm I'm trying to listen
don't look at me like that har us or
you're a Savage
but
anyways neis has revealed many Secrets
it has taught us how to fly the bombers
once based it looks like that Meme yeah
with the burning house in the
background well we had a burning that is
our story so far something else this
last image is our future oh to restore
the bomber to fly the open Skies and
armored safety running high explosive
ordinance upon ignorant Savages this is
our
what's this what's wrong with you the
entire story perhaps there are details
you like to know more about let me know
you guys seem kind of [\h__\h]
up but at least you're aggressive story
of our people you must have all sorts
which could help in our
situation snow glove there you wait I'll
look in a moment
um I have some questions about your
history why did your ancestors leave the
safety of a vault so you know about the
vaults yes we lived in one of those ours
was number 34 oh fr4 wasn't that the one
the other one you guys recommended but
the overseer wouldn't let you fire off
any of the really fun ones I guess all
the something experiment
is giving everyone in the vault
guns but that's just
America but there must have been a lot
of murder
upon fights
damn
Yeehaw little pops and bangs at the
firing Rangers just got boring after a
while yeah I love it when I throw a
grenade and it go
bang you're people people were willing
to risk it all for Freedom you people
were really crazy about blowing stuff up
yeah keep that opinion to yourself when
visiting Nellis Outsider it makes you
sound ignorant anything else you want to
know sound
European that's what it is but you are
ignorant you're so ignorant you don't
even know about the existence of Europe
and that makes you
ignorant so where are we at with that
huh small boy all you know is about your
shitty Vault that's all you know you
don't know anything about the outside of
the world you don't know anything at all
my rope no your
rope I'm surprised NS was empty when
your people found it how do you survive
to one of
[Music]
the several automatic Warheads detonate
here years ago leaving the
base even read the Savages of the was
ignoramuses all avoided Nellis by habit
what
what whereas your people had brought
Geer counters with them from the
Vault what's
that making a radioactive scrub we're
roasting him I want to roast
him yeah Atomic not automatic little
[\h__\h] to measure radiation attracts
radiation uhhuh
that's exactly right you're very
knowledgeable for a Sav an outsider
anything else you want to know you cut
it off very purposefully
huh how what are how witzer doing at an
air what does that mean how has no
taught your people to fly once we
restore power we learned that some
elaborate shares we've been sleeping and
were actually virtual reality
simulators we believe they were used to
train combat Pilots interesting we use
them extensively I alone have shot down
over 500 Chinese Zion 85
Fighters before you
ask
he he cut that off like I have shut down
Paws
s don't cut it off like that bad reading
bad reading no way you can be allowed to
use the simulators they're for our use
only sorry
this this boy who hired this
boy man oh to slip the sirly bonds of
Earth and dance amid the storing
birds that is the that is lyrics of the
next hot to song that's beautiful yes
it's exactly like that so free so words
can't do it justice keep cooking that
kid he
distur time to dance with the angels
how do you Sur did you learn where to
find an old bomber how do you survive
totally cut off from the world neis is
completely self-sufficient Community we
draw water from Lake me solar arrays
provide Power and we grow our own crops
little smarty
pants I need more survival where did you
get your protein oh my God you're all
cannibals are
they I guess poor nutrition going
explain a lot huh
the Ingenuity oh I don't have any good
choices do
I cuz this is not a good word is it is
not a
compliment I don't think none of these
are
[Music]
compliments oh it
is ingenuity Oh I thought it means like
you're not
genuine it or is that what it
means you're I thought it means you're
not not
genuine it means smart for
Americans oh you guys are so smart thank
you our self-sufficiency is a point of
Pride anything else you want to know
H um not
really loyal found a file somewhere on
the base with magazine articles
photographs a map even it seems that a
bomber apparently the means FL
in Lake me on July 21st 1948 I think I
knew that one just imagine that's over
300 years ago oh did I the photograph
shows that it was basically intact and
the map tells us exactly where to find
it except we haven't left Nellis in
decades oh I can answer this one you
could attach ballast to the plane and
then haul it here for repairs yes in
fact that's exactly what loyal has
planned to do you should go talk to him
anything else you want to
know yeah you're right they weren't here
when we discovered Nellis we found the
guns at a huge weapon Depot called area
2 many miles from here M it took many
weeks to drag the guns and their
ammunition back to Nellis and it was the
last time any of us set foot beyond our
homeland that how it's a batter is a
monument to the grit and resol of your
people I don't want to suck up to this
little [\h__\h]
thank you so much I'll be sure to pass
that on I wish everyone were just as
interested X is there supposed to be XP
showing up here cuz I hear the sound
voice
okay gosh there's a lot of folks argy's
our doctor he could use help tending to
any injured we got over at the workshop
loyal and Jack are always building
something the loyal may not be too happy
to see your kind running around
Nellis okay goodbye
bye oh oh I've been accepted okay okay
okay that was good of
me yay a bunch ofs who scor Outsiders
and hold technology over them sh don't
say that where have I heard that one
before don't say that stuff out loud
okay where's this
uh where is
the snow globe you guys said there's a
snow globe ah I see it can I take
it
[Music]
yay another 2,000 caps let's
go
okay follow the
arrows now I'm not so surprised anymore
about being shot down by these people of
this kind of way of
thinking oh hi sorry no time to talk
Outsider whoa whoa let me
in
whoa
oopsie o
but nothing here I think for uh my quest
is there they're like out there oh no
you guys are oh Jack you're the outsider
Hit the Road Jack and don't you come M
no more no no no but I hear you sound
like us I am you I'm looking for ways to
help out what I could use is some scrap
metal it may not sound exciting but
around here we have to recycle every
have some scrap metal the other thing
you being from the outside and all well
I guess you'd call it a personal matter
but
well H forget it no tell
me a personal M handsome guy like you I
bet there's a girl involved you think
I'm
handsome wow I wonder if she does too
she M tell me about this girl that
caught your interest tell me there's an
outpost near here the signs say Crimson
Caravan it seems like they carry things
to and fro for people out there I think
I was supposed to go there anyway while
I watch The Outpost through one of the
spotter's binoculars and sometimes
there's this girl there this special
girl and sometimes it's like she's
watching me back with her binoculars
except she's probably just watching
Nellis I haven't tried waving try it
maybe I could talk to her for you what
she look like oh you can't miss her she
has short red hair and she's the most
beautiful woman who ever lived you
really talk to her for me I'm fitting
for the Crimson carav she feels the same
way what if she comes here like you did
what if she gets blown up exactly what
if she doesn't like you oh this is this
is the biggest question what if she gets
blown up when she tries to visit you let
you handle I'm better with machines they
don't make my stomach que you should
think about that
one I look into it that would stranger
things have happened as in I would thank
you
forever a Jack's Love
Story your step sister cute I want to do
that because I think wasn't the Crimson
Caravan in this one
yeah heartache what if what
if we're going to go there
now right now
let's
go oh first I get lost a little
bit I'm the boss I am how do I get out
here
here yay heart find the numbers I can do
two quests two birds with one
stone two chickens with one
stone let me out
please okay here we go finally we
are
uh kind of oh there's a lot of people
finally we have a a uh uh this um what's
this word we're
determined and
confident in our
goals oh little
robot flying robot
drone oh what are you doing Mr gutsy
I want to talk to
him
yes imagine she likes him back and on
her yeah exactly that's what I'm saying
what what what if she does come here and
then you guys are so [\h__\h] up you blow
her
up should really teach you a lesson
about that kind of stuff am I not going
to get shut down by these people anymore
also oh wait I should go back and show
him I'm alive
right I'm still
alive I'm still alive well let me let me
first find the exit where I entered for
here right
no
no I'm still
alive okay I'm on good terms okay
wasn't it that
way yeah pretty
big this place to be pretty big Loyals
house oh wait isn't this oh I passed
here before [\h__\h] uh it's like more like
down there
no let me go
here yeah yeah perfect I
think this is that
way
damn now the question is is he still
there but you guys said it's free money
and seemed
like you guys were not wor about that
so what was his name I don't
remember I see
him I'm back
[Music]
yay Jumping Jesus on a pogo stick pogo
stick you're the first one to make it
through alive let alone manage your
return
trip yep here are your caps damn he
likes gambling Al almost look you like
uh from the gambling vault
H what is he not giving me 600 even make
a 700 or I'll tell Boomers to adjust the
trajectory you drive a hard bike here
you go yay have a nice day thanks you
too have a nice
day okay and now we want to go to the
Crimson Caravan company we could
go maybe here
get a little bit
closer never doubt the WWA again he
didn't know that I was a phoenix he's
been lacking critical
information oh this was the Crimson
Caravan I didn't realize that was that
oh
[Music]
oh oh wait no this is not what I thought
it was wrong ew
ew oh okay never mind I was I thought I
thought that these bags were the insides
of the Brahman from afar it looked like
that to me that it was like muscles or
whatever can you tell from
here okay who are we talking
[Music]
to here or
yeah red I'm looking for a red hair did
you know the strip's all stirred up
lately or I guess I'll just talk to
you welcome to the Crimson Caravan
Company New Vegas Branch what may I do
for
you I think I'm looking for work I'm
afraid we have no current openings for
caravaners or guards but I am need of a
runner a runner that's almost like a
career that's almost it okay
P complet it I'll take it what do I need
to do deliver this invoice to Dr hildern
you can find him somewhere inside Camp
McCaron Camp McCaron you guys told me to
go there too I need to find that now now
the quest can tell me where that is we
have a quest marker it's been a pleasure
indeed okay where is red hair ch
uh this
one I've heard that securitrons are
nastier than
ever oh I see you J you should go talk
to Blake or Alice they handle most I
don't suppose you watched the Boomers
over and now sometimes do you I watch
all sorts of things with binoculars who
wants to know and why
H I've been inside now as there's a
young man there who has a crush on you
nice looking blonde boy huh I always
wondered if he was watching me back oh
what's he
like oh he's a cat you should see him
blush when I flirt with her no no no no
no that's not make her jealous or so
give her that impression that's not a
good
impression he's nice maybe a little
naive seems convinced you're the love of
his live oh that's quite extreme too
really oh that's so sweet she likes it
I'd love to go meet him is there any way
the Boomers would let me visit
Nellis
um if I say this she's just going to get
blown
up I'll ask Pearl to make an exception
for you this is so exciting let me know
how it turns
out yeah that will kill her and I don't
know I want to see it succeed
[Music]
so
yeah that's where Pearl is let's go
there first and then I'll do the other
Quest now I feel like I'm on a
roll this is
better I
feel I have I have see I'm I'm I I I
can't find the words again I have this
aim I have an aim aim Dole Is No
More in
here oh yeah a drive yeah purpose
yeah Pearl Pearl how is your visit with
us going stranger m
Jack is interested in a girl well well
this is welcome she's an
outsider she works for the Crimson
Caravan she's with those traitors
they've tried to contact us before but
I'm not interested in trading with
greedy
s this presents a bit of a problem jack
isn't allowed to leave Nellis and I
doubt she would make it through the AR I
have to protect
her it would mean a lot to Jack if she
could come to NIS I'm Dan would be no
threat yeah let's just say the speech
thing I suppose Jack deserves a chance
at love yeah you can tell Jack she has a
free pass to enter but he is responsible
for her actions all right okay do not
make me regret this decision Outsider
tell that to
Jack okay see you later bye
bye I hope this Quest will not have a
negative impact on my reputation
here um but
oh what's next tell Jack Janet
this Jack Janet their names are perfect
for each
other tell Jack that Janet Jackson is
that a joke are they making a joke here
Janet and Jack Janet
Jackson totally right
who did you side with I didn't side with
anybody just yet but oh oh who are you I
like your helmet cute can I have I need
this helmet to look like
shinobu she's so cute with her
helmet I want to become pilot
Jack have you seen her the redhe head of
my
dreams am I your redhead of your dreams
guys orange is what they call a red
head in the outside
world
yes good news she feels the same way she
does you mean it that's incredible what
happens next can she come here how do we
make sure she doesn't get blown up I
already talk stop
panicking here take this Boomer outfit
I'll let the Gunners know she's coming
and not to shoot at her oh okay I'll
give it to her then nice nice
[Music]
nice M can I teleport from inside
here
no that's fine fine that is fine oh damn
it damn
it are we the chickens of your dreams
yes you're the chickens I've always
dreamed
of what happened
F
fend
ooh Fe was sleeping Fe was
feing cute as a clementine I love
clementines yummy yummy
yummy if only I didn't always feel
so like when I peel them I feel like I
have to peel all of the white stuff off
of it
too as much as I can I don't know I
don't like when there's too much of that
fuzzy white stuff on
there so I spent so much
time picking that off it's kind of a
waste of
time I'm one of those people
hello again how's your Boomer
friend um he's doing well I come back
when I know I wanted to talk to you
about him again I was
hoping I got a boomer uniform for you to
wear while you cross sells there's one
more thing I have a work contract with
the Crimson Caravan and if I walk away I
lose the wages they owe me that's your
problem you just one more thing for me
and talk to about it I know if I do
it'll just say no I'd hate to lose the
money okay I'll use my speech for it
hello don't worry about
it it's a you problem
but I will fix them
all welcome
[Music]
back are work contracts common for the
Crimson carryon company let's learn
about it first most Merchant companies
successful Merchant companies rather
have them it can be inconvenient to
replace employees on short notice the
contracts keep employees around for a
specific duration of time after which
they get paid after their upkeep and
expenses are deducted of
course what kind of upkeeping expenses
food water living quarters medicine and
clothes just the basic stuff it all
comes out of the company's
coffers are they legal yes and they have
been for decades Now The Hired Hands
know what they're signing up for we
don't hide anything with fancy
talk black company
things is it it's Crimson company not
black yay uh let's I wanted to know all
right Chan asked me asked me asked me
some I've heard like people who whose
first uh language is English actually
say
asked many
times
so shouldn't even be embarrassed about
it Janet asked me to talk to you about
releasing her from her contract ah yes
her infatuation with a she's never met
it's a small camp Mor gets around she's
aware she's breaking her contract which
is undoubtedly why she sent you to talk
to me instead of coming herself
J but she forfeits the wages she's owed
that's the price of contract breaking
take it or leave it but what if oh no I
need a bit
more I don't know if I have a speech
magazine probably
not I need to consider the take all the
time you need ah it's a
suit it's been a pleasure
okay it's h it's just plus
five if only the glasses gave me some
speech
too it's just plus
five may maybe do I have something else
[Music]
I don't think
so vodka
Works men
hats all the charisma
one Charisma is one
Charisma really this works welcome
back
my I'm should I take can I take one more
can I like stack them
take
is welcome back no oops
sorry it's been a
welcome
back
my it
[\h__\h] it's still the same I'm glad to
hear it
what it's been a pleasure I've heard
that securitrons are nastier than ever
welcome back wait I did I did I press
the wrong thing
y
it
it okay
uh this this this and this is a bad
combination but okay welcome back don't
do it in real life ah yes her
infat I'm missing
one can I do one more
thing did you have a hat
no I
think I think uh the there was another
Charisma thing
no or can I take another one of
these The Vault suit well I'm wearing
Benny
suit they don't stack
M
[\h__\h] okay this is annoying
but I'll
check my
stuff
in where the hell is
Novak there Yahoo
oh cuz I have some stuff
there level up return later I don't want
to I don't want to keep on returning
later to things starting something and
returning
later don't don't want to do that we
already did that with the other
Quest m
yeah you guys say you can find speech
magazines here and there but like until
I find them I don't know doesn't sound
like the most efficient way of doing
things wait I thought I had some
magazines
here o
Bo agility P per per perception or
so okay maybe I have to
buy uh magazines I don't know where any
shop
or Crimson Caron shop
[Music]
yeah we got to we got to take a picture
of the dino
though is there a specific spot that uh
kind of triggers
it I think so I think it's that arrow is
it
H this is a dinosaur right there's a one
marker here is that the quest
marker stand in front of it yeah I would
I would have thought
so but I thought there's maybe like a
specific spot that triggers it or do I
just do it on my
own like
this is it like a
weapon
mhm did that
work it's making sounds oh I think it's
taking
pictures can I see
them aim
down yeah cuz it didn't uh complete the
quest just now did it did
it take a picture of the thermom meter
okay more of the thermom
meter oh yeah yeah okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay
okay I thought the face would be more
important priorities
do okay
next uh we want to go somewhere where I
can buy a
magazine but perhaps you guys said in
Crimson Caravan I might be able to get
one
[Music]
uh uh this one this
one ah too late to check the new shop
shop I'm already gone too
late where is the shop in here
is it in the main
room
here wait till morning
outside ah next to the bus stop okay how
do you wait again
uh
here
waiting W waiting
okay boss stop boss stop would be
outside
no
is
there where what is
there what's
there there is always such a
great sign tell me where to go thans
it's the guy by the
shelves okay that one okay okay okay
okay you call that a bus
stump if you're looking to buy or sell
you've hope you have
[Music]
magazines what's a uh Speech magazine
called usually they're always like the
same right
science +
10 uh energy weapons plus 10 repair plus
10 oh you know what I might buy this
just for in
case I don't think he has what I
need I'll buy this
too meeting
people okay he doesn't have it
scrap
metal think I need that I don't know how
much I need but just going to buy it
just in
case see if he has a hat good idea good
idea cowboy
[Music]
hat n that's just uh one hat a Desperado
cobbo but per per plus one doesn't do it
right don't you have that hat that gives
CMA I wouldn't know
where
H I don't know
where then you get stuff for the
guy do the thing at the place then you
get stuff for that guy are you are
you what are you you you're doing that
on purpose right that was on purpose
right
wow what's in my inventory we already
looked at my inventory and figured out I
don't have like the right hat or
so I only have the trooper
helmet on Boon yeah where's Boon where
is
Boon how can I get back to Boon to take
the things that I gave
him you're making me carry the heavy
stuff aren't
you no back inside the dino okay I see
then we have another reason to go there
again again
again back and forth back and
forth okay
okay I thought he would maybe be in my
room but no
okay cuz you belong to me you should be
waiting for me in my
room okay let me see what you said you
came back must be doing something right
sorry I just stole something and I lost
Karma I didn't want to take it useless
[\h__\h] here welcome back can I get you
anything
sure thing have a
look barter plus five cool but generally
we always have way too little barter
anyway we wouldn't even I don't think I
don't think that would
help uh okay
he he doesn't have it either
I'm buy more stim packs true sure thing
have a
look
good
maybe maybe these two I got
money come back
so what's his name again Bo
Boon you a Manny
where is that
bro
Boon where is he he was not in my
room
bo bo at not Manny into the oh is he now
in the room at at
daytime sasuka you're using confusion
tactics on me wait he's not
here is he in his own room does he have
his own
room w w w w w you should be in my
room it's not a motel room right he's in
one of the houses I think
knock
knock what did I do if it's
red ding
[Music]
dong can I even
hello just go in really why is it
red keep walking
you scared me I thought he was running
to me I thought he was going to punch me
we're friends do you
remember no I mean can I look in your
inventory well let me know when it is
without hiring you
again you need to leave he's so
mean what do I
do not without
traveling you need to leave he hates me
he's so mad that I let him
go this is so Yaya
kushy so
menai just to get one thing back from
him keep
walking but then where the [\h__\h] do I get
Veronica back again where is she going
to
[Music]
be you can't help but notice that the
brother Hood barely exists to these
people out here we're like an you just
don't
now I but wait I want to just tell you
to
leave
um we H we'll meet up with the lucky 48
nice can I order to room service yeah
okay lucky 48 that's that's fine now you
is it
time I'm ready when you are I really
just wanted to check your
inventory that's so sad that I have to
go through
this speech plus five I can't wear two
suits at
once so that's not going to
help spech plus two that's not good
that's not good it doesn't have anything
that I need
bro
bro so
useless no he didn't have anything cuz
my own suit is five
speech
no
reload um this one I guess she's
there yeah you need
yeah I forgot what the Sun looks
like why are you in there I don't
remember why you are in there but it
seems like you deserve
it uh thank you for 41 months
yo well what
now what
now I can check a different shop I
guess don't really know where all the
shops
are you think it will work if she
doesn't get
paid Pride East
I'll check one more shop
but I don't know how to find L
shop watch out are
y' like sorry I'm
scared girl chill stop killing
people what' he do to
you is this a
shop make a RS ah you guys mentioned
this one thank
you hello oh you also like dinosaurs if
you're looking for guns talk to Mick no
otherwise
I've take a
gander uh first of
all no stamp PX
bro
wow no stim pack are you for real
do you think I need more scrap metals
for that one thing somebody mentioned
something about scrap
metals I can buy more of them they're
really
cheap free magazines in the strip well
where where where Doo also yeah that
looked like he didn't have any
[Music]
magazines naughty night where is what
you need
uhuh talk to make in the
back thanks for
magazines would you hello would you
happen to
have General no guns I mean I don't know
maybe guns would be nice too but have a
look we have something besides guns see
he does have some other stuff why does
he make it sound like he only
has
weapons oh no
no
a that's not even bad I'll buy that hell
yeah thanks that
helps I wonder if he had a magazine no
okay
thanks Hallelujah thanks for stopping in
oo
oh can I change the camera to see the
front of
[Music]
me I want to see my
frontal hey
hey I'm dressed like Callie's nightwear
now
just with a leopard pattern which I
really do not like hold
F yeah
oh yeah looks
good that will increase my speech for
sure uh where were we
going where are we going uh
honestly I feel like this would decrease
my
speech because it would make me
nervous but maybe it would make the
person that is in front of me also
nervous
so hey welcome back
Yoo uh I'm finally back let's do this
speech 75 are you really going to ruin
what's supposed to be a time of
happiness for her being sentimental is
not how I made the Crimson Caravan so
successful but I'll allow it just as
once I know you had a Sentimental heart
consider it a gift nice
wonderful and all I had to do was get
naked y
have you spoken with mclf yet I convinc
her to pay you what you owed you're free
to leave that's great I can't believe
you went through all this trouble for me
can't believe it
either oh
bye-bye meet Janet back at nalis return
to Jack Hit the Road
Jack yeah I'll go but maybe I should
change my clothes
again what was I wearing this one
damn I need to repair
this yeah B oh I think I remember we
talked about me repairing that last time
and I was like I'll find some I'll find
some armor to repair it with
eventually
yeah oh you think he might have had
some okay I'll check at least the
teleporting is really fast
convincing right I
know I know honestly when call puts on
that outfit and puts on her messy hair
or her twin Tails she's very convincing
to me as well hey there you looking to
she's super cute in that
[Music]
outfit actually surprising I think she
looks cute or rabid and sexy in that
[Music]
one the hair I I think it's the
hair okay can I uh repair it with a
normal leather armor probably yeah
right I get
both see
you yeah I want that messy hair
too cuz Kon Senpai she also with her new
outfit uh she got like a messy looking
hairstyle that also looks super cute I
think that's the trend now we got to get
messy
hair that one is probably Max heal since
it's usually
bugged what wait I only shouldn't I have
two of these leather
armors oh there's one more it just
didn't oh yeah it is it is bugged
okay well yeah okay well now we're full
Yoo how is my weight looking oh we're
good we're
good okay uh then
teleport this
[Music]
menu two
places
oh mhm what isn't this how we were
always playing
it isn't this
standard oh that was Janet
running oh well but she's here by now I
guess thanks for the Super
Chat doing tearless streams I've done a
few here and there but yeah it's pretty
rare
wait can I uh how how do I undo this
then ah there we
go it's like a Minecraft moment me
playing Minecraft in third person in the
beginning wa I need to be healed what's
with my HP watch your steps sister wait
where's where's
Jack is he outside meeting the lady
are they what h
[Laughter]
my game crashed let's
[Music]
go
cusa don't way I just
screamed my heart
out as if something really scary
happened oopsie oh
no wait
okay let's go yeah I was actually
thinking oh today it's going quite
[Music]
well and there we
go where are they ah oh hello it's great
to finally meet you hi there it's great
to meet you as well I'm glad you made it
out here you're even more stunning up
close than you were at a distance and
you're even more handsome up close do
you think it'll be okay if I hang around
here for a little while so we can get to
know each other better of course it
would I'll have you set up with some
quarters with some of the other women
hello that's it
wow wait was I supposed to talk to him
thank you for getting Janet to Nellis
I've never been so happy in my entire
life
yay I've got scrap met for you by the
way as well cool how much can you spare
how much do you
need thanks need more thanks for
dropping it off anything else wait what
do I get nothing in
return like I said I can never get
enough scrap
metal
bye oh I I just get Fame the more stuff
I give him okay so it's like an endless
[Music]
thing so close to leveling up well I
needed to I needed the I needed the
speech in order to get through the quest
and in order to level
up but yeah I'm like let's
go now maybe we should work on our
speech I don't know or not or not
medicine medicine for the other
Quest up to 40 we can do the 40 and the
501 with that maybe but not the 601 the
60 will be
rough so yeah we can add maybe five to
speech to get up to
70 speed medicine will help with the
healing yeah it's good it's
good save coming exists for that you
mean I should save before it wait no
doesn't even work
what 70 is probably a good break
point yeah I've heard that securitrons
are nastier than ever what are you
talking to follow your man follow
him man I'm I'm such a hero I'm not a
Savage I'm a savior let's
go okay
then deliver the Crim car an invoice to
Dr hilden at Camp
McCaron this is
next
n oh I'm already I've not discovered but
I'm accepted okay wait wait wait we can
go here
wait ah sorry sorry how is it not red
Hello I
can pick it
but no that's
uh that's interesting
wait
N I
can't I want to get it
lower the [\h__\h] I don't get
it why is this I really don't like how
it works in this game I don't even see
the mouse
better with a controller I'm not going
to switch to controller now a suddenly
suddenly
huh oh can I sleep here
no Boomer
Chef why was I able to why why did they
why why did they let me in here why was
it not
red
weird oh cuz I'm liked yeah but not
everything is okay I can't take the food
KCK him out oh if it's a one one on the
bottom level I can sleep in it okay what
your steps sister Hey sister go sister
hungry for GR
oh no
bye I want to no he goes back to sleep
it's okay I can sleep somewhere else
blah blah
[Music]
blah uh wait I was going to go
outside
oh oh that door was that always
open that connected to the same
room what what's the what's the point
don't get
it have you guys seen all the incredible
fan art I've been getting for my new
outfit
she I'm so
happy about the influx of fan art and
it's like pretty damn good there's some
really good stuff
[Laughter]
there it's pretty darn good yeah and
it's a lot of artists who I don't think
ever drew me before which is also
nice something about this outfit must
just be
really
enlightening to
them is it outside of the
farm
probably yeah it's like it seems like
both the BBA people and the leg butt
people are enjoying it
you can see by the art that these
artists draw if they're the kind of
person to enjoy upper assets or lower
assets it pleases both kind of
people something good for
everybody and now I've got so much art
to use for my thumbnails
again very yeah the neurons
urance very nice and also big brain I
can actually used old old F Knight um
art fan art if I still have any that I
didn't use yet for thumbnails for
streams that I stream in that outfit in
as
well two birds with one
stone where where are we where are we
going it's is
here what's
this
ma mcaren
field found
it yeah I think this is the first outfit
that fully shows your legs and exposes
so much boo at the same time well fully
shows your legs you say but I already
talked about this yesterday in my member
stream I don't think there's not much uh
skin exposure but yeah you can see the
shape and everything a
nicely but is it that exposed no not
really and honestly when I saw the
design before it moved I really didn't
think it was that
erotic you know that was not on purpose
it was not on purpose I thought it would
be more
cute and and aesthetically
pleasing but I didn't I didn't think it
would turn out this
you know
spicy I really didn't and I didn't aim
for it either and I didn't ask for you
know
those nice upper
assets what's why am I here again I
don't remember
yeah it made me think like M maybe a PLU
suit is a good
idea but I'm I'm I got to think hard
about the next outfit now I got to make
some decisions soon otherwise it'll just
be so late so damn late hey you got like
casino going on here
too are we going upstairs
I'm not sure what I'm looking for here
than we thought no wonder we couldn't
hold helios's
one plexed would be God like yeah but
it's kind of like not so
versatile that's the that's one issue
little busy at the
moment what is this place this the OSI
lab we don't get many visitors the smell
puts people off I think nobody ever said
science would smell clean and fresh
blood outfit anyway you get used to it
if you give it some time I don't think I
be making another like music video
outfit into a live Tod outfit next I
want to give the artist more freedom
next time whoever it will
be race suit plug suit I was kind of
thinking about race Queen outfit
before uh I don't know why I just think
they're
cute uh
and what was another one something
similar you know those kind of like
themes I think are quite original and
cute say
less I'm not planning on playing racing
games but it would be perfect for Mario
Kart and for sure we're going to get
another Mario Kart Arc sometime
right I have many ideas wedding dress
wedding dress now I also wanted to do
school outfit like
gadu delinquent kind of
version uh or or like uh Tech wear stuff
but I think I don't really want to do
that
[Music]
anymore I don't know I can't decide
there yeah there's too many
possibilities n oh yeah pajama pajama
was definitely up there
because I don't have anything that
like super chill
[Music]
casual and I really
like Callie's
pajamas yeah with messy
hair but no leopard pattern I hate those
those are so
tacky anyway need help you mean give you
work no that' be up to the administrator
hildr he's back there in his office
between you and me I don't think he ever
leaves plenty of Merks go in to see him
yeah the top half with the with the
sweater up it looks kind of comfy and
all that but I feel like the hair
doesn't look like I'm going to sleep at
all so maybe with with a different
hairstyle it could look more
comfy I don't know anyway good
on maybe I can continue working on that
one make it look more comfy hi Thomas
are you the one I needed to talk to hey
you got a second uh no yeah for you
always of course what what is it now the
Brotherhood is
failing I've always known that she's so
Random change course we're going to fall
apart or fade away she's so depressed
but until recently I haven't understood
where we went wrong or how to fix it I
think I need to go
home can it wait
M but yeah I want to go there anyway I
guess to the Brotherhood so I'll take
you back there first chance again great
thanks thank you I'll encourage people
to name their non-ugly children after
you
seriously he made me spit a little bit
when I just laughed out loud a pleasure
to meet you I'm Dr Thomas Hilder
director of operations OSI East I
presume you're here about Vault 22
no this is the first time time I heard
about it no they wouldn't have briefed
you would they probably better that our
Junior fellows stay within the bounds of
their pay grade anyway Vault 22 where to
begin oh boy Vault
22 what what's wrong with Vault 22 is
the
best I'm listening imagine if you will
the Wasteland In Bloom vast fields of
corn that gr from seeds and produce
their bounty in the space cor month
Orchards of trees their branches weighed
halfway to the ground hung with fat ripe
oranges a harvest that could feed a city
or a
nation and all of this all this
requiring no more than a few drops of
precious water and the efforts of only a
handful of human Farmers
impossible nothing is impossible
precisely science has proven that truth
a thousand times times over but how many
Wasteland Savages believe it present
company accept it of course the body I
describ to you is no Idol fantasy it
exists in primitive form only a few
miles from where we stand we need only
reach out and unlock its secret for that
Yosi needs you
me tell me more good I thought I sensed
the kindred soul in you beneath the
Wasteland veneer of course I believe
that the inhabitants of Vault 22 unlock
the secrets of vegetative growth plants
are spilling from their gate no one
tends them no one Waters them so I
become a in all directions find the
reason for this miraculous grow and I
promise thei will generously
compensated
what what that that's it I'm becoming a
farmer good no need to check in with the
NCR authorities I can authorize your
payment from OSI accounts vaults
typically contain a server room on a
lower level where they would have backed
up their research data a computer oh you
want me to find download all the
information your pit boy and you'll be
certain to bring me any notes or samples
that you find won't you hi hi
okay anything else I should know I
thought it was a fairly straightforward
assignment it's a simple question to
retrieving the data which shouldn't
prove CH this downloading the data will
be handled by your pitboard yeah you
might think of yourself as a mere means
of conveyance perhap self contended of
course bye best of luck to you not that
you'll need it you seem like a
reasonably competent
person I like how he's staring into this
obviously not functional
computer it's not even plugged in is
it okay did Dr Hill children this really
isn't any of my business but did he give
you a job yeah what do you mean I need
to stock up on stuff eh is it dangerous
he asked me to get some data from Vault
22 I shouldn't say anything I know that
but you're not the first person hildren
sent out to the Vault there were a lot
of Merks one after another none of them
came back then about a week ago there
was a scientist key she's unusual not
the sort of person you'd expect but
she's an absolute genius and and he
didn't mention her need to talk to Quest
bugs or any of the other
Merks uh he didn't mention anything else
but now he's hired you which means one
of two things either he heard back from
Key and she failed or he's given up on
her listen I make a fair wage but I'm
not rich not by any means maybe my kind
of money wouldn't have appeal to your
average MC but I'm willing to pay you if
you'll find key and make sure she's safe
okay isn't right leaving her out there
no idea if she's alive or dead so a
little side quest all right I had a good
feeling about you moment she walked in I
mean it I have that kind of aura about
me yeah
yeah okay right good
luck what what do you mean I need to
talk to him again really yes something
else you
needed I'm not the first first person
you've sent to Vault 22 am I I never
said you were you've been speaking to
Williams haven't
you
uh no Williams didn't tell me anything
I'm just a
genius all right I'll take you at your
word Williams didn't say anything at all
you just came to this conclusion on your
own yes no you aren't the first person
I've sent to the Vault I'm sorry that I
neglected to tell you but I don't see
how it makes any difference uh it does
about my decision making
hello thank you super snake Mario
hey have fun at work hope it goes well
hope you have a nice
day I prefer to know what I'm getting
myself into you want certainty you'll
never find it especially not in the
pursuit of
science take my advice forget about
Williams she's a talented researcher but
she doesn't understand people and she
can't see the big picture now I know
your time is valuable so I won't waste
any more of it feel free to show
yourself
out I actually saw another prompt that I
needed too something else you needed do
I have an invoice for you from Alice
mlfy from Alice yeah I'll see that she's
paid right away okay that's what I think
I actually came operation even out here
in the waist do keep them waiting was
there anything else we just hear about
the invoice actually yes but I'll do the
Vault thing too yes
goodbye I'll do the Vault thing too we
wanted to see some more
vaults I wanted to see some more
vaults and I think like after this
stream quietly the legion can count on
that um or after the next one or so
maybe Fallout streams will not be weekly
anymore but more like you know how how
Amit was doing
it and like all over the place here and
there like spread it out more and do
more random
[\h__\h] I think that was the plan
originally anyway like making
it um
more like a whenever I feel like it kind
of thing and a longer random
project yeah
I think although I don't like doing
things like that
generally
but is that the
exit yeah cuz I think I don't know
otherwise yeah I'll be rushing to the
end and then there will be a lot of
unhappy Fallout
fans going to be like
you didn't do this and that and this and
you missed this and that and
no oh we don't want to make those people
so
unhappy and yeah I don't know I'm
chilling it's good to have a a game as a
filler here and
there I
think where where are where what where
am I going
what shut the up wrong Quest
oh over there wow that's
far wait this route oh I walked through
here before didn't
I I I was about to say I remember those
mines H Mama Mia
here I go again my my how could I resist
you I don't want to use up all of my
stim packs yo if this is going to be a
Dangerous
[Music]
Mission wait do I have
to yeah okay wasted
wasted is this
is this before after after right is
it ah yeah okay sorry that that annoyed
me it annoyed
me uh oh yeah I teleported out of here
actually I need more stim packs man
where where was that place that sold so
many stim packs and I didn't have the
money for
it where was that again not that I'm
going to go there now for now I'm hoping
that I don't need
it Jacob's
town okay
mines see one there
be careful guys don't get blown
up okay I guess the ones that I blew up
in the past are not replaced yet that's
nice should I have gone on the other
side what oh oh the
fiends oh no it's a legion is it a
legion no a
fiend okay yeah I remember those fiends
here wait isn't this where the Wasps
wear or
whatever the Vault will be a treat
oh yeah yeah
well if you you are oh
oh
hello o oh headquarters oh is this where
I have to take a
picture hi
guys are we back I think I'm at a place
where I maybe have to take a picture
could it be that this is one of
them yeah the bottle
sign bottle sign ah this one
on yeah we crashed a little bit didn't
we
wow okay bring out the camera thanks for
watching
bye-bye also I should eat a little bit I
need more
food drinking Sunset si sarella in front
of the big
bottle m
wait
okay should I go further back oh no it
worked nice well you know what I don't
have a problem with this Quest it's
relatively easy to fulfill these things
so far and I am just doing it on on my
way I like it
I can get a bunch of ss of perillas
inside in here is there people in
here mhi mhi empty wait I forgot the
empty ones do they give me the bottle
caps too
I see an
enemy scanning for hostiles oh oh oh
oh was that his brain step into the open
and identify yourself law abiding
citizens have nothing to fear is that my
dog
talking or where you going for the
Brotherhood please step into the open
and identify yourself abiding ciens
who are we fighting doggle
dogle do
away
to please clear the
are what the [\h__\h] yes let's all beat up
on the
Rob what what what's with the
boxes come on what the what was that oh
oh nice do oh oh you already laid the
ground workor did he dog he smelled
those
robots damn so uh do I
take all of these there's
a single b cup IM b cup go imagine going
through all of
this taking each single
piece should I take the empty ones I
don't
remember
no yeah picking up little
pennies no okay you have so much money
that is true maybe I I would take some
full bottles honestly cuz I want to
drink
[Music]
them there we
go there we go
there we
go
no ah
sorry that's a lot of drinks
yeah I'm going to I'm going to share
with you guys don't
worry refreshment for all of us
I'll drink one
now any PCs that I can hack attention
this is now a combat you may suffer hot
go remain in the
area
by do not he barely
fought water will be restored soon
please stand by is that what you were
saying oh he's got some scrap metal
take
it what's the problem with these robots
let's just be friendly oh Mr janitor we
can talk no it says
talk what should I take the energy
cells should I are they worth
it activate the m the terminal okay okay
okay
okay oh they only have flam or
fuel don't know where the other one
was they're like ammo yeah for the
energy weapons
yeah ah there we
go
okay I wonder if there's a snow globe
somewhere in here I would like to not
miss
it haing to the
gate let's go I want to hack let me
hack no slow snow globe no damn it
okay here we
go convince constructed not notorious
convinces concealed contained handcuffs
creatures interesting a lot of similar
words again let's start
with convinced four out of
nine nine one two are they all the same
length one two 3 four five six seven 8
nine four out of nine correct could be c
o n e n d and then
yeah concerned would be more letters
correct I think continue also more
convinces no that would be almost
everything except the last
one contained maybe no concealed con con
con
assisted one two three no do
Tres
[Music]
one
no renovated
it uh no only the
Ed complete complet this one
two three
con see what do you guys think you have
to think along with
me ah eliminate options yeah true that's
um it isn't it like sometimes it
eliminates options and sometimes it
gives me my attempts back right I I kind
of don't want to use up the chance yet
but I'm thinking too much am I
but four out of nine is already so good
that we could figure it out with just
that I think
one
two Monastery one
two
no try
monitor monit Mon Mon here one
two yeah that looks about right hey y
oh
nice check
mail I want the person congratulate you
on the success of the new automated
janitorial system in particular 145 has
proven very popular with the staff I
can't tell you how many complaints I
used to hear but the straight bottle
caps getting into the Machinery one we
should have a meeting soon concerning
the rest of your stuff how's Tuesday
we've had reports of a possible small
water leak in the upstairs meeting room
the long-term effects of water damage
can be very very expensive so let's get
this problem solved okay not so
[Music]
interesting oh activate worker mhd is
that the
one commencing minor garbage
collection
okay oh let's go wait wait for me I see
my services are required once more it's
about
time that's it you're not going to talk
more of me I want to see him work
though want to see him at work come on
this place is filthy he will collect all
the Caps oh and then I can just take him
from him when he's done or
so you missed one here how much dust
collects if you leave things alone even
for a short while what about this one
pick it up hey you missed it again
you're a bad Roomba bad bad
Roomba I want to see if he actually
picks it
up he puted them in a trash can have
called me
earlier this what about this one or is
it just separate like he picks up the
ones that I can't see oop see
no I want to
[Music]
no how do I close that again this
okay there
go
scripted okay okay
okay but I really should not
no spend too much time picking up single
bottle caps here man
ah why am I here just to
suffer maybe I'll be back if I need more
bottle caps but is it even going to be a
good
amount if it's not a good amount
then I'll never come
back talk to the guy near the entrance
uh okay I didn't see a guy but
yeah 24 bottle caps bro let's
go good amount of your
PO okay I want to leave let's find the
exit
exit oh request
key what is this where do this
lead wait now I want to find a key it
requires a key it made me
curious yeah yeah I get it about the
ammo I get it I just don't want to
like I just don't want to clutter my
inventory too
much with things that I don't know what
to do
with oh is it can I do something
here is this for the door down there no
way found a very interesting
place what the 50 star caps I need it
what for what what
oh star caps you mean those special ones
that we uh we talked about in the
beginning
oh oh okay then what is
this that's that's a short
password
he jobs
check saf inbox
messages how's your new
toy Kenneth I hope you've been impressed
thus far with your recent purchase your
company has been and continues to be a
value customer what is this
about Sir the rumors of some sort of
contest are quickly growing out of
control we're getting flooded with calls
and messages asking if it's true that
we're redeeming bottle caps for prizes
do you want me to make an official
statement denounce this
rumor Stanley are you out of your mind
have you seen the latest sales figures
we're up 300% since these rumors started
and you're asking if I want to want you
to make it stop please stop by my office
so we can further discuss this
issue
scary Marcus I have a few ideas about
how we can turn this whole content
situation to our advantage I'm going to
need to you to work with advertising
guys on a very special project a meeting
request will be sent out soon by the way
how do you feel about
Cowboys I like Cowboys cow are nice I've
never met one before though Lucas I
couldn't be happier with the performance
of the new model if its current
performance is any measure it promises
to reinvent my company's entire
distribution Network I'd like to
intentially discuss purchasing a few
more in the near future how soon do you
expect what is this about what what
robot
what okay not a
some
lore some lore I want
more oh yeah c yeah Sheriff
mhm
100 100
lockpicking damn there's many times
where I see I could have used more
lockpicking
where did where did the robot go I
wonder over there that's where that's
where we found him I think
so where did you put the money
here
[Music]
who
oh to
fear where do they keep on coming
from he senses him where is
he
n aggressive little
doggle oh are you having fun watching
I'm
[Music]
glad I'm still quite lost here and there
but yeah where's the exit now I'm lost
for example I don't know where the exit
I never know where the exits are oh I
Got 5 XP what
happened has a robot been
killed this is where I already was right
yeah damn it damn it can I teleport out
of
here uh
uh no of course not check the
safe
safe I mean a safe file or an actual
safe safe ah
oh
yo
[\h__\h] I hate
this no
[Music]
turn get get lower
I'm running out of bobby pins bro
no I know it only turns when it's
correct but like I'm trying to move
it
no I mean I've been better at
lockpicking in other games yo just just
so you know
h
ah always save scum
lockpicks at this point I will cuz I
only have seven
left no
I'm using WD what do you
mean I swear to God what is what is
wrong with this one ah
what not even worth
it wait except for this one
oh are they
limited do I need to like find every
single one of them in the
world I don't think I'll be able to do
that to be
honest that was locked
too oh how do I get out of here only
50 how many are there much
more where am
I wait
no no I keep on going the same
way
I downstairs okay but not there right
wait
let's but didn't I come from
above hey
oh okay
okay quick double check cuz it kind of
oh yeah see I thought there was a
magazine
there what talk har partner welcome to
the headquarters of the sunset SAS
Barilla company Wrangle up stool and
listen to Old F jaw W if you're an old F
pal say a command now otherwise say
pleased to meet you and we'll get
acquainted or if you have more important
things to do than talk to old F say
goodbye uh please to meet y new town
Porter that old F just give you the lay
of the land if you're here to redeem
your Sunset SAS Barilla Stars dump them
into the slot in the barrel below and
I'll count them up if you don't know
what Sunset SAS Barilla stars are and
think old fesus is just shooting his
mouth off say star info if you're here
to challenge old F to a game of Lucky
horses
say BS if you're he about the health
advisory that aired on Channel 6
recently silly old the stuff that we
read in the
email uh is that connected to the the
star bottle caps is it all a
scam like you collect 50 and you bring
it here and then they they show you and
it's just nothing or
so I think it's all just a
scam
probably anyway uh I don't know
I'm sorry I didn't quite understand that
could you repeat
it I'm sorry I didn't quite understand
that could you repeat it I repeated it
but it didn't really
help a new to the hunt AR you well
listen carefully as old feses don't like
to repeat himself select sasparilla
bottles will have special caps with blue
stars on these caps are known as Sunset
sasparilla
Stars Why are stars there and what do
they mean nobody knows except maybe old
FES wrestle up enough of them and you
can win a prize SC get out there and
start drinking Sunset SAS barill okay I
know it's a scam but I'm going to do it
I'm going to do
it oh I gives me the quest oh
nice okay well we'll be back uh but this
was kind of distracting we wanted to
take a picture and then move
[Music]
on this is how it is I
suppose this is how it
goes now wherever we're going apparently
it's a dangerous place because you guys
I saw you in the chat you were like m y
also I remember we went up there and we
got [\h__\h] up up up up up
a
[Music]
nice oh too
far stop hurting my
dog he my best friend
yeah yeah
yeah bonus critical chance wait does my
hunting rifle have
that oh yeah it does but I can repair it
with that oh let's
go sad veronic an noises well she's
she's somewhere right what do you mean
why is she
sad because she's not my best
friend that's okay because her best
friend is also the dog
didn't know I accumulated so many
things
okay her H her Quest oh your quest do we
have to do it right
away what am I doing right now I don't
even
know oh not the right why did I pick up
the drained ones take it back get take
take it back yeah take it back please
was that in trash a b c d there we go I
don't need the drained ones
right I
think drain is
fine what I do with
them recharged when am I going to do
that but the flame or fuel stuff I don't
need those I don't need those
uh yeah but I was going to do
this I can do this later right we're
going we're going to do this one first
Vault
22 what was that what did I just pick up
man I wanted to open it up and look
inside
yeah I'm never going to craft ammo
probably for the quest huh what
quest okay this place is dangerous I
know
it I don't have to go this way though
right well
oh amolo
true
oops
MH I think my my shortcuts for the
weapons are not working
again let's use Maria Maria
Maria hug the wall do not go up there
yeah I know I've been there before let's
walk around
then Maria
[Music]
Maria Mar Maria mar
mar it's a K-Pop song by the way
map
check hydration check
guys are you guys
hydrated oh that way maybe
stay hydrated don't don't
die yeah it was the mama or like uh
wasn't it solo song from what's her name
again I don't recall oh this is not a
path
oh Vault
to it's the EO again the playground you
eful
playground is this bringing me to that
space station
Place feels like it but might be
wrong
oh it's up there or so
well I guess over there no but this says
stay
out where does that lead I've been there
no yeah yeah yeah that leads to Jacob's
Town ah Jacob's town the place of the
stim
packs that's
it oh
okay what does it say the plants kill
oh oh
really every
plant like do I get poisoned when I step
on
this this one maybe this one
kills o don't touch me ah
[Laughter]
not no everything's okay for
now Vault
22 welcome to Vault
22 the plants are attacking what if I go
up here
first kind of like cheat the
situation is there a secret
entrance that would be
nice nothing there really but look I can
I can kind of like make a shortcut in
case this place was dangerous but maybe
I'm maybe I'm super over cautious what
is this one don't eat me ah don't eat me
don't eat me eat the dog
first okay I don't understand what's
what what am I supposed to be maybe
those mushrooms or whatever that yeah
the mushrooms maybe the mushrooms maybe
it's the
mushrooms okay or it's just
inside maybe it's all just
inside quick
safe
oh o
enter
enter I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared porks and
beans I'm
scared oh program is
diges I'm scared
[Music]
I've established a temporary Camp inside
the entrance of the Vault power inside
is minimal but it's still running and
I've managed to hack into one of their
security terminals the log show that
several people have entered the Vault
over the past few months but none have
left it's getting late so I'll resume
the expedition in the morning key out
she's so dead or she turned into a
zombie or
something the growth in the interior
matches the exterior to a te it's a
little surprising given the scarcity of
sunlight in the entrance room but even
more surprising is that they seem to
originate from fillow maybe the fool hen
was onto something after all since my
pit boy is one of the frits on the frits
I'll try to keep a running log of my
discoveries in whatever computers I can
find and collect the data before
leaving oh yeah she definitely turned
into a zombie
definitely like I mean the moment they
gave me the quest that was kind of clear
please check if she's alive or
not yeah okay
yummy wait I should probably at least go
in here with full health
you think I got this I don't got this
make sure to use bat
okay they still
healing I hear keyboard tappy
sounds what the [\h__\h]
so far so good
[Music]
my dog would sense the enemies before me
probably so we're fine we're
fine oh there's so many paths probably
should get lower
probably oh I hear voices there's voices
in my head
elevator lab let's let's let's check out
the
lab oh
okay the trees will not attack me
right oh oh what what Rex what did you
see what did you
feel what are you
sensing
oh oh
oh interesting this just looks like a
nice little
Greenhouse my mom would love this she'd
have some fun
here why why do the plants kill
people What does that mean this is not
dangerous is
it did that try just move shut up
certainly not
okay okay
okay oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh dangerous plant
probably dangerous
BL why is it lit up with purple
light it can't be good for the plant
can't be
good oh terminal hey
yo okay oh we're on the right track
entry free this level seems to have been
devoted to the study of atmospheric
effects on plants with a concentration
on producing plants with high oxygen
yield given the problems these vaults
were known to have it sounds like a
reasonable Avenue of
research it's strange but some sections
of the Machinery down here appear to
have been modified for some unknown
purpose the restraints regarding oxygen
content have and systemic pressure have
been
bypassed I've been hearing a strange
chittering sound for some time now when
finally discovered its source there's
some kind of giant mantises that have
taken up the residence in the vault okay
that's fine I almost ran smack into one
the other day but the creatures don't
appear to react to my presence at all
perhaps the other scent here ran a fo a
foul of the creatures but I can't see
how a few scattered insects
could okay I hear I still hear the
keyboard I thought it was the chittering
but no could pose much of a problem to
experienced Merks yeah
so you think I'm going to be
fine if it's just a few
mantises where are they
though carep too much plants so true so
true okay
okay I saw that one but it went
elsewhere what's
this
inventory
ah it's not showing me anything oh
should I
wait retrieving inventory information
dot dot
dot this is very funny to watch really
oh nothing happens here it's
broken and here I can't get through
Hallelujah I'm glad actually
I'm going to get so lost again have I
been here no I don't think
so noise
complaint could maintenance look into
the duct work here on level two again I
know you guys took a look at this last
week but I swear the noise is back I
even have other people that can back me
up on it this time too in any case I can
already tell that this Vault did not end
in a pleasant way like the other Vault
we looked
at beautiful
beautiful beautiful
[Music]
this you think so
where where did I go I'm lost I've been
here I've been through here uh I think
like the section I already looked at
everything
huh yeah okay then let's
go back
to lower I came from there yeah no yeah
yeah find a way past the room of the
Mantis I think we can't get any further
there
okay food
production what if I'm going to be
production into a
food what oh for the Brotherhood
shoot them up again kill enemies with
guns yay okay that was a Spore
carrier uh interesting I didn't really
clearly see what it was the elevator
doesn't seem
to no whatever I don't need an elevator
I think maybe I'll regret that
though mhy mhi
time let's
go oh okay yeah we keep on finding the
right ones okay I finally found some of
the bodies of the scientists that lived
here they appear to be overgrown with
some form of lein le le they pled in so
well with the other Grove that I walked
right by several of them without even
noticing them uhoh I've uh taken the
proper precautions but the leion doesn't
seem to be contagious at least to ghouls
what do you mean is she a ghoul Le
lyen
whatever is she a
ghoul was she always a ghoul when she
came in here or did she become one in
here this level appears to be where they
performed most of the research NCR is
interested in I've been able to collect
a little but the vast majority of the
data from the research done here is
inaccessible I'll have to find the main
backup and download from there
okay dead bodies everywhere overgrown by
plants is what you're saying
YooHoo I'll keep an eye out let's safe
[Music]
again so far not too many
enemies not too chaotic
another
PC help okay uh let's read uh this one
first is anyone down there security is
trying to hold off well I don't know
what they're trying to hold off please
send security up at once with Dr Bailey
watching over his sick wife and daughter
in their quarters down in the common
area I'm officially in charge of the
level and I'm requesting security at
once we need medical team up here now Dr
Peters just returned blah blah blah blah
blah in the meantime Dr ordered that
door assistant mavers went into the
caves at 1846 today and still hasn't
returned requesting security escort for
science Personnel to conduct a search
not a hold they're like
panicking oh to what is
it how are you feeling what are you
sensing I wasn't done looking at that
room oh oh oh oh oh I saw
it oh it's a person oh now I saw it
clearly
a okay
okay wait so the the dog finds it before
the sport carrier even like activates
itself
nice cave door AIS a good boy RS good
boy disengage lock
denied needs a key oh behind the
door well we we're safe for now dle
don't worry as long as we don't go past
that
door chill why does he react to things
that are behind the
door not good stuff
they don't carry anything ever
huh is there a spork area here
H maybe is there one I don't I can't
see I don't ah maybe over there that
could be one oh yeah that that's I see
the butt oh what
oh for the Brotherhood for the
Brotherhood
or the NCR whatever we're supporting we
still don't know what whose arm crippled
your arm or what or I crippled their arm
right okay good
good dogu is still
hunting he's still hunting he's still
feeling
something don't leave me behind got my
eyes peeled got your eyes peeled huh
hey yo what's this yields continue to
improve should I read all this my God
splicing together cultiv the existing
corn samples corn has produced a hybrid
that responds better to the artificial
lights on a side note Dr Peters has
missed his work thir day straight due to
illness his work ethic hasn't exactly
been Stellar to this point so I'm
requesting confirmation from the clinic
that he's in fact
sick I think these are not so
interesting
oh I think they're
fighting seems like they're stuck behind
there okay okay chill chill
chill he what I'm learning plenty about
the Vault come
on I'm reading a
lot elevator stairs wait I came let I
guess we got to go lower
again think I saw it what's to be seen
oh if you just shoot them on in the head
right away then seems like there's
nothing to be worried
about this
[Music]
oh
oh elevator stairs okay uh here's so
okay we got to go here seems like it's
over what will we me meet some mantises
here well I hear electric
malfunctions where are
they oh a movie theater how
nice ladies and gentlemen oh it's a
toilet let's
go Toilet Time
[Music]
everybody
oh nothing interesting here maybe over
here M toilet
stinky
Uno
do
this yeah
[Laughter]
Jin that's it right oopsie no
no says okay it was in the mail
toilet be wary of the mail toilets guys
nothing here just a few Sunset per oh
actually nacac
Cola and some Sunset perill S sarilla I
don't care what it's
called
bro okay let's watch a movie I
guess is there something to see no oh
man thought I could watch a
movie I thought we would get got some
lore what a
boore did I miss the
computer I skipped it skip H what do you
mean for real
or if there's another computer with
stuff to read oh there's something here
low our lower
level don't know if I want to go lower
already it might be where it
continues wait where was I going what
about
this
o
no
okay ah okay here I wouldn't have
expected it to be on one of these higher
ones I guess no one will miss this
ridiculous trivia game the questions
weren't even at hard it looks like this
is where most of the people were when
they died the medical reports I found
suggested that most of them succumbed to
some kind of Airborne infection I'm
going to see if I can convert some of
the grow lamps into UV spectrometers to
test the air for
contaminant after numerous attempts I
found a range that highlights the part
particles in in the air that I believe
killed everyone in this Vault
preliminary tests show them to be spores
of some kind I've set up spectrometers
on several of the levels now and the
concentration appears to increase in the
lower levels at this point I'm concerned
that the plants here may constitute a
danger to the people of the
NCR so the lower I get the more y of
course of
course have I turned into a plant yet
I hope
not fungus Among
Us the fun guy is not a fun
guy I'm glad I can use this today cuz I
thought about this joke
yesterday uh
oh
oh we
oh override engaged
okay that door is fine and that door is
fine crew quarters and data
backup uh is that it I thought there was
more cool stuff in this room
[Music]
okay but the unlocking maybe that was
important
important now I think over
there to the lower
level let's
go let's
go I'm doing well so far right I can't
believe it's going to be like is it
going to get much
worse and I'm going to
die model Frozen let's go
ah not reloading in that moment oh oh
he's stronger oh no maybe not I don't
know was
he that's a really good
hint it was good to read that about the
bodies just laying there in the plants
good to know
the
clinic
oh might be a stim pack
here yay
[Music]
nice
ooh Peters Harrison T Dr Peters is
suffering from a severe case of Pia the
result of the spread of some sort of
microorganism in his lungs I've applied
the usual treatment and requested that
he refrain from
working Mitchell Pam BL blah BL this
entire group showed up throughout the
course of the day displaying the same
symptoms they're remarkably similar to
Dr
Peters isn't responding to the treatment
or more accurately his body is actively
rejecting
y a new group of
people with the same stuff oh
no it's the corona all over again Dr
Peters is dead his vital Flatline 10
minutes before he entered surgery I
decided to perform an autopsy
immediately and discovered his lungs
were filled with some sort of
fungi infection strangely the
fungi still shows evidence of growth
despite the death of its host I'll oh
I'll consult with one of the myologist
on the fifth level and see if they can
identify it
I don't really know how to describe what
just happened one minute I was uh
closing up for the day and the next day
next moment Dr Peter's corpse set up and
attacked me I was able to flee the
office and seal him it inside until
security arrived but what the hell is
going on yeah he turned into one of the
plant
people where did you lock him up though
that would have been a Vital Information
for
me to be
careful cuz he doesn't seem to be in
here
also known as
saplings yeah this would be faa's kind
of
Vault
[Music]
utility I keep on stopping so annoying
this discovered minor discrepancies in
the mass of the air being pumped through
the Vault all no harmless homeful
gases o lots of flam or fuel yeah fire
would be good for this kind of
place
sorry I
bumped against my mouse somehow I guess
but there's some tiny like fruit fly or
something flying around it's really
annoying take the LI
pistone y should pour some water on this
huh bobby pin oh my God how did you know
that that's what I need but just
one ooh flame wait should I should I
take a flamer with me we said previously
those are pretty
lame but
maybe against the plants they're
good well we can try
it wait where did I wasn't there flam or
fuel somewhere where did I see
that yeah here
uh okay is that a dead end
again seems like it yay Sparks like the
[Music]
flame got a fire today uper level on it
where do we go
here
quarters oh where' you come
from nice they're so
weak I haven't gone here I think have
I never have I
ever checked out the sleeping quarters
ooh pre- War money a
jumpsuit and a leaf blower I don't think
I need their jumpuit
suit
oh for the Brotherhood oh bro
strong I thought those head shots head
shots would do the trick oh there's
another
one and none of them carries anything oh
what another one oh it's a baby
he's a little baby he looked smaller it
was child so it was like a family in
here wait they even have a they have a
little green stroller in here a
man ooh cave door key cut hey
yo but the the cave do I have to go back
there anyway in order to proceed with
this place I wonder
cuz that come on that was um somewhere
else that was
higher don't see anything
here least favorite part of my favorite
game what
why this
Vault I like it so far yeah Rex is
really good for the
vault I looked for that one for hours
yay I found it one can't say that I'm
not going through this place
thoroughly oh oh another one from there
oh
nice stay down just stay down there
buddy come on stay
down is there another
one what's this sound
oh it's
gone no
okay hockey mask unarmed plus
[Music]
5 does that sound useful to you
guys a low waight I'll take it maybe
I'll be challenged to an unarmed fight
by someone and this is the only way to
win
okay
so I think maybe I do have to go all the
way back to the cave
thingy cuz that looks like a dead end to
me give it to her
ah
yo so
something good for me is it a dress
dismiss all your companions for the true
horror experience I was I once you like
you get a feeling for what's up here
it's not so
bad now I can't see her beautiful face
anymore
man I have to tell her to use Mee
doesn't she oh use Mee Nice Shot damn
doesn't she use melee all the time
anyway I guess
not use me yes finally everything is
coming up for
Ronica have fun did you throw away the
gun no
okay oh melee all right right you say
melee we had this before a long time ago
where was this cave place on which level
was it on this one no way
right just need to
find um
a
door you say it like me
really
yay what's he doing he's
angry he's so angry ah was it this way
nah it wasn't this way either I think
that was just the one
room yeah yeah
yeah I
uh what
what he's so
funny he's
molding he's walking
mingly chill Rex chill it's all good in
the neighborhood
stairs we go uh elevator uh I guess I
got to go back
still I hope that's where we continue
the cave
thingy I hope that's going to be
it just need to find it
again cave is on this level okay that's
good to know maybe here yeah all right
all right
safe quick safe what do you think Rex
what's behind this door weren't you
angry about this door
before requires a key I have the key no
I maybe
here be I'm
scared he goes r at it at it
boy I forgot can I do can I hit my
own that's enough of that my own uh
companions a dog is dead let's wait a
little bit no no rexie sney I can okay
then I might have shot him once you good
boy can I see like their health anywhere
no right I think
not can I tell him he's a good
boy happy Park a how you feeling happy
Park a you look better
nice okay
wow oh I can see their their health and
vs
oh
ah
[Music]
ah I didn't realize that to use it like
that all right this place is kind of
crazy it do be a Cave the Cave be
caving was right side the right choice
we will find out
you guys following me wait did Dogg Go a
different
way
dogger don't get yourself in danger n
he's molding again what do I do about my
molding dog guys how do you how do you
unmold your dog where are all the dog
owner at how do I unmold my dog he's
malfunctioning he wants to go this way
maybe it's the right way or it does seem
like a good
way nice shots
for the Brotherhood I don't want to hurt
her
man good job guys good job smash him I
just yell hey no I just used to hold
mine back until what made him angry left
you mean IRL right cuz I'm also trying
to ask you guys about IRL mantis is that
a egg oh yeah I'll take
him if that means they can't spawn
anymore he y wait a second can I go
through can we send the dog through
there that's
interesting can I crouch in there or
so
no looks like a
hole bug's only hole
man if only I was a bug Bug's
Life would be nice right now huh
okay I think it's where the door is we
got to go where the door
is okay are you ready to go to Pest
Control let's
go no dog
reaction interesting
nothing oh oh dog wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wa what if I have to look
at some PCS
here species
one mhm a distant relative of the more
commonly known Venus flight trap uh
seems to be performing well the plants
are a threat to creatures up to five
times their size due to their violent
nature of their closing Ms and those
that aren't allow swallowed coal are
often encap capacitated by their initial
bite
cool cool cool cool
cool mantis religio amen of all the
species we brought with us the common
mantis exceeds the rest in terms of
predation wait why brought with
us why do you
[Music]
bring did they well this whole vault is
about like raising plants and [\h__\h] right
right
so the Mattis is and all that they they
brought them from the outside into the
Vault too for for
what is that part of the
experiment
but what was the original point of
bringing
them also that they complement our
Botanical specimen by hunting down those
pest yeah I thought so it must be
something like that something good
hopefully last lastly mantises will
begin to cannibalize on one another when
other food is scars making their numbers
self-regulating when prey scars you
would think
so an
entomopathogenic fungus has been
developed to colonize the bodies of most
common pests once it has fully colonized
the host body the host technically dies
but the body continues to move by means
of the fungal Colony within it in this
manner the fungus moves amongst more of
its prey occasionally spraying spores in
the radius around the host body
infecting all who come near it it its
drawbacks include the time it takes to
kill prey 10 to 20 days and it's limited
Effectiveness when dealing with unsocial
pests is there no more Diaries is she
already like gone too far gone to write
Diaries I assume so if you get down here
it's too late h h
Doo didn't get really
far oh I no there yeah I I know I saw
you shot in his butthole death by oh
butthole in uh ammo
injection so now we saw one of those
plants nice
sorry I bonked sorry I bonked my my my
mouse against my keyboard it do be like
that
sometimes oh hard lock
okay hey yo what she fighting
ooh wow so
many oh you need help there are you
good
okay that looks like something's written
there no damn it I thought that PC would
be the one what about this
no yeah should do be looking cool with
that hammer
It's Hammer Time Veronica
says we shall believe her metal armor
metal
helmet I like to wear leather
armor I don't know I'm already pretty
full on
weight repairs you think she needs
it you're making me carry the heavy
stuff aren't you nah it's full
it's
full uh
here ooh n what is
that this is
special special looking download res oh
isn't this what I need
for request they're interested in this
yeah
oh okay but I still haven't found the
what's her name key
the quest you hav
yeah oh companion don't lose durability
on item oh okay
cool key well maybe one of these was key
and I wouldn't
[Music]
know oh maybe she's behind here could it
be
[\h__\h] nah I can't be here
there was a hole behind a
locker not these
right oh here oh my God
why I didn't see it as such a
threedimensional kind of
thing wait let's
save I wonder what's behind that 75 lock
uh door really curious
looks like a trash
shoot is she going to come out of there
[Music]
or
o what
the ah this is where the real party is
at
huh oh
I'm not going to reach probably I'm just
going to go down let's go down
guys
y
uh-oh oh can I
reach oh nice easy oh are you guys
shooting each
other oh no it's like those
it's like those
spiders does this have a egg too
no oh yeah the flamer would be
good is it
dead yeah but I didn't want to switch
now if I see one of those again I'll
switch
oh yeah there's one of those eggs let
me let me let let them do the
the the normal attacks now I'll I'll
start some fire
today did you just hit me can she do
that
who fire fire fire burn the Mantis like
I desire
nice efficient very efficient oh there's
so many of
them be
careful where did he
go so much to kill here how
fun he's having so much
fun it's like his
Playground now I don't remember where he
came from
oh I don't remember where we came from
did we come from
here thank you for the membership
welcome I'm just I just want to double
check if this is where I came from so I
can orientate
myself wait
Maybe not maybe this is not where I came
from cuz I remember the trash shoot but
no this is where we came from huh where
is the trash
shoot I don't see it
anymore oh is it not the same place no
this looks familiar this entrance feel
like the alignment is the same oh oh
this is interesting too oh oh my god
let's
go it's you
now don't want to burn you so I'm saving
really
[Laughter]
quickly my game crashed but I saved
right before it
[Laughter]
nice that's
funny that was funny I enjoy I see the
bright side about these crashes and that
is that they're
funny should be fine we're going to be
fine
right yeah now should I try this
again oh I got a Bug Stomper per what
was that I can walk over
them can I walk over them like
this more damage against bugs oh
nice okay oh your brain is very exposed
CH your sweet time I suppose the MCR
sent you
yay yay I'm so
[Music]
proud
uh huh no I know about the rescue andela
Williams told me to find you she's such
a deer not like that pompous little
peton she works for but that's neither
here nor not these plants have gotten
completely out of control a plan to deal
with them but I'll need your help like
this but I guess schools are really
strong how much are you paying so you're
one of those huh yeah fine I'll give you
all the money I have once you're done
already been through a lot of [\h__\h] I'll
explain more I'm not doing this for
free not greaty this is you know people
got to make money somehow in this
world you know how a Fallout World works
it's not all that easy
we can't all just do each other favors
all the
time damn she's fast she's a
runner I'm going to lose
her is she just going to run ahead all
the way to the exit I didn't really pay
attention what she said at the
end uh it'll take me a while to find the
exit I wish she would have wait waited
for me and led me the way
man go to the elevator oh can I take it
now elevator where are
you
uh ah
y a she will repair it Ah that's what
she said
nice oh there she is how's it going this
vault tech machine is so fragile I had
to jury rig this elevator a few days and
it's on the fritz again already Ah
that's got it see you upstairs
yay okay
uh
entrance this was fun I'm glad we went
to
this dungeon I'm glad we did it I mean I
also like to do you know main quest and
all that
but uh this was a
pleasure it's not over well she said
second level
[\h__\h]
oh is she in the
lab where'd she
go uh
lady
uh ah what you doing good you're here
ready to begin yeah I totally know what
I'm doing how can I help time is of the
essence so I'll be brief this place is
filled with spores that are toxic to
humans and we need to get rid of them
I've pumped The Vault full of a highly
flammable gas that once ignited should
destroy the vast majority of spores
there's one problem though the gas
becomes semi inert on exposure to oxygen
meaning the gas will have to be ignited
close to where it's being introduced I
need you to find the vents where the gas
is being pumped and ignite it oh and
survive the resulting
blast did I see any vents yet I idea
where these vents are I set the gas to
pump into the fist level since that's
where the concentration of spores was
highest I'd start looking there okay
typically these vaults use circular
vents in their air circulation systems
look for a wall with two of them almost
side by side okay there's one just
around the corner outside this lab if
you need an example oh
thanks you're out of your
mind
H how exactly should I ignite it with my
flamethrower the area where the gas is
active any kind of fire or explosion
should do the trick hell even lasers
would do the job if you don't have
anything like that I've got some
grenades in my bag in the corner that
you can use okay I have I have it
good okay we're blowing things up she
said around the corner wait what
what does she
mean ah these
two
right what the I won't be able to blow
these up or what these are just an
example okay uh level five she said
where was the
elevator
here okay
okay use P use pit boy light N I never
do I don't need
it
okay we need to find those vents I'm
sure they will be all over no nope maybe
not but not in the cave
aves right just around here did I read
this
before what am I unlocking I think I
don't need to do
that ah
[Music]
wait what wait
what what just
[Laughter]
happened did I get too close cuz I see I
see it's like wobbly air [\h__\h] wobbly air
do I just not get too close with my I
guess like if you have a flamer in your
hand you shouldn't get too close or
was even from
[Music]
here even from here
what I I was so far away okay this is
like teaching me things for if I ever am
in a am in a situation like this in real
life
what about
here this is too far
obviously grenades do I have
any but she said it will work with
anything well the most obvious thing
apparently doesn't work I don't have a
grenade I could have taken her grenade
but a laser she said laser too so what
if I take a laser whatever
oh oh this is fun we learn step by step
we learn I even ran to the side but how
far do I got to run it's like coming
really fast at
[Music]
me damn what do I where do I run
to damn it's so wobbly the air is so I
guess maybe here nah
I feel
like there's I don't know if it's a
graphic bug but I feel like oh I see the
gas
everywhere you can't unun an explo
outrun an
explosion wait a second let me
think yeah maybe I shouldn't get too
close again what what what about what
about can I hide in there
there cuz it went straight towards here
does it go to the
side I don't know I'm learning I'm
learning about
explosions like here maybe and then
close the door okay easy easy but
Veronica might die if she stays out
there guys come come over there we
go right if I just shoot like diagonally
over there maybe
oh wait ah
Dogg do I need to tell you to
stay just I want you guys to be safe
okay it would be terrible if something
happened to
you wait I think I didn't switch to the
earth I guess I was still on the flamer
because of the safe reset
I love this this is good good content
for a
clip compilation of how long it takes me
to to to do
this okay okay okay okay
okay everybody gather I don't have a
grenade it's
okay should breath okay okay here we go
I'm going to do it right this
time sorry can I do it from
here
no
ooh
[Music]
ah oh I didn't even have to close the
door that was fun I I don't know why I
felt uh that I could take this risk but
I took
it I took the
risk wait my
people uh follow
me come
[Music]
on is it just me sometimes the air more
like the atmosphere so it looks kind of
wobbly or is it actually the gas
effect oh it is it is okay
not where is she
again or did she
leave no she's here good good are you
finishing your Diaries huh ah I like
reading them you survived I was
beginning to think you hadn't you'll be
pleased to know that the Spore should no
longer be a problem yay now all that's
left is to ensure that none of this ever
happens again the research that led to
these Abominations must be erased it oh
it wouldn't it be good to keep the
research so people know it it's not a
good idea I managed to create a
connection to the vault's backup system
from here I just have to remotely delete
all the files and done here
H
oh H would it take long no it shouldn't
take all that long just a few more
moments and my choice that's strange the
system says that the files were accessed
recently oh yeah Source you wouldn't
happen to know anything about that would
you
uh no I've been too busy rescuing you
could someone else have done
it wait what what what happened if I
tell her I did it does she attack
me does she attack me then I lose a bit
of
karma thank you it's possible I've spent
the last few days in a cave after all
for all we know that man sends someone
immediately after you to swipe the data
while you posed his mantis bait nothing
to be done about it I suppose all we can
do is delete what's here and that's done
I've unlocked the door so you're free to
run along now I've lost Al P I lied or
because made it out of here without your
help if you're heading back toward
McCarron tell Dr Williams that she has
my thanks as
well I've G
Karm you lose some you win
some yay yay
yay happy day oh happy
day oh happy day
[Music]
well
done basically I go back and report to
both of them do I yeah
nice
[Music]
nice that was fun I was like so
terrified in the beginning I thought
like even these plants would attack me
somehow but it was all good I can trust
the plants again plants are trustworthy
after all my mom will be very relieved
to hear
that uh first level that was
fun nice this looks so pretty the light
from behind the wheel
oh oh oh oh you guys were waiting for
me
nice yeah B 22 so today we actually saw
free Vault I didn't expect to check out
that many but this was very much the
most exciting one wait right free vaults
right we saw three of them 34
21 and now
22 free
BS buy two vaults and get one
free yay was it only two I just saw the
34 true same thing same thing I pretty
much pretty much been there done
that okay let's try to get closer to the
quest oh why is it so
why does it lead me to
Novak oh I'm
jumping
yeah ah you suckers ah those oh
[Music]
no
W what what wa is that because of my
laser
oopsie damn that must have been my nice
W
ashes I hope it doesn't rise from its
ashes
ever mutated
bugs laser crits do that oh nice maybe
I'll use the laser gun more often it's
kind of fun
yeah the those cats the doors they
[\h__\h] us up last
time Big
Time I can successfully report my return
with good
news hm hm
H is he practicing how to
punch the the
the never
mind balls yes balls balls is
okay is this where I had to go we won't
go quietly the legion can count on
that they got a prison in
here
o o
Boyd's in there with a prisoner right
now boy is she pissed
o is that a legion [\h__\h]
nah you STI got like a sore thumb around
here you sure you're in the right place
almost so close do you need any help
yeah so far this has gone exactly as
expected it is one poorly but with the
work you've done for NCR already you
might be just what I've been looking for
we captured an honest to God Centurion
of Caesar's Legion recently o
spicy better believe it everybody
everybody in Caesar's Legion from Caesar
on down will kill themselves before they
can be captured they're so Twitchy
they'd probably do it if you reached out
to hug them but here's this guy who's an
elite commander in their army and he
just gives himself up even as his men
are slitting their own throats around
him I think you need a lot of speech for
this
a well I don't know about you but to me
that sounds like a man who's willing to
cooperate except he hasn't only times he
speaks get up to 80 or 85 he's a real
prick by the way and I'm supposed to get
information out of this
guy a truth drug is that
real why don't you just beat the
prisoner
senseless I like the way you think have
I said that yet problem is that the NCR
frowns on using that sort of t itic
there are some restrictions still in
place from president T's Administration
okay that honestly but here's my
favorite thing about you you're not in
the
NCR for all this guy knows you're
completely ins that's a winning
combination so you want me to do what
you can I think if you rough him up
enough and really put some fear into him
he'll sing like a choir boy so let's do
this when you're ready I'll go in and
give you a little intro then I leave the
room and you make him regret the day he
was born we go back and forth a couple
times until either he talks or he can't
move his jaw anymore good call bad
entertain for the day I'm the bad
cop let's do it a spirit let's try okay
I'll go in and have a word with him okay
let me switch my clothes really quickly
to better my
chances and
don't no na
spicy f52
mhm if I need more I can still take some
meds did she really go for the door even
though this is wide open
Lieutenant I was just thinking about you
that's
so I
was I was just thinking about that
pretty neck of yours how sweet I was
thinking about how it would look with a
legion
I'll pass do you know what I love about
our slave collars Lieutenant if you love
them maybe you should try one on bird I
look how tightly they fit I train my men
to make sure the slaves flesh bulges a
bit around the top and bottom what know
why it's all the rage and fashion
circles not quite if you fit it just
right their body never gets used to the
f feeling of wearing it it cuts in just
enough when they swallow or turn their
head to remind them who they belong to
and it's that constant reminder that
keeps them
docel in that case maybe you'd better
save the caller you were going to give
me oh for whom for me for a friend of
mine you're about to meet yay my friend
is very dos my turn and who is this
friend of yours you know all the rules
the NCR instituted to protect enemy me
prisoners of War of course I don't give
a [\h__\h] about it my friend doesn't oh and
cus if you resist at all I'll personally
blow your brains out come on in he's all
yours but you guys said the speech is
important getting
along and I need you to surrender your
weapons before you go in you can pick
them up from the L out what do you mean
I'm I'm already
in oh it's gone but I keep the silence
pistol how come I always get to keep the
silenced pistol I'm hiding it well huh
hey hey y wearing a little skirt ah are
you girl just kidding but I mean he's
he's asking me to make fun of him for
that you a little girl oh so cute where'
you buy that skirt I want to get one too
do they have it in my size I think so
probably it's probably my size
Anyway come on give it to me give me the
skirt what an ugly little worm you are
what pile of excrement did the
lieutenant pluck you from
worm oh I I love how the legion talks to
me I think you're confused I'm with the
excrement right now
what you must have some reason to be in
your line of work tell me what did the
legion do to you did we enslave your
children Slaughter your family before
your eyes to teach you a lesson whatever
it was I hope I was there to give the
order no he really wasn't that bad but
you should be asking what did I do to
the legion not what the legion did to me
you must miss giving orders now that all
your men are dead foot soldiers of the
Legion are trained not to have to think
for themselves to have conflict removed
from their minds they kill themselves to
evade capture because they are not
trusted to make such a decision
rationally In the Heat of battle but I'm
no foot soldier that's all the reason I
could captivity on my own without
revealing the tiniest ioda of
information to my
captors sounds to me like you were too
gutless to follow Caesar's orders I'll
show you gutless you sniveling bastard
I'll spill your guts into this room oh
really oh
oh something the matter cus you look
upset
I don't know I thought she seemed like a
nice lady oh are we switching your
friend is a miserable [\h__\h]
degenerate don't say it again don't tell
that again I don't think it's going to
happen my dog is angry too if we were on
the other side of the river I'd have her
torn apart my dog likes sausages if you
don't like dealing with me I can bring
my
friend yeah I'm already
in have it your way come on back in I'm
in I think he misses you I'm so in can
we bring my dog he's hungry for
sausages sausages in in pigs
blankets yeah we don't have anything to
discuss
worm we should discuss your worm you
sure talk tough for someone who's afraid
to die but I want to know how a coward
can coward can attain the rank of
centurion I don't know both not so
interesting but let's do this one coward
I've faced odds that would make your NCR
soldiers wet themselves I've LED charges
against men with guns carrying only my
knife and I can tell you it was they who
feared me but suicide is a weak death on
a battlefield it says to your enemy that
you fear
capture it says if you're caught you can
be broken
[Music]
I don't
know I'll say this one maybe you were
unafraid to cut any throat but your own
I don't know one okay you think I'm
going to slit my throat for some
megalomaniacal self-appointed dictator I
didn't work my way up to have it all be
taken from me out of some irrational
paranoia kaisar is losing it I believe
that he's been shutting himself in in
his
tent privately he complains of
headaches whatever it is it's affecting
his ability to
lead a he must have some migraines poor
little
guy it's probably from the cosplay Helm
that he's wearing all day that's
squishing into his non-existent
brains continue listening
oh should just continue listening
time was essential for my mission but we
waited 3 days for him to dispatch us
another of his headaches does that sound
like a man in command he should just
take off his cosplay his very base but
does heuse his AG no he's content to
have the agent spend his kns radioing
troop positions back to our base camp he
knows I'm here and he's left me to
rot who's the operative I don't know I
know he sends intelligence by radio like
we're getting along well right now
sometimes that intelligence would find
its way to my
caner I don't believe you're lying then
you're a fool that man reports to kaisar
on what I do here the legion isn't going
to take me back my only hope is to
escape and disappear but if I escape and
he reports it they'll hunt me down as
long as I live it served me to report
him as much as it served
you okay
I won't say that to him that's too nice
don't you feel bad now Legion burns your
body at the St conquer this place
nothing I could tell you would do
anything to stop
that boss you coming back or
no can I punch him
though I don't I don't want to punch him
what are you going to do about him huh
you did well I don't know how you did it
without putting a scratch on him and I'm
a little disappointed spe was enough it
saved the NCR some face yay and it could
save us more than that when all is said
and done I'm going to talk to some
people when we're through here this is
about double the standard fee we'd give
a consultant but from what I saw you're
more of an artist so think of this as
your
commission what what did I
get it's like adding a lot of things I
don't know which one I'm getting from
you I got to level up again Yahoo
yep see you
around
caps who are you at this point I got
caps
okay
uh yeah we wanted even more medicine so
that we can help in that
Quest I don't know let's just go up to
50 then we can probably take a magazine
for the rest of the
[Music]
10 and then speech up to 75
okay oh oh oh oh oh a new perky
perk purifier is a purifier of the
Wasteland you do plus 50% damage with
Mele and unarmed weapons against centers
nice stock of sport PLS W that's kind of
too
late with the adamantium skeleton perk
your only receive 50% of the damage they
normally would
oh oh sounds
good Misfortune appears to turn their
world upside down a it's like the the
female version of what we already
have
right hardcore perk don't get it
it's the female version yeah she
glitches oh
really it's not as good yeah I don't
know I kind of like
this
[Music]
um maybe I'll get
this normally I always let you guys kind
of choose but some of you guys seem to
oh it's great on normal
too yeah I do break limbs a lot when I
run into the mines
it will not be bad that's for
sure oh 3and B caps y well so I was
actually going to report something
here uh help me local map help me oh
over there on the other side you got
something to say or do you always look
like that excuse
me so rude after all that we just did
together wait was it downstairs or
maybe it was
downstairs I'm one of the best YouTubers
on the net thank
[Music]
you I try I do be trying sometimes
actually all the time oh hello Kaye just
called in yay you should have heard the
director but uh wait a I saved her I
that finish a sentence just reamed him
out for sending all those people to the
Vault I've never seen his face me from
the GetGo thanks for keeping her safe
here's the Caps I promise how many I
knew I had a good feeling about you hey
T hey thanks again really I owe you you
do you do key does too
wait hello hello hello I received a
pleasant call from Dr key it seems we
have you to thank for keeping keeping
her alive very charitable of
you I'm not a charity hey I'm not a
charity case I brought the data from
vol2 wonderful excellent work let me see
it it'll take a moment to decode on my
[Music]
terminal
H you never warned me about the dangers
in that place didn't I did you encounter
undue difficulties clearly not or you
wouldn't be standing here would you all
that matters is whether the data is
intact you little [\h__\h] think Williams
decryption algorithms seem to be working
yes here it is the data is mostly
uncorrupted this will make the board of
directors finally sit up and take notice
here then as promised an agreeable sum
payable upon delivery of the data you've
more than done your
part 1,200
okay might be careful with the data you
didn't see those plants in the vault or
did you your concerns are perfectly
understandable but I assure you they're
entirely misplaced you never used
technology that wasn't fully tested we
aren't some mly band of Vault Alchemists
we're with the government for goodness
sake have a little faith in
us yeah whatever I probably will never
see the effects of that so that's
fine but I am so glad we did all of that
it felt pretty good pretty good progress
today I don't know is there anything
else I can report already return to
Alice let her know yeah we can report
this cuz I'm going to end it
soon um and read some super chats
because I have to cook urgently
urgently before
it's the 13th because my salmon only is
edible until the 12th
and even one minute will surely make a
difference I wanted to cook yesterday
but I was like so tired and then I just
had
lazaga yeah it's it's Cinderella
salmon for
sure making salmon with like lemon sauce
and asparagus the sauce is different
because I have not the right ingredients
for the other sauce they wanted me to
make in the
recipe but yeah wait what we're
going oh so
close wait what that's what where am I
going
what ah now it's now it's showing where
I got to go I was
wondering spinach I hate spinach I only
like spinach spinach when it's like M
together with dough like uh
already made so small that you can't see
the leaves it's just green and you you
put it together with like noodle dough
and dumpling dough stuff and then a lot
of cheese sauce we have a a dish in
Austria that's called
spinach uh spla spinat SP M qua sauce
with with cheese sauce it's really good
one of my
favorite dishes from when I lived with
my
Mommy I tried to make it actually the
other day because I just saw some
precooked spinach
spla dumplings and then I just made a
cheese sauce actually it was pretty
good um I delivered the invoice just as
you asked well you've proven yourself
reliable so
far
maybe maybe but maybe not for
now has additional jobs yeah maybe not
right now we'll think about it anything
else I can report before I
go ah we'll do this next time we'll do
Veronica's Quest next time
yeah yeah lots of things to
do yeah I think with almost 5 hours of
pretty intense quest uh completing we've
done a good
job I've done a good job in
particular good gaming indeed good
gaming and I think we should take it in
you know these kind of smaller bites
instead of like eight hours of this I
think I would get pretty tired of
it maybe Amit was right to uh stream
this in smaller bites smaller
streams still a pretty big bite
yeah H he thank you guys for helping and
watching today I hope you enjoyed this
little Fallout
session some nice screams that can be
compilated into a good clip
perhaps uh tomorrow is my day off and
then the day after that at midnight my
time we're going to start The Minecraft
Project
yay Minecraft Project let's go what is
this
interesting and that will continue for
for quite a few days until we're
finished and yeah then the that means
that there's no schedule for next week
because I don't know what's going to
happen
really one block Minecraft
yay yeah yeah yeah yeah okay let's get
out of this
game
and I shall commence the Super Chat
reading maybe should I change clothes
I I'm going to change clothes for
y'all
wait just in
case oh ah
oops that was good that was good that I
hit
it cuz I accidentally
accidentally opened something else that
I shouldn't
have okay let's go to the F night room
cuz it's
new
[Music]
yay
mhm let me fix the
chat this can go okay yay we're back in
here
need some
[Music]
music what could be
good what could be
good ah this one
maybe all
right what are you looking at guys H
every time I see it's like the first
time see what
H the background right I was only the
second time anyway pretty
much yay looking at kfp looking looking
at my hair yeah yeah yeah no for real
the hair is nice
right a very very high
ponytail fluffy ponytail
okay super chats um how do we do this uh
I'm caught up on
members super
chats
[Music]
and I think
generally uh how we should do it is we
going to read new outfit super chats but
like the non Reds I guess and the non-
pinks
yeah cuz I I usually always read um at
least the ones that don't get a
Polaroid uh but the other Fallout stream
I'm caught up on that one right am I let
me
see yeah yeah yeah I've read that that
looks
familiar then it's outfit for real how
fitting yeah skim through them you need
to read the
k K
oh oh
K
oh
uhhuh
okay when did I do a
k wait say YouTube Shir it doesn't show
up here does it it wait no it doesn't
ah it's this one I found it found it
found
it the YouTube
[Music]
short let me get the
thumbnail Super Chat to rating time did
you notice the like tab on Twitter's
gone already I've heard that that was
going to
happen
no you guys always like to look at my LS
don't
[Music]
you can I look at my own yeah I can look
at my own no your likes are private only
you can see them but can I change that
that sounds like I can change it let me
see can you change it do you guys
know maybe
you can't why why do they why do they
change things that are fine the way they
are and like even such crucial features
like why like I understand for
example Al don't know not really either
I I wouldn't change that either like
changing hiding the likes from Posts but
like nobody asked for this right nobody
asked for like profile likes to be
invisible
nobody asked for
it nobody like most of most people like
for someone like me I have fans who
check my likes because they're curious
but for any for the most consumers on
Twitter which are non-f famous people
right nobody gives a [\h__\h] what you like
nobody will check out your likes nobody
cares nobody checks that the only people
whose likes get checked is like famous
people yeah so but even then I don't
think any of us famous people asked oh I
got a popup now with a ah
what as if as if it's like trying to
tell me I should be happy about this and
everybody's happy about
this did you get the same popup guys
uh wait
did you get this pop up
too why why that
emoji to better protect your privacy I
don't think my privacy was ever affected
by those likes my privacy is affected by
other
things liking more posts will make your
for you feet better yeah so you can be
more horny
huh well you could have been horny even
even even if it was
public oh wait now I guess it makes
sense with that wait I see what's
happening that emoji is
literally implying that hey you can be
horny
now oh come
on sometimes I like looking at uh like
other people's likes too like for
example um
um when I'm like tweeting at someone
like an
artist and like this outfits artist just
the other day I was checking their likes
to see if they saw my reply if they
liked my reply or you know stuff like
[Music]
that there are some cases where I even I
want to look at people's
leges so that's unfortunate
they're going to remove so many
features that it's just not the same
[Music]
anymore removing stuff like Twitter
circles for example that was like
whatever I didn't I never used Twitter
circles but some people did and I think
they made good use out of
it actually that was a probably a pretty
useful feature
Twitter
circles no not the stories I mean the
ones where you can limit what uh which
people see your tweets like for a
certain Fred or so not for all of your
tweets but like yeah certain
conversations you're
having not just limit who replies but
limit who sees it in the first
place I never used it but I think people
liked that
feature there used to be though yeah
there used to be like a story feature I
was reminded of that too the other day
on Twitter they had a story feature like
Instagram stories for
example what were they called but nobody
used it aets yeah I I don't need that
bag I don't think people really use it
much it was was pretty oh am okay am is
the only reason why we would want it
back but I think generally it was pretty
unpopular and not much
usage on the platform with
fleets am's fleets were so good I don't
remember them at all but I know she was
doing
it be would have totally used fleets
probably yeah
fleets maybe I'm actually surprised
fleets didn't take over because on
Instagram um you know Instagram
stories I used to check Instagram posts
more uh when like just as much as um
stories I would just go from my normal
Post Feed as well and check out what the
people I follow are doing but in the
past 2 years or so I I have been
completely I wonder if I'm the only one
I've been completely ignoring normal
posts I never scroll down for the normal
posts and thank God because like every
second post is a [\h__\h] advertisement
but uh the only thing I really look at
is the stories nowadays and that made me
think like damn you got to advertise
everything you you post on your profile
in your story unless unless I'm the only
one who only checked
stories way too many ads and irrelevant
posts yeah Instagram is pretty bad like
when it comes to
that but yeah stories I'm only checking
stories stories are more interesting
anyway but yeah so I'm surprised stories
are so popular on Instagram but on
Twitter it really didn't work
out and I think that's just because
Twitter uh you know it it was raised in
a certain way and the community was
raised in a certain way on
Twitter that they use Twitter
differently yeah and that's fine you
don't have to make every platform have
the same features as the other platforms
there it's good to have
differences it's good to have a reason
to use Twitter and it's good to have a
reason to use Instagram it's good to
have a reason reason to use Tik Tok if
you're crazy like
that didn't you hate the bluebird I love
the bluebird the blue bird I mean maybe
we had some beef when the bluebird was
still
there but that was just you know bird
fights typical bird
fights what do you think about Hol plus
I
mean I think as
[Music]
long the problem is it doesn't have
reach to reach new
people it will still for a long long
long time I'm pretty sure it will
continue to be very Niche and just our
community
so but it has some upsides for
[Music]
sure would be nice if they could
Implement a feature
uh where whatever I tweet on Twitter
will be automatically tweeted on Hol
plus maybe that already
exists but we' really have to advertise
it well to get a lot of people like at
least the whole whole life Community to
use it if we can't reach outside then at
least the whole Community should be
present there and that's difficult to
advertise it to that
point at this point it's kind of late
should have had Hol plus since year
number
one but we'll
see we'll see how it goes I don't know
if we even can use it yet because like
when it first was
implemented uh the en members I think
and ID members were not able to use it
yet I don't know haven't really heard
anything in a while
uh okay
let's read the super chats that I said I
was going to read
H okay are you
ready it actually actually exists it
does exist mhm you can already make an
account if you want
to has been very
[Music]
positive m
M if you're enjoying it that's good
that's
good why didn't the department tell me
about this what
department we need talent interaction on
Hollows so you can interact with us and
like f out exactly yeah I
mean I I I would go on there if staff
would tell me about
it7 the gamer crate thanks for the
pinky Kiwa it sounds like our beloved
sing bisbas is going through some rough
times at the hospital no with a
potential P pneumonia oh no oh no did he
go to the Vault if you could send him
some much needed love so that he may
have a safe and speedy recovery then
that would be love is is is is bisb
here is bisb doing better
already are you here you're doing
better okay I'm so happy to hear that
what happened was it like Corona
stuff are you
da or just general like asthma
[Music]
or thanks to me no you recovered on your
own or maybe thanks to some meds always
take your meds infection with my
respiratory
system okay [\h__\h] that infection if it
comes back let me know I'll kick its
ass for the r Jet and also the game CR
thanks for the sweet sweet support for
bisb very nice of you H hi T today I'm
finally celebrating getting kfb armor
I've got it actually already last
Wednesday but I'm quite busy lately so
celebrating it today thank you so much
for all the years full of fun and
happiness I'm so happy to be a member of
kfp love you Teno
loveim congratulations thank you for
staying with us for so long you're
looking fancy very shiny very shiny make
sure to polish it every day looking so
fancy So Posh well protected I hope all
the all the important parts of your
chicken body are protected with this
armor
thank you so much for
everything I hope we can get you what's
the next step again did we have
something after armor already I
forgot not yet right it'll be the the
the fourth year this September I got to
come up with something or did we already
decide maybe we already did deci side
the rainbow one right we wanted to
Rainbow to do rainbow
gold or
rainbow we could also go fourthe gold
and then fifth year
rainbow H I'll probably decide this last
minute when the time uh comes
closer yeah thank you
a Richard py
action oh you like happy material based
Studio R bangs with the pinky
T how you doing Studio Rob hope you're
doing well thanks for coming to the
stream M thanks for the pinky as well
watching from work I don't care if I get
in trouble I ain't going to miss my
favorite vertical bird streamer very
cute
waah thank you I think I haven't shown
it since because it's being a little bit
over
overpowered by the new outfit but um
I'll use my
3D
um face my upgraded 3D face again
sometime soon whenever I feel like
wearing my default
outfit yeah yeah yeah
yeah cuz it was really cute right oh
yeah I think we're actually still
working on the
Improvement of the eyebrows so maybe
once that is done I'll I'll bring it
back but I am very happy that I was able
to reveal something to you guys that you
enjoyed so much H we got so many good
reaction images from that damn so good
crazy Mage danan James Jackson dushan
chicken OK dun Dex Jaden dun George
sandov dun
or Honolulu thanks for the pinky com on
how difficult was it for you not to be
able to show that honest expression and
hand just gentle now so cute n well the
hands I definitely when I don't have my
hands tracked I'm going to use it less
and be less
expressive the 3D equipment I don't know
yet I didn't have time yet to look at
what's wrong with it to be honest m
I'll try again when I feel like
recording a dance video probably anyway
yeah I think my my
Expressions um it's nice that they're
more visible with the 3D that is like
the biggest difference
because yeah the the way it looks so
stiff is really
sad by default how stiff it
looks so I don't think I can go back
back to that anymore after having the
upgraded one love the go mouth yeah
should I make it even
bigger maybe a little bit bigger just a
tiny
bit could be good hu thank you for the
pinky and Trevor G thanks for the pinky
saying I love
M what oh because I sang the song
M it's beautiful oh I don't know why I
got so nervous for that whole stream I
think I felt very perceived and
watched
um
damn I I I don't want to crumble under
pressure so easily anymore but it do be
like that but at least a second wait did
I give it a second try I did right I
gave both the waya song and the M song a
second
try those were
okay but even
even the second tries I could have done
better I know
it I just get so nervous
[Music]
nervous but I hope you enjoyed it anyway
Trevor G and everybody else
I'm bored and you amuse me I
amuse I I amuse
you where's this where is
the where is the amuse video do I have
it
download what where's my amuse
video did I upload it to my Channel or
was it on ch's Channel
I think it's on che's channel is it or
on his Twitter the one that went like bo
bo bo oh was it a YouTube
shirt
ah do I amuse you am I some sort of
clown to youte
[Music]
my yeah it's a YouTube
short so to the dear Super Chat I don't
know if you've seen it before but this
is my reply to you do I amuse you am I
some sort of clown to you
nice I can't see the butt
cheeks
fine legit complaint about lack of butt
cheeks yeah we want to make both types
of people happy as we talk about
today
auga
auga and
taco J with pinky remember when K said
she's not cute well that was a
lie I have my cute moments for
sure I have my cute moments yeah
she got me spending oh spending all your
money on
me always cute oh w w wow wow wow
[Music]
stop a you guys are too
sweet
always okay okay I'll take it thank you
B Doug
Jones space waterful d Sky d end than
space wonderful than you candy STS
[Music]
thanon thanks for the pinky T spoiling
us with reveals upon reveals recently us
jimins can only handle so much yeah I
originally was not going to do like two
reveals in a row pretty much in one week
but yeah I I I figured I have to move my
reveal to be earlier and this is what
happened but this way
it was hype and entertaining so much
hype so much new stuff very refreshing
after a drought a little bit of a
drought of new
stuff a troll for fun D bang shami thank
you for the red super chat hello I'm so
happy I got to see you perform at off
guy and that I met so many fellow kfp oh
I came all the way from Costa Rica to
see you and it was wonderful from Costa
Rica what Fe I was real at ofai and it's
real with this reveal yeah and it was
also real with the other
[Music]
reveal or if that's what maybe that's
what you meant actually but I don't
think I revealed the announcement at
that point yet but
yay I'm so glad you made your way to
ofai because that was I think one of the
best
kfp
experiences we've had so far that was
like really
intense even I could feel it all the way
in
Austria yeah had a good time and I'm
just happy I'm just so happy you guys
had a good time that is the most
important that's what I do I try to
entertain so you're enjoying is the most
important to me I hope you felt like it
was worth it it seems like you did thank
you bang
shami maybe again
sometime Cruz D Fafa z d j Mony D
Unwritten D and
taco I am
a h j SW for the pinky you and improved
fre W was so cute thank
you yeah that that new waa pretty cute
new Wawa just dropped and she's pretty
cute I will try to make it to Breaking
Dimensions
yeah break into the concert if you must
just kidding don't break in but um
metaphorically maybe break into
it simple
this is the Tech Armor was beta testing
right if so thanks armor uh yes and
no
uh
it's yes and no it's like the same kind
of like blend shapes stuff
but uh it's not like she her beta
testing led to me having it cuz I don't
even have it on the whole up and only
have it
separately cuz yeah I would have to use
a 1 million wish if I want this on the
hall simply thanks for the red super
chat right back
at absur thanks for the red super
chat you are the best get l the best
what's so funny
HH do am I some sort of clown to you
wait
my restart do I amuse you do I amuse you
am I some sort of clown to you am I some
sort of clown to
you thank you do thank you so much for
the big big red Super
Chat CH
the Jim Tracy
D yay illusion not let's go Le d Leo bis
dun G dun fried screw thanks for the red
super chat kiala can fix us lonely
chickens I try I try wait are you guys
saying you're not fixed yet even after
all these years even after almost four
years you're still not
fixed what do I need to do to fix
you at this point you should be
fixed you're getting worse what how's
that possible am I bad for you am I a
bad influence for
you am I toxic to
you I don't like that
implication the new outfit fixed me a
yeah for sure it fixed
you no why are you guys so broken what
happened do I need to glue back some
limbs with hot
glue I should open a hospital kfp
hospital fried screw Mah maybe after a
choo choo it feels better right looking
for the top D Pride D le
D oh you have six cats picture please
can you ever take a picture of them all
together cuz I already have troubles
taking picture of my two cats just
because they don't usually stay together
but I've seen other cats who like to
cuddle and chill more closely so maybe
you
can probably the easiest would be to
bring out a liquid cat snack then
they're going to come over I'm sure
your dog runs away from the camera maybe
he's traumatized by it maybe something
happened maybe the flash once scared him
or
so or it's not that serious at
all Miss Flappy Boy Thanks for the pinky
happy reverse birthday yeah and what a
gift you have given yourself God I love
you go get a mentality this upgrade
elevates the frey experience above and
beyond it is all thanks to your own
initiative as so often this is
true points at super jet this is true
thank you so much for the sweet words
bad ghost pyro macaroni King D
macaroni d t thanks for the red super
chat K love you boss new outfit let's go
I am sad and tired chicken but I
remember K exist so just tired now okay
thanks for always being around even when
I take my meds and bringing joy and life
to the world or at least to me glory to
K Fe K
[Music]
forever well deserved
kiss so sweet my sweet
chickens don't be don't be
sad don't be sad Wawa is here Wawa is
here for you just for you
mp15 free garlics dun and again dun
thanks for the pinky as well don't
listen to Twitter sociopaths they're
exposit looking to find problems also
they they are some of the worst people
on the planet their opinions are worth
less than their I don't know what we
were talking about
but yeah well the ones that want to make
trouble they are little shits as we
might say in kfp
yeah well I wouldn't just say Twitter
it's just generally the internet is a
scary
place people always say like Twitter has
cancel culture but it's not specifically
Twitter it's very much so just YouTube
for example in
general I wouldn't blame Twitter for it
I love Twitter man I love Twitter
culture in general so
I've been on Twitter for so
long Twitter is my
home Brandon Lima Elie you are Tak Lou
wine pool D np15 for
D
Alex chicken
D oh super boramy d
soon thank you for checking out my off
gu
performance thank
you Anthony webb thanks for the pinky I
hope to have a meet and greet with you
at a convention Sunday
kiaha I'm sure we can make it happen you
just got to you just got to be lucky if
you enter a
raffle and I got better be at more
conventions I'll try I'll
try but you know the more now with
Advent the more members we have the more
the pool of members to choose from for
these events are so the more people join
the lower the chances kind of get for me
to be at the
convention uh sadly the bigger Ian gets
the lower what the chances are that you
guys meet
me
yeah then you you guys just got to like
strongly advocate for Wawa at
conventions cuz conventions can always
um like they can be like okay we want
whoever from H life just recommend us
somebody or they can be like hey like
off guy ask for me specifically because
they're
based and yeah conventions can do that
if I think they will do it if you guys
are like hey can you if you invite H
life can you try to get wah wa we have a
big kfp fan community that wants to see
her give us the w
I wonder who's going to be a Japan
[Music]
Expo that is something we're currently
all
discussing
yeah imagine not sending K to the Japan
Expo in Paris which is the first
European convention having whole life in
two years
n i i i i there's a possibility that
I'll be there
so in one way or another
so maybe no meat and great but one way
or
another
[Music]
um yeah so I I hope I hope that there
are still many European
kfps who especially French ones I guess
my country yeah did you see the
announcement that whole life will be at
Japan Expo did you not see it did you
miss
it very important for French
kfp very
important French like my
Blu-rays of
P you know what that's why I got to
that's why I got to go to Japan Expo I
got to sell I got to bring
my uh French Blu-rays to the bring and
buy and sell them cuz I don't think
anybody's going to buy them off of me
here can I can I bring something to the
bring and buy
oh
man got to go there in person or or give
it to a
staff
thead a thank
youne than w t thanks for Pinky I got
the weeken passes to off gu but I
skipped when I didn't me win a Mee in
green I can understand why they don't
announce the big events ahead of time
but I'm sorry I missed the concert I
hope one day I'll wait but you had a
ticket and you didn't
go just because you didn't win the medum
grade
what they didn't announce it like that
late that I would be like not just doing
a meet and green they just weren't
really really clear about what exactly
it was going to
be man that's sad I'm sad that you
missed
it now let this be a lesson to
you don't miss it next time when you
already have a ticket come on come on
believe in the process trust trust the
Wawa the world
tour well I mean the places they
announced so
far is that convention
so I would think it's going to be mostly
conventions yeah
[Music]
Jes G thank you for the pinky by the way
at the concert me and at least two other
kfp near me were
your what Your debut H my shirt proudly
all three of them were well cared for
and loved really cuz I think that one if
you wash it it may like lose the print
uh relative ly easily I feel like it
might have been one of
those that yeah fall apart pretty easily
I'm not
sure so many of kfp had so many of your
merch on them nice Flex it's still
intact yours is intact nice oh AI yours
is falling apart the print is constantly
falling apart yeah don't wash it guys
just don't wear it anymore just keep it
somewhere save just to look at
H or wash it like really
cold maybe if you wash it really cold it
wouldn't be oh was it you bang shami did
you also have that shirt on
y we need a re-release I doubt that that
will happen at this point I I I think I
um suggested it once
but but it's okay it will keep it very
very exclusive this way
something kind
to some f just you
know some things
[Music]
are cold washes help or wash it in a
pillow case oh yeah or washing back
inside out to prevent scrapes yeah yeah
that's that's some good advice
that's some
good how do you call
it that's some kind of advice that your
mommy would give
you not life hack like householding
advice you always flip I never do that
maybe I should be doing that with my
stuff
[Music]
your washing machine turns clothes
inside out on its own damn how does it
do
it your washing machine kind of
crazy you guys know more than me but I
actually I don't really have many
graphic
T's you eh anyway that's that's sweet
I'm glad there's you know
proof of that shirt existing still
around Moonlight the wolf than you soon
and H spank andhe thanks for the
pinky okay I just got out of work and
who is this what have you done to my
wa wasn't she cute especially when she
was blown up like a fish Islands looking
through your door or you are looking
through your door and I'm standing there
looking really closely for your peekaboo
hole that was the best that was the
cutest yeah M
sphere I don't even get it but I'm just
going to say it like you guys say it or
Cho but Di dou Jones
D
yay yay
yay yay yay
yay they repeating long
waa no maidens yeah he yo heo no
[\h__\h] that's also what I had to think
about when I did that hey
yo hey yo no
[\h__\h] okay I finished reading the
special reveal and announcement mini
okay Super Chat
H I'm going to skidadle I
think you've got to go me too oh we're
going to the same meeting AR
we see you
there
SK SC
[Music]
can secretly squeeze some skibbies in
there without you
guys being able to
[Music]
complain I have so much um
flag them in my throat these days why
why scat singing is fine Skiby toilet is
not but what if it's
mixed what if it's
both bad air humid H but Austria
generally doesn't get as
humid as other play things that are
legitimately humid but yeah butt oh
that's a nice butt
Fang I like that you can see
it
hello
y I feel like run block is going to be a
disaster faster with the recent brain
Rod Trend oh don't worry I don't I think
mostly myth is not affected by the brain
Rod I mean
go did mention
SK what in her like stream title the
other day right I was watching a little
bit of her VR stream yesterday that was
so cute that was so funny like she was
so cute and the the skull was so funny I
liked watching that but it was was
getting so late and I really had to
scadaddle so that I get a little bit of
sleep before the 5 a.m.
meeting that meeting went on pretty
long but isn't it nice [\h__\h] B is [\h__\h] B is
uh doing so much these days it's nice to
see her having fun and playing all kinds
of games
thriving
again I'm happy to see that and the
games she chooses I'm I'm very
interested at the
moment I almost want to play that VR
game of the funny
skull he's
funny is gone she's not gone she was
wasn't she just in that uh M
GAA OverWatch was it
OverWatch she showed up for that one for
example
she is she's
somewhere oh yeah and the Mario yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah she she showed up actually twice
with guda recently
yeah
so all is well right now all is well
swell
swell doesn't I'm only stream on weeked
now is that a thing did she say
that I didn't hear that
glad to catch your stream thank
you no she's just figuring out her
setup she said no such thing
okay
good yeah Kell's coming back from her
break so all is good in this
neighborhood and it's the perfect time
to start the myth one block adventure
together
yay and with that I'll leave you
behind um in the studio to maybe take a
shower yeah and change your clothes and
then go
home in German we say a
same see you the day after tomorrow okay
bye-bye
[Music]