do you like Swedish meatballs new role
filtered they're terrible more like
Danish meatballs to me in Japan I always
go to this Danish something something
ball bar Danish ball bars the sugar
coated danishes are so good I hate
Danish ball bars you're a terrible
YouTuber okay then I'll stop stressing
everyone out and eat this food now but
only a little bit because I'm still
hungry one's still dying what oh
the end
I have Phoenix feathers I can revive her
it's like magic isn't it it's the magic
of friendship you can drag your friend
out of the fire by their hair and that's
magical in my opinion
the next picture is a beetle and beetle
beetle is actually just an AI I invented
to seem interesting in conversations
like this yikes but oh well I'm
why are there so many cats in your
fridge