[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
PA
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
k for a moment I forgot I was planning
to go
here
K hello smoothie is really really needy
right now and squeezed herself between
my phone and my
keyboard very
cute H H is there a big delay or so I
say A you say
B I think it should be
normal okay okay okay we're good we're
good ah hello good morning it's a
beautiful day to learn some
Korean ah I don't remember anything so I
prepared a
dialogue um
please
please listen
[Music]
fore
[Laughter]
so I said I had a teacher last year
that's last year
already ch
ch last year for like half a year if you
guys remember I was doing private
lessons with a teacher and I paid a lot
of
money lot of money for it so making it
go to waste would be a waste I paid a
lot of
money for private lessons last
[Music]
year oops
money nor n uh
one yeah well now I'm using Papa go but
it would be nice if one day I don't have
to use Papa go for the simplest things
but I revived my dualingo which I
haven't used for probably also like a
year and I had the the the subscription
running this whole time it seems I think
yeah it's I think it's still
subscribed
H yeah this is like what we did in the
previous stream up to
here yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah you did
forget I I guess wait let me check I
think it looks like the the s to me
looks like I'm
subscribed
uh where is this here am I
subscribed you're learning on super
dualingo say goodbye to ads and support
our mission yeah seems like I'm I have
been subscribed for a long
[Music]
time oh I founded the Brazilian buttlift
yeah okay
[Music]
uh what was
it okay so I don't know if I should like
redo any of these I just tried to see
how much everything takes up in terms of
space
uh oh oh oh n Nuna Nuna I'm been called
Nuna Nuna is like sister right
oh wow wow W but I
am I like a fixes wow what was I saying
yeah I tried one just to see like okay
how much space it takes up um I don't
know if we should repeat the honest I
kind of want to see it's just like
dualingo always has been kind of random
in the things that they teach like they
try to teach you something and suddenly
they throw in like city names and then
they throw in a proper word but then
they go back to ah yeah or so like it's
like what are you what are you trying to
accomplish with this m
but then let's let's uh I don't know H
learn maybe maybe let's redo the basic
phrases okay cuz this is consonant no
I'm fine with that I
think let's start H
fighting
oh oh
milk thank you for starting off with one
that I
know okay okay oh dear see like okay
student is Hing I think Hing yeah
student
Hing song is
[Music]
no
uhhuh
key is
your that's one of the few words I
learned in my lessons I
and these two I don't really know
[Music]
um uh yo yo yo and IU let's guess ipu
entrance IU yeah
ipu yeah okay that was guessed I don't
know shimun Korean newspaper shimun
shimun
shimun is
newspaper um so probably they want this
s to korean's
newspaper
yay which one of these is baby like
that's just stupid if you're going to
show me pictures then obviously I'm
going to know by the
picture are you kidding
dingo what's the
point
pble stupid
dingo don't show me the picture but I
would have known anyway it's ai ai
AIA obviously it's not the spider or
newspaper
yo y what did she say yo
y y
y
Fox that's Fox did did they was it Fox
was Fox written like that previously I
guess so oh I wrote it wrong I wrot I
read yo but this is not yah she says it
like
yah but it's isn't it y
y it sounds different yeah yo yo yo
ooh she says like
yeah that's
confusing five in a row oh we're doing
pairs again okay man
milk and taste I actually revised that
uh like uh before the stream is mat m m
h baby is Ai Ai and fox was the y y y
y and chicken
oh
t t but then I think
T what
say it say it you said the other ones t
t oh thank you chicken wait it feels
like the first time I I knew about this
tuck
tuck p
p oh wait I heard about that in other
words before yeah the L L and K at the
bottom when they like this I guess it
just
becomes
Ramen nice nice
nice haing ah students newspaper
students newspaper student newspaper
y y
[Music]
yeah yes this e is this to to not to not
donut donut he just says it
weird donut well yeah it's like in in
Korean like d will often be pronounced
very strongly like a tea ye donut no yay
donut
yay donut pronunciation a little off
right but yes this donut is what I want
to
eat okay okay okay we're matching again
uh chicken
duck yeah song
was baby was ay AI Fox was
y y student is
[Music]
Hing
kimy
kimy Kim me Ant
cucumber
kimy I forgot kimy and it is
and uh
[Music]
which one of these is
key could it be this person with a
glasses and the book in his hands could
it be this this this carttoon of milk
with a glass of milk or could it be the
picture that seemingly looks like a key
huh
which one could this
[Music]
be I would say y but I guess I'm
pronouncing no I feel like I'm
pronouncing it wrong though because it's
an S and an U and an e y
see y
see do I say it wrong she says
weirdly she says your s m is it more
like I
say ah cucumber was
it this one cuz this one is uh these are
different ones anyway uh o e o o o
cucumber
o at least okay I know these already so
the pictures are not really you know
helping me or so so it's okay taste was
M Yay good job o e
u o stop with the Cucumbers perfect
lesson I made no mistakes
oh prove your Legend why do I have to
prove it you know I
am okay so we we we did wait I guess it
was just like this one out of these all
of the
let's let's do uh the last oh oh earn
legendary on every level to unlock the
final trophy oh now whatever okay let's
move
on H name common
objects which one of these is ice cream
okay so here's probably where it starts
that they're throwing things at me that
I haven't learned yet so it just assumes
that I already know them but at least
there's a
picture I cream ice
cream okay these are all actually copy
ice cream and cola Cola yeah it's just
the English words so that's easy enough
ice cream ice
cream ice
cream ice cream CH hey
yo which one of these is copy copy copy
copy I don't like copy C copy copy
[Music]
copy in in Japanese they also use the
English word but they say Co
he but there's I guess there's no h
really in Korean so they say copy which
one of these is
Cola Cola NACA
Cola nice the r Cola yeah keep on
repeating these English words to me
ke did you just say ke ke even though I
learned
the the no they mean they mean
this key are they are they trying to F
me off is key no it's not key no key do
you want
me but you taught me the Korean word in
the previous lesson why are you just
like doing it this way now it's
Yi H trick question
[Music]
maybe
a
a aart
youly what the
why are why are we going back to
boa speech like only English words now
cop it's like I'm English Copa uh
cop
ridiculous uh Paris
apartment wow w wow cppy ice
cream teach me something
[Music]
reala ice cream ice cream yeah yeah yeah
yeah I get it I get it I get it I get
[Music]
it that's great work let's make this a
bit harder please
do Boston apartment key write this in
Korean okay okay okay okay okay at least
this this practices my reading
so po po po po this
[Music]
poon Chi there's no y right she sh sh
po what's
that wow H this key uh e e ke
[Music]
CH can't be for real
man is this for
real wait so but do you just do this
again again because the circle is not
full I don't get it a yeah lesson three
of six okay T all right here we go
again
te
I there was a word for tea and I think I
knew it before for Korean what's the
actual Korean word for tea just jump oh
like like in like in uh Japanese okay CH
so let's not be swayed by this write
this in English h i
i oh this is new p p p moment ah
phone key and phone no no no no no and
oh God
wait uh
phone I knew it before the actual
word for for phone I was
taught
uh you just use do you actually use this
English words rather
than ch
ch oh
yeah yes yes yes
Americo Americo
Americo T Americo I
can't is that's why we stopped using
Amico I Americo I americ oh my God
monito monitor I I just thought you said
Bonito uh this this
monitor yeah
pone
monitor P monitor phone monitor oh oh
that's what what is that really what you
would call the screen of a phone proba
not more like phone screen
but oh the students
monitor Ice copy Ice copy iced coffee
easy let's make this a bit harder I told
you please do ice te okay okay reading
exercise I
I that was not so hard actually the
other words are harder to
read
[Music]
uh no
no it
[Music]
is
violin
pin pin ahin
binlin ah
p p p p
p black a black black
ah
uh
uh oh my cat cat cat a cat cat cat
wasi pble my stupid cat jumped H what is
this ah is this dingo
dingo P monitor p p p p monito monit mon
monit okay moving on I guess I got to
continue in this one
okay
gold I suppose ch ch
sh
sh silver key Sil silver
key don't get me confused lady
key gold
key what about orange
key
F what you say black black oh I just
learned it the chat told me
ha what hail hail hair no
way no way that Korean people say hell
to their
hair no what's the actual word for hair
let's find out Pap
Mor yeah Mor but I think I heard that I
think I learned that before
height height
white I'm pretty sure the colors I mean
yeah sometimes like even in in Japanese
you know there's chido and Kuro but then
sometimes like maybe
for also for
likei they will say instead of Kuro it
depends I
guess C white white cold w
hi to
Hell white hair white
hair oh grandma grandma
Wawa old waah
ha what did you say ha black
hair G Hill black
haill Black Hill
sh silver phone that's what that is can
you teach me actual Korean at some
point
guys white white hair
oh
white h h this the only thing that makes
sense in these lessons is the reading
exercise it's the only thing that's
helping me you could just skip I might
yeah I might have to but then I'm
there's every once in a while there's
something in between actually no for
this one it's really just English words
I was just going to say sometimes
there's something useful but no no
[Music]
no yay did
it oh no I have to I can jump here
because I guess because I have a
subscription but I wonder if there's you
know I want to jump like
here
huh okay let's let's jump
there ice key
[Music]
really sorry I I misheard
you key and T no problem keep let's keep
going shut
up
no Chicago
p
no
no no Chicago Cho poon
at least I'm I'm practicing my reading
put
Inon no
wait oh no pilat Pilates pinston
ping there we
go no not I F I skipped I skipped why
are we here again why are we doing this
copy Cola copy copy Cola uh
Cola Cola why aart key no why aart aart
Key Apartment
Key shut up Black Diamond why are
we this is still the hunger learning
stage is that the point of this ah maybe
because like then okay they maybe want
to use words that are like still
somewhat familiar to
you so that you can practice your
reading
no I guess
so do the test which test this is also a
test no or I guess not but I can't I
have to like I think I have to do the
lessons to the test up leeding to the
test what did you say black diamond uh
[Music]
oh child we have an actual Korean word
and Paris apartment
p
a okay yeah I guess it's reading
exercise copy copy
copy yeah roll p p I love that I love
the pronunciation in in Korean it's
cute
philadel Philadelphia
Philadelphia I
I this is a
[Music]
hunger sh
silver
King sh
[Music]
King how many times this repeating until
it's hammered into my brain and I will
forget the Korean words for
key okay okay nice
job P mon P mon
you guys are also going to end up saying
things wrong like not the actual English
pronunciation you're going to say it the
Korean way the Korean way is the only
way child's television H the the child's
the uh
the
I will I will i
e i
[Music]
don't forget don't forget the small
words in between or dualingo is going to
be mad at you what' she say p Toyo party
party P Tokyo party I I've been to all
of them I've been to all of them M I
have been there
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
t wow wow although M
Berlin not Berlin not good not the best
I mean you know it's all right I've been
there a few times actually it's not so
bad it's not so bad it's it's okay it's
okay P monitor p
[Music]
it's okay yeah it's not too bad it's um
it has some beautiful Stu spots
too
t
lingo pin Tokyo party we we already had
that
broin Tokyo
too PTY PTY I guess you know I have to
get faster at finding the words out of
these ice cream putty ice cream puty
party or Patty party right ice cream
party I want to have an ice cream party
at at
at uh bask and Robins
please I love bask and Robins I want to
bask in their ice cream can you say that
cuz you can bask in light in sunlight
right can you bask in ice cream
in the coolness of their freezers in
their chill
freezers I want a bask in their Robins I
want a bask in your Robins how to how to
hit up a girl uh at bask in Robins
getting ice cream you're like oh you
like basking Robins how would you like
to bask in my
Robins actually that's actually really
good
I mean not good like I mean it's not
going to work well probably but it
actually makes somehow
sense how to get the rest of the
Mas how would you like to bask in my
Robins please explain what your Robins
are first of
all uh Gold
Key C
[Music]
ke
no no not not
te
Americo we're almost through guys we're
almost through and ice
cream ice cream py py nice
[Applause]
yay no I understand this is reading
exercise I suppose let's let's let's
give them the benefit of the doubt that
that's what they're doing uh I don't
know I'm kind of curious like what this
is or do they always have a weight lift
is it does it maybe let's go to greet
people pass this test to jump oh okay
p p p p
P that's an actual Korean word
yo I'm off to a great start hell yeah H
hung p p h okay
Korea P outside outside outside outside
Korea outside ah out or outside of
Korea do we actually want to make like
something that makes sense outside of
[Music]
Korea yes
a yeah I remember I learned that siki
siki siki siki siki trash is siki That's
So I love that word like oh my God I I
um sometimes I get asked what's your
favorite Japanese word and I'm like I'm
I'm so like fluent I don't really
there's nothing really where I would say
it's my favorite word why would I have a
favorite word but I think this is like
something when you're still starting to
learn a language like with
Korean then I could say one of my
favorite Korean words is sui it's just a
fun cute word I like it it makes the the
the meaning of trash so much cuter
doesn't
[Music]
it
London London Lon
Lon a oh okay here we go again with the
English words I was wondering what you
were
saying
London flower ah ah this one h c c I
think
yeah yeah I
remember I learned these
wordsi
[Music]
kamagi what no idea what's kamagi
a it is Crow I was thinking because we
heard Fox before we heard pants before
it can't really be these so it's kind of
but what do you mean camera Crow what
does that mean is that is that a phrase
for people
who like to be or camera or not what
what does that
mean
camera oh and Crow oh together okay okay
yeah yeah go go is
end oh there's there was a solution too
okay
mouth
[Music]
oh oh No let know that
song This
one
is p right
p i I just can't hear hear her say
[Music]
it eat
this
[Music]
this star
this star and that star is it different
words for
[Music]
star yeah he says
it ah I cannot hear him so well P
okay ah ah what he's saying the same
word twice I thought Oh I thought it was
one word
H is and yeah I remember that okay okay
this uh star and that
star this star and that
star
wo
wo the song
Oh that song m
is a
[Music]
song
Kiss
message T ton is it that kiss or
ton ton po
[Music]
oh or message or
kiss
[Music]
mess which one do you want po they're
saying
po they want the kiss M Mah mwah
mwah okay nice cuc the Cucumber she ah
cucumber was O in but see
[Music]
oh yeah oh
yeah maybe like this I don't know no no
the pot
pot it is see see I had a feeling it was
looking at me with those
eyes ah
see New York out outside of New York I
am currently outside of New
York New
York most of you are probably outside of
New York right now me too oh my god
let's
go Korea day
chicken hung
[Music]
hle d d was it
this
no not not chicken
p
p p
Tu not nut I forgot the word for
day nut nut
not not not it is not today it is not
yesterday it is
[Music]
tomorrow chicken's egg
oh t
t it is how to say like something like
s apostrophe s okay I got to remember
that
t
not
s Soul no that's soul so uh
your could be this or it could be
Al yeah it looks at me like an
egg uh taret I
T
nice more like right
R uh
tofu to wait it's under t
t is that how you say tofu would it be
t t
t or o that was cucumber
right nice
[Music]
field not this not this maybe this pot
no
[Music]
no t t t t tan is feel
M see
SE flower with
c e mouth no
wait no not mouth that was
different it's not donut cucumber maybe
it's
Leaf okay rice
[Music]
rice pop
pop
yeah I remember
pop pop pop
what did you say
London okay I've been to London H but
not pan or New York S I want to go I
always hear good things about pan and
New York man would be dope to see
someday I got to go on that America Tour
New York Washington oh I see Washington
and I
see New York New York New York washingt
Washington Newspaper
shim shim
shimi
yeah my Shimon goes into the sui I don't
even I mean I don't even get a Shimon
but if I had a shin it would probably go
into the
sui
[Music]
newspaper newspaper shim shim
shim the
dress all right a English word Ah that's
that that saved my ass
yay I unlocked unit 7even let's go wait
is is this is unit 7even okay we can
greet people we have gained the right to
greet
people I'm excited there's some fly in
my water get out of
here okay
fighting start great people
yay
yeah
mey new
jeans you got them
I love new Jean's new
[Music]
songsing my
mind w w I love
it and what' you
[Music]
say that's just names oh wait e
wait e is that just how
you is because this is E Lee wait Lee is
actually written as
e in
Korean when I never
realized
what
what why did it become Lee did it just
sound like Lee to like English-speaking
people
like hundreds hundreds of years before
and they were like ah Le uhhuh
uhhuh oh
interesting or the the
Ki it is so complicated we don't even
know we just accept it that's so
interesting because Lee is like a very
common name too in Korea and and now you
realize it's actually written
incorrectly
CL uh Kim
s I'm sure there's a famous person who
has that name
probably
[Music]
CH
s new word song last
name
s toy last
what try last name that's what you want
me to put there my last
name oh I got
Bamboozled CH is also
my
ah you got
me last
name is Kim I think cuz m m then uh this
is yeah last name Kim mhm y I made a
[Music]
sentence I
am Kim Son
you are
Kim I am
[Music]
Kim You Are I
Am Park Chun
[Music]
not this time my last name
is what' you
say oh it's double Choy he said his name
is Choy then I couldn't even have used a
double I think I would have been fine
okay now hold I see my last name is choy
[Music]
that's how it is got to read it
correctly let's read the exercise you
missed well I mean it was a new word so
uh my name no wait my e
[Music]
so my last
name yeah
okay yay she's clapping but with a
really unimpressed unamused face uh face
Yay okay go
next I'm I'm young hi hi to you too
hasim
what hello oh oh this whole phrase is
one word right it's just a a really long
word it's like questioning it it's so
long right
hello
[Music]
hello very
long we are very polite
[Music]
I nice to meet
you
[Music]
students ah ah the name the student's
name is colum the
students I can decipher this the
students name is
k w w Who whoo whoo whoo
whoo
name let's
go ah Sona
is my name son is son is my
[Music]
name okay it's different ways of saying
this is my name
[Music]
uh my name my name
is but he is
my name is
s I think I'm learning I think I'm
learning let's
[Music]
go oh the robot is speaking to me the AI
is speaking to me my name is dualingo oh
God don't talk to me I don't want to
talk to you dualingo you are not real
[Music]
Hello nice to meet
you thank
you yes yes easy
[Music]
words thank you thank
you thank you nice to meet
nice to meet you I'm learning I mean I
knew these already but it's like nice to
to repeat everything and the other
things were also like well yeah I kind
of knew it but you know select the
matching pairs okay flower
c song
nor
cucumber hello
[Music]
how you know you heard people maybe if
you watch anything like Korean TV or
something even if you don't speak Korean
you hear this all the
[Music]
time yeah like it's not just how they
also say it like like like kind of like
or or like when they see when they
they're like maybe a little bit
Bamboozled or so I don't know they use
it in so many
ways oh when you're like troubled or so
you
[Music]
say it's
different it's different
what Hello nice to meet you
[Music]
let's
go my name is D okay okay now I am
writing the Korean things of what they
taught me the other way around and my
name is Jingo uh
[Music]
Kar it's good to like make your own
version of the sentence I think then
like replace their names with your own
name I think that
helps her Korean lesson was a cucumber
field what field field I already forgot
the field for the field the word for
field uh P poy poyy
[Music]
okay I did it yay next one next one
we're still in here greeting people
what' you
say
[Music]
uhoh he probably is saying welcome or
noong it's hard to hear Hong Hong but I
have to read
Hong is it
welcome yes ah to all the viewers
watching all the
duck h no and H
[Music]
H Korean uh chickens welcome to the
stream nice to meet you nice I would
like to have the that here too but okay
nice to meet you
[Music]
we have free cookies we do no we don't
have free
cookies but it's good to maybe bait them
with the free cookies go
[Music]
ahead hello welcome
I I am
okay are you okay maybe he's okay maybe
he's okay
[Music]
okay is what you say
I couldn't recognize what he was saying
[Music]
qu I am
okay
qu are the Korean chickens
okay yeah pronunciation I mean I should
just you know learn how to read then it
would be okay but even then I feel like
I need to hear it too properly to really
understand
is you know like son in Japanese so it's
like Mr or Mrs
H
so hello no hello
maybe hello
[Music]
s uh oh new word can I look lady ah y ah
no no no I I learned this I learned this
in my Korean lessons last year oh
uh lately I am doing okay uh Jun is me
lately lately I am doing okay I am okay
lately also works
okay is uh child uh I forgot well M
child
so
[Music]
like is doing well is doing well
maybe CH is well I
think right
yeah but without the
child what does it mean just doing in
general because that's the
[Music]
verb what is it like on its own without
the child ch
ch oh I read it
wrong so it's just doing
anything
so for example in Japanese is Gen is it
like oh
whoa my neck is not doing so
well uh okay let's make that sentence
neck is what was it
again
uh uh
Kiara
kiar n m uh
[Music]
cho cho
I'm still not sure about saying like
something is not
[Music]
TI qu
qu
quento no not
quen
qu my neck is not
okay not
okay okay okay
[Music]
is she doing
well in romanized letters that was C h
no j i n u
p this word CH it's e right Chik not
son is uh is
son uh doing
[Music]
well how how is jiun
doing yeah period uh
[Music]
how is
doing recently right no how have you
been recently or lately I guess
[Music]
both how have you been recently okay is
recently is
Howa is have you
been what recently lately the same
word same word same word same word
recently lately
it's the same word right English
speaking people confirm for me pretty
much same
word used pretty much
interchangeably it's a
synonym P Doo
P yeah I don't that I'm not taking that
lamam and
qu this is so
complicated you see these like small
things down here like they get combined
or like silenced and stuff it's like
weird you know qu
[Music]
qu
H qu qu qu no qu
theam is doing okay yeah it's silence
[Music]
right yes okay pears
is
[Music]
taste to be okay
uh all right thank
you
I ah ah
been doing well
lately CH
I've recent
lately
uh well
okay the P so this is another case where
it's confusing the P turns into an M I
guess I've been doing well
[Music]
lately so she is the person how because
it's capitalized I'm just going to start
with that it's a question so how is
soong
doing I suppose wait oh let me
read yeah how
how is so doing I think that's the end
of the sentence
[Music]
okay uh how have you been lately okay
I'm getting
[Music]
better way too powerful thank
you
yay that was quite
something I think I'm getting motivated
guys I'm motivated to learn more
go oh he's saying sorry thank you
because I don't know how to say sorry
teach
me CH I mean I probably learned it last
year
but uh over the table choice choice song
[Music]
sorry thank you you can
say that's also a way to say like sorry
or like excuse
me I remember that excuse me
excuse me I am sorry she is more like
excuse me yeah I am sorry
chy
CH how do I
[Laughter]
says it's c song title uh in
Korean um wow uh H uh
chy the what I just said chy Cho
[Music]
yeah uh it's like yeah what I kept on
saying to my teacher and she said back
to me because C and right it's like you
say G
to uh the person you're saying goodbye
to and they say it back with quo was it
was it was it yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah so you guys I say to
you
uh and you guys say to
me like yeah go go well go in in peace
or
[Music]
so
goodbye I have to say it less Softly I
have to say it more strongly but I'm I'm
I don't know that's one of my issues
with uh Korean reading I think
because in romanized letters they
translate it as GA a but the real
pronunciation is more like Ka but it's
also kind of like an in between right
but in Japanese there's GA and Ka so I
take it very seriously if it says GA
then I'm just going to say GA in
[Music]
thank
you and
goodbye thank you next next Ariana
Grande was singing this
[Music]
what did you just say ah it's the
kiss goodbye as well but in a different
way goodbye do I just say goodbye then
goodbye this this makes no sense because
I think yeah stay in peace there you
go what I was just talking about here we
go yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh uh thank you and and bye okay
thank you
bye that's so it
sounds that's that's not really how I
would translate it because like it's
very polite first of all so I would say
thank you very much and then I would say
um at least goodbye if not
even well I guess yeah the gaso G is
kind of difficult to translate but here
it says stay in peace
which it's a it sounds a bit exaggerated
in English doesn't
it but yeah it's more polite than thank
you
by he sorry and he says
goodbye I am sorry
goodbye he has just given up he's uh
doing the Walk of
Shame oh
CH P that's not really what you said
said is it
[Music]
po
gu but I read po
po I guess it's uh I guess it's silenced
again
very polite
[Music]
form oh you using German
letter and this this gets silenced the p
on the bottom gets silenced I guess
H ch
ch nice to
[Music]
meet same thing s like the matching
pairs
[Music]
haing here
it's speaking to me again you're
dualingo why are you talking to me what
would you want from me you want to
become friends with me I
refuse and nice to meet
you I
[Music]
am okay
oh no okay Jo
[Music]
Jo
wait
yeah
woohoo let's go
goodbye
[Music]
no that's fine
too I made no mistakes yay 100% wao okay
one more one
more let's recap this level with a
reward at the end is it ice cream ice
cream
recently how have you been
doing
uh uh
how have you been
lately song toy song
uh ah last name right m
[Music]
but you're okay I thought so my last
name the capitalized T is throwing me
off it's like you want me to put that at
the beginning
[Music]
goodbye Y what was that
again y
[Music]
Lee my last name is Lee
maybe but don't m Fox oh the
fox that makes no sense the foxes and
the foxes last name is
[Music]
Le what does the fox
say that is his name uh lately
[Music]
I'm okay goodbye but like it it is okay
goodbye there we
go hello an
[Music]
nice to meet you nice to meet you I am
doing
all
name not Shin not y That's key that's
newspaper it's
ID Ed and last name is song first name
is or or the whole name last name is
[Music]
so the
person how
is doing no actually nobody said lately
[Music]
so your child okay you're doing very
well I I've
been well
[Music]
lately thank
you and bye bye I'm out of
here
W I'm a leg no what do you mean I'm I'm
I am a legend okay
okay complet this extra hard Challenge
and level up to okay let's do it let's
do it
let's become a
legend
[Music]
welcome hello
welcome excuse
me thank you
[Music]
I
am
I that was
uh nice to meet you yeah nice to meet
you nice to meet
[Music]
you you doing it on your own I
am I'm so proud and
[Music]
is my
name is okay
thank you nice to meet
[Music]
you uh I
guess I am sorry goodbye
[Music]
toy ah
it's wait toy
in yeah yeah yeah he's he's uh he's
trying to troll me again my name is Joy
no last
name my name my last name is chy because
song is last name
e is just
[Music]
name
okay I am okay of course you're okay
you're you're a child you're still naive
about the world as long as you're still
a child everything's going to be okay
man don't grow up it this okay goodbye
oh okay I have to figure it out myself
[Music]
I guess well there's no G so I guess
it's well yeah yeah some some children
can also not be doing so well of course
but generally if you're doing okay it's
because you're enjoying the life of a
child son
hello that's a beautiful
name I'm okay
[Music]
lately
uh my last name is Choy
uh okay my brain is starting to stop
working it's okay I can still do it wait
we've been studying for one and a half
hours like normally people how long do
people do dualingo per day like 10 30
minutes but I've been studying for 1 and
1 half hours it feels like I've just
been streaming for 20 minutes though my
God it's crazy how fast time passes when
you're studying like this
I guess it's normal that my my brain is
getting
slower my last name is CH wa this is the
one that always like froze me
off my last
[Music]
name yeah you can't throw me off this
time I get it
now they want fish minutes a day but
there are people who use doing
competitively and do it for hours
competitively what they treat it like as
a game cuz they want to go up like a
ranking I think there's a ranking right
well that's insane people make
everything into a
challenge kamam is doing well okay okay
[Music]
okay he doing well and
CH we don't we want to say she's not
just doing okay she's doing well that's
why we need the CH
and okay hello my name
is Maybe
[Music]
no
wait you could say that but we
need or should I
add like
[Music]
this okay cuz you can shorten the
sentence but we want uh you know we want
it full fully completed let's
go how is jiun doing okay okay
um How is
[Music]
oh I have
legendary okay I'm excited about that we
we got a golden color gold coin for that
one that whole
thing okay let's try to study for 25
more minutes or so I mean 2 hours of
study is
pretty quite a lot h hly even in school
like your brain is going to start
[Music]
burning why are you teaching me only
names please teach me
[Music]
more there's only one option what's the
point when there's only one option
dualingo you cannot defend that that is
stupid there's just one
option uh okay
ah
you're I am for sure there's someone in
the chat who has his name
right is there is there not a Park T in
the chat h
[Music]
where is
P I am P from today no
no don't lie to me see one
option write this in Korean okay that's
going to be
difficult I'm
that's not a
challenge I
am what you
[Music]
say my last
name M's last name is
Kim
no Fox it's the Fox again ah I
was like wait this this is this is this
is the one this is the one that's like
out of place it shouldn't be here but
okay the fox last
name is Lee the fox's last name is
[Music]
Lee I figured it out this time mean his
last name is Kim okay okay okay focus
K my last name is CH
[Music]
uh let's
go I'm so proud of myself wow like oh my
God actually
amazing just for the sake of you know a
little bit of variety should we try
jumping here I probably have to do
another test for it and that might be a
little bit
rough just for the sake of variety but
you guys maybe have to help
me goodbye
[Music]
okay nice nice to me
too name m Eden Eden
my name is
dingo
brainwashing speed run to level 10 I'm
great at this thank
[Music]
you
Hi
how I'm
speeding the police is going to get me
and give me a
[Music]
ticket uh
is doing
[Music]
okay yeah yeah I'm on a
roll
hello thank
you sorry
[Music]
I
am nice to meet
you nice to meet you that one doesn't
come as natural as the other nice to
meet you so so I need a moment to think
about it how have you been lately
[Music]
H what
what ah is s doing
okay welcome nice to meet
you this
[Music]
one go
uh
I've been well
lately is okay
goodbye it's okay goodbye is okay
goodbye
[Music]
I
sorry
goodbye we're totally getting there we
can totally skip that level M's last
name is
[Music]
Kim my name
is
Sergeant s hello
s we can do a we can do
a see if we want no need maybe I don't
know uh
[Music]
hello I am I
sorry okay sorry
by that's not enough words I would say I
am
sorry
Goodbye Oh wait is oh
sorry why sorry it's fake you
oopsie okay one mistake I'll take one
mistake
[Music]
I am okay
lately your
your
y y can I start with yum or should I
start with I I don't
know maybe
[Music]
hello welcome I I I am feeling the the
limit I'm feeling it's it's happening
I'm braining I'm braining I'm burning my
burn is braining my brain is burining my
brain is
Burning uh hello welcome I know I know
that I know that but like it's taking
longer to think
[Music]
now oh excuse me she
thanks for repeating that one I missed
that one my last
name
toy
song what unlocked unit eight stage
achievement leveled up was okay well
then I am like really have my limit but
well let's let's try one of these okay
okay we skipped again this is the new
one right M it shows all
the oh it will still give me the check
marks even though I didn't do most of
them nice
okay okay o
ah
y I learned this yeah yeah oh and CH we
have the actual uh Korean word for
phone n is
[Music]
man
woman I work
[Music]
yeah that sounds
familiar
ah that man the man
works is the verb for working is the
word for
man who is that that d
[Music]
works that easy
which you are a phone what wait what I
know you're
calling I thought you were claiming to
be a phone that would be crazy I
[Music]
call M
phone
what ah dad won't
studies that woman that you're watching
now studies indeed
CH this is one of the words I actually
it's like somewhat difficult and I I
cannot forget this word because I used
it a lot thank God I don't forget this
one I always say
is study and H is to do flexing my
knowledge
[Music]
wow I I remember that is it
now yeah that woman the woman the woman
uh calls
now cool
[Music]
pick up the phone she's
calling ah
so is that that
woman is studying now jigum we had yum
and now we have jigum yum was lately
jigum is now okay remember these words
okay be remember that woman is studying
now
[Music]
is does K study that's what I was
looking
[Music]
for I can do this uh this one too quite
well it's like some actually Mo pretty
much mostly familiar words from my
studies from last year but it's good to
repeat it because otherwise it would not
be active in my brain anymore it's like
gray out and I have to refresh it what
did you
[Music]
say
what she sleeping someone is sleeping
sleeps now ooh
[Music]
CH was sleeping right
yeah
remembered I knew something was off
there was a new word it's new because we
didn't see it yet today to
sleep is Chada Chada name
isum woman is
y pants is p p Crow is
Kami
W Kam
is
Kam Crow woman that's how I'll call her
from now on well both narissa and crony
too kind of kamag is Cron
both of them kind of like both of them
are kind of connected with uh crows
right so that's actually funny
interesting what's your Canon crow in
whole life English now guys I guess
maybe narissa is more of a raven I don't
know hope you have fun at elf guy I am
so uneasy I have the data for uh the
gosu program uh like my my model my
converted Model H and all that but I
have not been able to test it yet
because I have not been sent the program
yet but they have promised to do so so I
hope that tomorrow at night which is
more like after midnight so it's
actually more like Sunday I hope by then
I'll be able to use it and at least test
it a little bit beforehand yeah I'm
getting nervous about it
yeah
anyway the man the
man is uh sleeping now sleeps
now to sleep Chada
[Music]
Chada nice I call
that woman is studying now uh that
woman yeah cuz the woman would be cool I
think we want to say that woman so it's
ch ch
[Music]
oh it this makes me happy to learn
Korean
again
ah what was that again I think I learned
that before too happy being I I am
happy
ah hang hang po okay
[Music]
I am
happy yeah I think
one more one more dog
o well thank God that there's pictures
but no I think yeah would have been fun
because this is
kangi cat COI oh we're dealing with dogs
and cats now after dealing with men and
[Music]
women
na
small na no something bad
oh
ill is ill something oh something
bad bad something something bad not
na wait nap is something ill is bad that
makes more sense and actually I can you
can kind of like um when someone is uh
speaking ill of you for example right
this they're speaking bad of you hey you
can make this this uh bridge in your
brain for that word or is it nap no okay
it's nap damn it that's a bit more
difficult nap ill something
bad the
baby is
small yes is is small the baby is my
baby your baby excuse
[Music]
me your baby is the baby
though my
my cat is
small H my cats are also relatively
small what was what was me to cho
cho m
[Music]
did I make a proper sentence that my
cats also are
small did I say it
right
yeah K Ali
[Music]
okay okay
okay and what was I feel like I remember
saying Cho just me too I guess H Cho is
Cho just me
too maybe I'm
misremembering yeah Cho me too ah yeah
yeah yeah so I can say CH I can also say
ch
ch uh me too no not
[Music]
really
okay what what did you say the fox the
freaking Fox
again the fox is bad what did the
do to you I mean foxes them they're like
crazy so maybe that's why you're saying
that your dog no you
like do you like dogs is that what you
saying I think he's saying that
yeah hey I like
[Music]
dogs bad
uh you what
I I like
Batman she's saying I like
Batman wow dingo it seems like
that is indeed what a lot of women are
going
for
[Music]
oh she likes bad
boys namja but did they not it says man
here okay but I guess because bad man
that no that's that's grammatically
weird because it have would have to be m
n it would have to be a plural
oh but then well it's not boys though
nja was man boys I think a little bit
different you don't say namja to a boy
so you're confusing me on purpose
dingo
boy was
[Music]
I do you like Duo you mean du lingo
you're so close of du lingo you're
calling them Duo
[Music]
now
corrupted mouth my mouth is big
[Music]
CH my mouth is
big I was saying my mouth is small
though the cat is
Big A
is
[Music]
big I
like
CH small cats that's what I thought but
I was confused by the order of the
sentence I like chonun
Chuck I
small cat
like
yeah okay
wait mouth something man
[Music]
my man what
man Big
Mouth Big Mouth
man big mouth
man mouth big
man do I translate this
[Music]
directly mouth oops mouth big man that
sounds weird let's say at least big
mouth man or or I mean we can make it
into a proper sentence but maybe they
will scold us for
that um man with a big
mouth
yeah
yeah I think in Japanese I would say
that
too a man with a big mouth yeah we can
just we can add these little words I
suppose maybe just like in Japanese
maybe in Korean you can do the
same
H cuz it's really just this I guess a
mouth this one has at least the e
e it doesn't say
whff but we can add it in our
brain maybe it doesn't need the
whff it's a phrase that makes sense to
the most in
[Music]
English yeah okay to be bad to be bad
was uh
NAPA NAPA
NAPA I learned something new I don't
think I learned Napa last year in my
half year of Korean studies it's like
the matching pairs K is dog woman is y y
name isum
how is his pants pants keeps on showing
up but nobody ever talks about the
pants pants are bad that's
why
La
duck and to be big
[Music]
um
ch right no
no CH was small
w i i I corrected myself in my brain
let's go to be small is chak chakaa
cha Chaka is small Cuda is big how can I
make this make sense in my brain
chak no I don't know can't think of
anything just have to remember it CH
small ch
I already I already forgot how to make a
sentence
[Music]
though
right uh could
[Music]
how do I say
big
becomes okay okay okay
[Music]
okay we F Tower
tower
Tower
[Music]
and I made my own
sentence nice nice nice nice
Tower okay now we know how to say Eiffel
Tower
in uh in in Korean what' you
say oh your baby's small my baby I'm not
going to make the mistake again with
that baby or so my baby is
[Music]
small ah you like evil men or bad men
I boys though let's go with boys this
time I like bad
boys
[Music]
oh
Ki
KI what what was the sentence what did
she
[Music]
say
Ki Ki KI
[Music]
dot dot dot exactly
did I forget the
word oh no I don't think I forgot
it I don't like
Batman Okay 89% that's okay for like
jumping over another time we've been
jumping so much but I think I think I'm
okay
now for today I think 2 hours of study
is you know more than enough 2 hours of
study is enough let's try again another
time uh let's read Super
Chat CH I like ch
ch another Japanese word that's very
similar to the Korean
[Music]
one
okay
uh ah super super chat
[Music]
super let's read Super Chat Super
Chat okay okay
[Music]
yay nice I'm so proud
man I'm so
proud yeah let's read super chats we've
made lots of progress I feel pretty
motivated to continue studying but it's
just the problem of will I
[Music]
remember well
fighting
fighting you did so good especially for
not having started in a while thank you
for real like I really have not started
for like a
year it's been too
[Music]
long super
chats yeah yeah okay
from uh you know what for now I'll just
read the ones from today for the Korean
Bros who are waiting for it okay it's
not that many
anyway h
bres d Tanaka from kfp
D ah the tips for the hle alphabet but
as we have seen my my hle alphabet
skills have definitely been decent so
we're good we're good J
monkey thank you for the pink Super
[Music]
Chat
uh
pong pong e
K
to what
what husb
I love
[Music]
you fan service in Korean is
working nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice thanks for the reading
practice for the thany but this is a lot
oh my God oh God if I try to read this
it's going to take 5 years let me let me
put this into paple
[Music]
why why do you have to scream he says
hell it's the manager again I was going
to sleep after watching all the vs but
but I ended up watching her now I have
to shout I know I'll wake you up when I
start shouting but I have to shout
that's the mission of the person who
witnessed the manager now I'm going to
shout oh worship is it it's a it's a
meme is it a Korean meme wow
[Music]
ah I
see is it a copy pasted
meme well thank you
Kaman that was interesting n n
interesting H thank you so much for the
support worshipping anytime meme
Ione D thank you dog
adoption let's go oh my God show me
pictures when you got the Dogo are you
getting a baby Dogo or like an adult
Dogo
[Music]
biet this is also really long is it the
same it's not the same meme right let's
see Kitty
yes I will okay it says I'm proud to see
that K Kore is improving day by day I'm
just grateful that oi has been
interested in Korean for about 3 years I
still feel warmhearted now and then I
hope you do a lot of broadcasts you want
to do in the
future thank
you I will I will uh I will try to
continue studying Korean I should just
watch more I always need something to
watch I should watch more of the Korean
shows like uh the Superman Superman has
baby for 24 or 48 Hours
one Superman the the
celebrity black Chan d
[Music]
King K King Kong K Kong come Moonlight
Butterfly Come for the pink Super Chat
wow w w w w this is also long you guys
also you don't expect me to read all of
this right I'll Take 5 years to read it
oh ah this
one I somebody I know this message
somebody else sent me this message
[Laughter]
[Music]
before it's the one that says I went to
kiala Cafe yesterday it wasn't open I
just followed kiala at the cafe I didn't
go to the cafe actually I just drank
cafe coffee at home in fact she didn't
even drink cof I didn't even drink
coffee then I don't really know this
seems like weirdly translated translated
I just really like ker yeah yeah yeah
it's another meme I like these memes I
read this before from a different uh
Korean bro and I didn't realize it was a
meme I thought you were making some
funny thing up oh funny
for the pink Super
Chat no no no no purple Puro is for red
super chat I forgot wait I gave pong a
discounted po I realized now
oopsie B oh wait how do I
say it's been a
while what's
[Music]
is that how you
say that is that how you guys say
it it's been a while
hello oh no you say it differently more
prefer
uh all
[Music]
sorry
I reading those wrong even though there
I should be able to read
it okay
[Music]
okay and
Prince of Denmark thank you see you
there bring the pen
lights for the pink Super Chat okay this
one's shorter I'll try to read it Kiana
[Music]
hanm not nor
sexy
okay are you really saying that or am I
reading it
wrong I think it's saying that I'm the
way I'm studying is cute and sexy
maybe uh
udy uh
uh
Chim
[Music]
[Laughter]
chimo are you asking me if I want to eat
chicken bul
du come I don't know what to say but
thank you it's a funny message it became
practice for me is it is that the
flirting phrase that crony taught me
before an
thank
[Music]
you thank you off Kai let's go you're
off to off
Kai you should be on to off Kai not off
to
ofai go on on to
ofai
Tera Sunny Tesla come
A M I already forgot the
word it's been a
Whiley
and oh wait a few more oh oh oh oh
[Music]
oh Garden
Park thank you for coming
and yum
yum
y thank
you thank you
fighting
G thank you that was intense
[Music]
h
what I heard that I can speak Korean
better if I sign the manager's signature
it's not weird because it's salary
increased
proposal
what what you going to fake my signature
or
what to get more salary what no
[Music]
no don't do
[Laughter]
that
or is that how you say in
[Music]
Korean let's read this thanks to Papo
please
[Music]
when you're going to Akihabara or do you
mean like you're going to Japan and then
from there one of the Places You'll Go
to is Akihabara or are you already in
Japan because I don't go to akih habala
usually
I don't have good
recommendations
but you should go
to
and okay Japan next week oh okay
okay go go go go go go go there but
akaba you can go too but I think like in
Akihabara you know when it comes to
recommendations you just walk around
that big street and then just you know
walk into some M cafes and stuff and
have fun there
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah I hope to see you sometime again in
my stream okay
MK any plus collab Cafe was great oh
yeah yeah yeah like it happened again
right come on recently I think Korean
Bros are getting absolutely spoiled
again with that event where crony and
Ena and the others were man I was
jealous now let me say that I was so
jealous that I was not part of the
event
recently
ah um with crony and
[Music]
Ena
for Fore
[Music]
spe
but it's okay it's okay because if I
M if if I if I can't go to Korean
event you just come to my stream
instead okay
[Music]
you just come to me if I can't come to
you it's that
[Music]
easy okay
nice and where was I yeah MK
thank you thank you thank
you should we try to
translate hasn't been long since I
watched K's broadcast but you're really
good at Korean thank you for doing this
broadcast even though your throat is not
so good no oh my throat is okay my neck
is not okay maybe there was a
misunderstanding H my throat is okay but
my neck is can I say that is it
going to translate that
funnny they're this oh they're the
same word oh yeah they are being
translated as the same word m
so h ah I could say my voice is okay my
voice is okay but my throat no no no but
my neck is not same thing but
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah now we got it I
think now I got my point across
[Music]
H reben
come but it's scent
in in Japanese Yen so maybe you live in
Japan but you're Korean or you're
Japanese but you speak Korean or so
[Music]
what does it
say
h wait I can read this
[Music]
iong y
H what's H I keep on hearing
[Music]
it Owen it's like it's
like always ah
hung always
a your
do recently lately now
was jum hang is always good words thank
you for teaching
me uh okay I'm finished with these super
chats okay today is Friday yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yeah okay I think just for the sake of
like
having it like you know having many
Korean viewers right now I'll read the
non Korean super chats uh from previous
stream from yesterday and the next
stream because I don't I I think it's
like uh too uh uh confusing
otherwise keep building the backlog no
no no it's not really backlog I read the
ones from today so it's all good okay
okay yeah oh and let me say to
Korean
huk
and
listen I think
[Music]
probably we're getting we're getting
there now I'm even going to be using her
program and I have the converted model
and everything so we can do collabo in
3D with
gosu my cute cute cute gosu it's
coming so more content for my Korean
Bros but also for my on Korean Bros it
will be fun I think yeah yeah finally
finally I really am excited to see how
that
[Music]
goes so for go basically actually the
reason why I did this uh Korean study
stream is because I new okay go collabs
coming closer coming closer maybe it's a
good opportunity to refresh fresh my
Korean her English is pretty good too
but you know I want to I want to say
some Korean words too even though I will
probably go completely blank when it
comes to it but you
know oh wait a second that Super Chat is
when did that come in did I read
that there's this red Super
Chat it it doesn't show up
ARS red super
chat doesn't show up in my list
actually
interesting I got deleted
why huh I I just saw it now
uh uh like accidentally so thank you let
me say the name H hello
Li a Hol Holo Hol
[Music]
Li yeah thank you for the rested chat po
I know I know but you made my ITA bag
thank you you know making an ITA bag
cost a lot of money cuz you got to buy
all of those all of those badges buttons
and stuff so so maybe you know you know
that's why it's sent an
[Laughter]
[Music]
ARS give him a
break okay also thank you for the 20
[Music]
memberships
Hos
Hos okay so uh tomorrow is supposedly no
my day off
um but the offy
performance is going to be live streamed
I
think um as far as I know I think so
right uh on YouTube maybe I don't know
if I get more information I'll tell you
uh but ideally I'm I'm embarrassed uh
don't watch I'm nervous don't
watch don't watch me don't watch me
thanks for the membership
renewal maybe you have to buy a ticket
I'm not
sure uh or is it on Twitch a yeah wasn't
it a twitch
stream so I'm not even really not
streaming I'm kind of streaming because
of that uh but yeah the the meet and
greet for me starts at like 11 p.m. 30
11:30 p.m. or so and then I have a
rehearsal like I don't know somewhere
3:00 a.m. or so and then I realized it
was way worse than I told you last time
the actual the actual performance and I
can't sleep in between because you know
I have to be on standby and there's like
rehearsal in between uh the actual
performance is at 7:00 a.m. for me so
I'll be working from 11:00 p.m.
to until the end of the performance uh
it's not an hour it's not an hour but
let's say 30 45 minutes or so um yeah so
like well roughly 8:00
a.m. the whole night man yeah graveyard
shift for real for real can't you take a
nap well no my plan is I'm going to
up my sleep schedule for this but it's
okay
I um
will
sleep early like maybe yeah I don't know
but my plan is I want to sleep before
the meet and GRE so like from I don't
know 400 p.m.
[Music]
to like 11:00
p.m. that's like 7 hours I
think if I can I need to be tired for
that then then if that works out then
I'll be fine throughout the night
but yeah it's like how do I cuz like
before that uh RBF is probably going to
come over to help me with some more
shelves yeah now the question is is when
am I going to sleep today I'll think
about
that I'll figure it
out
yeah exercise yeah I got to go on the
treadmill anyway get more
stamina I feel like it's taking a long
time for me to to build up this stamina
is this
normal is this
normal I will get sleep don't worry m
one way or another I'll probably be
[Music]
fine good thing is I have you know
blackout curtains is that what you call
them I can make it completely dark so
it's
good it really takes a while
man
yeah fight team please get well soon oh
I'm well it's just uh I have a stressful
schedule cuz let me tell you in Korean
um on Saturday 11 p.m. from uh to Sunday
800 a.m. I will be
working so I am worried about my
schedule about my
sleep H to
[Music]
my time not Korea time Cancel sun no no
no no I think it'll be fine I probably
be tired and sleep after that so I'll
sleep and then I'll do the members watch
along no problem I don't think that'll
be a
problem well for the
[Music]
membership the trick is what was that to
keep running for a few minutes after
you're already tired I I I've been
trying that for sure I've been trying to
push myself for sure yeah yeah yeah
I do that um it's not about it's not
much that much about me being physically
tired it's like my legs are just my
Cales
are absolutely failing
me so I got to uh work on my Cal muscles
so that I can run longer I think it's
because it's always at an upwards
angle that will kill my
CS
easier noodle legs yeah okay come by the
cops yay I think there was no new super
chat right so I think I can
go let me check yeah okay okay
okay no thank you for watching today I
will go now to figure out some things I
have actually I have to do something
that I am a little bit worried about
I have to pick up some letter and if you
have to go to the post office to pick up
a letter that's usually a bad sign I
think I think I know what it
is
um do you want to know one funny thing
what I think it is so uh I sometimes I
just don't open my letters because I
want to live an ignorant life I want to
run away from all my duties it's not
like I don't want to pay it's not like I
can't pay my bills I just don't want to
sometimes and
um I you know before I moved
I I was renting right and I was paying
my rent and then I
noticed I got a letter that said they
are raising my rent right before I left
so they wanted like uh like one or two
or threee more months of the raised rent
but I think I saw it too late and kept
on paying the normal rent but I didn't
get any notification about it again so I
thought okay maybe maybe they're letting
me go maybe they don't mind if I'm
paying the old
rent uh because I never heard anything
like hey girl you paid too little but
then recently I opened a letter that uh
said you owe us several hundreds
several hundreds of euros and I'm like
what is this it didn't even Clearly say
what it is and it came not from the
landlord directly it just came from some
company so that's what it makes even
makes it even more confusing but um it
did say the address of my uh previous
home so yeah I I I put one and one
together and I was like ah wait
oh are they going after me now for that
uh rent increase
a ah but I realized this letter the
deadline on it was a month ago so that
letter must have been laying around for
a while now which then makes me think
that the letter I have to pick up in
person is probably another very serious
reminder that I have to pay this with
some extra fees probably at this
point it's okay I'll pay it this time I
just didn't realize I didn't know I I
felt like it was weird that they were
just letting me go but makes sense okay
okay what are they going to do if I
don't pay well probably they like start
suing me or something I have a lower to
show it too well but like I'm I'm in the
wrong they're in the right I am naun yoa
bad woman m
why would I ask my lawyer they're in the
right anyway it's just kind of weird
because it came late they didn't they
never said anything while I was still
like renting I think I I maybe for three
months I think possibly I paid
the the same amount that I paid before
but that was less than what they wanted
I suppose I don't
know no I will pick up the letter
I'm just a little bit scared the
phrasing and the Frets in these letters
scares me and that's what makes me not
want to open the
letters Minecraft
server we like what Korean people are on
nor I don't know that server never heard
of it but I would love to oh I wonder
does
go Idol does her company like her group
do they have a Minecraft server I want
go to introduce me to other cute girls
from is
Idol I will surround myself with cute
Korean
girls pay so it doesn't get worse I I
I'm planning on it I wasn't really
trying to avoid it it's just uh I didn't
see the letter until yesterday
[Music]
H okay okay wait I think there's a is
that
[Music]
new just run the letter by your lawyer
no no no it's legit it's legit it's
legit I'm pretty sure it the the amount
of it makes sense I
think I should let open my letters no no
I don't want to I hate opening letters
cuz they're always like I want this I
want this it's just not a good feeling
oh Leen come for the pink Super Chat
hello I am Li
Li and it's already been 2 years since
we met and meet in great Korea oh at
that time I prepared a simple German T
Was preparing Korean I look forward to
seeing you again in Korea
and
N no not y y
y he kfp D wait does it
say I am female
kfp I don't
know oh no okay it says
still yeah yeah yeah okay
okay wow thank
you I'm happy that you're still kfp that
is reassuring
you can I help you pay less n why no how
I that's uh it's
legit it's
okay okay I will go now and in German we
say Al Z in I'm stopping you VLC no more
music no
more elevator music stops
[Music]
byebye I feel so accomplished
oh
[Music]
oh it oh you heard
it I thought I was muted
red
[Music]
director I can't redirect to to
Raina Raina hates
me I can redirect to Jed and
but I can't redirect to Raina what the
[Music]
okay going to throw you a curve
ball don't know really what that means
but let's do
[Music]
it you like this one