[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
Christmas
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
warning new background in three two one
okay
hello welcome wow wow that's loud I
guess for sure welcome to the new room
it's it's my room and it's the girls
room I bring the girls over and we do
girls talk here yeah yeah oh this is a
good room to be a girl in right well
actually I say this is the first time
I'm showing it so let's just you know go
down
just look okay so on the left side we
have a girly bed with a croissant
and some some memories on the wall and
the cute calendar and a cute picture
from the friendly reveal a cute window
with cute cards and then a cute
wardrobe with a cute aquarium well like
a caution tape on your aquarium because
the frog has to be in there and cannot
be taken out at any cost unless you mean
with taking out to kill her
um
that would be okay
um yeah yeah and this and that and
there's one of my chicken paintings I
like to paint my
um kfp
remember is uh naked in my pants
thank you thank you oh a cat
um some more stuff makeup tables well
there's even a Tiana figure on top of
the shelf on the right side I don't know
if you guys can see oh yeah and a photo
of yourself or is that Kelly that's me
my painting of uh Cali I drew that in
um but I drew it in passport too
oh the game oh yeah your argument
passport too is so nice
yeah I got proof we're not having been
able to tell
[Music]
me and then we are right now
go down go down oh
I have a question yes oh you have like
two pairs of the same shorts because I
noticed the shorts that you should be
wearing now are on the bed
uh-huh
well we're having a comfortable time
right now so I'm wearing pajama pants
okay okay I get it
this is my thing I mean who here is
wearing really what they should be
wearing underneath that
hmm
that's what I thought
no pans at the kotatsu yes yes otherwise
I don't know it gets so hot down there
your clothes may catch fire
oh yeah yeah oh you don't want any
sweaty legs
[Music]
that's sweaty you can change the
temperature anyway oh but yeah
except pajamas pajama pants are okay
yeah pajama pants are very girly yes so
long as they're not fleas because
getting sweaty in fleece pajamas is the
worst experience or getting out of a hot
shower into fleece pajamas is also a
terrible experience getting sweaty in
lever pants is also not good
does that make it hard to take pants if
it's leather don't you don't have to
like baby powder before you put leather
stuff on I think that's mostly of like
latex that's one of that's real serious
oh what you have to prep to wear pants
you have to prep I think you're like oil
yourself up to slide in a little latex
what
that smells so gross what yeah yeah
think of the reaction you could have two
because there's nowhere for your skin to
breathe these little layer and then
latex
before we get going uh let's introduce
our girl our new girl
who is this girl a girl
I am a real girl
whoa hello hi kafi I'm back yeah um it's
been a week
welcome to your sub Channel everybody
[Music]
hey girl hey girl what makes you a girl
I don't know I feel intimidated all of a
sudden by the other girls here I'm
nervous why am I nervous but that makes
me a girl yeah we have something that
you think makes you very girly girly
no not that I don't know
um
well I can I can say
um the ribbons on your cute twin Tails
make you very girly right now
oh yeah I guess so having twins
no oh I don't know what you call it but
the way your sleeves are that's girly
Ruffles ruffle ruffly yeah roughly yeah
oh
what was I gonna say
I was gonna say something
oh what makes you a girl
nah not dad but anyway
we are having girls
normally it was planned to be like you
know a thing with fauna and then we
would get a guest in but uh fun eyes on
a break and now uh you know Ah that's
what I wanted to say good at oh look has
been
um giving me signs of wanting to be in
girl stuff for a while yeah
yes you are here now and you are taking
uh up almost the position of fauna for
today so hopefully you can bring a lot
of like girliness here
can I just say no offense girl but you
are surprisingly very girly
your face because I took a peek at what
you what we will show later I was like
that's pretty early do you think I
thought I was because I saw you guys are
you guys posted last time I was like
whoa they're still they have so many
products I don't know what I'm doing oh
I I don't I mean I just kind of added
more than I usually yeah but another
thing that also made me realize is I was
with fauna in Japan and we went to a
store and she was like oh girl really
likes this store and it was the girliest
store I've ever been in which store
which one
I don't remember
it was very girly that's good
uh no girl does that remember
what kind of store was it no I do
remember because I remember when I was
hanging out with fun and we started
talking about like boutiques and stuff
and especially in Japan like Liz Lisa
and on cruise etc etc
might have something similar or similar
I know what Liz Lisa says I think it was
similar to that it was a clothing store
doll yes Japanese clothing boutiques
yeah they have so many cute things I
used to wear at least Lisa and ankuru
all the time oh they're so cute
your bags are so cute yo yes 100 but I
feel like if you like this lizard bags I
think you would also really like
Samantha but you know oh my god when we
were in Japan I remember we walked by
and I was like oh my God yeah leave me
here for the next three days yes yes yes
with the hearts with the Ruffles
collection yeah I just bought one of
their bags recently last time I was in
Japan really pretty band yeah
now I don't feel like a girl because I'm
I don't I don't really okay I get it but
also don't get bags and shoes bags and
shoes
no I wear shoes but like I don't get how
people get have so many pairs they're
like this is perfect for this outfit
like when just get over here a parachute
that is white or black and it goes and
it goes with anything okay one moment
could uh how many shoes do you think
roughly you owned
uh
uh count in your brain movement you do
the same
four four
no [\h__\h] way I have four but I need to
get a new pair because my the main shoes
I wear are going apart you at least mean
four pairs of shoes but not not four
single shoes right oh yeah four pairs so
I have two that I mostly wear
a white pair and a black pair
and then I have boots for when it rains
and I have
like um kind of like hiking shoes so
four pair of shoes for the whole year
yes oh my God I like okay
um did you not notice in Japan I wear
the same pair of shoes no I didn't
notice
I mean for traveling I I understand not
bringing like too many shoes with you
you know that's a good point that's a
good idea do you remember the number do
you know
I was counting in my head and I think at
the moment I have only like 10 or so
it seems like I have the most
I think I have like probably
around 30.
[Music]
well I have a shoe case and then I have
some more shoes like stored away that
are like kind of off season right now
that I don't wear anymore
oh my God
I love them
I have five I have a pair I never wear
oh but they're
they're cute counted still
yeah they're the cutest pair of shoes I
have and I never wear them
but what do they look like wait roughly
like stop oh it is
bad at explaining they're like they have
some
shoot I don't know how to explain it
it's like boot but not boot it has a
little heel I don't know how to walk in
heels maybe it has fluff around like the
hot heart it's burnt they're brown
booties booties little cute little short
types are we talking about we're not
talking about Uggs right
no not us
oh my God I want to know yes or no
I still come
I swear ugged yay often no problem with
that in my opinion for like like Middle
School everyone had them so I got them
they're comfy
kind of gross they get dirty like really
fast but you can put your phone in them
if you got the tall ones you could fit
like pens
I only like the really short ones the
short ones are cute and especially the
ones that have like a little ribbon in
the back you know which ones yes those
are cute
but yeah once you get like some rain on
them or so they will stain that's pretty
bad yeah they get gross like I'd have to
walk to school and stuff and like other
people like everyone's eyes just would
get greatly now I think about it yeah
they get dirty and they're hard to clean
yeah the fluff inside gets worn down the
more you wear them and then it just kind
of
yeah it does like it loses the
like comfiness because yeah it just
becomes flat no no and there's no
support I always need a new pair of UGGs
every year I can remember shoes that
were really popular oh the floor but now
I don't know any Brands like toms were
popular
songs yeah
what do they look like their shoes
sneakery types yeah
yeah
oh oh speaking of shoes that used to be
popular you know like maybe
um 10 years ago or so uh some shoes that
I used to love to wear was like
um shoes that basically look like a
sneaker but they have they have some
platform heels
wow I feel like maybe that you you could
still watch somewhere now this but the
type that I had was like I think
nowadays you wouldn't see it anymore
because it wasn't like the same platform
height throughout the whole shoe no like
the heel was higher I used to wear
something like that
yeah platform sneaker
they're not flat it's not flat platform
and the heel was even higher
foreign
I don't know five centimeters I don't
know how high is high I don't even know
I don't know
I say anything above
um
oh that's a good question what's like
what do you guys consider too high of a
heel to wear I don't like I can't walk
and heal so I don't know
I can even dance and heels I'm like so
used to heels I'm not
there's however yeah you say you can't
walk in them but there's certain types
of heels that are way easier to wear
than others like for example pumps
um I can't I can look or Dancing Dolls
unless they have a strap
platform heels are like the the
especially the the chop the club Clubby
chubby what do you call them
chunky chunky ones yeah chunky heels are
I think they look super cute and they're
easy to walk into
kitten heels are cute it's a little tiny
those are like little tiny tiny lift
right
cute
like is it like you'd wear them to work
in an office I've never heard that word
before but okay
but this looks awful wait hold on
this looks like an injury waiting to
happen oh that that's a healing I've
never worn those kind of shoes I wonder
if they're easy to wear
well I'll just I can't really show it I
guess I don't know where you got that
picture from
so I just looked up kitten heels oh oh
yeah look up kitten heels and look for a
red pair that comes up like it I don't
know it looks weird wow wow guys girls
girls that guys yes I need to change my
habit of saying guys I always say that
well
um we have like accelerated a little bit
too fast we need to talk about something
first of all okay sorry we have to hold
back a little bit first things first
[Music]
to see if she's like you know qualified
to be here nice stuff do I qualify as
girly girl
well I mean honestly I wouldn't even say
that this necessarily will give us any
you know not the qualifications or not
qualifications or so but you know you
know it's something I want to talk about
me and vumay and fauna in the last Girls
Talk episode talked in a a very lengthy
we talked about skin care and makeup
routines yeah
so I got gura to as a homework bring
hers as well and show them to us so we
can discuss I have a question for girl
after she shows her makeup I have also
questions please remind me I have a
question what do you want to start with
let's do skincare because I'm more of a
skincare girly than a makeup girl okay
true okay
let's talk about this could you start
maybe from left to right or so
yeah okay so I really I like the tatcha
brand
um really works well for my skin I use
The Dewy the The Dewy that's the cream
on the left it's very thick and good for
like when do you put it on
um
um usually every night but sometimes
just throughout the day if I needed an
arm and it's around I'll put some on
like if you have like a dry spot or dry
zones on your skin it's really good for
that
um and then that's the the the wash in
the middle is like a lightly exfoliating
a little goes a long way as I've learned
uh which is really nice yes
um and it's gentle sometimes I think
it's too gentle but maybe I just like to
be rough with myself oh yes yes uh but
then as you wash it with the middle one
and then on the right is a serum you
wash it and then you sear them and then
you put the moisturizer on afterwards
um is also to plump the skin and keep it
moist and springy so the serum and and
the
cleaning thing you use that every day
yeah unless I'm too tired and I just go
to bed
okay okay I like those products I've
never seen those before but they look
cute I like the purple
they're nice they're really really nice
fancy yeah yeah and then this really
confused me oh Paula Plex I only know
from hair stuff
I got it because because I don't know I
was like well skincare my routine I
usually do hair when I do skin as well
and then this is like oh look like it's
just like uh the golden one is a bonding
oil I think it's called but it's just
good for I think pretty much any hair
type and it just keeps it smooth you put
oil in your hair it's good for you
though if you've ever heard of putting
like Moroccan oils in your hair yeah
yeah other stuff like that
oil for you fish oil fish oil no that
would be stinky
that goes in your mouth
Yeah official it wasn't I've never had
fish oil though like Omega
omega-3 capsules
fish oil in there
though
I give them to my animal too
yummy wait you take fish oil
I used to but now I don't
um is it good for your skin Oh not for
skin I forgot what it does but
oh really it could it could be good
joints
yeah interesting you guys know some
stuff but that's not necessarily girly
yeah sorry no it's okay we can talk
about that too but I I have a question
so I used to try putting products in my
hair like that not that one but ones
like after the shower you know it says
apply on damp hair it always leaves my
hair super greasy
I don't know what my hair type is I
don't feel like your hair type is the
one that gura has from looking at you
girls I think your hair types are
different
[Music]
I don't know yeah it depends it all
depends that's why I think olaplex is I
mean I don't know that's why you maybe
can get samples if you want to try it
but yeah it's
that's the problem with like skin care
and makeup because you never know if
it's gonna work for you and you can't
exactly use it and return it exactly I
have like three different products that
I wanted I tried that made my hair
greasy I don't know what to do with them
exactly
the case of testing and testing and
testing but for olaplex I know at least
that they're they have a really good
reputation from like their dying Pro
hair dyeing product so so I I would
trust the brand at least it's the left
thing a shampoo or what is that oh the
thing on the left is what you use I
think for damp hair it just speeds up
drying and it's good if you want to
style it afterwards is like uh like if
you I don't know if you guys do uh
Blowouts after you shower or like when
you go out volume
I never dry my hair
oh I mean I never used to but then I
started and I'll start trying to do a
good habit
it looks so pretty but it's kind of too
much effort so I don't I don't try it
like that I usually shower at night so
oh but then you go to bed with a wet
header and then your pillows get wet oh
I don't shower before bed like shower
then I stay up for like another hour or
so so
yeah it sucks going to bed with wet hair
yes true true so you put this in there
because you also do it kind of daily
oh not daylight I think I've just gotten
into the habit but mostly when I when I
style the hair then I definitely do the
leave-in but then you also need to do a
heat protectant you always have to use
heat protectant and then another thing
you always have to use is sunscreen
which is the next item I always put on a
daily sunscreen yeah important but I I I
mean do I don't go out much and when I
go out I mean I'm only in summer I put
on some sunscreen
I got a really bad sunburn not too long
ago so I've definitely made sure to do
it every day now oh yeah I think I've
heard about your sunburn oh my God that
was bad I wanted to die oh is it a peel
did you peel it yes I was like a snake
yeah just like peely flaky Crispy
Crunchy yes I left my DNA everywhere
that was my favorite part of having a
really awful sunburn it feels nice to
peel it off doesn't it yeah it's
satisfying well because what I did was I
put on a a long sleeve sweatshirt like a
heat heat tech shirt afterwards it was a
mistake because what heat tech does for
it to work is it captures your body heat
and your sweat and keeps it inside the
shirt to keep you warm but I didn't
realize that I am severely sunburned and
by me putting on a long sleeve it's
going to capture that sweat and then
keep it in my skin so
that sounds disgusting somehow it felt
like I was pulling some fabric off my
skin it was really apparent yeah
you mess with the fabric into your skin
no my skin what is the fiberglasses
not good more careful no no no sunburn
please no more
where are your sunscreen
my last item is yeah me Elizabeth lard
an eight hour and this is good for like
uh if you guys get dry lips in the night
I always put this on my lips like before
bed and just keeps it moist
I think you can use
in multiple places it's kind of got the
consistency of like Vaseline so I've
used it on my hands I've used it on my
lips I've used it on like if I have a
dry spot that's annoying I just put it
on and then I I wake up moist
do you do Lip Cream lip balm or stuff
like that because I don't
um I have something that I rarely use I
actually used it last night but no I
have very bad habits with my lips
internet robot
again you're good again was just for a
moment robot movie oh
it's okay do you mean you'll peel it off
because I always peel it off I wish I
could stop at ASAP yeah I used to have a
really bad lip biting
will I bite them and pull them it was
bad you chew on it
it was pretty bad but what makes you
feel bad now what makes you want to buy
this like I can't relate what makes you
want to bite your lips
oh I just don't I don't think about it
it just has been there it's like
I feel like it happened a lot when I was
in school which is even worse because
it's like in public but I wouldn't
really notice that I was doing it oh I
buy my lips in public wait is that bad
well like okay I don't know how to
explain it was not just like a little
nibble like no no like you know it was
bad like I used to
I don't I don't win
it didn't hurt though it was just gross
I don't know why I did it
yeah I like to chew all the skin off
that comes off I don't know if you
caught me doing it but no it's so you
peel it by biting oh yeah sometimes if I
got an appeal go and then I'll just like
suck on it to make it soft and then I'll
just chew it off what and then no such a
technique I just rip it off discreetly
then if you rip it off it's gonna like
be careful of it I mean these marks and
stuff
but I wouldn't just bite like I'd bite
like the inside of my mouth too
oh it was just it was just nasty on
purpose
no I didn't realize I don't realize when
I did it's kind of like um
I don't know do you ever like shake your
leg or something or when you're sitting
or just stuff you don't do unconsciously
it wasn't on purpose
so now now you don't do it anymore
that's good for you no not really
sometimes yeah can I Still Still peel
peel peel it if it's dry but that's okay
I recently actually talked about this on
my stream uh revealed my bad habits and
a lot of people were like I have this
too I have this too actually like it
felt like 99 of the chat was saying me
too me too so we're all the same seems
like we all have some kind of lip habit
it's okay yummy it's like when you put
real for real usually when I'm trying to
see if chat can relate to something I do
they just go move me that's so weird
[Music]
they do it too they got to no doubt they
do it too
weird
well okay we're done with the skincare
so let's move on to the makeup I'm
curious about makeup because when I'm
when I you know looked at you up close I
never noticed
makeup did I I am not a makeup girly
makeup we were together
sometimes isn't it there's a there's a
name for
it not not natural look but there's I I
know there's a girl a little girl that's
what it is one girl are you a clean girl
no
what clean girl I think is like you
really focus on your skin oh your skin
care so you don't need to wear
Foundation or concealer or anything it
usually like maybe just wear mascara but
then they do something kind of weird
with their eyebrows I don't really they
like that they put they like they make
them really thick and they comb them
with gel to make them yeah
that belongs to clean girls that's the
clean girl thing I think so okay go
ahead and do that but I think her skin
was very clean when I saw it um why
thank you so okay let's look at this
cute little pink
[Laughter]
okay
um so starting on the left that is
mascara it's very nice
it is it's their curl something is it
good for curl because I'm always like a
good mascara like mascara it's like oh
my God there's so much hit and miss yes
I like it
um it depends on what style of eyelash
you look you're like sorry because like
some girls really like the the spider
leggy where it's really clumpy and stuck
together
the more yeah I like the more spread out
version I guess like separating does
that make sense yeah I don't know what
you're talking about I'm like picky with
how my eyelashes look like I'll try and
separate it in a certain way or let you
you apply more what is the technique you
apply more on the edges to elongate or
sometimes yeah I don't know much about
that but uh anyway next product is uh
it's like a tinted lip balm
it's very nice I like natural lip colors
because whenever I put on a lip color
that is too different from my natural
lip color I feel weird like I feel like
it looks wrong so I just like to stick
to really neutral natural colors yeah
and then this is the benefit dandelion
uh highlighter but it's really really I
don't know really neutral color
or more colors yeah it's just one color
it's like a really pretty pearly pink
and you can use it on your cheeks and
your nose or you can use it on your eyes
as well because I don't really like I
don't mess with eyes I can't use
eyeliner I don't know how to use
eyeshadow so I just keep it really maybe
I'll teach you I need to listen because
I can't I'm an eyeliner Pro yo so many
times in my life I've been uh like
appraised for my on fleek eyeliner I did
I remember commenting on it because I
was like your eyeliner is amazing there
you go and that wasn't even like one of
my good days that was one of my
birthdays
like you and crony are really good at it
thank you yeah I've heard that before
yeah yeah
I'm proud I've practiced for so long
with eyeliner
um it is so hard I can't do it and if I
do it on one side I can't replicate it
I go with like the smudge look because I
don't I used to try doing like you know
the more like dark shade or I don't know
what you call it but
yeah I used to try doing that then I
stopped now I don't know how to do it
anymore so now I like goes or I use
eyeshadow sometimes
good
it's not I don't know if it's eyeliner
or if it's just I I don't know
well do you do like the tight lining is
that what it's called I don't know is
that when you like do your your your
waterline yeah no oh no no I don't do
waterline universe that's so scary to me
that's the only thing I can't really do
there I used to do
yeah
this is scary I put that when I first
started learning how to do makeup
it's scary I think I tried before but I
think I did it not with black though but
with white because I was like many many
years ago I was getting like into
Japanese makeup and fashion and all that
and
um yeah not not quite giado at all but
somewhere in that direction and I I
noticed they do like white uh iron oh uh
thingies because they want to make their
eyes even bigger so I tried them
did you use Circle lenses too have any
of you used Circle yes
oh yes
very much like when you say circles do
you just mean contacts that change your
eye color of it no Circle it is our
contact color contact lenses that focus
on the outer circular they give you a
bigger Circle outside it's not much
about the color some have like a little
bit of color too but it's mostly just
because of the Outer Circle it makes it
bigger so those are they're a little bit
more uncomfortable to wear than other
lenses because they're even bigger
I think I have worn these before they
just they weren't that big but they were
bigger than my irises oh they're and
they're not sclera lens there's some
that are crazy they're called skunks
pull your eyelid up to slide them under
um
oh my God that reminds me my one of my
friends
um who also like uses like lenses and
all that she once had one girl behind
like back there yeah and she freaked out
and somehow she managed to get it back
but that was really [\h__\h] dangerous
because you [\h__\h] when that happens
absolutely sorry
[Music]
oh I'm about to trigger you more have
you oh
um have I shown you or talked about a
video where this woman would fall asleep
in her contacts
like just I don't know would wake up and
not think about where they went like she
thought they fell out when she was
sleeping or something and she went to
the eye doctor and they were like behind
like standing to lift your eyelids
20 contacts
my favorite discolored and
how do you fall asleep with a contact
lenses
I've done that before but I've like I
just wake up with really dry eyes and
like Ugh no it's really bad you should
not like the ones that I used to wear
like Circle lenses or whatever you're
not supposed to have them on overnight
but apparently like some lenses you know
that are just for exchange of glasses
some of those you can wear overnight
right I've heard there are I think there
are some but the type I use you you're
not supposed to
so please don't it would be nice though
I always wondered what's it like to wake
up and not be blind oh oh god oh you can
unless you can get your eyes lasers some
people do that a friend yeah you have to
wait until your eyes stop changing and
mine keep changing so
they're supposed to I think you have to
wait until they stop changing for two
years or something
maybe a year interest but
um it is my mom had the same like her
eyes just kept getting worse and worse
and worse and then eventually they
stopped and she like immediately she got
the laser eye surgery okay she had like
the worst Vision you could have I hope
you can get it someday even though it
seems very scary
yeah oops I want it I just want to wake
up I feel like I'd be very motivating to
wake up and like be able to see yeah you
know no no lying down watching TV you
don't have to adjust your stupid glasses
well I know an amusement park and
wearing the 3D goggles without having to
adjust your gloves I don't
yes yes
oh gosh I once I went to get my hair
done and I was wearing glasses I was
like why'd I do this why didn't I wear
my contacts today because I couldn't see
anything that she was doing I'll do it
like I gotta take them off
I had to hope for the best I could like
I could not see
um
but never again
okay um I could like go on and on about
lenses and problems with lenses but
let's continue with the lineup here
makeup oh okay it's almost done don't
worry yeah
the 2B next to the dandelion puff is
that's concealer because everybody has
those days
um yeah
my day I only use concealer where is the
liquid foundation you don't use liquid
foundation
girl without the eyes
plus I just really need like concealer I
guess oh my God
that's amazing I mean if you cover
enough of like stuff
uh then you don't need yeah
no because you don't need something like
oh you don't need it everywhere I don't
think but when I've noticed when I try
to be like okay today I'm not gonna do
full makeup I'm just gonna do concealer
on the spots that don't look good then I
start out and I notice that if I don't
put on the foundation then there will be
an obvious difference of where I put on
makeup and why I didn't so that's where
is it all in your head no no no it's
visible it's visible this is it the
right color is it the right color match
for you yeah but then again you know I
have like a million colors on my face I
feel like yeah yeah I feel like some
people have just more redness in their
face so that's why it can show a very
red face for some people
you could use a have you guys tried
using like the color correcting like
greens cancel right yes
it doesn't work for me I did try
sometimes it makes I I guess that's
maybe like a product issue like a bad
products good products but for me it
made it stand out a bit more whatever I
wanted to cover back in the day but yeah
have you heard it was a new technique
for that the new trend is people are
covering their entire face in like white
white uh makeup paint and then they're
doing their everyday makeup routines
because it's essentially starting on a
completely blank canvas and then
apparently it works on every skin tone
they say yes the product that is insane
it looks crazy but then you think about
it it's like I think okay I think I've
seen that in like Asian makeup videos
there's actually this one like this
one Trend I guess that I've seen and I
always use that so their face always is
like white in the beginning but then it
looks natural by the end they're not
natural but it looks like like their
skin
those makeup videos uh mostly like they
come from uh like Asia where they pull
out [\h__\h] out of their nose
that's what I'm talking about it's in
the same video
those are crazy man they shape their
nose and they've also put tape around
their face to change their face
it's crazy
watching those is very interesting
because like damn what you can do with
makeup is is incredible that's like like
makeup artist level stuff right the
skills
completely different persons I think
they use the product you're talking
about though I feel like that's the
first thing they do the white paint
yeah oh they just use very very bright
makeup because like baby they do that
first and then they put a different
foundation on
um
I don't know well that might have also
just been like you know the steps from
the BB cream and then Foundation a BB
cream BB cream CC cream yeah yeah so
someone wants right it's crazy because
it didn't always it wasn't always a
thing I can't ask my question anymore my
question was gonna be do you put
concealer on first or foundation on
first but you don't use Foundation no
concealer
but I mean it makes sense because if I
if I try to think back you know here we
have studio lights in OBS and all that
so you can't see clothes I think gouda
had very like you know the pigments of
her skin they seemed all like very like
you know how to describe
why thank you right no blotches is that
don't worry I don't know yeah I didn't
know this blotches or redness I mean
maybe there's a little bit of redness
but like not probably not me with my
like Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer
knows ma'am
that's nonsense I've seen you without
makeup you know you know I I I used to
what are you talking about I used to
always feel like so like I could not
never in front of my friends or or
colleagues or so I could never show
myself about makeup but recently maybe
because I lost all the [\h__\h] uh that I
had or other reasons but I felt very
pretty comfortable around you girls
much
um
plus so we got together we were gonna do
a bunch of stuff anyway and makeup would
just I don't know wouldn't that make
your skin feel like it couldn't breathe
um
yeah no not too bad but I'm just too
lazy to do my makeup these days yes yes
and your blush is your blush good I
actually I don't use blush I'm surprised
you use blush
I don't use blush all the time but
sometimes I also use it on my eyes
because I'm lazy and I don't know really
uh so like you can like take a big blush
brush and you just like dot the outer
corners of your eyes your cheek over
your nose on the tip if you want that
body chin but yeah it's a really pretty
pale pink it's cute okay
what is this
and then that is cat's Wing by Tony moly
clear compact that stuff is really good
I really like that stuff what is it you
use a compact powder without a
foundation yeah interesting what's
compact powder um
what this does is like pores like your
pore sizes it blurs pores uh and it just
kind of evens out if I have any redness
I'll just like dust it lightly I don't
want to pack it I've seen people pack it
in and that it can look like flaky and
chunky if you do that it's delicious
really lightly if you want to blur
um you can blur pores
wait
where what is this what's it called cat
swing compact powder well basically it's
just like powder you know I I use that
too I feel like you can't finish your
makeup I feel like we had this talk last
time maybe maybe it was with fauna or
someone no no no I remember this yes you
were surprised that I didn't wasn't it
like a finishing powder that's why you
didn't know what this is either
I actually have some now I do have some
friends
the last time I wear makeup was when I
was in Japan ah
so now you thought after that last girl
suck episode oh I gotta get myself some
powder
yeah because it it makes your makeup
stay longer right exactly yeah
have you tested it out have you seen the
difference
no I got six so I didn't wear makeup you
haven't tested it okay but when you test
it I think you will notice a difference
because then you can also you don't have
to be so careful when touching your face
and all that it will stay pretty much
do you apply it with a brush or a puffy
thingy or
um really whatever I have on hand
sometimes because it comes with a sponge
but the sponge can be kind of too
intense so yeah with like a fluffy
Brushy then I'll do that
well I guess you're setting the the
concealer at least
with that yeah under the eyes and stuff
next time I meet you I gotta look closer
at your face oh please
I didn't really wear I don't really wear
I mean I don't really
I don't wear much no well you know what
you know what if we if we meet again
let's do like a one one day when if we
go to dinner or so let's be like okay
tonight we we're gonna be pretty for
ourselves so we make ourselves pretty
please help me I think that's probably
why I also don't wear much makeup
because I'm scared it's gonna look bad
and I'm I'm not gonna know it looks bad
hair too I'm really bad with hairstyles
you know right away because it's your no
no
I'm bad I'm really really really bad at
hair I struggle to put my ponytail up
a ponytail what ponytail height do you
like I want to play with your hair I'll
help
[Music]
you still have it really high because
that's the only way I knew how to do it
but when I try to do different ones like
it's either like it's it's too much to
one side or it's bumpy I don't like how
my hair in the front looks I just don't
know what to do I don't know how well
yeah I can't what else I don't know I
can't use Clips like I bought a clip or
no they like they had to put the clip in
my hair because I was like I don't know
what to do
oh it's cute how lost you are but
boy I feel like
a ponytail damn that yeah
I know look I can do it it just looks
bad like there's bombs I don't know like
do I just have a bumpy
heads
I think with you maybe maybe the step
that you're missing is like you you you
take your hair right and you kind of
hold it up right and then and then if
you just put put all the hair together
with your hand yes it will come out
bumpy in some spots you have to have
your brush in the other hand and hold
the hair on the other hand and with the
brush carefully you brush everything
towards where you're holding the the
ponytail and then before it all gets
loose again then you tie it up get it
I try that
I try I usually that helps but then I I
don't know there's always something
wrong with it okay you too next time we
meet I will I will observe and we will
observe a little chocolate
I'll fix it I think there's like a what
ponytail looks best for your face shape
kind of thing uh like one trick that
maybe maybe you could try it if you want
that I've learned works really well with
me is that I follow when I wanna do a
ponytail you look at your chin and then
your ear and you follow that line and
that's the general height of the
ponytail that
um
it really works when I try it because I
just have the same problem like I don't
know I don't know how to do a ponytail
but when I started following the my yeah
chin Airline I was like oh that kind of
works better
I guess
something I don't
something I don't get is like for little
ponytails like your hair kind of stays
parted at the top right because it's low
oh what that was weird
if you have pieces that like frame the
face I feel like that helps if it looks
weird yeah like little bangs and side
bangs and and stuff like that
um
yeah when I do a ponytail also I leave
out like some front uh framing hair
pieces yeah yeah
like animal girls I also really like
pineapple hairstyles you guys do that
you mean a really really really really
really high ponytail
uh no uh would I you take a clippy and
then you take your hair and you twist it
and then you pull it up and you pinch it
and then the top parts of your hair kind
of spread out you do that yeah
I never do that but I wanna do I wanna
do that but I don't know if it looks
good on me I'm sure it will it feels to
me it feels like such a at home doing uh
my skincare routine kind of hair thingy
like just too it's cute because it's
easy to do right
yeah
but for me it feels like like a home
thing but some girls can make it work
outside I just don't understand how
how it can look like something I could
wear outside and add like two private
intimate
the internet
kind of this hairstyle bathroom
that'd be like the messy bun like that I
just woke up but that's what I would I
would I don't wear the the I don't ever
wear a bun out I don't know I feel like
the pineapple hair is but buns buns are
really pretty fun well even but you say
them and love to do a messy hair bun but
my messy hair buns never look like the
cute messy hair buns from the cute girl
it was just like oh oh dear yeah I think
when you don't care about what it looks
like and you just do it you know then
then you're one of the cute cool girls
who can do a good messy uh hair bun
without caring and how it works it just
works you just you just don't have to
care
lucky that's why the pineapple works
because it looks it looks good
I'm looking up all the hairstyles this
one is serangoon what not to do and what
to do I don't know how to do it I I only
know how to do this one on the left ah
which looks stupid
I get it it looks stupid on me
so much effort goes into the one on the
right that's the other thing girls did
it looks like oh it's effortless but no
it's not I don't get it
it's okay buns I also have issues with I
feel like it's not as easy as the as
girls like to make it out to be known
it's not that easy
no no as long as you're comfortable
um well we're done with the skin and the
makeup thank you for sharing uh I think
I can indeed confirm you are a girl
relations
yay okay
good I actually brought some topics that
she wanted to discuss so please
um I I give you these fashion trends
fashion what exactly did you want to
discuss about recent fashion dress
we discussed already a little bit in our
Discord group and I am already
confidence
this is some research yeah recent
fashion trends that are why what that
you like that you don't like or that
generally confuse you like the
the one we talked about la la versus
okay okay okay girls what the heck is
that guys do you know what that is a
girl or boy and okay okay girl a boy any
ideas
if you Google it you will not be able to
tell the difference
I I would actually I don't give a [\h__\h]
so I'm showing one of the pictures don't
worry no no faces the last one I'm gonna
show on our screen
here this is from okay okay okay okay
let's read okay okay okay okay a girl
likes to apparently keep to herself is
more a tomboy than girly chilled likes
to be alone introverted quiet good
listener things have had logical and is
more mature well the la la la la girl is
more extroverted girly live soon press
talkative things with her heart acts
before thinking less mature off with the
fairies and his flurries what does that
mean off of the fairies
or she's like um
like she's like oh I'm gonna go into the
forest and be a fairy is that what
happened she's going off with the
fairies I'm going to go to the forest
and spin around
honestly this seems like the the girls
that came up with this I feel like are
mostly la la girls
uh also under the age of 15. if he goes
into the comments yeah no if you go to
the comment sections like because I did
research on Tick Tock it's just I am
both I'm totally both
I mean I'm not I'm not one of these I
can't say I'm one of these Abraham okay
luck okay okay it's like maybe you're
both because these are very common
traits and people can like flip-flop
very general you could be okay okay one
day and la la la the next day but I love
the the boy one okay okay okay the first
thing is gamer
[Laughter]
um one of these ones gamer the funny one
dad of the group good advice giver
reasonable is going loyal has many
friends but a small Inner Circle okay
cares for his family and lalala boys our
dreamy make stupid jokes is the friend
that gets bullied oh loved by many
popular a friend that gets bullet but is
also popular sporty
388 needs the advice what does that
means
eight eight three eight is that like
this is that kid gamer what is this what
is three three eight eight
needs
[Music]
it doesn't bookmark number
yeah
that's my word that only guys know or so
who knows I thought it was like slang
for something yeah
okay okay never mind that scratch that
they just they're those that need the
advice they don't give it
okay okay so yeah well so of course
probably most people are both oh you
should have seen the comments for this
one it was like I need oh actually no
the caption or something everyone's
caption say hold on I'll read it oh it
was like the comments they're all like I
need a okay okay yeah
and I need an okay okay okay boy so this
is just their current Trend with yeah 15
year olds
um
it's like the astronomy people like the
I'm an Anna Capricorn rising sun that's
exactly what I what I started thinking
yeah
so if you are one of those but
um those if you like astronomy like that
but
I don't know it's kind of crazy
it's interesting what some of it or some
people go like maybe a little bit too
deep into it or rely a little bit too
much on it but then the other day I was
watching like a YouTube video and this
girl like looks at someone uh several
people and first try guesses their
zodiac thingy just because of their
first vibe that they give off on the
first words they say nobody yeah
and I was like well wow I mean I don't
believe in this stuff but good job girl
is it was it a YouTube video yes
scripted edited no no it's great
no don't you believe oh yeah you're not
a believer
I don't believe either but that was cool
like I mean you know
oh [\h__\h] I'm being judged I like how some
people would be like I can't be your
friend because you're a la la girl and I
just don't Vibe with that
I don't think so but I feel like
generally the image I feel like that
when I said that I think a lot a lot of
girls came up with that I feel like this
is like a little bit like low-key very
low-key hidden message a little bit
roasting okay okay okay girls don't you
think
like tomboy I don't know I mean some of
these I feel like they're trying to make
the Lilac girls look better here do you
want me to show you pictures like can I
show you other things I found that
we're like oh my God girls girls
I probably can't show it on the stream
but sure no you can't but you know
you guys are cute but I'm still like
saying it feels like the lava girls are
dumping dunking on the picture bumping
and dunking make sure the desktop audio
is off
here's a screenshot too oh pictures
what is it
I forgot that I thought music was a
thing when I played this
okay okay okay
[Music]
was reading a book and it's chilling
um
I see
what this is like before and after an
iced coffee this could be the same
person
yeah so that's why the comments say
um hold on the comments say
I can do both my two personalities it's
me like me
[Laughter]
I'm adding weird Tick Tock fashion
trends because we're talking more about
like also yeah thank you Mommy for being
our Tick Tock yeah all right
Google Google couldn't help me with that
one so I I went to tick tock I am not
gonna sacrifice my sanity uh to add
another social media to my social media
list and go on Tick Tock no don't don't
don't use tick tock it's stupid
it's a waste of everything something
something some I I saw this like said or
written somewhere just like yesterday or
so that like the YouTube shorts like so
many tick tocks get uploaded re-uploaded
on YouTube shorts and honestly like
YouTube shorts are like a filtered
version of tick tock like you get some
of the good stuff you get way less [\h__\h]
than if you were scrolling through Tick
Tock you know what I mean I think so but
here's the thing I used to
so the other questions do you guys use
Instagram like you yeah through
Instagram because Instagram also kind of
has something like
um
no
I think yeah sorry I mean Instagram
stories just no I think Instagram has
something that's like
anyways my point is
that's it
there are people that will be like Tick
Tock sucks he shouldn't go on Tick Tock
but then they'll go on like Instagram or
Facebook or Twitter is fine fine like
something back from Tick Tock that's
uploaded there but the tick tock is like
three months old so if someone tries to
say anything yeah you sent me a meme
like look at this but I've seen it on
Tick Tock three months ago yeah
you get all this stuff earlier if you're
on Tick Tock that is true
so late
it is a bunch of garbage ew Tick Tock
stinky smelly you said something funny
like look at this by the way yeah
sometimes you find a good meme or
something funny and you just really wish
the algorithm will keep showing you the
funny memes the things you like but it
doesn't sometimes you get a real juicy
algorithm though after like three
refreshes you're like oh finally oh I
found
experience after all no no Instagram
yeah Instagram reels the algorithm you
gotta refresh a few times but then
sometimes you find the funny ones you're
like oh thank God
think Instagram algorithm is pretty good
because like I I try to stay away from
that like success suggestion page but oh
my God it shows me like the prettiest
like hairdresser hair salon pictures and
every time I look I'm like oh I want to
do this hair color I want to do this oh
my God this hairstyle oh my God
like the alcohol problem is pretty good
no was there any other weird Tick Tock
fashion trends
besides this new okay okay
I forgot I didn't do my research
um I think that was the one that stood
out to me the most that was just what
something I noticed before
it seems like Y2K Fashions kind of
coming back I love white I think maybe
that's maybe maybe new jeans has an
influence in that I love what new jeans
K-pop group super popular right now
rising stars and they do they're the
whole theme of the group is like Y2K
yeah and they read their songs and their
fashion and everything yeah they're so
cute I don't know anyone
down
[Music]
yeah
they did oh my oh my God
you're my high boy that one too same
cookie
[Music]
I didn't know when to stop
but you know you know something that
makes me
sad I don't know what it makes me feel
but when I you know was in school in
middle school there was like certain
types of fashion and I did not like it
like I wasn't comfortable with it I just
wanted to wear baggy clothes oh but I
think then like type stuff like tights
and shorts and stuff
we're what was popular but I just wanted
to wear baggy pants and baggy shirts but
now that's what's popular in schools
apparently oh yeah like big baggy cars
oversized yeah yeah the cargo pants yes
kind of get it I mean I feel like the
things in Austria were different
probably than what you experienced but
yeah that's a good point like like
things that I would wear
um
probably I would still get weird looks
partially today but maybe there they
would be more accepting a little bit
even in America I think it's probably
like different fashion trends and stuff
like I could show you guys later what
people at my school wore but I don't
think it's what people I don't know in
like other places like I don't know I
remember
arcs arms leggings
pink pink leggings right Victoria's
Secret pink with the fold over tops
yes and then some girls would wear the
uh you'd either wear it North Face on
top
like lots of layers or like Hollister or
abercrombies or something like that oh
my there's one fashion trend
uh that I feel like in the past
five to eight years has become like a
big big thing that I cannot get behind
and I know it's so popular that this uh
maybe within our Circle right now I will
get a good reaction but overall maybe
not it's um I can't get behind wearing
leggings as pants
just leggings
that's what was the fashionable but and
the outline of your panties and I I
don't know every outline no no no no no
no I'm sorry no no
you see this is why I loved oversized
things
yes
like leggings and leggings that's what
people wore so I would wear an oversized
sweatshirt like every day I
but I was like one of the like people
usually wouldn't cover it yeah no yeah
did you have to have some girls they
would they would like wear uh like
string underwear and they would make
sure you could see it they would pull
the string up above the
legging line yeah like the waist line
yeah we had a dress code we couldn't do
that you know once I got dress coded
because there was a small rip in my
jeans above my knee you got dressed
up about just a little rip you could see
my skin above my knee but you know what
stupid is that you could wear shorts
that were shorter than where the wrist
was well yeah you have to be dressed
prop I guess
your clothes look look broken then they
don't understand it says the fashion
thing they shouldn't matter it was
really annoying but you know about
leggings just the other day I was like I
went hiking and I um I was gonna wear
something you know for hiking okay and I
think when you do Sports then okay
leggings
even though I I still feel embarrassed
about them I I would say they fit into
the category if you wear them for sports
but so I wanted to wear something
fitting for hiking and my I have like a
pair of leggings that is connected with
shorts and that that wasn't that wasn't
clean so I couldn't wear that but then I
had another pair of leggings and I was
like okay I guess I'll wear this for the
first time in my life now and I put it
on and I see like it's so embarrassing
so I tried to find clothes that are
longer than my butt um to combine it
with uh tried so hard and then you know
I ended up wearing like a pretty long
jacket because
you need to find a good pair of leggings
for like working out like a really thick
pair you mean I don't know I have a pair
that's like I I what is it like they're
running leggings or something so like
they're very breathable
but you can't see anything
like you don't but I've had leggings
where you can but they were cheaper I
think so you have to put in I think an
extra Buck
um
I still wear long like long stuff over
it yeah and you can wear shorts on top
if you want that's that's okay you know
um actually just just the other day I
watched a YouTube video where um you
know this is this this person is
interviewing people on the street in
Japan and they're like hey you know
about this fashion trend overseas like
in America and so on that everybody
likes to wear leggings and all these
Japanese people that are being
interviewed mostly girls they're all
like yeah yeah I mean I see it sometimes
on tourists in in Japan
um but like I could never do this like
every single Japanese girl is like I
could never do his leggings wearing it
underneath something yes but this will
never be popular in Japan because no we
don't want to like you see everything
they even said that oh when they see
tourists who wear that on the street in
Tokyo and so on they don't mind you know
they look good in it but for them they
would never they couldn't it's like a
cultural thing
about it in Japan
[Music]
doesn't they don't like showing uh like
chest either right like cover your like
the shoulder and the shoulders
yeah I don't know how they do it though
because when summer gets so hot like
damn how can you still cover up your
shoulders it's so hot
you know it's like with the legging
thing I you ever see people that are
like skin colored like oh my God yes
that's amazing
is this public indecency grade are you
just wearing leggings getting pretty
close to that yeah
I I don't understand that
yeah wait I wanna I wanna get your
opinion on this too oh this is a fashion
trend that I can't get behind I think
this is starting to
catch I feel like it's rather recent but
I'm not entirely sure I might be a
little behind
ballerina Flats wait oh your problem is
not wearing ballerinas with socks but
just ballerina this is everything in
general but also ballerina floods in
general I
if you are not a ballerina like if you
wear them yeah
I normally walk around in
I don't know and there's a bummer
because I like am I saying this right I
like Mew Mew but I don't the shoe it's
just I just I mean I think ballerinas on
their own are fine but with socks
obviously that's like a socks like that
no no no
I don't think
[Music]
I'm feeling
I mean I don't I don't even own a pair
of ballerinas actually but back in the
day I used to wear them sometimes oh
it's just I thought they were actual
ballerina shoes is there a type of shoe
that's based on ballerina yeah it's just
like flat shoes like these they're
called ballerinas you just slip in they
scream band recital in fifth grade
ballerina flood so we hit the flats out
we can blast on this clarinet no
right clothes thank can look really cute
no I'll take
instead wait what are your thoughts on
these
[Music]
why can't I have this picture no wait
no
questions
and what if I was going to no no
yes big yes yes
ah and I've seen it
I I have shoes like that
Mary Jane's pass
call them Mary Janes
yeah oh ballet flats wait pass not pass
pass is in like past they pass the test
they pass they pass okay ballerina
floods get a fail for me yeah I'm
[\h__\h] cute especially I mean with with
like underneath white socks that end
under the knee or like cute black ties
or whatever I don't know many
combinations
[Music]
I wear sneakers what kind of sneakers
let me see if I can find them I love
sneakers they're really dirty and
they're falling apart if it if I step in
a puddle they'll get on my songs like
it'll like go into my shoe be careful
you could get a foot fungus
um
a good thing I don't walk in puddles
because of the foot fungus
[Music]
um
but sneakers are so cute
oh no those are cute yeah you can wear
that with like almost everything too
yeah exactly
there plus if you're bored with this one
you could like draw on them or you can
like paint them
oh my God like when I was in school I
think
popular to start like on the internet at
least it was popular people were like uh
drawing on White Blank Converse shoes
and making like the sickest shoes ever
so cool
really
[Music]
it's perfect should we cook cameras and
yeah yeah
sometimes I wanted to do that too but I
never got to do it um
okay
girls girls girls
uh I have a question for you
okay
what are those what is this
I will show you certain items that
apparently will be familiar to girls but
you know there was like a list you know
and most of them I understood but some
of them even I was unsure and those are
the ones I'm bringing here to ask you
guys girls what you think is it and also
the chat feel free to guess what I am
showing you no cheating chat no kidding
yeah
no no no but um before saying anything
just say if you know what it is or not
if you don't know okay okay
what is this
I think I know I'm not sure I just want
to confirm with you girls I think I know
hmm
oh interesting I think I know okay
um
is like a phone case Okay
the dimensions are maybe confusing yeah
yeah like how big is it is this a piece
of paper like I think it's pretty small
with a sticker I think it is it's
probably like you're supposed to put it
on your nails and then yeah
but what the heck are the ones that are
fully wait it's sponges nail sponge you
put that down as the stencil and then
you dip the the solid colored ones in
your polish and then you roll it
possibly
what maybe real maybe not
see it
I think I know what you're talking about
they I think they use that for like
gradient stuff
oh
yeah yeah yeah
wait
I think I can get the solution
[Music]
Tic Tacs so okay I think I think it's
sometimes leave Nails it is it is nail
vinyls vinyls vinyls
Nails vinyls vinyls
[Music]
it's weird I don't ever see this I mean
I guess you cut it like around what huh
you put it on your nail and then you
fold it where the end of your nail is
and you file it off
oh that's that's how I used to do it you
used this before
before yeah oh good I know so many girls
names now they're fun do you guys like
nails
um I you like looking at pretty nails
but I never do them I I don't I want
pretty nails okay well you had matching
nails with crown Souls
we got our nails done but um did I okay
so when I returned home I needed to get
them removed right how did you do it
I went to a nail place oh well it took
them over two hours to remove them
they were like what on Earth is this
what did you do
yeah and you know they said from now on
we're going to ask clients when they
need to remove gel nails if they got
them in Japan because what what on Earth
yeah because then they don't come off
when you get your hands wet Japan
the charms were just completely stuck
they had they were like trying to file
them they were
so bad and so painful
oh they were just
yeah because it was Winter all right we
were on theme with the season
I got my nails so after that I got gel
nails again and they were just a flat
color but then I got sick so I didn't
like and I have the cough and I don't
like going places with a cough and so I
couldn't go to get them changed or
removed I was like I need to get you
know I want to get them off so I got
like a home kit to do it it did not work
it just made them look awful so trying
to like peel them off and then I tried
another way did not work tried it just
ended up soaking my fingers in acetone
and it kind of worked but I still have a
little bit left on some of my nails it
looks so bad but I'm just waiting until
it grows to the point where I can just
cut it cut it off
I see but that was like your you know
kind of first uh experience with nails
manicures before and I used to try doing
nail art but it was the normal nail
polish after two days yeah me too I mean
okay I played around a little bit with
nail polish but that's it
on acrylics
I remember your nails looked pretty when
I saw them they weren't like you know
they didn't have a million things on
them but they looked pretty
I like them I like I usually get the The
Lazy one I used to I used to I like got
like a big bag of assorted nail sizes uh
uh yeah you like glue them on yourself
but you have to like shape them and file
them down yourself it's a process I
don't do it anymore but I used to
because then you control the the size
and the shape of going like oh coffins
or squares or whatever they're called
almonds and you paint them uh yeah I
like pop on ones I think that's what I
was wearing when I went uh but don't you
ever lose your nails with those
yes
you can use that to pick your nose then
so it's good to put in bed
I am
had I I got those before I don't know if
they're acrylic what they were made of I
got ones where you glue them on right
and press and then shape them and I was
so dumb I did it before I needed to
write an essay oh no
what have I done this is right it feels
so weird so I'm useless yeah yeah
I will like I forgot about my essay
started looking at videos like how do
people do things with nails how do
people type with nails and I saw like
videos and they typed so freaking slowly
what you can't use glass to kiss that
goodbye
all right like look how they do I love
how they do dishes
are their shoes and stuff like people
with really long how to use the toilet
[Music]
yeah oh my God yeah that I I I I I put
on fake nails like glue on ones for the
first time like last year once and I was
so lost I put it on and it's like it
felt to me like how a doggle feels when
you put socks on him and he's like
[Laughter]
I didn't have the the thing to take off
the nails so then I was like even more
in trouble just like your moon man yeah
I had what guys so
probably after a week I guess the glue
kind of loosens up like probably when
you shower and wash your hair and stuff
so when you wash your hair like my hair
will sometimes get stuck under a really
small part of the nail
it feels so bad
[Music]
oh my God oh my God if you brush your
hair like it is your hair will get stuck
yeah give me this little opening
oh it hurts but then there's the fear if
you get water stuck underneath because
you could get an infection or a fungus
or something really bad if you squeeze
the top and you hear it going like
because there's water stuck under the
nails you gotta pull it off yeah
falling off eventually like on their own
oh my gosh it'd be so painful or they
get stuck on like I don't know it was
painful
ah so now you know Council got like
matching Nails
I feel worried about oh you know getting
nails but do you want to do it sometimes
okay yes yes I knew I knew you would say
yes
every time
[Music]
I don't need your nails
just for the sake of doing it once
and then I'll take him off
we all go get nails
right now let's go oh oh
okay girls girls pay attention next item
please inspect and first say only if you
know it or not
oh okay
not a sponge it I'm getting so it seems
like a file yeah but like I've seen nail
files and this doesn't look like a
normal nail file I know what it is of
course you do it's nail related huh no
you're wrong
is it for the foot for the soul of the
foot
what does movement know what it is
is it for the soul of the foot it's a
pumish stone
[Music]
I haven't used that in a long time I
kind of have the urge to chew on it
though yeah
it looks crunchy and cold like
um but I've seen this before in the
shape of a brush with like a brush
handle those are I think more easy to
use probably with a Ped Egg parmesan
cheese collector yeah
huh what you wanted to say something
did I I feel like you wanted to say
something no okay I feel like I did too
but I don't remember so okay okay well
that one wasn't so difficult I knew it
was something to file something but I
thought it was for nails I guess
we looked brutal though okay
yeah
okay next thing this one maybe will
raise more questions
for me at least are they double ring
fingers
rings for two
two fingers and like this is stuck
together I think I've seen it before but
I don't remember
we always know what is it let's move
anything
I I don't think it's a ring thing
anymore
yeah I think it's much smaller
earrings smaller
ah oh what earring is for the back of
your earring isn't it or like Am I Wrong
um
[Music]
are your ears pierced mine or not
I'm wearing clip-ons right now I try to
get some pierced but I couldn't like it
was so hard to get them out I couldn't
get them out and I like went nowhere you
know what happened I went to where I got
them they got the piercing because like
you know they give you yeah
keep in yeah for like a month yes and I
could it was over a month and I couldn't
I couldn't I was freaking out I cannot
pull this I'm not strong enough so I
went to where I got them done and they
said oh we we can't take them out we're
not we're not qualified to take them out
like you have to go to a doctor if you
want to take them out oh is this like a
once in a 9 000 years get together of
three girls who don't have ear holes
yeah well I got them out eventually but
they closed up I just think they're
closed now so they're no longer pierced
what
we told like the same [\h__\h] happened to
me for me the crazy thing was like my
whole like Teenage Hood I never had
pierced ears um I don't know I just
never got it as a child and then the
older I got the more I was like I don't
need it and I'm scared of it and blah
blah blah and then and then
um
sometime in the past
three four years three years I actually
I had like the spontaneous feeling that
I needed them I wanted them I wanted to
finally be a girl so I went to Claire's
because classes
spontaneously do it and then not feel I
mean I felt like a little girl when I
went and I was like isn't this normally
where little girls do it and she was
like yeah
but you can have adults too you know
um
they have some cute things you know they
always have like something where you can
like buy free get one free or so yeah
yeah but anyway so I did it right
finally and I'm like yeah yeah I did it
and she gives me this uh ring earring
that I have to keep in for a month she
says and I thought okay you know what I
don't I don't feel like I necessarily
need to take it out right away after the
mom so I kept it in for like three
months or so and then then came a day
where I went to the dentist and they had
me take it off for like a scan thingy
and I was like no problem and then okay
I had some problems taking it out it was
a little bit difficult but I got it out
okay that's not the problem I got it out
and I took the the thing the appointment
and then later like a week later or so I
I checked to put the earring or whatever
back in again and it's already closed
did you push it through
of course it was like it was fruit of
course fully fruit it was it was a hole
and I kept it longer in even longer than
recommended and I take it out for one
week and it's closed again and since
then I only do it again because I'm like
[\h__\h] this I'm not gonna do this all the
time
sometimes force it through after it
closes because sometimes skin it's just
like build up like it's stuck in it felt
really closed yeah that's how I felt too
because
eventually got them out but I realized I
probably could get an earring in there
but I don't think I had the right type
of earring for like newly pierced ears
because the ones that they give me which
break after you take them out you take
my brain back in as long as I got would
break after like you're not supposed to
put it back because they use different
earrings but
yeah I also just
um one of my ears are kind of weird yeah
I think I want to but I think I I told
fauna about it and she said that you
should really keep them in for longer
and like you basically need to wear
earrings for six months yeah I think
what you said
[Music]
do you not have holes right now in your
ears or do you just wear I tried it but
um blue I get I'm sorry barfi thinking
about it because oh
because I had to I had issues they had
them sorry I had them
and then also around the same time I was
like okay it's time to take them out
um I kept I fainted I couldn't I
couldn't like wow and then there's just
no more no more
can't do it um
you girls have no idea how like crazy
this is to me I I I I rarely ever meet a
girl who doesn't or woman who doesn't
have ear holes and then now there's like
two next to me what the [\h__\h] the reason
the reason I got them was because I had
a family member who kept buying me
earrings over the years I was like and I
told like multiple times told her my
ears aren't pierced but it's like she
assumed eventually I would get them
pierced so okay fine fine but yeah
that's the thing like I at some point I
was like what the what the hell I don't
need holes because especially in Japan
there is a huge selection of pretty nice
elegant uh clip-ons I feel like in
Austria if I would look here clip-ons
are only in the children's section and
like the most children like things but
in Japan even for like adults there's a
huge selection and and I think that's
because like a lot of Japanese girls
also don't Pierce their ears and
earrings are so pretty yeah they add so
much to your face no the clip ones that
I
I'm familiar with I always assume
they're like kind of big and bulky like
you can't you can't get dangly earrings
that are clip-ons
no there's not only bulky ones there's
like you know simple ones yeah why did I
get my ear oh wait because like right
here but you can change that you can
change the thing you can change it from
an earring if you want to if you give
you a bit of crafty and you feel like I
want to wear it with a candle yeah you
can change it
but I do think like Clips hurt a little
bit but yeah that's yeah I remember
right where my grandma's once and
if I felt like such an adult
but then when I took them off I realized
how perfect they were really bad for my
ears
pain
there are magnetic ones I guess they
probably would hurt less
magnetic earrings I don't know if I
trust it I feel like they'll fall have
you seen the magnetic eyelashes I'm
sorry yes magnetic eyelashes
they make magnetic eyelashes to the top
and bottom of you imagine Like A Lash
glue mermaid and now this lash glue has
like something magnetic in it so you put
it around like an eyeliner you put it
around your eye line and then you just
stick on the lashes and they will just
chill on there it's really really cool
but I've never tried it
what is the thing huh
it's magnetic I haven't heard of this
that's how Derpy this this girl looks
yes they do sometimes look up a Derpy no
no it's just because of the because she
did it before and after yeah
yeah well of course
but sometimes I I do think they look
good
I'm a little bit Derby sometimes but
generally it was pretty cool no I'm sure
this looks good it's just like when you
put two like you take a picture of your
face and then a picture afterwards and
you don't level it up very well like
your eyes are kind of looking to one
side
I think this is the same picture
movement but it's just a like one line
drawn through it with like Photoshop or
so
it's a lie it's a fake book
no it's not too big they just didn't do
it online
oh I feel I feel bad yeah some people
have very um this isn't this this lady
doesn't even have that uneven eyes but
something yeah really crazy uneven faces
I've noticed like we all get Derpy
sometimes I noticed that no proof of it
proof from charms the actress from proof
from Charmed she has a very uneven face
can you guys do weird things with your
eyeballs like your iris like can you
like look in different directions or no
no no no
uh I can kind of like have one eye hmm
looking forward and then the other eye
cross-eyed oh how do you do that you
look you just do it it's dying right now
or do you ever do you ever like do your
eyes in the mirror and like you can kind
of see your other eye and you can see it
looking like where your eye is it just
looks really do you know what I'm
talking about like if you go to it go to
a mirror and focus on one eye and then
don't look at your other eye but just
like kind of acknowledge it you'll see
it looking
it's really weird
look no no no no no I'm saying like as
soon as you've looked here like as soon
as you step back and look at your face
like it's gone it's just it's because
when you're looking at the other like
both of your pupils are looking that way
it's just a weird it's just a weird
thing
skill to show you know and no it's not
Escape I'm not talking about
I think it's a cool skill
but I don't have
just I can wiggle my ears
wiggle ears that's
that's someone of a skill
it's not as cool as making your eyes
purposely cross-eyed but
is it crisscross side what do you say
I don't know
is
like DIYs
mermaid can watch your front and your
back at the same time
human and not and not to me curiosity
thank you
this rules ever like experience I think
it was it only happened during like
school time some kids would like try to
impress you like hey look at this skill
that I have and they would like pull
over their eyelids the top eyelids
how disgusting oh I'd have people like
they'd roll their eyes back or something
other girls
this is not even Girls Talk man are we
doing he was like she's like look at
this can you do this girl and she looked
at her shirt and she went like like
with her stomach it was weird was it
like belly dancing
I don't know but it was
dancing I guess when you could roll
their stomach too whoa we should take a
belly dancing class no oh okay you know
sometimes I can teach us
yeah yeah
interesting okay are you girls ready for
another picture yes
I've seen it before yeah I think it's
not for I have the nail front part is it
for like the back part yeah stick it
like dead skin in your cuticles and
stuff yeah push it back the thing is it
also looks like a scalpel right yeah the
chat is like a little pill I guess it no
no you said scalp of food
[Laughter]
[Music]
you you basically with the middle part
you like what you you try to rub off the
the yeah
I didn't think about the middle part
having a function I don't know what it
does I thought that was just for grip no
that's what I would assume too because
it's like if you have to smooth metal
it's gonna get slippery real fast no no
it is a it has a filing function
I don't think it's usually used for the
front I think it's actually you know
because the whole thing is for like when
you call it the cuticles
oh yeah it seems for the grip because
then they could just make it with
plastic or whatever but you only ever
see it with this um you know whole mat
this whole thing in metal
it's like a file that part is like a
file
I'm just pretty sure too but then how do
you not make your fingers bleed like
what the [\h__\h]
I think it's painful I like squishing
some blood for some nice nails true
beauty is pain okay this one I guess was
too easy but here's the last one I
honestly if you get this then honestly
you can be a permanent member of ghost
song oh
no I but maybe well if you know if this
is also male related and you know a lot
of things about nails that you probably
do know
I don't know though
uh what is this
they look like wasp nest I can imagine
could be well not right now we don't
know for sure what it is do you know
what it is I think so yeah
think of this
it doesn't know anything
I see it in her eyes I don't know like
personally I would think maybe these are
probably like fingertip sized and
they're you put your fingers in probably
I never saw it in action but I would
assume and then
and then yeah like well then I don't
know are you soak them in acetone like
what movie was trying to do it's like
little fingertips
the one I just came with the foil
is it for Nail Care separate why is
there a pile of them because there's
many to your little fingers but
let me fact check that wait
individual because you do soak like you
soak some cotton around it and you're
supposed to wrap oil or plastic
[Music]
okay
what is what is okay wait I have to save
it differently
a thing that I know what it is baby you
don't know what oh no you probably know
what it is
what isn't what this is though they look
like yellow alien eggs or something
spider eggs or so oh stick them in your
nose
soak off nail cap for for a bloody nose
yeah you can like hide stuff in them too
like a little pocket extra Pocket
accessory
okay good look I challenge you do you
know what this is you probably don't
need it but do you know what it is
those are nipple covers yeah
okay
I know what those were too yeah it's so
easy because I used to always get like
ads for them
like a wish.com
okay
okay okay okay
how how about
[Music]
this one this one you will not know
um
okay here it comes are you ready
do you won't know this one
what's this
it's blurry what is that the spring
quality is makes it a bit difficult you
don't you're not supposed to read what
it says because that gives it away it
looks like a lifesaver it does look like
a lifesaver yeah
silicone thingy mm-hmm looks like Silk
honey
it looks like his hand is this makeup
related or are you pulling a funny can
you make it a little bigger it looks
like it also reminds me of like tape
well
I'd like to know if there's something
inch like what's inside it looks like a
bagel
it is weird I actually have never seen
it before myself either
and it was on you know a website that
has a like uh only girls know these
items but
turns out this is a trick question
it's a it's not really a girl's item
wait
yeah is it like a waffle maker but for
bagels it's
it's a corn Club the corner
doesn't it but apparently you put the
corn fruit there yeah
closely there's even a little image on
on the
oh my God it is
weird why why you can just use a knife
what it's one of those tools you know
kitchen life hack tools I mean maybe if
you like have trouble holding knives and
stuff like I can see it being useful but
if you have no issue
um you know with that type of stuff why
maybe it does exist for like if you have
shaky hands or like a Tremor or
something if you have a tendency to cut
uh yourself accidentally with the knife
in the kitchen yeah oh wait
wait think about this is apparently if I
look closely it says align top at on the
top slide down and then pour out which
means it kind of collects the coins
well who needs this the one I never make
I never prepare corn
oh why not you should corn is good like
it's easy to prepare but for some reason
like I don't know I just think
why I don't know did you buy it in the
can
yeah yeah I guess it's all there's too
many corn I guess out of the meals I
make really call for corn too
you should try corn cob Pizza like I
made before Oh
that is hmm
what girl scent what's that isn't that
for your face for your like uh
like for your cleanser or something to
really get close
it's not is it for your feet no it's I
know what it is
it's oh is it for your hair so for your
hair
the shampoo yeah it's a scalp book it's
fully a tour
get the dirt off your scalp wash it with
this I guess
I wouldn't use it though do you use this
no it kind of hurts I tried before I
wonder how dirty my scalp is
will they stay do you guys know I
thought you know your hair brushes
probably a lot of questions on there
this isn't everybody if you have hair if
you've hair this just pertains to you uh
apparently if you look at your hairbrush
after a while it might get like white
fuzzies on it you're like oh yeah
apparently that's like oils and stuff
that you need to wash off that's like
bacteria and ick and skin that has
collected and they say it once that
starts appearing on your hairbrush you
need to start you need to like soak it
or disinfect your hairbrush I don't know
how that's true
well I was just pulling it off I
remember once
was um using
using my mom's hairbrush and like I I
don't it's not that I wasn't supposed to
I just didn't want her to know
and almost immediately there's like that
Lynn stuff I was like what
like oops I was like trying to take it
out but the more I try picking it out
the worse it got and then just put it
back and I was like hopefully she won't
notice oh my God Dusty hair yeah
well don't don't worry about it I think
it's not I mean yeah I believe that but
I don't think it's such a big deal
to worry about you know
I used to have to use Head and Shoulders
oh
you can't wear black without the blue
sorry that was another dangerous
[Music]
Head Shoulders raise auntie
dandruff oh no it's just good for like
yeah
it's also antique dandruff I went to
camp and they had to give me head and
shoulders I was the only one who got
head and shoulders oh
did you get the green apple scent no we
got like a two in one
shampoo conditioner
oh it's okay it's okay but me don't
worry about it those times are over
anyway
and now that Mark probably now those
kids are using those products themselves
you know they don't even have hair they
didn't tell they didn't tell them
that's nice I guess then they didn't
tell them it worked my dandruff went
away yay congratulations goodbye
dandruff I wonder if it was could it
have been because like I was in the sun
maybe my head was getting like burned I
suppose yeah your scalp can burn if
you're not careful
it hurts
I don't know how that happens oh
you got a number two okay
excuse me no no okay
okay this is probably a hair curling
tool I would say yes
[Applause]
[Music]
you guys curl your hair
um
I would like to actually I'm really by
the curling my hair so I'm very
interested in in a new product that has
a
and it has arrived on the market heavy
girls heard of this like Dyson air
curling thingies a Dyson air wrap
is it what I'm thinking of it's like
it's like this this this void this whole
this black hole like it's just a it's
just a circle that's in and it's empty
and you it pulls air it pulls your hair
in and it just
you know like a lottery ball machine
basically I got my Dyson in uh
one yes I love it very much I can show
you like before and after pictures if
you wanted to see the Dyson
I have a vacuum but I I
yeah they make hair styling products now
it's
so straightens hair okay can you use it
to curl hair it can curl yes you can do
everything and there's like so there's
this base apparently and then you cut
then you buy like like extras that you
put on the base right go down yeah you
can it's got like a bunch of new
attachments as well they have like an
anti-frizz attachment you can do curls
you can do uh you can straighten it if
you want have you done curls with it yet
I've tried but they don't really stick I
don't think I do it right either
I don't own it I I watched a tutorial on
how to curl your hair properly with the
Dyson and and you just yeah you gotta
figure it out and then apparently it's
really easy but it makes cool curls
really nice but you have to make sure
that your hair is always listen to the
instructions they say like 80 dry
because I think I used it I think I used
it my hair was too wet and I was missing
like a chunk of hair
broke off holy [\h__\h] how do you know when
it's 80 what yeah right like oh that's
difficult
almost dry
oh okay oh well if it's drier than wet
then you'll be fine
risky because you can always remoisten
it I think maybe
oh yeah remix just throw some water yeah
I think so
make your hands wet and then go through
the hair I think that would work it also
makes you really sweaty because it gets
hot because it's blowing hot air on you
so interesting I want to try it out I
want to try the curling thingy out
because I actually I don't I have a
curler for my hair but I I don't ever
use it when I want to curl my hair the
only thing I can succeed in curling my
hair with is a straightening ironically
oh yeah yeah
I just go like
um there's like two two strategies you
can either do like a wave you know or
you can wrap it around the straightening
iron and then just pull it down that
works now
ironically
ironically for straightening my you know
for curling my hair I use a
straightening ironic
a master of the iron because that can be
tricky to do
yeah well I got the skills
I do want to
oh okay one more thing that I want to
talk about that good I brought up or
brought with her that I I want to hear
from you girls and talk about is
what color theme was your bedroom as a
kid
[Music]
if you had one or maybe you had several
can can I go first okay so my room I was
so happy once um I have a brother I was
so happy once I got my own room and
separated with my brother so then I made
my own room and my mom helped me paint
my whole room in like a pastel a little
bit darker than pastel purple yeah
like a lavender color and it wanted pink
and yes I went with purple purple is one
of my favorite colors and then and then
you know I had this like this um this
bad that was not not a fancy bed you
know we did whenever we were in the
wealthy family but I wanted it to look
cute and my mommy made my dream come
true of like you know a bed with those
like we call it a himalay pet in German
like a bed of curtains
yeah so we got that we made that the DIY
around my bed yeah canopy bed again
I like I like the the way I tried how to
make my room girly but then the one
thing this was during a phase during a
time where I was starting my job I love
Japan face my weird buffets and
I got like a lot of like things from
Japan and I would I would stick because
I was I I wanted to feel like I was in
Japan or I was more Japanese or so so I
would stick all kinds of things like
um like Japanese snacks I would stick it
on my wall with tape everything wrappers
after no it's still there was still
stuff inside I would stick it in the
woods yeah I wouldn't even eat it I
would just stick it on the wall like I
stuck like some like Japanese style
clothes on my wall and I stuck I had
this one big Big Empty wall and I stuck
everything on there and I got like a
million uh like Japanese alpaca plushies
the cute ones
yeah and and what else I I got like
really fancy Japanese calligraphy
writing thingies that are stuck on my
wall everything that's what it was like
my Japanese wall
oh yeah but purple it was purple what
about you girls
I'm trying to remember
you don't remember
well I moved quite a bit so it kind of
changed oh
um
I remember my walls were white I do
remember at one point for some reason
like there were two twin beds in my room
oh like but they were never put together
so it's not like I had a bigger bed it
was just there
I think oh I think when I had like a
sleepover or something and they pushed
it together but I don't I don't know why
it was there but
um
but no one ever stayed in my
rooms were pink
yeah it was like pink and white I think
was it a bedroom stuffed animals
where did I
did I puffed animals had a lot I don't
know I don't remember
okay I do remember oh my gosh no no I
remember something a different place
where I lived I had one uh one twin bed
and the room was pretty small and so I
think the only other thing in there was
my dresser and there's a closet and my
bed was kind of in the middle of the
room but it was really small so there's
just like a little space on the other
side so I think on the right was the
door and the left is where I put all my
stuffed animals and it was just like
just an ocean of stuffed animals on the
left on the left side of my bed
it was pink it was usually white and
pink but very colorful stuffed animals
but once once they got lice
and then we found no we found ants or
something on one of my stuffed animals
and so we had to like clean all of them
and I had a lot
oh I remember them and so nice
I remember it looking like
ants but
but maybe it was formalized I used to
have lies too and I got bullied so much
in school for it and then people the
girl that nobody wanted to be friends
with me because I I was the last
what I need to confess I I never could
talk about this but I was the light
skinned for a long time and me and my
mom tried so hard to get rid of it like
she would we would experiment every
single thing we would at one time you
know the normalized things they didn't
work the normal light shampoos and all
that and you know the the the
um comp the really tight comp that
really hurt nothing worked one time we
tried this we bought this like heat cap
heat helmet that you put on top it gets
so [\h__\h] hot and you try to burn them
that didn't work either I I tried I
swear everything and whenever I would go
to school and they would like a student
would find something they would like
tell the teacher and then they would
tell me to go home and then obviously
everybody knows and then me and my mom
would try again for like a week to get
rid of it but kind of questionable I've
been really ever got rid of it but I
would have to go back eventually and
they would think well maybe now she's
she's done but next time it was again
mean
um my husband
[\h__\h] it was a really traumatic for me
if it makes you feel better I had lice
like five times like five separate times
but
I think when I got it it was usually in
the summer so there wasn't school
um
so that just means you guys were really
clean right cleanly children really oh
yeah because they'll only go they only
go for clean heads
cleaners or what
no lice don't like dirty Dirty Heads oh
okay
I was the Crusty kid so
you guys were clean and then cleanly and
the lice were like I don't think that's
the image that the other kids got if
anything they all wanted to keep
distance from me nobody wanted to hug me
and you know nobody wanted to sit next
to me stupid they were um ignorant they
didn't understand like
I remember once I was in the car I don't
know why but my mom took me to the
doctor when I first got lice I think she
was like in panic mode like what do I do
about this so I was on the way to the
doctor and I remember itching my head
and then I was like I don't know there's
like kind of like dandruff or something
under my nails that like wipe my nails
on the car seat and then the stuff under
my nails started
[Music]
at some point you know I had so much
hate towards them so when I would pick
one off of my head I would like smash
them with my nails and kill them yeah
that made me happy what am I thinking of
in some cartoon
there was like a lot like I've seen a
club where there's like a lice
what was it there's like a it was trying
like this like lies living in a
civilization on someone's head and like
yeah
like one had a family I think I focused
on one and then later on like you know
people use the shampoo and then it was
like a horrible it was like an
apocalypse oh my God what is that from
that was something that was in my head
too when I was younger like I was
wondering like there's so many up there
they're so tiny my head is so big it
must be like a world for them like I'm
Earth I am their Earth
that's true you are you are their entire
ecosystem yeah
well but then I eventually I just got
rid of him like like Naturally by
growing older it seems like they prefer
children
kids are
why is that why do maybe it was at any
age I wonder if when you're younger your
hair is usually a bit thinner right
um maybe it's healthier
well how I guess it depends how young
I don't know they just disappeared at
some point after many years of suffering
with it good
about your color theme
oh yeah oh I was a blue light blue blue
brown green blue brown green blue blue
yeah
did you request it or I did
but I always wanted uh like pink pink I
wanted like a hot pink room
did they not did your parents not allow
it or oh no I just I always wanted like
a different theme like I would look
through the magazines I would come
through the mail and like used to have
like uh like like the Pottery Barn Kids
magazines and they had the perfectly
themed kid rooms like this girl had
lavender and hearts and this one was
penguin Superstars and there's from
resistance they had the really cool loft
beds I would be like oh I want I used to
have a lot of fans oh chill who is lost
beds gang only me
it's so cool because well we had to save
space especially when I was still living
with my brother and I had my computer
underneath hey cool yeah well so I would
I would like a late at night you know my
mom is a gamer so she kind of raised us
as Gamers so I got a PC very early I
can't remember but probably already when
I was like 10 or 9 and back then it
wasn't normal for a kid to have a
computer but I had it and then later you
have a shared computer oh I have my own
and then especially during like
um summer holidays summer vacation from
school I would like get so addicted to
uh anime MMORPGs and I would like play
10 to 15 hours a day
grinding and leveling and then at like 3
A.M or so or not no sometimes when my
mom would wake up at like 7 A.M I would
be still awake playing and I noticed
that she would get up because her alarm
would start ringing I was like okay so I
instead of turning off my pc because
that takes so much time I would just
turn off the Monitor and quickly climb
up to my bed and access if I'm sleeping
that's like Master Level of hide the DS
yeah so I haven't noticed sometimes you
wouldn't sorry go ahead oh once I got
like a laptop like my first laptop for
the first time I would take my Bamboo
tablet and draw like in bed so I'd have
the band the bamboo I mean the cheap one
and so I also had to be stealthy because
I step way too late drawing on the
computer and somehow I would like if I
like I don't know if someone was coming
up like upstairs or like I could just
tell and I'd hide my entire laptop under
my pillow
hot hot overheating oh yeah oh yeah I
could be warm very warm
I used to have a bamboo too that was my
first I think my first uh drawing tablet
yeah it was nice
had a pink one I was so happy first I
had a cheap uh white one and then later
I upgraded to the pink one and I was so
so happy
with them and it's made drawing so much
more fun because it was big
ouch
I remember saving up for it and it
taking so long and like how expensive
were they the bamboo yeah because I
think yeah back then they were 100 or so
yeah I remember saving up and then once
I had enough I was just
so like I don't know it was like the
greatest day of my life
I kind of missed my bamboo
ah you know what was also fun okay now
we're like not girls talk but kids talk
but you remember those drawing thingies
when you draw on like a tablet and it's
like a tablet shape and then you pull a
handle down and it deletes it
oh
the magnet one yeah I think so
I love that I just actually sketchy
sketch empty skins right
Etch A Sketch Etch A Sketch yeah I think
that's what I mean yeah I love that
yeah oh wait or these oh I cannot copy
paste
itchy sketch
um
cute
what kind of bandage you have
um just a box working in a matches on a
box spring day I don't have like a bed
bed I always wanted like a princess bed
or a loft bed but my mom is a princess
beds are fire hazard and you can't have
uh the other ones are too expensive so I
always just had like either mattress on
the floor or a mattress on a box spring
oh I feel like box I think mine was like
that mine was just on a box spring too
cool yeah to me box spring it's a pretty
American thing I feel like it's like
more common in America here boxing is
just so fancy to me it's like a really
expensive thing because you don't have a
box or you're going to need your
mattress is gonna sag in the middle
you're gonna get back no problem no
there are like lather type of things
that you put underneath
yeah that's the Box
no they don't no no no that's different
huh box spring and when you call the
other normal beds what do you call that
Latin yeah box spring that's different
pretty sure you could see the Springs
wait what did I have wait box if it's
like open and you know you put the the
slats there yourself that's I think a
different thing that's like a basic
basic bed frame frame frame bed
yes wait box spring which
kfp I guess I don't know
I think at some point I had um like
something covering the how do you call
it
like something covering over the
mattress frame or whatever like like a
quilt thing covering it but not the
quilt of my bed do you know what I'm
talking about uh yeah like a padded bad
thing often goes on top of those kind of
box spring but it's not like a whole
full-size mattress but a uh a comforter
yeah I think it's called a mattress
topper
um
bed skirt is what it's called bed skirt
yeah a bad skirt oh wait a bed skirt
hides the
the box springs yes oh maybe it was a
box spring I just remember it oh pretty
oh yeah yeah that's great
are you cute cute cute
cuteness points up up up
oh yes but can also look I don't know
very old-fashioned and old
[Music]
specifically ordered like Japanese
bedding when I was a teenager because it
has like all the Frills everywhere
around it and the Ruffles and the lace
it's kind of annoying to wash but it's
like so cute when it's made it's so cute
my last bedroom before like I left you
know to spread my wings
um it was so boring because I hadn't I
just didn't do any like I don't know I
didn't really care
very much it was like the entire room
was white with gray carpet that was it
oh
wow that was it why not why not my
room's not I just heard someone's
stomach tired
you guys probably didn't hear that but I
I heard the chat didn't hear it did you
it's okay my stomach crumbles all the
time
[Music]
no problem
uh one okay one last thing
speaking of food
oh good do you do you think I think I
feel like to me avocados is a girly food
do you agree
why you say that I don't like avocados
but to me it's like every girl these
days eats avocados
I think like there's like avocado
accessories stuff that's a girl thing
I'm not saying you're like a girl cause
you eat an avocado
they're freaking out no I just mean you
know I don't know I see like girls
nowadays are always eating avocados
because this is a super food a healthy
food it's like a it's
killer like recently don't you think
like in the past three four years I know
is that Boomers make fun of younger
people for eating avocado
because they've never had Chipotle
guacamole
more for us screw them
live your life on knowing it's a
delicious guacamole is too salty
it's like it's two or not salty it's too
too much too much too much lemon
is lime I think it's nice
it's too much oh I love it I eat it with
a spoon if I get my hands on it oh my it
like makes my mouth tingle like it feels
weird
easy
so
um I thought of something is it the
Boomer tumor thing
Boomer
oh I just know that Boomer like I saw
something about how Boomers were like oh
younger people don't know how to save
money because they spend all their money
on Avocado because all they eat is
Hormel chili they need to shut up
[\h__\h] is this Gouda
sorry oh that
said that lime or citrusy makes her
mouth tingling made me think of this uh
totally not Tick Tock that I saw I'm
totally not Instagram but they were like
this is why pineapple makes your mouth
tingle which I'm assuming is maybe
similar because pineapple and Microsoft
has needles and it stabs inside your
mouth and that's why your mouth
we need
what
what is it
I'm second guessing myself am I thinking
of Chipotle guacamole
a Navy I don't know I I think I am maybe
also depends like you know different
restaurants have different
what the [\h__\h]
digestive enzymes is what it is
stabby stabby
no no needles they have digestive
enzymes it's the fruit that eats you
back
I assumed it was like just because it's
acidic like situation yeah
don't believe everything on the internet
but it's so easy
well well well any any last girl
um words anything you want to
leave I think we're going overboard with
avocados because you can find avocados
and everything now it's like health food
you can make pudding you can make ice
cream with avocado yeah actually the
cottage cheese that's what people are
latching on to now have you seen that
cottage cheese people people are
replacing like yogurt with cottage
cheese the cottage cheese ice cream wait
what's this you blend it up and then you
add your stuff into it but the cottage
cheese is like salty and yeah gooey
food World which is very different over
there than from here
foreign
you live in a different world like you
know too many things and I'm more
permanently online yeah that's what I
was thinking like when I see Trends and
stuff like it's online because I don't
know what people do around me no it's
not online
oh I guess this is what the the young
people are up to oh this is what the old
people are doing now oh
will look at these things and I feel
like you you you think like it's like a
big thing everywhere or so but that's
amazing
yeah especially
okay okay okay
like no one probably
the kids
did anybody in the chat know about that
anyway probably not is anybody in this
chat under the age of 16 though that's
the question because that made me
that might be a big no no no no no no no
I don't know we don't know which which
question they're answering but I mean
you set up in Cummings Maybe maybe it's
you know it's coming
I I believe it is
not I'm happy it's not coming it's not
I'm happy
it's my cottage cheese
nice though
it is nice this is nice
okay girls uh should probably leave it
around that it was nice talking to girls
yes I have a girly thing to say yes
let's go to the bathroom together
okay I have to go to the bathroom come
with me wait I have a question oh get to
the bathroom
no no uh this is girl girl colored we go
to the bathroom together but do you do
you guys think it's okay to talk to one
another while you're in the stall yes or
no or does conversation stop when the
door closes and we're all doing our
thing I think it's more Awkward if it's
just silent okay it depends it depends
most of the time I think it's too
embarrassing and and awkward and no but
I've also tried the conversation path
and
depends it's a difficult thing I think
it depends like I will not start
conversation like I've I don't know I've
had girlfriends where like we'd go and
it'd be silent or I had some that like
would immediately start talking
[Music]
yeah when someone does does that I'm
like I respect you for being so
comfortable in this room right now while
we're hearing all these noises
suspect that like wow I went to the
bathroom with a hall of member and we
chatted in between the Stalls no
problems
well who was the Japanese lover uh no it
was an English member yeah remember what
was it you know I don't know if I should
say it because I don't want them to be
embarrassed if that's not something they
want me to share but I'm okay with
chatting I don't mind oh okay so
okay
that's interesting I was just curious
because I don't know because the
bathroom together but then I don't know
conversation continues or stops I have
something I won't say on stream but
remind me okay to mention I want to see
if you guys do it too okay
the the real girls talk happens after
the girl sucks because there's you know
girls things that we can really only
discuss under uh you know the circle
this circle you know private circle of
girls Secrets 12 secrets there's like I
don't know there's things that you want
to share about girls where it's like
yeah you know what I feel like like guys
guys like you know they can know this
they can know this that's not weird but
then there's other things where I'm like
this is like if if guys no no they're
gonna twist this they're gonna be weird
so I can't tell them because then the
girl code will be broken and then we're
going to do in the dead of night
well for by the way for the next girls
talk I'm planning something if if the
girls are up for it what I want to do
next is I want to have uh every
participating member right anonymously
to an anonymous person a love letter
in a situation that is like provided by
me like you know
um to you know see which Anonymous
letter is the most Doki Doki inducing
one
will be voted by the chat and maybe also
the members who are in there and then
after the most okidoki one has been
chosen we will only after that find out
who wrote what letter
who writes the best love letters oh can
we use chat GPT now
right now
you have to use your heart
can you do that
I don't think I can do it and have it
not obvious with me
You Gotta Be You Gotta Stay Anonymous
mummy
okay okay and maybe good if you want you
can always be on again
as I said I don't know if I'm included
in this but I'm gonna watch regardless
statue Boutique is a great writer from a
love letter oh I don't
care so hard
to use it as anything I won't reference
or get any ideas from it nope okay good
ah what was that link I saw that now I
have something in my eyes I saw another
one is it your eyes going crazy again
one thing is doing something different
than the other is my contacts
better take him out better get your eyes
lasered mummy I won't tell
laser vision
well did you have fun being a girl today
I did thank you guys for uh having me
here welcome thanks for coming to my
room I learned a lot
yeah I did too yeah Buddha is such a
girl she knows so much about Nails
especially
[Music]
when we have questions about Nails I
think we got to go to Google
I feel like the most girly thing about
Cali for example is her nails she also
is a big nail person and she's a girly
girl she has a girly girl side
it's the more Gap
yes you don't expect it but when you get
to know her you notice oh she's very
grown
you gotta uncover it yeah who do you
okay one last question who do you think
is the girliest in from your POV from
your knowledge was a girl used in Ian
what do you think oh of every Ian hmm
she'd be very girly
I yeah a movie we haven't
[Music]
oh yeah
well I I could be wrong but my gut's
telling me fauna for what I know so far
no it's not me don't it's not me I
didn't meet
no no not yet say it oops
[Applause]
you met everyone but movie
I think so oh damn I believe I've met
everyone but girl oh uh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
which one is it I wonder
yeah hopefully
no that will be a magical miraculous day
when you two finally meet
it'll be awesome it'll be interesting to
have like to meet somebody because we
sound so similar to like
talk to each other in the same room and
hear it does that make sense to me yeah
but I
and once I feel like people sound
different in person
so there could be
um true
[Music]
I mean Cara you've met both of us is it
different in person
um
I mean I can generally like even now
clearly make a distinction it's just
like something I mean different from how
we sound online
they got me sound online
[Music]
not much
I think it's mostly like a mood thing
like IRL mostly where like you know more
like chill you know so then the mood
maybe brings it down a little bit but I
don't think it's much different
I think fauna got movement I confused uh
we were together because I think either
I said something or how did it happen
it was a noise but yeah this is bloody
okay
yeah it's just like from the floor is
the line it's a very it's like yeah
Minecraft oh was it doing Minecraft
yeah right before it was probably doing
Minecraft video I'm probably more more
times other times too
but uh it's just small small moments I
think so when you make when you say a
whole sentence I think you can tell it
apart
if you can't you're deaf yes
people told me before that I
might me with my old microphone
apparently
sounded a little bit like Iris
I've heard that from a couple people but
don't know
I'm gonna have to see a comparison video
I don't think there's a comparison video
but some people said that yeah yeah yeah
I sounded very different with my old
microphone that's a fact it's been a
long time since I used it
um
Iris it's kiaras is that
oh that was kind of how she says it
doesn't it yeah
it's Iris oh but now look at that like
that though that was good I don't think
I can like
can't replicate how she normally talks
but the high-risk is Iris like you hear
that so much
I feel like it's easier yeah certain
phrases are easier hmm
well well thank you thank you for the
phrases well
um so thank you girls this will be the
end of girl saguda what are you looking
at
your channel
okay it's okay so let's say goodbyes
goodbye
thank you for listening everybody to the
girls talk we'll do it again sometime
bye sisters
[Music]
some people who are looking forward to
hearing your Valley girls today there
was none
too bad I killed belly girl still
that's the last year
oh sad so sad
okay bye bye guys and in Germany
try harder come on
she's mumbling Kremlin
[Laughter]
now
[Music]
laughs
foreign
[Music]