[Music]
you
now
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
me
hmm
[Music]
oh
huh
[Music]
hello
oh this is uh weird
i logged in
um
i
i don't think
ah
never mind never mind um
ah there's snow
there's no
oh oh oh oh oh
how do oh oh
again i forgot oh my god there is so
much snow
um oh
potatoes nice potato potatoes
hello yeah that was a good start
[Laughter]
lag what leg what do you mean lag i
didn't see lag oh you mean my hits i was
just not hitting it correctly prop
probably
uh
probably not even the lag
welcome everybody
it has been
a while
since oh god since the last oh god let's
get out of here
since the last
wait that's too loud wait sorry
i'll fix it
[Music]
since the last minecraft stream it's
been a while again do i have fireworks
no i don't
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h] him
why is he on fire now oh it's daytime
now it's so hard to see when oh my god
oh
i normally never do that because i never
am fast enough
uh
oh god okay stress level
are you talking about a different game
here
uh where the [\h__\h] am i uh where is home
that way i think that way
um
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god oh my god what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
wait
um
[Music]
stop what kind of welcome is that
did you not want me to come back
minecraft
kangeno
yarikata yo
please be kind to me
oh [\h__\h] the snow
i don't see [\h__\h] is this how it's gonna
be in my skiing vacation
hello cat oh my god the rain is so
[\h__\h] noisy
why isn't this right now
what the [\h__\h] is this weather and looks
like [\h__\h] without my shaders
i'm going to turn my shaders on
again uh
video settings shaders
[Music]
oh man
that that makes it a bit more bearable
a
question
that you guys might be asking yourselves
what are we doing today
the answer is
whatever you want me to do
i
don't really
um
oh yeah i came here originally in my
free time to get gunpowder not in my
free time after the last stream i was
like
hanging a little bit here to get
gunpowder
um yeah i was thinking
we could go to the try to find a lush
cave again because we kind of failed
last time
i know
we could do that circles
but that's boring we'll get go there and
then we won't even be able to
transport him here probably because the
no pretty sure not probably pretty sure
this is just so far away
what is these circles well is there a
chance uh
well that that area where circles is is
already loaded so
i would not be able to find a one of
those trees
uh
above ground i suppose
so
oh my god cats my cats are like playing
with a paper bag
it's very noisy
uh
find a director eight add name text
oh well that's like um
that feels like such a
small task i want bigger tasks
just dig down
and hope that i'll find what i'm looking
for
[Music]
the weather is terrible
just want it to be over oh my god i'm
gonna shut myself in in the
shitty weather like that who left the
doors opened me
dig down and fit
right dig down until you find world
peace
lava and peaceful
a bigger fight at the end i already did
that i mean not alone but
um [\h__\h] that i don't want that
[Music]
what is circles oh there are some people
yeah i mean circles is pretty old i
suppose so some people don't know
um
honestly everybody who's crying about
circles is overreacting let me just tell
you that my dear new fans
circles is a horse that i named
during some other travels a long time
ago
and i i left circles somewhere because
the travel back would be pretty
impossible
because it goes through big big oceans
so i left him
with uh in a safe environment
and ever since then
people are asking me to get circles back
[Music]
i know there's an armor there i threw it
out did you not see it and i did it like
a few seconds ago
he's just enjoying life yeah oh it's
clearing up
that is much better
much better
yeah um
[Music]
circles huh
i threw it on the ground yeah oh
i threw it on the ground indeed all
right oh yeah
oh the thing is like i can't let's see
how many
how many fireworks i can even make with
that because i think i i ran out
completely yeah yeah yeah
um
the question is can we even go that far
worst case
worst case justice once i might go to
the japan server for extra
gun powder gun powder
[Music]
and fireworks
uh
huh wait wallpaper
i don't know i picked it up where's my
smile where's my where did i put the
paper
well there's one gunpowder
i definitely have a lot of paper
i just don't know out here
[Music]
see i mean how many stacks did we use
last time
fireworks i type it in japanese all the
time
that's
is that how much did we how many stacks
did we have last time
feels like this is all
all i can make
used them all last time
yeah yeah yeah i know i know
two to three stacks
and with that we did reach a new area
but
[Music]
um we couldn't find anything i don't
know if i was just blind but
or if it's really that rare
i'm gonna see
a base thingy if maybe maybe maybe maybe
maybe maybe maybe maybe
maybe we can get a bit more
a bit more you kept refusing going into
caves oh cow carrot you you were just
waiting for it weren't you you were you
had your adult premier pro opened the
recording button started and taking
notes
waiting for me to do [\h__\h]
in minecraft
i know i know i know
understandable
well i hope today i can deliver you
something more interesting
than just flying around for hours and
hours and hours
uh
that's so loud minecraft minecraft why
are you so loud
is this a block noise
what is that noise
or does it only change afterwards
oh well let's just
lower in general
okay let's show
minecart ace them
what the [\h__\h] oh
uh
going back to bale's thingy
oh it looks so much better when it's not
horrible weather doesn't it holy [\h__\h]
but people haven't
heated the grass in a long time how is
that on purpose
it's the the ground is so
fluffy and fuzzy
wow
a friendly that would have been friendly
creatures that's not a creature
what minecraft
makes no sense it's on purpose oh
oopsie
[Music]
okay more fireworks please
please bless me
with your fireworks
of your gunpowder oh wow six
oh yeah i i didn't have afk a while
after
my last stream that's where i got the
the the ones that i already had in the
inventory
[Music]
um thank you thank you you are adorable
too
oh
boca roy see i've never been in
bungaroney before
i wonder what cronie is doing is i
wonder if she's awake
are you
up
can you
deal me some gunpowder in minecraft
[Music]
if it's probably not not available
i did write her a message maybe she's
gonna get back to me
her pc is dead
what ah the blue screen oh [\h__\h] well
does she not have like anything like
um maybe i can log into her account
or wait maybe she can just tell me where
buncaroni is and i'll go there myself
movie knows where the bunker is right
maybe i could try to see if movement is
like oh what is this
oh
maybe ina has some
wait didn't i already i already stole
some from mina i think
uh chad will guide me i kind of don't
want to go there without cronies
permission
i i've seen she's really quite um
quite serious about keeping it a secret
about her privacy
everyone goes down yeah okay but like
even if i go there without permission i
also don't want to take something
without permission
i'm i'm
i'm a good senpai
[Music]
everyone everyone knows why is everyone
invading her private space
visit to japan do you guys know where
there is gunpowder in the japan circle
who could
what time is it in japan right now
pretty little dance
[Music]
um
i can't ride gunpowder
[Music]
yeah she's feeling pokemon isn't she i
saw it yeah yeah she's streaming [\h__\h] i
shouldn't disturb her
uh
i don't know it might be it might be
it might be enough if we oh you know
what we could do
you know what we could do
we fly there for for that mostly we
don't even have to fly um but then we
get a horse
that will totally be circles
uh and then
and then uh
[\h__\h]
the most most of the path we will just
go by by horse
foot
crossfit
what do you think
[Music]
that way we would save a lot of
gunpowder
or move move okay
[Music]
go
go what the [\h__\h] did someone break this
or what
oh let's go
on horseback yes
does that sound good
oh is there actually i feel like i asked
this
what the [\h__\h]
that's the sign you meant chat again
oh man when did you make that
did i already enchant
my
dragon but riptide that only oh that was
bad
that only works in um
water no
[Music]
yeah thank you
because an eternal phoenix's beauty does
not change over time
it needs rain oh
probably won't get five we rely on that
baby decide cool good job
good job well okay so
i think i
have settled with my idea i will go on a
horse travel i definitely have uh
saddles
somewhere
[Music]
i'm diamond diamond
there there it is
should we give it armor i'm more armored
than that somewhere yeah give me some
golden almond why the hell not
um
okay
okay okay okay okay
so we will go on another trip guys
need to lead in the boats across the
ocean with circles
who said who said i'm going anywhere
with circles
ah should we get circles
but
we can't i don't know we can't no horses
don't go in a bowl
what do you mean i go on the boat with a
leash
no no no don't get excited i no i don't
want to no that's like how the [\h__\h] will
i get circles all the way here it's so
far away
ah
[Music]
you can drag them behind the belly
that's gonna feel like take a million
[\h__\h] years
what if i just find circles a new owner
huh
like a village or so
would that make you happy
if circles is alive that is the question
[Music]
they cannot go in boats i will not fall
for that [\h__\h] again no one can convince
me that a horse can uh join me in a boat
that's the biggest
[\h__\h] i've heard
and it has been proven wrong
um okay then let me clean up this
[\h__\h] mess of an
do you guys inventory the coordinates
for circles i'm sure some of you
have it some of the circle freaks uh i
know you do
[Music]
oh my god
of course
immediately i've been immediately
provided with
coordinates
circle freaks
circle freaks that's your name that
shall be your name circle freaks
this is what is in there
[Music]
um
your comment is now pinned yeah
you know what if he finds circles he may
have the golden horse armor even though
i'm not bringing him home
home to this he will get a different
home
because i mean you know traveling such a
far distance
it's just too much to ask of an animal
[Music]
at least i will you stop complaining
if i at least go there and find him a
safe place
if i do that then i never want to hear
the word circles out of the circle
freak's mouth ever again
i can try to maybe try maybe bring him
home but if i don't then i'll just find
a villager so but then you must shut up
okay okay
those circles was like a father too sure
um okay um
sorry my brain is as always need some
time
[Music]
we have a bed
we have a bucket of water we have food
we need some more food we have this [\h__\h]
we have arrows we have armor
uh-huh
oh i mean we're gonna probably go for
the neva or are we no i guess we're
going back foot completely because
i originally i don't even know how i
would
find circles
uh
by going through the never i think we're
going by foot
or by by by wings like a phoenix
um
okay food
why am i always lacking food
[Music]
emma has a baked potato farm right can i
take some baked potatoes um
of course you can
oh thank you ame
thank you
and no one replenishes food one must do
it themselves
oh
that's the that's the good stuff oh yeah
thank you i'm in how do you activate
that like this oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i want to like
do it for her
i don't want to do it wrong but
is this how it is is this how it works
oh maybe not
maybe not
i'm turning it back
ah i have to do the seats first here huh
does she have the seeds
[Music]
ah wait it's not seeds it's just
potatoes right
let me do it let me do it
uh
don't eat it
love those potatoes
don't eat it why you must always eat
kiwa
thank you for the offering uh amelia
watson
thank you for the potatoes
[Music]
thank you
yeah yeah it's the simple things in life
that make you happy like baked potatoes
all right what else do i need guys
i think nothing i'll eat i'll leave
elite to at least try uh
there have some alpacas on my leashes
hello
[Music]
you'll stay with the others right
stay with them
where did the leash
out here
don't fail though right
now
okay
uh then i think i got what i need i'm
gonna
leave the pepper
[Music]
potatoes
made
by ame with love
i'll bring this box
i'll bring it as well
i'll leave some food in there
[Music]
streams box
boat
i don't see a boat
[Music]
you see a boat i don't see a one i'll
make a boat
[Music]
oh okay
circles
the circle freaks have one
i am giving them what they want should i
bring another
[Music]
last time
where did it go did i leave it there
[Music]
where did my end
go
do i need an energy
i had so many under chests
[Music]
2 000 meters is that a lot in
in minecraft terms
whatever i am just not gonna
bring it i don't care i don't i don't
need it i don't need it
or do i [\h__\h] i'm scared about my hot
wings
i'll be fine i've extra hot wings as
well
all right
one block is one meter oh okay well then
uh loop
let's look at the coordinates minus 200
so that's
this way
and then
mine is 2 600.
oh
that's that is a lot it's kind of that
way i think
[Music]
build a bigger bunker to keep him more
secure don't worry don't worry we'll
find him an owner and stuff is there
anything i forgot if yes and tell me now
[Music]
is it going down it's going down this is
going up that's good okay
please i have a leash
apple oh circles already likes me
supposedly
i think i'm sick okay and the chest
there [\h__\h] it we're doing a violent in
the chest
[Music]
i'm away if i can fly i have extra
rockets and i have the yes i have i have
extra rockets
no
problem
first number oh yeah already down to
four
[Music]
we're going up
oh wait this way
no no
um
this way
this way this way
[Music]
in case i was too late now
i'm i've been pretty good in uh not
losing stuff
for quite some time now
wait it's so close with the elytra when
i originally um
did the circles
uh adventure back then
i had no lighter yet right
but with the horse it all felt so so far
away
[Music]
wow we're almost there right that's so
quick
i remember i think i built light around
circles as well
[Music]
we should sleep
okay we'll walk from here maybe or
should we no
[Music]
i said
that looks cool
[Music]
can you hear me
i can smell you circles
[Music]
hi bunny
oh this these remixes are so good man
i'll never get sick of them
getting closer
there goes
did i
i think i did build something around him
oh oh
wait it's still 600 let's fly
a minus [\h__\h] minus minus 200 minus 200
and 606
directions
oh it's supposed to go
uh
is it going up what's going on
i'm going right right now i'm going the
right way i think i am going to rightly
oh that's
that's it that's that's it that's it
that's it that's it
that's
that's the direction
[Music]
no
that's it
oh god i'm so bad at this
yeah it's a whole live remixes if you go
and look up whole live remix there's
like i think free
free videos by now
that
um have
like different kinds of remixes of whole
live original songs
they started out with some lo-fi i think
this is bossa nova and they also put out
a jazz one i think
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] um i'm so bad because oh 200
needs to go up up
[Music]
a waypoint mod uh-huh
know what that is
[Music]
can you like set a certain coordinate
and then it will show you from far away
like like in pokemon for example with
the quests
is that what is that what it is that
would be indeed extremely useful wait
i'm going i'm going the wrong way i'm
going the wrong way
this way this way
minus
one is 200
[Music]
um
house
[Music]
oh my god
how the [\h__\h] are you still alive my man
circles
oh i didn't i didn't expect
my emotions still be so overwhelmed the
moment i see you i'm so glad you're safe
i told you he's safe i told you guys
oh santa claus you're so beautiful
oh circles
oh
[Music]
circles wow you're shiny now
how is he still i felt because no one
really came here after i came here so
nothing attacked him or so it's been
months it's been a year or so more than
a year
history comes back in circles yours you
are as beautiful as the day i lost you i
left you
did i make a door i didn't to keep you
safe i didn't make a door
oh man
circle arena
oh you can actually
see he could have always jumped above
that if he wanted to
well okay
uh we can try to go back
but like
i'm not sure if it's gonna work guys
where is home i need my
i need my horn coordinates now
he waited for me
oh
circles
that is so sweet i cannot i cannot leave
with anyone now that i have him again
uh does someone have
home home coordinates
i wish i could fly with him
no you can't
[Music]
can you fly you mean if i fly with my
elytra and put a lead on him
he would probably
die um by strangulation
if i did that
uh 300 minus 400 something like that
probably yeah
um
we can try to make uh as much
um travel as much as i can
uh
on land so first of all
what is it 300 minus 400 or so
let's try to get these back on the plus
now
circles is alive yeah oh my god my horse
thing
sorry
[Laughter]
sorry that shocked me as much as it
shocked you or probably it's no it
shocked me much more than it shocked you
um
oh my god
well can i be really sick
what are you doing
properly
[Music]
am i going the right way for now i think
i am
yeah we're trying to get both numbers
back into the plus for now
oh man he must have missed me
stop stopping so much
any golden food items can help them get
oh
no
i don't
should i have brought like uh
food for circles
will he not follow me otherwise but i
have a lead and he's listening to me
generally
[Music]
hmm
let's see how far we get
he's jumping from happiness okay yeah
okay okay i forgive that's
understandable
ah
you know when he always said go get
circles i don't know it felt like such a
long travel back then that i felt like
if we go now it might be like a [\h__\h] ton
of effort but
it really wasn't that far away and now
with wings
was not far away at all
so
here i am
okay we're leaving we're leaving the
desert yoo-hoo
yoho
circles we're coming home
coming home the title was actually not
about circles i didn't think about
bringing back circles
but here have some water
have some water yum yum yum yum good
toys guitars
be careful be careful circles
yeah yeah i didn't i didn't plan i was
just talking about minecraft to be
honest i wasn't planning on bringing
circles
back home but now the title fits very
well doesn't it
be careful careful of the ground circles
i want you to come back
healthy or not back but circles has
never been
in my home before
wow
oh god alright go down i guess
[Music]
he has never had a home isn't that sad
how long can someone check how long has
it been
when was that stream
[Music]
uh
also i'm gonna check well you guys check
that i'm gonna check the coordinates
[Music]
423 days
oh my god
that's over a year
[Music]
wow and you guys kept bugging me about
it
all this time
so let me check my coordinates oh wait i
see
i still have the screenshot from back
then
look
[Music]
does it say the date on here
i don't see a date
i think
oh it did did it
he was so young that dad yeah he's aged
but horses how long do horses live
they live long enough don't they
someone must have taken care of him done
giving him some food maybe some zombies
who liked him
[Music]
i need coordinates where are my
coordinates
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] uh
wait
circles you're not gonna run away are
you
stay
stay hoisty protect me
okay okay okay wow
if you if you guys want to attack
someone attack me not my horse
[Music]
although he has some good armor so he'll
probably be fine
no i'm not gonna die i'm not gonna die
i'm not gonna die
i just need some coordinates
[Music]
i never take screenshots of my home
coordinates for obvious reasons because
usually i don't need it what just
happened i never
what just happened what was that noise
was that noise
oh okay nothing
i don't know i don't know i don't know i
can't find it uh i'll just what was it
what did you guys say 300 minus 400 or
minus 300 300 minus 400 okay
okay then we just need to get the set
to
minus 400
uh which is
[Music]
wow
m
[Music]
to
uh
our
end
now which way is the right way
would be very i think i think this way
maybe
this is the path of the end
but it's not the end of circles it's the
beginning of circles
[Music]
is that oh wait ah maybe it was the
other way
for now it's
still going down so we're probably
still fine
this is the right way oh you guys know
our server is so well
look out for holes yes
i have circles now i need to look for
holes
oh
ah this way
oh well we didn't even have to go in the
boat we could we were actually able to
travel by
by
ground
all the time
horsey circles are you too fat for this
really
oh yeah
what is so does this side path
or is that the actual path that i was
supposed to go on anyway
what what was that
[Music]
circles
calm down
which one is the right way
is this
[Music]
there's a towel there oh god don't fall
down
very confusing
oh god
[Applause]
it's not meant to be walked by a horse
wait i have a scissor
[Music]
i'll make some space for the horse
beautiful
i wonder what circles is thinking right
now
damn it feels good to have her on my
back again
i chose the words
wisely i could have said it differently
[Music]
what is this path it doesn't really feel
familiar
weirdly even though i must have
walked it a few times if it's really the
right path
well there are no
what a creeper has exploded here
probably
oh that looks familiar
i think yeah yeah yeah yeah that's where
we fall down into the water
[Music]
check coordinates
that seems about right seems about right
[Music]
no more deserts for you
only there's these beautiful
grasslands and flower circles it's like
a you're like a disney princess now
your dream of becoming a disney princess
is coming true
oh look
look tickles
[Music]
that's all something i built with
nanette do you know you don't know nana
do you
she's a cute girl maybe you'll see her
someday
yes yes this is a land of sophisticated
artists
as you can see by the buildings and i
know it looks like the future because we
are in the future
i know it's fascinating look at these
buildings holy [\h__\h] i actually never
took a close look at
ah
what she did up there is that a
is that a takodachi glass building
with the
thingy and then
i guess that's probably supposed to be a
sakura tree inside uh the cherry blossom
tree
i didn't check like what she did to fix
the disaster that happened recently
hello hello yes look other animals cows
they go moon chickens they go book book
and alpacas they go like [\h__\h] you
but they're really sweet though
those blocks
azalea
where did she get us a layer of look and
another layer tree
how where
explain
me please
[Music]
did she found did she find the lush cave
in the resource server
[Music]
well well well horsey welcome oh my god
look
this is kiwawa home this is also kiwawa
home this is kiwamo home and this is
kiwamo home everybody's keep our home
yeah
is that that wonderful you know what you
can chill in in these fields
if you want
yes there's water and food
oh sure have fun circles are you happy
you must be so happy circles look oh
look at him wagging his tail
no
circle stop walking i want to take a
picture of you
[Music]
you're as beautiful as the day i lost
you
wow
happy jumping
for a turn of the king name tag oh
that's a good idea do not even have one
in here
wait a second look i'm confused
let me place it down let me place it
somewhere
oh no it was not in here
i don't know i thought it wasn't here i
saw it somewhere
[Music]
i'll go get your name tag you stay huh
what oh yeah
shackles
he won't go too far will he
circles
be a good boy
you're close
you're out of
control why is he going away how do you
control a horse
come on come come come come
do i really need a leash for you
he's like oh i i'm out i don't like this
i'll go back to the desert this is not
my home no it is your home now
it is
i have to tie him to a post yeah
which post do you like circles maybe
something
here is pretty [\h__\h] nice isn't it you
know what the the boxing ring
can be yours now
and you can like walk around and eat
some berries how's that how's that
where did the leash go
oh man circles
your complicated horse
i don't really know
how horse's feelings work but anyway
this is your
this is your place now
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
so
i had
name tags
[Music]
i have name tags maybe down here
barry bush kill horses well he won't go
there
he's a smart horse
[Music]
he's now in the in the ring
in the fighting ring
also hey you think it's too dangerous
minecraft experts do you think
he will roam around so far that he'll be
hurt by these bushes maybe just remove
this one
this one but i don't think he can go
further because he's on the leash
hope she
[Music]
i might have to put a name on it first i
forgot
right
well we all know what his name is
he belongs in the museum
he kind of does
he has quite the story
circles
the one and only legend
i mean honestly if we think about it
there's not not much that he actually
did um he was active for one stream
he just uh
let me let me ride on him for a while
it's not quite that much that really
speaks for him being a legend but okay
he survived okay yeah for surviving i'll
i'll respect him for surviving
that is indeed a respectable thing
[Music]
he loved you isn't that enough
you love me circles
he couldn't have he could not have like
stayed alive in the desert for so long
if he didn't love me right
yeah
oops oh [\h__\h]
the horse who waited 400 days
i just need to get rick who the [\h__\h] is
rick
was that another horse i don't remember
rika has been forgotten who is rick
who's rey
what
what rick the donkey ah [\h__\h] the donkey
[Music]
okay so now what do we do now now we go
get um
now we look for the
lush cave
because inna found it on the japanese
resource center right
no one has yet to find a
a lash cave
on our server as far as i know
[Music]
yeah bjm is a banger
i i know there's a close one i've been
told the
coordinates before luckily i forgot
[Laughter]
i don't remember them i
i've been spoiled uh we tried looking
for the for lunch cave on her own and
then failed and then someone told me the
coordinates for one
but
i
i don't remember it anyway oh i think i
know where the end of the cave is i left
it at the
[Music]
headquarters
yes sorry brain empty
[Music]
okay we'll go on trip number two
to find
what
i deserve
a lush cave
um you guys have any recommendations on
what else i should bring if i'm gonna go
grab a
i'm gonna gonna go find a lunch cave i
think i have everything i need there's
some stuff in here too
a crafting table some logs some golden
boots that i need to put on anyway
uh
yo
baked potatoes
fireworks
yeah
and the chest i told him no no i didn't
take the totem last time and i didn't
die
i'll be fine
[Music]
okay it goes
do a comfy blankie i have one i have one
this is next to me
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] are you doing here
what is that mommy
did i spawn the
respawn
i beg for the never oh what
so if i die i respawn in here
oh my god that is cool
since when can you do that
down
an old thing here oh my gosh it's so
dark in here
it's another update
[Music]
it's so dark i'm gonna turn
off the
shaders for a little while
[Music]
da
that is not
that's not how you do it oh i wonder if
kyle carrot now
finally can make a circles video
because now there is an ending to it to
the story
cow carrot you could make a circles
[Music]
what was happening there what was
happening there i was so scared
what was happening what was happening
what was happening
[Music]
maybe if i just go to the right side
yeah there's an opening there but did i
fall down i didn't fall down right
because it's all black
[Music]
[\h__\h] i'm scared
i'm scared i don't want to dance i'm not
gonna die i'm not gonna die right i'm
not gonna die
[Music]
i need to i need to do something about
that i kept it open so that i don't know
maybe uh some scenery you know i thought
it would be nice
never mind
never mind then
um
i will take some
take some blocks here
and close that window or maybe just open
maybe just open one of it
why is it stopping there okay
consider glass yeah i don't have glass
it's gotta be fine without glass
see you never in the level you know
listen you know because this is actually
another stop
this is i think where the copper
expresses
so at least you would kind of see ah the
window starts here and that's where the
copper express is yeah
but maybe not
maybe better
if we just close it all up
[Music]
da
let's go
put windows in a high level ah
true
but kiwawa has other things to do that
are more important now
[Music]
oh
sora go go there
okay
okay we have arrived in the meso biome
whilst these stairs are terrible founded
this design who was it
who made this shitty design
looks like crap
hello
danger zone
oh god oh god
what did he just
go through
why do the enemies go through an instant
and we have to like load in
i mean i knew that was coming but i
don't know
oh there he is there he goes
my portals
the martin area
um
oh [\h__\h] i didn't bring a boat uh no i
did bring a boat apparently
oh
is it this way
i think so
[Music]
infinite that's what i thought
is that infinite obsidian
[Music]
um
i have a feeling we're gonna have
troubles finding what i'm looking for
today as well
um
wish me luck
proud to walk over magama
yeah i know i don't know
another boat
if i ever ask for boats
they are here you know what i'll bring
one actually we might need one
[Music]
ah
okay
let's see uh there should be a and
they're just here
[Music]
you need to splunk more caves you mean i
need to explore more caves
is that what that means
but it's so scary going into those
and then
i need to dig like
really really low
and i won't even know if there's like
you know something there anyway but okay
um if we have trouble finding one of
those trees again
then we gotta check out some caves
yeah
using a texture pack for the leaves to
make them stand out
sure is is that something i can do
quickly
[Music]
okay what what tips do you guys have to
make it stand out isn't there also like
um
another way to do it
that's
[Music]
it how do you how do you install
textures i've never done that before
wait
let me try to find it
[Music]
take a cat to avoid creepers if i could
i would bring a cat everywhere
in real life as well
what did you think of that
[Music]
drop them in the texture pack folder
they do stand out what's beautiful
it do be beautiful
very pink the whole tree is like a a
bright pink that will make it a lot
easier i think
um
so
do i drop the
the only the mc meta file or the whole
folder
oh
wait a second the folder
uh drag and drop files into this window
uh-huh
selected open
dragon drag and drop
it should be a zip file oh
oh is it okay if i just leave it as a
dip
do not extract ah okay that's the way i
gonna hide the screen for a moment i
don't know what it will show
oh
oh wait it's that easy
[Music]
yes
did it work because now it's not here
you just saw me cooking yes right
do i have to
open the game again
is that it
drop open
wait
push
[Music]
open it
my
[Music]
open pack folder then drop the tip into
it
yes it's fun party in a bossa noble
remix
it's whole live songs only that i'm
playing at the moment
[Music]
okay i reopened the game
uh options resource packs but isn't it
supposed to show up then now here
[Music]
huh
and available it doesn't show up still
well it still doesn't show up
oh well someone said do not unzip it do
i have to unzip it after all wait but it
isn't oh it is in resource packs now
like in minecraft when i go to the
minecraft folder it's in the resource
packs
or do i need to unzip it in in the
minecraft resource packs
okay okay okay
i unzipped it
wait a second
[Music]
kind of confused
when i click open pack folder it opens
it opens a
windows window
where it's uh the directory of minecraft
slash resource packs and it shows it
shows that azalea
the cherry blossom recolor is in there
but like
what do i do then
huh
[Music]
but like when i do this
then i say yes
um
i'll i'll do one more restart
i did
i did it zipped and i did it unzip
and both just
say do you want it in here i say yes
should wait
restarting game
restarting game um
[Music]
uh minecraft
don't worry guys this will be worth it
because it will make things easier
it's a shade another shader is it it's a
great color
or texture pack a texture pack
[Music]
multiplayer
it still doesn't show it here
it still
looks like this
isn't it supposed to show up here like
all the resource packs that i have
which is zero for now but oopsie
[Music]
um dragon and i'm gonna tip to that
menu
just what's inside of it
if it's in the recent spring it is
unzipped
go out of the pause menu and go back in
alternatively you can try it and open it
from the pause menu
pause menu you mean
[Music]
here options resource packs it's not
there
please pack files here
here yes
take it yes sir done
is it done
[Music]
it's not working why it's not working
for grandma aren't you
click programmer art
what
[Music]
it has to be one folder if it's a folder
then it won't work huh
[Music]
orange super jet
the zip doesn't work when dragged only
works if your tracks extract the folder
inside the zip somewhere first
and drag that folder
okay wait so do i delete it again out of
the minecraft thingy and then let's
extract the folder
inside the dip somewhere first and drag
it fold it
i feel like i've done that too
[Music]
and i'm doing it again right now
yeah i did it again
because i i dragged it from the download
uh
folder
not a zipped one i dragged a folder that
i unzipped in the download folder
into the game
and then when i click open pack folder
it opens uh the windows directory of
minecraft resource packs and now it's in
there again
as a as a
as an unzipped
folder
maybe it just doesn't work
resource pack your download is not the
same version
well yeah the the recolor is 1.17
and mine is 1.18
it's like below does it have to be the
exact same version
is there an 18
i don't think there is an 18.
[Music]
um
let me see
there's only 17
what about this one
research back have to be the same
version
but then how wait but like
azalea trees only showed up since
18.
how come the pack is for 17.
[Music]
outdated would still show in the list
quit game
open game minecraft
oh they were already in 17 oh okay but i
guess just not lush caves
ah
[Music]
i need an updated version
wait even if it shows up are you gonna
tell me it's just not gonna work anyway
or is there a chance it could work
there's no need for it to be the exact
same version okay i hope that is true
options
it's still not in there yo is there any
other maybe like 1.18 minecraft
recolor of um
as a
azalea
tree
[Music]
azalea minecraft texture packs
um
cubed what the hell is that azalea boats
what better asalia
but these are all not that obvious
there's
i want that one to work
[Music]
azalea border optifine
oh
overlay optifine border overlay
is this this is not a resource pack
right
oh no it's a texture how does this work
doesn't say anything about no it does
say 18.
how to install minecraft resource packs
sorry guys we'll get it done
uh
[Music]
um
resource packs
[Music]
open resource pack
oh azalea border
what i don't get it
yes
that one worked
[Music]
that one is working
i put it immediately shows up so i think
the other one is just it has an issue
somehow
the other one just has some kind of
problem then that i
i
have no way of
dealing with
but wait do i have to
you have to move it from the left side
to the right side
or is it is it fine now if it's an
available drag and drop files into the
window to add
how do i
make it work
yahoo
there it is
[Music]
so now
this this one i have
the other one didn't like
oh
that's okay this one hopefully
will make it easier to so supposedly now
there will be a border
around it
oh let me see there's what does it look
like a stair sample
ah
it's it's pretty shiny
[Music]
it is pretty shiny
pretty
i think it stands out
go to inna's house well now i'm here
now i'm all the way here now i don't
want to go back there
we're going to fly now
saturday
i will
[Music]
leave some things here maybe
no
i don't need to
i'll wait
put that in there
[Music]
okay
now
finally we will find a lush cave
should we still go the same direction or
should we go like left this time i feel
like i want to go a different direction
[Music]
where should i go
chords i have the coordinates from here
try a completely different area
okay then we go straight left
i hope i have enough fireworks but this
time i don't think we need to spend so
many if if the azalea tree really is
that obvious
we're going we're going east now
[Music]
east
okay mountains
the azalea train as far as i know could
be anywhere and for people who don't
know the reason why we're looking for
azalea tree
is because
by the way is it from any distance
is because for the new lunch caves they
might be
um anywhere um even in already spawned
territories
uh but they would be difficult to find
because you have to go underneath and
just be lucky by mining under
wherever
yeah you want to mine
that's a lot of ocean
uh but in
um territories that you have not
my shield oh
oh
territories that you have not yet
explored
um azalea trees might spawn
and
uh that will be a sign
a single a single answer entry that
might be the sign that underneath uh
there is a
lush cave
my shield
okay
[Music]
i don't have to activate shaders or sell
it right
for the resource pack
it will just show
right
[Music]
it has been a while
i just haven't really played minecraft
recently but it's been a while oh no
since it has been updated at our servers
[Music]
there's some pink flowers
it's kind of sus but that's not it
[Music]
mountains mountains everywhere oh that's
a cool cave that looks familiar that's
not the cave that we checked out before
right no way horsey
oh village
am i still going east yes kind of
village village
i feel like i've been in this village
before but every village looks the same
to me
it could even be up at the very top of a
mountain right
[Music]
east east
this is definitely new chunks okay
i believe you wow
lots of
lots of flowers blue and yellow
amisame titty
oh
that's loading in pretty slowly
oh sheet
uh is it really that rare what the hell
would i see it from so far away
with the border
did someone ever tried it out before
what do you mean clickbait
you can see my cleavage the same way
it's in the thumbnail right now
you should be able to okay
i don't clickbait
i would never do such a thing
why is there nothing
nina
silly
wow
nice fountain guys
[Music]
i'm i'm
purposefully flying around um
uh
in a in a
curvy way
hoping
to
um
cover a big area
by the way is this you guys did you guys
see
me and emma
hanging on twitter today
and were you wondering why why we were
listening to each other's
noises
we were just uh
recording or like waiting to record
something
so we were in discord together with the
girls just waiting waiting
i was during the waiting time i'm going
to show this something cool
[Music]
in here too it could be anywhere
i think
[Music]
glad it was a fun time um
it was um
[Music]
it was
yeah it was fun
uh
we didn't get to record what we wanted
to record so
it was just us waiting and just uh yeah
[Music]
but but the waiting time was so fun
yeah we have to record another time holy
[\h__\h] those are some thick trees what's
wait oh that's all that's
all right what do what are those
victories again what the [\h__\h] is that oh
oh it's burning
huh
[Music]
i thought it was
some tree on fire
[Music]
target acquired oh interesting place it
is in it's like
looks
weird
[Music]
i wonder if i would have seen that if i
didn't have it on let me turn it up and
see it how obvious it looks
[Music]
oh
it stands out a little bit i suppose
but that's what the [\h__\h] is this shape
that's that's very nice that we found it
in this forest
one of those trees again isn't this dark
wood
yes dark oak love logo
okay then
let's
build
a headquarter i suppose
should i bring my bed down
share some leaves off
ah for like later
wow
wow oh pretty leaves
i'll take all of them
you will be no more you won't be another
tree anymore yeah oh let's uh
oh no it's all good all good
will it grow back
i forgot do trees like this grow back
uh i want those
leave that above ground
if you say so
you always make my day really i'm happy
to hear that thank you three waves don't
curl back oh
oh
[Music]
am i imagining this or do new
new flowers keep on popping up though
this tree is weird
[Music]
okay
i think this cave is really far away
from
uh
home
so
i don't know if the girls really want to
come here if they're looking for a lush
cave but i will share the coordinates
with them
and we will now
go inside i will take this i guess and i
will
leave my fireworks i think
i'm gonna leave
i'll leave all this here
yes
if i can
[Music]
we will never hide away from myself
never fast travel yeah but like we
didn't go completely straight so it's a
bit mutsukashi
to
meet the
the kiara ice express
i can try eventually not this is not our
goal today
maybe eventually
in the future but not today
okay
okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
oh i don't have many torches
cheat
do i need more
well
we will hopefully
uh not need more
okay
bring extra extra coal we'll probably
mine some coal
now what do i do do i just dig down
or i should dig um uh stairs right
stairs
don't think that will be how would you
know how would you know
oh
yes
yes yes my elytra my elytra put it put
it there
bro my wings
it will probably open into a big cabin
oh
yes i'll try to be careful
[Music]
okay
i'm scared
oh they did some ground work for me
alrighty
oh it's raining
and we found shelter immediately is that
my silk touch no okay
okay i guess i'll just keep on going in
circles because i don't want to go like
too far
um
like if i just stick straight because i
have to go pretty low all right what was
that
where's the level
that it's gonna be on
and also stand on two blocks and dig
down
oh uh you know what i'll make a
one
one block stare
i although i'm not used to it so my
fingers are a little bit
like what are you doing
[Music]
uh lush caves are usually huge even if
you do straight staircase you can still
hit oh but what if i'm just by accident
digging in the exact wrong
uh direction like what if there was a
huge lush cable over there but i'm just
going the other way
i don't want that to happen
why am i doing this properly
i think i am
sashimi
why does it feel so weird doing a one
block
staircase i'm gonna go this way
[Music]
what did you guys do today by the way
although if you're from like an n a time
zone you probably didn't really do much
at all
[Music]
what did you do
i just woke up good morning sunshine
woke up to watch me ah
isn't that the best thing to wake up to
play pokemon
oh
i see um yeah
something that's difficult to work with
it should be below this right
uh hello uh
yeah it's not a lush cave
[Music]
i don't want to go down there
there's a lot of enemies there
is this the last cave it's below it i
think
work then pokemon archaeos shoveling
snow oh
[Laughter]
where are you
showing yourself
[Music]
can i also be in sunshine you are
big left i feel like i should dig left
yeah
i wanted to do that too
i'm not happy with that place
oh dirt what the hell
water
why is there
where's the water
why am i so confused about it water is
not that uncommon in caves is it
uh
oh
that's a good sign
third means lush cave
so if i swim down there you think i
might
find it
wait a second
what if i'm gonna drown i'm gonna drown
i'm gonna drown i'm gonna
[Music]
i'm gonna drown i'm gonna drown
keep digging
what for the
scared
i'm scared i'm scared i'm scared
i want to drown
[Music]
pockets in the ceiling what's that mean
huh
[Applause]
[Music]
make a door
a door
door
[Music]
foreign
door
did i not bring the door i should have
brought a door with me
well now we have free doors
[Music]
should i just do
you should be scared cave diving is
really dangerous yeah i thought so
like what if i do
dive enough and i can't find a spot to
brave in but i guess that's when i just
placed the door
but
don't i have to go sorry i'm really like
freaking out but don't i have to go
lower
don't i have to go
lauren is where are we
43 like is it even normal to have
something that high oh my god
how will i even find back
oh there's some light
well towards the light yeah i feel like
i saw light is there is that light i
can't swim so well i can't swim so well
i'm really bad at
diving
in my crab
please don't do this
dig up and make a hole to breathe
[Music]
copper
oh that's not it what is the wrong side
ain't going going
[Music]
okay i'm braving i'm breathing
um is this it
[Music]
is this my lunch cave
no that's not my luscious
there's so much water i don't like it
how will i find back
come on
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] what a sound
leave a bed mine around
follow the third trail i don't see their
treasure
[Music]
i need to go down
why is it gonna be like that
mine around it around one or one around
wood
around that
uh
yeah
i don't quite understand what you mean
with digger around there like the water
won't go away
is there any way to get into it without
going through the water
oh you mean dig around from here
let me see see i found i i probably went
i chose i chose the wrong path i should
dig
a different way this is probably what
it's telling me maybe this is better
oh cool nicer
[Music]
oh that's a lot of coal oh my it's a
cold gold mine
cold mine
[Music]
all right all right we got some coal
sorry guys i'm being such a chicken
about this right now i don't want to die
with my never rat pickaxe you know i'm
really scared about that
uh
[Music]
i want to be extra careful
such a noob man it's been so long i used
to be so
so
confident in minecraft
no no don't know where that went
oh by the way if you were wondering
because i asked you guys what what you
were doing i today didn't really do much
i personally just got up
uh had some breakfast
which was cake again pound cake that i
had um
and then i got ready for the recording
that didn't happen
uh i waited
waited for that i was like on standby
[Music]
and i waited and i waited
and then it didn't happen then i chilled
a little bit with my cats
[Music]
oh i love guna nagan i don't know why
you're mentioning it but i love it
and
then i cleaned my apartment a little bit
yeah because someone will be taking care
of my um cats while i'm gone
and
i gotta clean it a bit more than that
maybe i should turn around now
should i just go this way
how low are we now 42 again okay
oh is this good too is gravel good as
well
gravel gravel
is gravel good sign
[Music]
no
no gravel not good
[Music]
um
okay yeah grab
oh
what's that thunder
holy [\h__\h]
that's so loud
wow
[Music]
i hope nothing's burning down out there
i've never heard thunder in minecraft
before today
did they have that in 118 or has fonda
always been around and i was just lucky
to not be struck by thunder
[Music]
[\h__\h] gravel [\h__\h] gravel
almost killed me
plastics
[Music]
fonda has always been around
i know that's how inna's house caught on
fire but you know because it never
happened to me before
um
[Music]
monsters all kinds of sounds man the
ambient sounds i need to turn them down
they're [\h__\h] scaring me
freaking me out
it was always a problem until copper
rods are added but i legit i swear i
never i never heard thunder before in
minecraft and i played my fair share of
minecraft until now
[Music]
maybe i was just lucky
it's because sparks like the flavor
how you can learn
physics or science
in
with takanashi kiwawa's original songs
so sparks light the flame
and turn the dark of the night and today
i mean i wouldn't quite say that the
thunder
turns uh the night in today
just just for a moment perhaps
i think i'm fine i found it but the
sounds are scary
oh there's some spikes i found it though
i found it i found it
[Music]
[Laughter]
and my inventory is already full
shut up it's so scary
oh weather off
better that that will turn off the
thunder right
okay now we need to get ready to fight
because there's some i hear monsters
[Music]
why is there
why do i hear
skeletons burning
oh my god
oh my god oh my god oh my god
[Music]
should i turn on my shaders
what is that
is
wow
i'm gonna lose i'm gonna lose where i
came from
oh
you're here too but no other enemies
because it's too bright for them huh
[Music]
okay i don't know if that's like just
normal size or really big but
i think it's normal size right probably
don't don't fight me is this where it
came
[Music]
oh from you go away i'm just trying to
look at where it came from
oh god okay you're really
dangerously situated right now
oh god is this yeah this is where it
came from
i
think he's dancing
he's also happy that i found the lush
cave
[Music]
oh i don't know where to start
i want to loot it
oh
[Music]
oh you're coming from that dark
split
in the in the in the cave oh oh hello
what the [\h__\h] up what the [\h__\h] are you
what are you
you're a witch what what is you
oh hi hi andy you could help me maybe
check out like what's up there
[Music]
oh
a zombie villager oh
koi i don't want to fall down there let
me let me place my [\h__\h]
oh
oh my god okay
and i'll drop some stuff
here
i don't need this oh rooted dirt do i
need that
it comes after me
let's drop it into the water here
some german please no
i refuse
you have some rocks
don't work in you
iran i'm on the road
merge coal
keep rooted dirt what does root of dirt
do bit useful for building pops
how
how or so
[Music]
and the man's just vibing screenshot
cords
okay got it got it
beautiful it's so green it's so lush
here of these little tiny look at that
what in
little tiny baby bush here
flowering would that turn into a tree
or does it always stay this tiny do i
have to mine it with a
so touched right
[Music]
oh
flowering azalea that turns into that's
a sapling wow wow wow oh it's so cute
it's so small
kawaii
should i bring these ones too
that is uh just azalea
ah there's flowering and non-flowering
ones huh
and we'll become a tree of your bone
melon
does it need to be on a moss uh
block
[Music]
oh hello i saw you
andy spain
are you having fun and the man
[Music]
also a lot of clay
take the moss yeah yeah okay okay
you get the saplings from that
what saplings from the moss
[Music]
um
which ones are the most most blocked
moss moss carpet once
boss block was book
[Music]
oh
i'll just take everything i see right
now
yes this is pecoranda
[Music]
when you bone meal moss you can make
anzale can i also make the flowering
ones though
we found that moss burger oh i love mug
bird you guys know mom's burger
know what that is
fast food chain tank a chain
chain
that we also have to destroy because
it's too delicious we have to destroy
every fast food chain that
is too delicious
much better yes they have good burgers
they have like huge tomato slices in
their burgers
which i think is awesome because
sometimes when i order like my favorite
burger crispy chicken from burger king
they actually almost always only have
like really tiny tomato sauces in there
but i want the tomato slice to cover the
whole burger you know what i mean it's
just not enough
are they high quality yeah they the ones
from mars burger i don't know they they
taste
they're big and they look good
i love tomatoes
um
oh
i need this too right
berries but cronie already has a lot of
them i think
i will replace it with some light here
it's not too dark
did you guys see um
piccolo senpai or do i cut it uh
differently
i cut it with my scissors right
you guys see piccola senpai
no not what this is um
[Music]
doesn't change anything
uh eating
uh her stream today was about eating
carrots
[Music]
and i was just like
she had this supposedly ambitious goal
of eating free carrots
holy [\h__\h]
that's like a million of them
oh where's my where's my boat
[Music]
oh now they're fighting each other nice
yes
but i was like i [\h__\h] love carrots
free carrots is no challenge and aren't
you supposed to be a rabbit
aren't you supposed to be a rabbit
are you supposed to like
like
uh carrots
okay
where the [\h__\h] did they all come from
yeah
i know she doesn't like carrots but i
kind of get it because i feel like um
when i ate carrots in japan before i
noticed a difference in taste
they taste in japan they taste like
not as sweet
so but i still can totally eat them
maybe oops [\h__\h]
maybe raw
is where the problem is at
i was thinking you know i wanted to
counter her
i own i almost want to counter her with
a stream where i eat a hundred carrots
but it makes no sense because i'm not
supposed to be a rabbit but i like
carrots and i feel like eating free
carrots is just not a challenge
that's not a challenge
but maybe i could eat maybe i could send
her yummy carrots from europe i don't
know that's impossible probably but
but maybe she would have more joy
more joy with the
carrots from europe
can't eat them raw but i like them with
fried rice
in the curry they taste delicious i'm
sure pico de santa has no problem with
eating them in a curry
oh hello lapis lazuli
oh cute
oh my inventory is full
what are these sounds is that the the uh
lights thingies
there's an upper level above that
i don't necessarily like need i don't
know what what do i need i need some
moss blocks i need some trees just to
have some stuff you know there was no
particular other reason why i really
felt like i needed
this stuff
like i'm not like planning on building
anything particular
but but i want those
glowberries
[Music]
drip leaf ah yeah i think i already have
drip leaves though oh [\h__\h] where did i
come from did i come from here
no
no i didn't
no it didn't
there are no treasures in here though
right
[\h__\h] where did that come from here
[Music]
here here
i just want to bring some of this stuff
home and then i'm already satisfied drip
leaf was this strip leaf
yes big drip leaf how is there a
specific way i should uh
how i should
take this home with a scissor or
[Music]
smack it punch it
punch it
no i want the dribbling
okay got it
do
um they like if you place one do more of
them grow
[Music]
yummy
another one of you where's my bowl again
but that's not mine
oh stop
i have
now experience in fps games in real fbs
games so you guys are no match for me i
mean you never were but
uh that's my chocolate box
if you use bonemeal
all right so let's see we have steve's
moss blocks i don't need more box blocks
to lie i'll i'll fill up this one
um
yeah hmm
don't i don't even know what i want to
do with that stuff but hey we now have
an easy way to find more
and
yeah i guess i'll go get some more of
those
uh drip leaves maybe
[Music]
dig straight up you mean when going back
is that a smart thing to do
oh what about this do i need these oh
that's clay oh
oh let's go
[Music]
i always felt like making clay was
annoying
i already forgot why you guys told me i
need clay
i don't even know the reason anymore
[Applause]
hello
for bricks oh true that's that would be
helpful
oh god oh they're coming here because
it's getting darker and darker
and there's sensing and i'm here
[Applause]
that's that's too much already uh
clay clay clay clay clay clay
coal coal
proper copper
the light is fading
indeed
do you really need this
[Music]
i didn't even need that much food
i didn't need most of the things i
brought once again
let me get this done
some more of those little trees
do they
do they provide different kind of wood
izalia wood does it is that the pink one
is that the pinkish wood
cause that's exciting i want to build
something with the pink wood
spore blossom
mr
that's boring
oh
pink wood i guess i meant jungle wood
what is that glow lichen lighten
lighting
[Music]
here
uh
you guys come out of nowhere
you know i have a weak heart
i might have a
uh a good um uh oh god doctor coming for
me
resting heart rate uh
but my heart is still very weak when it
comes to bamboozles
okay no more of that
are we good
guys should i take anything else
books per minute
[Music]
okay
oh thank god i have endless arrows
unlimited sport i wonder what the one is
that what is that what is that where's
the sport blossom how do i take it
[Music]
how do i take a spore blossom
[Laughter]
oh my god
uh it's a pink flower on the ceiling
pink flower on the ceiling
you found the ceiling
giant pink flower where did andy go by
the way did he get killed by all the
monsters
what would that be
[Music]
okay
uh
there are no sport blossoms here oh is
it only in like certain caves
[Music]
take your
what
[Music]
i can take them
what was that
[Music]
wait oh oh
they like caves
easiest absolutely ever yeah things just
come to me when i'm not looking for them
i can only have one per bucket though i
don't have the iron
oh [\h__\h]
how do you take them
i didn't
oh
wow wow
[Music]
i have a new pet
wow
[Music]
it's so nice in here
it's always like on a date but
i go back i go back i'm scared i don't
see one of those flowers that you guys
are talking about either
[Music]
oh there's some iron here um
gosh those arrows in my head they hurt
[Music]
oh wait when i when the iron comes out
like that
what's that we're gonna do it do i have
to burn it
melt it smell it oh no he wants to come
with his friend
i need another bucket
a lovely date so far rimley i'm sorry i
don't have much to talk about today
but you can always ask me things guys if
you feel like
you have something on your mind
you smelt you have to smelt it right
[\h__\h] whatever i just
ah should i take it should i do the
effort
how do i smelt [\h__\h] again
why did i i bring some iron
[Music]
how does your fruit feel oh i don't know
it's okay
i'm okay
don't worry so much about it furnace
oh cobblestone
that's too much effort
it's too much effort one is enough which
one is the rare one
i suppose not this color that i have
blue was it a blue one
[Music]
i run
it's only eight blocks of cobblestone
[Music]
okay
blue is rare
i like the the one that i have though i
like the i like the white one remember
when axel wrote oh she when they first
came out and people
the japanese girls were like going so
crazy over them
everyone was farming axolotls like crazy
one thing that i can say is that these
whole life girls
once they have gun powder once they have
something
that caught their interest they go
really really hard on it
they won't let go yeah kind of doesn't
but
like fubu krishna there's so many very
very passionate girls
uh is
impressive
maybe
maybe um you guys can use that as
inspiration for your life and now it's
arc and pokemon
shiny hunting yeah
i'm i don't really like that like kind
of uh stuff what am i looking for
smelter
uh
burner cooker
what's it called again
furnace thank you my brain is a bit
slow today
[Music]
uh so
hello bet
there we go making some iron oh i wanted
to pick that up
and dance
every single one counts
[Music]
how's it going
i need three for a bucket i think if i
remember correctly
ah there we go
[Music]
let's let's get him we found an
actual logo we might as well hello
bring it with us
whoops what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] die [\h__\h] die already
i'm mad all of you
huh
i just hope i can bring it home safely
are you here still what
there it is
it's too dangerous here there's no food
like how the [\h__\h] would you get food
here
they're pretty aggressive right i heard
that these axolotls
are pretty aggressive
[Music]
did i already put it in my in my chest
they don't look this cute in real life
though i think
[Music]
there we go
is good i'm still looking for axolotls
[Music]
oh
they kind of do what they look cute you
mean they're cute in real life wait
wait
[Music]
axolotl
no
i call a lot of things cute
with if i'm being very nice i guess i
could say that looks cute
but the nakedness
is just very creepy to me
naked is very very creepy to me
eh the baby is there oh is it what it's
what look
it's an animal they're all naked well
but
they don't look
well they don't have um what do you call
it
like normally fish have
chopin uh scales i don't know
and uh
isn't this supposed to be a fish
it doesn't have scales looks weird
yeah
freaking me out
anyway
um i guess we're done here i'm i'm
already satisfied this doesn't have to
be an endless super long stream um i'm
gonna make our way back of course and
maybe chill around a little bit more but
mostly
[Music]
the mission of the day has been
accomplished
when the pies are not on fish they're
amphibians
yeah they also don't really look like
fish so that makes a lot of sense yes
yes yes
but yeah they look creepy because i
guess because they're not fish they look
creepy
um all right all right i guess i'll go
i guess i'll go
if i find my way back that is
uh
where i entered from where
i entered from
good question
what's it was it here ah thank you
[\h__\h] where where
oh where
where i don't see him
ah
yeah come closer you little coward
come here
let me kill you
all right i'll run around one dig up
should i just dig up
who says here that i should just dig
straight up who's for
digging straight up and who's for going
back the same way i came from
make another bucket
um
[Music]
don't take a dig up
up dig up digging up digging up
a staircase
i hope i will find my
yeah it shouldn't be too difficult right
to find my my my headquarters up there
okay i'll
dig up um
here maybe
what no no
why don't i just go where where it came
from
i'll i'll give it a try
i feel like
i feel like that's just me asking for
trouble if i dig all the way up
[Music]
yeah look that way that's so much easier
why do i need to dig up if i have this
path
did you guys think i was already so far
away from my from my uh stairs
there we go
[Laughter]
[Music]
this is easier
all right
i hope the thunder and the rain has
stopped by now
oh oh it's daytime
[Music]
a little adventure but i think this time
we were already much more
effective than last time
hell yeah
and now we just put in
this
this boy
went
into the ender chest
because we got we got circles and we got
all this cool stuff yo we got some upa
lupa's axolotls the reason i say
apopaluca is because in japanese they're
called upadupo and it kinda ingrained
itself in my brain more
beautiful progression
[Music]
what was i gonna do
i'm like so useless today
brain melted uh
put this
in here take this take fireworks
[Music]
there was a mob spawner right where your
stairs ended oh
you mean in the bottom how do you know
did you see it
[Music]
it did feel
weirdly dangerous
build a tower
i can do that if i have some materials
[Music]
should i build a sand tower
the question is not how i'm going to get
down
get down
[Music]
okay
i love to get done it reminds me so much
of like nostalgic times
from many many years ago when it was a
meme on nico nicole doga
it was a big fun meme
everybody was like making funny videos
yeah i wanted
i want to make one now too
but i feel like it's a bit late to jump
on that meme
but
maybe maybe
maybe when i get 3d
maybe i can make a video
in my 3d body make a lot of sexy poses
and crazy poses and get down
okay i will
build a tower
level
[Music]
there we go that's much better
yes i have it it's here
[Music]
what's around here
is there like a witch's house somewhere
that would be cool um doesn't look like
it
at least not from here
gosh this is scary
i don't want to go up so high is this
enough is this high enough
[Music]
oh that was swamps but but the the
mansions are in places like these right
our mansion adventure was so much fun
conquering the big big mansion
porch on top yes that i wanted to do
that i indeed wanted to do that that's
why i brought some dirt
oh god oh god i'm so scared
the woodland mansion yeah that's what
i'm talking about i didn't mean the
witch's house
okay now kiwama fly
if you can
[Music]
sometimes when i'm nervous and under
pressure i have some problems with
starting
um the flight you know
tamarind and kimchi
thank god it was so close
[Laughter]
no problem no need to worry everybody i
am i'm a phoenix i immediately revive
from my own ashes hallelujah
hallelujah
[Music]
what pressure the pressure from all of
you watching me
stupid tower
uh
okay
um
what am i doing what am i thinking
i'll put this here
[Music]
okay
shall we go
shall we go home should i leave my bed
here
i'll bring it with me
[Music]
remove shield to fly what
you're saying i couldn't fly because of
my shield that makes no sense take the
energies yes yes of course uh
[Music]
touch stay touched
okay ready to go
nice
uh the coordinates something around wait
no we're not going home we're going to
the mesa biome headquarters
uh
let me get the
[Music]
hornets for that
shield thing is a myth
shield has blasted you need a bigger
platform to build a momentum
that's that's what it felt like i didn't
have enough momentum
[Music]
coordinates are
about
here uh
and i think 1000
no ten thousand eight hundred
oh
ooh
so three hundred
sixty free
and
thank you
i feel like another one's coming soon
yeah everywhere
oh did i just type that as a comment
where did it go there it is
message
pin it
pin it to the top
beautiful
thank you guys for saying it always in
german
if you are curious to learn more german
tomorrow i have a members only stream
where i teach my chimpkins my members
jenkins
some german
well basically it should be west right
this way
[Music]
300 now i'm good huh
you don't want to educate yourself
i want a treasure hunt
oh in the treasure no bad kia wawa
bad kiwawa no treasure hunting oh
i will never learn to excuse me what a
rebel chimpkin you are look what i found
[Music]
as if we didn't already have enough oh
now my inventory is full
damn
nice gold block
and obsidian crying obsidian
i don't have space um let's get rid of
that
[Music]
okay
i'll take the crying obsidian
crying obsidian
i've said german for several reasons
remember none of this
yeah that's how i feel about
other languages
that i've tried like italian oh i
remember a little bit and i really
didn't actually learn italian for that
long
i learned it for three years but only
two months
per year because
i had a really weird school system for a
while
uh
so i actually really didn't get that
much practice in and considering that
it's in total just six months i am
actually quite surprised
uh that i still remember
quite a lot of it
yeah yeah
i was the best italian student in my
class
of course that surprises no one because
you can hear that from my oh beautiful
italiano
mamma mia
no need for a dolly if you're italian
i'm going to do it when
[Music]
west
no italian is very helpful if you travel
to italy i would say
i think like from my experience in italy
not so many people but it depends on
where you go
if you go to like a some kind of not
extremely popular
beach place and it would be helpful to
know some italian
and if you know some italian you might
also understand some spanish
can't speak italian if you don't move
your hands
that is true
you need to feel the passion
although like one thing i've noticed or
i've been told
when living in japan
people
japanese people often pointed out that i
move my hands
a lot when i talk and i don't even think
that i really move it that much
but i guess we're japanese yeah hello
this is so scary can you load for once
oh my god
quit
uh
[\h__\h] this this way
[Music]
um
what was i saying oh yeah
they told me that my gestures
are very
big and strong but i think that's in
general not an italian thing but in
general european or just western thing
i think americans probably move their
hands as much as i do
um
it's just not even that much just just a
a little bit
i'm very much a gesturing type of guy
that's fine i think that's fun
um but then
the other way around after living a
while in japan coming back to austria
all the people in austria have been
telling me
um
already years ago
that i
um
now adapted some japanese mannerisms
whoa let's fly through that
ah
where am i going this way
it was dangerous yeah
um bowing my head a little bit yes i
could still mostly hold back on that but
the the bigger thing was
and i still do that this is one thing
that i
i can never
no don't don't don't get distracted
i can never stop doing
the following thing
[Music]
oh don't look don't look cuba
it's not good for your heart
uh uh where am i going oh my god west
west coast oh
wow wow
uh
and it's like when i listen to someone i
always go like hmm
[Music]
like after
like about five words i always go hmm
just to let the other person know that
i'm listening
really just
sounds
i guess similar to that
villager sounds down
um
[Music]
i can't stop doing it
horses
[Music]
and sometimes i notice myself doing it
a bit too much and then it kind of gets
a little bit embarrassing
uh 300
[Music]
okay
westerners don't do that nobody does it
here i'm sure there's like maybe
other cultures where people do that
but in austria
no one which actually after coming back
from japan really feels lonely like
sometimes i wonder are you actually are
you even listening to what i'm saying yo
i i do doubt it sometimes what is that
what is that what is that what is that
what's that
is that just not not of my interest not
of my interest
yeah i start doubting if people are even
listening to me sometimes
this one
this one somewhere this way 300
this way
and you guys are listening you guys are
telling me you're listening by answering
in the chat but when i like talk to real
people
and they don't do that
um
they don't do that
makes me feel anxious i feel like i'm
talking to a wall
i'm kind of here um
almost i'm so close i feel it
oh
don't dive into the lava
[Music]
i wasn't lost here
it's on my own
[Music]
about 10 000.
well i guess i might as well just
straight fly to i didn't leave anything
here did i i might as well just fly
straight to the portal oh wait the
portal is there but oh oh oh oh
anyway
hi
toku
perfectly timed my friends
perfectly done quick bed
oh
oh well
um
that's not gonna happen
excellent landing captain you're welcome
airlines
uh gold golden armor oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] i
don't know where it is can we do it
without
[Music]
of course we can we'll be fine we'll be
fine we'll be fine run
[Music]
there was no particular reason by the
way why i chose that price it was very
random
if you're quick i'll be quick
entrance to this ice way it's
immediately by the gate so i think i'll
be fine
i'm scared i'm so scared i'm so scared
i'm so scared i'm so scared
what a deal
oh
i i didn't have any other windows here
did i it was just that one big window
and i closed up now
[Music]
or turkey time you could call it turkey
time now just the one
so fast right so efficient
gas gas gas
speed speed
speed by the way
i've heard i've heard i've heard a rumor
that elena is doing a
a singing stream tomorrow
and that she is gonna sing sparks
[Music]
she's going to sing sparks
so keep an eye open for that or an
ear or an eye
or both of it
oh yeah that might be the whole theme
that she's singing uh whole live songs
perhaps
i did that before too
i wonder maybe she's going to sing and
she's probably going to sing an energy
song too
i love lena's singing voice she released
the song cover today i listened to it
she's so
so so lovely
[Music]
oh is that one gonna attack me
not if i escape first
yeah
oh hello oh don't go away
i wanted to talk to you you're gonna be
here after i wake up right
uh-huh
cinderella yeah i actually was thinking
of doing a song cover of cinderella too
but there's so many things i want to
cover right now so and i don't want to
put out more than one song cover per
month but you might get it eventually
from me as well
if you have oh
not a huddle
yeah
not interested thank you
though eventually
a cover salamander i listened to that
today
um i like the song but i think
[Music]
me singing it it has a lot of like very
short um
pronounced lyrics like
[Music]
you know what i mean
so it's not really something i would
choose to
sing in a song cover because i wanna i
wanna sing stuff that showcases my
singing voice a bit more you know you
know
all right we've arrived successfully
we've done the thing i will clean up on
another day i think this is just too
much [\h__\h] in my
in my inventory now
yay
[Music]
look at all that stuff some crying
obsidian wow i have six to four crying
obsidian
and i have no reason to use it
thank you yeah i need cronie to help me
yeah
cows
[Music]
got some good stuff
don't really know what to use it all for
i guess i'll use it for decorating well
what what other reason else is there for
azalea leaves huh
it's really just for decorating
a crown is pc i hope she can fix it yeah
[Music]
a lot of a lot of problems recently like
girls getting sick and girl's pc
breaking inna's internet like what's
happening
what's going on
[Music]
oh my god i feel like i'm gonna be the
next guys
i'm gonna be the next one
[Music]
hopefully
i feel like i've done i've had my fair
share of problems like that especially
in my first few weeks of whole life so
i would like to
refrain from that and take a break i
don't want to be
i don't want to be next i don't want to
be
[Music]
no it's true it's true
it might be cursed
whole life might be cursed
can i eat some snack
nick
i have mikado here the western pocket
oh i did i wanted to provide you with at
least one tangent that's still on my
tangent list
what i forgot i was too focused on the
coordinates
i i have a tangent guys
it feels so unnatural with me just
coming up i don't know where them leave
those for later nah later is super chat
dolls
so
i've noticed something
in my own private life
you know when you go to like a
any kind of store
and um
[Music]
and you
look a lot around a little bit and you
maybe show a little bit of interest but
you're just not sure
if you want to buy something
and then
and then maybe even the
whoever works at the store
comes up to you and you know tries to
talk you into buying something and
you're you're maybe even really
considering it
[Music]
but you're just not sure and you're
gonna say oh i'm gonna look around a
little bit more or
or i'm gonna look into the other stores
and come back or so
i've noticed that
there's too many times when
when
one says i am coming back to the store
owner even if you have good intentions
and you're really considering coming
back
way too often i think people just don't
come back and i wonder if if i say that
to a store owner they're probably
already thinking yo this [\h__\h] is lying
she's not coming back
even though i mean it sometimes
i feel so sorry about it but they they
probably immediately detect that it's a
lie and they're like shut up don't even
say that i don't want to hear it you're
not coming back but it's just like i
don't wanna you know i liked what you
had in your store i maybe don't like it
enough to really spend my money on it
but i just
i don't wanna
i don't wanna just walk out and be like
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h] i'm not buying anything
i i just wanna at least maybe i don't
know give him some hope or
or appreciate the stuff in the shop a
little bit
especially if they're like
if i'm like in a conversation with the
store owner
um
and and like
they're like trying to make me buy
something i don't want to just be like
no and leave
that feels rude like that's like as if
as if whatever you have in your story's
not interesting enough for me
i
i don't want to be like that
you know what i mean do you guys do that
too do you guys tell store owners uh
i'll come back
and then you never come back
that's so sad maybe they're waiting for
you like circles was waiting for me
speaking of they like apples right
i don't i think i forgot to take a photo
in the cave [\h__\h] well we have a photo in
circles at least
a pretty one
he doesn't need it do you like carrots
oh no now he's eating it
oh okay okay he doesn't there's no
animation of him eating it but
he ate it
i did so wait i do that sometimes i try
not to do that
never done it
what do you do you just
walk out like you don't care about the
store owner's heart
they like golden carrots
will you show me that he likes them
just browsing
[Music]
i don't like saying that either
i just in general i just prefer if shop
owners don't talk to me at all
but like especially in japan they're so
talkative
he's smelling the carrots he smells it
i think he really likes the the smell of
it oh see if i don't show it he's like
meh
put them carrots
on it oh
you're welcome i have a lot of them i
don't need them you eat them
ski the show
trevor
says people wait for me to come to them
yeah yeah yeah i mean for shy people
maybe it's maybe they prefer having them
talk to them because for me it's like
shut up don't talk to me unless i talk
to you
can i look at him from
here uh yes i slightly see a little
piece of circles
in his golden shining armor
my hero horse my heroes heroes
[Music]
today we were much more productive and
efficient actually
we were more efficient thanks to that um
thanks to the
ow ow
the outline the border
the border of the
azalea tree
ye
so we're gonna read super chats i guess
it feels so short what the [\h__\h] why is
this minecraft stream so although three
hours i guess that's
i guess that's uh a decent length
[Music]
we found circles lunch capes and uh
where do i bounce by i definitely want
to do that
um
ender dragon rematch underwater temple
i don't want to template something i
haven't done yet
[Music]
um
so weather the weather and the
underwater temple and i need more level
right armor that's something that i need
to do as well
[Music]
yeah maybe
maybe in springtime i can get the girls
to kill with her together with me or i i
doing it alone i'm not sure
i want to prove my
my existence as a gamer
[Laughter]
by killing the river alone
but we could still also kill it together
you can spawn the liver as often as you
want right
[Music]
river is a pretty intense fight alone i
wouldn't be alone i have i would have a
million bees just kidding i always say i
want to do it with the beast just
because i saw one video of someone
fighting with her with an army of bees
but i think that's really [\h__\h]
difficult to put together
[Laughter]
it's like millions of bees attacking the
wither
and a million and million yeah
[Music]
on the [\h__\h]
hello
[Music]
it's been so long that i played
minecraft and i feel weird about closing
it without saving
you guys ever had that feeling with
minecraft
it just feels wrong
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
all the time on nintendo switch yeah
you play games that do auto save for web
but speaking of nintendo switch
i now finally have
a micro sd card for my nintendo switch
let's go
i
i don't have to
continuously delete
games
in order to download another
for the past
year i always needed to have
um i was always only able to have
maximum one game or like two games on my
switch
at a time
i didn't have when i kept on deleting
whenever i wasn't playing at the time
until i needed uh for the next time
how big is the micros it's pretty big i
forgot i forgot but it was a pretty big
one i have more than enough space now
[Music]
it was so annoying to keep on doing
eating stuff
it might be the 128 gb and i i bought it
like from nintendo because i wasn't sure
if off-brand ones even work
because i have i have a feeling they're
doing something like apple is doing to
try to make uh things only work if you
buy it from their brand
[Music]
they do any anyone would work really
really
well what was the other thing was it the
internet the ethernet cable adapter that
only works if you get the one from
nintendo
[Music]
you got ripped off oh no i don't feel
ripped off it's fine it's kind of fun
[Music]
it might have been might have been the
ethernet cable i'm just completely
a generic adapter for even and it works
yeah
oh
oh well
at least i have it now yay
yay
yes all my games now have space
on my switch
[Music]
i can't wait to play pokemon the day
after tomorrow i stopped in a pokemon
tomorrow will be members only
um oh actually i have a recording
tomorrow as well
and like i have to get up at 9 30 uh
which is a good reason to end it early
today but i still read super chat don't
worry about it um but yeah i have to uh
i think i have to get up at nine
[Music]
a little bit more before 9 9 15 or so
i have a recording actually it's not
really a recording
it's like
i get together with some people to do
something
for something
[Laughter]
there's a lot of a lot of things yeah a
lot of things going on i've been
recording a lot in the past weeks and
months and everything is like for a
different purpose somehow
[Music]
yeah
dropping in snow not really
you will know you will know once it
comes
once it's like i don't know available
[Music]
it's all coming together mystery i'm a
mysterious woman
i have to keep some mysteries
but yeah
not looking forward to waking up so
early but i can take a nap afterwards
[Music]
thank you for the membership
my new song orange no no i don't have
such a song
my my currently in the works original
song doesn't have a thailand and also
doesn't have lyrics yet
um
[Music]
oh i can take the pink comment down
dinosaur thank you i always forget
welcome new egg egg or new bunny do you
like like carrots i love carrots
sorry for being so uh
careful
and annoying today
unnecessarily careful perhaps but
hey is it really unnecessary you saw me
dying when i tried to take off flying
i was
i was out of practice today
[Music]
it's been a while since my last
minecraft stream so i was out of
practice
yeah i don't want to say no
previous experiences of zen losu have
traumatized me
you did a good job adapting sparks in
japanese any chance you'll write some
for the new song ah me myself no
i know who i'll be asking for lyrics um
i want
i wanna try writing lyrics myself
eventually but
i feel like for the upcoming song i want
someone with experience to ride it
i don't want it to be a failure you know
lyric wise i want it to be good
i would need to like get a bit more
practice in i think before i do it
myself or like i could maybe co-write i
suppose but
um
[Music]
is japanese term for losing everything
yeah yeah that idea of me wanting to
write lyrics to audio stock tracks is
still
it's still a thing and also that rap um
battle
stream
i already talked to kelly about it a
while ago
but um yeah everyone's like very busy
right now first before we're doing that
um
we're doing the omo cat
fashion review
um probably by the end of february
because like i'm leaving now and then
kelly will be leaving for a while
um
she mentioned her her thing right i
don't want to say anything but i think i
heard her mention it
why she's she's gonna be gone for a
while i think she's mentioned it to her
viewers
yeah the surgery yes yes okay
yeah
and
so because of that it's still gonna take
a while but the longer the better to be
honest so that you guys still have time
to receive the omo
merchandise
[Music]
coordinator
still waiting on my stuff
well if it doesn't come in time it's
okay i'm still happy like every time
seeing it if you guys show me your
merchandise on on twitter so even after
the review you can still send it to me
on twitter and i'll give it a like
because i'm excited to see
when you guys receive your things
[Music]
got my stuff a few days ago yeah yeah so
many people have been
getting their things
so i think it's
time to do it
i'd like to join the omega review but i
didn't manage to buy all the things i
wanted
i hope i hope there's enough
people out there in the in the holo myth
fandom
who have the
courage to
show themselves of wearing
the the merchandise you don't have to
show your face you can censor your face
you can censor everything you want i
just want to see how you put together an
outfit
uh with the merchandise
[Music]
you know what also would be cute if
someone there were like a
uh keychains and were there badges too
were there badges
but you could like also make like a you
know those eater bags you could make a
bag
and like decorate it with a [\h__\h] ton of
keychains and [\h__\h]
and and buttons
badges and buttons
pins
[Music]
i have a myth
nice show me but it needs to be like
something with omocat so just add a few
things of from omaha cats
stuff
[Music]
i already made mine yo
thank you
acrylic stands i'm not sure how you
would use acrylic stands uh to implement
it in
in your
drip
but if you find a way to do it then
go for it
um
are you challenging me you can take it
as a challenge do it
don't wait
okay let's see
thank you for using the art as your um
profile picture
kiana's keyblade oh your name sounds
oddly familiar
oh what does this say here i'm very
excited for the inevitable heart attack
from the threat of zen lost this stream
i didn't have 10
once again
how many days we need we need one of
those counters
of we have gone so many days from zen
lasso
i think by now it would be quite a lot
of days
[Music]
i'll think about myself on maximum drip
you're thinking of participating i'm
excited
skip mine uh what do you mean i just
started
i don't see yours here
[Music]
maybe yours is like mixed somewhere else
i don't see it
did you even send us once yeah back in
the day and so a while ago
i was before pudding
i see i see it before pudding i only see
del star from the art in chat
[Music]
wait maybe maybe yours is like pushed up
higher for some reason
um
yeah i just started but um penetration
no uh i only have
did it go through
i only see them for the art and chat
stream that's i i looked with a strg
f
or ctrl f
i don't see any super jets from you here
weird
maybe it didn't actually go through
holo eliza shows it
well if you sent one petrochem duncan
was it a red or a pinky
or just uh something besides that if
it's a red one i'll send you a kiss
anyway
[Music]
nah
okay
and
neglected youtube play button thank you
soon son neglect that is showcased in my
apartment
he just said his birthday my giraffe oh
oh nicer
thank you for getting it
blue dancing blue you won bingo nice
voldemort
[Music]
oh my god bestie voldemort doesn't talk
like that you're fake you're fake fake
voldemort get out of here
[Music]
thank you for the um
yeah you have said that you'll only eat
normal cheese but what does that mean
exactly do you just not like blue cheese
or do you uh have a problem with soft
cheese like brie as well would you eat
sage derby cheese given how it what the
[\h__\h] is that it already sounds weird let
me look it up
no i'm not eating that [\h__\h]
no
anything that's like green or blue or so
i'm not eating
um
no
what is that
although
apparently it tastes like cheddar
is that green color the
colors from sage
ah if it's like something
i think i understand
that the the the color doesn't come from
the
shimmer
mold right it comes from the
the herb called sage
that's maybe
acceptable
maybe acceptable
[Music]
since it also seems to taste like
cheddar
[Music]
um
but yeah in general i don't like shimmer
case any kind of cheese that has like
mold on it just disgusting
but
i can eat brie
brie
cheese uh
i've uh
just the other day i ate um fried
fried pre cheese
with uh
uh
prices
um
uh it's some kind of jam it's a berry
jam
fried brie cheese with some very
specific very specific berry gem
it's very good um
fried cheese is so good yeah
brie has molded i think it um was not in
when i
when i eat cheese like bread
try to
stay away from the
the skin layer
and just eat like the inside that's uh
that works that works
but the one with the green mold and
stuff i don't even want to get close to
that cheese
[Music]
yeah
um cheese skin ew lingleberry i had
lingam berry it was lengthenberry did
you guys ever eat lingleberry jam before
if you eat fried cheese with lingonberry
jam
it's so good
i can recommend it
lingonberry jam it's just what like what
ikea also likes to serve you could
probably get lingam married geminiki i
am
otherwise besides ikea it's probably
difficult to get overseas
[Music]
lingleberry jam is what you have to um
eat schnitzel with
our
most popular
food in austria
schnitzel
it's a
a fried uh
real
meat i suppose
and usually we eat it with lingam air
jam and uh
potatoes and stuff
[Music]
99999 promising
schnitzel
someone is saying no none i have to eat
it with a
ketchup that's the germans you can uh
if you put schnitzel in front of
austrians and germans
you will see who's german and you will
see who's austrian by seeing if they're
eating it with lingam mary jam over
ketchup
ketchup is oh my god scandalous
it's like
oh
i mean
if there's nothing else around
if i don't have lingenberry jam at home
then worst case
i would maybe eat a little ketchup
and the thing is like if you order
schnitzel in germany they're probably
gonna serve it to you with ketchup and
not lingenberry because
yeah if you like in germany they eat it
differently but that's because they
don't know better
[Music]
they just don't know better there they
have no idea how to eat schnitzel
correctly
lemon on schnitzel yeah lemon always has
to be on the schnitzel
hey
mcorma's 89 down question thank you for
the tip by the way unfortunately that
one didn't work but it was an
inspiration to
to the other resource pack that we found
thank you
spectrum
hail scarf duncan thank you can you
check on the mystery hole and see if
there's a lush cave there
i wonder
some people have
um
told me that there is a large cave under
our headquarters i suppose somewhere
somewhere under the headquarters
is it
is it under the mystery hole
yeah my hole has a dungeon and [\h__\h] like
a mile
it sounds weird to say it like that
[Music]
[Laughter]
hello
oh
[Music]
thank you yeah it's me the holy one
today i didn't visit phoenixton but i
gotta work on phoenixton again
yeah bye thank you for the red super
chat mwah here's beautiful as a day i
had you oh you still have me i'm here
for you i'm not leaving
oh although i will be leaving for a
little vacation
but it's not even a full week so
i will be back soon don't worry about it
don't don't be sad
watch
i mean i'm in streams
specifically amit
[Music]
too late for me ah then watch inna
oh my god
oh my god guys
i i normally don't have time
to watch other girls
um
full streams like i checked them out
every once in a while but i never
watched the full streams but
oh my god so i watched the whole inna
stream on needy girl overdose
and you know as i said before she played
it very
similarly to me
she had the same ending too i think if i
remember correctly but oh my god mummy
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
i watched mummy's full stream as well
it was uh
questionable
i
i i am speechless i don't know what to
say
i don't
i don't understand
[Laughter]
[Music]
at least at least it was very different
from mine and enan's play through i
guess that's um
that made it interesting
um
on day three she made the girl take an
overdose of pills and killed her
um she then afterwards
or try to try to kill her and then
afterwards continue to
very often give her the full the full
the full thing
yeah and she always deleted chat
messages
so i don't know if that was um
actually caused by her deleting all
messages but i felt like the streams um
were shorter and uh
and that angel
spoke
less or like that was actually um
reacting
negatively because all the comments were
getting deleted was that because the
comments were getting deleted i'm not
sure how the
mechanism works but
she was like reacting
angel was more like reacting as if there
were a lot of hater comments even
even if there weren't but since muma
deleted them i guess the
she took it as yo
there's so many hater comments
hmm
i'm not sure if that's because because
of that but anyway yeah message deleted
message delete
my best mug no
as a streamer if if i had a mod who
deleted literally every [\h__\h] comment
like what the [\h__\h] what no i how i
couldn't stream
i wouldn't be able to stream yeah and
she kept the bad comments she deleted
all the good comments
huh
i wanted to backseat man
but she did it on purpose she tried to
trigger
maybe us and she she wanted to
break the girl in order to fix her but
she was already broken woman there was
no need to break her she's been broken
from the beginning
and then she had like
later on she had the problem that the
game kept on
uh going game over because she ignored
the messages of kangel and then kane
will eventually just leaves
out of nowhere
because she ignored the dms
oh my god woman
oh
she tried that was a
interesting way to play the game
definitely different from me and inna
she she did get a lot of uh followers
around the end after restarting
the game a few times
because she did a lot of the scandalous
streams that i just
i just couldn't
it would have broken my heart to let
kangel do all those yell buy streams
mummy modding mummy stop deleting the
messages in my chat
[Music]
[Applause]
mommy stop
[Music]
no
woman i'm going to take away your
moderator right
[Music]
i want to have a conversation with my
chat
i'm 10
who's the 14 year old where's the 14
year old one
[Music]
i'm 14 i dare they are
oh my god
m
yeah well
i don't know
i don't know what to say she shocked me
mummy
woman shocked me but i guess this this
again proves what you guys keep on
trying to tell me that mummy
is evil
you guys tried to
tell me several times before but i
didn't want to believe it
but now i have to
she's evil
[Music]
she's an evil she just has a dark side
that's evil
[Laughter]
thank you an r41v15
thank you for your first super chat
looking for the top donkey shank mr cats
makes thank you for the pinky
suddenly in the title you're as
beautiful as the day i lost you seems a
lot more beautiful did you prepare the
super chat after a year of being locked
in the desert horse jail we get to see
you again
thanks for doing this you wonderfully
merciful bird lady character art yes
mercy i have mercy
[Music]
you're welcome so many of you kept on
asking for circle circle circles now we
finally
finished this side quest
i was busy with the main quest
i told you i would event to eventually
complete my side quests
this was one of them
and thankfully circles was alive i
didn't know how i would ha how i would
calm you down if we would reach that
place and we would see a fence with no
horse inside
you guys would be like oh my god
that would be like gosh
calm down
circles is just circles got picked up by
someone okay circles was adopted and you
would have cried and cried and cried him
thank god circles was there
totally expected an empty fence
yeah but no one no one
loaded that chunk ever since i left i
guess
so
[Music]
circles was still there
yeah
i sent a farm upstairs
[Music]
circles or it should be viva la chiara
but just for that one super chat i'll
i'll
i'll allow it just once
circles is indeed back i'm glad you guys
were so excited about it i was i was
surprisingly excited as well i didn't
think i would be this
hype about it
[Music]
your name
is misleading now
[Music]
i know it's you
that's a weird name
furlock thank you for the red super chat
congratulations on bringing home circles
this is just evidence of how much you've
improved at playing minecraft you've
come a long long way from the newbie who
buried herself in sand on the first day
you're inviting mighty warrior phoenix
in savior of defenseless animals
but defenseless
but
but circles was
not defenseless he was
surrounded by a fence
furlock i don't think you did that on
purpose but wasn't that amazing of me to
find that pun in there
i'm so proud of myself right now
[Music]
oh man
hell yeah
[Music]
oh that was just
too much of an opening for me
it was an open invitation invitation for
me to make that joke
you know would be proud
i think she would be proud yeah
cupcake
[Music]
you just caught a shiny glamour
damn
i want a shiny one too shiny pokemon
[Music]
hmm
name of the gym
[Music]
i'll give you a link
whole live music studio bossa nova and
jasmix
hmm
i have a sylvian though you mean a shiny
one what the [\h__\h] give it to me
anyway thank you for luck
it is very
funny to think back on my first
minecraft stream man everyone starts
somewhere but i'm glad i was able to
start it on stream
and have that legendary
amateur minecraft experience recorded
for all times forever and ever
[Music]
is that fixed um
not really but it's like
they said you you can use it if you want
there there might be a risk to it but
it should be fine
yeah i hated the first person view and i
played most of it
in the beginning
in the um
third person and the chat was like come
on kiwamo change the perspective
i still to this day think
at least as um
as the from the point of view of the
audience i feel like having it in third
person
it would be
[Music]
um
aesthetically more pleasing because you
can see more
um i feel like you know
first person just feels so
close it makes me feel claustrophobic
yeah i like to see the character too
me too me too but for playing after
trying out first person of course
playing with the first person is most of
the time
easier especially when trying to
fight mobs
yeah
but i like to see more of my
surroundings and it's just much better
in third person to see my surroundings
[Music]
i feel like a reaction to your first
minecraft scene would be even better
than the debut or yet i feel like i
already um
reacted to my first minecraft stream
before but not the whole thing because
it's way too long
but i i i think i
did it live on stream before a little
bit
i kind of did ah was that a member's
only stream
oh
we can do it eventually sometime this
year
yeah
maybe we can even rather than making a
stream out of it maybe we can make a cut
video out of it and really just cut out
the funny parts and edit it like me
reacting to myself
edit it into a funny video maybe rather
than a video rather than a stream
[Music]
to my debut of course i've reacted to my
debut of course i have during my one
[Music]
thank you for the pinky in the resource
pack folder you need to put the zip file
not unpack not in a folder just to
download a zip file
yeah i think that's eventually how i did
it but something was just wrong with the
first file that we downloaded maybe it
really was the the version
being
too old to outdated
maybe that was the issue maybe it was
something else
thanks for trying to help though
everybody thank you
john menzer
and thank you for your first super chat
okay
oh papago
yo yesterday i had such a good laugh at
the papaco
text to speech thingy
um in clip form as well
[Music]
it was so funny
i had tears in my eyes listening to it
again
[Music]
your editing makes me think
how do i say it kindly
respectfully
a bit too
a better sexual for say so i don't like
myself
some of your
[Music]
interpretations no i didn't have to go
to another idol meeting but i was crying
yes here's my eyes man
it did sound i heard something i
actually heard something else um
partially
but yeah yeah yeah i think i think
putting that down on purpose
that was 100 on purpose the translations
yeah
you down bad
down bad for the tts
but tts is not
not
real you know it's just a voice in your
head
prime on the ground
oh i think pudding is dead i don't see
you putting in the chat
oh man
bros are waiting for your russian snack
unboxing a lot of us have some doubts
about what they put in there we're
already sure that we can do better very
sad that we can send you can't send you
anything the thing is though it comes
from a different company than the one
where i got the korean snack box from
um
actually i think yesterday i got the
info that it has been sent out
and i can track it
what
[Music]
um
i wonder where it is now let me see let
me track it
[Music]
i want to see where it is
maybe buddy
maybe
it should arrive
after my skiing trip i think
truck
where where are you wait i can't i can't
track it yet this is weird
they didn't actually send it out yet
they're so late why are they so slow
i think by the end of uh
by the end of february by the latest i
should be able to do that russian snack
box review
so please be a bit more um a bit more
patient thank you soon
[Music]
rick the horse oh
thank you um
wait rick has been freed what do you
mean freed
rick the horse rick
i thought it was a donkey
[Music]
hi dante i want to tell you what
happened after being freed i met a cute
horse girl and one settled she said she
was never gonna give me up but one day i
found her too cozy with an alpaca
oh wait you mean the
horse girl is not me right i'm not the
horse
but one day i found her too cozy with an
alpaca i'll pack us our rude and say
[\h__\h] you a lot exactly so i ran away
crying
that's when i bumped into roll
[Music]
i told him everything and he ordered the
kindest hee-haw ever it was the
pick-me-up i needed now we wander around
the sunset he pays for my who
frustration and i pay her for his
trimming rose were alive
uh
a roll was a donkey rick was a horse
another horse so you wrote that so that
i have a
happy end
uh lord to tell to my viewers that is so
sweet whoever is behind that horse
that's very sweet of you this is the
true lore
i'm glad it's not salty or angry it's
just
he found happiness
[Music]
i'm okay thank you bubbles i'm okay
i'm feeling fine
roll the donkey unintelligible donkey
noises suck a [\h__\h]
the profile picture he was such a
beautiful donkey
oh man
look at him
that's the profile
picture what a good picture i took that
picture didn't i
looks so good
looks beautiful
i miss i miss bro
huh
[Music]
maybe i can get one of his children
eventually
[Music]
workers are also people who do shopping
do it the same way you do and understand
completely how shopping works ah
do it the same you think you mean they
do it the same way i do
i don't know
i just i just try to be considerate you
know but then i feel bad about having
lied to them
corey chameleon duncan but sometimes
when i say that i'm coming back i really
mean it but then in the in the time in
between i like
think rethink if i really want to buy
that object and then i'm like i come to
the conclusion that it's not worth the
money often
which is probably good because then i
would have bought it
i would have maybe impulse bought it at
the
store um and then
regret it because i don't need it so
it's better that i just say i'm coming
back later and think about it
i fight the impulse yeah
i have to i have to do that a lot
otherwise i just buy a lot of useless
things
[Music]
i have legit forgot where the store was
before that's cute
that's you are little dojiko
clumsy
clumsy girl
clumsy boy
who can be
male and female
[Music]
i enrolled into a german university but
i'm not needing to fly over on and only
need to take basic german module who
learning in advance will definitely help
prepare for it
um please don't expect too much
from my german lessons i don't know i
mean if you take it seriously and
actually take notes you might remember
some stuff but i think learning a
language
um
especially in language like german you
you should learn it differently like
from a different order like i started by
telling you some words and phrases
but normally
you should start somewhere
more simple somewhere else i think
but i'm not a serious teacher so
i can't do that for you but
yeah
yeah you have to learn the grammar and
stuff and i i'm not gonna spend some
time learning uh teaching you the
grammar because i don't even know
i don't even know grammar myself anymore
i don't know how i would explain it
impulsive chat thank you
maybe he'll pick up picking up some
chicks during exchange programs oh
that's your plan i see you see
the german girls are pretty cute yeah
there are some cute girls out there
maybe you can come here during
oktoberfest and see them all in the cute
uh dentals
maybe if you're lucky you'll see a
glowing phoenix in the dental somewhere
hey although i have actually never i
don't know if i said this before but
i've never worn a dandel before
i wanted to
i was thinking of buying one last year
but now it's winter time
maybe maybe in summer
maybe in summer i'll buy one and go
somewhere in a dinner
now i want kiara in the denver fan
artist get the look there is this one
fan art recently that i really liked
that looked so cute so pretty
it's just like uh the upper body but
wait you guys probably know which one
i'm talking about from this
this
one
which is
it looks
not exactly like a vandal is supposed to
look like i would say because the corset
um
it's it's close to it though it
definitely has
dental
tendencies
and there's a there's a basic
digital design going on there with the
ribbon and the lower um part it looks
like a apron
and the blouse underneath
you're you're getting there
big chickens by the side yeah those are
huge man why am i just small
wait hold on
[Music]
it kind of gives me like um
it gives me handle vibes but more like
medieval fantasy style
simple
like i look like an
npc
i look like an npc in those clubs i
don't know what i'm trying to say here
but i like this panel it's very pretty i
like the the profile of my face
[Music]
simple and clean yeah it's beautiful i
love that art thank you that's good and
then of course there's that one fanat
from
uh mama looney
[Music]
i don't know if i can find it so quickly
nope i don't think
so but she drew me in something like a
diandal before as well
something similar
an original candle
that looks really really cute too
i don't i can't find it now
[Music]
that's a really old one
actually surprising that uh
given my
given me saying i am from austria
there is
basically no dandelthan art
what's going on there what's going on
guys
people just don't don't think about it i
suppose
but one day i'm telling you one day i
will get a dandel uh outfit for myself
done it might take a long time but one
day i'll get it
and then and then and then and then i'm
gonna get a lot of fan art for it
ribbon left i forgot uh which one was uh
what what the meaning for that one was
again to be honest because i never wore
a dental myself so i didn't really have
to
think about it too much
but left probably means that you're
single depending on where you
um where you tie the ribbon of your
dindle
it shows the people if you're taken or
if you're married or if you're widowed
and so on
um
[Music]
yes
people need to know i'm austria not
australian hmm
[Music]
what if you wear only the ribbon
pudding
you pervert
go sit in the corner
and reflect on your actions
[Music]
putting pudding pudding
i was asking for sure
yeah yeah your friend is yourself
i know
anyway open the mic i'll see you
tomorrow during the german lesson then
all right
[Music]
you're wearing the okay honey right now
yo
thank you is it comfortable i haven't
received the omo cat merch yet but i um
i didn't order it like you guys did i
um i got it you know from
like directly
but there um cat is like sending it to
the office first and then the office
will send it to me so it's taking its
sweet time as well i have not received
it yet but i have
um asked for
um
my merchandise of course so eventually
i'll have it as well
[Music]
or that is like yeah dude like dude
i say it all the time in german i'm so
addicted to the word
uh where one side
where was i
uh here
saying
voldemort action of your dunkishan
outrun the wind tank shanks senora thank
you
pinky hi can i finally i could get my
membership and officially join kfb so
here's my first super chat to celebrate
i admire you so much as a woman and
wants you to know that you make my
everyday weather looking forward to more
wonderful times with you thank you me
too
thank you for becoming a member please
enjoy yourself here
hope you're gonna be here for a long
time
patrick
skye down
for the
pinky and just went out to get the mail
and my parents were answered that was
the birthday match just wanted to let
you know the slippers fit and my cat is
live in the box everything came in
your cat
that's why you ordered it in the first
place right for your cat
no a fresh new box
with a cat
it's a nice box really
[Music]
ah sweet
thank you i'm glad it fits i'm glad it
arrived safely thank you for waiting for
it i know
i know the the merchandise takes like a
[\h__\h] ton of time to arrive
yeah
hopefully um you know we've also done
hold a live website now offering at
least for some countries
offering to
um
offering those services
hopefully things are gonna be uh
improved in the future
[Music]
biofania c duncan a rock hard
one extension
nine thousand dollars so many people are
saying that merch is coming now oh my
cat let's go
you have not been praised not exactly
uh leo free o o x thank you thank you
oh yeah
oh you're gonna upload it on twitter i'm
excited
that way you know i'm i
if you do it that way i'll at least be
able to check out everything i don't
remember to go and read it every day i
i don't go on reddit that often it's
already on twitter wait like a new one
let me see
let me go check out arts of ashes
[Music]
cute oh cute
wing
i found
[Music]
let's see
let's take a look
number one
after is this the first page
you assume it is
after 20 minutes of insisting a group of
kfb employees known as the circle freaks
was formed
and managed to convince canada to look
for the legendary and loyal horse
circles
now how the [\h__\h] do i get circles all
the way here
it wasn't that difficult
yeah they had no choice but to find
circles i don't want to hear the white
circles from the circle springs ever
again
[Music]
after flying with her hot wings she
landed close the coordinates she the tcf
the circle freaks
gave her assuring kiana that it was
circle's exact location in the world
sleeping noises
i'm done i can smell your circles
smell disgusting you haven't had a bath
in a long time
and in the hot desert oof holy [\h__\h]
the cords were blah blah blah by the way
if you want to know
and get a [\h__\h] found circles actually
at the moment while i was looking for
circles i was speaking japanese at the
moment i found circles i was speaking
japanese and i was just saying in
japanese that i
i'm not sure if i can find circles and
then what
there he is
and the last pageant
how the [\h__\h] did you stay alive for me i
managed to stay alive for 423 days
because i knew you would come back for
me
and i wasn't planning on bringing
circles back but she was so excited to
see him that she decided to make the
trip walking the trip homeworking
instead of flying even though i really
didn't plan on bringing him back but i
was so happy about seeing him
you're as beautiful as the day i lost
your actual dialogue also the original
title of the micro sim yes she gave
circles golden hour hell yeah circles my
man
yay
thank you what a what a titty wholesome
heartwarming story that is
yeah i'm also waiting for that cow
carrot video now you're hearing this
kyle carrot
you're you're the one to do it who else
is gonna
dig out a
423 old stream
to take that part
and make a clip out of it with today's
stream who else is gonna do that huh
[Music]
and i mean of course a lot of people
also like them to make uh the the clip
so guys of course anyone and the more
the merrier
as always
and a ramos duncan
oh i think i got it
changed my pfp because kiara is cute
oh that's me last few streams and
chitchats have been so fun and comfy
i've had my merch for a while and posted
it but i will be glad to post again near
one but yes please do everybody who
already posted it please post it again
when we have a hashtag or something and
pyraming for the pinky
i'm sorry empress but on the 22nd i must
abandon carefully
and journey to the happiest place on
earth where is the happy wait is that
disney wait where is the
when is the happiest place on earth
disneyland
well why are we not wait
isn't some kind of european northern
country the happiest place on earth
for a moment yeah for a moment i thought
you would die
okay disneyland okay
very nice for on the 25th i shall return
from this land of the mouse
uh on the galaxy's edge
seeing friends for the first time in two
years oh
no problem that's just uh a couple days
but thanks for already letting me know
have fun in disneyland i've never been
to american disneyland but one day
if if i make it i want to go there and
then find that super cool
um cast member
uh that i told you about before she's so
fascinating
she's so fascinating
she just does her act so perfectly
[Music]
the evil queen yeah
i hope she still works there by the time
i ever get to america
gotta bring good on a leash
yeah
if
if i ever go to disneyland with her now
i know that i need to put her on a leash
or in a stroller
but just hold her hand but handcuff each
other
[Music]
every
every imaginable location yes i want to
eat lots of food
[Music]
but i would feel kind of bad about
eating in america i feel like like i
would um
leave a lot of food on the plate
but i guess i'll just always have to say
please pack it up for me so i can take
it home
and then
probably i won't even eat it but just so
that i don't leave it on the plate
it's just
yeah they're just too big too big but
you guys told me before that that
they're so big because it's pretty
normal to take things home
in america
um
i want to try all the burgers all the
burgers
[Music]
we're done reading super chats guys
four hours
we've been way too efficient today it
feels wrong
we need to waste some more time
no this is good i have to wake up early
i have to wake up early
so i have to sleep early
i'm gonna play some pokemon i want to
but i have to stop like i've been
playing so much off stream
i need to continue the main story now
so
i'll hold back
[Music]
thank you thank you cruz thank you soon
thank you dad
[Music]
i will stay as long as i can did
thank you soon okay and tomorrow members
only
uh
we're doing german lessons
oh the the reservation will be up
tomorrow
yeah
thank everybody for hanging out today
sorry i didn't have much to share today
sometimes i just think of my tangents
and
in moments where i don't even need them
my brain is just
too empty sometimes
thank you for the pinky and late by day
was just a reminder wednesdays we were
and super chat pink
oh mean girls
that is so fetch thank you thank you for
the pinky
[Music]
thank you
thank you guys
stop trying to make it happen stop
trying to make stuff fetch stop
happening
stop
[Music]
so i'll see you at the members only
stream tomorrow and in german we say
[Music]
good night also to my mom who's probably
watching this good enough
good enough
good night
good
night
now
and go to bed early
[Music]
thank you thank you
where is the oxygen
[Music]
um
in there's the kfp
in india in delhi
it stands for krishna food point
[Music]
we need to sue them
[Laughter]
[Music]
additionally there's also
a kfb in finland
which is also a restaurant apparently
[Music]
and
a kfp in
rwanda where is what is where is that
[Music]
oh africa
someone sent this info to me on twitter
[Music]
interesting
so that's three places that we have to
take down let's go
[Music]
laughs