​Takanashi Kiara (小鳥遊キアラ） - HINOTORI
​Producer/Composer: Kai Gojo (五条下位)
​Lyrics: Aya Shinno (真野綾)
​matataku hoshi no yuri kago kaketa serifu o
​tsunagi awaseta Memory
​seinaru juusha ga tsutau shinwa no kotowari
​inori ni mimi o sumase
​Tell me, I can hear it clearly,
​Tell me koe naki koe ni
​araburu kodou wa kizu o kogasu
​homura furisosogu sora ni mi o yatsushite
​midarezaku aka wa benigeshou
​amata kasanaru shiren mo ikinuite miseru
​I will live to keep on fighting till the dawn
​tatoeba saki no mienai zero no kyoukai
​mayoikonda toshitemo
​nandomo kurikaesareru kokou no shuuen
​soko ni nokotta Answer
​Don't break, I will never give up,
​Don't break hane ga kuchite mo
​kesenai tsuyosa wa toki no shirube
​haika maiagaru daichi mi o kugurase
​moyuru ake no naka me o samasu
​yaiba majiwaru kissaki kawashita chigiri wa
​Lies and truth, come to light at the break of day
​I've been trying to find my destiny
​But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
​If I go wrong, what awaits me in the dark
​Could you tell me please, where I need to go?
​Tell me, I can hear it clearly,
​Tell me koe naki koe ni
​minagiru ketsui wa kage o harasu
​homura furisosogu sora ni mi o yatsushite
​midarezaku aka wa benigeshou
​amata kasanaru shiren mo ikinuite miseru
​blazing flames, show me the path to luminance
​And in the next life too I promise, I will find you
​Guitar: Daisuke Bito (尾登大祐)
​Artist: Mamaloni
​Movie Animation: Calliope Mori (森カリオペ)