[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hello hi
hi
no
still there
my energy Jam
I can barely hear it good microphone
could barely pick it up okay hello
[Music]
I'm here too yeah I'm I'm so small
that's because I'm standing in the back
of the room that's why I sound far away
baby
but we're back with uh another try round
two
for real for real yeah for real the
internet has recovered thankfully yeah
the the number one the number one fix is
restarting and power cycling which power
cycling she said it sounds fancy it's a
cool word to say and to use for turning
something off and on again yeah
I think you said and then I said what
about resetting you said oh we're
setting you use for a lot of things yeah
I'm pretty sure you know there's a sport
called Power walking I think oh right
there's probably also power or something
uh Power no that's just bicycling
powerful cycling
Maeve no I don't think so I don't think
so so is now in 3D oh yeah but different
pretty yeah I'm just using proprietary
software oh
and so going I can move my arms kind of
like one arm at least but she's got
she's got the the full 3d yeah because
we are recording some more things yeah
right before the stream yeah but now
we're here for one time actually I'm
gonna switch this to not Studio mode
yeah be careful with the wire
spooky whatever wait there's so many
wires everywhere so it's a little
there we go wires are like tentacles
what like yeah I know I guess
you're so small
Jordan no
no I gotta make myself smaller
oh we could do like that like
wait opposite yeah so no not say that
it's hard not to sync up wait
wait there we go
we got it but you still you're still too
small even when I go small I'm like on
your normal height
because I'm kneeling right now I'm gonna
make you taller fine
um
as me because she's the boss here
yeah this is my studio
I'm there
why are you freaking out what'd you do
yeah I have a pinned on my taskbar sorry
wait where is it is it grab your hands
where are we
is it the big one the small one
oh uh the the big one big PC so the the
I don't remember which Mouse I have
there's we have a two PC setup right now
and there's two mice right next to each
other it's a little confusing so yeah
oh
[Music]
all the way here right we're here to uh
do some target practice which we did a
little bit of before when the stream
went down but thankfully everything is
smooth sailing now so we can actually
experience Kiara uh shooting Airsoft for
the I guess it's technically the third
time because
I do have three different types of
Airsoft I have like a pump action one I
have a CO2 one which you have to put
compressed air can inside that's the
revolver and then I have an electric one
which is charged you actually have a
charging dock for the battery but I
can't find my rifle so today we just
have the revolver and the handgun she
has a [\h__\h] rifle guys stay away from
her hunting rifles it's really cute it's
not it's like it's only this big okay
well only only this picture
uh same thing yeah question
how does one know
uh how does one tell uh something from a
Target and a no target how do I know
that this is my target like when you're
looking at it or just in general General
um well you know what it's uh it's good
to shoot not moving and not alive
targets I think oh yeah it's good to
shoot dead what not yeah
anyways
if you're talking about the target sheet
in the back if you shoot the red spots
you'll be able to see like where you
shot it'll show up as like yellow when
you actually hit it for real it turns
yellow yeah yeah how can it do that it's
because it the back side of it is yellow
I think so it just scratches off like
the front layer but it also goes through
so it creates like a little a little
yeah you have a lot of shotguns down
there yeah
well did you let out your aggressions
with them that's from the other streets
that was from the other uh you know the
other shooting streams should I put on
these classes yes we're wearing safety
eyewear a protective Highway okay
gonna reload the revolver because we
went through a bunch of bullets and I
think it was really funny to watch her
uh shoot this one because the compressed
air it was so heavy yeah it's heavy but
it also uh like it you can see that the
compressed air like kind of like a real
gun you saw the air yeah you didn't see
it I didn't see that is that right in
front of your face I felt it felt it
yeah I think that this one compared to
the electric one is kind of more similar
to shooting almost a real gun in a way
but obviously the kickback is not as
strong she knows all those terms FPS oh
really cool I've heard of that one
before
little tiny balls they're so sparkly you
could make like bracelets with those
they're brilliant these look like uh
fish eggs what is it um
last time when we did it you shot like
pretty close but if you stand further
back I can adjust like where you oh yeah
yeah there we go like International from
here yeah the further away the better
you can test your shot
oh so this this Airsoft some airsoft
guns have like a safety like a real gun
but this one doesn't okay I'll just move
over a little bit oh I don't want to
cover yeah I'll move I'll move no where
are you going I'm just moving myself go
closer to the Target
I mean you know only an obvious
I'm gonna shoot I'm gonna learn how to
shoot and then you you chickens will
have to be even more careful let me
block the chat they're testing me and my
patience
um
do not test my patience
do you hear me
because I have very little of it all
right I've already I've already learned
in the first stream how to do this yes
line it up you're not even holding it
right well well
I think you're left-handed so yeah guess
your trigger fingers on the left right
yeah yeah so you wrap okay let me show
you again
I do like this because I'm right-handed
and then bring it bring this hand
underneath um
come on
I'm just trying to line it up you know I
need to hey
just wants to hit it
yeah I'm just I'm not making this my my
new job or so
maybe you should switch from a sword to
a gun no no no Medieval Times she said
earlier in the 1800s were Medieval Times
can you
happen
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right all right
what are you aiming for it's like pool
yeah
I aimed for the curtain okay you hit it
you hit it
hmm
oh wait it's like like this okay
I holding like that
for emotional support
[Applause]
ing it wrong no one else
we're gonna switch this one it's two
it's too big
you need to oil it with WD-40 oh I gotta
reload this one to entertain them well
and reload them okay
once I practice my monologue
what do you think
I am already a model a role model for
all my chickens that would be fun if we
like did a fashion show of all of like
our whole life Halloween merch oh I was
thinking actually I was thinking of you
today a fashion show of all your
different you know you want to put the
magazine in so you just have to slide it
you just put it in here and then slide
it so you can do it like really hard and
get a really cool sound like
you seen a video game where you reload
slide it in
yeah yeah put in like like a you know
like a shape yeah now stop it
that wasn't so special yeah it sounds
cool it sounds cool
what do you think what Omniverse fashion
show I like it doesn't even have to be a
stream you could just do like a video
where you'll come out and Vlog with all
your different ammas okay anyway
I think we're pretty long I guess yeah
they have plenty of models
all right all right all right uh do I
hold this the same way yeah in theory
yes all right okay I didn't line it up
because this one you have like good good
posture almost like you're supposed to
like you're supposed to if you're
shooting real you spread your legs kind
of bend your knees a little bit and then
you bend your elbows
no don't lean back you're gonna
oh my god oh it's not automatic
oh
it shot like 50 at once there you go
what the [\h__\h] but I hit it yeah
you wanting it up yeah I did
we went like
I was planning to automatic later we'll
test it later
[Music]
yeah you didn't do it all the way I did
nice
again
I think it's just that one rigged should
I turn it to automatic so you can get
that one no
what the [\h__\h] I think I think it's I
need an oil that thing so yeah I hear
the I hear the little pellets going on
yeah that's why you wear glasses can I
say okay I underestimated that's that's
problem
do you do you vacuum here or collect
them back again can you use them again I
have yeah you can use them look at this
this is from the Christmas tree
I just swept them all like under a
corner she's sweeping it all under the
rugs there's things that people will not
find out about her about their palettes
she has like a million under a curtains
can you reuse them yeah you can reuse
them sometimes they break in half though
that's so Eco yeah
[\h__\h] man should I um aim closer to the
right side or so I think I think it's
just because it's maybe got Rusty or
something while I was sitting in here
down here in the damp
you're hitting them I'm hitting them
every time nice sound try the top one I
think that one will spin
you'll spend my goal right now
you're hitting it though get the second
one second one I'll get it for you on a
minute first try
oh I jinxed it
but you know what now that I can do this
if I ever am at like um let me call it
jam up a carnival thingy oh again what
you should have to get like little
um plushies yeah and now I feel like I
could do it but usually don't they use
like pretty long yeah yeah and they use
like the hunting rifle one yeah the
hunting rifle toys and then it would
have been good to have that here so I
can fry this one yeah somewhere in here
I just gotta look for it but I tried
looking around I couldn't find it
anywhere
yeah what the [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I did it
wrong yeah
what are you going for second one second
one
second from the top oh okay there we go
but they all know
use your trash can you turn them around
I don't know why it would make it
different but I could probably do it
with like uh
what you're wasting you're wasting
pallets it's fine
what the [\h__\h]
I gotta reload it it's empty
use two fingers fingers to pull the
trigger if you need to I guess okay does
this one have stronger palettes inside
uh no no they're the same I do have
metal pellets though but that one's for
the rifle okay well you guys can even
see that I'm closing my eye actually in
the the camera is like here so when I
stand sideways I think it doesn't track
mostly oh wow okay lining it up and
yeah
didn't work
I didn't hit it you didn't hit it where
did I go
okay I'm going for the let's say the the
top one
hit it you got it yeah but it didn't
turn around on the second one yeah I
need to oil that thing hmm
let's go for our bottom
yeah
I didn't see it
sorry I didn't see it I just you know
you guys just gotta say oh I saw it
wow that was amazing
just like parents do with their kids
yeah
[Music]
I
didn't hear it I didn't hear it
you need to wash your ears um
let's have a battle oh good
oh my God
just carry on it you scared
is it
you guys the way she's shooting yourself
oh my my eye hurts from from squinting
so much
okay
and I'll try them
I'll try the right side one okay this
one you can shoot faster with
ah
I wasn't licking again
[Music]
is it true that she actually hit it I
did it turned back
turned back on that is the obvious proof
see
ah yeah it looks different it looks
different
yes they said they're they're being
honest guys she said no I've got the top
one even though it's like angled
turn those [\h__\h] around
week week finger
thing
look now that's good thing
are you squinting
you have to aim and then when you shoot
you open both your eyes
acid they like stuck in between oh oh
you did reverse yeah
the impact
oh yeah I mean hitting has no problem
okay yeah Target well I gotta turn off
the webcam really quick so I can remove
the thing okay one second don't cross me
I put this gun gun down oh okay all
right
it's them okay let me move this up
thank you
okay bringing it back up let me just
double check
okay
why why croissant
so the the target is a little tilted
yeah I couldn't get it straight because
of the curtain behind
but uh you you won't want to see which
one you're gonna shoot I got it it's the
middle one
but you're pretty I mean you're not even
that far I think you should try from
back there
I'm not on the screen anymore oh we can
go like to the corner you still should
be yeah
here I go for the middle one yeah okay
I'm shaking you shaky
oh I went somewhere uh I think you it
went a little to the left
oh I went up sheesh
that's difficult being so far back yeah
oh I got right
nice my eye hurts
you squint
aim and open your eyes and then shoot no
then it goes somewhere else you can't
hold it steady I'm going for bottom run
okay
empty I'm empty
you can do this too this turns the
chamber and then what does that do
really just turns I don't think you need
to do it to be honest I think it's just
just it's cool
have you look oh it doesn't well you
have to pull it back with your thumb
all the way
okay okay I'm gonna reload this up
should I close this again no no it's
supposed to that's the hammer it's
supposed to stay like that
okay
yeah yeah I think so maybe what if it
goes back out and then my face yeah I'll
shoot it I don't think you have to do
that but
[Music]
you guys see that
all right
I'll go I'll go bottom left to say [\h__\h]
you to everybody who called me by him
left yeah [\h__\h] you
[Music]
your finger strength is really terrible
it's not just my fingers it's my whole
arm but yeah
wait wait wait that was supposed to be
really cool okay
wait it didn't not really that one from
earlier
um I feel like I saw the curtain having
more reaction oh
how can I even train my my fingers I
can't lift many weights my fingers yeah
I should still think you're
skateboarding maybe that helps too
tricks
improving my finger strength next hand
chem stream here do you want to switch
back to this one now yeah wait one more
shot
oh wait were you aiming for that yes
I was looking for the top left one
you guys see where that goes yeah should
be visible yeah you guys can tell right
like on the camera
yeah yeah
there's grip things grip things for that
oh no for training your fingers oh oh
right the strengthers have you ever seen
that where it's got like uh you do like
this like oh and it's
like this
you squeeze it and it's like a little
Loop of metal that has like it kind of
looks like jump rope handles ah
I thought that was to punch people no
it's to it's to help grip strength oh
yeah oh well how about the same button
has the strongest hip strength in all of
her life she could probably do this
easily probably
okay top left
uh
oh pretty close
wait I should be further away though
right yeah you should
she's like about maybe 10 or 15 feet
away
where'd that even go no idea the first
one went up tall over the bottom right
one
ah oh
I didn't see it bottom right corner oh
okay okay okay
this is the FPS stream that kfp was
waiting for now you'll be able to play
PS games right I mean
um it's different you yeah yeah it's
very different but as long as it's with
you a male play any FPS game you play
fortnite or four nights at FPS the thing
is so I've been told that I do better
job at like playing
um not first person shooter games but
third first person shooter games you
could probably play fortnite then oh is
that right person yeah fortnite
got one yes yes I I could I could do
that yeah
I mean did you ever use that for a
stream yet no I haven't used this this
is new it's not that we can just use
this do this
without like any particular trackers or
so yeah it's using camera whoa I can do
that at home too now okay yeah you guys
might have seen some other senpais of
the street yeah hand stream you want to
try automatic
if you trust me with that yeah you just
stop pressing when you want to stop
shooting okay
what if I make a heart for you go ahead
yeah I tried that actually
you got one you got one
out of like 10 Bowlers
I'll probably run out of them yeah you
[Applause]
wow that was quite the impact yeah I
think that's the only target I have I
would say let's shoot something else but
you have no more time no I have more I
could put it back up I'll put it back up
you want a new one the switch no no
let's just switch this one
oh
these guns can do it I thought they only
do normal people normally two automatic
is semi-automatic
what is usually like uh you gotta like
um get the bullet in the chamber but
this one's because it's our thing I'll
make sure the watermelon we have a
watermelon oh yeah I do have watermelon
actually because I bought two
watermelons and I ate one but the other
one's kind of old you want to shoot the
water do you think it will go for a
heavy but I I don't know it might go
through what I think with this one
because it has more uh like force to it
like airports this one should work we
should eat it afterwards though okay if
we open it up like that yeah yeah this
should be fine otherwise the ants will
come in although I gotta turn the camera
off should we put should I just get the
watermelon yes as I was eyeing the
watermelon
these past today
oh orange oh
guys yesterday I actually slept over at
Emma's place because it got kind of late
um slept over at her place I slept on
the couch you know
it was it was nice you know and and and
and she cooked
and I ate the best corn of my life
I was so into that corn yeah it was good
it was so good oh my God it was the corn
that has like some not all white but
some of them were white so it was like
super juicy and super sweet
um
on the cob on the club with butter and
you know
salt pepper nothing special but the corn
on this only was already like so damn no
yeah yeah yeah yeah would you say it was
amazed I was amazing
yeah the thing is I can't find white
corn like that in Austria I've never
seen it before look at this uh this is
it's fine yeah okay is that is that a
sweet potato yeah
the sweet potatoes are pretty freaking
like
strong and how do you say the word
what's the word
they're so
hard oh yeah yeah
tough potato that's the I don't know
danger danger
potatoes dense yes
okay imma impress me oh I'm shooting it
first yes shoot the sweet potato
fall off like immediately yeah but I
guess they're all cool
we have two oranges one watermelon and a
sweet potato and we're gonna eat them so
don't worry it's not going to waste of
course not yeah
worst case is it okay for you from here
absolutely kind of long
it's your clothes
well potato God
oh
you missed
um
but didn't make a hole I wonder probably
not I don't know I'm just scared to grab
it right now I can turn off camera grab
it
plug it
I cannot see you I think maybe I hit the
top of it I think it did make a hole
maybe well maybe it got like a little
bump backwards bump grab it really quick
okay
it's hard to reach
oh there's so many pills
whoa wait I think wait don't turn it on
yet but uh can we show this do you see
my thing can you see the preview oh sure
yeah
a little further
um
in front
okay are you ready I'm ready do I shoot
next
uh yeah I don't know if that one's gonna
do much but that one you could yeah less
less less impact or what yeah it has
less impact because it's electric so it
doesn't really have like so much I'll go
for orange okay which one right one
right orange
whoa oh it's stuck it
show up on the kitchen yeah I can see it
nah
cute cute
I'm giving his pimples pimples
you should land the strong shot into the
watermelon make it make it explode it's
not going to explode
did I hit it uh no I don't think so
no yeah yeah yep
oh
it's oh there's water coming out oh it's
bleeding oh thank you yeah it probably
like popped off again but it definitely
opened up some juice
oh that's amazing cool now it's your
turn
okay
now with this liner you want to use this
one I gotta reload this one well it is a
pretty big Target maybe it'll be fun
okay one second
[Music]
crazy shots
this is the content I wanted it's Judy
watermelon
that is like a genre on YouTube on like
exploding watermelon oh it's bulky
watermelon slime on stream your fruit
skills are remarkable Fruit Ninja okay
here you go
I smell fruit in there
the orange and especially the orange
Aroma the sweet scent
and you're going from melon uh yeah okay
look for another shot in the melon
oh yeah it's like dead center I see it
oh sheesh okay I'll go first with potato
sweet potato let's see what happens
lining it up oh [\h__\h] I think
I'm gonna go to the right side
I think that one you do have to but okay
well we'll see
you guys do you see it a little bit
maybe
I landed another hit on the right side
of it
to go for the left orange okay
can you stand like a little yeah it has
been um so far left alone
untouched yeah
is that orange
Spanky where did that go
I don't know I don't think he shot
anything because I'm pretty sure you
have to pull back
pull back to this yeah yeah I'm pretty
sure okay maybe not but it's fine when I
landed a shot in the circle doodle yeah
yeah yeah
oh [\h__\h] those accidents
I feel like it was easier to pull the
trigger when I had that back yeah
because that's how you're supposed to do
it
tell me
it's been a while since I've used these
I forgot uh that's what okay guys you
cannot make fun of me anymore about the
noodle fingers okay you understand what
was happening just now that there's
there's just I think I can show it I
think it's fine
oh perfect do you see that thing that
was not pulled back before and that's
what makes it much much more difficult
sorry
wait I see something on the camera
nothing on the orange on the on the side
it scratched it it went in or it only
scratched it I think all right Ricochet
let's go let's pull it back let's go
whoa that went up high yeah it looks a
little too high you're lining it up no
you guys should see her she looks so
badass she's got her safety glasses on
it's like squinting oh I can't hit that
one
it's so far
yeah you want to try with the other one
um
no no that one might be out of bullet
soon what are you doing
just cool techniques
I think it's out you are you're the one
who will bring us the fruit dinner we're
gonna try with this one it's not on
automatically okay my eye
she's going to too hard
maybe Chad has some aiming advice
you hit the orange several times only
which one the the last one the last one
really good guys I don't think so maybe
they're just being nice turn on auto aim
okay
yeah take cover or be my cover or I
don't know
you want me to like kneel in front of
you I know I'm sorry oh do something
cool that you're doing usually like you
say cover me it's like the other person
has a back turn cover me it's out here
this one's back nope I'll reload this
one oh oh she backed me up with weapons
I'm supporting yeah she's my job
what'd you call me weapon jockey isn't
that what do you call the golf people
who give you oh yeah yeah I think so
yeah
[Music]
whoa
I will allow us to hide you have to aim
much lower I think that one it it shoots
higher than what you aim so yeah you
should aim lower
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
come on
[\h__\h] out
almost stumbled okay are you switching
back
um
I think
we need to penetrate the watermelon more
okay
I have metal bullets that I don't think
we should use them we have metal bullets
not not bullets they're pellets they're
pellets you know I saw I saw a knife um
out there yeah throw it no no I don't I
don't know how to do knife throwing
we're not doing this okay maybe I'll get
like someday ax throwing but like small
ax or like
ninja stars yeah
let me go oh I should get a dartboard
actually that'd be fun oh yeah I suck at
darts so badly
they're difficult are you just fortnite
dancing now no no
dude you want this one
how do you do this one
uh yeah that looks right oh
what should I shoot melon
melon we do that we do automatic
okay
[Music]
I think
we've been dazzling the the watermelon
this one has gone on for too long
[Applause]
we're bedazzling them we're putting some
gems on them they're like it's like
sequins yeah I think it still has some
left really yeah
we had sweet potato
not okay
die
okay you're ruined my cool moment sorry
you're not supposed to shoot it like
that anyways of course you should it's
cool you can because it's air socks but
if you tried doing that it might think
gangster
we should we should get a car in here a
car and then open the window and drive
by and shoot the watermelon
GTA baby
this is GTA
you know I really I really freaking love
GTA 5. I wanna play
um
the cowboy GTA look like the Redemption
too yeah
yeah I think you I think you have fun
with that
um
hold on it's too many
I'll do my cool shot
what trick shot
okay
here we go
she's fixing her hair you don't see it I
broke a nail earlier yeah I don't
remember what we were doing but
terrifying my my thumbnail just and you
were putting my markers on oh that's
right yeah it got stuck on her on her
clothes
scary all right sweet potato
sweet potato
you have insulted me one too many times
did you get it no I feel I don't think
so
you gotta hit it on this side so let's
try I can see it oh
[Music]
what yeah but sweet potatoes not all
sweet potatoes are yams but oh yeah
sweet potatoes because I think it's a
type of sweet potato I'm pretty sure
okay well you know
it's been 45 minutes we should sing yeah
okay that's some good target practice
I'm gonna cut those oranges and
eventually I think the melon might be
bad already so I don't like that one but
I was planning to use the sweet potato
for uh tater tots like sweet potato
potato chats oh oh yeah you should talk
about the cookies
I'm so excited for everything else I'm
I'm gonna make cookies already the
second time last night yeah and and and
and she was talking about the fact that
she wanted to make like apple pie or so
with her apples but she didn't have
stuff for the apple pie I guess not an
ice cream and she was missing the ice
cream so then you know because I really
liked her cookies
she made apple pie cookies basically she
just
um she caramelized the apples
and then she put it on top of the cookie
dough and then put it into the airfryer
and I was kind of doubting it but it
turned out really good so she had the
chocolate chip cookies and then not
chocolate chip cookies but with
caramelized or like cinnamonied
um apple slices on top and it worked
really well it was so good and
almonds cookies are so good because
they're fresh and they're warm and
they're they're crunchy on the outside
oh yeah because I I make them in the air
fryer no yeah it was good but no ice
cream so just just some cookies for um
you know you know small dessert no after
dinner they're so good and let me fix
that microphone a little bit we still
have some cookie dough right oh yeah I
still have some cookies
okay we can make another another batch I
only make like two to four cookies at a
time so yeah yeah I'm not making a crazy
amount all right so I have the mouse
here yeah using your leg as a mouse pad
yeah
wait so what is this this is
that one first yeah sure do we remember
I'm gonna you know I'm gonna I don't
remember hat you when when you should
sing is this it
um uh no so this one I didn't choose
which one to look at um just go with
that one yeah
okay good the text is big and I can
scroll yes okay so we'll do it like this
well I don't know we'll have to
sacrifice I know it's kind of weird
laughs
[\h__\h] wait let me zoom out we don't need
to to see the the video
no oops what I do oh no I don't want to
print no printing
guys tell us in the chat if you if it
sounds like there's a delay or so but
hopefully we'll be fine
ah
[Music]
that messes up the I mean I'm fine a
little bit okay yeah um I'll figure it
out
okay then I'll pull up this and then
I'll minimize this okay
you sound far away eat the mic please uh
like I can you can say I think I could
stand a little closer too yeah
we'll talk louder anyway when we sing uh
yeah
okay BTM off
I don't know if I remember this but
we'll say hi I also haven't sung this in
a long time
are you ready ready yeah
yeah here we go
[Music]
okay when I pet you it means you should
sing
okay
[Music]
sorry if there's double it should be
fine ah
[Music]
I'm just saying first so did I sing
first I think you sang first I don't
remember how this goes
time
[Music]
good evening
music is pretty quiet yeah it's my first
year I couldn't see if maybe I could
turn it up ah
that's Max we
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
all right let's go
was that okay guys yeah was the music
loud enough
tell us feedback
or else or else we have no never mind
and we have gone
oh sounds good A bit off key that was me
I told her I'm like you're gonna you
might have trouble also it is really
hard for us to hear the music yeah
because we don't have headphones we're
just doing it off of uh it's far away
stickers tiny delay oh we offer them
really like noticeably
um
we got I gotta uh work on my delay with
audio and stuff here at Amish Studio
work in progress that's probably because
there's no go XLR what do you mean Go
Solar always fixes my my delays oh
really oh never had that oh okay only
okay but some offer should we play it
from the phone oh but then they won't be
able to hear it
not too bad not very noticeable okay
okay what are we doing next
um
choose randomly ah sure this one why not
do you have it it's in the yeah it
should be in the Discord chat okay I
have never seen this before but I've
heard it a couple times so I feel like I
can sing it
just had to choose a song and I'm in you
I feel
I feel many Japanese songs
I mean it feels like a good amount for
me is it playing I can't even hear it
louder louder
start again
[Music]
College I think you've seen this better
than me
[Music]
[Applause]
you need me too
I will give you all my love
[Music]
be in love with you
I can't move you're lucky I can't move
I'm stuck here
[Music]
tomorrow
Lucas
[Music]
she doesn't even turn towards me yeah
cause this mirrored for some reason I
always look away from her when I look
there I think it goes one more time yeah
coming up
[Music]
give me the job
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm dancing too
foreign
[Music]
the window washing move this one oh
[\h__\h] just dancing circles around me
literally
sounds funny
I didn't realize that this song was you
know so so obviously me as a teammate
I have a teammate
oh man
I'm for real for real for real just guys
insert yourself
self-insert
I am you
I am youth self-insert yes
they can't dance like you ah it's not
about that no they don't got the moves
I am Kiana yes you are me I am you
represent
all teammates We Are One all for one and
one far oh is that is that a song or
something why am I still wearing the
glasses what the [\h__\h] oh yeah yeah
that's um that's a Japanese oh some kind
of J-pop song
when are we singing next next uh katsu
gets me catch me
foreign
hopefully
wait oh I don't know what the volume is
on that thing
[Music]
stop
take my birthday
[Music]
okay
the lyrics are so fitting too
are they I don't know what it means
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
YouTube
down
[Music]
she looks like a crazy person
I'm having fun yeah yeah
yeah
that's cute yeah thank you we're both
like
struggling equally with the song
I'm sorry
no it's fun I like stuffed karaoke yeah
why you can see when I go on my tippy
toes
I'm taller no if I go on my tippy toes I
love it
we have one more song guys
yeah please do that
yes brother
this is my friend um uh I can't even I
can't even move away I'm stuck here
please please take a boat again no
pictures no pictures no pictures yay hi
I'm
um what's up what's up
is there someone behind me
wait I have an idea you just role play
okay okay
Roblox
headphones
don't remember me it's a really good
song
oh let's sing something together oh
right right away okay
wait is this uh next song
um
no this one yeah what about the songs I
don't see it
where is it that's okay I can find it
yeah
okay
one more song
it is a little bit I feel like the mood
is changing very much of that song all
the songs are sort of happy and sweet
and lovey-dovey and now there's this
song oh yeah that's that's it yeah you
didn't click it properly I have the most
okay
oh
are you ready
[Music]
foreign
whoa
[Music]
you sing first yeah you got up now no
you go
[Music]
where are we together
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
looking at me
I thought it sounded pretty good
where would it where would you even
start from now
oh
this one yeah yeah okay okay
together
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm sorry
paralyzed
[Music]
I'll see you again
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm trying to clap okay
you can do it you can do it I can do it
one hand yeah
a club for you
yeah that was super cool aggressive
singing much feeling yeah much heart I
thought yeah so much uh so much spirit
so it's soul in it yeah yeah staying
there yes much so
I was acting everything out
it's like interpretive dance
I used to do that a lot as a kid it's
pretty fun oh show me no like I used to
do this ribbon dance you know where you
have the stick on the ribbon to dance
yeah I think it can be interpretive
dance oh cute you should do that in the
future like birthday or an anniversary
stream yeah you can probably give you a
ribbon like a a prop yeah and and the
ribbon will like move you just good idea
yeah we'll do it whatever it's so cute
because I think I saw maybe minutes yeah
I think somebody else did it just
without the ribbon oh but don't dance
oh that would be so cute I'm dancing
with a ribbon so girly another sign that
you should come to Girls Talk
ribbon
don't you guys like talk about I don't
know exit something hey thanks
um makeup makeup yeah makeup and hair
stuff and and I don't know we talk about
random stuff like bags and shoes
[Music]
I have two of a woman so
indeed she is
a woman yeah beautiful example of a
lemon yeah yeah so
that was three days in a row yeah a free
edition and again Savannah yeah I was I
think it's really cool I'm glad that you
were here to test everything out and
push it to its limits especially today
like even though we didn't use it this
stream but being able to do what we did
during the last time we tried this
stream earlier today is really cool
because we tried to use my mocap system
to capture both of us at the same time
and I think it looked good but it did
work it was uh I need some more work no
it can't be improved surely surely but
it was really fun for me because I got
to figure out how to do that on my own
yeah it was really cool thank you for
giving me like opportunity to use 3D
because you know alone in Europe I never
you know can do this kind of stuff all
the most I can do is at home 3D yeah
yeah thank you so much if you come back
again to use upgraded Studio When I Get
It upgraded again I belong to actually
because like there's another song that I
really do want to make a music video for
but I'm I like like trying to figure out
if it's like you know
a good idea but yeah I'm gonna be bang
because I had a lot of fun with you and
you fed me so much yummy food like yummy
cookies
please tell me a Denny's for breakfast
yeah yes I think yeah Denny's again for
breakfast
I mean I even tweeted about it I was
craving Dennis but thank you
thank you yeah they forgot to give her
it was pretty sad looking there's like a
pancakes and then there's like one
little egg and that's it look this this
huge container no it was it was two eggs
though it's just very small Oh I thought
it was only one yeah but there was no
meat even though I chose bacon but you
got fruit fruit healthy healthier than
bacon yeah instead of like the hash
browns or whatever and then and I got
the the pancakes
um
cinnamon cinnamon roll pancakes
I guess maybe it's American Commercial
yeah it's a really cute cinnamon stick
and he runs and dances
he's here right now um yeah but he's got
a Jamaican accent ah
[Applause]
it's not gonna work out
do you say Caribbean or Caribbean it
depends I think I interchange between
both
that was a discussion I had the other
day was there even a correct way to say
it dude even Caribbean say it
differently it seems I don't know I
don't know I don't know
I don't know [\h__\h]
Caribbean Caribbean I made up a whole
story about a person called Caribbean
doesn't sound like a name anyway so
three days of amateurally awesome thank
you for using your brain so much I'm
glad I got to do that yeah thank you for
impressing me with your 3D stuff I hope
it I know I know it'll turn out well
because we already did we already
recorded stuff and yeah it looked good
oh God I think so it will be fine it'll
be like do you but even better yeah and
now we eat the watermelon uh yes
the watermelon's over there
let me see
whoa oh yeah like some of them went in
huh I had this pretty deep I went to a
holy [\h__\h] yeah this is why you don't
want to get shot by Airsoft even damn
that's cool it hurt I mean it went
through watermelon skin probably break
yourself smells good oh yeah okay okay
you can have it I already ate the other
ones
oh all right then till we end
yes
smug
it's not even that big it's pretty tiny
in my arm you guys can Photoshop a
little kfp in there oh wait like this
hold it hold it like like this
watermelon watermelon
[Music]
hahaha
now Photoshop the kfb
do it oh oops
all right
let's do it throw it hold on I'm I'm
Gonna Catch It come on
it's my milk oh it does smell good
nice yum
all right
well let's turn the BTM back on at least
what we say
we have to leave we have things to do
so I'm recording to finish oh
oh I can't hear the video I'm pretty
sure it's fine
[Music]
yeah
yeah jamming out
let me let me move it so you can see our
feet
[Music]
don't look at that I see nothing there
was nothing there
[Music]
you dance against me
oh I guess so
and
[Music]
all right I'm back
let's let's make a heart
I think it might be able to can you do
like a thumb up I think I can do a
thumbs up and I'll do what's up with my
skirt it looks so short
is that normal
look at it oh it's the ankle it's a mini
skirt I think it's the angle yeah
because it looks like it's no it's like
way shorter than normal it's an angle
don't worry about keep it that way okay
all right you can do thumbs up I think
I'm trying why is this wrong oh yeah
yeah
my phone died oh find my phone I was
trying to make the the meme with the you
know the meme where a fan takes a photo
with an idol and he tries to make a
heart which really does
it should have been faster I forgot to
put it on charge oh all right well
goodbye everybody I miss dead I take her
home now
I'm stuck here I can't move I have I
can't I can't even say no
Miami
my
um I'm gonna fade out now any last words
all right
that's her last one
goodbye everybody thank you for watching
thank you for waiting for the stream
sorry for the delay yeah sorry but it
worked out in the end and we had fun I
hope you guys had fun and I always have
a lot of fun with Kiara
I'm actually standing right over here
well you could do like the app no you
probably shouldn't say outline bye
all right goodbye everyone
[Music]
foreign