[Music]
[Applause]
no no no no no no
no no no
no no no no no no no no
no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no
no no
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
somebody tell chunky wonky dead I cannot
tend to her now
[Music]
keeps on meowing at me
if I stream she will understand right
foreign
yeah there she goes bye bye turkey wonky
hello
[Music]
how you doing guys we
hello I'm wearing my sash again Tales of
a rice Ambassador and this time it
actually moves with me hey
[Music]
back to my duty do I sound okay I was
playing around with my mixer a lot and I
think I improved some things I hope I
sound okay yeah a new fancy armor made
by an artist who was involved with Tales
of a rise oh what a coincidence oh man
oh how come I chose an artist that was
involved with Tesla rides with a
coincidence
hahaha
um
it's just you know coincidence
everybody I'm excited to present to you
uh a sponsor stream themed towards after
Tales of Horizons
uh recently freshly announced DLC beyond
the dawn yay I have received a new
Mission a new job uh as the tales of
arise official ambassador to the English
region I
um I'm obligated to say that
of the English region
I am super excited oh my God like I am
I didn't imagine I did never imagined
Souls
I really didn't think that there would
be DLC when when Tales of arise ended I
was feeling empty and Hollow
and I thought yeah that's it I have to
wait another who knows how many years
until the next big Mothership game
that's what they call it right two years
ago
is when it first released damn see I
don't know the date anymore but
two years it's been two years man yeah I
think another places they call it
Flagship but then with tails off they
like called it Mothership no
Maybe not maybe I was imagining that
but you know what I mean normally it
takes like years and years until new one
comes out it's not every year
um and I thought well who knows if you
know I'm even still in whole life when
the new one comes out but it was a
pleasure to you know be in charge of
promoting Tales of arise during my time
here and I was like you know man this is
never gonna happen again man this is it
my duties are over but surprise surprise
stop doing posting I'm just being you
know I'm being emotional towards how
lucky I was that such an amazing game
was released
um during my time here and I got to
promote it uh and then big surprise
the reason why it's such a surprise is
because Tales of games don't often do
this you know
releasing DLCs
so it's like super super special every
any everyone who plays the tales off
series understands I think um
so
yes beyond the down down the expansion
for Tales of arise was announced last
week and is currently available for
pre-order
do you hear me do you hear me say ah I
say I use a b
uh I said are you baby
oh okay there it is oh my God
this okay okay okay okay okay that's not
let's not you know
um get angry I'm very angry but let's
not get angry if there is a weird
portion in the archive I will cut it out
uh sorry my yeah
[Music]
my internet provider
let's get back on track I'm so happy
that it's now back in a reasonable time
uh ideally it wouldn't happen again but
I don't know if it will happen again
then we'll reschedule
to a more safer date you know it's night
time here where I am so it could be that
they like to do maintenance in the night
time starting again I'm tweeting
now
okay
so I am sorry
and yeah please feel free to retweet
retweet my tweets that I just tweeted
very irresponsible of them well they
gotta do it at some point but I would
have liked a warning that would have
been nice
yeah uh okay where were we where were we
[Music]
ETO
I think I know where we were uh at the
yeah here
beyond the done the expansion
for Tales of arise was announced last
week very very recently and and is
available for pre-order so we'll take a
look at the latest information
uh together did my tweet not go out my
tweet went out right
and yeah we might want to predict what
the story is like Etc and also reminisce
a little bit about the previous you know
tell the actual game the original game
uh also I just want to say I knew about
this way before you guys but I was also
surprised by the announcement because I
didn't know that the trailer was coming
up at the state of play that caught me
off guard as well yeah what a flex right
I was so surprised as I said before the
stream went down that I really did not
expect the DLC
but I am pleasantly surprised so spoiler
warning for the stream the stream uh
please note that the streaming this
stream will contain spoilers of the main
story of tales of arise so in case you
haven't played the game and you or you
and or you haven't played I haven't
watched my streams of me playing it
and then you know it watch at your own
risk
but I recommend
if you you haven't finished the game
okay I don't think I will give any
spoilers that are like really really
really late game okay there might be
some mid-game spoilers
but hopefully not too late game I will
warn you again before that comes if
something comes up yeah but please play
the game tales of arise the OG game if
you haven't played yet uh and or and or
watch my streams on it um
so I have actually waited to watch the
trailer uh together with you guys
because
as I said I didn't anticipate the
trailer to happen
uh on this one date so I wasn't ready
for it but now we can watch it together
and we can react to it together
Shawnee
also the Chat is dead on the screen let
me see if I can fix that really quickly
um
revive
there it is okay two
more did you guys watch it
cause I waited just for this I I was
patient whoopsie
that I don't know if you saw something
but that was just my my desktop my
pretty well what desktop not yet yes yes
yes not yet
together yes seen it no
okay you didn't know about it until now
there you go I would only want to review
I watched it in the immediately thought
of you yay
okay so many people also waited then
we'll watch it together I think the
audio setting should be correct let me
know if it's like doubling or anything
[Laughter]
one year has passed one is the end of
the great conflict between Dana and Rena
one year after the original games ending
oh so
our journey continues
look cute there she is don't let her get
away after her
she's all here
because her father is a lord nice to
meet you so people are out the truth is
that people always doubt hate and reject
if we go our separate ways we won't
cause each other any problems
and I'm in nowhere
[Music]
are you hungry
if you are I can that's that smirk
the day is ending
but my nerves are calm oh
the voice is so mature oh the hero of
Dana Defenders abomination
oh
oh apple looks so powerful yay
oh was that Magic
let's go
[Music]
all differences must be erased what is
that once there are a lot of differences
there will be
enough
a mask like another mask
because like nothing was always just for
a little longer
be patient
I can't wait that's so real that's so
while breaking just for a little longer
until November 9th be patient
kind of want to watch it again but okay
maybe can we watch it and like stop at
interesting Parts can we it's a short
Trail let's do it
so this is after the merge huh is it
one year has passed since the end of the
great conflict between Dana and
yeah I still saw so many planets though
oh wait this is uh sorry it's already
fading but
uh
what's this place is this the place uh
where the the witch the Witch boss
[Laughter]
which city is this
I don't remember all the city names but
so
[Music]
our journey continues
cause like things are like there she is
don't let her get away after her merge
now her gang's all here
okay so here's my theory for before I
knew it was a girl and she's a daughter
of a lord
white hair
two different eye colors small you know
but this is not the game theory so
dannon's from around here are after her
it's her father it's a lord yeah Dan and
saw after her
because if why are they not at peace
already like
it merged why why not just be happy what
nice to meet you the truth is that
people will always doubt hate and reject
I guess because they still have negative
feelings towards like anything that has
to do with the Lords because they slave
enslaved them I guess
so they're just yeah old grudges still
which grudges were against you know
grudges against
all kinds of people that are not the
same people as you were the reason why
there were so many conflicts in the
first place in their worlds and now
they're continuing it have they not
learned
oh we're already having heated
discussions man if we go our separate
ways we won't cause each other any
problems it's like in the spaceship
which maybe crashed and then there's
like a earth growing over and or so am I
going crazy and I'm in no pain
right
[Applause]
in most important question is there
gonna be more hoodles or no
if you are I can fix that
the day is ending
but my nerves are calm
how's it the hero of Dana defend this
abomination
oh and anyway
truly Phoenix Vibes oh my God look at it
what and that his eye
what's in his eyes
What's Happening Here
is is is is she
sucking some energy out of them
she she looks kind of like
negatively shook like she's like what
are you doing her stance looks like that
the others also kind of on edge like I
could see I could imagine them seeing
this for the first time
and they're like yeah what are you doing
[Music]
two different eye colors could possibly
be very very very complicated characters
like
it's like one eye color represents like
a different personality of theirs hiding
inside you know
so what is this mask and why is she
looking absolutely terrible maybe maybe
she had to wear it and this is the
remains of the massive how big is the
mess all the differences must be erased
once they're
[Music]
putting my hand on my face normally
well your face is a bit bigger than your
hand maybe it's not her because it looks
kind of
kind of because that's also just a part
of it is it it could be horoscope
someone else's ah
and maybe she
she puts it on again though like what if
but didn't she like maybe feel
negatively about it there will be
I feel you elephant he's so upset
because he doesn't understand what's
going on me neither
just for a little longer
be patient
there must be much going on here I I can
tell yeah okay okay okay okay okay
the ball run well okay well
theorize something about Wolverine but
isn't born dead huh
anyway okay that was that
um
okay okay oh my God
uh BDM
turn yourself back on please
thank you and take a while until it
starts rolling
hello by the way who says spoiler alert
we watched the trailer we did that
letter the hoodle turned into pixel was
so shook by that
he's like fading away turning into
pixels
okay letter from official team of Bandai
Namco Tales of a rise and they're
talking to me guys
thank you kiana-san for always making
Tales of arise so much fun to play
you're welcome and for your enjoyable
video of the main game to the very end
yeah my stream I played until the very
end yeah it has been two years since you
became our ambassador today
and gave us your passionate support even
before the release of the game yes
I can't believe how hyped I was and I'm
so freaking hyped now oh my God nothing
can bring down my hype not even the uh
internet provider
and a number of fans continues to grow
as this latest title is loved by people
all over the world thanks to this we
will finally be releasing a DLC on
November 9th 2023 which is how long to
go it's almost October like a bit like
two and
not even two months right
yeah not even two months
called
tales of
tails oh the tales of a rise beyond the
dawn
I wanted to emphasize it which is a
large-scale storyline expansion to the
original game large scale storyline
expansion we hope that you will support
us again as an official ambassador of
course
my dream came true once again yeah okay
so apparently there is an ambassador
mission for me well
[Music]
I have something to do something
specific what could it be
oh number one let's find out the latest
news on the new DLC for Tales of arise
with everyone at kfp
easy easy
aren't we doing that right now so we can
we not already check that one out
maybe not
number two in order to spread the appeal
of tales of arise which is once again
gaining
oh it's kind of written differently
oh no yeah I have a more more uh
complicated version of what's written
there uh oh it's all one one
ignore that number two in order to
prevent the appeal of tails of horizon
which is once again gaining momentum we
would like to invite drum roll
am I announcing this for the first time
who has been playing Tales of Symphonia
and Tales of the Abyss and is interested
in Tales of a rise yeah
collaboration with me baby
it's just gonna be like the the Japanese
ambassador
maybe I don't know but uh I I will I
guess take her hand and lead her deeper
and deeper into the rabbit hole that has
tails off I was really like
so excited when I saw that she's like
playing Tales of Symphonia and teles on
her streams yeah but it's a bad time she
gets into Tales of her eyes oh my God
yes
[Music]
yum ah I also want to stream more tales
off games
so please do a streaming a stream
introducing her as an ambassador oh
oh so that means she will be like an
ambassador okay yeah let's go I'm in yes
so we are gonna be doing a stream
together next week
on Tales of arise beyond the dawn yeah
together
you have been appointed Ambassador as
well it seems yay by the way uh oh yeah
this is number three AKA number one
they're all important
and it has already been two years since
he became an ambassador do you remember
Tales of arise well
in the following sections we will
occasionally interrupt for the
Ambassador Ambassador Ambassador license
update test
don't take it away from me no it's all I
have it's all I got no please complete
the quiz and show us your performance as
an official ambassador
wow
well I wish you best of luck from the
tales of arise official team
oh okay okay so there will be like some
quizzes to ask
um yeah some questions or something I
suppose exciting though Bring it on I
actually just played this over rise
right before the stream
so everything is fresh in my memory no
not everything definitely not everything
where are all the hoos let me tell you
all the locations of the hoodles now yes
Corner number one
is this the right slide
uh if maybe yeah yeah yeah yeah and
tales of a rise main story let's review
the main story so a little bit of uh an
overview from yours truly maybe you
already got a an idea of it by watching
the new trailer but Tales of her eyes
centers originally centers on the planet
of uh Dan which is ruled over by the
people of say it with me Reina Reina
Reina yes correct and that is the
neighboring Planet
so the problem is Rana like
steals all the resources and energy from
Dana yeah and then not happy because
it's being like sucked the life out of
it and people are there uh just like
Alvin are being like enslaved to do work
yeah in really really
bad conditions like Mining and stuff you
know
and yeah yeah yeah and then Alvin meets
Shion and it's uh you know from there on
the story starts
so in terms of a rise celebrates the
25th anniversary of the tales of series
now the blue thingy here it won the best
RPG award at the cave Awards yay I
forgot it did that I would I I think I
forgot about that that's amazing
congratulations I'm pretty sure I was
aware of it at the time and probably
pretty freaking proud too
it sold a total of two points
is worldwide in June at the point of
June of this year
it's playable on PS5 PS4 Xbox series X S
Xbox One and steam we played it mostly
on PS4 but then we changed to PS5 at the
end I think because they made it
possible to move over your save file
really really cool so yeah great game
that we enjoyed thoroughly
[Music]
and now we will try to remember
something spoiler alert again
just in case you'd missed the first
couple ones
yeah we will react to the memories
oh remember these people remember their
names
yes and
my favorite of course my wife is kisara
opened my eyes to a new world
but honestly for like Alpha and the main
protagonist generally I'm always lying
you know I love my girl characters but
Alpha is a great main character because
he he kind of like for me is the perfect
kind of main character in terms of
Personality like he's not uh I prefer
like mature types of characters over the
more
um you know young energetic Crazy Ones
he's mature down to earth he's cool
he's got like fire in his body
mm-hmm you know what I mean yeah he's a
great lead for the game and he has so
much chemistry with xion too actually
everybody has such good chemistry even
though in the beginning everybody has
like you know you know fought with Tyler
uh what's the what's that in English
again
um Pride and Prejudice Prejudice uh
against each other over each other
um
yeah but they all work so well together
it's a great team together
um
yeah they they didn't really like each
other here and there but we worked over
the the Prejudice and we became besties
for Life yeah so I was Alvin and xion
rinwell and LA on the right side and on
the left side
who was one of the Lords
who were like
for the most part evil but he was like
decent so we accept him in our team
[Applause]
can't Overlook law
very powerful punches here's some some
scene flashbacks
top left is like the beginning of the
game right where he's still like working
in the like mining camp thingy
wearing his full mask
kind of resembling the mask from our new
character I don't know
yeah uh top right I actually don't
remember what is this
what is this
you tell me guys if you remember and
bottom right is she on suffering with
her foreigns that are you know making
her Untouchable is it the first boss
well that makes sense
yeah and bottom left is the I think the
first time we fight the mysterious
very mysterious handsome guy who I
originally fought and I was very certain
of it I think
that it just was alphaned from the
future or so
didn't I say that
I'm pretty sure that's what I was saying
I was making up so many crazy uh
theories back then
honestly a decent guest they look kind
of similar and I thought that would also
be the reason why they cloaked him so
much
to kind of like not immediately reveal
who he really is but you know it was a
fun family it wasn't a spoiler because
it wasn't true
but maybe you wanted to think that on
you know that it was that
fear we're crafting very fun but that's
just the theory I'll claim Fury all
right here's some more scenes emotional
we had many emotional scenes with she on
an elephant
yeah and oh yeah on the bottom right we
see an anime scene it's the top bottom
left also one maybe
um but yeah sometimes
um there would be anime like drawn
animated scenes
uh for like really really special
moments and they were really really
pretty
um but I must say though just just to
praise
Tales of a rise into the heavens uh that
the 3D animations there's so many like
really high quality 3D cutscenes
some of them will look into in a little
bit
um that really are just
they're so high quality because the the
facial
expressions the emotions are conveyed so
strongly through that in my opinion and
also the the body Motions like
everything is so smooth and everything
is so detailed
um
so uh I was so excited every time there
was a cutscene and there are so many
beautiful cutscenes
so it's it's great it's like uh you're
watching a movie honestly
um
yeah yeah on display on the top left
image you see xion's shion's emotions
like I was just to prepare for the
stream I was watching back on some
cutscenes and I was like oh my God like
this
oh
this conveys so many emotions it's crazy
yeah
and here we have the whole team and I
went prepared preparing for the stream I
found this screenshot very interesting
we gotta get back to that in a moment
because
it's also in the trailer I think we have
to talk about it later okay okay okay
yeah this is uh the end I guess but um
we have to talk about this okay don't
forget about it so
we are gonna
look at our first ambassador
fastest
guess the number one
listeners vote what is everyone's
favorite popular scene
oh okay I will make a call
uh that you guys can vote but before you
vote I make my guess of what I think
uh you guys will choose
there's four choices of scenes and I
this is why I was prepping before the
stream uh there's uh these scenes that I
captured three of them I captured from
my own streams so we can react to me
reacting to them
and the fourth one
I did that
I did not
not a team
and my own playthrough
and I'm like what
there's a hot spring
in this game
why did you guys not make me see it
how could I miss it you don't remember
it either I was trying to get it uh
before the Stream
but you have to do so much to do it it's
I would think many people would miss it
um
it's special but I mean
it's obviously a very special reward for
you for people who did a lot in the game
yeah so
we will look at the scenes together are
you ready I I captured them they're kind
of long because I wanted there to be
context but they're so worth it okay
and let's start with the top left which
is already such a heavy hitting scene ah
it's uh for people who need a little bit
of context beforehand this is death fear
the father of one of our main characters
long
and they don't have a good relationship
um law just doesn't like the fear
definitely tries everything but you know
and
until this happens
oh wait
okay gotta hide this okay
it's kind of long guys it's eight
minutes
but it will be good okay
two hours
reacts to Wawa
is that the Lord
objects and slaves
I Lord cannabelt valkyrus
it's very emotional okay
passionate the Brazen worm who would
dare threaten the peace so this is one
of the Lords
no
evil Lord
he then made them made the mistake of
thinking he could hide it
we have to save him and engrave this
edict into your souls no such fool's
right to life in sislavia shall be
forfeit
[Music]
now embedded
you should listen carefully
I couldn't believe that before they were
going through this I am prepared to
offer you an unprecedented it took a
while to realize that this was really
happening
please
[Music]
give them up before those assembled
he would never do that
fine time I have
Zephyr protects the crew
because he's a good guy
make it louder
okay they're still just hitting him
thank you for the membership feeling the
urge to tell everybody no
you can tell them where we are we're on
our way here anyways
do you want me to say
[Music]
um
first tell the people about the mistakes
you made then the whereabouts of you why
why am why though
[Music]
why tell people what does that do for
him mistakes huh he's giving him an
opening for a good moment
good story moment I've made so many
things
gonna come and save him
it's not gonna happen because he's
watching the broadcast all my life I've
had to fight
but I have known nothing but love
[Music]
I was so caught up in the struggle to
survive in this world
neglecting my own family yeah he's
listening
I don't think you did anything wrong
with that fear
I have lost so many good friends
hmm
I even lost my wife my son
but he's still there I'll never be able
to fix these mistakes not a single one
it sounds to me as if the greatest
mistake of your life was never learning
to stay down when you were beaten
so sad
a good man once told me if I take up
this fight I'd have to pay a price
[Music]
turns out he was right
just feels like very retrospective
the very people and things I was
fighting to protect them
payment
he's such a good guy
don't
I don't regret keeping up the fight for
a second
about a single day goes by
what I do not think about what I have
lost
not telling others how much they truly
meant to me before it was too late that
is your answer that's the greatest
mistake of my life
do yourselves a favor and never become
like me but you were great but you were
great
don't continue
until it's too late to fix them
but ask yourself what it is you couldn't
bear to lose
what do you want to protect with all of
your might
roll down and never let God
listen to that voice deep inside of you
together no one can hold you back and
the same goes for the ones the lord
inside your own hearts
no no no no no
[Music]
let's go along
save your father
he's still hanging in there
hanging that's kind of mean to say he's
really hanging
okay
I've been such an idiot so then you
think he's fine right you think oh okay
thank God
ah
I need to think all is well not exactly
the best time to catch up no
no should I cut it here or should I let
you see what happens after
you're right about that still the same
cutscene so you know the sun are you
until all this was over
I'll see too with the person at fault is
reprimanded appropriately
what
oh well you've served your purpose more
excellently than anyone could have hoped
the gang the gang is so late suffer
if it isn't the infamous alphen of
calaglia yes and he's joined by his
fellow conspirators the likes of traitor
we will kill you dude they're not
conspirators enjoy the time you have
left on this Earth yes it looks so which
is not earth and they're not alone
oh yeah
violence oh manic you finally made it
Reynolds is so cute the rain is over
right now
hey look you hear me they look like
you're related to one another
wait a second
type of Shameless face
[Music]
but
but that's a Master Core what
no no no no no no no no
so the master cores react to each other
I see how interesting
yeah
no so you thought he'd survive it's over
yeah it's just a puppet
he's just a puppet yeah it's really cute
every second
yeah let's cut it there
let's cut it there
and
that just hit so hard because you
thought he was safe
and then they go through with it after
all
killing a father of the main character
on screen like normally parents die
before the game begins and everybody's
just like yeah I don't have parents oh
yeah I don't have parents either oh what
a coincidence I don't have parents
either my parents died here and there my
parents died here and there but they do
it here in in our game and it hurts so
much if I wasn't laughing at me saying
the same things as I did before I would
have cried
now this is such a powerful powerful
scene
um
and La tried to fix it and reunite at
the very last moment but it was too late
long
yeah
so the number two
is
also a pretty long one
um maybe I can cut it early but I feel
like if we need the whole scene but you
know let's watch
do you remember back when I was stabbed
this is pretty late game guys spoiler
alert
yeah I do I thought for sure that he had
killed you back there
that wasn't the first time
the first time
was when I was only a child
after that no matter how often
couldn't die
who couldn't die so you're Immortal
how's that even
foreign
tell me how how is something like that
possible
thorns
they're me but at the same time not
they're part of me
I have no idea why
but my Thorns will never let me die
at least not before I meant to being she
on is suffering I can't die before your
death
when my Thorns free themselves
[Music]
it will be my death
I've seen it
a darkness that swallows up everything
until nothing remains
division of Oblivion I can't escape
this also sounds like retrospection
sounds like Cali's rap lyrics no that
sounds like retrospective Paula no
matter what I tell myself
she's outdated it's not
yeah
wait the whole reason you
needed the Renaissance was to get rid of
your Thorns right so we thought
if I burn away what's inside
and what will happen to the rest of me
yeah
right we can't know either way you look
at it I'm going to die
but if I am going to die I figure I can
at least take my Thorns out with me
that's
what I've been after this whole time
[Music]
that's why you turned your back on your
fellow rennets and chose to fight with
us isn't it
[Music]
well we've all been fighting to keep on
living
you have been with us fighting
desperately to die that's so depressing
right
that was the plan
but then I met all of you
and I
[Music]
before I knew it I didn't want to die
anymore hmm
[Music]
don't lose hope yet
we'll find a way to save you
there's still time to
pointless why because the darkness won't
just consume me
truth is
it will consume all of existence as well
it was only a suspicion at first
ever since the red woman triggered my
maiden powers
I've been more certain than ever before
it was then
[Music]
that I finally came to realize
my Powers were holding my Thorns in
check the entire time
[Music]
but they don't anymore
not since then I guess oh when the wedge
fell um
every day I feel the Thorns power
growing stronger inside of me
soon
I won't be able to hold them back
anymore
and when that happens
all existence
no
and that's why you wanted to leave by
yourself
you planned to find the renaissama on
your own and sacrifice yourself to stop
the thorns
[Music]
we won't let that happen
I didn't care what happened to me or
anyone else
and what happened to the renins or the
dannins didn't matter to me at all yeah
she was pretty
ignorance I know I have to die
but I don't want to
now that I have this
come on friendship
magical friendship I wish we had never
met ah then I wouldn't have to feel him
don't say that oh
that's it
he doesn't feel pain
[Music]
it's no better than being the slave how
can you endure this elephant
[Music]
I don't care what anybody says
I won't let it happen
yeah well here he kind of like this
fight until he get into strong
[Music]
before
oh look at him look at his face look at
her face
even if it should mean
that it'll be the end of everything else
Tito's eyes
squinting out of desperation that's
detailed baby what do you want so you
want
your decision ultimately
but if you decide not to fight fate
I will
even if I have to do it alone
no plot chicken you won't be alone
I'll fight as well
as well Count Me In as well
I want to be a force for good not hate
hey
and me too
I meant it with all of my heart when I
told you before neither of you are alone
in this at all she's so pretty
nice
and I for one don't believe this Venture
is without hope
she honest the descendant of a maiden
from 300 years ago given the
circumstances it seems very likely that
those events have something yeah that's
where I cut it because that's when some
music starts it's already long enough
but yeah
yeah
yeah when you get this scene after
playing the game for so many hours it's
it's quite quite emotional because like
it really looks like right before the
scene it looks like she's about to leave
on her own and we catch her right before
thankfully
um
yeah it's it's so emotional their facial
expressions just oh chef's kiss
okay next one is really short so don't
worry
it was in a boss fight but not today
he's panicking
I can't I can't let him use that but I
don't have really anything
it was a one-on-one fight very intense
myself
[Music]
oh it's okay
from being controlled but that's a fact
of never-ending hatred
don't you understand
only hand in destruction
[Music]
disgust me
it's wrong
it takes true power to forgive [\h__\h] oh
slam dunk
y'all
awesome
strong shall always Triumph here it was
like one of those fighting games
[Music]
yeah that's the Warren scene
and they're The Wolverine Showdown
it was very intense the fight was really
intense
always like it when uh you know you you
lose your party members and you gotta do
it all on your own that's when it feels
like really really really panicky and
intense
oh there's one more that the one that I
have not had the pleasure to experience
uh and there's this one's like way too
long if I show both parts so question do
you want to see the hot spring guys
version or your hot spring girls version
you know the answer don't you
you don't know of course
yeah I knew it I knew it and one second
I didn't put this one in in the right
placement because this one I added kind
of last minute uh what's up
[Music]
okay
the the guys one though I personally
found to be actually more funny than the
girls one but you know girls are cute
girls are cute girls girls girls girls
girls are cute
so yeah bias let's go
home
[Applause]
ah
I feel alive again
that's from the youngest of us
really though
this is nice
[Music]
I never imagined I'd get to have a group
bath with you girls
[Music]
your Skin's so Flawless Girls Talk how
do you do it you must tell us your
Secret Girls taco lab thanks girls
it looks so silky smooth
remember
you're so muscular kisara
I'll pretend I didn't hear that renwell
why not law what
there are some walls that boys are meant
to surmount what does that mean
why does he understand that he's
supposed to be the stupid guy only by
surmounting said walls does a boy become
a man
oh and doesn't so happens I can assist
with that oh
[Music]
wait there's something
are you game
this is an important right of manhood
right
speaking and listening is an important
right of man a lot of principles
it's not a bad thing
I wouldn't deny me the chance to be a
man would you what indeed you wouldn't
take away the opportunity for a young
person to flourish
that's pretty cool but he can be kind of
dense sometimes he went a while not
feeling any pain
you can't deny you're a match Shion
oh
yeah totally oh she got the signal
and she sends manageable
that's what you get
what was that for renwell
the dirty-minded Devils that's what to
happen
oh my God and then there's he's burning
there in the background ah that was the
girls scene from The Hot Spring
oh my God I can't believe it I can't
freaking believe it okay let me guess
you don't say anything yet I would say
my favorite was
[Music]
um
either one or two they just both so
emotional it's like hard to not choose
any other
um
I remember one hit me really hard but
two maybe hit me even harder back then
in the actual playthrough so okay wait
wait wait
wait don't eat it yeah I have to guess
what you guys I think you guys will go
for two
uh let me do let me do it here and which
one was your favorite
one
two
three or four go I say you like two
but I mean the last one though was spicy
[Laughter]
the the guy one is also so funny though
they're both so good how did I know
how's it going how's the poll going no
no I'm not ringing it what do you mean
I'm rigging it I need to guess before
like we have to you know be in sync
that's the mission
um
trying to click one but click two but I
accidentally well there is no turning
back I think the
poll results are clear it's a two is
winning by a landslide so
I think we are properly in sync thank
you very much thank you soon I win this
Mission yay that's 20 points for me
our matches our taste match tastes match
uh perfectly don't they Yahoo
okay
now that we finished this Mission we
shall take a closer look at Beyond The
Dawn and I am like totally over time but
I don't care because we had you know
like 20 minutes down time right and also
I just want to talk about Tales of our
eyes so
um everything's okay I'm doing this on
my own on my own choice
I can unpin the message oh yeah thank
you
okay so
what is the new DLC beyond the dawn
Beyond done is a massive expansion that
is expected to take about 20 hours to
play filled with a story that depicts
the world after the ending of the main
game and quests that delve deeper into
the personal lives of each of the party
characters yeah we'll find out more
about everybody hopefully the scale of
the game is such that it can be called
Tales of arise 1.5
going beyond the realm of DLC so they
claim and it will make you fall in love
with the world of arise even more
it's like your your love arises again
can you say that
yeah the story is about 20 hours yeah
20 plus maybe mm-hmm
and there will be new enemies new
dungeons
new subquests new additional costumes
probably new skits as well of course and
I wonder if there will be new hoodles
but I cannot confirm that
I don't know about that but I wish I
wish
so uh plus some extra information for
fans who have already played the main
game if you're curious the story takes
place as we heard one year after the
final battle
however and this point is important
because it confused me
the story takes place before
that illustration you know the one the
one special illustration of the end
credits
so I'm not gonna say what don't say a
chat for the people who don't want to
get too spoiled
um so it's it's before
hmm that one image that implies
something heavily
so it is a story about the questions and
answers left to the main character alfen
and the personalities of the party that
were not told in the main game as if to
say there was such a story before that
ending so we'll get a lot more uh closer
looks into everybody's personalities and
after stories that I was very curious
about anyway you know like everybody
looked so happy in the end but you know
I wanna I wanna look closer at that so
since the story takes place after the
Two Worlds of Dana and Rana right now
Rana have merged the maps are different
from those in the main story in
particular the lives and conditions of
the people living in each area have
changed dramatically so yeah we shall
travel around again to see how
everything looks differently
so that made me think
this image
is from the trailer right
but then
this is this the same place is what I
was thinking but like this is before the
merch
and this is after the merch
because it looks kind of similar but
kind of different there's like the same
kind of like land geography in my
opinion with the water and all that and
you know this like Peak but then
like some extra things and some things
are missing because it's merged you know
I mean it's not entirely but see those
Towers those Towers
those circular Towers they kind of look
like that don't you think it looks like
the same Cliff yeah there's more land
though here I guess because it's being
filled up
because of the merge good observation
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
yeah I think so
that's why they're showing it probably
so that we realize hey this might be the
same place
only makes sense to me so yeah
[Music]
um
what kind of story is beyond the dawn
let's look closer at the screenshots
from the announcement trailer like here
they are walking together
have not yet happening that much after
ever
uh and here they meet this girl is this
real I wonder if this is like in the
game actually chronologically the moment
where they meet her but the city in the
background looks like it's doing really
well
kind of like you know everything looks
uh cleaned up and pretty I think those
are like huge flowers pink flowers in
the background everything looks neat
and they
are
sussing out this new girl and renwell
and law are sussing out each other I
guess
um
real subtle there thank you and here's
some moments
where yeah we explored some places in
the trailer and then what is happening
on the top right I don't know but Alvin
doesn't want this to happen it seems the
bottom right was so badass
let's go
and yeah yeah I was saying yeah I think
it's like the crashed ship
being like overgrown with Earth
here we have some more screenshots The
Masks The Mask brings up so many
questions and then Ballroom
why is he back didn't we please remind
me did we not take care of him properly
[Music]
is this gonna be like surprise I'm back
but I thought we took care of him
properly
maybe it's a flashback oh
he's super dad he blew up in the end
okay okay
yeah it might be a flashback
hopefully it's a flashback
yeah but uh
so people are saying maybe they're
related but I
I will show because isn't that maybe a
little bit um
well well well so let's learn a little
bit about NASA meal um
[Music]
um let me read this
foreign
interesting name a girl with unique
blood and Power
oh
she was fostered in then I guess but due
to constant scorn from an early age she
has closed her mind and has come to
feign indifference and emotionlessness
toward everything
oh she Harbors a deep sense of
inferiority due to her own uniqueness
and she has already given up on the idea
of being accepted by anyone
we will accept her whether she likes it
or not she must accept that we accept
her except with
she was chased out of the town she had
stopped in while wandering alone
oh she met Alvin and his party and you
can't read it probably but it says party
outfit in this party
I like the character design
I like the the hair is pretty it's like
you know she gotta cut her bangs but
besides that
um
yes I wonder how young she is because
she looks really young but maybe it's
just uh
you know sometimes sometimes they look
young but they're not
so
I have another thing to read out here
that sounds kind of similar but I'll
read it anyway after the battle of the
Fate for the fate of the Two Worlds
Alvin and his party meet a young girl
named azamil who is the daughter of a
Brennan Lord and a Dane and will the six
be able to change the fate of the girl
who will eventually fall
is this spoiler
it's written here I have to say it well
the six being able to change the fate of
the girl who will eventually fall under
the curse of the Mask
I mean yeah it's kind of like maybe
implied in the trailer something is
happening with the mask but did you guys
know
you guys know that it's a it's a cursed
mask
I didn't think it was like stated that
clearly
explore the world again with party
members who are bound together by a
strong bond now a male meets the six is
friends but will they turn out to be
enemies huh Lebanese
so which Lord's daughter is nada meal
what does the mask have to do with it we
don't know oh
and here it says the girl's father was a
random Lord who once ruled this land as
a ruler yeah her mother however was a
slave of the denim oh
oh
[Music]
how did that happen
although of privilege descent she was
shown by her own father and persecuted
from an early age to her to her Origins
why why does the father shun her like he
did that he created this no
um I guess it's like a mistress but
still like I mean
[Music]
her mother was a
slave
interesting
I wonder if we'll find out who the
mother is to and if the mother is
someone we know to or or it's just a
random new character
[Music]
yeah
oh oh okay we have a test
another test guess the correct answer
with the audience okay okay are you
ready for this guys
the mother was isn't that what that said
yeah that's how I understood it the
mother was a Danon slave
oh oh okay that's how I interpret my my
mind auto corrected it then okay so
ready okay concentration everybody
concentrate what is happening in this
scene
uh-huh the scene where xion finds Rin
well
and holds her head by the way these are
exclusive screenshots that were not in
the trailer apparently okay so the scene
where she finds run well and holds her
hand feeling because
this doesn't necessarily mean that the
words that are supposed to be put in
there are this length by the way
yeah I would say feeling like happy
because like she can touch her now
I guess that would make sense yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah what do you think
guys
[Music]
hand holding is not lewd and tears of a
rise okay they have different standards
happy because no foreign sounds right to
me
same same
you can show this on stream yes
happy because friendship
happy because reunion
[Music]
yeah yeah re reunion I wonder how long
they did meet I thought they would be
like still besties and meet all the time
after the game ended but maybe in that
one year they didn't meet much
um but I would say uh like just happy to
touch her hand
I guess yeah I guess it could be a
reunion kind of situation maybe it's
both like happy to reunite and happy to
touch
okay then we shall look at the correct
answer and the scene where Shion finds
renewal and holds her hand feeling happy
uh-huh because the curse has been lifted
oh oh and she is able to touch people
again after a long time yeah
[Applause]
yeah
right I told you long answer
don't judge by the words that are hidden
um
easy easy
just gotta put one-on-one together and
get number 25 points okay
nice that one was fairly easy let's see
if we get the next one correctly
another screenshot that apparently
hasn't been on the trailer
a scene in which nazamil who is
unfamiliar with
due to her upbringing is
I'm pretty sure that's supposed to be
cut off before him
well I mean it's probably
from unfamiliar with
kindness of people but also this place
and where this is is this in in
dohalem's uh city right
so
yeah she probably wasn't there before
ever yeah
um
the culture
the kindness yeah kindness of people
I'm familiar with personal relationship
is afraid of the Holland you think she's
afraid she doesn't look so afraid her
face looks like kind of unimpressed but
but not like not afraid
[Music]
I'm familiar with City customs and is
falling into Holland oh that's kind of a
cute answer
that would be cute if she's just like
following but she doesn't seem like
she's like that
um open to being Titi and
you know
yeah yeah cause yeah
[Music]
um
yeah because she's she probably doesn't
want to open up to them right away that
easily
right she's baiting him
I'm familiar with communicating with
other people and nervous and shy
what
her dad was a lord so maybe she's
interested in learning more about Lords
in general
questioning
I will say
it's
well she's unfamiliar with
generally the surroundings
here because she hasn't been
out much because of her upbringing
and is therefore
um
wary of dohalem
Maybe
ah how about
how about suspicious of those
[Music]
Ah that's that doesn't make quite
that much sense
[Music]
I think everybody's suspicious of her
not so much she's suspicious of them but
um
what do you want to lock in guys
she looks like she's listening to him
yeah but is it such an easy word that
they're gonna put in there
just listening to him
okay okay asking questions okay let's do
like listening and asking questions okay
questioning yeah okay okay
let's check out the answer
a scene in which Nathaniel who is
unfamiliar with common sense and the
life of Dan and Rana people due to
upbringing is questioning the Ninja
well
more or less
I would say more or less
right close enough close enough
questioning
yay liking Common Sense oh that'll be
uh an interesting character to meet yeah
we will teach her Common Sense honestly
she only was kind of lacking Common
Sense too
somehow so also honestly law as well
nah maybe not love
dualim was also kind of lacking common
sense sometimes like everybody was in
some way somewhere lacking some kind of
Common Sense every now and then
[Music]
half the cast yeah
law is a lost cause yeah
renwell was not renwell was pretty good
yeah pretty normal okay
I'm gonna quickly switch
um
my PowerPoint
because for the second half I have an
updated one
um
[Music]
it's this one
a moment
uh yeah that looks right okay then we
cleared that mission I would say I mean
who's gonna be the judge here
I say it's me
oh yeah so and next corner is costumes
we'll talk about costumes that are
bundled with the DLC that will be
available
so we have first and foremost here
um the expansion download oh you get
special data six costumes plus a special
Quest oh
a silver weapon set mm-hmm
and a travel support pack of items the
outfits look cute cute
I wonder
like what what's Sheila and Alvin are
wearing
I feel like have I seen this before in
an illustration I don't know but
it looks like they're getting ready for
uh some food
matching cute
and honestly rainbow might be one of my
favorites out of this out of these
brainwell
once again an absolute cutie pie
right
who's your favorite
when was the best year right
I wanna get that outfit for her yeah
she's so adorable
so
um this time you know available for
digital pre-order if you pre-order you
will receive an outfit as a pre-order
bonus item
and yes yes we have more
screenshots oh wait her hair is so nice
too like we had a braided ponytail
thingy before but this one's kind of
different it's like lower cuter more
loose
and oh my God renwell's so cute oh
look like oh guards or so I guess
very very fancy everybody no
does this outfit not like obviously
imply something
can't tell me it doesn't
she even got a cute tiara
whoa and they got like flowers on their
man or is that I don't know
I I I think it does yeah
no they're just good friends
[Music]
[Laughter]
expression he looks pretty cute here
it's like he looks like head empty no
fonts
right
cute and then we have these two oh very
serious these two I feel like are always
so serious
nice side ponytail covering one eye on
my beloved kisara yeah yeah yeah always
so classy looking yeah is in deep deep
thought what are we thinking about here
what are we thinking about how to
improve the world and save the world
once more from this weird mysterious
girl perhaps
[Music]
and then
for this this is uh another outfit I
have a actually a video for this so let
me show you this wow
it was
yes these two outfits are actually
um something that was shown in the
second anniversary illustration that was
celebrating Tales of arise a while ago
and they were wearing that in that
illustration and it's now a DLC outfit
outfit yeah they're looking very slick
like first we have those like white uh
fancy outfits and now we have these
black ones with Shion being in short
pants though and that's a really
interesting hairstyle though
[Music]
um
waito and waitress that looks like
waiter outfits to you I don't know I
don't think so it even says elegant
costume
so digital pre-order bonus if you want
to get the game just pre-order it
because you're gonna get all this cool
stuff right so
you gotta
it's the only thing that makes sense
looks like formal party wear yeah I mean
I could also kind of see them wearing
that at uh the waiters of a really
really really fancy party like a royal
party
um you convinced me wow
official Ambassador my work here is done
Okay so
now after we looked at all the fancy
outfits and you know how much I love
dressing up my my team in the cutest
outfits of my liking
we are gonna continue
oh wait there's one more image exclusive
cookie
cooking new ones it looks so good oh so
yeah there's uh there's these four
versions oh
Edition that has a special cover wow the
deluxe edition of The Ultimate Edition
I don't know which one I will get
a hard choice
but yeah you got some time to decide
just make sure to pre-order before the
game comes out and then you get all the
fancy stuff
yeah and now we have
four one two three ten
million points apparently I didn't
decide this the staff decided this okay
I was winning already anyway I didn't
need this extra extra points
but what 10 million
Ambassador test number four as an
official Ambassador and dance beyond the
dance
okay hey it is easy leave it to me
let me just drink some water
oh
you have enough to skip this no I think
I have to do this
so everybody have I convinced you yet to
pre-order Tales of arise beyond the dawn
which is gonna be released on November
9th so keep checking back for more
information maybe we'll do more streams
especially the one with Subaru stand by
Chance the rise beyond the dog expansion
includes the main storyline as well as
special data with additional costumes
struggle and content featuring The Hero
heroin pre-order the expansion now for
9 USD did you hear that I said 29.99 USD
and get bonus customization items and
cooking recipes oh my God we love to
cook let you cook let you cook and you
and you so check out the PS Store Xbox
store and
incidentally for those who haven't
played the main or Rice game and are
starting from scratch a bundle version
wait
wait tears of arise beyond the dawn
Edition that includes the main game and
DLC will be available at the same time
for her a whopping and totally fitting
59.99 US dollars so I recommend it to my
friends who haven't played it yet you
and yo and ukfb you have to play it why
have you not played it yet if you
haven't played it yet this is the one I
choose for you I make your choices I
make your life choices they are the
smartest of them all I'd also like to
recommend this one for Subaru Senpai
perhaps for next week streaming oh if
she wants to get into it she has to get
this complete version get it all get it
together
and also
um
dear Bandai Namco hotels team please let
me um stream the game later on because I
will stream it
I want to stream the DLC
yeah please please thank you
Tesla rise beyond the dawn pre-order
[Music]
no
Link in the description I think
[Music]
yeah mission accomplished even though
there were Stones put in my way
no referral links no no I don't think we
had one last time either
uh just a normal link but maybe they
will look at the time things were bought
and they will see a spike right after my
stream who knows so maybe do it now
pretty sure you had a link last time
well I really well what I have is what I
have so just click what's in the
description yeah
uh that's fine that's fine
do you get bonus points if we order from
your description I I don't think it
tracks but uh it's okay it's okay
just uh I think it's fine
they trust me
they trust me so and next week I think
on Tuesday me and somebody stand by I'm
gonna have a collaboration stream uh
about Tales of Iran's beyond the dawn so
check that out if you want I would be
very happy very delighted to have you
there and yeah it was nice to look back
onto some very memorable scenes of tales
of arise
to also you know maybe get ready
emotionally for the unexpected but
pleasantly surprising DLC
your first collab Japan friend that's
true she was my first Senpai Colombia
yeah yeah I'm so happy that she likes
tails off games because it's my favorite
series of games in the world
oh
you should play a simple
wait she played dinner sheep didn't she
play it on the GameCube
did she stream it from a GameCube
do we know
because
oh my God
she already finished it right but I
would love
to play the PS3 but you can also
multiply on PS3 right
I will suggest that
I'll go over to her place and I will
play a little Tales of Symphonia
together
like how I played with my brother back
in the day when I was like small small
Wawa
oh my God yeah
oh let's go
that would be so cute
okay so I I have stalled long enough
probably I I would love to talk about
Tales of rice endlessly I'm just I'm
just so I'm just so happy
I can't believe it I
I have to stop myself I'm so excited I'm
so excited for the stream too uh thank
you guys for supporting uh Taylor rice
and also me and supporting me playing
tens over rhymes and if you want to
reminisce a bit more the playlist of me
playing the game is on my channel for
you to check it out
um and then yeah I'm so ready for
November I'm so
me and in German we say auf winners in
and please make sure to pre-order Tales
of rice beyond the dawn thank you
thank you hopefully the archive turns
out decently
bye-bye
[Applause]
um
yeah thank you bye love you bye bye see
you tomorrow for my 1.5 million uh
subscriber uh Marathon bye
[Music]
foreign