[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
sorry guys we're going back for a few
minutes sorry sorry guys
I like
[Music]
foreign
yeah and at the end of the stream uh
please stand until the end because there
will be a huge announcement uh at the
end of the stream does everybody want to
say uh hello so I can also check the uh
volume of everyone's nice and and cozy
maybe maybe start with uh India
hello wow I am
hello nice thank you
uh next Cali
howdy hello hi it's it's me Calliope
Mori I have this
Kauai if you haven't slept and oh [\h__\h]
24 hours more actually no wait 24 maybe
20. no it's a lot of it's fine just
don't worry about it I'm happy to be
here I feel more alive than ever which
is strange and I feel like is a thing
that shouldn't be happening but here we
are anyway I'm happy to be here guys
[Music]
check
Domino's
and I am also part of the No Sleep club
I'm going on one hour since I slept
after the Mario card
why would you do such a thing oh it's
not intentional it's never intentional
to be awake so long
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay I I turned up uh you know a bit and
I turned down a tiny bit Cali so I think
now it should be balanced hope you guys
are happy uh I think the only one who
has not played worms yet is Kelly right
yeah I've never played this game
no I have not oh I watched this [\h__\h] did
you play the the tutorial Ina oh not yet
okay so I can guess on the way the three
of us I'm good at me we're gonna babysit
uh the two over there Ina and Cali okay
rule Face bar is not jump space bar is
item use so don't try to jump the space
part you're gonna probably blow up
something in your face oh I need to warm
up so I forgot the controls I played it
once and I forgot okay no space bar no
space bar
okay well then let's uh get into it uh
you guys are already we need to click
ready okay I'm ready
I'm gonna show you we're gonna tell them
so this is a tactical game you have to
choose your spot where I'm standing that
map looks
a bit difficult a bit a bit but I guess
it's basic because it's pretty evasive
I'm sure it'll be fine okay it'll be
fine okay we'll all land on the top you
know you teleport in first oh okay okay
okay I'm I'm the camera oh my God sorry
if it's shitty guys I'll try my best
um oh yeah
oh we're a little laggy
is everybody loading in who's who's
playing right here what's happening
um I think it's you me Yara I think yeah
okay five four what what I don't know
I can't see my mouse this is weird
I think that's you yeah I didn't have
orange
well now I can see myself what
organization
I like it
I think oh okay
thank you
a nice haircut
it is gura
dude epic
see the ocean and stuff it also raises
after a certain amount of appearance
our first game so I made it pretty long
turns for us so it's gonna be we're each
have a minute so you can move we can
pick a weapon to use and your goal is to
kill every other word okay
so we have four worms we do have to
teleport them and I guess I just did it
so you guys could you okay
so in other words as the game goes on
you want to go up so you don't get yeah
it doesn't usually load so slowly
um yes yeah maybe I'm ready
what is this mouse what is that Mouse
how do you open the inventory again uh
we're just spotting in right now so
it'll uh we'll we'll uh it'll open up
but yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
oh Yara has a nice spot no don't go
there that's confusing
yeah
[Music]
what no my worms are named oh my God
yeah
until you kill each other you're killing
each other oh my God you know again I
think so I'm chewing gum oh it's me okay
I'll go right here oh yeah
right in the corner oh hidey hole huh
also I didn't realize how old this game
was this game is literally
prehistoric it's so old
true I can say that though because I'm
also old and prehistoric
yeah yeah
okay okay I think this one's our last
warm probably oh okay
um
let's see uh
[Music]
yeah I think this one's the last time
well played
oh it's me
oh although it's good
I'll buy the milk yeah let's see I ran
out of time
it's very uh there's long range ones and
there's close range ones and the way you
can aim is using sorry English
sorry I don't remember it but we'll
figure it out
last one for real last one all right
you'll get it all right let's go
yeah this is worms WMT so it's not the
oldest version but um
[Music]
interesting
strategic planning is going on here
right now oh wait it's me oh it's me
okay
um
no
but she has hands
Kelly Okay evan okay um okay let me
spread out my worms a little oh wait up
here yeah
I wonder if that thing explodes beside
you
okay no
[Laughter]
looks like exploding Barrel quickly oh
this map is too big and I have not
enough Mouse
worm
last one
and right
uh all right now we're ready all right
not happy with my placement
okay all right I realized too late what
was happening
stuff that drops craft in this game if
you run out of like weapons that you use
and so if you pick up some of those uh
work boxes uh toolboxes you can um craft
new weapons
Kiana okay let's right click okay right
click to open your menu okay okay right
click right click I don't remember how
to play oh God how do you play this
again I played this game once in my life
is it wasd to aim
I don't know what are you doing yeah
I don't like these minion sounding
voices
oh
it wouldn't be fair if she didn't tell
me well I won't hurt you
might as well happen
that's a cute name
okay I don't know what these do but
if you have any questions yeah that's a
bazooka you have to account for the wind
a lot of the time it could bless GW
behind you yeah oh there's the arrow
yeah you want to use space to shoot
um ah careful
oh
that's me right wait yeah is that um
I think it was the
West okay okay
and then you press and hold your left
click for like the charge
in front of you
you literally have a player
that might actually really block people
off the map yeah
space bars
foreign
yes
spacebar charge up that shot oh my God I
couldn't check oh or not
oh my god oh no that's powerful
him yeah
what on Earth who's next
yeah
I know
it's the little ribbon on the 60 second
mark
oh it tells you
um
can you move again uh A and D left and
right that mean is w and S
all right well I can't do that I don't
know why but okay
oh I guess you're stuck in that little
little thing but you can jump right
something something
oh
[Music]
um
you guys are strategy Pros
I'm not sleeping shut up come on
sleeping have fun I'm gonna follow the
edge because okay
you can go down there and like poke her
off or no I'm not giving any ideas
oh different item okay okay oh it's my
turn
no it's not just kidding
well now I know
okay
I can replace my jelly okay oh look at
the Tucker oh man what
your placement of your character over
there I don't know if you meant to do it
it's fantastic
yeah wait this is the high risk High
reward player I can't move right clay
you are moving uh oh I am Andy Andy to
move
what am I I can't see where I
oh there I am
look for the haircut which one I was Hey
Y'all man I see you okay
[Music]
um
yeah once you do damage or take damage
your turn is over but you have a little
bit of time to move afterwards oh [\h__\h]
oh they do it do it do it yeah
I get it something wow I did something
45 my worm nine to five
you would fall into the water
or I'd fall on top of the race car and
run over the other place
thanks thank you
oh the blowtorch um I think you can just
dig through the map with oh oh okay oh
shotgun
so if you're going to use it you think
you get two
okay
one more time
[Music]
no
I I know I switch to what I'm
controlling oh wait I think uh there's a
switch at the bottom you only get one
it's called worm select you see it I
don't see a switch it's in your
inventory it's uh I don't know what you
mean after okay
uh
wait where's the oh Ninjago teleport why
select
only once huh oh well
uh you just use it and then you should
be able to click on one of your worms or
something
why are they British
um
I don't have time
oh my God
oh my goodness it's pretty entertaining
damage
wow it's exploded
remember that
you can't get me you can't get me
I can do um
oh we don't have any tactical strikes
that's
oh
damn it the thumbs are a little scary
Dynamite
hey hey
hey
[Music]
oh I see oh no Henry no oh [\h__\h] to open
your menu and enter us to jump you can
actually jump in this game I was trying
to jump on a hit shift
enter
ships
can I turn how do I
uh you're on a turret right now
it's one way yeah that machine
what a turn
epic wild don't worry you might end up
winning anyway
this one
honestly Cali is like the Dark Horse
right now she has taken like yeah I
don't know how to play this game
if you want to jump over that ledge yeah
there's a box in here oh banana
uh you can't I guess unless it's the
player you can't see what they're doing
but there's like a probably yeah there
she goes oh she climbed up oh no it's a
very long live the king moment Oh no I
got all right
she wants to come for fake Cali but
there's a wall you're probably like
dynamite or something explode the wall
and oh I can't jump the way that I want
yeah okay so if you put a dynamite there
it might throw it yeah oh yeah probably
you have to run away because the
dynamite you get five seconds to run
yeah
I'm having a hard time getting through
here
you know I'm the jump keg
s
[Music]
that remind me of jump King right
we're having a hard time right now I'm
joking you're a record holder though
yeah but the third DLC is something else
I tell you what
this will see you right
okay
I feel like okay
oh this is a little tight here okay
um
what's a bunker Buster that sounds oh so
that one digs through any like now
oh yeah it makes a explosion underground
essentially okay
looks like a job for is it this one now
no no way
okay
grenade why are no oh that went a little
too far oh
no
that was in the air it's okay
oh so do you guys see the timer on the
bottom left yeah so when that timer's up
the water is gonna start Rising oh no
oh no oh what a horrible place
get yourself out of there
uh
what no I didn't
select no no can I undo it
is
she got an item that was tactical two
items a healing an item I think
there's some pretty crazy items that you
can craft another box of things
but
wouldn't stay with space
so misleading
oh no she's stuck no no no no no no no
no no no no no
what the hell oh wow
um
okay let's do this then
ah okay let's see Oops why do I have a
grenade still ah
let's try this again
thank you was that on purpose was that
where you wanted
hey as long as I hit somebody hey let's
go
um
try the green item next to you I think
it might be an item yeah no I
owe for that [\h__\h]
um
yeah wait how did you do that hey
hey
are you the jumping King is that just
jumping wrong game Kelly
you could use the bat or uh bye
line of fire
she's gonna
oh wow
oh no purple light you're in
dangerous is there small damage in this
game too Cali's surprise Kelly's to help
we're figuring out the games good
morning
Shopkick
Chad taught me how to backflip thanks
chat
oh yeah
okay
oh no oh this is a little little rough
oh it's a bad spot yeah yeah you could
you could use uh um what was it you
could use a pack a jet pack yeah it's at
the bottom now we're playing we're
playing some
gamer
you might be able to Bounce It Off the
Wall if you trust too short
look at that
oh my goodness I was going for that
perfect shot the other wall
fine
it's fine
okay
uh
nose right there
oh Connor would also go over there but
um look at that look at that tank it
looks so yummy
imagine the power
I recently found a liking for FPS a
little bit but I'm not really sure how
to use guns that's my problem
oh that's unfortunate
it's frame great baby
oh just you wait just do it here oh boy
oh wait
wait what what happened you're just
gonna hurt yourself Enya
oh on my screen
oh it's okay yeah it's kind of buggy I
also saw something weird before
don't worry about it
you have to make it explosive yeah
finally some damage oh my God you hurt
me keep so strong so strong so true
don't underestimate the power of a sheep
oh where are you going for girl you know
you know Kelly is in that building you
know on the first floor
[Music]
grenade
you can also dismantle some of your
items like if you like this look I shoot
through walls
Watson does some craft there's an Uzi
cholesterol
is a SMG isn't it yeah does it go
through walls though I think it would go
through walls
first thing yeah
quickly quickly
[Applause]
right on target
a dragon Wowie
yeah I'm gonna say
something in a tank
oh let's see
oh like this
um yeah oh my gosh she's gonna Splash it
wait oh where's she going
can I hold on
yeah
interesting Daddy
yeah I'm a great driver
I'm gonna wedge this tank right here
oh
the angles
how does she do it hide am I on the tank
and try to get out of range oh no I I
know Kelly's hiding in there
hey did you get it oh no I didn't she
was hiding the building is so strong
that's the mess right four to five
building
uh yeah I was trying to figure it out
but um
Henry looking real yummy there
to remove Henry entirely no
delete
gosh oh the tank can jump nice
that told me oh yeah
what happened
interesting I see how it is
no it was easier to aim there you know
over there though
oh is it gonna fall in the water oh no
no no
no oh I'm too far
okay here we go hey what can I use the
airstrike oh here it is oh no oh
my worm
wait ah
came back
oh yeah
where'd you go
oh she fell
oh no
oh
you want to get away from away from me
oh it's got a bakrid
until the water starts Rising oh no
Jules is in danger
you'll not survive
foreign
today
no
what do we got here oh oh I did shift by
accident
you can still walk though
oh the other way where you go oh my
goodness you're still gonna joke here
they don't really look like worms
they look like slugs and Ellie looks emo
I can't get tactics
I did what I did what Kiara said I
jumped oh yeah
hold on it's hard to hit you there yeah
I am safe yeah it's a blessing in
disguise
perhaps I'll go water arriving soon the
lower you are the lower
I guess oh a sheep
a sheep good night Roger
there's a super sheep okay okay also The
Holy Hand Grenade is really op but you
only get like one yeah
what what oh I can like oh ground pounds
she
strong overpowering
um
today no I guess hello safety oh where
am I here okay
um
you can push Army out of that Mech no
yeah
uh backspace backspace okay oh backspace
thank you
same time
enter and backspace because enter is
jumping uh Backspaces
oh she's going for the medpack
okay okay
upwards
I'm not 100 sure how this one works
again
oh oh okay okay
that was close
[Music]
ready
to come
it's my turn oh okay let's see what you
want to do
with that goldfish brain of yours I
think I'm gonna call it an air Striker
oh boy
oh the tank covered here
ground
that was a big round
that was not as bad as I thought it was
gonna be
to craft
that placement of that worm is really
not the best home
no no I gotta figure out a way to maybe
you should use a jet pack or so
after a jetpack you can still use a
weapon or ones that not the case
but anyways
can you skip a turn
oh I guess you just wait
it's like bazooka this is it gonna knock
me off the edge here
any question I'll find out for us
oh my God I'm gonna do damage to
yourself for sure yeah
Kelly takes a bath
feeding her friends and family
hold on
oh there she is the hiding worm Watson
keep on Crafting
don't worry about it
oh no
hold on have you not already done here
a shark thingy
um
the Sheep runs until it like is at a
wall or something then we'll turn back
and then it keeps on running until you
make it go boom you decide when it goes
yeah
I see oh it's a double
let's just that's fine we're ganging up
we're getting up on you
one
you would have killed all of us probably
yeah probably
wouldn't be worth it
oh wow
they're an airstrike
right are you sure yeah are you sure
yeah right around there
all right around there
more damage to Kelly
oh baby a double down
you gotta live for the rest
I think Dom's gonna die though I don't
know
right now with the water coming up
oh perfect
oh
stick it out of it maybe
I would I mean 18 is really not that
much
I mean
yeah something like up on top just to
lower her HP there you might be able to
hit
um
Apple
[Music]
I'm not good with guns you know
yeah good old Dynamite yeah
me neither
or fire Pudge too short
I can't hit anybody else
it's a game very fitting oh gosh
oh no small army what the [\h__\h]
oh
no oh no yeah
home run baby oh
no the water it was an operation safe
move me
fuels you gotta survive
it's a little longer let's go movie
Let's Go baby God where can we go okay
oh no does the water rise every turn
yeah doing something yeah
actually Jules can do it parachute this
is fuse put it a parachute how do you
use parachute when you're falling down
but you can use jetpack if you want to
go up
um no you don't take damage essentially
the parachute who are we looking at
where are you uh
all the music
it's getting intense now
um
yes who makes the Lone Survivor okay
hi hi
hello oh let's see
it's like a movie it's so dramatic
punch her out the cliff
Kelly I love you well she's going a bit
more dramatic
oh she's going for small office
okay okay
[Music]
um like next turn if I use worm select
can I like use an item again or I think
so but yeah you want a warm select then
probably teleport you should be able to
use another item arms like wait how do I
so I didn't figure it out to how it
looks it might be like w is maybe like
picking
that way no I'm not sure how it works
yeah
um it's a tab
they have not working not oh okay Play
store and then tab ah okay okay oh nice
okay
all right and then teleport
I mean
I should just do as much damage before I
go and disappear from this Earth just my
last one oh damn oh no what it is it's
my last one oh no okay
damage
I can do
it destroys it destroys it
go big or go home
anyways what's she going for
what's he going for
I mean I can try to save myself but
uh so does not really worth it okay I'm
not sure how to fly but
yeah oh
hello
wait I can still attack appearing no I
don't know 30 seconds will move oh yeah
Place yourself in front of oh on the
plotter Kelly
doomed
ah
oh one of um
yeah yeah I think okay I think it's
better to go away
oh nice aiming
[Music]
again getting the robot
oh
is it a girdle is that girdle hey guys
let's not let her Escape
you know
what to do
you know what to do
This Is War
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
okay
oh yeah it's the blue one at the end of
the first row oh thanks
oh God
[Applause]
thank you hold on
guys
LW
yeah there we go space bar yeah
wait are you sure that's maybe that's
blood in your coat
give me a hand
give me a hand uh oh I I who's next is
it me let's go all right oh no please
I see
you
know we'll make a treaty
do it
oh that's drastic that's drastic
no no
[Music]
I feel like I can get both of you here
come on
that's too close you're gonna get
yourself too
you sure you won't go big or go home
I can't believe
the king
um
[Music]
but maybe the bat goes too far
I'm gonna remember that as long as you
pick an angle that goes up it should be
okay okay
I would like to take a moment to thank
my take my take my mom and dad and my
family and my gem mates thank you very
much for such an amazing years so bad
because I don't know how to play
baseball well I'll give it a try and I
would like to thank um um
[Music]
that's pretty good but then again the
water oh yeah the water is a little
yellow right here we should still have a
Teleport
I do I do yeah
all righty
money oh no Hey There She Goes
they're okay
okay
um oh man oh boy
yeah I think I'm set here
might as well
to
our feet hey
well you're making me feel bad all right
all right
um let's see think of the news
I'll play fair
okay okay give it a shot to miss
okay oh oh yeah right that exists too
what was that one world
wait which one was that
um I think that's the bunker or
something bunker Buster yeah yeah
[Music]
well I think we have enough time to play
second game girls so now that we learned
a lot yeah oh yeah yeah definitely oh
where is this going
[Applause]
all right
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah you came up from like not doing so
good yeah
it was the big picture here was the big
picture
beautiful wonderful okay you know that's
fine oh no don't worry no hard feelings
if you guys don't see me
the next round a little bit shorter only
because of the announcement yeah oh yeah
yeah yeah like okay I'm gonna I'm gonna
go back to the menu and just edit my
team super quick I just want to change
something okay
I'll re invite you guys I think the
lobby might still be okay yeah it's
still open we can invite you back okay I
don't know who's gonna be later because
then they'll have to change like and
pick the map
I think I think I have to look I mean I
feel like I can't change it I can change
it I can change it so it must be good
then huh do it do it just tell me what
what to choose it shouldn't be too
intricate something like something yeah
something on the same a rainforest a
flat surface
Orient a soccer field I don't know
Wormhole looks too hard that's too much
yeah
um that's probably also too much
Countryside this looks pretty simple
I think the the first one that you
changed was uh a rainforest thing yeah
they keep on changing
we just did Orient Ed
there was a simple rainforest one we
have somebody random in the lobby oh and
you kicked us here I'll make a new one
I'll make a new one okay yeah
[Laughter]
[Applause]
it might change I don't know because I
maybe because I didn't make it public so
yeah okay
I accept it
is there one
yeah it should regenerate hold on let me
see cute
yeah
yeah this one looks nice okay okay I'm
Gonna Change to Pro well maybe
destruction probably structure
destruction
items I guess the round time's pretty
good at 45 seconds uh oh wait turn time
yeah round time put it at 10 minutes so
after 10 minutes the water will start to
rise okay okay
because
okay oh let's go
all right I'm not gonna put teleports
it's gonna be random is it okay that's
good that's fine that's fine
all right yeah
everyone wants to push ready
okay
obliteration I was ready what happened
war between mythical beings just like
that animation that fan animation oh
yeah yeah
[Laughter]
oh Kelly
wow we are really close together
right now it's uh Cali's I think oh okay
oh do my weapons carry over no I don't
know
I don't think there's crafting in this
one dang oh it's okay yeah oh wow
actually it's kind of hard to aim like
right there unless like you do a
homemade missile
you know first round holding this
yeah I wonder if I think it unlocks
after a certain that returns oh boy oh
damn it wow oh wow oh yeah damn it uh I
didn't was that the land I don't
understand no no it was a grenade
because I saw it moving oh yeah the
landline's still there I don't think it
went off
oh sweet
oh well
oh Sleek I'm gonna put the round time at
10 minutes I think I messed it up it's
okay
should be fine
oh that's terrible
oh
oh can you do it I'll show you what
happens when it goes wrong
for the wind I've actually pressed it oh
it's a jump King you gotta count for the
wind
yeah
it's fine it's fine can you come back
again
almond so you get kicked out
children oh I'll be approaching
what will she do
anyways
um I have a plan actually okay
[Music]
um
that's big damage
oh I will land in the home
okay nice ready
oh look at that that's like beautiful
sweet distance right there
you don't get them back
uh do you have fire punch no
you're mildly I love the fire punch
I booped her
[Music]
I don't know what she's going for ah
it's so awkward position I don't want to
go down I want to stay as high probably
throw a grenade up
like just like easy to control
there's like a really short on it
because there's no wind right now
there's one going down so I think it
you'd have to do yeah a little tiny bit
stronger tiny maybe a little higher
because I want to go to like either a
movie or jazz hands or even soda oh okay
I feel it like
um
yeah well let's uh
let's try you'll have to hurry
we need a feeling foreign
come on
enter
you can set a timer for your tornado
what did I just read all right no I
think it's five seconds or something
it's like pretty short
okay
disgust is what makes you touch that
ledge failed attack so quickly
yeah
oh my God that was huge that was nice
Cali's gonna be dangerous in this game
when she learns it yeah
ah this is a little a little difficult
here
um do I have anything
um
okay okay Callie you see you're so
fleshy
oh sorry he caught me you have a fever
are you good
I'm using a fever oh baby I'm just
talking I'll get good
wow
[Laughter]
oh lucky
it sounds like the Pillsbury Doughboy
let's go Buffs in
Young
I don't want to go I don't know what to
do he'll play
you can Dynamite again show us what
you've got I only had one oh
Oh Captain over there you can chuck a
little uh
I want to get up there but I think that
mine is yeah okay probably
yeah
oh yeah I'll try to learn from you guys
um
just you wait just you wait oh no we are
not quite ready for a war it seems
time for Cali oh no what am I gonna do
it keeps on hurting yourself
[Music]
I should have parked myself right below
I went through you on my screen
yeah
from the previous round I feel like we
were kind of better before
no no no no no no no no no no no
okay no I'm not no no no no no no no no
no
[Music]
no oh I can still look at him yeah
foreign
[Music]
I tried oh
it's your presents that's hot
it's a present for you
oh
there's so much damage
oh baby a triple
only how do I uh let's jump and backflip
yeah yeah parkour let's go
to the Stars
yeah
okay
no I have no time
[Applause]
okay okay tried
it's like small amen would love
it just spray in the corner
they'll chill in the corner nope
okay oh okay okay oh she's getting ready
already
okay let me try something here
about a poke
um
Punky poke oh I don't have one wait what
is it called a little finger no no not
that one uh
oh
the choices I don't know I don't know
what the names of anything are
I'll try this one because I have four
there's an item called Old Link wait is
this a grapple hook come on then it
looks like um yeah oh no wait which one
it doesn't look like it yeah ninja rope
yeah it's a grapple hook or it might be
it might be a rope With Grenades on it
hurry hmm
oh there it goes it's fun it's fine
oh no it happens
um what you got
g-dog ranchy dog
yeah
you should go somewhere else
but on the top with the little little
green present at the top
[Laughter]
no you know what I'll stay nice and
comfy the highest point on the map
no I have to go I have to go how's the
parachute work
uh it's just so you prevent fall damage
when you jump from a high spot ah you
can teleport you have five seconds oh
god
oh There She Goes
[Music]
sorry what is this round ridiculous
um
I am the worst enemy in this town
[Music]
oh she's going for it oh she's an
airstrike now yeah
oh my God
[Music]
Chad where's the difference
oh my God is that a triple leave me
alone
wow wow wow that's a lot
oh boy oh my goodness
oh by the way guys gouda and Cali at the
top right now so
um
last time I said that about you Watson
no one listened to me no one listening
to me exactly
right next to each other well that would
be a smart place
come on
come on Boggy yeah
he's thirsty for Revenge yeah boggy
Wants Revenge Revenge on YouTube
up there
wow wow wow
oh baby oh mermaid amazing
[Music]
woman
no no
your own words
sacrificing it what
oh god wow
no survivable survival
oh look look who's at the town now
[Laughter]
[Music]
I can't that's a it's pretty cold on
this map you should touch the furnace on
the right
nice and warm warm up your hands so you
can aim better
oh no
um
is that like the middle or is that like
where we started the middle like starts
oh really
yeah we'll see how
focus on the one you want oh
that's the middle yeah um
oh
how about you
oh small hummus no hanging on the little
bit of wine
still alive there
oh time for buggies Revenge all right
buggy
saving bread we have some last points
before you leave this world
's not hot worms
okay
beautiful nice it was damaged
what's the damage
I tell you what
yeah was it working yesterday
I see that just means one thing and one
thing only two worms that have taken no
damage it's meant to be it's my channel
[Music]
what happened
how does a punch do a little bit less
damage than him
the single Target versus AOE you know
AOE is more spread out holy
holy stuff
there it goes
watch it
oh what's the name of the one that digs
through the ground what does an old lady
do
she bakes cookies
to the ground
the old lady
no no does a blowtorch dig through the
ground
yeah yeah
oh Lily
I'll whip you together oh oh he's got it
oh wait can you show the castle he's
running away
like a weapon blows to the ground
okay
[Laughter]
now
are you gonna fly around
and I still think you're in trouble yeah
oh that shotgun oh
no need for that I might reach her okay
do I get a blowback from a shotgun I
don't know
yeah try and find out
one of two ways
[Laughter]
thank you
all right oh my God I can't [\h__\h]
breathe I learned all of that in death
Loop
s
all right jazz hands uh what are you
gonna do buddy
what you gonna do what you gonna do when
death comes for you
exactly that's a good question
um let's find out
what I'm gonna do what I'm gonna do
oh
[Applause]
she wants the Sweet Taste of blood
um okay
[Music]
all right yeah
yeah
there's not that much a difference
okay well that's powerful voice sounds
really big
oh my God
we're never gonna see a holy grenade
like a tiny piece of Earth that was like
there yeah
that's incredible
no
smart getting stronger okay
um
Water Rising in six
grenades I forgot space bar is not just
oh [\h__\h] sorry what what's up
I
forgot space was a jump you know what
happens understandable Oh My Grave is
next to girls
the right side of the map
foreign
I
would assume it's a bomb because it's by
the Sheep but I don't know yeah
it's just like blank you and how far is
the Bazooka suit
ah yes
Kiara
oh
you gotta count for the win did you
account for the wind Chiara
are you still alive
okay let's see what we got here
um hi jazz hands
Talent Oh Holy Grail what does this do
you want to see it work for once please
jump
the world
yeah he went High
oh yeah
wow
wow wow
it's also known as Hollow frill the game
yeah
all right what items do I have I'm still
learning I'm still a learner you showed
us the show
you guys wanted to see it
oh
indeed we did
um
you just have one more worm right yeah I
do
yeah
first not today
that's okay
um I think it hangs from like a your
apartment
you're welcome Chad oh no
um
yeah yeah
I am going for green dog movement more
damage with that one if you go somewhere
else
with that one turn you could do so much
more damage yeah I'm sorry
There She Goes
um
and I got it
baby I care about that
all right all right who are we going for
okay what did banana do banana bomb I
think it was strong it's definitely
stronger than it sounds
yeah everything that sounds weak is so
strong
yeah banana ship is Opie
oh oh nice goodbye
for how long please I only have two
worms left
we need you need something stupid
okay
hi
this is gonna be 30 seconds of jumping
again
nice nice okay okay she's shot cutting
okay
[Laughter]
the first time
oh you should have been able to oh yeah
oh you weren't able to yeah
it takes some time until you can do the
second shot that's weird you're still
yeah you have to reload the shotgun you
know
at the back my husband is I don't know
if I have three minutes left until water
rises oh some of us might not survive
too much time we might die before yeah
how'd you get another one
yeah yeah
dog let's see
oh this way is nice I might go over the
water
[Music]
please
this is so big
but she's still not dead
okay I'm almost gone she's still here
you can she's still here oh my God
all right now please have mercy
that'll be good to hear
about the area okay she's right over
there across from you 55. hey hey we do
MIA
[Music]
that says
you can actually kill the left one
probably with 25 HP okay okay oh wait
actually that's that's what it was
playing here
I don't know the plan I just I just I
just looked I was slowly
Welcome to Hell
stop
oh she's going for it
oh
um what are you feeling like a banana do
a trick shot yeah yeah do it
oh
[Music]
is it like okay
give me the damage
how do you jump
uh enter and space make sure your face
[Laughter]
exactly oh wait is this the time for the
you smell it
poke me poke me oh she's going for the
uh okay
[Music]
My Cheese House
is it still the one that I missed the
first time sour I think it's famous yeah
on the left on the edge yep yeah
still a lot chilling but only for like
40 more seconds
who do we have to take out Ina Ina must
be taken out but I don't know I don't
know what how he's got the top spot
right now she has the highest spot in
the map nobody's touched that worm at
all
yeah that one over there
I'm gonna try the old lady but I have no
idea what it is
oh
my turn
okay let's see
what's this grandma
little torch my bazooka oh what's this
banana bomb banana
you like banana
yeah then there's a lot of potassium
so much
wow
oh my goodness
I have to work on my late game you guys
there's a there's a my early game is
pretty good but my late game's pretty
bad yeah
that's true
you don't need the health
you have to move yeah
it's okay
Cali's the only one that can take
herself out
[Laughter]
I mean you really wanted to kill me
oh no she's going for the helpful
I'm so sorry
why
yeah
I know who's gonna win yeah
we have the uh Guru Kiara yeah
yeah
I take it as a limit
oh
oh going out strong baby four
whoa oh
dead oh she's on fire can you help me
Miss how to go anywhere
oh my goodness
oh you're gonna drown on the keyboard
wait this is
oh no you want to win
[Applause]
there could only be one wait how oh you
have to shoot up okay yeah yeah yeah
just do it you don't like boom yourself
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
all right oh no
oh no this is
one for the long game oh
going for the health pack okay ah you
have an item that can take her out um
Now or Never I have an item that can
take her out
or or do you quick read the chat
again
like that anymore
oh no Kiara
it's now or never uh you got a blaster
off the map oh here
you have a banana
oh my God
do it it doesn't go that far no you
gotta just aim it aim it aim it aiming
that up no email like a little to the
right a little bit yeah
[Applause]
no it's really heavy once you gotta hold
it for a long time
okay
it might be best if I just skip my turn
because I might accidentally eat myself
oh boy I'm just gonna go ahead and take
some extra precautions here oh my God
that's pretty evil
oh
[Music]
Mario yeah
what a huge brain
Kill Me Softly kind of without telling
skills
[Applause]
myself
probably probably
[Laughter]
yeah me too one of the few games that we
can play as six people so five people
yeah
that was fun
yeah that's true they're like yeah point
five point five I'm gonna position us
together so that we're cozy and all that
yeah
you might want to just press Escape
Escape
I'm not showing the the door or the game
screen dollar oh is that what you mean
or the buttons the buttons the buttons
[Laughter]
not good it's all good it's a work in
progress you know yeah not perfect oh
beautiful
oh the chat to where does the chat chat
goes above us
yeah guys only if yet there's the big
announcement is an announcement
we have an announcement to make I'm
covering up uh
uh before before the announcement I have
an announcement
oh yeah
I hear that word one more time
girl did you know we have an
announcement
um
announcement exactly yeah
Kathy said merge chat what do you guys
think it is what do you guys think
acrylic stands I want to see your
guesses
yes acrylics
oh my gosh 40 debut yes
I get to smell my favorite Idols
in a bottle
Japan perfumes already what would you
guys know like orange orange and lime
roses roses yes definitely salt salty
salt sea salt sea salt yeah that sounds
good for those smell like coconut and
cookies oh yeah those are nice that's
yummy I don't think like you know
blueberry cheesecake
I'm yummy I'm hungry same
yeah I should go make more cheesecake
yeah yours look so good yeah
uh What uh the one who will be
announcing is I think uh uh Kelly right
yeah I did ask you if that was okay yes
yay
yes the time drum roll please maybe is
it time uh uh it'll be a little early
but I feel a little early
okay what should we do
what's your favorite thing about your
outfit you guys oh good question let's
go from left to right okay
okay
um I really like the contrast between
dark blue and like the gold and like
orange yes I really like that and to me
it just like activates my brain cells so
I'm really really glad I got to have
this outfit and yeah
the colors the fish is so good yeah
is it you said it's a robot right
yeah he's a robot because if he's a real
fish he might suffocate and run out of
oxygen in the bag but because it's like
a very smart android robot that also
talks sometimes
um
so that's why it doesn't blink huh yeah
wait fish don't blink right
now
they look like oranges and I have to go
ahead and cut them off with surgical
scissors it's actually quite fascinating
yeah the fish that grows stuff on their
head some of them are like bread
specifically for that or they have like
yeah guys big warty foreign
my favorite thing I think is uh
twin tail hairstyle because um yeah yeah
that's that's I mean I also love the the
wingies that I got but I think if I had
to choose I've been doing a thing that
like with every new outfit uh I've been
trying to get like a different kind of
gradation in my hair and this is yellow
line maybe yeah
some some accents added there so yeah I
love the I love the shape of my twin
tiles very much
oh boy I like how I'm themed after
kagami Mochi but then also I like the
little green things in my hair because
they kind of represent like the uh I
think it's called The Laurel wreath
similar to my previous outfit but it
also looks like seaweed but then also I
really like uh the Ebbie on my head
because I actually Drew this shrimp
right
like a an idea for Nacho Mama but she
was like oh no it's cute I'm gonna just
put it in the real design I said okay
uh my favorite part is actually uh you
guys think included in my um
so cute
I don't know if I can read it yeah
yeah
it's so cute oh
yeah I love it
adorable hi I'm back
I can't kill and then Kelly can say what
she likes her the most and then go into
the announcement okay uh what I like the
most is um I love that like my Ribbon or
the uh the front of Obi uh has like a
bunch of different like scenes on it
it's got like Ripples and flowers
um for like different scenes but like I
also love the smokiness and I also love
the hair ornament I love everything here
can I do this I wonder if you guys can
see there's something I didn't show on
uh the outfit reveal because I forgot
but I can do this oh one second I have
to do it from here I'm sick
okay wait and shorts
[Music]
I think Kelly had the most drastic hair
change
yeah
someone who normally has super long
straight hair to see them with super
short to straight hair yeah
I want to eventually get thank you I
want to eventually get my long hair um
with this outfit as well but that'll be
for next time right now we've only got
only got short but that's okay that's
okay I still like it a lot I think it's
accentuates uh your bare shoulders yeah
culture you look like like cute girl in
school I would have had a crush on with
the short hair
[Laughter]
oh man
well I guess we can go ahead and
announce the thing okay
oh boy I've been waiting for this
so wait uh you guys may have remembered
that for Halloween we released like um a
little fun song called myth or treat
right
um
um no it's no it's not it's not
Halloween you sillies it's well this is
uh this is different because this time
we are releasing our very first
full-length original song
[Applause]
[Music]
the art is by our very own Nino my
inonis and uh your boy wrote the lyrics
and made the music video and everybody
else contributed their beautiful vocals
yay it's premiering in like an hour
right I think so sometimes
live English Channel
um please go check it out
um the track is by uh Farhan who made
um the track for myth or treat as well
um I think you guys are gonna love it
um I hope that you guys like the theme
of it
um and I hope that uh you listen to it
many times it'll also be available for
streaming in a couple of days a couple
of days we will certainly all let you
know when it's available to stream uh
wherever you want so yeah this is
streaming it unlike the Halloween song
yeah yeah but the Halloween song I think
we were all like so happy with how how
well you all received it the audience
um yeah how much you liked it so right
after that I think it was immediately
after that we if I've got together and
said okay you know what let's do a
proper song together now how about that
yeah we were very motivated thanks to
you guys thank you yeah thank you so
much thank you for your hard work Callie
yeah
you know how much did you suffer drawing
those patterns
I slaughtered today isn't it oh my God
they're so beautiful though when I was
editing the MV I was like dang Ina's art
is so delicious
hi
easy to replace the files it's all good
see when we get together we can do
anything you guys we could just be like
a full team honestly yeah exactly
[Music]
the most fun song I've ever recorded so
yeah
like all of it that's so emotional like
I'm working on it I was like
ah I started tearing up working on the
MV actually
did we say logo by Spirit snare well
we're mentioning everybody yeah
the first logo I commissioned from him
and now he's done so many and now he's
done this one yeah it's cute it's so
pretty it has like a like like Japanese
elements in it like traditional I think
like the The Fog behind looks kind of
like yeah Japanese so you mean like I
think listen to the song you will
realize that the logo is very fitting to
the feeling of the song
yeah definitely
um also I want to give an another big
UPS to um our managers who kind of like
helped us and everybody behind the
scenes who gave us the okay and we're
like yes you guys can take the reins and
do this on your own and everyone that
gave us the power to do that everyone
behind the scenes working with us thank
you so much for giving us this chance
and we're gonna make many more together
um
a lot of creative uh how to say creative
right direction Freedom yeah yeah yes
yes so yeah they said just just make a
song and we're like okay so we all did
it we did it we worked together
um on it and I hope you guys love it
yeah
thank you everyone
good job everybody maybe one day uh when
we all finally get the 3DW that we can
all perform it together
yeah that would be really emotional
doing this song in particular together I
think yeah
yeah
okay oh man yeah that is that everybody
uh oh
disappeared I'll come back to the last
moment
does anyone have anything else to say
this is a huge big announcement
yes I'm not playing jump King today
because Jay Chad told me that four
streams in a day before I got any I got
zero sleep I shouldn't do it so 26 hours
from now or so I will finish the
freaking game I will finish it I will
finish it I promise yeah
one more uh happy belated happy birthday
to
anyone
yeah
this week and good our congrats on the
Mario Kart High placement oh yeah
I brought home that participation trophy
we can put it on the wall now I saw you
were good like in the preparation
streams you did but I did not know how
you would compare to the other Japanese
members because they are so good right
but then you blew everyone away
and like also when you when you race
like on stream everybody's targeting you
for the most part so like when you get
when you get wumbled on stream it's like
well okay I'm being targeted so I assume
that it wasn't going to be quite as bad
and it really wasn't or maybe I just got
lucky yeah I think it's a lot more luck
and unlucky when it comes to my cart
yeah definitely
well that was the fun thing right the
Mario Kart tournament yeah
let's do an En one
last year we can definitely do it again
this year you know we can add different
rules too oh yes the battle one or like
team oh actually now that we're 11 in
Ian we could kind of do a full internet
but it would kind of be short but we
could do teams
I kind of have a little announcement as
well just to prepare you guys
um but um I'm actually organizing a
semi-casual uh Pokemon tournament the
day before the new games come out it's
on the 17th of January so um if you guys
would like to to join uh you know where
to find me but just letting you guys
know that um some folks will be
participating and um I'm getting ready
for that on the 17th hope you guys will
come it's it's semi-casual it's not like
a a super formal thing because we don't
have a ton of time to prepare so it's
more like just a fun like you know just
getting together to play some Pokemon
before the new game and celebration kind
of things so uh so yeah just let you
guys know about it and I'm also
organizing a jump King speedrun race if
anyone wants to joining
if any of you others would like to try
it's open for anyone it's very just do
it at your own pace kind of thing so
that's okay okay
all righty oh yeah okay and uh yeah uh
by the way tomorrow I'm doing the the
shrine stream where some of you will be
calling in and I will read your fortune
and all that so yeah it's a little bit
of a special stream hope to see you guys
there and yeah please keep on supporting
Holo live whole life English whole beef
all of us well thank you everybody for
your lovely support you guys are so
awesome uh we really really hope that
you will like the song and then stream
it as much as you can
[Music]
it's not merchandise
[Laughter]
yeah
I mean we have the Halloween stuff I
don't need something oh yeah a full song
that we could say this is something that
describes our our works on our
experiences also I'm so excited because
I've been holding my tongue from humming
it on
streaming
no I mean we really all wanted to make
an original song together but like we
just weren't sure if it was like okay
and there were some like uh hiccups in
the road that kind of like uh kept us
from doing it but now now it's no no
problem we're gonna make as many as we
can as we want because we know that we
can
um so please look forward to more music
from us yeah I said about having myth or
treat you guys you guys loved it so much
you gave it so much support and love and
like seeing that yeah everybody else
seeing that it's it's really encouraging
for us you know they can do this myth
can do this and then it's like yeah we
can oh yeah hell yeah we can
this is Unstoppable release those
bangers
I like the Power Rangers yeah
Power Rangers are kind of animals
one last thing next week will be Council
revealing now
yes
oh my God how excited do you guys
remember when you guys did it yeah very
nervous oh wait our first one for you
April Fools
well I mean like proper our first outfit
I remember I was so nervous the night
before I couldn't sleep at all yeah
yeah that'll be looking so gorgeous and
Flawless
at the same time as us just like one
week
so let's go everybody and support them
Market in your calendars put on some
alarms or whatever don't miss it yeah
and with that I guess everybody uh want
to sign off
okay sure okay
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
I only have it in OBS right now please
the comments are too fast
pin it you're zooming
bye
[Music]
thank you