[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
no
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
n
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Laughter]
is having
hallucinations no is no I okay Kiara was
like who's making that sound and Kiara
was like Moon walking in place and then
a start Moon walking in place it's you
guys no it's you I was standing still
she was standing still I was also
standing still my my my stream will be
on my side I believe it but it's too
late stream is never on your side you're
alone pom
[Music]
[Laughter]
you're you you
side who me
no no
wait huhuh what's going on here hi
what's going
on stop it and introduce yourself
stop this game has t go Crouch I thought
it was hold this whole
time pull pull
yeah introduce yourself
oh
okay oh can't see your face
everybody yeah it's a little
intimidating it's kind of
creepy
hello hello I
puu no you're
w i I'm one all of the worldwide what
was it what were we worldwide wife web
we are the worldwide w web world I'm I'm
Wu of the worldwide
wide web web thank you it's not that
hard to say
it why are you having so many trouble
saying
that I just woke up okay oh oh yeah can
you give them like the story of your
your your current issues that maybe
issues arise because of your current
location
yes I might stop pointing at me I feel
wait who's who's making that noise
what wait who's making that
noise there's no noise there's no
sound you hear
again my chat hears it
currently sorry I'm currently in a hotel
in Japan so I might poof out of
existence maybe maybe a sound from the
hotel
room oh of
haunted um all right anyway you heard
enough of that wife yeah next next one
who oh this
we we I I
wo what no she's Moon walking
again she's not I
[Music]
love I thought we were all Wu no only
she's
Wu oh then I'm
po hi I'm wewa from
it's our first collab our
first I'm we from the worldwide wife web
y
walking I'm so
happy so happy we're finally collabing
cuz we even met IRL before but we never
collab so happy
finally didn't you wait when we met IRL
didn't you like pay for like my whole
dinner no no yes you did yes you did
stop pointing don't answer
me
no that was that was pretty cool and
handsome of you oh then yes I
did thank you so much maybe this time
maybe today I can thank you for all of
that looking forward to
it wow what do what do you know about
this wife
there she got some great
assets oh yeah oh
yeah I'm embarrassed
[Laughter]
stoping I mean
yeah I even got fan art of myself drawn
in aa's outfit looks pretty sexy I can't
blame you looks so you yeah I saw
it I love the PO I saw it I saw it yeah
okay go on the stage the wife
stage hi Darlings I'm waisa of the
worldwide waiu
web
yay live this is this is my wife because
I'm literally going on a honeymoon with
her yes that's so fun stealing kiaha for
myself I don't really know if that's
really applicable because I invited you
I don't know how you're stealing me you
don't need to tell them that
K I'll her on
Tuesdays other Tuesday yeah yeah we just
switched
off yeah okay okay I guess oh my gosh
she's Moon walking nobody's moonwalking
who's
mooning Me Maybe maybe we don't know
about our moonwalking no I'm not do it
again know what you're about do it do it
again do it
again yeah wow
Moon Moon
walking I mean guess wait that's so
smooth oh my God she's actually so
smooth with
it she's a smooth
criminal it's how people can get so
excited over the most soft and simple
features of a game M wow so easy to
entertain
Ki hello I am The Mastermind behind the
worldwide wife web I am the wife of
everybody if they make me a wife I will
be everybody's wife let me wife you uh
today I came here to go to the wife
convention this is the wife convention
right yeah yeah yeah of course we just
need to pick up a few things first oh
okay then call me wa your wife let's go
let's
go my
[Laughter]
wife what you guys have a lethal company
wife uh no you you guys maybe I think I
like the I would pick the Bracken oh oh
the I like The
Nutcracker what I don't think I played
since the Nutcracker existed
oh is it a Monster yeah yeah yeah oh
okay okay I don't know them yet well
shall we set up and start our first
mission then
we should wait we have to explain
to
okay yeah okay have you ever played
phasmophobia yes and I do not like it oh
well it's like the exact same thing
except different yeah yeah of me of me
okay so basically kiaha we're going to
be going to moons okay and on these
moons it is our responsibility to go
into these uh long abandoned buildings
and collect materials that at the end of
3 days we are going to be selling um
There Are Rules so you're going to
actually want to come over here since
it's your first time and go ahead and
read this
manual uh that's on this table oh
there's a manual say fa it's so hard to
read though yeah it is pretty hard to
read a few species FAA is dominant by a
few
species she's d
that's what I thought the first time I
saw that too I was like I see okay can
manual I thought I thought I'm reading
the manual get the man oh there it is
sorry it's kind of
long so we could also just explain to
you as we go but basically we're just
looking for things to pick up bring back
to the ship if all of us wipe we lose
all of our items um so if everyone's
dead it's best to just
leave there will be monsters chasing us
to place on the counter and Bug ding
ding the Bell until the company answers
the door and remain what what what is
this about selling scrap to the company
yeah so Day Day Zero technically or the
last day we go to the company to sell
all the stuff that we found um and we
have to place it on a desk and then ring
a bell for them to come get
it how do oh oh there oh oh oh
uh I can't I can't read and dance yeah
dance what did you expect what did you
do did you do
something oh did you just answer the
question it's so dark oh there we go
yeah I answer question but I also don't
know how to use the terminal I don't
think we have use the terminal for the
first one I think we just loc on the
right the just
go
need to R risk of damage the autopilot
pilot ship will not stay on the moon
surface midnight please don't worry
you'll get it
keep keep a crew at home can I stay at
home
no no no
no no you can't no just type the code
for how do I know the the broadcast code
or whatever girl you'll tell me right
you'll tell me all of this um yeah of
course yeah yeah oh that's a lot okay
let's
go ship how do I punch someone you can't
well you can you if you pick up like
there's like stop signs inside if you
pick it up you can hit people yeah you
can hit people or you can hit monsters
team kill yeah so when a monster attacks
me I I should try to attack them back um
well some of them you can and some of
them you can Walker okay Walker some of
them if they see you
it's that's crab W I feel like oh we're
moving we started let's go let's go
y she like guys okay I will run I will
run wait did it
start no one started I thought the game
started Why didn't it start Oh I thought
so too press it sounded like it yeah I'm
going to
start let's
go okay please hold my
[Music]
hand all we have to
do comp
ecosystem okay FL threatens other life
forms okay okay okay I see good morning
this
way I don't know they've left me is this
the moon are we on the moon yeah we're
on the moon there's no way no I didn't
leave you come here wait I ordered one
flashlight H
okay wait can I run we don't need a
flashlight it's
fine but I have nothing you girls have
items no this way yeah we don't have
anything yet got to make some
money oh my God it's Christmas te W
wao I haven't played since before
Christmas so I'm like where are we where
is it okay um it should be where is she
going if we go back to the
ship actually I don't know where we
are I shouldn't lead
anyone okay it is this map so it's over
here
right I've lost
them I don't know where I
am okay
ship they must think I'm
dead What creatures am I
scanning
hello oh okay I know where we
are
hello way you run
to so you just hold e and go ins
time okay but where the [\h__\h] is
everybody else just go
in hi who hi is it just me who finds the
acustics so so
upsetting find the
what the Acoustics are so
upsetting
alone
it's so awesome it's like 2010 Xbox
mic
yeah nothing here but nothing here okay
nothing so far everything's still normal
but I'm like I'm getting nervous when is
the RAR
[\h__\h] don't go don't
go oh my
God
what what do you mean there's a
Bracken
where
areana it's
okay where are
you are you okay there's a bracking you
weren
lying come here I'm lost come upstairs
okay okay
okay
go [\h__\h]
man
my wife why did we go he heard me
because there's a
Bracken where's pomu oh P bringing stuff
back to the oh my God what a
queen she just Dr um we could go down
here and go in the fire exit and see if
there's anything different down there
the
mountain okay it's so weird don't
understand anything there's like a
monster in this game that I think if you
look at it for too long and it can like
start chasing you and then it kills you
yeah he gets mad and then I
look oh oh I like the I like the audio
in here Brack's over there uh the
Bracken yeah where I I looked down that
hway second too I looked down the
hallway you can go see okay yeah go go
ahead
k
the Bracken is my choice of waifu for
in-game
[Music]
characters I'm too
scared I don't see it oh you have to
scan no oh you'll you'll know when you
see
goodbye that's not
the I don't know what that was what was
that it looked like a fat a really big
guy
yeah where's
Pom that's the ship I think okay or
that's her
[Music]
hi why are you
laughing she's enjoying life where going
um well there's a bumper I think and a
bracket oh right inside well when we
were going through the main entrance
the
oh did she jump down to join
us they're so
Fearless oh it was just the it's just
chilling I saw him come here [\h__\h] uh
you
wouldn't we're going to lose day
one are you stuck no I got aying glass
do something kill him you going to burn
him with the Sun lead the way
pomu I stayed there I think
he's
he's great good job good job wait did we
all live I think he found us we're all
good well I think we should go back yeah
yeah we found
[Music]
enough you're joking
[Laughter]
me hey is he chasing
me someone take my
flashlight oh my God
God
unbelievable
me I said my flashlight I bought a
flashlight and now it's
useless now
what oh my God she's just going to
hide
do I always die first
absolutely hurt
my what are you doing here a
moment
a what a bro what are you
doing what are you doing oh don't oh God
the Bracken oh god um I guess he can't
come here think we're in
trouble I was in in this room like for
two minutes and I didn't see you where
have you been oh I was
out I think she got
bored there's no spec of her on the
screen you're so right not even a green
I mean blue sphere nor her
vision give a
SL slight reminder that she
existed oh my
God will be fine it's still there
maybe well it's not fine you leave me
alone oops she just going to die yeah
I'll close the door I can't believe I
got caught by that thing I thought if I
was quiet and just moved slowly he
wouldn't hear me chat how do you escape
that guy don't make noise don't make
noise Crouch walk Crouch walk work do
you just have to run or does noise
matter I'll try F please help with the
giant you just need to run okay being
quiet doesn't fix
it I'm
sorry it's my fault for not knowing how
to handle him don't get seen line of
sight weing it's deatha oh it's death so
sound doesn't
matter see but can't hear okay tell me
to shut
up
flashbang or run stun grenade if you can
afford it
okay
okay good to know thank you guys for the
information I appreciate it I see the
ship yeah just learn as I
go [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
a why are we screaming why are we
screaming there's light there's light
oh all the P sh will leave at Mid hi hi
hi I made
it almost
there yes is there a
dog no dog I'm I'm going kill there's a
dog yes there's a dog there's a dog I'm
I'm stting I'm stting
I'm
my gosh I think so I saw something
running oh it was a worm there was a
worm I couldn't tell that sound was a
dog my God IED she I'm
like no my wife is dead who will go to
the wow the yeah I mean yeah I'm still
going to the males with you what do you
mean a how back live it's worth 507 no
one no one got anything else I could cu
the tried to kill me the second we
walked it is this the only thing we've
got all you got to do is yeah I grabbed
that I haven't played this game since we
last played
it oh yeah it's been a while thank you
for 20
memberships thank you for 20
[Music]
membership
nice wow nice so was that that was
pretty bad wasn't it we didn't really I
was pretty bad situation yeah it was a
pretty bad we did pretty good I mean
yeah we did good we just got
unlucky is our qu zero out of
130 nice yeah yeah yeah
yeah we can do this pretty good oh let's
go let's oh let's
go Who whoo wo it's the same map three
times in a row so you won't get lost
yeah you remember yeah yeah oh there's a
beehive guys
[Music]
careful oh there's two
beehives so those are actually worth a
lot of money so if we can get them it's
really good but you got to be tricky
about it
basically uh nor they're close they're
both close I think we'll be good yeah we
could try to get them at the end and
then just have everyone else on the ship
so let's
go get them at the end get them at the
end oh it's not the same map every yeah
we're on
March cute no it's December h no the
Moon is called March honey
[Music]
wow
why are the lights off sometimes they
are oh what was that sound is there one
way is there oh K I forgot to tell you
so when you right click you scan and
that's how you can find items and stuff
okay nothing down here always be
okay okay ABS always be scanning always
be SK I like this okay
okay oh I got a
key like a gun oh careful for
turrets I thought I heard
something I think I heard a chunky wony
hi who chunky wonky has come to
assassinate my
so that's not nice you thank you why am
I alone and
why why are these
locked thank you
chat there really nothing down
there
um hey guys where's the EGS the fire
fire
entrance it's over this way
right maybe
not there's like three of
them
I've gone too
far
what the hell was that jumping around
was that one of
them well the fish I placed
here is
gone
so yeah one of them must have run it
back
yeah yeah it
is you
hi oh wait that was my stamina
that's what my stamina was
this
rain you guys heading
back yeah hi because they'll follow
they'll follow us into the ship that's
why okay you want me to we have to do it
at the end though oh I was looking for
an an entrance in a fire
exit find find
emergency don't be such a loner stay
with us I'm
[Music]
sorry I want to try to get a
beehive oh wait they're
off wait isn't this the way we just came
from or I see a a
door I'm
hungry I
need who want to be eaten by
me
I think they found it
somehow yeah but it's getting late I
don't know I'm going to I am going to be
a loner and hang out at the ship
actually I'm
scared it's getting late um
it's getting late and it's best if one
of us survives I say about to attempt to
get a
beehive so how do I grab it without
immediately getting killed by bees
that's the
question cuz I know Zen taught me I need
to leave it at the side of the
ship but
how dust I full Stam
run and then drop it do a loop around
watch out for Doos oh yeah you're right
it's getting really
late okay that's the first
one I don't think I can get the second
one though with my
health um so I
think I'm going to check and see if
they're
alive okay yeah there's uh that's me
actually okay pom's still
moving pomu is
moving
okay let's
see kiaha still
moving uh but it looks like something's
on Kata
no
um oh she got Bracken
okay ay is about to get
Bracken I
think oh
no
oh oh
God
she's not moving so I'm inclined to
think that she is
dead pom's still moving I think pomu
might be coming
back
pomu pomu not done yet pomu get in
here I think I saw a dog oh yeah be
quiet okay um I think the other two are
dead I think it's just us no way uh yeah
yeah so I think AA hasn't moved
assumption is correct um I have gotten
CL a little creature by yeah yeah um
well those I think are the bees so what
I'm going to do is I need you when I say
so to hit the start ship I'm going to
grab the bees okay and then I'm going to
bring them back in narissa narissa
you're so brave okay are you ready okay
hit the leave button I'm ready
ma'am no wait I'm dead go get the me go
get the Beehive
no get the Beehive hit the button no she
died so fast there is uh
wait oh pomu hit the button get the
Beehive and run not the
Discord hit the
button oh was that the right order yeah
yeah yeah yeah get the
reive go I'm running
[Music]
I think I did
it oh hell
yeah where'd she
go lazy if we were
laziest I
got oh my God I got more stuff this time
the braet is in love with me or
something mine is 60% oh [\h__\h] where's
our beehive oh go you guys go
what where's the Beehive I I brought it
in I brought it in oh they knew that we
did it for Discord so they don't count
it oh my
[Laughter]
God we
recorded the game developers are
watching the stream right now well we
have about
156 reason of uh
stuff why you turn off the light turn
off the light you scared
me noting Allowed no you know you know
one good thing about living alone I just
realized is that nobody can like turn
off the lights in the room I'm in
randomly by accident does anyone ever oh
my God no that's so annoying do people
do that to you that's so mean do people
do that when I when I used to live with
my family I mean it just happens doesn't
it like when you in the toilet Idol
meeting and what
what what no I mean not on purpose just
by
accident this is ay our only exclusive
experience maybe it's maybe Americans
have the light switches on the other
side of the
room yeah the light switch is on the
inside yeah yeah it's usually on the
inside the inside your bathroom light
switch is on the inside in the bathroom
yeah yeah yeah oh wait is this a
cultural thing yeah probably maybe I
think so oh interesting I have some
light switches uh uh for example my
guest room has a light switch on the
inside but my bathroom has a light
switch on the
outside I see
him
why now I know what to do when you're on
the toilet when I see
you no wait now Rea knows now re is
going to turn the light off you're
right no no
opportunity you will not
dare wait did you die there's monster
there's a monster an animal he kissed me
what is that he kissed you I'm not sure
I'm scared though which
animal
zooming where oh the bird the bird
that's a hute [\h__\h] bir why on the
ground he's walking around just a bird
oh what that's not how birds move what
the [\h__\h]
why are they on the
ground where's oh I see a beehive but I
don't think we'll be able to get this
one I'm going to get it you
guys you are you're going to get it
okay I need to make up for my failure
run leave me go to the building you can
go the very end no I need to get it
closer failed construction is okay why
don't they fly anymore why are they what
the [\h__\h] what where is what are they
doing where even is I found the entrance
yeah entrance is
here
oo we're on bow again so it should be
the same map that we did the first time
they can't hear
me I'm going to die I'm going to die to
get the Beehive but I need to remember
okay that's right there and the Beehive
is right
here so from The Beehive I need to run
straight I need to get full
health
full full
health don't run at the bees I mean of
course we're about to be very
dead we're about to be very
dead
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I failed I already failed it's fine
oh my God there's two
beehives it's whatever we're giving up
on it I didn't grab it correctly it's
over it's
over it's over we're just going to go in
we're going to look for
stuff ideally you want to bait the bees
how
though how do you not grab the hive I'm
so confused anyways it's over I'm still
alive what the [\h__\h] are you talking
about you have a problem you have a
problem yeah yeah are you guys flirting
without
me talk [\h__\h] about you what the fu where
where
where I'm in your
walls actually don't know what that
means this is what I assume it
means is pomu
yelling what the [\h__\h] rber ducky your
door you make bad times so much fun oh
my
up anything damn I can never find
anything this game is so
[Laughter]
scary
like come on you're telling me there's
nothing in here nothing at
all
what what do you mean new dat new
creature data sent a
terminal
wait I didn't me to
crouch [\h__\h] oh I'm so dumb oh
no
anyway K's running from
something what I'm not quite
sure where am
I
K oh that's nice no kid that's not
nice turn the lights on R ducky collect
oh somebody else ising
what the [\h__\h] is
this cor is so
expensive CRA
huh where's
p
pmu
p Play It's
Over go away yeah she turned on hard
mode for
real oh pomu disconnected oh
no oh we was
hiding why will no one come pick me
up oh
no stream got turn oh did she actually
cuz it seemed like she had lag going on
mhm can't click this button I think I
disconnected cuz I lost internet um you
can keep playing until I'll I'll join at
when next game okay okay we were Ki is
going to die
so oh
no it's so over just start the
ship she should just start the ship
so cuz he's not GNA move
right oh yeah I can just vote to leave
sorry
[Laughter]
K oh
kiata oh
kiata
[Music]
I can see
him oh it's
over it's
over is it good if I just don't look at
him I mean I can't make it past
him wait what if I
jump
nice oh it's too late though she's not
making back to the ship in
time wait it's surely there I should
should up up or
down
oh my
God I was I was desperate I was
desperate you did your
best I thought maybe there's a path
there but there wasn't oh my gosh that
was so silly was that a scream or was
that a
mob no idea maybe you maybe
scream
yay yay does someone want to reinvite PO
yeah yeah can you can you reinvite in
this game chat or does it have to be so
when you when you hit um I think we
might need to drop off the items real
quick have to um I think I have to
remake the lobby because you can't
invite
people yeah yeah but I I think what I'm
saying is I think we can drop off the
items get the money and then try to
revite okay let's let's try that real
quick I don't know how to go to the
company can someone please reinvite me
whenever you have the chats thank you um
how do we selling stuff and then we're
going to save a file and we're going to
reinvite
you thank you I miss
you I think to go to the company we just
press e here right no um use the
terminal to rout to the
company okay on our way let's go yay I
have no idea how to play aren't you
proud of me that I actually did kind of
escape the Bracken first yeah you did so
good I was watching you thank you
somebody watching me not helping me okay
hey I can't help you I don't we have a
teleporter should have come back you
should have come back oh you were dead
okay right no I was
alive okay just drop everything off here
oh oh okay can we be killed during this
process no no of course
not of course
not so confidently okay K believe after
we drop all these items off uh can you
come hit the Bell until the guy shows up
we don't have to sell everything right
the Bell uh we might as well Bell yeah
just hit the Bell a guy will show up so
you can just sit there and just uh
there's a bell on that table down here
oh we got
it
yay
oh
okay that I feel like I heard some
noises from Monsters out there so no no
we work for
Monsters okay so now let's start the
ship and see if we can reinvite pomu
otherwise we'll remake the lobby okay
okay oh wait ringing the bell would that
do something like
no I would never I wouldn't never
K be careful or I'll turn off the
light
yeah mhm not when you're
po yes yes that's exactly when I'll do
it both have reached yeah
yeah what no way yeah has like 250 no
okay yeah I can reinvite now will it let
you yeah no okay uh would you mind
making a new room at we okay I'll do I
just quit
quit Goodbye
takii Oh I'm
away they've kicked me
out they've they've discarded me like a
wet paper
bag I'm just kidding
[Music]
obviously yo we were together and
suddenly you were gone and I was like
what the
[\h__\h] yeah um my internet decided to just
I know
it yeah so but now you're back yeah can
you can you tell it to not do that again
please
yeah I think it maybe got really
flustered it was like so nervous around
you like I mean we were just by
ourselves so oh so cute if you're so if
your connection is so unstable then I
think I'll I'd rather stay with one of
the other girls
next holy [\h__\h] on you can't
[Music]
rely holy [\h__\h] God damn call an
ambulance but not for me not for me
people
we
we I just got thrown away so she looks
so serious on the computer I love you
pom okay what is she doing what is doing
on the
terminal wait what did you say my my
headphones came
[Laughter]
out oh stream will
know over for me guys what are you doing
me how do we start the
game Oh I thought you you knew you what
you were doing I picked I picked the
moon and I ordered some stuff but I the
the land e e star hold e on this like
the thing on the here if you hold e then
it'll be like oh wait no it's not giving
the I didn't get the
prompt where start game oh it's because
I'm the host uh oh okay
oh yeah you have to
be
sorry
yay this new map oh I almost jumped yeah
it's a new map
pumpkins yum yum I like the
pum okay I stay with youa don't die okay
I heard a flashlight so I'm going to
watch for
them loner
I'm what why is it echoing we're not in
a
room this Moon
Acoustics he what are you looking for
what are you doing I'm looking to the
sky for the items I
ordered ah they come from from the sky
yeah there it is oh what the [\h__\h] I
thought it was a
dragon okay grab a
flashlight
that's all order oh wait another one oh
my god let's go okay I think they
already left right so I'm going to go
put this extra flashlight in the ship
okay
[Music]
okay we wish you a Merry
Christmas and this way when we
inevitably die we still have a
flashlight big brain
moves
Kiana okay let's
go okay
okay so are you having fun with lethal
company yeah it's quite quite a lot yeah
I mean yeah I I barely see what's inside
uh but maybe that's really just all
there is inside yeah there's not like
it's not crazy you know
okay okay we got to go deeper mhm deeper
deeper we got to get in I want I want to
actually manage to bring an item back to
the ship we'll get you there I don't
think oh look here they've left this
giant item out so why don't you take
that and bring it back to the ship I
don't know that really counts as such an
accomplishment no so whenever you find
you'll get big items that when you hold
them will say hands full and whenever
you get them just drop them out at the
entrance so oh she's gone okay
I'll I'll but wait are you going to
follow me yeah yeah yeah I'll stay with
you hi wait do you have another big item
M Kato wait for me oh wow wow Kato wants
to bring something back to the the ship
so that actually makes sense that you
come in with me now cuz you also have
something yeah okay and you lead the way
I think it was that way it this
way oh down okay
mhm WEA have you packed yet
no I'm waiting for my thing to get here
cuz she said WEA said that she like
usually packs so early I packed the day
before I pack a month early well it's
because it's my first time in a really
long time traveling uh from hell you
know but I don't know a month in advance
is kind of crazy it's cuz I get
anxious no it's not because you get
excited and want to you know no it's cuz
I'm like oh what if I miss
something okay okay here we
go I just drop it on the floor yep just
drop it right on the
floor and
then okay let's see how the others are
doing before we go in they better not be
dead okay P they're moving yeah they're
moving but it looks like that red thing
they're being chased by something oh oh
yeah oh they're aware I think they're
aware yeah I think they're
scared interesting should should we go
um
yes okay have you been using your
flashlight at all oh wait there's oh
there's like never mind oh I was going
to say monsters now you can charge your
flashlight
here so whenever the battery runs out or
gets low
[Music]
oh it's the same effect as with the bees
oh scared me don't worry oh my God
they're staring it
down and now they're trying to
run ladies
ladies so we so we oh I think they're
out right okay I think they left go to
them um oh pom went back in
they're crazy maybe there's an item that
she really wants to get yeah oh oh no oh
oh they left right when they was
charging at them look at them
go let's go they're so
smart you think the day is much longer
um I don't know what time it
is where do we see it's 30:3 so we
basically want to be back by
5 oh so maybe we've wasted too much of
the day we should go you chicken we
should go I am a chicken h no there's
still oh no look there's a
monster it disappeared now into the
darkness but uh uh-huh are you sure is
it under your bed H Nissa yes come on
chicken come Oni oh there are two dogs
on them they're staring down a dog you
chicken okay go get them then K go bring
them back yeah with you though no one of
us has to
live good
luck oh I'm probably running in the
wrong
direction oh
no where's
pomu
that that didn't last very long oh Kata
come back I heard a dog drop your
flashlight
okay are they dead aly's still moving I
think she's on her way back but I think
pomu disconnected again oh no no
[Music]
pan
No oh I feel bad me too
restart game foran yep we'll wait for a
wewa to get back and then we'll remake
the room stupid Hotel
internet did you
[Music]
DC oh
man you know do you know that pomu has a
company in Japan e no uh and they do
they do um what's it
called really really yeah yeah
p
pusu p no it's called pom no key pomu no
key
mhm yeah for real though every time I go
there I think of pomu says pomu I would
think of pomu too oh yeah A's going to
die wait why the [\h__\h] did I not think of
that P
nice
we we
oh wait it was a sound sensitive wasn't
it yeah the dogs will hear
us I mean we're going to have to restart
so I guess it doesn't matter if we die
so let's just start the ship and leave
her uh
wow sorry
AA
we no how he just
leave bye we hear
me no she actually
did
wow oh no no it calls pom lazy don't do
her dirty dad oh my God I was so
scared I'm lost um Pomo disconnected
again so we need to make the room again
right beside me
a maybe she should be alone maybe being
next to somebody like does something
so should I remake again but she didn't
she didn't seem to I don't think she's
back CU she didn't write anything after
I let me
see was that
[Music]
yes are you okay you want to come
back I want to come back here I'm ending
My Stream So I'm just play
okay okay less pressure on the in web
wait someone said it Autos saves when
you go into orbit so are you guys saying
if we pick a a moon and then restart the
room it
will try I just don't know if they mean
like now or yeah and now it's fine right
because save it probably saves after it
shows the report of all the players
right yeah right I don't
no um you are in order it's already
saved it said it's saved okay now it's
safe to oh we will make a new room
please start it'll save the progress
thank you shoort okay
reming
[Music]
nice I've been
kicked same ho same sa keep loots
nice nice nice nice
nice now I just
wait loves me the
most I'm back darn it did you hear
backom raed me so she loves me the most
wow hello more she can do is say
no can you hear me
yeah
okay I was like
you're like I don't know where to go I'm
like it's okay follow
me
a you survive this time a little bit
longer let's go let's go let's not waste
time yeah let's go um you guys see
there's some there's some flashlights on
the ground for you guys so please pick
them up thank you
yeah don't lose
[Music]
it okay a after
you oh yes I will start
[Music]
theame yippe
yippe oh my God yeah take it uh remember
to charge it here follow you Nissa uh
are you sure about
that uh we you grab yours I'm grabbing
it okay yep I'm going to buy some more
stuff H did you guys die to dogs or no
they didn't I didn't
die Pro
[Music]
Gamer oh did they just leave
me did they just ditch
me guys
wait
guys come to me
okay what are we getting pick up this
walkie
talkie walkie talkie
time yeah um only two so if we travel in
pairs okay I got one um I'm dropping the
other one right here okay so I said I I
I won't go with P anymore um
so where's the flashlight I
bought who wants the walkie you we got
the walkie oh okay take it okay
onward we should do we should do we
should do little um exchange wife
exchange I go with a pom goes with WIS
okay okay okay oh my God Wife Swap oh my
god do you
read there's a TV show maybe maybe
America has it too
where
hello think you're going to say it's so
stupid P okay we go this
way
okay going
down what's a nothing's in there the
backs there's a on the map what why do
we keep getting so many
brons this oh Jesus there's a slime at
the entr Slime oh you guys are here oh
no
slime slowly
slowly it's okay no
joke but it's so
slow we can walk around it ow ow ow ow
ow um guys I think the SL is in love
with me oh there's and then
there's is in love with me oh it's G
theun com you can say stuff like that
but so far it's not doing [\h__\h]
yeah okaybye yep go on wait where's we
I'm here she already went here okay I
check that room there's nothing in
there
here why is there never anything good in
these
rooms I know like our Goa luck has been
so bad I know right right I like to look
up
random
ONN
what I found a
key it's smoke
Smokey I see
theml is not helping that's because
there's a steam
leak yeah I can't find the B you got to
find the
valve there
oh oh it's he
do
oh I think I'm
alone no yeah we're here follow the
sound of my voice we're in the them guys
my flashlight is dead oh my God what the
[Applause]
[\h__\h] I did it yay y y where hello hello
oh oh hello hi okay
we're all here together
y a steering
wheel oh yes take it I can finally have
Direction in my
life my flashlight
died are you guys wait where did they
go
nowhere what if I walk in here and
I why can't I pull the
valve going to turn around and there's
going to be
a I've lost
them
there's so many little guys
everywhere
hello hello
hello how are the other two
doing
I where are
you I'm going to to the other side oh no
oh no
p
pomu
H I don't know where pomu
went
yeah I think pomu jumped off an
edge and
died I think the ship's this
way
yeah
oh she's alive
good
okay well there's kiata she looks awful
um
dead
but pmo and Al are still
moving that's
good pulo
P hello oh a
worm a worm uh-oh Al I'm in the ship oh
yes hello okay let's go everybody ready
Kara where's
Kiara
dead I don't know what
happened but uh let's just get out of
here cuz the dogs are coming
out hey get back in the [\h__\h] never
forget you get back in here she'll
automatically get thrown in I think okay
good
it' be really funny if she didn't here I
[Laughter]
am
oh
nice wh sustain the most
injuries slime was in love with me what
happened you I don't know about other
but P you just said it in the ship why
did you notice so late what the hell
that I was dead took you a while
um it's a pretty big place okay but you
know basically I was just walking like
so close to you girls and I was walking
normally casually and suddenly I walk
over a ledge and just fall and die is it
just me or it really laggy when
you what was lagging sometimes because
the game is like a indie game like the
microphone gets really like pixelated
and when you were explaining it just got
really but did you understand I
basically just walked off and fell and
died really not not an exciting death it
was funny
though that
happens that's like the lethal company
experience that's why it really is now
did I lose the the flashlight yeah oh
[\h__\h] sorry okay I'm sorry Mommy it's
okay did you order something again yeah
for me this
time
[Music]
hey I'm going in yeah you and PM leave
leave a walkie-talkie for kiaha okay oh
yeah here you go thank
you oh okay I'll it
[Music]
up you order I ordered a pro flashlight
the strong
flashlight let's
go yeah we party
hardy
partyy I'm staring at someone's butt oh
guys guys
relax my but is quite
famous yeah it is I was like oh
okay my my butt is on the Hollywood
sidewalk whatever it's as it should
be mhm oh hi
guys
hello we you're in charge of the light
of course where are you I'm at the start
I picked two things up so I'm going to
put them K oh okay yeah I'm behind oh
wait where are you where you go here oh
okay hi I'm back welcome back which way
you want to go I was going this way oh
oh we can go way this way anything here
if you happy clap your butt cheeks if
you happy you know clap your butt CH if
you're happy and you know it and you
really want to show it if you're Happ
you know clap your butt cheeks punching
okay my goding I'm
punching
the door
me rele
okay well
pom pom just there
P that was
freaky yeah for real there
I don't know
speed um if you're scared then cleans
your but butt cheeks we could go through
the fire EG yeah let's go get the fire
exit what about this yeah you just
ignore the fish okay let's go you pick
it up purpose they leave it there okay
okay okay that's good I think we clapped
our butt cheeks a little too loud yeah
we summoned the
spider spider was jealous because the
spider has no butd cheeks yeah there you
you're so
your but Che has one hole one
bit right tell me more about that one
hole what do you mean the
spider go bring that back to the ship
yeah
[Music]
girl wait what did she pick up a giant
uh engine thing oh good I thought it was
a
mask I haven't play the
fu uh the spider's up here
so the door mask up wait is the mask a
mod or is it actually a part of the game
what I think it's a part of the game
because I think someone used it
yesterday Ru put on a mask it's actually
oh yeah that's scary okay I'm
leaving what such a chicken I am a
chicken I'm literally kfp what do you
[Music]
mean good
excuse waa did you pack your UND no I
haven't facted yet I I what if I did
forget them
kiata and I guess if you can have mine I
your ass would probably not fill him out
but well excuse me I'm also quite gifted
in the ass Department what do you
mean well I don't know if your has your
ass ever ripped apart jeans like I
ripped apart not jeans but I also don't
wear jeans you ripped apart what have
you ripped apart in um
leggings but leggings are like leggings
are weaker material than jeans yeah but
I don't wear
jeans you talking about jeggings yeah no
we're talking about RI ripping uh
undergarments with your butt and and I
said I ripped jeans before and she has
only ripped Lin before so I would say my
butt is strong but I'm saying I don't
wear
jeans so it's not a fair
[Music]
comparison like Tomb Raider your butt
excuse me no no no no no no no it ripped
it like you have to imagine like when
when someone really strong like a
bodybuilder flexes their muscles and
then there their shirt just
like you
know you know so like that I did that
with my jeans I guess well do we got
everyone nice little have you ever
ripped a pants with your butt yeah
no no likely story I did but I mean okay
now I am now I am probably flexing as if
it was my butt but before I actually
said it's the mths and I still believe
it's the moths
okay so before you told everybody it was
moths but now you're you're taking that
story back well yeah I'm taking credit
now because my butt could do it if my
butt wanted to but it was the mops yeah
oh like the Moss like chew through it I
think so how dare they yeah how could
they do that that's so rude should have
been
you
why does it look like we're
incriminating each other like a you're
the one who killed
Kia they say
objection objection
OB all right who's getting eated off the
ship we got so much lot you jump off um
you die here we go oh [\h__\h]
idiots [\h__\h] idiots those [\h__\h]
idiots now we're going to get
min [\h__\h]
idiot those dogies you [\h__\h] donies
idiot
sandwiches donys did I drop the
walkie-talkie look we lost you dropped
everything you were
[Music]
holding
yay oh my God I thought maybe if I had
jumped it would have like no back into
the ship
no know what I mean I thought it would
happen I thought we would be Sav all of
that money it was for
science yeah all right let's go drop
everything off shall we oh okay do we
have enough we'll find out real
quick I think we have more than
[Music]
enough
H Kara did you learn about
this about the
what K you have to after we drop out the
last part
yeah all right click the button anything
else which button the Bell that just
went off just keep clicking it till it
shows
up which one
okay oh
um y she's played this game so many
times you wanted that to happen to me
yeah cuz I love you I can't tell if it's
you know you know the males and sharks
and stuff you know sharks don't really
like to eat humans
though well I have a good relationship
with sharks so I'll tell them to do that
why would you do that they won't like me
I'm not
tasty do we have enough oh
400 let's get pomu
back oh man why why did that happen why
for what what was the
purpose I didn't think it would happen
so
fast did pom know did she know yeah she
knew it was going to happen I think she
didn't think it was going to I didn't
think it was going to happen so fast
$92 we got fined for your death what the
heck I'm sorry where is okay let's
see so pom died unnecessarily
twice
yeah it's okay cuz every time that you
disconnected it didn't count as a dead
so we didn't get charged so it's just
making up for it so true logic okay yeah
L it's M for real yeah if you died if
you died two times for free and then you
had to pay two times for death it's free
yeah it's just evened out now okay okay
okay I won't die anymore on purpose I
didn't die on purpose before but you
know I won't really die on purpose okay
um are you taking us this time mommy
somewhere that is
fine
thank you for being our Navigator yeah
thank you thank God yeah I don't want to
touch that keyboard okay let's
go we can't we can't afford to go to
Titan
yet one day all right there's more wait
before you guys jump there's going to be
more flashlights coming for
you thank
mmy Weg mommy wish you a Merry
Christmas I've never had a sugar mommy
before I'm so excited yeah now don't let
the plane land on you or you will
die wor all about that yeah I knew that
happened where is it where is it where
did it who is it because we didn't put
out milk and cookies
maybe
is
okay you yep oh strong Flash oh big
flashlight all right don't lose them
this time Tiana or whoever has the other
walkie if you want to leave it in the in
the thing since we don't have one so
that way if you die you don't lose the
walkie-talkie okay I'll come with you so
smart so smart
[Music]
okay let's go I'm happy being the bread
winner I'm happy to find loot and
provide for this family yes I will
continue to just buy
stuff I didn't think you guys could hear
that from that
[Laughter]
[Music]
distance
it's so what the hell I've never had
like the smoke be here what does the
smoke do what is this it's the it's just
a it's a smoke it's the stuff okay watch
out because you can fall and die here
how do you find the
V oh hello
hello stuff I found a big loot nice yeah
there's a bunch of stuff
oh can't
[Music]
see uh oh there's a loot bug there's a
loot bug you
guys the vent is open the vent is open
oh
no be
[Music]
careful where the hell is
it we need to we need to find the valve
yeah I'm the ball finder the B
finder oh my God I can't see
[Music]
anything we found it no I'm I'm going to
leave ah you
did
a I'm getting out of
here what the
[\h__\h]
alra where who lived oh my God you both
lived y
y um I hear her walking around out here
talking yeah oh okay but I don't know
where she
is oh I think I see her in the ship
maybe
maybe maybe she went through the fire
exit
yeah this
way fire
[Music]
exit
good tidings we
bring hi guys thank
[Music]
you winner is there more steam or am I
going crazy no I don't think
so oh okay
what is this place there's nothing else
here well I guess we should go back to
the ship and leave
then she's such a chicken oh wait this
way just
kidding oh this thing is this guy is
also harmless where is
he uh
[Music]
um what's
harmless oh my God missa there's a
monster there and I'm going to die
there's a monster
where behind
me no there's not not
anymore um
okay what the we need to get out of here
okay run yeah um okay exit exit exit
exit you just exit
exit radiation where's the exit I don't
know we need to get out of here follow
me where are you I don't think it's here
follow the sound of my
voice
run let's
go we got this let's get out of
here
oh W let go M it's so good that you were
there yeah thank
you nice when my wife's wife saves the
day you know we're we are we are all
connected with our wiess so it's true
don't have to call her your wife's wife
she can also be your wife hello hello
don't go back
ining I did I almost
died
oh well you didn't I have to walk around
I didn't no you can jump down
woo nice all four surviving
and no
way looks like these lights really saved
the
game I didn't bring anything but I was
here for support yeah oh yeah also I
brought a key but I I didn't use it
again like I never you can save but we
can we can use it save them
mhm yeah we can save it for next time
yay we have so much
[Music]
stuff adopting the ID wife sharing
system yes we have a wife sharing system
yes yes all right so we
depart
iness from Fire
Emblem what's this posted
girl what's this post it gra it you can
type it into yeah to the computer it
just tells you stuff you're I think it's
mhm it's
[Music]
lore oh my
God I'm the CEO I'm not the
intern okay um you know someone has
everybody starts somewhere Kiara okay is
this is this real no
is
what what's real what's real someone in
my chat said type boobies on the
computer what did you do it what
happened I don't think you need to type
in on the computer they're on the screen
aren't
they yeah they're they're
trolling what what no no no no it's a
it's
oh code it's a code gamer talk
80085 I I don't know about that
one oh is it not boo bees so should
there be
88 uh one three
five
boobies oh three nothing
happened yeah
135 type
135 nothing happened but when I typed
boobies it asked if I wanted to buy the
boom
box oh wait maybe do you B no I didn't
it said you want to spend I don't do it
that is what I call customer
service boom box is 6 boom box yeah we
don't need a boom box on the menu it'll
just automatically or we could save up
for the
jetpack yeah or we could save up to go
to tit Titan mhm Titan okay let's go
save up the Titan okay so we need uh
about I think it was about 400 to pass
So currently our stuff is worth about uh
uh
157 so we still need to get quite a bit
of stuff so we got it yeah we got
this we didn't even die land ship um
guys want to try going to
March again okay anywhere that's not
Eclipse I'm not I'm not I'm not going to
chance
it
okay we're going to I'm going to switch
we're going to wipe for this no just for
she's switching wives can you believe it
this one is I'm going
tot I
choose wait wait wait een Meen een me
miny mo catch the tiger by his toe een
Meen miny mo I don't know how it
continues go we are okay wow didn't even
consider
me no I was with you last last
[Music]
round okay I think we're witnessing a
lover's
quarrel no no no oh
no the
birds birds be
bees wait is that why there's birds and
bees oh you make a good point P but is a
little spicy Leal company spicy spicy
[Music]
spicy H
how we just started okay for this room
okay let's go I hope I will not be a
burden you never I have a
key
okay we got a big flash him
light fire exits right
there there's a mine
there
um okay so
mine
here obviously I want to see if I can
find anything else
first but this would be good to come
back
to
later
for the content
no yeah if we got lucky with Beehives we
could pretty easily reach the
quota but I have a feeling that won't
happen oh hello hi where are you oh hi
right here hello I got that's a big axle
um I found if you go the other other way
I think right there's uh the fire exit
and there's another one of the the
things but if you there's a Mine by it
if you pull it though it'll it we need
to leave so don't don't pull the uh the
glowy
thing what I don't does the glowy thing
actually do anything yeah it makes it
makes everything get
harder okay there said it's left it's
left apparently anyway oh left okay yeah
don't so just don't go left nothing
there
nothing's
there all right let's bring this
back man
coil not getting lucky with Beehives
either
shoot
don't trust pomu she's going to pull it
no pomu is a good girl pomu wouldn't do
that don't say such things about
pmu
okay total 239 not bad let's see how
everyone's doing real quick before I
head back
okay it looks like probably AA and Kiana
are
good um Pulu is back in and she's being
chased by something ah she went where I
told her not to
go is she getting chased by a
Bracken it ran away when she shined her
light on
it oh
p
what the
[\h__\h] okay wait let's check real quick
again it seems like they're outside and
coming back
no they're not in the building
anymore p
she going to grab it oh yeah she's going
for it let's see if she makes it
out okay poma's
out they're still trying to find their
way back to the
ship they'll get here eventually right
hello hi hi you found the way
back oh my God you're so good at this
game we only found landmines that's all
we found we found some stuff pomu is on
her way back too oh no there's a monster
guys guys guys guys stop there might be
dogs okay
[Music]
pomu I don't I'm not sure where she is
[Laughter]
yeah
but people people oh no no P pom no no I
have to save her where is that can we
zoom out uh
no oh no no oh she went inside and
dodged okay she's at the entrance does
anyone want to attempt to meet her there
save her we save your real wife uh drop
your drop wait drop your flag flash I
dropped
it she's outside again
right okay and there's no
monster just very careful oh oh
Found Love Story Love Story ti ti indeed
the ship is here the ship is here here
here here
we here g
g was already running
made you [\h__\h] wait those guys aren't
bad right they attack oh there's one
near the ship out over here hurry and
get on and let's run ready oh my
God ready ready I almost died to the
Bracken too that guy came up on me and I
turned around at the last second we kind
of saw we saw him so many times he was
so cute we are we are ladies of
competence moly
jeez let's go I think we're pretty
pretty close to our quota I think we
need 3.99 we're at like 368 so if we
just get a few more items sometimes it
doesn't count everything sometimes like
the game
glitches I think it's not that I think
the the is
different oh no we're at 396 if you
stand over here it scans them all better
yeah yeah is that how it works in the
game like the company buys items at
different rates every time I I'm not
sure don't forget to charge your
flashlights oh thank you
this
okay is that enough is one charge enough
yeah it is yeah
one scanner only scans a set
Limit Oh you're trying to scan kind of
random it's percent based on what day
you go different rates based off of days
left oh I
see oh okay I don't
know depending on where you
stand let's go let's do our ve
go I'm going to take one is this is this
the last one yeah this is the last day
so we just need to notp so if everyone's
dying just whoever is left leave
okay I go with pomu now okay me yes and
that's probably going to result in
seeing so let's go let's do this yeah
let's
go why are you so fast I used all my
stamina okay the ship is underneath okay
yeah we just keep basically huging this
way never
remember and then we go up here yeah you
got to like yeah can never remember
where the ship is on this
map and this one's more
tricky here we
are all right ikim show
[Music]
girlsim
show let's go this way a where
[Music]
one I'm scared don't be scared we got
this oh my Go She's So comforting though
um nothing else okay tattered metal
sheet let's
go oh I wonder if there's anything in
here oh there's a lot of stuff in here
oh oh it's just a robot
mine it's so loud there's a cookie tin
too uh maybe we should drop this off so
it doesn't attract
stuff yeah we can go back okay my hands
are full I can't even walk
upstairs yeah it's a restaurant chain
that you know you know they make
polariz
what a
robot little
guy what was there it's just the oh
nothing we're yeah he's just loud
so they want us to take the robot to the
ship right away apparently so I'll be
back so you three travel together maybe
he brings a lot of points maybe I don't
know wait the remote is good got
[Music]
[Applause]
remote yeah I should have grabbed more
stuff
oops my
[Music]
mistake the ship's this way
right
yeah it's
[Music]
cursed yeah I guess being loud is not uh
great
okay cursed
item got
get be
bot
okay okay this going to be my AR where I
finally remember on this map where the
sh is do you need
help wait where are
you
ala come back come back up here I'll
help you
okay I'll help you I'll show you how to
get back oh hell yeah okay so yeah go
where pomu is going so you always go
under this thing do we leave you going
to get any
under this thing get under here
support and then go straight through and
then you hug right basically so you go
right and then you go right again and
then the ship is right over by these
these things basically anything that pom
collect means I collected it
to why you laughing also I got the
remote control so woo she did I mean I
found it but she grabbed it oh my God
God I went the other way
[Music]
yeah this map confuses me so bad
mhm I know this sound's
weird
yay okay we have so much stuff yeah no
our place is crowded we definitely make
the quota so do we want to keep looking
for a little bit or do we want to go
what is it
scan it 12 outside the ship totaling at
approximate value of
1200 I want to go back
in be quiet be
quiet is there a dog
yeah yo I was you were closing the door
right when I was about to leave again
dangerous oh did you just start yeah
there's a dog right outside
I could take
him you take that's not a dog that is
not a dog yeah it's a dog that'll eat
you so you can see it
okay damn it oh he's
gone really motivated I want to go back
inside gets eaten by a dog yeah n I'd
win n I'd win so loudly I was just like
sh shut up shut
up oh it's over
Dam it okay okay we can go to the next
map no we got to go to the
company after we sell everything do not
unal life yourself at the ping pong
machine again okay
[Music]
survive okay let's see how much money
did we
make a lot I hope so
[Music]
Grand
take what going Titan baby what is it
chat just because I did a little ping
pong doesn't
mean
anything what do you
mean like
[Music]
P should
we think we should
[Music]
what are you doing going to sell
we yeah open multiple
times oh I sold something I don't think
I can't tell if it's open oh it's open
it's open it's open open what
out oh the ping pong is
selling yeah take it guy oh stand there
when you're selling it it will eat you
yeah 100 wait do we want to sell
everything or do we want to yeah we want
to sell it all let's just sell
everything we're not swey me yeah we
need to go to
Titan no keep the keys some people who
play this game are sweaty and like save
things for later
quos yeah bo be careful be
careful back hey get back back here he's
not opening the door
okay maybe he has money to
buy it just opened it wasn't opening
okay now we wait Mr Man Okay vamos vamos
chica
vamos
[Music]
Yi how much money how much did we make w
W how much money
much Ru don't watch your
stream oh oh I'm inside okay should we
go to Titan or the other one first uh we
need to go into orbit first
pom yeah you're outside come she's right
here no I'm right here
oh oh oh okay I thought maybe I thought
you were just some hanging suit like
this
one oh I'm just like I'm a mannequin
yeah yeah I don't know that was
weird did you guys see her I don't see
her should we go to the house one or
should we go to Titan we're going to
Titan I'm sorry I already sted this yeah
I like Titan what Titan the difficult
map it's a difficult map you're a
professional now yeah we're going to die
now because it's foggy on Titan we
haven't died in a while yeah honestly
maybe I should do a a a die for
entertainment K wants to die for
entertainment
purposes okay wait I'm going to buy some
items before we leave
[Music]
okay
wait for it to come
down there's
snow snow snow what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] it's foggy this TI it's foggy
so don't here yeah you go up why is it
why why is it why why why is it doing
this cuz it's foggy it's like extra
foggy holy cow no why why my my I think
I have a bug what's
wrong do you see my
hand what about it what happen why is
your hand doing that I don't
know drop
[Laughter]
it guys where is
it I don't know it's
uh is this way
oh I found it okay hit it hit it that
was cheering it's like the it's like the
cheering animation we have in our
app I can't find you guys where are you
I'm
lost okay okay follow my boys this is a
great
start I have my light on I'm yelling yay
okay are they all here in circles I
think oh I'm at the come here eh where
are the rest of the shovels on the
ground where wait did you not pick one
up no oh we can hit things with this now
yeah oh let's go our weapons wait there
was three on the ground and now there
I've got two of them so I have I have
one for
p should just go in it's time to go but
where the [\h__\h] are we going it's a good
question where are you
iide going to go up I'm just wait I'm
right behind you hey pomu are you near
the
ship she's at the entrance yeah I'm at
the entrance now could find you guys I
never find any
entrance it's right
here I'm so lost no behind you behind
you behind me behind me yeah here here
go up here oh my God okay where's Pulu
oh up here climbing yeah they're
climbing nice now we're all the
way there's a a shovel yeah oh oh it's
not you still have it yeah yeah she's
bringing it to you
oh okay oh my God my it's already
12:00 maybe we should just
leave thank you the we have to do it for
the company yeah we got to do it for the
company
let's go
in we have to meet our quota there's a
key we must meet our qua yes we
must I
have in the
cup in a
cup sping there's also
a yeah here's a sound here a should we
bring it back because I already full
inventory yeah me too and this is really
rare this is expensive yeah bring it
back not rare but you know all expensive
nice
huh why you got close to me I just the
girl
[Music]
what's happening why are they
screaming on the wall was jumping on the
wall what you a where are
you I can't help
her are you still
alive
where are
you I'm here I killed a good
job
um I think we should just
[Music]
leave I have no idea where you even
are you sound like you're really close
to me and I'm by the
exit Okay I'm going to follow you
okay but I just have no idea where you
are I don't
know
um I think she's this way
somewhere ay do you still hear
me Al Al
do you still hear me yes I can okay I'm
by the exit so if you can just get to me
okay if I die I just want you to know I
love your cover of I is one of my
favorite producers thank you I
[Applause]
loveo oh [\h__\h] it
work okay let's get out of
here I have two heavy things critical
injuries okay um I can't carry because I
have too many things like this
mask oh no homu are you coming
up yeah I'm coming up we have a heavy
item could you carry it back yeah I'll
carry it thank
you oh yeah you can take that one okay
I'll drop the other one yipp someone
just stay behind no we should all leave
it's almost
wow call me a coward did they get it I
only I was inside for like 2 seconds
found five items and then left I saw
like one square meter of the inside I
killed a bug and then I killed other bug
you kill the Box yeah it was really
scary damn it I didn't use the shovel at
all that was my first time killing
anything in this game
damn how
trou KN lead meana somewhere
somewhere is the ship like right okay or
or this
way what does that even mean this way
over here over here what is over here
mean I'm lost yeah right right
right oh we're
safe oh okay
okay okay I think we should leave okay I
heard
screaming and that scared
me who scream I don't know maybe uh we
have
$466 worth of things right now you have
the mask
yeah don't let pomu
pick put it down put it down pomu I why
what does it it'll turn you into an evil
monster it'll kill you yo I saw that
clip of when when teleported you into
the ship with the mask on I I saw what
happened I know you are capable of doing
I've changed my
[Laughter]
[Music]
way interesting I didn't do
[\h__\h] okay but I'm like way more
productive in this game than in uh
phasmophobia yeah this is fun yeah
phasmophobia it's fun [\h__\h] there the
only yeah this is just like phasmophobia
um control wise everything else is very
different it's just
fun this time this time I'll go inside
and do something yeah didn't you pick
stuff up though that is I did but it was
like immediately after we entered I
didn't see anything from inside oh my
yeah do you like my D I do I love
them those up are we
going yeah let's go
yeah what was
that what was that sound
effect you pulled the lever pull the
lever well back you did a little is this
is this not the Titan
no we can we now that we bought it we
have it permanently so we can go or I
think AO will on the save until we die
die yeah I have to pay for it every time
nope just once yeah I thought oh there
he
goes who are you Visa did you buy
something again no sorry I I'm just I
zoned out for a second I was letting my
cat out of the room a baby yeah maybe
every round are you going to miss C oh
they're saying apparently no we do pay
for it every
time oh but last time that's what you
have it until you
leave oops you know what you should do
what you should cut off some fur from
your cat uh just a little bit take a
Polaroid and then tape the fur on the
back of the Polaroid and then take it
with you in the
wall SC you are so crazy what say oh
guys sorry apparently I lied I'm sorry I
didn't realize that we had to stay in
orbit of it so we can't go
back no it's okay
oopsie no we that was that was a real
natural oldw there oh
yeah
yeah hit me don't hit me oh I forgot to
charge my
flashlight
fire why did it do that when I killed
it that was so nasty so gross Mass [\h__\h]
you is there something cool
here oh I don't want to fall down again
yeah don't jump be
careful nothing he something Stu around
I I I am so not scared anymore now that
I have a shovel yeah
right the shovel has freed
you it's going to take me like 20
seconds to scroll over to my shovel when
I see an
enemy you'll see a Bracken and then you
won't be so great well he's different
he's it makes me nervous he's tall dark
and handsome yeah he's just like an
ender you
[Music]
sorry
hey I came the wrong
[Music]
way oh my God
wait can I open this yeah you can open
it
[Music]
romanof this is the exit
right
yeah
vent is open isn't that the bug we
killed
already surely there's not anything
else they wouldn't do that right
everyone else is dead no they're
not we can even
check
see they're all
alive all
alive yeah while I'm
here
what is that
outside guys what is that
outside one that it seems
no I see pomu I see Aira I see Kiana
ah
oh
a well guys come on you can make your
way
back come on get out of there
a wewa are you
okay sorry you
died sorry for your death at
wewa Weston
pepperonis it'd be a baboon Hawk I
see oh I think they found the
exit
are they actually there you girls hi A's
dead
oh no how did that happen I'm not sure
but there's a monster nearby
somewhere where' you all get
333 oh 400 ooh there's lots of loot here
I I only brought a big valve and we we
were like almost
lost find our way back there so much
loot by where died
right I think it's the loot bugs I think
it's the loot bugs she's the loot
Master well let's leave
we'll have to buy another flashlight for
a
wewa yeah
weed we we'll miss you we'll miss
you
byebye
[Music]
oh oh nice
guy wait AA took the
mask oh no where is it it's on the floor
it's on the ground okay
good injuries I was
thrilled was it a loot Bo no it was the
things that like hang on
the uh the ones that down onto your face
and like Eat You
Alive I was like yelling I was in the
room beside where you guys were and I
was like guys help me I I heard someone
scream you that was me
I didn't hear anything I'm so
sorry oh she Hur oh man oh Manara you
left her to
die I was I was alone already at that
point
okay for
you wait why did it only give me one
item wait I'm going to buy you another
Pro
flashlight yay yay
and oh
[Music]
okay I guess I can only buy one at a
time just ate me
alive then if it's everyone you're not
pomu she
heard I didn't what do you mean have no
idea
open I have no stream I have no
stream
she 100% I'm innocent no proof a we
watch for the thing thank you and
everyone charge your
flashlight yeah thank
you Mommy Mommy
[Music]
respons me
hopefully a shovel and a pro flashlight
get it all for yourself
tonight is this freestyle or are they
real lyrics like that no it's made it's
freestyled oh okay good good freestyle
thanks oh it's
somewhere you find it a we I here
they're already
there they started Christmas without us
W okay you got both of them yes thank
you let's go can I go let's
go oh my God wait I've never
seen
oh I wonder if I can
find a
beehive you think there's a beehive
someone's asking where I'm going a good
question I I forgot where I was okay I
thought I was on a different
map I thought I was on the other
one that looks like a
beehive
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
well look I may not be smart I may not
be smart and by I may not be smart smart
I'm not
smart okay don't run into the hide bait
them to fly and Sprint around the nest
okay so get them to come at me go around
the nest and then pick it
up
okay ah I'm just not good I just
[Music]
suck oh my God I'm
amazing
I'm so
good I'm so
good okay it's very close it's not quite
in there because I don't want it to
harass us inside but this way it's
closer that surely this
time surely this time they can get it
right you think you think cuz I'm lost I
don't know where they
are I'm completely on my own
um I'm on my
own I don't know how to get to where I'm
going
ah I'm going to
die it's so over for me
where is
everybody maybe I should just check on
the map it's too late for
me it's too
late okay that's the ship home
base hi
hello is anybody dead be careful of
bees no we're okay okay good I mean a
might be dead I don't know oh
okay a looks like she's walking around
okay so pomu in case I die we have the
Beehive it's very close it's not in here
because the bees will get angry okay
right after we put the shift to take off
someone needs to go grab it hi okay okay
I volun and then just drop it on the
floor in here no once we take off the
bees will the be will get stuck on the
cuz I'm almost dead too but
yeah can we just hit the Beehive of the
um they'll electrocute you because the
the shovel is metal so they will kill
you
instantly oh oh don't don't drop it hold
the Beehive apparently hold it in the
ship hold it in the ship so yeah once
you grab it uh after the ship takes off
immediately go grab it and hold it don't
drop it okay okay okay okay I'll do it
now a just needs to know it looks like
she's coming back so we can tell her too
no
Al I found a
beehive oh I was fighting for my life
wait there's something really big in
front of the door I have to grab still
wait
okay no it's just
one how many things we have
okay hi I'm almost dead from
beasting oh you know what happened to me
me and pom were walking around and then
this thing that that sucks your face was
going to attack me and before it
attacked me I punched it once but it
still got to my face and I thought I was
going to die cuz it was it was already
sucking but then p p hits my head with
the shovel and kills the the bug let's
go but then literally 10 seconds later
the same thing happens again yeah
that'll happen that will happen sadly
save me twice save me twice how many
times did you save me whistle I'll save
you in the Mal divs you won't drown I'll
I'll save you but aren't you you're not
an efficient swimmer either yeah but
I've got big bobes so they'll make me
float in the water uhhuh we won't S okay
we should we should got combine your big
bobes with my big booty I've got a big
butt too we'd be
perfect
oh oh they went back
in ah they can't help it yeah they
wanted to get the thing help it mhm they
made it I'm now they just need to make
it in
here let's go oh there's something there
shh it's okay just be quiet just in case
is it you think it dog it might be a dog
I'm not
sure Bow Bow Bow Bow
[\h__\h] how how were the dogs doing you
played Lethal company right with them
yeah they did really well did they let
the dogs
out
no no
good okay good they're both
there
oh come on come on are they even I can
hear them oh oh it's right there
yay
yay they were it looks like a reskin of
an older mob y we made it
yay or maybe it's like a all right I'm
going to go get it there's a wait wait
wait wait we have to take off first we
have to take off
first are are you ready pomu there's a
giant yes wait no hold on I don't know
where it is where is it oh there's a
giant there's a
[Music]
giant wait did you start
it oh yeah oh um
sorry keep holding on to it yeah yeah
don't let go I'm not letting go I won't
I'll never let go sorry
k Sorry
K yay
in
between recovered my body
so oh yeah CU you died in the ship it's
so squishy yeah right okay keep holding
on to it and let's go to the
company
Mai how much is that
worth a
lot it still doesn't say how much it's
worth when I put so good oh beehive
19 yeah 19 that's it oh 90 90 no it's
got to be way
more
19 yeah
Oh I thought the Beehive was worth like
I thought it was like 100 I thought it
was worth at least 200 yeah I thought so
too is that
okay
value apparently they vary from 67 to
100 plus that's only 90 for us even
though we're this cute I know right give
me a better price so easily not worth it
not worth it Jesus not that
guy I think it's full okay I can't yeah
oh I out watch
out that was tery yeah right doesn't
like the
tee professionals
o professionals professionals
baby no we we still more remember when
you heard the screaming before it was
from the phone
oh
yeah time to go sell the mask he's
taking it right now don't sell the
mask why not we gotta we gotta use it no
it's evil what do you mean I want to see
what happens okay I'll bring it
back
no so we we still we still have a one
thing up here
though you do watch a YouTube
video stupid come on Chad come on you
literally watch the clip you know you
see yeah but like I want us to
experience it together I'll be right
back okay
okay now put on the mask no let's
surround we can surround her and
no I'm scared will she kill us
all wa who's going to wear the mask not
me
is that sound oh God what is she opening
we have to protect her PA
you're what's happening I don't know
your mic wasn't muted so I needed to
protect whatever was going on oh I just
got my French
toast wait the one from
71 yes oh my God yes the oh my God I
know exactly which one it's so good
never had it it's so good the one from
7-Eleven oh my God Japanese 7eleven we
got to make it
clear I heard I heard American 7 is not
good I've never been hey we made so much
money wa oh God I CL was going up higher
and high okay so we have
$1,227 we can go the Mansion one what
one is the mansion Ren or
Dine um which one is okay wait there's
two of them but one of them the cheaper
one is the more worth it I think
ah um yeah what one it
sucks what one dine D is better din is
better but is that one the
Mansion yeah fine
okay let's go will this one be the last
one because remember when you girl said
off stream we're going to do two hours
yeah yeah yeah
yeah three more days I haven't noticed
well we're going to have to die anyway
because if this is the last one so um we
could just go here explore a bit and
then do the mask yeah oh my God I'm
so oh a little love
bite
a Little Love
T Little Love T charge your flashlights
everybody Char raining oh no it's
raining uhoh is there electric is there
lightning okay p take the mask it's all
yours and leave your flashlight and your
shovel oh no
okay do it all right shovel at the ready
ladies you're going to die
right let's go in first though right
let's go in first okay let's go in first
okay okay you lead the way
pomu this
way shitty
weather where
is a
we we a we we
we
we we we we I'm com don't worry okay I
bought something ooh okay let's wait for
it yeah let's wait I'm excited I don't
know what it is is it the jet
pack is what did you buy a
we what what's this do oh it's already
in the ship oh I don't have to wait for
it did you get the teleporter is it the
toilet oh it's here it's the to what
the
wa
nice
who well some privacy please some
privacy okay let's go where we going
sorry guys we're going to kill pomu when
she puts on the
mask look whatever makes you happy we do
like a hide and seek we'll do like I'll
go hide and you guys find
meil head find us first
yeah I love the coil heads they're my
number two oi after the
Bracken a
good where the
entrance I'm in water this is water
don't go in don't go
in [\h__\h] you water water is
[Music]
rising you got to turn around you you
got to come
out guys the water hey where how where's
the building how how do we get in I
think we have to go this way we were
baited by this light
thing no the lights right it's cuz
there's raining and the water like piles
up really fast uhoh I don't know how to
get in I don't know how to get why don't
we leave and see if the weather is
better
tomorrow okay that's a good idea tried
our best yeah we tried we came we saw we
died it's fine it's fine yeah we di D
Dash cuz the Moon is called dying you're
so
silly [\h__\h] weather n defeated by the UK
yeah do you want to use the mask now P
or do you want to wait until it's
clear I want to wait
building everybody
in let's go a British Beach I flushed
before we left did you wash your hands
we don't have a sink well that that is a
penundrum isn't it it's okay I put my
gloves
on Can we is this okay that we didn't
get get anything yeah because we're not
trying to win cuz either way we're going
to start stop playing after after this
so okay okay moons let's see Dy is
eclipsed so now we'll get to see in
eclipsed oh
no you don't have to go to a new place
or you can just yeah can we cuz it won't
let me go okay yeah let's do it yeah you
just land again okay Eclipse weather
Eclipse
woo there's a toilet oh skib skibby
toilet let's go
[Music]
uhoh
no okay I think this place is always EC
is it no it's not always it's not it's
not eclip right now right it didn't say
it is it is it is well then we're about
to die probably right
now
oh going the same
way I think I hear a
giant how do they call you the
nisler um because bi boo called me
nisler
oh
mhm my little bi boo
Zoomer it's okay we also have a
Zoomer Yeah in our wave our third is
W in your
way yeah our third is the
[Music]
zomer here we
go oh yeah okay God I play
CH if only I make my
move okay Ron calm
down whoa what is this cool place it's a
Manion
oh it
is oh hello oh I found
gold since this is the last round I'm
just
going make
[Music]
my you want to turn
with what happened I've never I don't
know I've only seen a really TP you I
don't know what happens like
to re next Harry Potter
okay it's a Holy Grail right in Harry
Potter am I going in circle are you
holding
it yeah look I might
definitely
go there's a bug in there hi oh
oh hi come here come
here what who hit me she hit me I didn't
mean to I'm sorry I'm trying to hit the
bug no you hit
me no I
didn't okay anything I'm hitting on
you oh I like that though here
yeah
so
powerful
[\h__\h] oh no [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h]
that yeah keep on hitting it yeah it
will die
eventually what all
this
it
PVE not
cracker hi B
girls hi how's it
going connected in death not oh my God
that was like so much so many things
happen Nutcracker there was
was me with the mask on yeah wa that the
first thing we started hitting was that
Pomo I thought it was an enemy uh I
don't know what that first thing was but
apparently it it only moves if we're not
looking at it but yeah the coil
head well that's a coil head this has
been fun we're not going to meet our
quota that's okay we can just go in and
do our best
yeah
we're still we're still at we we have
one more day right yeah yeah so we can
go in and do our best how much money do
we have left and then we W make theoda
and then Kiara can see what happens when
you don't make
the oh yeah cuz I guess we never saw
that before no so you'll find out today
you'll find out
today oh
there oo let's
go let's go let's go
[Music]
we're Pros we're Pros have a l we're
kind of
amazing I thought at least the first
round we would
lose yeah no we're just we're winning
quota it would have been so embarrassing
know why we're winning worldwide web yep
the worldwide
W worldwide WB we can add another
w
world even more W's where's the
door door what right here wait where are
you hi I'm in the other room oh right
here again let's go I want to go
upstairs where did you where did you
enter there's a robot but I don't want
to pick it up cuz it's loud yeah we're
not going to makea anyway so there's
a might as well just have fun exploring
yeah
here here I'm hungry guys I need to cook
you poor thing hi hello oh you heard me
yeah you're
hungry oh what the [\h__\h] is that yeah I'm
hungry hungry what is this that looks
kind of
crazy
I'm gonna go drop
this
wa
painting painting painting
ined
key
[Music]
key the
key oh what was that
a m
my God there's so many landmines I
know I'm
scared it's this side it's right here
yeah I saw it in the little corner
yeah I like this Mansion oh yeah it is a
dead end this way we
[Music]
go AK my
show I wonder what the enemies
here I know another land M
here how does everyone keep running into
landmines I don't even know where I
am I can't get out of
here okay good oh bottles
here come save me oh there's a gift box
o open it open it up what you
get yeah this is my no this is my home
now I live
here no I live
here this is a dead end
too I can just managed to escape nice
where are you guys hi I'm in the
entrance I found a
ring found a ring yeah and I
found a Billard
what is that a clown nose oh bilard
clown found a mug that says number one
mug and I was gifted a Rubik's Cube nice
shall we try to bring these back to the
ship even though we're not going to make
quota I think I'm going to keep
exploring yeah too I want to see what's
upstairs okay land mine that's
what I feel like I don't think there's
proposed to K that's a good idea yeah
that' be quite the good
[Music]
k
k yeah she's definitely alive and are
you sure piing it
she I don't know if she want to dive
onto the mine
chat my
[Music]
intrusive
sh
wife hi pomu what
town what's that sound I'm not
sure okay I'm just going to follow you
okay dead
end say
anything res
World maybe she's downstairs
did she
leave oh God I'm being haunted by the
little
girl
[Music]
what if I I hear her breathing she's
like oh my God she's right here oh she's
gone now oh my God I'm going to die to
the little girl my head's going to get
exploded it's okay just come here come
here what happens I'll get you out yeah
get out
a oh uhoh I think she put on the I think
so too
found I guess so you put it
on I knew she was
dead created you created the the the
wife web you want to kill me you never
you are creat the white
web you got C on for real is standing on
the stairs oh my God he's running after
me oh my
God you want to bring the U painting in
the
ring yeah where's
oh she's also dead oh well let's go back
to the ship and leave shall we I I hope
I don't die as a little girl though if I
die nura it's all on it's it's all up to
you why would we die to the little
girl she'll come out here she'll explode
my head
what yeah just do
that oh
oh my
[Laughter]
God oh my God the dog I actually I found
a mask and I I I actually didn't know
what exactly would happen even though I
already experienced it so they told me
to put it on and I thought I could
freely haunt you guys when I put it on
but I didn't realize that I would die
and then not over yeah m so
funny all right that was so good you
just got quiet all of a sudden I turned
around but it was just because I on my
own to find some stuff so it was natural
that I became quiet but it was fun
watching you girls looking for me yeah
we were looking for you so um because we
have nothing
oops because we have nothing we don't
have to go to the company meaning we can
just explore dine one more time
oh you yeah and then uh once we end this
day we don't have to worry about
collecting anything because it's Day
Zero it'll just uh we'll experience the
loser thing so what say you we paid good
money to be
here we just go again or I say ye oh ye
we don't even have shovels anymore
there's nothing nothing at all I didn't
know you could go to a moon on day Zero
I thought you had to go to the company
if you're going to lose anyway might as
well what the hell is this what is this
water what the
qu he okay everyone Look
Away not water oh what the
[\h__\h] just climb around
it
yeah go to the can we go to this side
I'm already I'm already
over me too I am s over
hi
hi so
over where are you I already lost you
I'm just following I'm following it's
okay okay hi hi we lost the other two
they'll they'll make their way
surely
okay oh there it
is okay we Manion again
yeah but I think here it's always the
Mansion okay
nice yeah hi
hi always got to make sure you're still
close by cuz it can change so quickly in
an
instant that's
true well now we can't protect ourselves
what can we make it step step on the
land mine
somehow H kiata look behind
you there's a little
girl no there's no she's gone now there
was a bug I was looking at the bug you
were looking at a girl what about me I
thought he only have eyes from me oh my
God I'm
upstairs oh no hi oh my God foil head
oh my God I'm sorry
poo oh [\h__\h] me oh my God oh God oh I'm
going to die oh this is so bad oh my God
I'm going to
die
over it's
over oh
no blow him up the is everybody else
dead all together why does she oh my god
oh why does the light not work on him
where are you just kill me
now
[\h__\h] one
step oh my god did you guys see the
little girl from my POV I saw her in my
own it's in your head my God it's in my
head take your pills that was so evil
which did you guys die to coil head the
yeah the N Nom n n yeah they died to the
coil head oh the coil was funny all
right we were did you die before us um I
died outside cuz a dog ate me and
I should have climbed the rock with us
should have climbed it with us as you
have
not your performance has good work
everyone hide with you welcome to our
disciplinary get in the corner
to get in the
corner Among Us Among
Us
y hello hello
helloo
hello oh wa switch to Discord yeah
Discord bye-bye
game I closed game okay
that was fun actually yeah see you were
so worried that it was going to be not
fun and then look at you yeah well I I
think I would say we're Brave today it's
quite repetitive though it is a little
repetitive but that's why like uh the
the worst levels get like the the more
things that are kind of introduced but
it felt like we kind of had really bad
things right off the bat you
know yeah we we're a great team of
w
and it was really nice with this group I
like this group me
too w web also pretty we're so beautiful
like oh my God SL so true
besti thank you for wait wasn't it Pomo
who invited yeah thank you P thank you
pom yeah I'm glad that we could play I'm
glad that after you ended your stream
you were able to play for real know oh
yeah sorry I keep you seeing no that's
fine as long as you didn't have to leave
completely I'm happy yeah no I have fun
I had a lot of fun thank
you thank you girls I love you
girls oh my God oh my God oh my
God
worldwide
win winning w web girls
we girls yes oh why did you change your
picture because you're not playing the
game anymore but it's
weird it's cute that's my Discord icon
how could you say it yeah Le
cook oh okay I I'll consider it she's
gaming she's gaming
gaming
gaming what was I going to say I was
going to say something but I forgot God
remember
uh uh I'm
remembering uh [\h__\h] subscribe to the
worldwide web everyone yeah subscribe
subscribe and leave a like
and
yes everybody type type into your search
bar on your browser worldwide Wu web
winning.com
everybody don't
ww I'm going to buy that domain right
now
worldwide actually
winning I know I don't think so what
happens if I put it in connection failed
connection what does that mean we're not
real uh we're real we're real we're real
to me we just need to establish it you
know yeah yeah I think with this collap
we have established it yeah yeah
that was fun thank you girls I I I wish
you a a happy New Year
soon
Christmas and and I wish you much love
and um don't forget about the fun times
we had together the love that we shared
it's happening it's happening I don't
know like don't don't don't divorce me
okay I could never I wouldn't even dream
about
it never ever
ever we're the
wwww now mhm
W the quad W quad
W so many W I'm going to make food now
okay
okay thank you guys that was so much
fun thank you let's do this again some
time
L to everybody making
[Music]
out e now I'm freaking out e
e why you say e you're the one who
started too much K see bye bye by bye
everyone thank you bye thank you for the
M
bye okay uh thank you guys jail bir so
much we're going to be raing into my my
wife uh beu who is going to be streaming
very very soon in like 3 minutes so
thank you guys so much for joining I had
a good time and I hope you all did too
and I will see you all next time by
Darlings
[Music]
yeah sorry no zatu time I think I think
they they want to chat a little
afterwards so sorry sorry I want to talk
with the collaborators about the collab
see you guys next time
[Music]
bye-bye