e
e e
you're not excited enough K wait I have
the intro
music in
music it's very are you the intro music
I oh sorry no no sorry hi guys hi
hi
hello Disney
World oh my sorry everybody for the
delay but we made it we did not leave
Ena behind we could not go about Ena
thank
you never never
ever look at us beautiful cute girls
together on a Disney date today except
on good us screen apparently m is Steve
Steve n Steve what
happened did you not shave your
beard it's been a long week for
me I'm kind of
nervous mention all this Disney stuff it
sounds like we shouldn't be saying it
very odd ah no no we we may talk about
it I'm I'm sure it's fine um says here
use headphones for the best
experience uh well well today we are
visiting the Magic Kingdom with the
following
members from
[Music]
H from
and M from Whole Life English woohoo I
don't have an opening
hello oh hello and and and me
[Music]
um I think gooda yeah already before the
stream outed herself as a big nerd so
she will be our tour guide today I am
the Park tour guide because I know much
too much about the Disney World Park
that I should but I do mhmm this what do
you know you know everything I know that
this is pretty accurate I can tell you
that the monals are to the left the bat
transportation is Straight Ahead behind
us and then to the the other left is the
bus transportation to the on park
properties and hotels and then over here
is where you get your tickets and your
your hats and then they check your ID
and stuff like that and then this is
like this is concessions here you can
get a bunch of stuff that might be a
little expensive and then inside you get
strollers which is what I'll be pushed
in today
yeah I see okay I don't know where the
bathrooms are though good would you like
to tell us which Disney worldland this
is modeled after which place which
country this is this is Disney World
from Florida USA Orlando baby Florida
Florida
look yeah yeah Gator yeah who here has
been to this and which one and how often
M you start I went once when I was
smaller I don't remember much I just
remember the one with the boat like the
steamboat and it scared me the steam
boat scared you yeah the animatronics
scared me or that you know the guy
fishing there's a guy fishing and it's
terrified me terrifying fishing guy
understandable what about
in sorry my my uh stream is having a
little troubles but
um I haven't been to Disney World but
I've been to Disneyland once
oh Disney Disneyland
inia California California
oh uh I went several times in Japan to
Disney sea and Disneyland although I
prefer Disney sea and I went to the one
in Paris two10 but I never went to the
one in the
America so this will be my the first
time I see the OG the or is this the OG
right no this is not the OG but it is
the superior partk tell me it is the
superior one okay how is the superior G
tell me it's bigger it's more updated
but most importantly it's
bigger
oh nice okay I'm excited if G said so
then oh wait
um uh JMA the bgm that is playing on my
stream I knew you would be worried this
is from audio stock this is I know it
sounds like dis music but it is from
audio St always mine Disney
F just in case okay don't worry so shall
we get going let's
go could I lead us yes yes have a
problem oh [\h__\h] stream yeah stream's a
little little scuffed right now um oh no
Bedrock Edition so Bedrock might be a
bit
um bed Rocky kfp is it fine on my
side aren yeah in CS day give me one
second Mon and then the monre will take
you to the the ticket ticket station I
think it's called the transportation and
the ticket center for those of you that
uh don't stay in the Parks and then and
then I can actually tell you the
Montreal the Montreal track I know it it
goes okay go on it goes to the
Contemporary Resort next to the Bay Lake
Towers which is the Disney Vacation Club
memb only Hotel uh and then it
goes
wait I might be missing one but then I
believe it goes to the Grand Floridian
Resort and Spa uh with the wedding
Pavilion as well cuz I guess some people
get married in Disney and there's a
wedding Pavilion and then it goes to the
Disney's Polynesian Resort which is like
Hawaii and stuff like that I think I
might be missing one and then it goes to
the trans
and Ticket Center with continuing
service to Disney's oh God Hollywood
Studios I think
maybe oh no no no not Hollywood studio
sorry Epcot it's been a while oh okay
well good it's like you you used to have
like a part-time job as a tour guide in
Disney World actually the monreal the
Disney World monreal system has has the
please you know please stay seated and
stuff like that I used to have the
Spanish monologue memorized but no
longer have the Spanish monologue
memorized
but I can't fall I can't follow good
anymore you're so informative G do I
have to pay for you being here with us
no it's okay I'm
sorry no no please continue this is good
cuz like uh it will be will be an
informative stream like yeah they used
to sell the they used to sell the the
Spanish monologue on t-shirts as well so
I'm not that crazy it was like a fan
favorite to hear I don't know why but it
was yeah they have the instruction yeah
yeah yeah like
a stay ride yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah but
it's just for the transportation thing
also bus AC is the best
AC also there's food here we get to eat
the food in the park as well I remember
reading there's the we can eat the do
Whip and K was like what's a what's a
doip okay I sorry sorry for the I think
I might just not stream today oh really
really sorry yeah I can't fix the
internet damn it I'm sorry now that
you're so cursed today I'm sorry I can
try one last thing but um I I don't
know I'm so sorry no problem good will
entertain us with everything she knows
so a do whip which can get in the game a
do whip is uh it's like an ice cream
swirl it has vanilla ice cream and then
orange like sorb sherbet or you can get
like pineapple or something like that I
don't know it's one of those like cult
classic Disney snacks but quite honestly
I can't stand the taste of it I'm more
of a a churro person or perhaps a Mickey
waffle or perhaps a Mickey a Mickey ice
cream bar cuz it's the perfect
temperature and it's like cold enough to
bite into and it doesn't really melt
maybe it's chemicals I don't know I like
to believe it's the taste of magic in my
mouth while at the Disney World Resorts
what's the cow lip thing that you
mentioned before what something lip you
mentioned some whip lip dop do do lip
the do lip ice cream one it's the
orangey swirl it's like creamsicle
but too
yeah okay okay okay you know remember
how much
uh probably like eight bucks six to
eight bucks ice cream I think so yeah
well it is Disney it is Disney they also
have an egg roll cart I do like
cheeseburg egg rolls
yeah my stream we can go sorry about
that Yumm okay and oh by the way we can
get autographs in this book look this is
fascinating meet your favorite Disney
characters around the park I wonder if
we'll actually find some and then we
have the map here that we can always
look at but we don't need a map cuz we
have GL I'm the map I'm the map I'm the
map and we shall adopt Taco D in Good in
My Stream streaming please
just feel free you're welcome
everywhere take a seat and enjoy the
show where do we go first where do you
always go first good uh I usually start
I go to Tom Marland and I work my way
around that way because I like riding
the People Mover cuz it's like it's
essentially just it's actually really
cool hold on the People Mover The People
Mover it usually has a really long line
but it's really easy uh you go on an
escalator up and you sit in this like
it's just like an automated it goes on
like a track all the time and it goes
actually through other rides in the
Tomorrowland section like there's a
stitch ride and then there's the Space
Mountain which is one of the three
classic Mountain rides and you actually
go like underneath people while they're
riding the ride it just spins you around
a little bit it's pretty chill it's
really nice you can't eat on it though
but I really wish you
could Okay g okay do you have a script
or something with don't I just know too
much about
this I feel like I really uh did the
right choice like actually um I I was
the one who thought of uh doing this
collab and I was like okay who did I
invite and first I thought of Ena
because we had a little bit of a a Milky
Mouse Arc in Minecraft before and then I
was like okay who else likes Disney and
I just assumed G is a type to like
Disney so I invited G and for M yeah
also assumed you maybe like Disney so I
guess it was correct that assumption
yeah I'm just Sur with G surprised I I
expected everyone to like Disney but G
has so much information about the them
part yeah awesome I'm so surprised
I love it I love when people are
passionate about stuff go go go let go
go should we go in should we go in let
go okay I usually enter on the right
side I don't know
why why does the top the right side the
running icon is it showing for you guys
when you today and enter the world of
yesterday tomorrow and fantasy let's get
a
stroller really get
strollers I can't run this I'm why do
people get strollers do we have a baby
people baby seen people with strollers
they have a wheelchair is this who I
think it
is is this playing
music I turn music off I
thought I don't know if I is it note
maybe wait I have music off
though it might be not block can we walk
on something and might turn it turn test
I'll take it cuz I'm not streaming I'll
I'll check go forth M yeah go forth
Steve we are so scared of B the big big
b Hammer there's no more music wa there
is there there is go back go back back
go back backit
I turn off two boox and note box I don't
hear anything now is it sound as
well oh wait there is music yeah yeah go
back go back
Wen I don't think I hear music oh you
don't should I turn off sound
blocks you just in case I turn say no
copyright I don't know this music though
sound like Disney this must be fun
Dan World screw it we're going to live
life on the edge
[Music]
everybody where's where's come on over
here we need to
t
t guide we're I'm hungry I've been
running around so much need food need
food where's the food where
chos I hear music
oh what w what there's a character y
there's the the fairy Tinker Bell wa I
why she
R she SL my book oh my God sling my book
I never did that before when I was in
Disneyland Never B going to the
characters
y why
do I've never even seen one of these
characters before only in Paris wait do
you have do you guys have sound effects
turned off yeah I think I I have
everything turned off now where did you
go turn off
down here's my only the only knowledge
that I can Flex that GAA probably
doesn't have um is that apparently okay
so this this part may be good know
apparently every Park Disney park over
the world has like their own like
character that they use as a mascot and
for Paris it's Tinker Bell did you know
that g what what do you what Baris
Disneyland their their mascot is
Tinkerbell
I it like fly over the there go my only
Flex that I can
do I don't know apparently every park
has one is it Mickey Mouse the
Mas over the castle right think
over mascot that they kind of like push
forward oh my God can I get your
autograph are you an imagineer hello you
look like he just works here
OHV wait what's really sad oh you just
worked
here guys guys good is spaghetti dogs
yeah the spaghetti dog it's Tony's
Tavern you buy a spaghetti here actually
that's really where's the food then for
spaghetti dinner the
rest the guy has food the guy
has give
me yeah how do you order
food there Mickey Mouse ice
cream
Sor Mickey waffle you're taking all the
food lollipop I'm taking all the food
sorry
oh wait how do
you Chate everyone take some
good
pick pickles pick Garden salad salad is
good Fri chicken hot chocolate salad
gra delicious churro I love CH does fill
up that much that one the was good oh my
god
look art Mickey Mouse
how do you eat oh I'm full oh yeah I am
full too I I'll just call the
Cho people in in in American Disney
World actually run around with Pickles
in their hand yeah you can buy pickles
there yeah they're next to the power you
don't eat next to the Powerade yeah next
to like the iced beverages Powerade and
the disis the pickles pickles in a
bag what I mean I like pickles but I
wouldn't just eat them as a snack like
that in Disneyland what the hell must be
following there's like a b place there's
a b place and comes around here frash
Canon looks this is a fire station even
though I don't know if it really is a
fire station oh merchandise I don't
think you can go in but this is a
merchandise store
here
merchandise merch go get the merch
there's no merchandise oh maybe there
is see I
is can you buy anything wear it I
wonder oh cute oh my
gosh can I wear it yes you can I can
wear
it oh my God oh my God oh my God wait
this oh my God wait how do I do this
maybe now Steve looks better I hold
good I looks so good on
[Music]
you my
S that's so cute
girl hat
too what is there something for your
head oh you can wear a shirt M they have
M blue shirt yeah I got a there's a ear
ball like balloon maybe you can hold the
balloon you need to restock what the
[\h__\h] wait how do you put on the
backpack oh got a balloon oh
lollipop oh that's so cute oh momm
that's one it looks so cute on
you is so funny with
[Music]
the cute I'll take can we stand together
where are you how
do how do you hold you you're already
holding it just just hold it like so
cute where iside where is outside
outside is this outside I follow Kara
K's okay okay I found
it cool selfie selfie selfie where did
you not
go where are we looking the Castle's
right there okay this is perfect wait
which Castle this one this one this one
Castle it's the okay
sorry oh my go how does one take
screenshots in Bedrock is it just what
what was it I don't know it's
not F2
before well uh chat chat please take a
cute uh shot of us please thank you take
a screenshot I don't know how to
do
cute oh my God so cute oh it's so
cute thank F F12 I don't want to I don't
want to fall into any traps like that
closes my game yeah Bedrock I don't know
how Bedrock okay okay follow follow
candy that's a candy this is a candy
this is the main street
confectioner uh rumor has it that they
actually pump smells into the park and I
believe this is the culprit it always
smells like
delicious in the other shop there's
still backpacks if someone still wants
one oh here in this one in this one
where I am there's still backpacks like
two backpacks and sweaters and stuff let
me see well oh
maybe there personing stuff here let me
see oh oh there's even there's even more
stuff over on the right side if you go
back to the right that's a
cute Minnie Mouse Minnie Mouse backpack
no Stitch I will go stitch stitch I want
this
one
cute more stuff
[Music]
here I'm going to put these
back cute oh my God I need I need this
one I need this one balloon balloon
balloon
the balloons look crazy they look so
stiff they look like they look like
lollipops yeah like huge lollipops oh I
want to lick it this is fun I love this
this is almost as if we're actually in
Disney World oh oh wait there's somebody
else over here do you have more stuff
can you play Minecraft in VR because
then it would be even more immersive you
can really bed Minecraft in VR
I'm not sure if it's Bedrock but there's
more stuff here ah this is the same
stuff that we had
before
blue I like
yellow oh
cute cute you look cute of
course of course of
course cute let me see outfit let me see
how this let me see Ki everyone cute
pink the T ears those are so
cute and then we have Ena who is Mickey
Mouse cute with the tail hat looks like
she's German
[Music]
secretly tail did you see the tail tiny
tiny tail it's like an antenna
is Minnie Mouse them super cute
[Music]
hello this is
exciting okay okay what do we do next we
have we are dressed up we are absolutely
sty being in fashion I like the color
coordination for G as well with the blue
and the yellow blue and yellow perfect
works it works very well some Stitch
matches girl so
well yeah so cute let's go like a spirit
animal this is true but good what is
everybody's favorite uh Disney
character good question good question
yeah there's a Starbucks in here
somewhere I'm not sure I even have one
who are these people go this is the
quartet going to dance for us dance
dance oh they dancing they
[Music]
say you don't hear it I can't hear
anything I hav't they're not singing for
me yeah they're just Dancing Yeah they
dancing dancing what there they go the
Dapper dance yeah yeah yeah yeah Tipp
tap welcome to Disney
worlding about how cute we are I of
course I'm like 95% sure there's four of
them and four of us what do you think
that means it means on the next we're
going to replace them we're going to
I shall be orange I am orange this is
where you get a chili dog this is
called where did g
Goin she the child that you have to put
G
leash backpack where is where is it and
this is the ice cream Palace kid okay
either this is the chili dog and this is
the ice cream or this is the ice cream
and this is CH no chili dog ice cre
leash I found her come get the
noodle oh no you can get I've actually
never eaten there but there's noodles
over there and that's the Crystal Palace
that is a Disney character dining spot
Buffet I've never eaten there but I've
always wanted to I think it's really
hard to get
seating wow Disney why lit up right now
are there going to be fireworks can we
activate them I
wonder trash
wow it's
huge huge man this is actually accurate
cuz I recently updated the park to have
this additional walkway and stuff here
so this is
actually my good eyes
delays Crystal
Palace there might be characters in
there oh yeah we need autograph
what am I doing right now on your
[Music]
screen falling and falling and falling
how do I stop this help maybe try moving
forward maybe there's more food don't
try me uh what are
you have you tried stopping uhoh sorry U
I don't know you and this chat is called
a Kodak picture spot it usually means
something entertaining is happening I
don't want to leave the game right now
because May everybody's going to get
kicked out
oh my God my my eyes hurt my brain hurts
oh no I'm in the Twilight Zone how do I
stop how I stop is kod still a thing I'm
not really sure anymore uhoh I'm not
boing boing boing I I don't know how to
help you oh God oh God oh God uh I can't
push
you yeah there's no Friendly Fire we're
getting close to the egg roll card I can
smell it to go I want to go
yeah get
popcorn hey go here po here I was able
to
eat come a little bit I think hey hey
what happens if you guys jump into the
water I guess just back up yeah yeah so
some type of
glitch oh
no turn on friendly fireing
still land I'm trying to stop as well
but like I I can't stop we haven't even
got to the ride yet come on this is the
ride I'm on ride the ride this is not
the
ride one time I was standing here and I
saw a bullfrog swallow an entire french
fry entire French like an American
french fry like a you know that one big
O Adventure you know that one big french
fry you get yeah it swallowed that one
one big one if I leave the world I think
we get kicked out yeah we don't want
that doing I think you should though
you're stuck there
C safe and end and Happ maybe hide your
screen just in case hiding you're good
to go now hold on guys we're going to
yep
disconnect oh
[\h__\h] okay wait I'll go in again hold on
guys we we the world there's
teleport I'll go to the bathroom the
bathroom okay okay in the real the real
bathroom oh yeah I'll be right back
I'll maybe the Disney bathroom okay oh
I'm in the water okay try to join the
world again okay cuz my part is fixed or
I'll also send you just in
case
still yeah I still have them oh yeah I
think still has them nothing is lost
it's all
good sorry for the trouble that's okay
it's
[Music]
okay I am wow
it's welcome back sorry for the trouble
back what is is this a ride is it a
Crystal Palace buffet with Char or is
food it's food
found with character who are these wait
does that mean there's character here
apparently you can click on the map to
teleport so if you get stuck again car
you can
maybe you can click on the
map there's more food here guys
need take
that is this the first aid this might be
the first aid or where they put the
babies I don't really know
you know like want to deal with the
babies the
babies also you run by double pressing W
I just
learned I'm just using
Ctrl okay
[Music]
back where you want to
startland we go on Space
Mountain where is Space Mountain or M we
I think we should go to tomorrow land
first yeah this way I see your
balloon where come here we are together
we don't see
you are you with us I'm
here don't lose theour guide everybody
hold
[Music]
hands okay
s when I bounc the ears bounc do you see
that on your side really a yes I do I
think I do BL
BL also these are the bathrooms in the
park I don't know if that's important
but I'm just going to say the no Terrace
yay terce there's also a firework show
here but I think it's expensive they
it see this is where they sell the food
if I get annoying tell me to shut up and
we can uh no no no you're the perfect
perfect
gu or food I want chili cheese we have
so much food places in Disney yeah makes
me really hungry
man
oh chicken so
pretty they also used to have a a
garbage can that talk to you what what
yeah I would like move around and it
would I found
characters and does tomorrow have an
attraction Mike wasowski mikow
[Music]
please
sorry glazi that's not right who's gski
I thought it
wasowski so cool is it Mike Bowski or
Mike GL door I want to go in I want to
is this not
liced oh my gosh he's the silence
what his hand on his hip I'm so wait
even the W it says Mike W in here but
then his name is GL outski right there
but his his signature has a W for
wasowski yeah who are you little green
man is the real
one think you're doing something he's
dancing I you should take off your take
off your cost you fraud it's
wait what's your name
huh SP is it actually let me see your
zipper he's like he does not have
zippers is
real it's like four girls bullying The
Fluffy
Boy bully him tickle him tickle tickle
tickle tickle Mike actually Mike doesn't
have he would just be skin right he's
just made of skin scales or hair or
anything well just poke poke his eye
poke his
eye lizards like maybe little
scales okay oh is that an attraction
that looks fancy this is the thing I'm
spacing that flings you around there's
actually a ride to the
right let go want to go on the ride wait
is that Buzz Light it's buzz you see him
what did he just do
my oh my God
what hi look at his eyebrows
B sign my autograph please
big hand writing he's really short he's
tiny not stitch stitch is kind of stitch
has a belly hello so big and belly it
does have a belly
thanks
Buzz he's so tiny is he
good bully
bully wa nice
pose and
Beyond I can't wait for the new movie
coming it looked so good oh
yeah light here okay what's next can we
ride the
ride Space Rangers
manide
ride
Ranger oh wow it looks just like you
what the heck I'm so cute the one I did
recently in Paris and I was really good
at it the waiting room looks like it
too oh go
wait and oh only two people at once I
think yeah that makes
sense Okay girl okay I'm r with okay sh
we have to wait for it to end oh okay
well I was really good at this wait
where where are we shooting here this
thing wa where exactly are we shooting
is this one but you're in the way I hear
something
red right the red
or do you shoot do you shoot the oh you
have to
shoot zero it's we both still have zero
moly that's a lot of stuff I maybe we
start we start from here
maybe
see I wonder if it's going to take your
picture like the real ride
doop that be cool shoot shoot shoot
shoot shoot shoot
wow it's just like Disney I have to wait
yeah this is the waiting line oh the
wait you want pick for us oh a pickle
maybe we can make a pickle sandwich oh
yummy wait is this the same like other
Minecraft C I'm winning why am I in the
wallel out of the
way I can't see
I got to catch up that's a long
ride oh my goodness you are so far ahead
of me
yes there's actually secret places to
shoot I wonder if they still work in the
game I mean yeah is there yeah I us I
used to look them up before I rode the
rides the
plac think trying get on to my level you
can't be a Hol bird look at his nose
he's like
I have no I have no
hope in the waying I think it's ending
what is it I thought he was I thought he
was looking at from every
angle you still me but you don't really
kind of optical illusion where it's like
even when you move it looks like it's
looking at you it's say lifeless
lifeless one color eyes go
yeah this is fun
got his so sorry waiting right now or
what's happening we're waiting waiting
in we wait
[Music]
thingo what do you what you usually do
good at doing waiting times you must
have some extra techniques I pull out my
phone oh okay pH time I see oh
yeah that's like really the worst time
is the waiting time for me I hate it I
like looking at restaurant menus while I
wait and also other wait times I point
and laugh the longer wait that what that
the end yeah oh I we in
space sh the space so hard that's so
long sounds
like ride really crazy I'm excited to
see how accurate it is I'm excited
wait two hours for a three minute ride
it's the
Disney they're taking over I'm
destroying it wait so if you go to
Disneyland or with Disney World how many
rides do you ride in the one
day good question uh oh
stilling
F get on if it's all right if it's like
if I go with my family and it's like a I
like to do the single Rider line lanes
for like
[Music]
thatly and you with a random group of
people just get the getting a really
fall one I guess that is one Strat to
get get more
R yeah I mean you only
Str couple minutes it doesn't really
matter amazing I think it's ending for
real it's ending that is on the ride uh
the points are um
114 and 55k on M so I have like
double wow okay I think I think it's
that was most
enjoyable it
was where is the exit I'm just stand
lady here we can walk what happens I
don't want to try okay wait wa what's my
what's my rank do we have to wait for
the C to come all the way back around oh
my God
maybe wait wait it's the start now we're
both oh nice nice nice nice nice nice
y first
CL
pilot
how get your blaster
ni oh my God it's accurate is it
now we get
listen but the last part they didn't
have in Paris the the alien shooty
part oh my God it's kind of
accurate wait how do you shoot click
right button I mean left click click
left click right click for me or right
it was
left maybe that's why your points were
so low
was it supposed to be left click for me
it was right click maybe both Works wait
not yeah it's because in the beginning
there is nothing to shoot yet you think
it starts but there's nothing to shoot
yet has already got 62,000 points
what oh
no will carry me I can't shoot anything
is this accurate not really no I feel
like it was kind of to the I don't know
you have to
[Music]
it I'm going on the
rocket they very accurate M do you see
the the the
lip wow we should all go together on
this one
too M there's a flying thingy that you
can go get go on
I guess it doesn't want to work is the
Astro
Orbiter yes yes yes
yes move your head move your head
in I told you Chad I told
[Music]
you let's go what's happening get
up I'm
trying LIF wait LIF rocket
the maximum amount maybe we can wait
maybe we can together this
one this where to take a picture I think
I don't know who's
this maybe this is two people only as
well
oh let's ride
this oh no I'm going to get so motion oh
gosh I like these rides oh
you have the Dumbo one what is thise
but it's dark your
[Music]
SK oh my God this is
just this is like when the little space
guy comes how did they do this in
Minecraft that's crazy yeah space
Sho wait can we go up got
control how do this in Minecraft I know
right this is crazy Minecraft Tech
here I'm so
lost go first person nice doesn't
actually do anything time to points what
are you supposed to do I'm not sure hang
out and chilling oh I think I did
go
firsts wait what did you do I just oh
that's it I up and down up and down oh
what are you shooting let's wait for the
other girls I
guess let's go down, okaye byebye you
almost have a million this way like call
me
G oh I almost got
aa oh can't quite get a million so
sad oh you almost had a million I am
a what the [\h__\h] I am a cosmic Commando
or am I
wa how many oh wow almost 200,000 for
Ena oh okay so it's good Ena Ki
M
just a little bit too late
the target like far away at the top they
give you a [\h__\h] ton of points
like, I was trying to do the same ones
again I thought you were supposed to
spam it oh here they are where are you
guys H this is the Carousel of Progress
that has a lot of history behind it it's
really we just went on the on the space
orbit do you guys want to go too yeah is
it here here here elevator I don't think
I can go on it I'll close my eyes I'll
close my eyes you felt sick because of
it yeah elevator LIF oo how do we go in
I
miss oh oh here we are yes how many how
many can we
do robot
girls well together
look you can look up and down to control
your rocket oh it's just looking looking
oh
boy
[Music]
this I'm not
there to the
Moon uhoh I
F oh no but you're in the you're in
another
car
Lo
yeah it's amazing what's possible in
Minecraft but I mean obviously a lot of
work is behind honestly really impressed
yeah I mean this Disney after world that
we're talking
about
Disney wow a the sky is so beautiful
yeah this do is there
fireworks there should be we'll see
eventually there must be and the H but
there won't be a parade will there oh I
don't think probably no parade well
fireworks is
manageable how are you elevator I made
it how do you e in this game
who I think I wasn't supposed to do that
I was fun that was fun
next one next one go nice okay next one
what's next gura H next Space Mountain
baby our first roller coaster let's go
okay you know what's up and there's
bathrooms space Oh anyone need use
bathroom I do
bathrooms Space
Mountain oh cool cool flashing lights
and colors chat be War beware no problem
I want to turn on sound effects really
bad for these St Point wait you hav't
turned off I haven't turned everything
off I turned everything off
okay
cool okay I actually never did Space
Mountain before even in real life cuz
that was too much of a chicken but this
pretty cool already in the waiting room
so cool look Space Mountain is just kind
of old but then it adds to the thrill of
it cuz you're like is this going to
break oh no
or will I die will they get it on camera
oh should we go for Omega oh is this
a know oh there's oh how how you get
there you get there I don't know I think
this to
Jo it's only two it's only two only
three I'm in I'm in it's four it's four
four okay good wait is here here in the
front oh shoot the oh I got the best
seat in the
house
what going space where we going in
space wait what vehicle energized oh oh
we're going
up oh my goodness the
little that is so cool
we're going up oh there's even like
roller coaster like sound effects
they're upside down I don't hear any
should I turn them
on uh there's no music but I wouldn't I
don't I don't think there's no music The
Creator mode turned off the music that's
copyrighted
music there just roller coaster sounds
oh no it's dark it's completely dark I'm
scared
gling oh glitchy
oh oh wow
this for
me the back wait where's backward and
where's forwards also why is kir on I
don't know anymore I don't think I can
look
oh is anybody else just glitching
through space yeah I just see girl
glitching space experience exactly we're
just traveling real
fast wait how did I up in the back yeah
I'm in the front
now I wonder how they did all this
anybody he from K or is she
barfing I think I think she's barfing
wait are you on the ride
k no what out or I was on the ride
before everybody else and then everybody
jumped in and I got kicked
out what which is so ironic because a
few days ago on my stream I was like I
knew this is going to happen so I was
like I'm going to definitely be in there
first cuz I know it's going to be H
happening and I won't be the one getting
kicked out
but are you done already yeah done I'm
done I I I I tried going on the other
one but I don't know I I do I go into it
but it won't let me move maybe I now
that you're done maybe I can try try the
other one the Omega one but I want to
see it too where it the roller coaster
huh
yeah we went through
space you just you just went until it by
ride clicking no I think so we're going
to be brave we turning on just wait for
the timer okay ah okay okay okay okay
[Music]
c i I'm going to go on the ride now okay
you want somebody to ride it with you oh
wow that's it's okay I'm already the way
no you can do it it might last this it's
just you actually so it might be worth
it oh my god well I never I never had
the the guts to go on this one for real
so this is like a test run maybe one day
in real life I can ride it let's go
together do you have a merchandise for
me it's the same
merchandise as you already had where's
the exclusive merchandise why does it
take so long to get out of the r it's
part of the experience
and
caner chat is with me yay well we're
going up Chad I'm so scared I'm so
scared tell me when they're taking the
picture by the way I don't know where
they take the pictures and this is this
we're here space this is the Raceway
smell
of
diesel oh
like like a certain car where's front
and where's back I lost oh my
[Music]
God babies guys you good
think I think she's good Discord is
muting her I'm hearing a line of
wow
wow wow oh that's the ti the ti that's
the people M holy holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] I
can't imagine
how what so fast even in Minecraft oh my
God oh my God can you ride the People
Mover no maybe don't ride it without
me holy
[\h__\h] myy wo wo wo W wait can you wait
this not where we just were no okay I'm
done Astro orbit I'm
done oh you're going on a I'm coming
back oh it's just a
walkway a never mind it's just a big
walkway instead of riding on a car I
don't want to walk Disney
World have those things like they have
in airport like uh like you know those
little
cars people they have that um
was people missing child
missing um I don't
think please please uh please get to
this is where I saw incredible twerk he
waiting for
you I saw miss incredible twerk here
where is bunny
hello oh I see
you you know you the only one who tried
to find
me it happened yeah this really have
distracted right now with the twerking
who was it Mrs
Incredible what what's
incredible Mrs Incredible M I want see
what you're saying
no she's not actually doing it working
right now what what what are we looking
at I see
anyone oh you are let's keep going whoa
all
right
where I can't see your head's in the
way let's keep
going okay wow there's a lot to do in
here well that will be a clip
[Music]
well you see I watched I watched the P
stream of this Disney adventure and I I
thought I was prepared but I was not our
traitor the trees even look the same
that's so cool they look like blocks
they're Ling to Minecraft you
right is this the I love that one
way me too
okay
yeah let's
[Music]
go how you press
W interact with the wheel to speed off
smells smells just like Mario
Kart oh Mario Kart so cool though
imagine if you can do this in the like
Minecraft please make it
possible I'm catching I'm cing inner
Corner maybe if you have a resource pack
full horse to make it into a car may
maybe watch me drift this
[Music]
corner SMS you don't want to be in the
T oh who has to ride the teac
DFT oh
I
again is that the right it might not be
I think we
went wa what
oh okay oh
here cute that so fun so cool I love
that that is that is not quite accurate
though cuz it get it's way more
controlled in real life you
really how do I get off the red
yeah okay okay fun I like this
one what coffee tea
Burger coffee coffe I need some coffee
[Music]
your only visitors are here attend to us
now what do you some hot I to eat my
stuff I hav't anything yet L my my teeth
on that
one hot wait should we do
teacups or no te now that everybody's
eat this way
yes going on a spin ride is not a good
idea it's the best idea what do you mean
are you sure there might be some
projectiles children
attractions one time uh I got my body
stuck in the the gate here oh no
yeah here it is I was trying to slip in
between and I accidentally got my body
stuck peacock I want the pink one I want
the pink one oh can we all get blue oh
we got to get
in the wheel
[Music]
spin
faster oh God oh God I'm so
[Music]
Dy oh God this is actually kind of
like I can feel I can feel my
lunch chat are you enjoying this view I
feel my lch just to keep looking down do
[Music]
this actually kind of makes me sick it's
perfect I'm
soy oh god oh I my
head these games have it's over no let
me it's over okay it's over oh thank
goodness are you are you girls good is
everyone fine
how's my head's kind of yeah my head
isting it's like the real thing oh feel
like real thing would make me less sick
than yeah I think it's the U minecraft
like honestly I did not expect so many
different attractions to actually
be
playable interactive So Co who is you an
animatronic he's actually much scarier
in person but he plays piano what does
he do he's like he's like a like hello
ladies and gentlemen eat your Che
[Music]
bger well where do you guys want to go
now should what's next what's next you
we are asking no where should we go
fancy Land This Way fantasy land okay it
used to be oh she's already so far ahead
oh my goodness they updated this is
actually accurate it's it's accurate
it's historically accurate this is
actually scary spooky Adventure now o oh
oh can you ride this one it's a roller
coaster also I hear music oh we must
ride it music I don't hear music how do
you not hear music wait hold on what do
you have turned off I turned everything
off this is the Dumbo I was thinking
over change
theic remember though
wait I leave ambiant environment maybe
that's
different dangerous game you play but
[Music]
I want to be
Mis this used to be this used to be
Toontown and then
we
Ani B surface I've never I don't know
I've never seen that one before I want
to get
banned want
Dumbo I want to ride
Dumbo oh my God I found [\h__\h]
can someone do a goofy impression come
onina where's
goofy what he's he got is he a mouse CU
he got Mouse hairs is Goofy a mouse or
was a dog dog is a dog a gar wait where
are you guys g girl where's goofy
pleasey here here here where is riding
dumball already here no we're not riding
dumbbell
here
goofy
goof Chad
you
thank your
autograph let's find the
secret oh cute I feel like every
impression I do just sounds like
wait we can ride the roller coaster
course oh wait wait for me where where
at goofy you can I don't want to ride
Dumbo I want to ride the snow the Dumbo
fish dumo is Dumbo too childish for you
or what yes Dumbo the flying yes I'm
going to go check the way time I'll be
right
back okay I'm
Dum dumble Big Ear dumble Dum
so
theast oh he's over here wait we went
the wrong this is not oh there we go
here she
is oh no why poo look so smug actually
I'll go I'll go I'll go we'll go we'll
go watch the we'll go watch them on the
ride and we'll eat snacks fun fun
at oh it doesn't move when
watch M take piure of me mama mom get
the camera it's moving cute get the
[Music]
camera if you don't eat in Disney do you
die will I die if I don't eat what I
don't know I was wondering
yeah Mama I'm going so
[Music]
[Applause]
fast wow so
cute sound
I hey every look at me I'm
flying I'm Mama it's already
over oh that was so cool mama did you
see that now it's time to ride don't
know who I'm talking to
coaster big coaster for big children
right big children that totally are tall
enough to ride the ride we are totally
tall and totally don't get told to wait
outside I am this
tall we're all the same Hi here's
F I think G might be too small for the
ride no no I am tall enough do I need to
bring out the measuring tape I think
it's 136 CM or is it 140 is it
136 white there's
white the
[Music]
Poo thank you does it look
like if you need some apples you can
come to myass
White
my got P's autograph Winnie P who's
thank you
it's it's no white German I think so
yeah I got so I guess she doesn't need
to come to my German class autograph
dude
nice wait what's this place like the
woods is this 100 Acre Woods no it's the
Snow White ride it's this way this way
this way this way this way I like how in
oh yeah I like how in this this world we
can jump over fences can we implement we
still do that in real
life yeah but I want to do it in Java
Minecraft pleas oh Java this right has a
lot of stuff you can touch intera seven
dwares mind
train train for
Minecraft get on the ride this yo I'm in
I'm in I'm in oh why can I not get in oh
my to don't make
me two no wait it's not two
wait okay okay
okay I I guess we wait I guess we're
going first have fun what we do we just
just now we get
to never did this one in real life
either I this one's
fun I like how how the chain like shakes
it's up to date you can tell because the
lap the lap B thing lap belt doesn't
shake when you put it down oh
the oh my God the glitching oh it hurts
oh my eyes that both of the girls who
got in are not streaming yeah oh no now
we wait
um they're
mining they're mining I think this ride
caught on fire a little while ride where
you just so cool what oh thank God it's
Shin shine bright like a
gems Diamond I yeah Diamond
P one of them is sleeping that's
me this is just like real Disney K when
you did you hear that KF did you hear
the
[Music]
sticky how do they do
this wow that's crazy oh it's so
cute this is the awkward time where
we're Wai in line um
where do you want to least i' got some
food that's good eat some food and I
have a cold ass cheeseburger from like
an hour ago
o yummy I have a hot dog are we going to
the forest now stinky change my now my
keyboard indeed needs some
cleaning
huh the glitching is just there's a lot
of out of
the see nothing it's butter what's in
the Sky What's
there not diziness is in the sky let me
tou what we mean we touch the diamonds I
think they're coming back it's so white
on the right hurry
up put the js on they're dancing could
have several rides go on at the same
time that would have been smart says
Karin that would have she what was that
one's name
Dopey you think I can entertain my child
for hours while waiting in line
this not tolerable they mag really
really really loud and
inactive hi look it
shakes oh there we go just like me it
does beware it's going to give you a uh
not so good feeling us
us go let's go let me on the
ride get out here get out of
here I
am we to the bathroom okay go
ahead
line here we go
we're in we're in there are more
bathrooms here I like oh God the speed
is like
anime is this the B is it really
this think it was a roller coaster it is
a roller coaster oh
fun oh cute this is really pretty it's
like a like a medium oh medium roller
coaster oh this speed lines the anime
speed lines it's
likeo the camera move along this is kind
of better is it what's
better is that a
Reindeer shiny hi ho hi
ho the St [\h__\h] bird view is better
kind of this is pretty
grumpy Dopey doof and Doc you know all
their names yeah and yeah so this is the
new cave update huh caves and CLI that's
dark oh cute the clock is somebody said
shoot at them no no this is not a
shooting
game don't kill the dwarves man you're
supposed to sing with them HiHo
sh sh sh sh sh sh oh now we're going
into a
forest
it's that I was looking for smile cuz
it's where you take picture
Che don't don't don't don't we cannot we
[Music]
cannot I'm going to be honest at roller
coaster I'm the type to First scream
very loudly for 5 seconds then be so
panicked that I stop screaming lose my
voice look down close my eyes and become
a
baby I'm not able to look at what's
happening around me oh so that's what
happened to me one time what
oh are we done who's she dancing with
who's this the dwares oh cute tit TI
it's like her harm that's a d goe a
dwarf they're riding like like like you
know a dwar what if he have a head
around his waist as
well Apple witch the wiky
Witch what what Chad what the Wy Wy
witch what I
say what we're
done cute I like this one it wasn't that
area Space
Mountain so it's on my level I can
handle
this where are the other girls oh I took
momy to the
bathroom right here we
are we are put our service in the
T
careful careful careful
[Music]
and I get the gray stuff where's that
gray a bird white has a bird it came out
of her butt give me that gr poop on it
comes out of her butt I'm not kidding
what the bird this bird comes out of you
know watch I'll do it there she does she
oh my God does wait where are you oh did
they find cast member with white we're
back with Snow White yeah where I Snow
White
yes I see you guys we on the way what
comes out of her butt a
bird okay skip the whole egg part oh my
god oh
cute what else is under her skirt show
usn
white how did we not see this before
didn't we touch her before I don't think
we might have been just looking from the
front the
back comes out of your butt
huh
hyy I think it's from his oh no it's
from his
side why
is else it be yes what else would it be
well we need the okay where are we going
next tiny oh there's a bee there you be
did you guys know Bears can make juice
what huh um what kind of
juice m whatever whatever whatever one
the Poo
has that's honey that's honey what said
it's not
honey where are we going where we going
what we're following the Goa the
uncontrollable and Ela oh my
God everybody ignores the other cat
members when there's oh
my you sign my book I want to call you
Sven but I don't think that's right here
sign my book I think sven's the uh the
that's the reindeer the reindeer yeah oh
iot his name Christof of course Better
Than People the snow goes white on the
mountain tonight nice
[Music]
El where's Sven yeah
where's they not make a where
Olaf
[Music]
stand oh Prince Charming's Regal
Carousel oh is it the the the am go
around here yeah go around is that is
that oh your
is it
Rapunzel my bad ma'am you're
blond what happened with your
knowledge where's the long braid huh
andil I think better than try to find
though hope it's
her knowledge and that's where it
ends oh thank you penio Village this is
where you get a really big cinnamon bu
bu not in
game far was the same in every store but
there's a
choice Yum Yum Yum Yum is it here maybe
it's it might actually be in another
Brown
building what's what the fck the gr Stu
yeah good question the gray St failed
food it's yummy maybe it's in there that
you get the I think it's there
wait is there like a food guide for
Disney
World a food guide perhaps probably
maybe even like even if it's just fanade
they it probably exists I think this is
where you some Instagram that's about
hello sir Disney food
hello oh
[Music]
yeah I forgot your name
g
g Ariel's in her Grotle let me in how do
we get to Ariel Ariel
ell
arel what run run run run
[Music]
run of you so
pretty gorgeous oh my God maybe she'll
give us
kiss tails it's time for a pickle wait I
can look if you fall in the water it
makes you get out see you're not allowed
to die here can't have any drowning in
Disney can't have any anymore I want I
want to swim is there something there in
attraction or what I don't know I guess
no they can find another ride mhm how
yeah there's been so
many Let's see we have that we have that
what is
this Prince Charming the Regal
Carousel what do we have here we getting
ready to go into that part oh Liberty
Square nap time
liare has it has it ever been daytime I
feel like it's been night time it's been
daytime okay
turn Disney 5 days here in Disney
World just how have you guys ever did
like more than one day in a row Disney
cuz I've always only been like one
day have like him
yes a corn
dog oh
[Music]
oh you got a cute butt cute boat cute
everything they're
together man those Idol autograph even
like each other I don't remember I feel
like they always fight yeah of course I
do what the hell is going on here though
what what is Donald Duck doing in the
light uh in the
ceiling don't know is he stuck can we
help him I think he's eat that one of
the actions one of your he's being
mangled by this propeller Peter Pan
Peter
P
dances she just wave we should have done
it with Ariel damn it
Peter you
okay what is that Flex oh
my think he's so cool there an
attraction here pean pan flights I did
this one before do it let's
go okay I'm in for sure no one's taking
this away from me I see okay it's only
out of time is it two okay maybe it
should be one
streamer how many people okay well it's
two streamers it's okay can I follow you
into the what happen can we just walk
through yeah I kind want to see what
happens if you walk through it yeah
let's walk through you can I tried that
but it blocks you from going in in
different
attractions oh we can't go in no that's
so
fancy fancy ship
[Music]
hello oh
well and n f d off we go oh they talk to
us off we go wow look at that
City oh wow that's so cool another
another attraction yeah m f where
something else over here is it England
it's is it London Chicago Ben I don't
know but there's some sort of water
right here no [\h__\h] way good ass you
can't convince me on that one is exit no
no no no trust me that's it's a small
world is this it's it moves oh that's so
cool probably wait right we try it well
we can can tell me that that is Mars and
not the moon no think oh we can cross
over here wait why is it so
dark oh I pirat we're in the universe
oh okay wait no no no oh wait wait
please please please oh countown
interrupt wow wow
fire with the volcano looks pretty I see
oopsie what
[Music]
the music
here we go look up look up I can fly fly
fly fly fly ex wait which one is this
one is it oh mermaid hello o
hello world of lter a world of fear well
they're
stinging I guess that turned it off but
maybe they're singing I didn't turn it
off though oh maybe it's cuz it's
copyrighted look great
oh this is oh
it's don't jump don't jump lady don't
jump
no Pirates are taking over now I've got
you got you Peter Peter Peter
Parker I just it's okay I don't
understand how they make these M mhm
like where's is it how they do that
there's an alligator somewhere TI to
like level Tinker
bellai know she's shaking please let her
live no oh there's the
alligator oh my God he's going to eat
after all oh he's standing on his mouth
I guess yeah he's going to get eat I
feel like it
be that's cute I don't know you can you
can do now if you want to we're done
here um we're on a different ride I
don't know what which one it is it's
like right across
from It's a small world
after
it's cheer it's a world
[Music]
how you get in here oh like this in and
then you can go go go up it's incredibly
slow but I'm enjoying it the right are
we on the wrong side oh it's even the
lady that you wave at hello ma'am right
up the stairs up the stairs up the
stairs I feel like this ride wouldn't be
very cool though without the sound
effects no I it's just silent it looks
nice though you don't have to ride it it
had the music it'd be way nicer what is
there is there any more roller coasters
left that we didn't do I think so let me
see the map let's see there should
be number seven Italian Italian
however th there's a roller coaster
there's Haunted
Mansion oo there's p a cariban ride
yes that's kind of like a roller coaster
to do damn is is there Splash Mountain I
want to no it doesn't seem to be here D
okay wait this ride is actually so long
no really slow really
long yeah wow you guys are over there
maybe K and I will go explore a little
bit more yeah this going take a bit go
ahead go
ahead I hope that's there's no way to
stop anyway we're in asan I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry oh I see Japan
no no problem
dadap that's pretty we see your we see
your cousins is this supposed to be like
sharks I think this like all around the
world
cousin yeah do you want to do the hunted
Mansion K are you scared are you scared
is this going to be Outlast
2.0
oh oh I wish I could hear the audio
scary I've been in haunted haunted
haunted mansion Disney Land Before
flying carpet I'm
prepared right or left I think you go
straight this way oh no no you don't go
this way why would they put this here I
go through every
continent it's in case the the line gets
any
longer is this the way in I think we've
been
scary goes cre
and and strange and frightening
sounds look at the hippo EO for the
house there's monkey noises whenever C
clicker where the air is defly still why
is this partl the rest is German that is
the time when ghosts are present
practicing their Terror with goulish
delight
oh we can move
on oh this is where the gets taller
right welcome foolish
Mortals monkey monkey on I am your host
your ghost
host next to you my
goodness there's a penguin P finally
step all the way in make room for
everybody there's no turning back
elepant I'm scared y I'm shaking this is
so s our tour begins here in gallery
where you see paintings of some of our
guests as they appeared in the
corruptible look at me oh it's moving
it's moving
H wait uh
we
metamorphosis is this room haunted room
actually stretchy it is it is it is or
is it your
imagination no it's really happening
where are we now
this no windows and no
doors which offers you this chilling
challenge to find a way
out really was that was that a thing I
think they just opened the door for me
eventually there's always my way
Birds
mommy oh there's light oh oh there's a
way where there's a will there's a way
oh I know I can ride something oh yeah
ride brother my
brother brothers the birds are my
brothers M and Ena aren't in a totally
different world right now sry yeah we're
we're we're traveling around the world
it's great Hawaii oh my God we about to
be in Hawaii you oped out of
thank
[Music]
you this is really well made real
thing you guys want to go on the one
there's a lot of no song but the details
really not pull down to safety
Park they will lower for
us it's just burp
M did I you eat some something was like
oh yeah I was eating on the right and
leg decid watch your children okay I'll
be watching is everything on fire this R
Library does look like it's on
fire only ghost stories oh they're
dancing around how they okay that makes
more sense I thought they were just
thought they were
99 happy
hunts what shadow is
that this this is really creepy without
the music it's just there surf
sound yeah I have I have Jazzy music on
so it's not quite the right
atmosphere they all seem to have trouble
getting for realy oh my God
monkey
koalas oh they're
koalas oh in Australia
oh oh no they're Bears no they're oh
this is key bird look to the right
delightfully unlivable here in this
ghostly Retreat every room has wall
toall creeps oh creepers everywhere
don't explode please and hot and cold
running chills sh listen what what what
I don't hear anything this the North
Pole the North Pole you hear something I
don't see s ears I don't like sitting on
the edge of the ride I feel like
somebody's going to grab me I want to
sit in the middle turn us around turn
this around
ooh I hear creaky sound oh who's trying
to get out of this the are really nice
though I like
it where's that sound it's
snowing what it's snowing over there
yeah how the hell is it snowing over
there we're still in the small world
right that we still in the small world
right small we might be we might be done
at the same time hey
I got stuck here once for like half an
hour oh
yeah
here somebody stood up and would sit
down or something
yeah the spirits wherever they're at oh
my they oh my God it's a floating
Bubblehead they made you look very
minecrafty small is relative
yeah it's not a small world
world is very big aw can the sper your
tambourine is that chicken is that
chicken under the shadow chicken it's a
c cre and CES toads in a
pond Let There Be music from regions
Beyond oh my God whoever made this is a
Disney nerd there it is the Hidden
Mickey plate what the heck I mean Disney
made it probably
that's such a weird detail though oh wow
which detail you see on the table do you
see the plates on the table yeah one set
of plates is in the shape of Mickey
Mouse's
hand
a it's going to take another minutes to
be
before material
oh here comes the bride oh the her oan
is gorgeous she has beautiful lips she
killed her husband different God his
head
off like the end but it might take us
five minutes to get through the end oh
yeah that's
true we'll be around the same time
hopefully till death Us Part ironic
is I can read
[Music]
that by your
side oh they sing
thaton
soci wear
[Applause]
[Music]
will never be able to sleep again it's
like I'm really
there are
they surprised to know these songs by
heart all of them damn the haunted house
I don't know where the haunted houses
oh another archival kiaha to
disappear it's a
hitch
oh don't know he's got a he's got a P
nose
but look like Donkey Kong oh we going to
see ghost in here oh yeah not in the
seat though it's me it's behind us I'm
not even here it's none of us I think
we're how big can this map be
right
eventually is
that are are you
good oh no be sure to bring be sure to
bring your death certificate what death
certificate cuz there's 999 happy hauns
and there's room for one more here it is
oh that could be should we wait for them
do you want to do you want to go
actually do you guys know by the way I
think know how I mentioned that somebody
scattered ashes in the Disney parks
actually ashes were scattered in the
Haunted Mansion ride oh my
God actually sense we done we see your
names is a berry
pish we should probably uh not separate
not separate
anymore cuz that was a we a lot longer
than I thought
yeah okay what's
next roller coaster roller coaster W uh
roller coaster please roller coaster
let's see the map let's see the map all
right we are here there is
11 does it show it's a small okay we're
passing that one you guys did that one
you guys suffer through that one uh yeah
the riverbat sounds pretty l honestly
what else do we have oh that scared me
as a the
caraban yeah let's do that one yes
number five wait we can teleport
right oh I think so I think you click on
which number number
five number five try I can't even see it
that well can I like zoom in if you zoom
in and there's like a little way Mark I
can click teleport oh ah
may there's Aladdin ah wait where where
is where is where is the pirate thingy
bottom bottom
left I got Aladdin
all well guess I guess we have to walk
no you can
teleport you have to click on the guy
yeah pretty close oh God this is
actually like one of nightmares I had
one time like imagine you're on a Disney
dark ride and then everybody disappeared
and just stuck on the Dark Ride Like
even at night hello
Aladin I
like I'm
here all
Pirates this way I
know
[Music]
he weing we're losing her again
it two people ride again two people a
long line wait I have special music for
this interact with part the Caribbean
let me in let me in let me
in we're really far behind I think this
is how many people can do this actually
is this a four person oh it is four
people maybe maybe maybe monkey oh y we
here y let's go
nice oh it hasn't been that long since
the last time I was on this one just uh
I think oh when did I go
in when did I go I see the ship over
there
this is the gang's all
[Music]
here this is my music playing don't
worry about
[Music]
it that's what's up
ahead it's like small world again
slightly fast
you PPS
from dead man tell no tale yes not tell
us I I should tell tails that are not
told yeah please narrate
narrate dead dead men hell no tail okay
well you're going to tell us one anyway
aren't you
man
[Music]
that
o this
[Music]
SK properly warned you so accurate
that's so crazy who knows when that evil
curse will strike
[Music]
the Davey Jones
no are you laughing
oh it's dark oh no it's the
drop it's so dark I don't know if we're
even moving it's dropping
screen I think we are doesn't work so
well in Minecraft when it's so
dark is Dr
it oh no we're not
droing
W oh the sound effects the war yeah I
want ha the good thing about you guys
not streaming you can enjoy it to its
fullest go down jump into the long save
[Music]
yourself fire the Cannons boom boom
there they are the part I can smell the
water I also I also
like smell
delicious well that Christmas surprise
everybody TI be brave Carlos don't
listen
to the fromer tell him
col what are you doing
wait did they put did they Minecraft toy
uh Johnny Depp for this oh he be better
he should be he should be in the ride
somewhere did they get permission for
his likess I think very much at the
end I remember him
being for
10 take a take
a take
it wow that's really really updated oo
they look better than the Minecraft
Simpkins and they look better than the
Minecraft
goats and the
Goos the
GH e why does she look so
modern I I'll buy look how cute
it drunk man is he drunk oh no so
this look no no it is a bottle no I
don't know what this is ke I think it's
a key it's a key wow they even have the
little things going
onot I hear chicken quel lots of
chicken all the all the women chasing
after their men of their broomsticks
everything's on fire what's going on oh
no oh no oh no they started a fire today
they scam
Sparks is the ha guy in this G look at
those cats
why they have green
eyes
alien and they look kind of
[Music]
freaky I don't know how the song goes
the dou was so
cute yo yo ho
oh my
God me they have hat
guys a lot of hats out he's like you oh
[Music]
I the Hat
art I think why is that man hugging a
pig oh foot guy too oh
sorry it did you miss the touch his foot
I used to like to look up in his pant
light cuz you can see the electronic
parts of his animatronic like that don't
do like that he's the one showing his
ankles the gole has the key
do they have
[Music]
offerings there he is
there I got a
bad
Minecraft I can't see
your I can't
see
cute I'm sorry what if I abandon ship
can I do that
I got kicked out you can change seats so
what what is going on why you changing
the seat so everybody gets a good
view if you if you try to get out of the
boat then it changes the
seat every can see yeah shake it up
shake it up oh thank you all right good
front front row now but it's kind of
late for that thank you though I got to
see your what that was
cute was that it oh that's it
[Music]
wait I somebody how oh there oh
cool damn impressive stuff really oh and
the goods store of
course the goodies M now already want to
go okay
okay we we can still go on more
attractions
so goomo is she buying merchandise no no
no I'm here there's a jungle cruise
there's Big Thunder that's a that's a
real R roller coaster I want one Thunder
number
seven seven number seven I'll try no
that's not it wait wait wait wait wait
where's number seven let's turn this up
ah Park music you heard me not really
anywhere to teleport there so we just
walk there yeah I think we can walk it's
like to the
right run away from the copyrighted
[Music]
music which way do we go this way oh no
I think it's this
way they used to S really good french
fries here used to not no more this my
God they have the freaking the freaking
french fry
stand story Girl
Bill b give me some n oh my gosh she
okay we got Jessie down excited what'
you
find tacos
tacos it's Cowboy land we got the
country
be we got
the wait you saw that go oh there you
are I'm right here okay okay I guess she
walked instead of teleporting yeah they
got one of them
quarters quarters
things shooting Gall
where there's a snake in my boot there's
a snake in
my
[Music]
I I like it that
much is that shooter FPS no no no
no another diamond where where did we
want to go where did we to go way we
want to go to the
oh okay roller
[Music]
coaster country bear what's what what's
happening in country bear
jambourine
uh it's like a musical show with
animals okay okay I see oh oh
Tiana hello oh she's pretty she like a
wding dress oh wait that's actually
because they're changing Splash Mountain
from Splash Mountain into something
that's themed after Tiana and Tiana's
movie so that's
actually that actually makes
sense she's like a spoiler I got 22 out
of 28 how much do you guys
have yeah we're pretty close to getting
all of
them it's time for
the let's go th how do we get up here
though
this
climb let's become mountain climbers is
this the we got a
shortcut oh is
this where's the oh there she is hello
we want to do it we want to do it on the
wrong side oh how did we get here the
exit we have to
go up the entrance should be here ah
okay this way oh [\h__\h] I need to eat my
burger oh
oh no it's not this is the exit what the
I made a
mistake wrong
okay how
do confusing oh that look just like the
real thing that's so cool fling Ling
colors this so again that that we went
there before
wait had to get there get
there uh you uh you go you go out the
front go out and then uh go wa don't go
yet around no I won't you have to go up
the
front the front maybe here no is it here
is it this way this seems like it it
looks like a
line it looks like a lineup line I'm out
of food too we got to go get some new
food after
this I need popcor bgm is loud I was
trying to drown out the oh my God the
light is so
long
oh I found it hello I want a short
please she jumped over the fences maybe
I entered through a different fence way
oh it's going to tell me we're going
through the full length no problem I
would pull up banjo music but if I Tab
out it's going to we have
arriv enina is coming too there she
is okay I think this is two oh it's
four players okay
good nice we got the front usually yeah
the line is really long I think oh me
and good in the front seat let's go
let's freaking go we
coaster hurt L to look at if you're like
third person view oh
gosh wow ghost bats or what is that oh
my God they got the loud
part it's so
loud oh my
God drilling or what this part is so
freaking
loud they actually put it
it we getting wet here
[Music]
oh my goodness where the mess w w w w w
I can't look my
head
[Music]
co
sorry we're going up again no no more I
can't take no more more I can't take
this
anymore lunch everybody let go of the
lap belt put your hands up I've already
letting go I'm already pting them
up actually have a hand up post that
work wow wow wow wow
glitch oh it's this part I'm so dizzy oh
my God okay
oh my God girl from the back your ears
are like
flapping so
cute like even in real life I'm really
hungry right now I am too f i a big hot
dog a big Boer big big chili dog I have
some chili con car without chili in my
fridge girl wait how do you make chili
con Carney without
chili you don't need chili for chili con
Carney that's like having a hamburger
without the burger is just a bln with
cheese
and you cheeseburger without the cheese
exactly at that point is just Burger I
mean I me put that's a burger is there
me than it carness and chili
there is meat though right cuz otherwise
you can't even call and then there's
beans and then there's corn and then
there's bell pepper so everything but
it's just not spicy uhhuh oh hello we're
done yeah yeah that's
fun there's so much to do oh this is
like the real thing I feel like we'll be
here for hours and hours yeah I we we
should sleep in one of the Disney hotels
wish they have that here go kind of soon
cuz I have to take my animal out okay
should we do one more ride problem I
mean we can maybe do one more ride yeah
sure but you guys if you guys want to
keep going you can I just I can't stay
much longer think it would be a good
timing good us let I'm still here I'm
looking at the
map what would be a good last attraction
we didn't go inside the castle by the
way the castle and we didn't see the can
we activate the fireworks let's do that
let's do that let's do that let's do
that I think that's a good way to end it
yeah maybe if we go to the to the castle
maybe there's something to activate it
yeah let's go let's go that'll be a
nice or is that Alice Alice wait who is
this who the hell that's just a cast
member no is it all right wait we'll
find out oh God no don't go to
Tom don't go
oh never
mind Tom Sawyer y
like I don't think I ever went to that
Island just need to go to the center and
activate fireworks okay would be nice if
it was night time though does someone
know how to make it night time in
creative mode chat I don't know how to
do that think so what do you girls know
there's Jessie
oh me too me too I'm real real life
ending maybe is there some food where's
the
shop pickle there might be someone in
the Diamond Horseshoe get out of my
face man poor guy I need hold on he
might have enjoyed that I
need oh this looks
guy yes m what we go for this time what
did I not have yet popcorn
spetti whip I thought you were saying d
d lip or lip like someone's lips okay
now I know what you were
saying now I get it okay I think I know
how to set it if it works okay let's go
see fireworks oh fireworks it's not
enabled in this world it says so I don't
think I can knew it
what what is not enabled uh setting the
time custom time oh w w w to make it
dark might just have to wait a little
bit maybe yeah oh this like h
of the best ride to take a
nap oh the sh this is the Sleepy Hol
where you get really yummy fried
bread custom umbrella yeah
what's pretty we should build this and
know we should build a castle a Holo
life Castle interact with cast to start
firework wait till
night
music
wait his name is different there's also
a random man oh
oh
min oh should we not
yet not yet not yet let's wait a little
bit okay oh but we're only we not have
already I guess I
was right okay
pl we don't need
him Minnie you go Minnie Hi Minnie is so
small
she's tell
me what's I don't know what that is I
don't know that is look at it know this
is time
automatically
starting go
go where are you come to the middle here
oh hi oh yeah take a take a screenshot
guys take a screenshot hello wow
there you go where are you facing that
way hello wow
wow dreams do come true we do Disney
together happy
beautiful that's it happy New
Year but wait there's more oh wow these
look really
good yeah W oh that was Big
W look I don't have my sound on so I
need to make sound
effects there's a big
one accurac or what about this I don't
know
[Music]
that was the big end was it no there's
still more oh not there's
more I do like the Disney opening when
with the S like
[Music]
oh miss that
one the aim wrong
oh the trumpets oh that's
big who that's where everybody goes like
w wow someone making videos with his
Nintendo
[Music]
DS what a what happened to me last time
in Disneyland someone was taking videos
of his Nintendo DS
yeah you can do
that I mean it was one of the newer
Generations I think I didn't know can do
that appar quite video thing
right you you can take pictures or
videos
of I'm
taking oh
wow
know oh my gosh it's just never ending
oh it keeps going well this has been
really fun though I want to say that
it's been really yeah thanks for than
for the
guide no better guide than you sorry I
just kind of ran around making monkey
noises no no you're very informative
perfect you guys want to take a picture
like like like facing this way oh this
way this way I miss the
finale um if you change the angle if you
change the angle oh my God the saxophone
wow wait is there I don't want to wait I
don't
want look front
ah take a screenshot guys I don't know
how to do hry I don't know how
to get rid of the balloons they're kind
of they're kind of really big okay wa
balloon okay yeah yeah okay oh perfect
beautiful are you taking them send me
one later
Ina okay hold on give me one second
get oh that's good that's good oh yeah
F5 G no oh it just keeps going
[Music]
is this the finale the music's like
Grand be it oh oh wow I mean I imagine
if you actually at Disney World you'd
want it to be this long oh that is true
wow
wow o
planets okay I think I think that's I I
think I got some good good shots here
thank you
may not telling me I took one but I did
take one and it's saving it somewhere
yeah okay
wow this is it come
on I think it's G to keep
going endless
fireworks that must cost a lot that's
that's money being shot into the air
that's
quite you guys fireworks fireworks they
want to go space that oh that was
definitely that was yeah did you know
that it's like different uh chemicals
used to create the different colors of
the fireworks and they smell like sulfur
which smells like stinky oh cool oh
wow wow wow wow wow we missed that's got
to be that is it yeah that definitely
was it we're trying to take a
picture oh we're back wait you take a
picture and the back of my
head I tried but I have some like UI
stuff in it it's okay I I took a lot of
good ones last thing I want to check is
if we can go inside the castle here I
think we a very quick look inside
hello I want to keep these Stitch ears
they're so
cute
yeah honestly I would be surprised if
you have never actually bought those in
real life in Disney World before
no
Cinderella oh man
cerella okay of course she's in the
castle of course that is worth going
through yeah that was worth it hello
someone's over there see 25 wait we were
here before we were like Pocahontas and
and
uh okay okay cute
thanks for having us andella and all the
other people here thank you girls for
going on a Disney date together and it
was a lot of fun really impressive I did
not expect uh this to be so full of uh
content we didn't get to do
it did everyone have some favorite
attraction
oh I did actually enjoy the small world
one even though it was very long it was
really cute like it was really well made
yeah definitely
I oh Space Mountain was good
yeah with the Stars like floating around
you that was
really also like the cars one the Doom
Mario that
was I like that one in real life a lot
as well it's one of my favorites in real
life
so okay well everybody if you you are
interested you can check this out
yourself with the actual original music
this is not sponsored but I think it
would be fun to check it out with the
actual OG music without muting
everything you got to get bed
rock oh
my from her butt what the hell is that
it's tiny Casper Bae Bae is that
you this is yellow B forgot the name of
that one oh good I Disappeared uh oh
all right then I think we can end it
here you can get inside the
castle oh I'm in the castle oh through
here through here I'm in the
castle the castle it's breakfast area I
can actually you can this is an actual
restaurant you can actually eat here
yeah there nice there probably always
super crowded oh I see a staircase is
not very impressive in here though it's
just like you know with the breakfast
place windows I love breakfast wow oh it
is
cool looks like you need like
reservations even like before actually
coming here in order to get a seat like
life I mean this is really a thing six
months in
advance only for the for the biggest
Disney fans the most Crazy Ones yeah yes
okay shall we shall we uh take our leave
yeah
yes okay well thank you for watching
everybody thank you
everybody hope you enjoyed it let's hope
that someday in real life we can all go
to some places Disneyland together
girls I want to go to Disney C in Japan
with you oh that' be fun Disney I want
to be a real guy in Disney World so then
I actually literally to run you guys
around please please be our guide
yeah it will not be suspicious at all if
uh at Disney C you suddenly see 11
foreigners in a group
um one with a back don't worry about it
one with a shark
tail who Could That Shark Girl possibly
be and and that Shrek girl that purple
Shrek and that bird with the feathers on
her
top who's that girl wearing I'll just be
wearing like a conspicuous mask over my
head so no one can Rec dress up as No No
actually that's not allowed even at
least in Japanese disn't let you can't
dress up as the princesses at least for
there's one day where you may but all
the other days you're not allowed to
Halloween you
can okay anyway well thank you for
watching uh
goodbye
everybody goodbye bye byebye by
bye have a magical day goodbye yeah
byebye W magical day in the Magical
World e