[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
this is
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hello
did you miss me
you surely did right
[Music]
Ohio
a little bit yeah we did
correct answer
hello hello hello hello hello
good show
oh I missed you guys too just a little
bit
wow wow wow not as bad as the other
times this time why
why
you don't like me so much anymore
[Music]
I don't hate you guys
no I'm just
I I was that was preoccupied but uh I'm
happy to be back
sound like we love you or anything ah
it's not like I love you or anything
either
yeah you don't love me I don't love you
uh same same for real for real
yeah well it was
um two days I guess without me
is that
at the at the bottom of the game screen
is that a Pokemon
that's a Pokemon I'm telling you
um
I wonder if we'll meet that thing today
I'm planning on finishing this today
yeah it's a Diglett
okay I'm planning on finishing this
today
um no matter how long it takes but last
time we were I think we got like um 40
through the game so let's go and and I
have some things to tell you about my
weekend and then please remind me at the
end of the stream to show you a video
okay remind me at the end of the stream
before the Super Chat reading if I have
time to read super chats okay how many
chapters are there it says chapter four
I thought I I took a little video
nothing special I just want to show you
something
so here we are again do I remember how
to play this yeah okay I think I do so
this is a new place
oh there's like a house there big house
all right and let's go explore me
this game looks good yeah it looks good
and it is good did I not tweet of course
I tweeted
I'm pretty sure I tweeted I remember
writing it and all that oh cute I popped
back to the grassland just across the
river
oh
you mean like the place we were before
way
yes I did yes I did interesting house
[Laughter]
it's like different blogs
stuck together that shouldn't be stuck
together
was cute I like this look
let's see who's inside knock knock
oh
cute noises the little cartographer oh
oh that's the book
is that about me
after being led out of the Wildwood the
little cartographer arrived at a strange
building hitting the monster who really
is who's writing this who's writing this
as bookie
oh my God what
she followed her curiosity inside and
picked up the first book that she saw
[Music]
just then the storytender entered oh
oh
there's that darn book I've been looking
everywhere
it's very obviously placed in a very
obvious spot
it's a good one eh that was really
riveted couldn't put it down he did not
write it I think and then when I did I
forgot where I put it
ghostly's Bear Hugs farting sheep
what an adventure
[Music]
he looks like the one from up you're
right I did watch that movie
well clearly you have good taste welcome
to the story Chalet we're not easy to
find you must have a notice for
knowledge I'm the story gender and I
take care of a rather unique Library
and you'll find lots to love here and
our stories are always changing in fact
they've been changing rather quickly of
late
oh she was in the middle of sorting some
books but these old bones could use a
break let me show you how things work
around here
not that I asked but thank you
[Music]
ah I I also have a carpet similar to
that I think very similar hmm
when I lived in Japan though
and this is the dessert wing of the
Chalet
I think I had one like that oh I'm
imagining things not to be confused with
the dessert dessert desert desert
dessert dessert Wing which is setlist on
no is that the construction where are my
desserts I wanna eat some desserts
please please
like I mentioned each way and contained
stories related to a specific area of
the world
sad health
[Music]
noise a fried sad yum yum I recently
started reading a good one In This Very
Room it was about an old lady searching
for her grandfather and
oh that's my grandma
I know right what a good premise
when I left off the granny was getting a
bit exhausted
huh huh well I see you excited about
learning or to be a curious young mind
again well if you go and have these have
had these books I'll be in the writing
room just let me know if I can be of any
assistance
so wait she was like in the desert but
she wasn't here was she destination
searching the stands
first one uh-huh okay
there was sand as far as the eye could
see it was inescapable between your
sheets on your skin in your sandwiches
[\h__\h] sand is [\h__\h] everywhere
when the sandstorms were at their most
fierce whole camps would be buried
Roots leading back to the grassland and
other neighboring regions would
disappear
a certain young Padawan agrees very much
with this
these packs could be found Again by
Intrepid adventurers or at times
unwitting Wanderers
[\h__\h] coarse and rough men
the desert could be a harsh place and
was a home to a resilient nomadic people
the movie Star Wars was filmed here the
shifting Sands worm way of life often
confounding the Flora and Fallen series
and within it to melt a wisened wizard
woman searching for her granddaughter
thoughts and Elena's house was a Dragon
episode
[\h__\h] me now give me some time man
they have been separated by a storm and
yearned to be together
yes very much yearning to find my
grandma again anyway can I look over
here
no I'm so connected Maybe
oh
is this where I entered
but it seems like I can like
connect this to this
oh yeah the Gathering of the Magic Bus
what the grasslanders found endless ways
of improving their lives for clever
applications of plants
using an amalgam of different rubber
plants they created a new type of
Footwear
these Magic Bullets could be stretched
to fit any sized foot and raise the
running speed of its words can I ask
the last known pair awaits someone bold
enough to support them wait is that like
a secret I could have already found
if I was more Pharaoh in the grasslands
I wonder
somewhere in the grassland wing of
basement two of the story Chalet
huh that's me right now no what
yeah
[Music]
the last lone pair wait someone bold
enough to support them somewhere in the
grass anyway it's in here it's in here
[Music]
are they are they hinting that the boots
are in here or that are they just
hinting that the one who wants to wear
them is in here
hmm
no no no no no
good night sleepy sheepy
sympathy for Red Devils
Gangnam Style opal Gangnam Style well I
love the sore potato sour potato
traditional begonia Bob at least so
entitled what Wonka's mournful Melody oh
song titles Hey There Delilah what's it
like in New York City what's going on
here if all of these are references and
I don't know all of these
what is this a reference to good night
sleepy sheepy
what is this one for
are these all references
begonia Bop
[Music]
Sympathy for the Devil Rolling Stones
what so all of these are why why what's
the meaning of that what's the meaning
what do the titles mean Mason
Moments by Nature the people of the
grass don't typically migrate once a
generation
they traveled to Barren lands bearing
seeds in ancient immigration techniques
the grasslanders are deeply attuned to
the floor listening to the voice of the
earth and coaxing its growth through
song yeah yeah there was one singing by
the time the Next Generation migrates
the land they leave behind us of fertile
Paradise
well
[\h__\h] y'all wait here is basement one
shot I'm reading this once again I think
it's that second floor right
ha
[Music]
basement two
basement one we get some bootsies let's
go
um it must be this one
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah oh who's typing a ghost
wait basement
basement one
isn't it
in that basement one is it because I put
it on the same level do I have to try to
get up there
oh wait I could probably oh wait it's
new
honey again
I already read it is it a bug
it's still the same thing oh wait maybe
it changed its position
[Music]
you didn't
okay that's the fourth time I tried that
uh madam
I wonder can I go up if I place it a
certain way
because now I couldn't go for the door
ah the doors need to match up too huh
I can't go but now it says first floor
wait did that always say first floor
what I'm so confused
I'm so confused
let me let me go anyway in this room
first
[Music]
pop up
what does it say first
see it changed what if I go up here
second floor but I want to go to the
basement how can I go back to the
basement ah
it's a mark four
no no
um
[Music]
I did it I
wear the boots where are the boots where
are the boots where are the boots
okay let me talk to you first hey there
welcome to the riding room
this is where all of our stories are
created though I can't tell you how yeah
it's obviously a ghost typing what the
[\h__\h]
um
you need to get to the grassland Wing
this low what
the news ones are made for walking
that's just what they do
walk all over you I'm so old it's not
secret I just don't know no one does
that thingamajig over there just shrooms
to Malin has been for as long as anyone
can remember
my job is to change to the stories and
that's a good that's good enough for me
if you'd like to know more about the
story show like this is the room for it
I keep some of my other favorites here
too
let's see The Observers above their
people served an essential function to
charge the lands noting any changes and
shifts over time immemorial they
traveled by Airship so Grandma is an
observer quietly observing from a high
above rarely disturbing to people below
oh grandma is a god their navigation
skills were Peerless passed down through
the collective memory of their ancestors
this so cool like the way this world
works
simply they were cartographers by
trading by Blood just like me for real
for real like for real for real for real
though for real for real for real like
for real actually for real I mean it
deep in the forest in an unmemorable
Corner sits the story Chalet
this peculiar building can be tricky to
find when you're looking for it but easy
to stumble across when you aren't it
houses a remarkable library of books
overseen by catalog and catalog by a
storytender these mysterious tomes are
endlessly updated by an unseen hand
documenting stories and cultures Around
the World Around the World Around the
World Around the World Around The World
the building itself is an architectural
Marvel with a deceptively simple for say
that obscures its more sophisticated
interior
okay okay but where where are my boots
[Music]
my book Lies open on the desk nearby a
typewriter to have settling on its own
spooky
and I like this trainer like this
[\h__\h] speak okay let's try to get up
oh okay so here can actually go up but
now I am in basement one I think
[Music]
I did something right yo
but what how where are the boots though
basement basement free am I in basement
free and then
bye yeah yeah I missed them well well
now I have them hey oh am I faster oh
yeah I think I'm faster
to inside all right is that all I can do
here
I wonder
oh my spirits I didn't notice them when
you first arrived yeah I didn't have
them but let's not tell him that I
didn't steal anything these were meant
for me
these books boots were made for walking
and finding your grandpa
um what
okay what did he say
but you're eager to get back outside and
put it oh yeah okay he's telling me to
go back now I suppose uh
[Music]
let's see how do I
there we go
with her fancy
oh it's that little cartographer I knew
that nothing could stop her
she would head out to cross the river
and find her way to the desert where she
helped her grandmother waited
desert ikazole is that ink
oh no no
no no no no no no
[Music]
okay wow I'm so fast
though I'm so
I'm saying all right how do we get to
um
is there any way for us to get over
there
no not really
um no
no there really is not
can I jump
ah I can go over this part
oh trail to the grassland return to the
grassland
may I
thank you
finally oh
welcome back what's bright we were
worried when you were disappeared did
you happen to see the ghostly
ah he's gone oh well I figured I'd ask
Malco will be set to hear it I think he
was still holding out hope but everyone
will be glad to have you back yeah yo I
know that look in your eye are you on
your own secret mission now
[Music]
oh
you're looking for somewhere Sandy
I don't know if such a place but
sometimes motor Shepherd arrives home
covered in sand
Mal have you met Mo before
ah this place is still as messed up as I
left
couldn't someone have cleaned this [\h__\h]
up for me
oh my God
where do I want to go who is you
are you the shepherd
oh
wait think
why why no why
why
okay
foreign
let me check out that guy
and see if we met him before or if he's
new and he's the sand guy ah wait you
just stop
you who's that dude who just sleeps
that's it and you see that they're all
around you just look around they're all
here
all right person
oh wait why not get Sandy don't tell my
dad what I don't know sometimes I just
wake up that way
oh maybe the Sandman came to visit Santa
[Music]
you know when you sleep
Sandman comes
so that's why he said it's just sand
from being sleepy
maybe I can show you when I'm asleep I'm
wide awake now but there are probably
some blondes that can knock me out but
I'm no plant expert
okay you want me to make you fall asleep
I could just wait for you fall to fall
asleep don't you fall asleep rather fast
anyway
as you always know the best okay
um plant experts
wow who what did that person look like
again
this seems like a place where a plant
expert would live
to grind
wow wow this ain't Minecraft are you the
planned expert
[Music]
missed a note
wait in in the room in here
oh
gongo silly hunting
oh [\h__\h] where where where would you oh
God damn it
oh
where would you go I
[\h__\h]
I caught them
foreign
[Music]
you guys know that song
that's a new shoes huh not new boots
[Laughter]
he's only making good time in them but
he wants to be tired from running around
someone's chilling what plants could you
used to help our friend sleep soundly at
tonight I know I know
it's not a competition everyone can
answer I think each of the children has
something to tell you when you gather
the plans put them inside the spot
oh
I'm ready for the other gift card okay I
guess
whisper grass
through it oh sorry sorry it sounds like
a bunch of people going
remember leaves
[Music]
are you guys riding this down what did
you say by the mouth of the river
right next to both the river and the
open ocean
okay let me just do that first otherwise
I'll forget everything a mouth of the
river next to the ocean
is this a mouth of a river
next to the ocean
wait
did she say
this this is that what she said
[Music]
oh wait what
this little ocean
hmm
[Music]
one more
for the mouth of the river you know
right next to both
the river and the open ocean
oh
Maybe
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
what
I can't put that there
uh
I
hmm I can't attach pieces that don't fit
each other you know
so
yeah yeah I would try to create
something but still it has to be like
I have to build something that would
create it in the first place
I don't have the right piece oh
that's the case and let's check another
one first slime was not gross in a field
of yellow leaves
like the ones that Auntie turia attends
yellow leaves
like uh these ones and these ones a
field of it
let's just bring as many as possible
there
[Music]
I was hoping for that to happen
big brain okay so here we get a new
piece of map hopefully
um
no
maybe maybe I will be gifted one
oh
wow
we got one of the things
okay she still just is very occupied
okay okay okay
I don't want the grass but I also want a
piece of map anyway what are you saying
dozing daisies they slowly not and make
everyone around the tech but that's what
I actually want there are a bunch of the
bunch planted near the Circle Road
Circle Road I say you want me to make a
circle
last forever easy
that's very easy is it is it though okay
never mind not so easy
oh my God it was fine it was just very
easy I know what to do
oh
see
we got it
well now
um do I have what it takes for her
thingy mop the river right next to both
the river and the open ocean mouth of
the river
but this thing is new
and that one's new but these don't
really seem to be helpful
I don't know what that means
[Music]
the mouth of the river sorry one more
time is is is
where the river starts
right
where the river meets the ocean
can't make the meat though
make the meat
Doyle Dallas
oh
happy coincidences happy accidents I'm
not gonna claim that that was me
that was just me being lucky
[Laughter]
that looks like a shovel or something
like that okay but
[Music]
um
interesting we would wanna try to get uh
like so and like
like myself no
okay now we can go down
am I speed running it I don't know am I
am I so fast
I'm just big braining it oh
tell me you saw it young sapling tell me
you saw the Ghostly
[Music]
no I'm sorry I was just so excited when
it appeared it's just you disappeared
right after I thought you may have found
it
Bloom eventually
[Music]
oh
this is what we're looking for I have
all three of them so wait how do I check
there we go
wait what why did I I have two should it
make you sleepy and what is this one for
then
I wonder will it be useful for me or did
I just get some unnecessary ones
anyway we'll go we'll go to make him
sleep hopefully actually let me move on
to another
piece of map
makes things quiet
I don't know do I need all of them hmm
I hope I hope I hope it was worth it
yum yum
yum yum okay wide awake okay good to
know
I have this solution
flowers
[Music]
oh one more one flowers you really
oh
spoiling us
there you go last one
oh he's sleepwalking wait oh let's
follow him
how do you do that what the [\h__\h]
would you like some more tea
oh we're gonna enter and never came
perhaps are just sheep liking this new
area
kind of unusual isn't it
okay
quick learner I got an achievement
calling me a quick learner
you hear that kfp
never call me stupid ever again
oh
it's what a terrible idea
I didn't tell you to touch them just
told you to look at them
I can talk to the cacti
why you keep touching I'm not touching
him I'm just looking at them oh
I knew
cactuses have horns wait it's not cacti
wait it's not cacti
the plural
hi homie
it's both okay good
I felt smart oh
hello you cutie patooty
search steadfast mounts elbows
they're able to conserve water in their
bodies the clever things it makes them
too heavy to cross the yellow Sands but
it's helpful to have extra water around
just in case it's a good thing we found
those cacti when we did a sheep see
who says cacti
it made a horse sound do they really
make horse sounds
when did I get so cold you better
believe I'm sharp as a cactus but my
body feels like an ancient Temple these
days Sandy and full of skeletons enjoy
it while you can kiddo beautiful isn't
she this golden desert of ours
curves as far as the eye can see
the heaven Lush Oasis all to ourselves
but it dried right out
front hort
ah
we've been searching for another water
source ever since
the cacti may not dry but we squeeze
every last drop of water out of how do
you squeeze them without hurting
yourself
how do you do that I guess I guess okay
well this is literally how you do it
capped ouch there's some kind of like
machine for it huh
some equipment and supplies doesn't
stand
all right interesting but now we have
new maps so let's take a look at them
oopsie how do I pick them up again
no uh I
I I oh I see that's like a more deep
desert
does it does it does it really get like
more yellow the more deeper you go
you can believe it
I'm scared in the cutest coolest game
ever
[Music]
that's like I did not expect that
don't don't be scared don't be scared oh
oh my God okay
it's like um every now and then not the
whole time
kaito is now also a horror game yeah
what's that what's what's there what's
there to see here
I don't see anything interesting
wait a second
um
[Music]
well we're hoping to find one in there
to sustain us yes even though I don't
have elders Captain said Mama went
looking for the desert Haven but we
haven't heard from her since I do hope
that girls all right okay I have to find
someone
you must be punched young sister I wish
we had more to offer you we're down to
the last few cacti and Granny Noah is
looking a bit worse for wear I'm fine
yes yes of course you are
we were barely able to set up this camp
in time before the sandstorms rolled in
the rest of our unit headed west across
the yellow Sands
are you familiar with our desert no
please tell me more about it be careful
in the yellow Sands they're ever
shifting at the landscape around you can
change in a heartbeat
the White Sands around us are calm you
can always use them to find your way
back
okay
now she gave me a bit more information
but
um well she did say it's ever changing
so maybe some things will change after a
while
I literally didn't do anything
Nanny wants to nine on it wait what
oh wait this is another thing of the
Wind
oh
what did I do
I did something right and I did
something wrong and I did something
right
maybe it's these Hills and I have to go
to the Hills
in the right order
oh
no no sounds
huh
oh
oh I guess okay okay I just continue
going that way I guess it's the same
like yeah okay it's the same like in in
that Forest
we just continue that for a few times
and then
hopefully at some point
something will show
it gets higher every time
maybe this time yay
[Music]
almost done
we have new pieces of maps there we go
all right so we can go here and then we
can go here
we see we escape from the yellow desert
to find another calm place
oh a shield a shield that's so German
again
shield in German is sign in English
similar pronunciation but written
differently so sometimes when I see a
sign I think oh it's a shield
follow the footprints in the yellow
Sands make sure they connect aha
footprints
are these footprints
you see what I'm seeing
those look like Footprints my screen my
middle screen is extremely bright right
now
a tiny love test of a series of numbers
scrolled on it
oh no uh coordinates
90 minus 180 270 minus 270 90. but
aren't coordinates usually only three
numbers
oh it's angles oh I guess yeah okay
90 oh god oh
90 okay turning 90 degrees is like from
right to down from down to left from
left to up right and 180 is from like up
to down for example right
and then
217 is
is it from like if we go clockwise from
up to left
okay okay okay
so uh
uh it would be
if this is clockwise
then first we go
uh we turn ah wait are we turning this
piece of map
so once we turn it to the right then we
turn it twice the left then we turn it
price to the right then we turn it fries
to the left then we turn it once to the
right
uh does anyone remember that
I think
so
once oh
[\h__\h] I think twice to the left and
then was it twice was it fries to the
right one two three and then fries to
the left one two three and it wants to
ride
ah
oh oh
I figured that out I'm like oh let's go
Mommy
a luxurious chest filled with shimmering
treasure I like this mechanic oh
surely no one will miss one coin I'm
just taking one wow well she's just a
little girl I guess she's not very
greedy
unusable vessels
uh-huh oh a long abandoned hand watch
out for Scorpio oh no
scorpions that's really scary scorpions
in the desert hundred percent deadly
would not trust them
okay we got a golden coin
now
am I supposed to go back
Bonsai shop can I maybe bring some of
these
what
I got an achievement not so sharp but
I did not what was that I I got a puzzle
piece is that a secret
I don't think that
um it's supposed to be like I think it's
a collectible
probably
Secret
s
wasn't I looking for a human
wait did the map always have footsteps
too
oh oh wait is that ah
wait okay never mind
uh
okay now they're the right side okay
follow follow follow follow
um now these are currently looking to
the left so now I turned them
to this side I think mm-hmm
me
this is fun but okay this one I think
maybe like that oh
[Music]
I've learned nothing about this one
sometimes it's not like it's not like I
have HP
without you
oh
okay let's go back I guess
um that was
ah maybe that's a dried out Oasis
huh
oopsie
hit
okay going back
up up up up up up up up
I do love games that lets the player
actually feel smart for real yeah me too
it's really simple but I I feel smart
used to me sent a picturesque Oasis
and I said it here but I need to
conserve liquid
oh and you would gasp look gasp
Oh Captain went missing a few weeks ago
during an especially strong Sandstorm
she's the best water sticker we have I'm
sure she can survive on her own but it's
been so long Franny Noah must be so
worried about her
hello little sister you have the blood
of a water Seeker in you I can tell not
everyone can read the desert so well
we lost track of Captain samala but we
will find her just as well just as we'll
find some water soon
we Seekers use all of our senses to
locate water
we inspect the appearance of the plants
we sense the movements of the animals
the density of the air Clues are
everywhere
[Music]
look you know my mom almost sold me for
one of these before
[Laughter]
when we were in Africa
uh she wanted to sell me
hopefully not seriously but she was
offered two camels in exchange for me
yeah
yeah we were on a trip to Morocco
I think I mentioned it before
two camels I think it's quite
quite the luxurious Exchange
oh cats oh
yes I know it I know
fall down coconuts coconuts
it's uh some some something to drink for
you guys you wanna
um yellow Sands
you're worth way more thank you I would
agree
if they made it free maybe yeah yeah two
is not enough no no
I don't know like how serious was the
person offering that in the first place
again those lines along the way so we
could follow her but some got swept up
in the sand could The Haven be real
maybe she's already there okay
Dairy
oh we're back with the puns aren't we
okay we have a new one a new Contender
let's see what this one looks like
I'm at least four cameras worth thank
you a camel is worth 5 to 20K well
that's very
Broad
what the hell I offer six camels why why
are those camels show them to me first I
oh
now it's really changing look at that
touch no touch
no touching
no touchy
it changed but
all right
if I go in again it changes again
it did but it just rotated the map
oh maybe every time I go in it rotates
it
yep that just rotated it
so
what for
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
go next
well nothing happened when I entered
this one
when I go back here it rotates again no
no it didn't
oh
well then I enter again from this side
it changes again but when I entered from
the other side it didn't change
okay wait now this one is the same
what is the riddle for this one
lonely
thank you big brain gamer
I am very much like you today I am a big
brainer big brain gamer now
wait this is the first time I'm not sure
what well what I'm supposed to do
oh
I don't know I don't know
[Music]
hi guys maybe I just you know tell them
what's up
I found some of the other people but
[Music]
um
foreign
I should go there too
ah
oh wait
you can connect them like this
yeah and I got
foreign
the sand so far oh it's fine with my new
boots nothing is able to enter no sand
can enter my booties
I'll keep an eye on those Cathy in the
yellow Sands oh wait a second wait a
second
they grow
oh I think I am maybe maybe understand
but they all look the same she why did I
get a new one when they're all the same
but okay okay okay she said something
about you know groups of cacti
and keep an eye out on them we did see
groups of cacti there
yeah but it's not like I could interact
with any of them so what if
assuming that these are on the right
um
orientation
if I move it like this no one more
then they should meet yeah
and then then I I add another one
three times turning no wait
maybe I get a fourth one no
oh wait I did it wrong
ah idea was right the idea was right I
just didn't turn it enough times
fine
oh hello what are you doing all along
did you eat your companion
a noble camel chewing on a lung orted
silicon scarf hmm nah it wouldn't do
that the camel wouldn't camels don't eat
do camels eat meat I feel like they
don't
like the vegetarians no
potato
they do
they can they oh but they wouldn't eat
meat
mates unless the person already died and
they're eating like an already dead body
Maybe
I hope
around man eating camel oh no no no I
don't think they would make the story so
dark here that's too dark
I found some strange ruins sisters I'll
meet you in the middle of them I know
I'm close to Haven captain
stranger these ruins you mean
what happened to your
call
and your your scarf yo well what
happened to y'all
oh
wait
I see
it completely changes
every time I enter it changes all of my
yellow desert maps and now
no no don't change again
no it was perfect right now
oh
is it just me or the stones telling me
to go down
on this phone's telling me to go down
well now they're still telling me to
come down if that's the case
oh [\h__\h]
let's try but I could be wrong maybe I'm
just going insane right now
well then it would still mean go down oh
[Music]
or I just tried to connect them like
this
now they're together
um I'm not sure
these ones oh
do I have
no I only have these ones
okay I'll just go down I'll just go down
several times
wait then this is
yes I think
[Music]
Nani
the message what message
what message
let me let me listen again
foreign
okay
uh depends on how they're turned now
[\h__\h]
I don't remember
I've got them
we have to check
them
but they still ruin still right okay
okay this one uh huh
uh huh
oh
something like that uh not not quite
these ones are right
what about those I think the bottom ones
are right
there you go
let me go through please
Captain is it you Captain I have a
coconut you can drink the coconut Don't
drink don't cry
I
I see it
through the sand so hazy built up from
the earth cold cool Stones wrapped
around water deep below and somewhere
beyond
she's crazy she's insane ah
Oasis but she's imagining so strong
she's making it happen oh
oh it's dried out too though
how about I make it all one big thing
[Music]
I don't know does it have to be in a
certain direction
maybe we need one more middle piece
that we don't have yet
foreign
I'll talk to her again
I see it I'm so thirsty have my own
coconut oh it's dry what the [\h__\h] why oh
wait here
see this
this is the fourth secret piece the one
I collected like a few minutes ago
where are the other ones I didn't get
the [\h__\h] those
oh man
hmm
anyway let me look around a bit
yeah never mind
[\h__\h]
oh shh
[Music]
she needs water but it's not like I can
do anything with those
um which one is the new one anyway uh
maybe this one wait if I throw the
frog there
oh oh
there's a thing
happy birthday to who to whom
happy birthday
ah thank you so much your second
birthday
noise congratulations hope you're having
a lovely birthday
happy birthday to you mama
said happy birthday to you
yeah
congratulations
in the Sunday pillow can I am
hmm
broken bucket I can't throw in the coin
why not
[Music]
I know that reminded me of tunic but
maybe I was wrong
[Music]
maybe I should just go back and tell
them that I found the captain
where are the ones that I want to talk
to
oh
yeah came back together
the Coconuts were empty but we found a
few more cacti to bring back
this is
we're just regrouping then we had to
headed back out to find her I know why
she is
take care of yourself sister if you find
yourself mumbling or too tired to move
you're dehydrated yep I found someone
like that and that is your captain
if you encountered a noble white camel
that's our Captain's Mount she leaves
him to wait just outside the yellow
Sands if you find that Camel perhaps
you'll find a clue to a cat I'm further
than that I'm far past that
[Music]
I wish cartel would speak when it
matters
she's right there
um
camel Tom
you good sis
you're not good okay
what about you
give this to me
you little [\h__\h]
slightly sad don't be
she's not dead yet and thank you for not
eating her
okay okay I guess I'm showing the scarf
to the other peeps as a proof that I
found her
here you can see this one
you don't want to
look at this huh where the [\h__\h] are they
not looking at it
it's not like I have a button to show it
for them oh wait
yeah thank you genius in the chat genius
go to the well
go to the well go to the well
[Music]
save everyone ah
Corner that I picked up is you being
used as a bucket
let's see if we can get the tiny amount
of water out of there wow
okay
now we bring this
to the lady
hopefully
without any casualties
is this a package
here's a bucket with some water there
you go
get a hold of yourself girl
oh there we go
thank you for saving me sweet sister I
almost made it to Haven but I lost my
unit along the way please give me a
moment to contact them you have a phone
or what
oh potato
so [\h__\h] way
I've hasta my friend
apologies I was sending a message via
sand beetle is this real is this a real
thing they do there
we Mark our position on their shell and
they burrow towards the footsteps of
others they shed their shell every few
days so it doesn't bother them oh
smart
sand beetle
I mean
I've had pigeons and and crows and and
owls I don't know which one bring
letters to people before
so I wouldn't be so surprised if that
thing or the beetle would actually work
maybe there's like an actual like you
know like a natural
orientation sense that beetles have or
like some way you can manipulate them to
go in a certain direction you know I
don't know I mean and who knows who am I
to judge what is possible and whatnot
no messenger beetles
don't this
don't this is my in her dreams okay
we're in the middle of the [\h__\h]
desert we have to cling on to some kind
of hope
Beetle must reach its destination
please
uh did you pass my sisters along the way
might I ask
I'm so relieved I knew they'd be fine
but I wasn't sure how far my Clues would
get them
if I'm right this indeed the gate to the
desert Haven but to open it I need a
special artifact a trap has passed it
down for Generations knowing it would
show us the way when we truly needed it
I believe the time has come
sadly I wished was that mean
thank you welcome
mm-hmm
entertainment Can you tame a beetle
be a very smart beetle
what's the smartest Beetle I came here
for the thumbnail welcome now you must
stay
don't go away
buy a crib of sand Brooks and one
absconded with the artifact while we
wait for my sisters could you please
have a look around with them
alrighty thank you kindly I'm truly in
your depth you find one remember they're
too fast to catch unless you distract
them somehow one stole a bracelet right
off my wrist once oh the coin decline
they like shiny things I have a coin
that's shiny
um we don't have anything shiny nope I
did it I have something shiny already
don't worry
um
so where am I supposed to find them girl
she gave me nothing new
in a yellow Sands use something shiny
okay so I just go into the yellow Sands
and then hope for something to happen
now
let me bring all of them up here
let's see
it's kind of scary
having to
um find the sand Rogues
kind of scary why do I put the shiny
thing
I have it with me
oh
wait I thought we were talking about
like humans
talking about an animal
oh
what the [\h__\h] something new was there
what
I thought it was a human
a group of humans eh
sand broke
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
that's not shiny at all why did it take
the map
oh yeah yeah
interesting
what's what's what's new here
why did I get this piece of map
hmm
anyway
whoopsie
hello I have oh everybody 's here yum
foreign
and yet it still stands but what do
these symbols mean
well did you see that band of sand rocks
scurrying by they make my skin crawl who
knew the desert would be full of rats
don't we have snakes for that for real
women
I didn't think I'd make it a ninja kid
though but still got some says super
Savage says or whatever the kids are
calling it I wasn't going to mind like
only granddaughter go thirsty she may be
my captain no Captain my Captain but I
love her just the same there's amazing
riding on the gate almost as ancient as
me says something about the light
foreign
[Music]
camel
reunion I wanted to see that too
the artifact you found it I'm
overwhelmed with gratitude you're truly
a miracle sister now if I'm right we
just have to put what are you saying
have you guys noticed this one thing
that I've just noticed these are all
women
and in the in the in the forest we met
all men
we have to let these people meet
and make babies
oh
oh like the good noodle and Zelda yeah
well let's just make some babies and
then they kick them out
nobody ever thought of that it's only
for because I I saw I saw the other
gender over there if they would never
know about it you know if I didn't tell
them
I am saving the world
yes
ah
wow
put down a fight in place just like this
okay
[Music]
come on wow holy light holy macaroni
whoa can I go inside
[Music]
the artifact is set so what's the final
step going inside taking a step is the
final step
reveal the Haven under the light but
which light
is the Haven really beyond that gate how
exciting let's go
let's go oh
aha
[Music]
this means something
foreign
[Music]
not quite
ah I don't know
[Music]
you're telling me that's not it
foreign
[Music]
ah wait
if this is correct
[Music]
a [\h__\h] genius
you know because I saw that um this like
castle castle shaped thing it was like
you know the top was you know not full
you know and it was descending you know
so I thought oh I need a piece that's
descending you know and then I saw oh
this isn't full so I can't go here and I
guess it has to go here oh
my God
you're now
oh
[Laughter]
I saved the whole [\h__\h] desert
every single piece of sand is in my
depth which is a Brazilian bad trillion
pieces of sand
more than that
how many sand is there in the desert
what a question
more billion
I'm
dead
at least two at least four at least
three
what are these answers oh look at that
oh cute it's like a hot spring for them
she's drinking and washing her face
nice good for you
everyone is also a camel bath I'm just
going to not think too hard about that
yeah you want it yeah yeah yeah
don't think too hard oh wowies
really speedrun that damn
[Music]
it
stay hydrated everybody yeah
well well we don't even need it well
anymore
maybe we'll turn it into a wishing well
and finally have a use for those coins
it's amazing we're going to need a
bigger camp and a boat
Boat Boat
[Music]
we just walk around
oh there it last I'm grateful to yakido
you helped track down my grand I mean
the captain
and then
why isn't it this game with grandmas
losing their granddaughters
helped her find a Haven you're an
honorary water Seeker as far as I'm
concerned
from this place
you feel that earthquake It could only
have come from the volcano are we going
to a lava World Net
no rest for the wicked out
of The Frying sand and into the lava
wow
I always knew they even was out there
but it still feel surreal to be here
we couldn't have done it without you as
soon as we as soon as we track down some
more beetles I'll send messages out to
the rest of our tribe to join us
I wish you all much much luck and I hope
you stay alive
for a long time
don't
don't stop hydrating I mean
this this amount of water should suffice
for a while on it there we go
don't waste it though
I wish I could talk to the
I always in my head I always want to
sell Pop Guns it's not alpacas
savior of the desert yeah let's
whisper the secret tunnels Beneath The
Haven don't mind you might not find your
way back once you enter that's fine
my job here is done
nothing has left to do
starts leading down into the doctors
want to check it out yeah
yeah camels are just ugly alpacas oh my
God I can't say that don't not while
they can hear it
oh
we're back in the forest
oh wait there's a boat
that's new the boat is new
um anything secret here
foreign
[Music]
okay let me go first into the house
maybe there's something new in the house
oh well yeah you know exactly what's up
oh
my God
you're here
well I lost you forever
[Music]
I was so worried when you didn't show up
at a meeting spot but it sounds like
you've been busy the story kind of told
me you dropped by here and on your way
to the desert did you find any clues
about your granny there
[Music]
is he the sad rat
how else did he get the coin
I'm sorry I'm sure it's just a matter of
time but I bet she's looking just as
hard for you
oh I felt the ground shaking too I
thought it was just my lunch disagreeing
with me until some books fell off the
shelf the volcano must be acting up
again their options are quite shy to be
behold to behold
that's not my grandma it's my friend
the sky darkens with thick black smoke
and orange Embers drift through it like
snowflakes
sounds like My My My lyrics
in the new myth song
um that smoke might make the sky harder
for you Granny to navigate cuddle I
wonder if you can warn her somehow I bet
it's worth a try
warn her hmm
maybe I can make a balloon
with a message
foreign
I bet we can find some clues in the
volcano Wing I'll meet you there volcano
Wing
that's new such impatience I am sad to
say the volcano Wing has been missing
person well then why the [\h__\h] did she go
she lost forever sometimes the rooms are
weird you expect and sometimes they go
missing if only I could visit the top
floor again something
oh I can do that for you oh please
ignore me just a wasteful yearnings of
an old man anyways that can't be of much
help in locating the volcano Wing but I
can usually find what I'm looking for if
I read enough books no better place to
start
the little cartographer has come up dry
looking for granny in the desert but she
had all the burning issues to deal with
how could she want her granny about the
volcano that was about to erupt and
before that she had to figure out how to
get there
[Music]
nanny
actually his curse I tell you while
exploring a celebrity rainfalls I came
across the floor sign bearing no number
but an obvious question yeah I saw that
before I ran to the stairwell in the
Panic only to discover that the floor is
above and below it were equally unmarked
I saw rooms I'd never seen before on
these unknown floors and fled in Terror
from the shop I will never return to
that Unholy place
huh
okay so you want me to try that with the
question marks in the hopes
of finding
something
interesting
let's see but now it's now it's basement
two oh
[Music]
nice fruitful how did I do that before
foreign
[Music]
wrong wrong thingy
okay let's go here
nothing nothing new here okay
oh but it's a question mark floor
so
you can go down into oh
[\h__\h] it's just you again
[Music]
next question mark right yeah
uh-huh
[Music]
Nani
question mark 4 and we have a new book
thingy
rip merch what do you mean uh
wait
ah Jackson ah
I heard about that from uh on Twitter
wasn't wasn't you someone else tweeted
about it I already told my manager when
I saw that so
where we're gonna see what's going on
there
let me
take a screenshot
it's not acceptable
you what I I got pooped onto what does
that mean you also had the same problem
mine's still not arrived as well from
2021 one
I mean yours was lost too did check your
emails like
many people had this oh my [\h__\h] god
screenshotting
I'm sorry I'll see I'll see what we can
do I don't really know don't get your
hopes up but
um
[Music]
that's not nice
it's not cool
I'm sorry
maybe maybe something can be done about
it if you get a full free
um
refund
[Music]
um I don't know maybe maybe I can try to
ask for a restock like in general for a
re what's what's it called
you know getting the 2021 merchandise to
be
um
you know made again
for the people who yeah rerun thank you
and then you guys can order it through
um not for kick Jack but for
uh
just through the whole live store Maybe
once again
so I'll gosh
oh you're passing your skin jacked I
can't use whole life story
um
okay okay I I'm gonna try to make it all
right anyway the water Seekers were
highly
no try being responsible for the
survival of their people this Resolute
group would seek out new water sources
often journeying far from home their
senses were highly attuned to the desert
environment around them to Aid them in
their search
once the new water stress was located
their tribe would migrate to join them
camels and all
that did indeed happen
so I'm not sure
what I am to do a basement one but this
one oh so that one's also new read again
no it's the same still last time I also
kept on sparkling even though there
wasn't anything new basement one
[Music]
placement tool
made something new I combined it the
right way yay
nah first one to go down and then we can
try to go up I guess on it
where am I oh
off
interesting
[Music]
the volcano floor whatever
I think I found something
uh-huh
I had just about given up on finding a
volcano Wing when it appeared out of
nowhere
I wonder how that happened
this is such a strange building anyways
I think I found something helpful in
this book have a look the volcanoes are
popular in tourist destination due to
its temperate weather and world famous
Spas Travelers can take a long way up to
sending its face over the course of
several days or hope to catch a ride on
a friendly member of its thriving
mountain goat population gold population
[Music]
though the fastest most reliable paths
up the volcano lie deep within the
forest for those who can find them
sounds like you can get the volcano
through the forest
if there's a path I know you'll find
that no one is better at finding the way
for the world
[Music]
would you like me to go with you
oh my guess I don't really care I'm fine
alone I worry that I just slow you down
yeah you don't have those Speedy boots
I hate to split up again but you find
your way around so quickly in time maybe
of the essence it is it is so hurry
along without me and in the meantime
I'll do some research for us here wow
what a lazy beat uh
well chemical on a burning truth or what
what kind of emojis are divided on the
accuracy and scientific bases of the
volcano coland calendar
proponents of the calendar claim that
it's been an invaluable planning
resource for countless Generations while
the tractors dismissed it as a bunch of
meaningless zones who's carved on the
wall by some Vagabond in any case
residents of the volcano always seem to
avoid disaster somehow whether or not
they're just expecting it uh-huh
was that something interesting
it didn't seem so interesting
uh wanna go
into this one
oh
whoa root routes mother's Road stretched
across the forest as she grew and far
beyond they grew along hidden paths
snacking their way to distant lands
across the world these pastors settle an
upskirt to all but the most Intrepid
explorers only the trees knew how to
access them and they didn't speak much
did we is this something we already
solved
Barry and earthworm compared yes
but messenger was chosen as the 255th
Watcher Lampa and his reform Patrol the
wild before they can set fat steadfast
friends and Protectors of mother Sally
and Aaron Sparrow snatched enough
along with the trees for the reminder of
his watch
well to this day the countless Prague
progeny of Olympus girlfriend beneath
our feet hunger for dirt and ready to
help is it the earthworm that we met
okay ah
trip
many years before true became the 2056
watch and Chip was a small beardless
term Sheriff did not make any friends
easily did not make friends easily I
would spend many afternoons exploring
the Woods by Trip South Jeremy
one faithful afternoon sure followed a
sad hooting noise and found an outlet
struck in an animal trap
a trap turning it into a stretcher to
carry the outlet in until it healed
German chips owl companion were never
apart after that they now tend to Mother
together
now can we try
or is that for later are we able to make
like a top floor
[Music]
let's see oh
foreign
[Music]
nothing was going to keep her from her
granny okay you know what I feel like
maybe this whole top floor thing is for
another time
and we'll go find
Grandma
uh what was it with find in the forest
um
I'm not sure
I'm not sure I don't remember can I take
the boat now no
that's just uh where we came from
maybe have to go for this thing again
ah
no Wayne we've been here before right
well maybe we have to be here again
is this new
[Music]
this thing
I don't think it is but maybe we just go
there again I remember that oh
[Music]
I'm going to see all the furniture which
I've known we're in need of his skills
say they need me me we can't seem to
find true if I mean the new Watcher I'm
not sure I'll ever get used to saying
that deep in his vulture or getting a
bird's eye view from one of the bigger
trees maybe they've seen something
interesting
what
[Music]
the trees
oh I found something is there more to
find
look how fast they move
sugoi
taste dope super lit
hello
who needs a bird's eye when you have
cactus
tree moving powers
checking every area but nothing else
nothing else nothing else really
foreign
with this
[Music]
by the way
on the weekend I was oh
and wasn't streaming right remember
so actually I used the opportunity
to go to a Comic-Con here
Comic-Con Vienna Comic-Con in Austria
yeah
I am honestly
I I've been there several times but I
never actually like entered the actual
area where you need a ticket
this time was actually the first time
got some stories to tell
[Music]
me
that's also yeah why I asked about Jack
Gleason on Twitter
hmm sharp absent but vulture C Northeast
mother with haste
where did that come from
Northeast
yeah yeah
um so I went to
Comic-Con I knew that my friends would
go to
hello
just checking the area why is this all
moving why is it the bug actually
supposed to be like that right
here just super nice I
I prefer like normal Anime conventions
over comic-cons because
there's just so much that I don't care
about at comicals
you're very glad to see you again those
herbs been hiding needed a break from
watching mother grow she's very slow and
very quiet tell troop of your travels
have you visited other forests perhaps
met someone who likes watching trees
someone who needs a job
[Music]
the volcano sure visited once when he
was a sprout
not sure how to get there though perhaps
trip can ask the Wildwood old Waters and
teaching serve a bit of tree tum
Russell Russell West Russell
the world would say something about a
bee in the witch how exciting holy [\h__\h]
this
they scare me what is happening
hmm treb is still learning apparently
they say a tree has an each
not sure what it means but maybe you
could scratch it
I will draw your reminder
thank you
thank you I didn't need that but okay
it's time to return mother now okay
everyone can stop joking for church I'll
see you there bye-bye it's not that way
it's left left
how do I scratch the trees when they are
moving away from me
huh
[Music]
Can you know
Coca-Cola
do I maybe scratch the big tree
Screech scratch oh oh
that was very understanding of terms of
absence did you find an itchy tree to
scratch it but it looks just like chirps
drawing
it's not this one
oh
ah maybe that one down there
Screech scratch
[Music]
what does it look like oh see
huh
[Music]
foreign
that one
they look like they're scratching the
branch is blocking the whole are too
heavy to move yourself
uh
who who would move it for me then
I found it but okay I'll go to to our
chirp friend maybe he can help me
[Music]
I found it yeah please help me
no
no you don't want to help me
[Music]
I don't know what I'm looking for but
well maybe I can
find someone maybe you want to help
huh ah he will help me
Scott's talking Earth six okay now Texas
who's there no but perhaps 60 years go
deep
sleep
oh no he won't help me
well you know if I ask you again
body friend
go deep can we get deeper
I follow
I follow I follow path
[Music]
maybe find
something
can we get much deeper that is the
question oh
trees here don't move
[Music]
I'm lost
so deep
what does it mean what does it mean what
what does it mean
one second
let me pull up my memos
ah so and at the Comic-Con uh
never mind
never mind to Comic-Con I wanna just
talk to this bird
[Music]
why you not come down to talk to me
yes oh my God it's gonna stretch scratch
the tree for me because it's so sweet
[Music]
the birthday was the purple was there
was that not a special bird
all right we are
here again oh no
where am I supposed to go this time
is it updated now with Like A New Path
um
[Music]
oh God oh my God
okay we don't have to bother with the
other one too long it seems
sometimes in a while but it's too dark
to read oh I saw I saw here the the
light is somewhere
to have to find
there we go okay so so
uh on Saturday
I went to the Comic-Con and then I was
waiting for my friends to gather
somewhere already there somewhere not
there yet even though it was already
pretty late
me and my friends
go to these things very late it seems
I did not have a ticket but I I was you
know I went to uh to like the wrong
station
and naisu I went to the wrong station
first oh wait can I light it up thank
you
because the venue and it has kind of two
stations but there's one main station
for the main entrance
and I
I had to walk from the
the station the wrong station in the
back entrance basically all the way to
the front
and during that I got
and feet hot very bad because I was
wearing new shoes
but
the good thing about walking down there
was
um there were a lot of people because it
was already pretty late there were a lot
of people
um
walking towards the station to go home
and uh they were like
two dudes
a group of two dudes one of them like
they were like I don't know a couple
meters away from me walking towards me
and one of them like separated with the
dude with the other dudes to talk to
some people and then the other dude
he saw me walking
went up to me and asked me if I wanted
his ticket
and I'm like hey yo you know what
perhaps yes I perhaps want it
because I did not have a ticket I I
thought I would be fine without a ticket
because normally at this convention uh
like there's like a like a hall where
you don't need a ticket there's nothing
there but people won't chill there so in
the past I always just chilled outside
there
yeah what a chat and then I I took the
tickets I didn't have to pay for it so I
took it
big big thank you person did not know me
but uh they just you know felt like oh
we don't need our ticket anymore so I
guess we'll give it to someone else
lucky NPC encounter
hmm
let's read this one two three four five
the mountain is alive oh wow that was
not helpful at all
yeah so then I went all the way to the
meeting point that me and my friends
decided on
um but then
really after walking down that those
oh those
um basically one station to the other
station
my feet had blisters so I needed some
some Band-Aids so I got my friend
because I I really couldn't move anymore
at this point so I got my friends to buy
me some blister Band-Aids
very nice to get them for me thank you
arigata thanks am I supposed to make
like uh what
the [\h__\h]
pack
does this actually have a real meaning
[Music]
I should
what
did I miss a torch
good question
I don't think I did
ah
number of torches it's not like I can I
guess I have to put the the one I have
back to where I got it from
oh
no one two three four five six seven
eight nine
ten
[Music]
I can't undo it can I
oh yeah
thank you
I can't undo it
ah oh my God you guys uh
you guys
one two three four five six seven oh you
make me feel like eleven
[Laughter]
oh there we go thank you for the hint
chat
anyway okay so I got the I got the band
names and I
put the Band-Aids on after that
everything was fine and then I hung out
with my friends one thing I saw
and this is you know this is an Austrian
convention so I did not expect to see
any whole life cosplayers but I saw one
good at cosplayer
she was carrying
um like a bag of McDonald's
I took a photo from her from behind when
she was Far Away walking away with the
McDonald's and I thought it was a funny
photo
one girl cosplayer yeah yeah I thought
it was accurate
but the fast food junk food
hmm
yeah
one of the Woods
is the achievement I got from that we
are now
in the world a whole new world oh
what was that
it's me
you said a secret tunnel are you a guest
be my guest how to tell fumble
bye-bye
a rotten rotting wooden chest maybe
don't open it yeah well it's okay I
don't wanna
so Mal Dewey shelves storage containers
that smell vaguely of food
Disney dmc-a-r-t-a let's go
wait I want to see was there like a
thing
I don't know okay
huh
[Music]
oh cute music
capital
City
maybe but it's not like I can sing
Disney haha
gold shaped marking yeah we heard about
the goats
oh hello you look funny oh hello okay
what's that accent supposed to be
oh no that you have chosen to stay with
us
[Music]
our entrance
showing up during the last eruption just
over there we've tried pushing it
breaking it holding it good names it
refuses to move
[Music]
any face the first George is free of
charge so I'll let my sibling snow here
they run the Lords with me
tonight let's take excellent care of her
foreign
[Music]
beautiful
oh wait can I not enter
sorry
that goes up here
purple plants they smell of sulfur but
so does everything else
we can't go past this huh okay
huge Rock seems mildly offended
cool cool very cool
hi there just checking out the area
to dining hall and kitchen up
don't forget to stop a glorious lava
Fountain before you move on Sample
sample you glorious lava fountain
[Music]
strong electromagnetic field on the
ground please avoid use of delicate
instruments
why are you telling me that
sauce
[Music]
I can't move these ones
it seems
but it says go up so
no
is this what you want
foreign
[Music]
tell me more
please forgive my rudeness early and we
just usually don't have guests arriving
from a storage room that is but we're
very we're very very I mean very happy
to have you why what is the difference
very very very very very very very
okay if you need anything my name is
pink I'm the youngest of the Palma
family my siblings and I will make you
showing your stains are lasting and
comfortable also make sure that it
contains an absolute minimum of lava
related injury may I give you a tour of
our grounds yes please I'm currently in
our grand lobby as you can see and just
below us you'll find a world famous lava
Fountain
it's like a chocolate fountain except
instead of chocolate it's full of
therapy face wilting llama yeah
laughs please don't eat it hmm I'm not
planning to but I want to see this lava
[Music]
oh wait I understand
I understand
I understand I have to connect them
above ground
to change what's on the ground
[Music]
on look at her dancing
spectacular isn't it guess travel from
all over the world to our lava Fountain
some of them throw coins and then make a
wish but they usually just end up listen
they hadn't stood so close to the
fountains
I think if you throw a coin in there
a certain column somewhere will cry
Golden Tears
please watch your step
a show we have a wrap and sometimes it
is an active volcano after all but
there's no need to concern Manuel from
our volcano calendar very closely we
always take the necessary precautions
and we're not due for an eruption
anytime soon
now that we all feel safe let's continue
the time I'm going to run ahead to make
sure our geyser elevator is working we
weren't expecting guests so soon I'll
meet you back in the ground Lobby and
we'll head to the kitchen next yeah
why does it look so delicious honestly
it does not look delicious
but that one's attached
touch touch
oh
it's still the same right
observe man Keep Your Arms by your sides
and simply step onto the elbow oh does
that blow me up no way
wow
[Music]
let's go
nice oh look at the boobs Mountain Bird
is this
bird can if you're lucky you'll be able
to witness out Birds
small
I want to see
[Music]
let's bring it a bit closer
oopsie
and got this one here
whoa hot hot huge thingy van smells like
cooking
whoa oh wow what are we cooking
wait there's another one
more gold shaped markings yeah yeah did
I miss one
oh oh Place something you could eat off
of them let's literally what you do with
plates
[Music]
funny man
is that a carrot
organic pineapple rare wait is that a
thing
organic pineapple
it's not a thing not really I mean you
can grill a pineapple I guess
that's what they call
that maybe
okay sorry to disappoint everyone it's
not a fan don't
Kiana
build the stones of all sizes impressive
uh-huh
[Music]
12. [\h__\h] you
no
I am 11.
there's a kitten Elsa world famous in
which we prepare a variety of some
church dishes for our guests you won't
believe how few will get sick middle is
our head chef she's a superb cook braced
swamp yams sour Mountain Nettles crispy
Cactus loves with good butter
here I go making myself hungry goat
butter
mmm
where are we now oh
not it
oh huge dining table beep huge plates
too
hello ma'am you must be a special guest
I hope you're hungry as of already
preparing and started preparing a most
renowned dish Ash smoked honey bird
no honey
you're right to gasp well because we're
out of seasoned Ash blooms are a bit
unpredictable so it may take a bit
longer than usual we're at the mercy of
the mountain I'm afraid but it will be
worth the wait
ah should I help you guys with the
cooking I know a thing or two about
cooking burps
[Music]
but migrating whoa where you going don't
fall into there you're gonna eat you oh
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
it escaped up another one oh God it's
hard to open your [\h__\h] eyes man
you stupid burp you stupid bub
ba
let's see
okay I'm soon as wait now now that I saw
the burp can I go down again
or no
no
wait it's flying on the map so I think I
know what to do I have to once it's over
there on this part of the map
I have to lead it somewhere
but I don't know you know I don't know
how far
what's the goal
what is the goal I wonder
what
I mean
oh we can roast it several times
will it go left now
[Laughter]
oh my God is it getting redder I feel
like the color color changed
it's a special roasting technique
so take a good look take a good look
I don't really like that
oh
no I killed the bird no that's so brutal
oh is that how they did it before
Robin's existed sure they had this
possibility to change the ways of the
maps yeah yeah
oh I got the burb I can surely Rescue It
foreign
new piece of map
the couch
[Music]
how do I reach the goat
if I place it like that maybe
because I'm hoping this platform yeah
will bring me up
I'll head back to the lobby okay okay
she really wants to eat first okay okay
okay
I think I'm ready now
to eat
oh Pat from underground oh yeah maybe
maybe
truth
[Music]
wait let me turn that in a way so that I
can access it right away
I got the bub girl mother
whoa what a beauty I guess don't usually
catch her own dinner but it's certainly
faster thanks for the help I can't wait
to hear what you think have a seat and
I'll be right back with the rest of your
mail
oh okay
I'm being forced to eat you guys it's
not my fault
thanks for to the mountain for this
bounty let's dig in and then I can eat
more birds than you
um I I think I am the master of bird
eating I'm sorry
about space
[Music]
hahaha
that was so fast wow you ate 20 Smokey
Birds I only remember making one
what do I get for that
nothing
nothing burp then what do you think
yay I'm so glad you liked it
I think that was her basketball again
you can continue the toy Short Line just
need a moment to digest I'll meet you at
the guest rooms okay bye bye I'm meeting
a goat now
[Music]
greatest of them all
hmm
good for baby oh my God
the ghosts are creepily with their
creepy eyes don't don't do that they're
not that creepy
hey goats what's up
[Music]
where where would that lead me
oh my God
am I back in the beginning
look look good oh where's Hill I thought
it was gonna be a goat
my mom I didn't expect you to beat me
here I'd hate you for you to get lost in
the palatial estate anyways welcome to
your quarters we put you in the Master
Seat communally located directly above
the hot spring world famous wolf my
brother Indo and lingo are waiting
nearby to assist you
oh it looks like a fancy Spa
I mean not really fancy I mean but you
know like a like a really they know what
how they do their [\h__\h] kind of spa
pamphlets welcome to Goat Grotto
smallest rock you've ever seen
Nature's spiciest water hotel liability
and you honey bird can surf or indulge
it's a good question
[Music]
ostrich
can I get a massage please
[Music]
[Laughter]
You Must Be Our Guest I'm not sure how
you made it there but we're very happy
to have you you must be exhausted after
exploring of many amenities want to like
to rest briefly you know Innovative
slate bed it's quiet it's overnight
thing
and look up here inside whenever I've
ever seen one place lie down and make
yourself comfortable let the racks work
the magic I don't know how the [\h__\h] I'm
speaking right now
you're failing it's a fact the rock
stimulate your pressure points literally
paying attention and time swearing the
energy until yeah oh yeah stare at that
but then yeah let it flow into each of
your limbs roaming your car and
massaging your muscles there's nothing
else quite like it
foreign
do I have to get naked nake I don't want
to
know
[Music]
is this water no
Stone pillow
this is not the kind of hot spring that
I know
is this one oh
hello
I apologize ma'am our hot spring is
currently never not a hot normal spring
it's more of a cold Northern really what
what
is that possible
I won the full refund
what the [\h__\h]
refund I demand the refund
I came here for the hot springs
ah [\h__\h]
should work
I've been scammed Bamboozled quite
possibly oh [\h__\h] I'd have to turn it God
damn it
I wish I could see it already at the top
[Music]
foreign
in the Rock and Another Piece of map
is that volcano calendar calendar
today's forecast says Ashley with a
Chance of fireballs Pleasant
don't miss the hot spring it's my
favorite part of the world
we'll wrap up the tour once you all
warmed up she might be my favorite NPC
in this game
I like her attitude
[Music]
shame Spring's not working oh well it
won't make them work
oh see he's gone
he's gone maybe he's up and the new new
spot
oh
um it looks like they want a sponge it's
clogged up there we should be way more
relaxed by now
the real world pool apologize if you've
seen the signs delayed we should
probably move the sign
are we meeting in the grand Lobby again
or what
[Music]
to dining hall and kitchen
ah I'm confused
let's go up yeah
[Music]
what is it with these goats they must
have some Secret
that they're not willing to tell me yet
hello you're still here
[Music]
can I get a second meal
I I I'm kind of hungry you know
and
here
dude dude
new tile oh
which one that one [\h__\h]
can I go back
up say I didn't forget that yeah
goats tend to Define each other that's
true
yeah I've seen pictures of goats being
in funny places
huh
the goats
we need to go to go to tuber
Skyrim animals
I forgot another thing what do you mean
what
[Music]
did I forget this time oh look at that
whoa whoa I kicked something loose
oopsie there we go Hot Springs
well the spring has sprung but the hot
has yet to hit perhaps Rambo knows
what's wrong
could you check the fumble in the ground
Lobby I'm a little underdressed
could
you could put on some clothes I don't
know seems like a simple enough solution
okay I'll go
I think he just wanted to chill and cool
down a little bit
[Music]
and he made up a stupid excuse for it
yeah that is already the greatest of
them all
[Music]
I'm gold I'm gold I've been told before
that my sheep impression sounds like a
goat
is that what it was
so I guess in theory I already did um go
before
[Music]
oh
welcoming at the moment my apologies
I'll hit the most people from today
but could you have a look at it you seem
to have a good chance before things to
be together I think of it is a secret
extra tour together
oh God are we gonna ride a goat let's go
oh heater is located
it's only accessible we are good
news
mouth oh are we talking carrots we're
talking carrots
okay let's go back to the Cults against
[Music]
let me tell you one more thing
about the Comic-Con where am I though
Comic-Con Comic-Con went to the wrong
place and I found one one
in the in the in the artist alley I
found one one booth that had some
somehow live Prince and merchandise
pillows and stuff
that's the only one I saw but I mean
understandable most of it was like
focused on
you know
Comics related stuff like us and yeah
well I was happy to see at least one
representation of whole life there
yeah wait did I just come from here I'm
confused
[Music]
yeah pillows keychains
Prince I thought you I love friends hmm
but I've seen that person's art before
in my art hashtag
yeah looked familiar to me hey yo I have
a carrot you want the carrot come on
okay let me start you
[Music]
are we going to volcano crater
maybe
[Music]
thank you God
whoa wow no no
no no no no
please
Sam Sam I'm sorry Sam I can't bro
wait have I have I had a sad face this
whole [\h__\h] time
why is someone telling me
throw the cats into the fire do it
you didn't tell me
why didn't you ask me koala why are you
so sad
why didn't you not tell me
no neck crack
[Music]
I was on purpose for a minute maybe but
not the whole time
I look cute or sad
that doesn't that's that doesn't make me
happy
[Music]
I was trying to see how long it would
take no wait just tell me
damn it
thanks for helping us out ma'am we're
probably risking our lives but you can't
put a price on Comfort let's get to that
heat let's get the heater fixed you
should be prepared uh for anything down
there ma'am
anyways head on down and I'll read you
instructions from up here oh
yeah it was in a safe place I'm your
[\h__\h] guest
give the ramp attack when you get to the
bottom
um I'm hoping I don't get to the very
uh
that's unexpected yeah yeah okay
hi
okay listen carefully first head to the
big wall at the back
back
what do you see us back
where is the back is up back or is down
back or is right back
is is up back
uh I think it's up yeah
big wall
here okay
do you think the free switches flip the
one on the left
okay
[Music]
just kidding head to the middle and put
your hands on the wheel I was gonna
dance do you do you do you say YouTube
all right you're going to need
[Music]
first turn left twice left
turn right three times
turn left twice
turn right one wow
[Music]
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h]
um uh what
help
s
[Music]
is this a bug
oh
[Music]
do I die
what
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
Maybe
I was like oh oh oh maybe the lava will
go away when I turn it a lot of times
like shake it away but no I made it I
made a big air
look at this little [\h__\h] laughing at me
at me about to die look at this big
[\h__\h] smile
sing she's dancing
is this like some kind of cult or
something
oh my God unbelievable
is going to wrap why are you all here we
have to get flies possible you [\h__\h]
idiots
only half of 10 times before
I got that out of a slight man what's
everyone yelling about
oh boy that tall lava is going to feel
so good in my cold body I assume
oh I hope I'm allowed to collect all the
Smoky Birds after it blows
okay um are we gonna go or are we just
chilling
okay ah we have to get as far oh wait
maybe I should go over here and then I
move the move it away
yeah wow what is that
I saved everyone
well what's the smokey smokey Hot Like a
Phoenix yeah whoa
no that's just
it's time
um
[Music]
laughs
I I need to get away from these people
these people aren't saying they don't
care about my safety at all
Hunter so springy I love it okay
okay
oh it's so relaxing eruption inspired me
black and Cave news with fire and rock
candy
man
sorry
[Music]
she's so happy
like just yeah just say you're happy
kaido until you leave and then you give
them a bad review because if you give
them a bad review while you're still
here they might not let you out of life
then remember to tell your friends how
safe it was
I totally will
that it's for you please pick it up in
the grand Lobby when you check out
okay
well that was the exit of toilets trees
toiletries
[Music]
we can go to Grand Lobby now directly
thank God thank you yo it's always at
the gold spot now
up
gold ready at all times look at that
it's open
oh no you already survive for you
I miss you
did you see dear option what aside I
just barely escaped could you not
[\h__\h] wait for one [\h__\h] second you
see how we continuously miss each other
if you would just wait for five minutes
in one spot I probably would not miss
you
that volcano seemed to move at the last
moment how fortunate or perhaps you're
getting better with your map you clever
girl I hope you got away safely too I'm
not convinced anyone knows how to read
that damn Galaxy the smoke is making it
a bit hard to navigate and my engine is
close to overheating there's an iceberg
at the edge of the world I'm going to
swing by to cool things down and let the
skies clear meet me there if you can
love Granny uh I will try maybe that's
the last World hopefully
because uh my throat would like a break
I wanted to leave the volcano yeah bye
bye suckers you didn't kill me hooray
I'm alive
and maybe she's testing me maybe she
wants me to learn about everything you
know oh we're back in the forest
oh
the boat maybe with the boat we can go
now then why was it here last time
though
anyway I guess we'll go into the house
first it seems um to be our meeting
point now
hi I'm so glad you're back I could
really use your help
um what's it this time
I'm just I'm feeling a little homesick I
thought I'd feel better if I could read
about my Island maybe even find a way to
sail back there's a boat out there
but I can't find any books about it the
Storyteller said he'd help me but I
thank you forgot
I didn't forget you whipper snapper I've
just been busy cleaning up downstairs
someone made a proper mess but right
while rifling through our collection
I'm sure she didn't mean it whomever it
was she was just eager and inconsiderate
maybe she should watch kiwawa's VOD of
cookie yummy one two and three to learn
how to be more considerate well if you
girls can get things squared away
downstairs I'll have some more time to
help I could look for our files and let
you know what I find
of course we can do that
arranging things
[Music]
yeah I'll I'll arrange it
hmm
I'm fine thank you I'm fine
thanks for being so considerate Jackson
okay wait uh okay Wayne we just show us
what to do you know it's all sounds so
similar to the book I'm reading for no
matter follow me downstairs wait wait
wait wait is it this book that's right
here
[Music]
she went up there automatically
most of the books put away but these
boxes need to be moved
can you transfer them from the left bed
to the right mat just make sure to keep
small boxes
okay stop talking stop talking just let
me know yeah yeah bye-bye
I see
what did he say in the middle it needs
to be in the middle well that's too easy
I know to the very right did he say to
the very right
okay
it was very right
hey Google what are you doing
okay I'll tell him I want to know
um I'm done
let me read this first
return for the volcano it looks like we
singed she needs to meet her Granny on
the iceberg and no idea how to get there
but if I just had a good friend needed
her help
it's already let me have a look
I didn't even have to have to leave it
was like so fast
find box worked at next batch is ready
for you it's a shade trickier effects ah
all right let's see I see
[Music]
I can only move one at a time
I see I see uh all the way to the right
I suppose
ah wait I have an idea yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay base is there uh what
[Music]
is there what is there
to the stair put this here but it's
there there we go let's go
classic puzzle
[Music]
you have another one come at me bro
one last badge okay
oh
[Music]
where are they in the other room oh my
God
foreign
[Music]
to the very right
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
easy yeah
yeah that was fast I figured that one
out fast
okay uh
can I already move it
yeah okay
every time
well I thought you'd never do that I was
just [\h__\h] around with you
how the [\h__\h] did you do that oh my God
what this lady is stronger than me maybe
I should hire her
no
I want to talk to you things are looking
tiny in the universe or godsend I found
the sailing book your friend was looking
for is in the island wing okay
hooray huh
so much about the culture of my Island
here and some of our Traditions happen
on other Islands too I always thought it
was just us I thought so too
spending our days living within and full
of soil most earthworms are experts on
the matter it is said that if you give
salt to a worm they can point towards
its source donut album All worms are
created equal and some are more accurate
than others many have been LED astray by
an over eager yet unskilled Worm but for
those looking for a little help finding
their way home the red worm can be the
invaluable companion
huh
what
I don't think she cares about this
oh maybe there is
maybe it matters
there's a way to navigate the ocean
using Seoul from your destination I'm
glad we grabbed some all right
we did
oh yeah
now I just need to warm to sniff it out
hmm
I still have the worm
I had a warm on your the whole time
yeah gross but I was like
eel how is it still alive I have
everything we need I think it's time to
sell did I luckily grab the right book
right away I know I'm not supposed to
buy I just need to see everyone but even
from afar
oh I think that's good
I didn't even ask about your feelings
you find out anything about your granny
how was the volcano
shaky
I'm so glad she's saved and she wants to
meet you on an iceberg
my people have spoken of such a place
near the edge of the world I don't know
how to get there but perhaps they do
I already headed back to the island so
we can find out more there you can ask
around and I'll do some shopping what do
you say cartoon will you come back to my
island with me of course
come on great let's get back to the Bone
I did a lot of reading while you were
gone and it was great but it turns out
the theater of the mind can't beat the
spray of salt water on your face I'm
excited to get back out there
what if we go to the island and
everyone's gone
like really dramatic
really sad and depressing
maybe they're all like you know
killed
showing after her best friend's little
cartographer left the store Chalet the
blue haired girl's mind started to drift
she imagined her people back on your
Island laughing and fishing and she
missed him greatly she made up her mind
to return home to visit them instead of
sail however she was quickly swabbed by
heavy ocean fog and her Compass stopped
working huh
several times in vain before giving up
and sadly sailing back to the story
tonight though she wasn't the time to
give up so easily the blue-haired girl
decided that she would look for every
book in The Chalet until she found a way
to navigate home she headed downstairs
inside the rifling for books this book
you know there's this one book that
tells the whole story about me and this
is a book that tells the whole story
about her
cute there's a reason why people of
certain traps can never return home
after the sale for their Coming of Age
it used to be that's some who left would
try to sell home only to be floated by
the ocean or bad weather
their families would never know the
truth of what happened or assume they
didn't want to visit
by following this new tradition parents
can better prepare for the pain of never
seeing their children again it will
never be easy but they'll know what to
expect of tough but needed tradition
Oh by telling them to never come back
you at least don't you know have to
question yourself
why isn't she coming back is she or her
he dead
because you told them to not come back
so they could be alive
it gives you hope I guess but that's a
weird way of doing it in my opinion
friend was set to sail yeah they'd
return to the island where they began
with the help of a wrinkly companion and
somewhere far beyond that Granny's
Iceberg loomed large
all right let's go
both time let's cruise uh you take the
song I'll take the sail and we'll keep a
close eye on warm body okay
back on the high scenes
[Music]
ah
uh anyway it's so good to be sailing
again
I don't think your map will help us this
time that's what's that warm-up to
ah okay it's going down there which way
do we go uh
Southeast
I need a moment guys you don't have to
tell me
getting kind of foggy
huh
uh what the [\h__\h]
it's a good question you want to think
about it take your time
uh well I guess South
can't my worm just be straight
and let's go south it doesn't feel right
huh
oh it made an end oh we should have just
looked upwards then okay okay
North okay okay
nice she tells me that I'm kind of wrong
okay
ah well that was fast what the [\h__\h]
smartworm
what was that oh dude you guys look
familiar with this moment sir you've
never seen us before well that makes
sense huh
oh that was close
wait why why would you not want to be
found
uh
[Music]
let's fill up divide the boat into two
pieces sell toward 11 o'clock turn
around we're headed toward a dead end
I don't know
that seems the most logical thing to me
we're in the lake wait that's maybe good
we I don't think we I've seen I want to
see maybe we were never on the middle of
a lake before
question mark
why not keep on pushing that
a question mark
sell clockwise and then go straight yeah
oh
do it
ah
yeah
was that the right answer
and that's your highlight but we made it
great job everyone I can't believe we're
really back here you and you're screw me
friend don't quite a team try to end F1
Wiggles I'm going to wriggles
okay let's put up and look for Clues to
the iceberg we can meet back here when
we have some info I'm going to stay out
of sight since I'm not supposed to be
back here well you're not even gonna say
hi
I know it's just a tradition but it's
important to my family see you back here
in a Bitcoin
that's so sad but at least we already
saw they're alive
[Music]
[Applause]
but go shooting on review of course he
isn't there you know the tradition oh
yes of course well please give her a
huge player hug if you see her we miss
her Julie have you traveled back here
for the fishing Festival it only happens
a few times a month that's pretty often
I'm gonna have the lonely overall rod
and bobber
Maybe
think again for a company we hope she's
doing one of them feels I love for her
even from afar we think about her all
the time can you go sail a whole Arch
pulago
she's a born Adventurer and you should
take to it once she got a taste she just
had to get out of her comfort zone
[Music]
are you following me
oh my God such a [\h__\h] mess who left
this place in such a mess huh
cool
who the [\h__\h] did that
[Music]
okay it's time to cancel past kiwawa
same problem
Ahoy but to learn I hope he travels I've
treated you well once again your timing
is fortunate a four-hour fishing
Festival is upon us call it a festival
but don't tell my wife ah stop trying to
make Festival a thing it's not gonna
happen
full will be held nearby at big fish
look
we'll have fishing competition NATO is
always welcome they won't let me enter
since I'm a fisherman but trade but that
means I get to be the host with an owner
I think we have to participate
[Music]
how more how much longer do I have I
wonder how much more voices do I have to
make
the fact that we circled back here is a
good sign at least
I think two chapters so Two Worlds this
one and the ice World Maybe
can you guys read for yourself for a
little bit
um
foreign
at the end of the world
oh
cold weather builds character
that's why I know from people are so
nice huh
[Music]
chickens can't read of course you can
even yourself you just didn't know you
had the skill
[Music]
oh the price is a map okay now we have
to participate
but I never fished before
oh
oh she's back there
[Music]
okay okay
coming back
[Music]
foreign
time to learn how to fish yeah I mean
why not yeah I don't know anyone who can
fish though
ah
that's a big Blair hug
oh was that for my dad hey I really
missed everyone but oh no this is so sad
oh but I'm glad I got to see them from
afar at least oh
oh can we at least tell her parents you
know I saw her five minutes ago she's
doing fine
to find your granny we need to get to
the iceberg we need an ocean map yeah I
know yeah
[Music]
we don't plan let's go finishing the
festival takes place and big fish lost
nearby it's our biggest look at our Lake
you can probably guess what it's shaped
like like a hole I still don't want
anyone to recognize me though
I'll be right back are you gonna dress
up
[Music]
you're gonna look so sad people aren't
gonna question who you are like everyone
knows everyone on this island
there's no way to recognize me now I'm
great to go I'm ready to go they might
recognize me but maybe they just won't
say anything
oh wait there's the the
I mean this one
does she mean this place for the fishing
Festival
no no one's here
maybe I have to make another place
she said big
big she said oh
wait that's like a fish mouth
foreign
look at that I can make something funny
[Music]
um but that was not it
ah
let me ask her again
she did say yeah whole
oh look at that fish oh
what
uh Rhiannon as your name is now help
Big Fish love is a fishy looking Lake
nearby
well okay I mean
ah wait I should I just [\h__\h] turn it
it's not that wait
we'll make it a bit longer maybe how
about that
long long fish
[Music]
no
wait I've never been to that piece of
map before apparently how come
[Music]
okay now I've been there
chicken
[Music]
maybe let me look what I have
I would have thought that's it
[Music]
why is that not it
does it have to be a certain direction
or
foreign
[Music]
we'll get there eventually
no
no no
no no the split River looks like a tail
hmm
a weird tail okay
imagination
and then
maybe this here and then this there but
um
[Music]
that's a huge Lake now but it's not what
they want apparently
[Music]
um
foreign
that doesn't look like a fish at all ah
[Music]
ah wait
maybe we need another hole in the middle
you know look
is whole in German but what do you want
on the sides girl
[Music]
what do you want
that makes no sense either
well maybe like this no
oh
[Music]
just wait okay how about we make the
biggest fish possible
oh wait we make we make EV we use
everything
[Music]
foreign
this could look pretty good
it's like a fountain
what that's it that looks ridiculous
ah
hi let's go
so every piece of Lake River had to be
connected
[Laughter]
yeah
oh well we're figuring it out so proud
we have two Outsiders in the competition
this time very exciting best of luck to
your Rihanna Man and friend not
suspicious at all that I am with this
person and has a name that sounds so
familiar to shiannon huh
you get hooked up funny the Mario
brothers are safely locked away
our rules are the same as always first
one to collect every type of fish wins
oh my God but how do I fish what
God I didn't know it was me when really
you think maybe he did notice you know
he just didn't say anything
um
can I lose this competition or can I
only win
I wonder
is there is there special
maybe fine do I have to stay there can I
don't just not just go
here and try the fish over there now
okay I'll ask her
well I'll talk to him too
no one will tell me which only one way
to find out same for me yo
I always look at how relaxing this is
even when the stakes are high it's just
nice to slow down I remember when my dad
taught me to fish he never caught
anything himself so I'd throw back any
fish I caught before he saw them I
didn't want to make him feel bad oh well
tell me how to fish oh
[Music]
you see it the boy
on the top right I feel like he's
telling me that there's a good fishing
spot
especially I drew them for you
thank you
Okay pink fish orange fish blue fish
green fish
thank you don't show anyone else has a
secret
you have to give it back after the
competition no I don't wanna
how do I know
there's more to this I'm telling you
I love fresh fish this one won't grow up
into a picky eater believe me I won't
stand for it eyes color slippers ill
they're good for a growing girl in a day
so beautiful
[Music]
uh
no thank you
[Music]
thank you from a five-time champion the
secret is choosing the best one while
I'm railing in your Rod the moment you
see the bobber bobbing uh-huh
[Music]
is there a right spot
I remember teaching on how to fit she
just couldn't get their hangover poor
thing huh cast weight real is so simple
I don't think she caught a single fish
but she never stopped drinking
yeah yeah yeah yeah she sucks she sucks
at fishing
[Music]
oh oh wait oh yeah yeah maybe I should
look at the drawing
tell me something wait um
no
I understand
I think
yeah
maybe yeah I think I think
[Music]
ah wait
I'm I remake the shape of the fish so
this is supposed to be the blue one
but there's a little little thing down
there
which looks like this but how how do I
connected wait can I is it okay if it's
shorter than this if that's um
what now it needs to be longer it can't
just be this right that doesn't quite
look like it also I'm not even on the
map anymore then
um
[Music]
oh God what
ah
okay
so
this goes here and this goes here
and then this goes here
ah but know that huh
[Music]
it's like almost like that
oh wait
like this
huh and now I fish and I get something
maybe
oh
that looks like it no
look at the bottom right one
I guess maybe I have to use all of them
okay okay I can make it longer it looks
like it's a bit longer there anyway
it doesn't look that long though
oh
the water
thing
where's my fish
let's go
oh okay next one next one next one
let's try to make the pink one oh God
um the the zigzag is on the bottom
okay
[Music]
Tic Tac is on the bottom
uh
to the side to the side to the side to
the right side
so
then don't I need this one here
no
[Music]
foreign
got it
big thinking
thank you that's so long
[Music]
Now's the Time catch the
feel weird [\h__\h]
funny one okay let's do the green one
zigzag on the side
and pretty early on curve to the right
okay
I already forgot what I just saw
but
I think it's relatively simple
like this
first try
oopsie no no
foreign
in Japanese
and koi is fish I made a pond salad
koi
okay last one the orange one
as a curve okay Spike downwards curve
and yeah okay
I I totally get it I told to get it
Spike
[\h__\h]
uh downwards
like so and there's uh I think like this
like this
something like that it's not quite Maybe
oh it was correct yeah
[Applause]
amazing
wow we got all of them should I give the
notes back now
it seems someone may have caught all the
fish types here
[Music]
yeah
gonna come over and
give you the fish
wait let me give you back the map
yeah they look exactly like the drawings
okay but you don't want the map back all
right fine with me
foreign
cool fish you got on this island kind of
crazy
wow they look so colorful
um one of each time the winner of the
competition is me and my friend price is
mine yay
yeah
yeah oh that was cute that was fun cute
um
it's been great seeing you again kid but
I imagine you have other Islands to
visit especially with that fancy new
ocean map you want I have so much I want
to ask you about xi'anon but I suppose
your life is her own now tell me though
is she well she happy very much so
that puts my mind at ease
mine too thank you for being such a good
friend to her you're welcome back
anytime thank you
Now put on some pants dude you're in
your underpants the whole time
she doesn't talk she's she doesn't speak
English sorry guys
um
farewell
let's go oh back on the boat
hey Kato
thanks for doing that with me
I was really happy to see that my
parents and everyone else were doing
well even if my dad still can't catch a
fish to save his life you helped me get
home and reunite with my people and now
it's time for me to help you do the same
we're going to find your granny I just
know it
to the end of the world I'm oh hi
behind
wow
it's Christmas music
wow we made it oh it's so beautiful here
I've never seen snow like this before
Last Christmas I gave you my heart
soon soon those stores are gonna start
playing Christmas music guys
I'd better keep the boat moving before
it freezes the in the ice if you want to
start looking for your granny I'll come
find you once I've found a safe place to
talk
okay
[Music]
uh the music is pretty
whoa what is that creature
over there
can I do some ice fishing
oh hello
oh hello oh hello
[Music]
but didn't expect to grab a new friend
though you don't look nearly warm enough
with the snowflake
stack my scarf to keep you toasted thank
you so sweet
can I put it on I'm glad you like it I
have plenty more where that came from
we'll need to support each other to live
in the house place like this look like
you traveled a long way to get here I
hope you find whatever it is you're
looking for
thank you sweetie and like your your hat
has like squirrel ears or barriers or
whatever really cute
give me
take that piece of map what the [\h__\h] uh
maybe she will dock here eventually
even though it says it's not safe though
oh well
oh wow
that's a huge piece of map oh are we
playing touch
every for real
but it can't get through here can I
oh yeah oh yeah
foreign
[Music]
to fix the bridge and ah once you fix it
it's safe enough to
stop here okay wait what let me let me
think about this
here how about this
how about how about this huh
yeah that works if I first
if I first go over here
then
then that should work
wait huh
all right
yeah this should work no no
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
how did I do that we will never know
well he could erase it himself now if he
wanted to
uh-huh
I got the backpack maybe the Rope is
useful too no no
okay okay okay
oh actually
um I forgot to say
on the on this on Saturday you know I
wrote on the schedule and then I'm doing
meet and greets but actually
um
as I said I also went to the uh Comic
Con on the same day so I woke up I did
meet and greets
from like 12
to like one o'clock or so and then I got
ready for the Comic Con and then I went
to the Comic Con and I spent the whole
day there and then uh I we had like
McDonald's food
and then uh I hurried back home
I was like back home 30 minutes before
the before the
um meet and greet and that was really
really tired at that point
because the day felt so crazy long I
realized once again
holy [\h__\h]
when you actually do so much in one day
and like go outside and socialize and
stuff
then the day feels like double the
length it was crazy
that so I got home and I started the
last two hours of meet and greets and
like 10 p.m I got done at midnight
so I was busy the whole day with no
break and it was really exhausting too
because
um when I woke up I only had time for
one little small piece of of bread like
a tiny one a soft soft tiny bread
and that's that was my breakfast and
then until until around 8pm
9pm
I did not eat a thing that's when I eat
ate some McDonald's and until then I was
like suffering
from Hunger I thought I was gonna starve
to death the the hunger was so strong
that I had back pain and everything pain
um
yeah authentic con experience I don't
know why I didn't get any food earlier
and but yeah
oh I was really hungry so the McDonald's
was biggest salvation ever
um
and then I went back and I quickly did
some meet and greets for two hours which
was really fun
I feel bad for showing you food it's
okay it's okay wait was that the second
slot and at that point I already had
food don't worry
but no I guess not that was no no it was
not it was it was the first thought
wasn't it because it was still bright
outside yeah yeah yeah
oh don't worry about it at that point I
wasn't that hungry only afterwards I got
really hungry
but yeah the original plan for me was
like
um I have in mind that this convention
was happening on that weekend but I
wasn't sure if I was gonna go and then
the meet and greet dates I offered some
dates to my management and they got back
to me kind of late on like which date
they're going with so uh I wasn't really
sure if I was gonna go to the convention
or not until like
like like recently
but then yeah I tried to plan it so that
it's not too obvious that I'm going
there
I knew it at the beginning of the week
already that I was planning to go but I
didn't want it to be too obvious that's
why I I tried to convince you guys that
I was just you know doing other stuff
like meet and greets and then you know
yeah
for safety you know need some privacy
yeah here's your backpack cornichon
fix it please
that question oh that question I was on
purpose at that point I was like about
to leave anyway
um but I'll tell you what happened there
I want to talk about it
[Music]
nice thankful thanks singing
goats
these Bridges have become our lifelines
I need to tend to the other Bridges but
I'll owe you a gherkin
why is this not water
oh wait
I mean it was obvious because I I saw
There Were Trees here and still still I
I kept on saying our boat will come here
no
I'm stupid oh wait did he make a double
one over there was that already there
interesting
uh wait I'll go
uh back up
and I'll go like here and then
I'll go well that that still doesn't
work
let me try
heck wait no I'm super confused I
shouldn't have done that then I don't
know which which bridge is which one I I
keep it like this
uh
foreign
[Music]
I'm confused
what
ah maybe maybe maybe
Maybe
maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe maybe
maybe maybe maybe maybe
I can go for the forest maybe is what
I'm thinking
which is kind of like I feel like
a big big um
inconvenience but okay
[Music]
like this no like this hey I can do this
way maybe not the best way but
I got the map the piece of map this is
also a big one it's also a big one oh
we're handling big Maps now
I'm a big girl I'm a big big girl and a
big big world is
if you need me
[Music]
[\h__\h] I am on this piece of map now but
not exactly where I wanted to be
I can do this no no I can't never mind
uh
this works but that doesn't help me I'm
stuck
uh
huh
some of you gave me a [\h__\h] shock High
smoothie in my beautiful baby
okay I'm here where am I even trying to
go right now ah
uh here no here
yeah that could work
[Music]
this movie has entered the room yeah
um someone else what else I I saw the
whole life a fan fan booth and and I
bought I bought some
some nice on that day that I wanted to
show you
what time is oh my God it's almost
midnight am I finishing this game soon
please say yes
slippery ice ahead
but can I show you now since I was
listening I just mentioned it and I'm
talking about it now I'll show you now
so I took a video of the of the stuff
that I bought I wanted to show you
because I thought it was geniusly cute I
was looking for something I liked and I
found something nice let me show you
wish
really cute
and we have these stickers candles
Adventure
really cute and frogs I was happy to see
some frogs
stickers I don't know what to do with
the stickers but they were cute so I
bought them
then we have Oishi nickel some some cats
that you can eat
yeah
uh-huh very cute and since I bought
three sets of stickers I got a fourth
one for free
ghost stickers I bought some ghost
stickers very cute spooky very spooky I
know that was very scary I'm sorry guys
and then they had some cards I was
looking for a birthday card because one
of my friends had birthday but I
couldn't find one I understand in front
of a Christmas card I'm gonna give that
to someone for Christmas
cards with pickup lines and there was
like [\h__\h] I want them I want to buy them
but like who am I gonna give those to
but this one was so cute I had to get
this one hey cutie it's cards inside
there's nothing though
and there was ah this is the big thing I
got a calendar and it's like
um famous uh art things with cats it's
so genius okay this is I really wanted
to show you this so there's January
is The Girl With a Pearl Earring by
Johannes Vermeer
uh sorry spoiler
February is flower thrower by Banksy
and March is the Kiss by Gustav Klimt
isn't this amazing
as I needed it
in April we have self-portrait by Frida
Kalo
uh-huh with the mono bro May is oh
Etsy The Birth of Venus by Sandro
Botticelli June is American Gothic by
Grant Wood
cute
oh spoil it you didn't see that
oopsie
come on come on July it's the Mona Lisa
by Leonardo da Vinci look at that Mona
Lisa in August we have the last there
is
September is the seated woman with bent
knee by aegon Sheila October is the old
guitarist by a Picasso November is
Napoleon crossing the Alps by Jacob
Louis David
sorry about the pronunciation the last
page is really hard to get with gloves
one second they are so cute right and
the last one creation of Adam by
Michelangelo
have to censor that
I really wanted to show you that
yeah it's so tedious
that was
So Sophisticated much art very beautiful
so creative
yeah that's gonna be my 2023 calendar
[Laughter]
ah I love it so much
I want one oh thank you Sal
um the name of the Creator on it so you
can go for the VOD and then look it up
and maybe they have an online shop they
might
um
okay where the hell was that going
where was I going
what
that's something
slippery eyes honestly oh
oh oh interesting oh
but I need more of that slippery eyes
because the only one is up there and I
don't have anything else
interesting
[Music]
I have to find another piece of map
um
[Music]
well freeze other water what is it
connects oh you're a [\h__\h] genius sir
wait no way are you there
oh wait
but no I can't connect this for example
connect the unfrozen water
um
would be cool yeah
oh
for [\h__\h] sake
oh come on
this this part is really difficult
thinking of the big pieces is really
difficult
I don't even know where I want to go
I guess I just wanna
go go up to the top right of this piece
[Music]
hmm
interesting I could go to the other side
and then
try
oh this works
[Music]
I'm getting over there's a challenge
though
[Music]
the challenge of its own
I hope it will be worth it
let's try to go over here
hey I'm aiming for the part that I
haven't discovered on this piece
well I guess I could also check out the
part up there if I could reach it
I'm trying guys I'm trying I'm trying
ah wait what wait wait wait ah
[Music]
here yo let's go finally finally finally
finally finally I
new piece
hello hello there you must be newcomable
travels fast around here I'm like our
icebergs
CLS moves actually move pretty slowly
the separate and drift around sometimes
for a few hours and other times for days
they always drift back together in a
different shape look since there was
seven aspects but we've only counted six
he's a great archaeologist and a king
survivalist so I believe him we all chip
in around here tickle protects us from
the ice Beast let's peace Lucy made me
this jaunty shirt out of pine needles
and firsts I've saved the entire ocean
so I helped track the movements of the
icebergs I'm sure you'll figure out your
role if you decide to stick around
my role is moving everything
and confusing you guys so you don't find
home anymore
um I see bream
the trees look like feathers to anyone
else or only me
okay we saw that and we have a new piece
which is a square
interesting
interesting it's a different
one on every corner
I could
try to go back
to the icy part where I was on before
but I also want to
um wait how about
I can try to get on
there later
whatever for now
ah
open the door please no why would you
lock it what
[Music]
ah no no
it's missing the Final Touch yeah can I
like make it into a Snowman
oh wait I have a scarf oh I have a scrap
do I need to make a snowman I have a
scarf maybe I'll find like a carrot
and I don't know stones
um okay
first oh we can we can go here
again
and I will try to
holy [\h__\h] this is this part of the game
is a big thinker for me
a big thinker
once again
[Music]
so I can oh no I can't do [\h__\h] here I
can connect it but I can't do [\h__\h]
oh
what
oh my God guys
[Music]
foreign
Norway Norway no way no way
it didn't get any bigger
[Music]
guys
[Laughter]
[Music]
movie what are you looking at
um
judging by the
um functions that we had before in this
game I understand where you're coming
from
[Music]
staring at something
I don't know what it is
because it's behind the box
[Music]
anyway I wanna I wanna finish this game
um
[Music]
I want to I can even enter this place by
going uh through the top left or the
bottom left
because it seems like the bottom left
door is not locked compared to the
others
so
[Music]
that is fine and all but
I first need to get out of here again
let's I don't know let's go here
and then
um
[Music]
stuck ah this place works
am I getting closer to it again maybe
foreign
oh I found the ice again wait no this
one I can't enter [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm trying to get some areas well I
can't reach them
hard to get to anywhere at all
[Music]
uh
I've used all my thinking devices
oh wait okay this one I can go to oh
what
give me those berries
No No Berries for me
[Music]
um hmm
no nothing here
oh yeah
[Music]
nothing
good
nothing good
okay
don't
now remove this
oh
that does not work
that's the um
wait
ah it's just a way of how I look at it
if I see it from
yeah if I see the doors from the outside
now from the inside
there's only one that's not locked
which is the one on the top right now
bottom no wait no no they're all locked
they're all locked are they
wait is this one locked or not
but this is where the Snowman is
so it's locked okay they're all locked I
think
[Music]
why the [\h__\h] I I went to the ice before
it should be possible again
um
it has to be this one okay
so
I connect
[Music]
ah okay I have an idea I think
yeah okay I have an idea
you have to focus on the path not on the
goal oh
foreign
[Music]
why the words have never been spoken
uh wait uh
wait
ah
that's your philosophical Phoenix thank
you thank you
all right all right all right let's get
going
[Music]
these don't connect
well that sucks oh
that connects possibly or maybe not but
I can
[Music]
go there which I think I haven't been
there yet let's just see ah
oh is it a free piece uh Snowman to be a
snowman
[Music]
wait
it's probably a three-piece Snowman and
I I haven't checked out on the top left
I think
so that would probably have
the last piece
and
uh
it won't let me
gets to the right place yet I suppose
all right oh wait this works no never
mind this could work or does it
no
no this doesn't work either I don't
think I can get there yet from here I
first need to do the the Snowman thing
maybe
am I sure no I am not
um
foreign
because I've been
I've been looking at it in so many
different ways it will always just lead
that to the edge of that map
never mind never mind oh
[Music]
Mamma Mia now I can go to this side
I can't go inside yet but I can go to
this can I
[Music]
yes I can yes no I can't
sir another ice piece no
oh
foreign
lost track of where I'm going
maybe maybe I can't
[Music]
oh no I'm stuck
oh oh I got it holy [\h__\h] this is
confusing
ah
and now
it's just like
the big
salvation
oh
[Music]
what
you're not denying space you're not a
beast at all well I almost saw my face
don't kill me
kill me oh so there was there was no
easy way no simple way you had to go
through of course several rotations and
several repetitions
ah hello mama let me bandage you oh
thank you have you heard Lux Legend yet
he's our leader in the renowned
Adventurer he says that one day we'll
find a precious treasure on the fabled
seventh iceberg
treasure Hunters travel great distances
when they hear our Legend
but most lose hope after time and leave
the iceberg I suppose those of us left
still hold some hope in our hearts it's
a legend where you brought you he is a
legendary part you hear no my grandma
where my grandma
I see treasure means something different
to us all I'm sure you'll find yours me
I'm hoping for some help with my hunting
my spare is getting blunt from all of
the ice boots I'm battling or doodling
in the eyes while I keep watch for them
well you all bandaged up stay cozy out
there thank you yeah
[Music]
yeah oh let's look around
no it's falling
all around me children playing
having fun
it's the season for love and
understanding
Merry Christmas everyone
Merry Christmas
everyone
we're gonna have a party tonight
[Music]
the Christmas tree beneath the
candlelight it's not fun okay okay it's
Christmas time baby oh yeah remember
yeah remember that undercut Christmas we
are kind of walking and I did oh that
was cute
thank you
um I like your scarf
thank you I will use it not for myself
but probably for a snowman I'm sorry
[Music]
um
even with these gloves my hands keep
going numb while I'm knitting oh that
sounds rough
treat
for me the treasure will be my grandma
Willow pickle
about way over Paul Jay let me tell you
about this by swearing it connects to
various biomass of the iceberg won't be
on each guide so regardless of which
were the of where the iceberg drift too
we can easily connect to them
how's that for some high school facts
baby
interesting
[Music]
okay can we at least leave oh oh yeah I
got a new one oh my God it's really
[\h__\h] tempting
uh
yeah yeah
please I need the god of Tetris to help
me here
I am art of power
can I open the door
I wonder wait a second let me just place
this here
open oh thank you please stay open thank
you
oh this one's locked from the other side
what the [\h__\h] so there was something
with those
Gates there
maybe I can oh no don't go there maybe I
can say hi to the Snowman where was the
Snowman
ah see now it stays open okay
[Music]
snowman snowman was I guess down there
in the woods
[Music]
hmm
so are you two-piece snowman or
three-piece snowman oh
it was a two-piece Snowman
here I want to use this let me use it
why not why not
trust me bro you even have already the
carrot nose
what else
oh hands oh some sticks huh
or hat a hat
okay I'll keep an eye out
um now
now we want to explore this new piece I
guess uh we can go from here
[Music]
this is the season
um love and understanding [\h__\h] I won't
get anywhere
if I go through here
Maybe
I need some help help
okay from here
Maybe
no never mind
I
I know however
nothing I know nothing
I know nothing
[Music]
can't wait till Saturday wait what's on
Saturday what's a Saturday
what's on Saturday
Oh Canada okay
Sunday is hotel by the way finally hotel
is coming back
on the thumbnail that I posted today I
did not use the new background yet but
to be honest it's like I I had it be
made so that it still looks
very similar like it still has the same
vibe
from the old one you know
[Music]
because I I wanted it to still feel
familiar
have the sense of
familiarity
cccc
you get me you'll get me hello smoothie
welcome back yeah I know it's past
midnight almost
um
I will
I will need some more tabs movie
please wait
I have no idea what I'm gonna eat
tonight
no idea
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] this is nine out of ten oh God I
started with chapter four today I think
[Music]
oh wait that fits perfectly Hill
hmm
um
okay let's let's try to go
it does that piece has no wood piece
okay I think we can't go directly I have
to go for another one let's see let's
see which one connects
that connects
eat a snare we have to go from the
bottom right there
we have to go on that dock so
easy
come on
oh oh [\h__\h]
what happens if I go into the fog
nothing
spoopy
when it's so cold it creates white fog
is that a thing in really cold places
[Music]
oh I love yellow
I'm impressed you man yeah if I only
look like they're never getting the
[\h__\h] area sometimes he joins me here
to study the Old Lighthouse he thinks it
might be related to the seven flash book
since we're too far out for most boats
can't navigate the folk myself so I
usually drift over on a nice float
what's that
I've been standing in the patterns of
the currents ever since I arrived here
just today I found this beautiful piece
of paper watch for sure
[Music]
yeah thank you I've been trying to flow
a message back to my home Island for
years I lived there more than a decade
ago but soon wait
so many people don't know
you can never tell yeah it's you
I realized that earlier than cattle
like this
[Music]
this one about I don't believe it I
recognize this carving work anywhere my
mother made this it was my home island
did you send this along for me
this makes the world thank you daily oh
must be nice to hear like from your home
for the first time in like 10 [\h__\h]
years when you're like there you don't
have a way of communicating
you far far away you have no idea what
they're doing how they're doing
though I can't see my parents again
me too well once my heart even in this
freaking place
pretty don't know what great stroke of
Fortune brought us to get a new color
but thank you
it's not Fortune it's Destiny
oh
can I have your hat for my snowman
now
I Want to Build a Snowman
you wanna build a snowman
doesn't have to be a snowman
okay bye
oh yeah he gave me a new map please I
forgot
can put here
okay bye
oh
ah useless
no it's falling
oh there's six here
were they always oh yeah
oven
are you still there
what x so didn't somebody say anything
about I wish I had an ax was that on a
different Island
I feel like it was on a different Island
hair
can I camp
[Music]
maybe it really needs a hat and then
describe
then then the sticks were not the Final
Touch what are you talking about game
silly silly game you don't know what
you're talking about okay I see I see
we're gonna go by
uh
Forest Area
yo don't make me miss out on anything if
you guys see something suspicious here
let me know
that wasn't it either that was not the
right entrance either
[Music]
no it's falling
all around me I'm so confused
we're still having fun
I need to go ice skating from my
understanding
Merry Christmas
everyone
we're gonna have a party tonight
terrible
and I can at least keep myself on the
feet and I can go
um relatively fast and I don't know but
I can't do any tricks so sad
I wish I could
so
let's see uh this is the new piece I
want to
connect it like that
can I or do I have to
Maybe
maybe I have I don't know I'll try I'll
see how it looks like
okay that's not working well what is
that is that a hat
oh what's this
I'm coming for you
uh
that's not it either
oh no not the [\h__\h] ice skating riddle
again
maybe this way
hopefully
huh
[Music]
that's not it
it has to be
I I have to enter I suppose from the
bottom judging by what I just saw
which Maybe
um
maybe maybe maybe
like this
yeah
oh wait no I can't go to the left here
I have to start from the bottom again
ah
[Music]
oh my God I'm sorry guys I'm sorry
I wanna end it too
[Music]
I'll get it
wait I've already had it like this
before
[Music]
please let me go oh
my God
let me go
[Music]
no I'm not going apart free I'm
finishing it
okay I'll try here
foreign
okay
[Music]
uh
no
brain horde
nah please connect
ah so close
oh
[Music]
can I even
I need to be able to get there because
unless unless there's a number of peace
another ice piece that I have to get
but I need to hat I need the Hat you
know
foreign
if it's even possible for me to reach it
I feel like it should
feel like it should be possible
the hat is optional moment
I don't need it to progress oh what
what it's just for a secret puzzle
please oh [\h__\h] that I thought it was
reported
I've been wasting like 10 minutes on
this
[Music]
okay I can get everything back together
let's rethink rethink
then in that case
uh
of it and this piece this piece okay
let's look at this piece
I need to thank you taichi
I need to
enter
from a piece
that's both
up
no
it's both forests and that thing there
or
oh
can I
this this would work
it oh my God
I was always there
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] am I
can I can I go back to the base please
thought about that bass all right it's
all about that bass
oh [\h__\h] hell
[\h__\h] hell
ah
kill me
[Music]
they won't be able to reach dad I
already tried I don't wanna I just wanna
I just wanna find a bit okay I am I did
not think that this would get so
frustrating
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
don't lose your mind
don't lose it kiwawa
[Music]
I am lost again
oh yeah
yeah baby I think I found a way maybe
can I please go home now
let me go home
I used to be so smart remember those
times guys when I was so smart
those were good times
Good Times
[Music]
oh oh no oh yeah
yeah
remember this combination if I ever need
to get back here
now what
this right
oh God
what's the buck up
yeah I've been so busy fixing Bridges I
must have looked back to the monolith I
don't usually have to snow pile up like
this and I wouldn't you know it I left
my backpack of tools
I know I wasn't even good for amazingly
pickly
would you possibly grab my back oh [\h__\h]
you
I seem to making it just fine yeah yeah
I'm not losing my mind because of it no
where the [\h__\h] is your backpack
shown on the map
[Music]
it's somewhere in here
what
[Music]
what's Wendy Woods
where is Wendy Woods
huh
[Music]
um
that's the windy Woods
what
I have to turn it
I see the backpack
uh-huh
okay that makes me stuck
okay
aha
maybe like stop
wait
turn it there
yeah
Oh wrong way
I am just gonna brute force it now guys
oh
um this way it's right there
I couldn't pick it up I couldn't
oh
[Music]
wait
laughs
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't know uh
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
no there will be no part free
where is it right now
hmm
kfp don't give up on me oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] take it
no I'm finishing her today
why did she not take it why don't you
not take it
it's right there it's right there
oh I can walk you but I'm falling back I
guess
but I don't
understand
[Music]
this is me and
not very far
[Music]
wait
do I turn it right or left
right
or left
help me
[Music]
write
what
[Music]
foreign
[\h__\h]
I wanted to go the same way but then I
got stuck now I'm confused
[Music]
stop
which way
[Music]
um I I noticed I can open the map while
moving yeah but it's a little bit
delayed and I think it starts like
moving again from the point where you
would have ended up as I'm not sure
though
[Music]
okay
I hate this I'm stuck on the stone
what now
[Music]
stay here stay here
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's just start here
fall from the bridge okay okay never
mind okay so I'm in the corner
[Music]
foreign
I was pressing it are you [\h__\h]
kidding me
[Music]
I I I'm so mad
I was trying to like reach it properly
but
you can just walk through look I I'm mad
I'm mad I'll take that shitty [\h__\h]
stupid ass backpack disgusting I hate it
you suck stupid pickles they've been
molding in there it's so stinky and
stinkier than my grandma's feet oh
solve this [\h__\h] riddle let me out of
this ice world now
oh my God it's like a golden path
uh I see a pattern
[Music]
on Saturday left the treasure behind one
of the impossible value news like people
found a way back here and found new ways
to survive I've been looking for the
treasure ever since I still believe that
we'll find it when we find the Fable
seven fives back and I don't know where
to look next I can't come to this moment
for inspiration the feelings of these
patterns left violence or Circle I'm
sorry that I'm reading it like this now
but I want to get out of this now okay
um free mysterious patterns what do you
mean free
well if I turn the map will I see it
differently
oh
no oh no
what the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
oh
no I'm not doing part three
[Music]
um
okay one is like that
let me try this
pew pew pew pew but what does it mean
what does it mean one and two and one
and two also they're like some some
invisible ones is that important
is that important maybe
blue
okay
and then
and then this one
[Music]
is
you'll you'll
uh yo
yep yep yep oh
yep and then
there's two
two that are a little bit okay no game
didn't crash I was just tapping out okay
what do I do with this information
[Music]
what could this be uh
what could it be
[Music]
it could be
something with these map pieces I get
that well is it though the outer lines
Maybe
and then I don't know
other ones
let's say
I don't know
yeah each doll is one square I got that
so
how about how well
how about
what
about
what about the same
lines what is wait each dot is one
square
what
the the lines
aren't the lines each line is like you
know a square and the the dots are the
corners
those are not the corners
don't touch the squares
okay okay we need something with free
free dots uh on the bottom and in a row
but then
nothing to the side
except for the top one two three this
one okay this one and then and then and
then and then and then and then uh
that doesn't work that doesn't work
and then I need
I need one that goes
what about the connecting thing I don't
get it wait
[Music]
oh I made one
I'm a genius I hate this
well I like it but I hate it because I'm
impatient
okay
uh-huh I see now I see I understand I
understand okay leave it to me love it
to me
how about uh connected
one
it's hard to see from my doodles like
the first one I was doing with a
screenshot but the other ones I just
doodled on top of the screenshot
a bit difficult to
see now
um can I use is this one okay to use as
well I wonder
let's say
hey just look at it
I'll just look at it
ah this is the one I already did yeah
okay
um oh I wonder if um it only lights up
after it completed everything also in
between when you're like when you
connected one right thing or something
like I said
it won't do it okay so this one should
be easy one two three uh okay okay so we
have
basically
uh actually this one I wonder I'll use
this one and then
uh
-huh
I think
I think this one
but it won't connect like this
um
the thoughts the dots are squares right
what
Square
um
foreign
[Music]
Hallelujah one more thank you
okay let's start with this one like this
from the bottom and then maybe the
square no maybe not
[Music]
maybe it's like something like this but
that won't connect so I need a
um this one
um
right that doesn't work
oh
I'm smart
[Music]
just random Precious Moment those
patterns under my life so glorious
indifferent from every angle
yeah I was gonna follow it
I was gonna ah
[Music]
a white path
can I follow it now sir no you little
[\h__\h]
let me go I made it huh
did I can't oh I guess it doesn't work I
wanna I have to make it reach that place
ha okay okay okay
[Music]
how
uh-huh oh dear okay
up up and then I I follow it oh my God
it's the only way you can connect all of
the tetris pieces with one another
what kind of
okay that works this thing is just in
the way
uh-huh
uh next we need one of forest and the
other thing
that does not work
[Music]
it doesn't work
um
[Music]
and I went do I have any like other
pieces over here that I forgot no
okay okay
[Music]
um
maybe maybe I connected it wrong at this
point already
could that be
[Music]
use the patterns again
I broke the pan you need to use them to
make the path no
no
[Music]
I don't know I don't know how I like
them up
something
like this
yeah so that probably
I don't know
foreign
[Music]
plot is wrong
I I would hope not
there's something missing here
[Music]
okay but this this part seems fun
I think makes sense
uh
how did we do this one
[Music]
not like that I guess which one which
one was this one connected with
[Music]
this [\h__\h]
the square so I had this one right
[Music]
oh no or not
okay
Square
[Music]
like this
does that make a difference
[Music]
what do I do with this one
Forest
[Music]
I wish you could like like select them
and and move them together
[Music]
what's up this piece
what is this one now
[Music]
ah what
I'm so done with this
[Music]
foreign
it's literally the golden path is just
White
[Music]
foreign
what
[Music]
I'm gonna use the [\h__\h] guy now
I
need salvation
[Music]
need salvation really you didn't even
all of them
what
[Music]
guys Bamboozled me you made me think I
have to connect all of them what
[Music]
oh yeah he just walks over there doesn't
he
looks straight to Tetris piece I hate
you
[Music]
okay can I please get a shortcut please
thank you
shortcut though
[Music]
oh
we are going to finish this no matter
what once when's my stream tomorrow
[Music]
yeah my sanity
I want to keep my sanity if possible
[Music]
I'm just looking for a way out now
here's a layout but that doesn't really
do anything for me maybe let me go
I don't know
I can't believe there was still so much
left here to this game
but
I thought we would have a walk in the
park huh
today
I thought we would finish this
earlier
I've been
okay let's go back to the middle
here we are
oh okay and with that where which one is
the new one yeah
hello
now I'm by the way on purpose looking
sad
this is all on purpose did you guys see
the new membership wallpaper I hope you
like it
it's halloweening with my kitty catons
yay oh hey it seems like we're done here
wow it's a treasure
whoa It's feeling warmer
whoa
[Music]
very spooky Halloween art right
no
open the treasures my grandma inside
please go back down
um
[Music]
stand in the empty yeah okay
uh treasure box Marine Senpai it's
puppies it's husky puppies
[Music]
how the [\h__\h] did they survive in there
oh my God I'm gonna cry it's so cute
puppies
it wasn't for that stupid ass snowman
I'm glad I didn't waste it for the
stupid Snowman
whatever this is
cute puppy time
I'm okay
friend yeah
get me out of here
before but before that I take a puppy
[Music]
cute puppy babies but this is so
unrealistic they were stuck in that
treasure chest for how long
grandma
Grandma why are you making me do this
come to my dress yeah and you're shining
down below did you see your granny you
you can't believe it
I was all set to school you up in there
she about that she called up but oh God
it wasn't happening when I did below the
clouds I don't think I can risk Landing
there I'll need to meet you somewhere
above the clouds find the tallest place
you can
call this place
can I get the house to be really really
tall
I'll find today it's a promise this time
can't wait to hold your moms we have so
much to explore together
um
stop babies
oh there's some dumb
oh I want a puppy let's go
yeah they would be good companions no I
don't know if they would like to stay on
the sea the whole time
above the class no one jumps to mind but
let's head back to the store Chalet I
think story Chalet is exactly where we
want to go where is your boat
[Music]
where's your boat
it's not shown on the map
where did we even come from
[Music]
and also did not look at all of this
apparently
is it actually on the top left of this
piece
it's grounded where the [\h__\h] is your
boat
[Music]
it won't tell me uh you want me to say
goodbye
yeah this game wants me to talk to
everyone all the time which I don't mind
no but now I just don't wanna I just
don't wanna because I just need a shore
of our Island okay see this was really
important
ah all right can we go now no okay okay
goodbye thank you
thank you
oh you can't help hunting oh that's nice
thoughtful of our ancestors
making them close and I think Huskies
don't mind the cold
looks like I got my wish after all cute
anyone else
can I go
um
can we go now yep goodbyes are all done
see you have to talk to all of them
I think that's fine though like I like
that and then they make you talk to them
I'm just a little bit
you know time pressured right now
no I didn't finish the Snowman
it's fine
start to end up where you at my friend
up downwards
um
welcome back girls it's always nice to
see you how can I help um I would like
to build this place so high that it can
reach the sky
who's that can't land there
huh
sorry it's a long story maybe you'll
read about it one day do you know
anywhere that's tall enough that we can
get above the clouds
actually the top of the star Chalet see
see I knew this was for later the last
time you mentioned it because I couldn't
do it now
a small house it might appear that way
but you'd be surprised I once found
myself on the very top floor there were
no books up there but the view was
breathtaking
can you show us how to get up there I'd
be happy to Young Miss but I haven't
reached the top floor again since
[Music]
I can show you what I know please follow
me wait I want to read the book
now
ah here we are this looks more like the
basement than the top floor
yeah yeah it's just a basement but let
me Regale you a moment
dude it was just another morning many
months ago and I was doing my rounds
with the Chalet reading the new chapters
feeding the spiders that sort of thing I
would still have asleep and wandered
into a door I didn't recognize before I
knew one I was ratcheting upward and
spelled me out of the top floor oh that
sounds more like a dream you had
possibility but I spent the entire day
up there and my sunburn was very real
has had the most glorious views of the
forest I'd never been to high up I'd
hoped to find my way back ever since
with the smarts on new gals I bet we can
figure out how not sure about that story
if that adds up but it's the only way we
have let's look around and see what we
can find cartoon
[Music]
kind of seems like the last puzzle
the strength of a tree is measured by
the growth of its roots as they say in
the wild world and the mother tree is
the strongest of them all when fooling
around the mother trees roses to make
Center press the entire world tip on the
ground
I don't think that was important
um these were already red
um that one is new
I really seen door there we go allow the
scanned few storytenders access to the
observation deck
someone scrolled a message across the
page the top floor is real and I found a
way there it's real I don't have enough
space to fully explain but this should
get you started good luck future story
tenders a small Scroll of paper flutters
down
okay okay
[Music]
I'll take a screenshot of that so I
don't have to keep up keep on opening it
up
oh
let me just check something new here
send me a wave wove its way through the
burning decision important message and
the new Oasis have been found
Okay so
this thing I recognize
and there's in this one
[Music]
oh then this one is
um
here
then I think
this one is here
oh here
foreign
this right now but wait it needs to be
stairs
maybe maybe like that
[Applause]
[Laughter]
underestimated maidens you can't have
fade and think I would do it so easily
oh there's new books
choice but an entirely unpredictable one
running into a friend and last time you
see them for a while you have to ask my
trips together again the residents
install Supply boxes of essential tools
this is the last few infos you can get
in the game
[Music]
no idea how it works well you have to go
by the two pieces they tell you
wait I tell you how I did it because I
didn't cheat okay I just want to make
sure you know that let's see if you look
at this
you see there's two pieces that have
signs that we know from the rooms so
those are those are fixed and then you
have to start on the top right with one
that only goes to the left
um in between you need some stairs
because you have to be able to go up and
down and the bottom left ends with one
that um only has a connection to the
right the middle one there needs a
connection to both sides the corner
piece needs a connection to the left
side only
so it's actually easy
same
both sides only to the right only to the
left stair stairs stairs middle piece
that we know middle piece that we know
only goes to the left only goes to the
right and stairs you know
ha
let's go up
let's read my story hello grandpa had
just barely missed your granny at the
iceberg but she knew she was close all
she had to do now was to find somewhere
tall enough to get above the clouds they
headed back to the social insurance as
it was wasn't
[Music]
it
oh my stomach oh [\h__\h] okay and to the
right ah
destroying the shores as you often did
before getting lost but that day he
found a photo sitting on the North Pier
as if it had been left just for him and
then the message inside he was so
excited that he managed to find his own
way home his wife removed the message
and unfilled it and immediately burst
into tears
[Music]
oh my first one I mean the most oh happy
end
so it doesn't mean that I'm not on the
way to here
uh we throw the Bottle Into The Ocean
yeah I think we did okay nice
are they forcing me to read everything
because I'm I'm at the top now basically
the couch
oh is it at the bottom oh oh okay okay
like um one door that like makes you fly
[Music]
ghosts still do be typing I see this one
no
[Music]
yeah aren't you surprised
let's go let's go let's go no no no no
no no
all together really
you guys wanna meet my grandma too
maybe because he's my grandpa
you know I always had that suspicion
oh
well
the view of the forest
[Music]
well
I've never been this high up
does anyone else does it honestly it
looks like we're on the same height
that's the tree
just really far away
my is magnificent as I remember and
would you get a loaded that's right I'm
sorry girls it looks like we're still
below the clouds even up here
that's what I thought
don't worry we just need to get a bit
higher how about on top of that enormous
tree
um
um I mean if we were at the top of the
house where I just walked all the way up
to we would be higher than we are now I
think
but okay
maybe it's still growing
Grandma maybe okay
please don't tell me that getting up on
the tree is a riddle on its own
no way oh yeah I'm ready to go
[Laughter]
[Music]
it is
foreign
that's very nice of them
hello everybody nice to meet you again
if you need some ladies I know where to
find them
lock on Payless Messengers
mother's been expecting you
what about the grandmother though she
told me to gather everyone here at the
time for family has come
[Music]
no Grandma will be there this time for
real for real
mother says to thank you for your help
in the river but now it's time for her
to help you yeah she better
[Music]
eat me up eat me up
yeah let's go
three times
didn't expect to catch this no no I'm
streaming very late now what be careful
I I you're gonna fall down
oh because be [\h__\h] careful
keep your arms to your body
holy [\h__\h]
this girl she's gonna fall down isn't
she and then and then grandma is going
to catch her with the airship
are we finally high up enough can we get
much higher it looks like the claws are
still above us
and maybe we can Spot somewhere even
taller than this you can see the whole
world from up here it almost looks like
a
h
oh no
what am I doing
don't tell me I have to connect all of
them and they're like scattered all over
wait it's one big riddle again
I am putting everything together
[Laughter]
[Music]
but doesn't matter how
oh I just need to find all of them is
all of the fitting ones but they're like
all [\h__\h] over
wait is this only
okay okay wait never mind it's just like
this you know this area for now and then
only the ice area and so on okay okay
but still I regret leaving everything so
far away
um okay
[Music]
hi hi what if it has holes as long as
everything connected I'm assuming it's
okay Anna I did them all
foreign
I like the music
it's like
the last
[\h__\h]
almost have it
just some water
that's it complete
this is a weird map I'm sorry it looks
shitty but this is what your map
officially looks like now
yeah that's what it looks like yeah yeah
okay
I might go to new one I guess it changes
the music a bit
[Music]
foreign
this is just this is perfect for people
of OCD at the end they get to although I
guess they would have already cleaned
everything up by now
foreign
but I'm sure cleaning it up like this
feels really good to them
oh I couldn't even connect that and no
no
um this
and
hi
yeah that's the grassland feels like
forever girl it does
okay now when you do the forest
let me tell you a bit more about my
Comic-Con then I guess
so
yeah on the first day I did I did the
meet and greets and all that as well
yeah yeah and then the second day yo I
was so exhausted after the first day
that I wasn't sure if I really wanted to
go on the second day
um but
um actually right now
um as I wrote to you guys in the members
only post
um my childhood friend from school from
high school she's currently in Austria
again she lives actually in Japan for
the past many years
so it was kind of like really really
really rare opportunity for me to see
her again
um
and yeah she was gonna
oh no
she's gonna go back to her family I
think like today so I didn't have much
chance to see her so it kind of had to
be
um at the convention so I was like oh
okay I will go see her at the convention
we'll have dinner and all that
yeah yeah I talked about her before I
think last time when I was in Japan I
met her once for the first time in many
many years I meet her like once in 10
years somehow
so you may remember oh that's already
completed oh
you may remember
now one time she yeah she told me that
she found out on her own
because she was like
she and her colleagues were
like kind of looking into YouTubers and
then she found this YouTuber who's from
Austria and you know
obviously she knew me well so she
recognized me easily
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah I am
that's my girl
so I was excited to meet her
um I woke up I took it easy and I took
my time did my makeup made myself look
pretty on those two days for the first
time in a million years I made myself
look pretty
for the occasion normally I'm like I was
just chilling in pajamas at home looking
like [\h__\h] so this was this
a little bit better about myself again
because on both days so many people
complimented me about my outfit saying
that I have such incredible taste and
that everything I put together looks so
good you know my friends they were like
mostly in Cosplay or normal clothes
but I tried to put on some
cute-ish clothes you know what about
this piece how do I how to connect that
one
always
sand like this
yeah so everyone was telling me okay
your clothes look so good yeah
where are you getting those clothes from
damn looking so good looking fly and
looks thank you
I actually had quite the problems
putting together outfits because I
realized it's getting it's been getting
so cold here
and all my warm clothes are in the in
the
in the basement and I haven't gotten
them back I need to bring them back
[Music]
I'll do that soon
all my warm clothes are somewhere hidden
so I had to improvise a little bit
to get
oh dear this will be the most difficult
one
has to improvised a little bit there
mm-hmm
what was nice it was nice to get
compliments
[Music]
it's not that difficult you can just
collect like the tiny edges
just like this really really lazy
connecting
there you go yeah and then I arrived and
I met up with her and but then she told
me that she has another friend and she
um you know only has this one chance to
see her before leaving again
so most of the day she spent with that
other friend and I just you know spent a
few hours at the convention
um
my friends really not very long like I
arrived and I I gave everyone some some
snacks I brought some sweet stuff
[Music]
my all my friends
oh there we go
there we go and then I went inside for
the first time I got a free ticket again
this time I prepared a piece of paper
this time and I wrote down tickets
question mark pian's hearts
and I stood there for literally one
minute and somebody gave me their ticket
again a lady that was leaving it's so
easy
thing about you know leaving coming to a
convention early someone will give you
their ticket
for money
okay are we falling down now no we're
just growing okay
and then yeah for the first time ever I
went inside the Comic-Con and not just
chilling outside
and I I don't know I I guess you know I
checked out the artist alley on the
first day and on the second day I
checked out the main hall a little bit I
was hoping for a Bandai Namco Booth but
there was no freaking Bandai Namco Booth
very sad
um but I went to the Nintendo Booth
played some Mario Kart and then I walked
around
still looking for the Bandai Namco booth
that wasn't existing
uh and I was also kind of keeping an eye
out for like whole live merch because I
saw some you know those those
you know in conventions those places
that have like all the daki makura
covers and all that the loot the ludaki
makula covers of all kinds of like anime
characters and stuff they have that and
they had a lot of like famous anime and
so but they did tough hole after
[Music]
I feel like the day will come when they
will have a whole life there
yeah
they had some cute stuff the Lego like
Animal Crossing photo uh area with like
a bench and stuff a tent and stuff I
think
um
and then
and I was just walking around the hall
and then what do I see
I see this was really late it was about
to close you know I see the the
autograph
uh area
um where you can go to like famous
actors and get an autograph and I was
just passing by
um but then a staff member who knew me
from before uh came up to me and was
like okay what's up and I'm like oh
hello I'm just checking out the hall and
then I'm like oh what are you doing in
there like oh yeah I'm just um I'm like
the the staff for one of the one of the
actors
uh for the autographs sessions meet and
greets uh and I'm like oh that's cool
who are you who are you protecting and
they tell me about it and then I'm like
oh cool I guess you have one of the Game
of Thrones actors in here don't y'all
and then they said oh yeah we're too you
can like totally try to go get an
autograph still now and I'm like eh
like you have to make like early
reservations and it's all sold out
booked out reserved forever and I was
told nope
nope not at all
and for 40 Euro 40 bucks I can get an
autograph from Jack Gleason the actor
from Joffrey King Joffrey from Game of
Thrones
an autograph and some of them do photos
some of them don't want the photo want
to take a photo but you can talk to them
and all that
I'm like hey maybe I should do this I I
never I never did something like this
before
but this is a special opportunity and it
wasn't so expensive I had I had some
cash with me
and you know I spontaneously did it even
though you know I didn't really like
Joffrey but that's just because he
played his character so well
so I did it I bought a ticket and the
moment I bought it I got extremely
[\h__\h] nervous about it
[Music]
I was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] then by the way there was no one in
line no one except for like one girl and
uh she was not nervous at all but she
was a little bit drunk apparently
uh and this was at the end of the day so
I guess like in the beginning of the day
there probably would have been more
people
um it was really really in the last
couple minutes before they made the
announcement that the convention is
closing so I'm like starting to panic
I'm like jumping and walking in circles
like [\h__\h]
I was like I've been like that I went to
a big fan and I'm sorry but
I came from Frozen now so so that's what
I tweeted I'm like what the [\h__\h]
Jack Gleason hoping for you guys to help
me find a good appropriate question for
him
um
but then you guys did not like most of
you didn't even understand who Jack
Gleason was what the [\h__\h] guys most of
you were like who was so and and that
was short five minutes where I had the
Tweet up I did not really get much help
from you I think one question was maybe
helpful but I I had in the end three
good questions
and uh I wrote down his answers so here
we go whole talk with Jack Gleason
um
so I I I I I I was an absolute nervous
wreck mess when I walked up to him I
said hi this is my first time doing this
which is funny because just the day
before I was the one doing so many meet
and greets with my fans and here I am at
the meet and greet with an actor and I
can't [\h__\h] compose myself
it's my first time I'm sorry I don't
know um but I I prepared free questions
so
um yeah here we go
um so first question I asked him was
um what's your opinion about House of
the dragon and he said he didn't watch
it yet but he's looking forward to it
I'm like what why did you not watch him
yet and he says uh because oh yeah he
didn't have time yet but he's interested
and yeah he wants to watch it and he
asked me how it was and I said well it's
very focused on incest so that's that
oh but I said it's pretty good yeah
and then then I asked him oh how do you
like austrians in your first time and he
said it's his first time yeah
um and uh I was like okay how long are
you staying when are you leaving don't
worry I'm not gonna stalk you I'm just
just curious
he said yeah he's only here for like
three or four nights he he came two days
ago so he's leaving tomorrow and I'm
like oh my God that's so
everything properly so I I made some
recommendations like right next to the
convention venue is uh like a like a big
um amusement park uh I told him to go
there if he wants to and and
um uh that there's like you know people
in traditional dental and leader who
wasn't running around now because of
Oktoberfest and all that and yeah and he
said oh well you can always come back
you know even if it's short this time
yeah and then I asked him and asked him
since we were on the topic of traveling
uh I was like oh how about how about
Japan have you ever been to Japan and
he's like yeah I've been to several
places in Japan then he started listing
up all these places that he's been to I
didn't write those down because I could
could not remember but he's probably
been to more places in Japan than I have
been to hmm
and many many places he's done a lot of
traveling he's been from north to south
all over and he really likes it yeah
yeah yeah
so then
here comes the main question that I had
I asked him do you know YouTubers
and he's like what and I'm like vtubers
virtual YouTubers and he's like what no
no what is that
so is that explaining I'm like um well
so it's like um
anime man girls and boys and all that
streaming or making videos on YouTube or
twitch and
um you know it's basically like a normal
streamer but yeah behind you you know
cute looking anime look and so he was
like oh I see I see now I can imagine
yeah yeah yeah so what what did koawa do
kiwawa showed him takanashi kiwawa
so that he would understand better what
it is
um yeah so he says he thinks it's cool
and it's interesting
so he also told me he likes like
Evangelion
Evangelion yeah he likes anime and then
and then and then and then so this whole
thing uh you know it was about you know
getting an autograph so of course I got
an autograph
um so let me show you
[Music]
of course since this is my real name and
um I went there looking exactly like
this uh I gotta scientist
voila
y'all and I asked him to draw a little
chicken which is what he did on the top
left and I explained to him because it's
because my my community you know they
consist of chickens which probably was
kind of a confusing thing to say but
but yeah it was it was his attempt with
the chicken and he first started out
drawing it by the feet surprisingly he
started yeah with the feet and then he
made a big egg on top and then he made
the head and then I was really confused
because
um I'm so used to docomo chickens which
don't have like these two body parts
it's just one big big round egg
basically and then I was like where are
the wings and then he starts drawing
these like knives stabbing into the body
of the chicken very confusing
but yeah yeah yeah in the end even
though I was a [\h__\h] nervous wreck in
the beginning I think I actually did
pretty well because once I started like
chit chatting you know queen of tangents
I actually was able to hold up pretty
nicely and have a relatively good
conversation that I'm really proud of
yeah and I got this on grab which is
really special
yeah it looks a bit better in reality I
know I couldn't get a good picture for
some reason it's a bit darker in reality
oh
will you post it on Twitter yeah I think
so I was waiting I was gonna post it but
then I was like no I should show it on
the stream first so I was waiting to
show you guys first you guys are the
first ones who heard about it
yeah
very [\h__\h] special and then after that
I left I left the the main hall I
gathered back with my friends and I I
flexed it at all of them I was like look
at this and everyone was like what a yo
what the [\h__\h] that's so cool let's go
let's go
yeah that was a nice Flex a really nice
Flex
damn I met a famous actor I'm so cool I
never I don't think I think this is my
the first time I met someone
you know like that one-on-one
I think it's the first time
yeah
um
well it was actually like pretty normal
he was very nice
oh
yeah it was very nice and like I even
saw him the girl before me asked for a
hug and he hugged her I didn't ask for a
hug I forgot big regretty spaghetti but
um
but yeah he uh he hugged her so he's
really friendly really open and friendly
hmm
daijo but don't worry about it it's fine
it's fine
it's daijoku
we have to talk to a lot of famous
people for sure
um
so far man I don't really think so this
is as I said the first time I would I
talked one-on-one
um
foreign
[Music]
to my mommy and my sister and so on too
I think they will find it really cool as
well no connections use this type yeah
no connections necessary it was really
easy to get into the meet and greet
um and also we talked like like for I
don't know it felt like seven minutes or
so there was no time limits they were
really chill I guess because also there
was no line behind me and I was the last
one I was the last one yo last one
hmm
so I probably stayed in his memory
probably made quite the impression
he will never forget
takanashikiwawa
yeah so let's finish this
it is kind of rip off the clouds can you
see him Granny
um
no
no honestly no it must be close by
well did I miss her while I was
tangenting
[Music]
[Laughter]
grandma
okay okay okay
[Music]
oh my god oh there you are that's
dangerous it you're like almost bigger
than the oh my God
up
I know we'd find each other dear girl it
was only a matter of time or should I
say a map
uh
it was so resourceful to track me here
used all your brain cells almost lost
your mind but you found all the pieces
of our map
true Master cartographer just like your
granny and who's your companion
hello ma'am
I would say I've heard so much about you
but Kanto is a little on the quiet side
she only answers and emotes
kind of neat to teach your English at
some point please these millennials
[Music]
she's the best though she's taught me so
many things and we've been to so many
cool places and and and I want to hear
all about them child but now that we're
all together right on to show me
firsthand we can take the Airship and
we'll use the map that you girls
discovered
you can introduce me to some of your new
friends and take me to your favorite
spots
join me the waikato
let's go let's go
yay
why are we on top of that we should be
inside it's so dangerous no seatbelt
fever
oh
I can see why I wanted what what my face
so much I just got to see you again
that's so fast oh my God I talked to the
bear you laughed
[Music]
it's nice to see you again
oh Jeb is so confused
oh spicy
I'm just so glad that we're what you
said it sister and what a little Slice
of Heaven is there's all bones of mine
thank you
would never have found the Oasis without
you you little fearless lady here
her and speaking of mine he knows camels
carry quite the stage
stinky it takes a few wrenches
[Music]
now listen up students we have a special
guest today she's traveled around the
world and seen countless of amazing
things
cool it's a rare animals exotic fools
and possible landscapes
so many kinds
borrowing vulture Vines blah blue blah
blah
's already
not a tough crowd
[Music]
oh not here grandma get out of here they
want to kill you they want to kill me
too
I'm glad you like it grandma that's an
old Palma family recipe I thank her
forever
[Music]
so let me get this straight you have a
coming of age of money for four types of
fish what
now that you mentioned it it was more of
a fishing competition in any case movies
were there yeah yeah they were mermaids
we saw them sounds like quite a
combination hey dude I'm still not sure
if I won no you did not
fears
115 if anything
your little girl is going to tell us
I've been looking for the savings for
Iceberg for years and she found it in
the afternoon yeah we can't laugh which
won't do that the Apple doesn't fall
from the grandmother tree
keep a close eye on those whatever
sneaky pups pops
ah the story shall Lane has an HD unlike
me huh uh oh oh yeah oh yeah oh you're
looking really hot sexy maybe you want
to go to my secret room okay with that
Sunny those days are along behind me
this time I'll take you up to my Airship
instead oh yeah oh yeah on the seventh
cloud is that where are we going hell
yeah let's go I think that's what you
call it seventh clouds
is what we say in German
oh yeah I'll take you there I'll show
you where where it is I'll bring you
there take me higher
can we get much higher
hey guys we're so much fun but I hear
the ocean Whispering my name
I still have some more exploring of my
own YouTube before I find my new home it
was lovely meeting you Granny thank you
for sharing your stories with me
and you won't y'all I'm so glad you
caught the found one another best of
luck there
yay bear hug player hug
I'll miss you so much cartoon Miss
friends forever for real for real
I'm a guy like for real let's go thank
you
I love you I don't tell my grandma
[Music]
damn
holy [\h__\h]
that was
quite the journey longer than I thought
five hours
oh God
[Music]
thank you so much for watching everybody
it was a really cute game I'm sorry I
got a little salty at the end because
time issues is already half past one I
didn't think I would go that long
foreign
[Music]
except you know for the ice Iceberg
world but that might have just been a
bit more difficult because I was already
you know past my bedtime
who knows
who knows but besides that they were all
manageable and felt pretty nice
finishing them all
don't forget them now the video I always
showed you guys I showed it in between
when I you know was tangenting
that was the video that I wanted to show
um
so uh besides that obviously not gonna
Read Super chats now uh but I posted the
um question thingy Gathering thingy for
I am a senpai for whole talk oh cute on
Twitter I'm gonna post it on the
community board now for the English
question so if you have a question for I
am assembly please leave it there on
Sunday we're finally having Hotel
welcome back yay what's going on here
am I playing her
oh no
not moving
it's so nice to be back with Granny when
I miss you lots these guys have been
beautiful it's only been a week but
we've already seen so many amazing
things we even made it for another storm
we're prepared for anything now thank
you for being such a great friend to me
I hope you find Ricardo can put
sentences together
I hope you find wherever you're meant to
be and I'm sure I'll see you there soon
also you won't believe that I found uh
what I found hiding on the Airship one
of the icebergs
smuggle aboard good thing she likes the
seafood still anyways we'll miss you
write me back when you can
how is she gonna make the her letters
Rich Skye but okay
oh God don't miss you too
oh what she got one too
stole that puppy
oh
she has a companion now she's not all
alone on her travels
oh it's sweet
in the end
[Music]
yay
yeah cute nice good game gg gg both bark
bark
um
what now ah there you go
[Music]
chapters mode unlocked oh now when you
start a new game you can even start from
the beginning or choose any chapter to
begin on
secrets
I see I only got one one more would have
been the Snowman
but I have no idea what the others would
have been
no clue
okay I'll put out the reservation
move forward to our stream
and um
yeah
then I'll see you uh tomorrow is the
members only Super Chat reading because
I have to finish those members only
Super Chat those it will be
um starting at 4 P.M probably so I'll
see you guys there I'm gonna try to find
some food
um I was gonna cook but I don't want to
cook at one half past one a.m [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh thank you thank you thank you
guys
um I'll see you again
um the non members I'll see you again on
Thursday for GTA Friday for GTA schedule
is up on community board and on Twitter
if you want to check it yeah let's have
a fun week together and yeah
thank you soon for watching Everybody
um do you is almost at one million so
let's stream it
if I'm uh when I'm back for GTA it will
hopefully be at 1 million
okey-dokey
I don't have any quick pizza right now I
have nothing nothing
maybe I have pancakes in the fridge I
can have a sweet dinner pancakes the
same what I had for breakfast pancakes
with with
um crab pancakes with Nutella and
strawberries yeah
oh I guess I'll eat that
huh
yay
um yummy yummy yummy yummy yummy I got
loving my time
and I'll continue telling you more about
my weekend there's not much more but
I'll continue telling you more on in GTA
I suppose yeah yeah
yeah
um
[Music]
thank you guys for watching good night
and blah blah blah blah thank you thank
you soon cute game
cute game and in German we say
thankfully most people in the meet and
greet
um knew the greeting they were like
maybe two two or three people
who did not quite seem to know
migrating
but I think they were more like clip
watches which is fine too very sweet
that they are supporting me too
so much that they would buy the
merchandise
foreign
people honestly most of them were oldies
as well
um
yeah I asked a lot of them how long they
were watching almost all of them I want
I asked most of them were watching like
since the beginning
um
[Music]
oh close to the beginning
okay I'm gonna go now
foreign
yeah a lot of them were lurkers hmm
two three four four maximum where
non-lurkers
yeah
I told him to stop lurking
bye-bye good night
[Music]
foreign