[Music]
oh my
God
[Music]
finally
she sounds like a
Chewbacca
[Music]
yeah she's she's kind of pissed because
she had she purred so much into the
microphone and then it turned out the
stream was not on
right yeah you did all that work for
[Music]
nothing
baby
oh y baby oh I think so electric recent
holy [\h__\h] I feel like I'm going to get
electrocuted one day on my
computer everything's so
electric like when I touch my cats when
they're like chilling around my monitor
and and all that and I touched them and
I there's like so much static you guys
can even hear
ITP I don't know the lks of my own
song but it's so much worse than usual
right now so I don't know did I put
something the wrong
way oh oh science people I have a
question just um
there's a there's a thing I got with um
a product so I got I got this like phone
cooler a while ago right that you attach
to USB slot and on your phone and then
it cools down your your
phone um you know what came with it a
weird round little thing about the size
of the
cooler that says radiated
radiator magnetic
deflector and it seems like you can
stick it to something cuz it's tape on
the back
side I didn't use it so far I don't know
when how where would I use this but it
seems to belong to the to the cooler so
possibly you might need it in certain
situations with that I think it's like
cuz you attach it to the phone right you
attach the cooler to the phone and if
you have a problem of some magnetic
interference or so I don't know then
then you can use this but I had no
problem without it but I just
wonder a thermal pad what it says
magnetic deflector how is that how can
that be a
thermopad n
I don't have I don't even have real
scientists in my
[Laughter]
chat yeah
[Music]
whatever sounds like a scam about as
much as kfb is a
[Music]
scam no no KY is
real
anyway Kiki
I'm
small small small this is this is the
size I should
be small small W hello welcome to the
stream
yeah before we
start uh this stream is not really
sponsored
but um I got some products from hyperx
maybe you saw my YouTube
short uh where I also um advertised for
them I made such a good short I'm not
even getting paid
but I thought well I have this idea and
I want to make something good out of it
um the other thing I got that I'm using
right
now is this from hyperx Cloud free
wireless okay just so you know I'm not
sponsored I was just uh you know I'm
just telling you I'm using these because
they gave them to me
um yes but be let me just say here the
details wow 120 hour battery life hey yo
he yo I never use
wireless uh stuff at all generally so I
don't really know if that's normal but
to me that's sound sounds like it's a
lot of
time yeah it's a gaming headset yeah it
does have a microphone but I'm not using
the microphone uh I asked them if it's
okay to not use the microphone cuz I I
don't know I I can't imagine it being
better than my own but it might be good
it might be good I didn't test it you
can detach
it and five full days oh right math
going I didn't think of it like that
five full days
sheesh yeah yeah yeah so far it's really
comfortable so let's see how it will go
over the course of the stream and now to
the real stream
things uh I I am going to play well I
will make myself
bigger I'm going to play this
collection of unofficial Halloween games
collection myth or treat it's some my me
related uh
games yes made by Mon amiral Mon amiral
sounds so French is
French no game sound I think that
currently is
none did that you heard right The Click
yeah yeah I don't think there's music on
this screen turn on music there is no
music music is
imaginary
ah okay so apparently it's pretty short
but there's like five games you know one
per member and they're all really cute
looking normally I actually I don't play
many fan games so far right besides like
Holo cure and one time I played the the
fighting game but feel like generally I
don't play so many there's like some
that I didn't touch at all that
everybody else was
playing like the throwing
game and also I didn't try H hon NOA the
whole life sck
I Liverpool kickoff what are you a
British British
kfp
H yeah yeah delivering hope that's the
one yeah yeah so I haven't played many
but I don't know this is this looks so
cute I really like the the visuals of it
because it's small myth so originally I
wanted to play this like around
Halloween but uh a little bit late sorry
um but it's the end of November it's one
month after Halloween so we can just say
it's Halloween today
Halloween let's play so there's these
five different games we're going to play
all of them cuz even with all of them I
think it's pretty short yeah oh this
says 10 to 30 10 to 30 3 to 10 5 to 60 5
to 60 that's so
Broad and 2
minutes yeah so they're pretty short I
guess like I could probably do them all
in five minutes like each but uh we want
to drag it out it's going to be a short
stream I guess though um which is fine
some some short streams are good yeah we
like that depends on your math skills I
guess so yeah holy [\h__\h] uh oh you guys
have to help
me all right let's
go pumpkin party with Amy oh that might
be
loud I'll turn it
[Music]
down select a power up near the cauldron
oh this is so cute there's there's pink
Army there's like relatively normal Army
there's blue Army and green army piering
shots still kind of loud oh my God wait
can I what's your
uh music
volume out in my ears and is this
better yeah it's an FPS game piercing
shots shots Pierce through plus one
enemy or
obstacle aha attack speed plus one
attack per
second uh infinite potions last only one
wave restores all your health oh well
currently I'm full fully healed so how
about I don't know
shots FPS but with a with a magic stick
oh they're
[Music]
coming they need more than one
hit let's go link is in the description
by the way guys do I need to protect the
pauldron
Y okay I'm getting I'm getting back and
that looks like a boss
yum this pretty fun so
far
oh do I need to collect those things
those clowing yeah oh maybe yeah please
don't go away no it went away I might
have missed a lot of those green things
oh wait it says 30% at the top right
select the Power Up N the CLD um wait
does it like
stack cuz I previously used this one I'm
guessing it's stacking right no jump ah
but this time they come with some minus
keep
UPS
a oh except for this one this one gives
you a heal but I'm still pretty fine
life steal killing enemies heals you
lasts only one wave oh yeah the other
one did not say it lasts only one wave I
think but you get to be
slippery M oh you failed to collect all
of the
magical
oh they only come with a debuff because
I didn't collect the green stuff well I
didn't know that would have such a
negative impact
ah slippery no jump I didn't jump at all
so it might be fine let's let's let's
not jump I hope I don't need to jump in
this
round oh nice attack speed really good
that's really helpful and let's collect
all these things I don't know if I can
collect actually all of them that will
be kind of a challenge give me the greas
up y y y y
y I wanted to stay close because I
wanted to collect the things but holy
[\h__\h] me kill him kill him kill him kill
him going to second no no don't kill me
don't kill me no
no I want to collect the face please
no I think I think I did with collecting
everything yes 100% And 1 HP
um yeah the problem is the full heal
comes with without a debuff anyway but I
need it but I tried so hard the only
reason I don't have HP right now is
because I tried so hard to get those
green
points [\h__\h] maybe I
can n well I need to heal wait I have
potions wait how do I use
them what's the button to use them
do you guys
know didn't realize I had
ption oh
[Music]
right I threw it
forward
and it didn't heal me do I have to land
it on myself
like I have to catch it wait what what
how do I have to shoot it probably maybe
wait is oh it's a grenade oh it's it's
not a potion
then it's ah let me res I want to
restart I want to restart cuz I'm
learning all these things for the first
time okay let's let's do let's start
with uh actually no they don't have the
attack right now maximum health current
health wait this is
different infinite potions wait potions
but it is explosion potion explosion
potion
they they have this one's different is
it not I'll go with piercing shots let's
go this is kind of
fun yeah let's pick this
up what the [\h__\h] bastard this is the
boss holy [\h__\h] it came like out of
nowhere oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God here take this yay
tight
swag
sickening all right all right all right
I'm doing better let's let me pick up
these
things I hope I got them
71% a
okay not
quite which ones did I not pick up
man uh
attack speed but slow movement h no no
thank you oh this one does not have a
debuff h then I'll shall take this one I
don't need to heal yet either so
uh-oh H need something heavy I I felt
something coming closer with really
heavy steps but I guess that was a Kino
say
yes oh come on I want wanted to pick up
that
no Take that a
[\h__\h] barely picking up the green stuff
what the
boss
nice please let me pass for thank you I
don't care if it does some damage
h ah damn it 40% only
[\h__\h] it's quite difficult
what okay we get no I don't want to use
the potions they're really
useful maximum health plus five ooh
maybe that
[Music]
one I I eventually want to get life
steal too
but I
think cuz that also this comes with a
pretty bad debuff holy [\h__\h] let's go
with this one it's a heal and extra HP
for later oh God
should I take down the boss first of all
oh that wasn't the boss I thought
because it was a different
color
uh-oh okay they came charging at
me us please no it barely hit
them uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh come on oh my
God please be nice please be
nice there should be a difference in how
bad my debuffs are depending on how much
I actually collected I wonder if that's
the
case I need a
heal infinite potions attack damage
maximum yeah I need the full he he
that'll be pretty good 15 15 is pretty
good okay this it is
intense next wave how many waves are
there come on
yes pretty good right let me collect
this no no not worth it not worth it
doing it like that I have no more
potions die ah ah ah
ah uh-oh
uh-oh uh-oh oh wait potion
oh what do a three charge
ah no don't go don't go don't go don't
go no don't go go no no I got it
wooo oh nice
72% didn't lose that much HP but now
live SE would be nice it does come with
a debuff come on the others
don't then I might go [\h__\h] I'm so
reliant on the debuff I like the attack
speed though
yeah do you think I can survive with 8
HP I'll
try I
better
yeah that's pretty
op I barely got
them the worst that flying enemy is he
gone where is
he
oh they have like armor uh-oh uhoh
ah yeah that works that works that works
don't die
now y y getting close and he dead
yay
70% I
tried 2 Hp though I need I need the full
heal that's
definitely although in infinite potions
is like pretty op
too
[Music]
M let's let's get a full healing and try
to not get too uh hit too often in this
round so that next time I can go for
something damage heavy
again oh my God oh my God oh my
God
please let me through please let me
through please let me
through uh-oh okay gab
gather ah pretty good
ooh oh my God that's a lot of enemies
here one more
yes why is this so much fun holy [\h__\h]
this is way more fun than
anticipated okay please please please
please wait wait wait wait no no no no I
have to stay
[Music]
away 7 HP
51% how many W sorry there maybe I go
with infinite potions this
time
yeah I'll try I might die but I'm just
going to spam
them
hey
hey where did they come
from where did they come from holy [\h__\h]
I can't even I can't even collect the
things oh my God oh my God oh my God oh
my God oh my
God wait is this like infinite
waves
[Music]
yumy that was so much fun I think it
might be infinite wave so then then
there is no end to this
game I'll try one more time let's see
how far we get cuz this is really fun M
while we still have full HP we should go
for attack speed so that I don't have to
feel forced to take HP right now or
yeah get it while we
can look at that
[Music]
aim I hear them
running let's use the potions in the
beginning
too cuz I don't I don't I can't really
remember but I think they get recharged
right [\h__\h]
you ah the the points disappeared the
shiny things
disappeared I was going to go back in
that
direction really really you got me
there no please please please please
please ah I don't think it
counted already have oh it reaches like
even within the battle recharges sheesh
okay still uh ooh ooh no potions no [\h__\h]
no
maybe well the thing is that this one is
like forever but this is only this
round I could do it without potions some
if I'm careful and if I don't care too
much about
the the the
stuff the green
stuff although with movement speed maybe
it won't even be so so
[Music]
bad okay yeah I got to take the
permanent one
maybe hope that it's like good or or
this one but slippery Movement we didn't
have it before and I don't know if it's
like really bad I'll go with movement
speed yeah I mean it's just a little
bit oh my God oh my oh oh my God e
ah come on yes okay okay okay okay okay
okay oh the big boys do I have piercing
yet I don't think I do oh but looking
pretty good yeah but I need to get out
of here
ah
ah I can no this is the last couple
ones
please give me some of the green
[Laughter]
stuff
okay movement speed I no I think it
would only affect me okay I need the
heal or no they don't have the other one
then I shall take the heal
now now I kind of wish I already had the
HP nice
not so
good something's
there pretty good
aim ni
he I wonder how far you guys can get
like which wave this was my best wave
[Music]
maybe so we don't need the heal we could
take
something
uh a run with potions for a little bit
more attack damage m M oh in case you
guys want to try it out there is a
browser version if you just look up um
or if you click the link in my
description there's a browser version
but please just download it because the
browser version I don't think it really
works for anybody even my PC can't
handle
it uh all right more damage I might die
let's
go get the fast boy really
quickly what
I didn't think there was an orph thing
coming out of
there please please please please please
kill them all I am so far from all the
points do I have I don't have potions
this turn right [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] let me th it's too late it's too
late I'm going to die baby oh God I got
cored I got cored no wo
0.9 never saw that
before okay I think they're all in this
group that's not too bad then okay okay
ooh
nice M I'm so dead this is less than one
HP in a
dream uh yeah I need I need to
heal there's no other
way [\h__\h] I still only have
10 well somehow dodged it even though I
ran under him
nice who wait I have potions
again
nice
okay that's a lot of
enemies
ah so much of the good stuff getting
lost oh that's a that's a oh
oh go go go go go please please please
let me let me I need those I need those
shiny
things
okay oh not so bad that was a pretty
pretty good round
M I was clinging hanging on to those
potions so
this is gaming worthy of the famous
announcer from paladins yeah you would
almost think I'm Alit because I'm
playing so well like an FPS God but no
no this is kiaha playing I know can be
confusing
but no heal necessary but these debuffs
I don't like them slow nah I think I'll
go with infinite potions this
[Music]
time
didn't I die last time too at infinite
potions
[\h__\h] why why why why why why why why why
why why why why why why it like frows
him so far cuz I'm aiming down so I
would hope that it's like Landing right
at my feet I'm dying I'm dying I'm dying
I'm
dying I'm dying I'm dying I'm not even
even getting any of those pretty
points no I'm surviving I'm surviving
I'm surviving I'm
surviving
ah you know what this
means yeah then the maximum potions
isn't even that
effective you know I'm taking the
heal
a big boy a please please please be nice
there's surely something behind me yeah
yeah yeah yeah
bye totally wasted that one potion but
the the second one at least was pretty
good come
on give me a good boom like I've never
seen
before
give me that boom bo bo give me that bo
b
Bo that's a lot that's a little bit much
y I'm
stuck no need distance need distance
need distance need potion need potion
need
potion where's my
potion
look at all that yummy yummy
slime hey one HP and the dream
[Music]
hey I need to heal again oh
[\h__\h] yeah
bye um
okay
sh what's the green one
a kind of potion wasted I
think take
this
yeah so
far got to stay far but like this is
ridiculous I'm not getting anything
ah what where did they come from holy
[\h__\h] please have mercy on
me oh another
one 2% for real like what could I
do with that much coming at me I I I I I
I I have no choice
ah even at the end I lost one HP
[Music]
there can you charge a shot
no but I just realized I don't have to
click click click click I can just keep
clicking um one maximum potion oh refill
potions I can have free potions then
piercing shots 50%
no [\h__\h] I feel
like should I do life still but it only
lasts one wave and I start
off I I mean I probably get one HP per
killed enemy shall we do
that I don't know which one's really
better in that case just healing myself
to the F but then maybe by the end of
the turn I at least won't be down to low
P again cuz I'm I keep on healing myself
up I'll I'll try that maybe I'll be full
HP at the end of the turn ha inury in
Fury that's what should
happen please let me throw thank you
thank
you throw the where's the oh [\h__\h] it
came with no potions oh oh
oh oh
0.3 I need to kill
somebody oh it's only 0.5 healing
uh well okay slowly but surely oh God
let me get out of
here ah yeah bye yeah I'm dying no
please let me go please let me go please
let me
go okay okay okay the
hurt is assembling I am not getting any
green stuff in this turn that's okay
that's
the do I get more HP if I kill one of
these like more interesting looking
ones tree [\h__\h] you
tree thank you for
that maybe give me some of that no
please I beg you I beg
you it's Christmas
season you can be a little bit more
generous have some
mercy 18% and 8 HP okay I mean I came
out of that with uh more HP so it may
have been the smart
decision um now well I might go with
this and we find out
how bad the slippery movement is because
at least this thing is permanent and I
will be almost fully healed you said
it's Halloween true true true from I did
say I did say that myself
too slippery I don't think it will
affect me that that much maybe it
will I get potions at least right oh my
God ah what a
was
this is
exciting uh oh this is the bumb one yeah
yeah
potion
slippery I can feel the slipperiness
now oh
God ah no please I want someone that
please please please please please
please I'm getting
nothing I can't even collect it properly
no go go go go a
20% ah he do
enough I don't want to be slippery again
it was actually
annoying at least for like collecting
things and can't do like harsh
movements but you only I don't think
it's so noticeable when you watch I
think it's really a a matter of you have
to play it to understand I think wave 10
we've never been this far I'll be quite
satisfied with that
uh
no that could be fine because this is
permanent and I never jump so I don't
mind the no
jumping but free
HP nah I wouldn't survive
that I got to take it but at least we're
up to 15 this
time oh it's the bump one let's keep
that one for a little bit later ooh a
there's oh another
one maybe maybe can detonate now yeah
yeah
yeah ah so
far so
fast what did I run
into I I risk it I risk
it no
they're
they were all behind me so many I was
trying to get more points oh well that's
10 waves and
377 pumpkins pretty good pretty good
he I'm happy with that I'm very
satisfied that was so much fun holy [\h__\h]
see you guys should play this this is so
fun I kind of recommend it to the other
myth girls too cuz I I think this is
worth a
stream now can the other games keep up
with that fun this was a hectic first
person shooter against living Pumpkins
this is a first person horror game it
can't be that
spooky it can't be that spooky set in a
spooky hospital it better not be that
spooky okay let's go murderous
malpractice or whatever that
was oh
[\h__\h] no I don't like
it
yeah I don't like
it I don't like it wait what did the
wait the the the the guide is gone it's
a wd but what was the
rest can I do something I don't like it
I don't like
it I don't like it I don't like
no no no I'm so scared why am I so
scared run to shift okay and I have a
cat hair in in my
mouth no I don't I don't want to be no
it's Christmas season I take it back
it's not Halloween anymore I'm sorry I'm
sorry what am I looking
for what am I looking
for what what am I looking for what does
this
say can you guys read this I
can't and is there a button to open
the the doors cuz I don't think I can
open
them clicking doesn't
work so far no nothing is scaring me
but I'm still scared
the music
stopped the music's not looping sir sir
what does this mean does this does this
mean something
maybe oh they need to Loop the music oh
is there actually behind me wait no no
uh maybe maybe there's a maybe it's a
bug maybe I'm
not maybe I'm supposed to see something
here
okay I saw something and the bgm is
back the [\h__\h] is that a dead beat it's
definitely dead whatever it is it's
dead this is disgusting this corpse
didn't have a key really really I
finally find something and it's
useless
okay well if there's a there's if
there's a dash key there will be be
something chasing me eventually
right and what can I do besides running
shouldn't C in this form have like a a v
v knife
H at least there doesn't seem to be
stamina that's pretty
good okay let's try to remember these
things so that I know where where I
checked before so I checked like this o
area this
was this probably where
the body was no all
it it's okay I'm not scared
anymore oh where are
we I have no no sense of direction right
now hey and o a and o what does it mean
no just classrooms I would think
no I think you're running from
C I'm not C right
now what this El
squiggle never else
quiggle turn
on my FR I screamed out of sheer Terror
even though that was probably just a
little
tease is she still
there Kelly I thought it was
you I don't want to play this Halloween
is over I don't need to I committed to
playing some horror games only during
Halloween so that time is over so I
should be like free to go
now but I'm so scared what do I even do
what do I even do like there's no exit
or
so what I do when I when she's chasing
me can I ask her nicely if she has the
the
[Music]
key St objective I don't know I oh wait
try to remember places and where keys
are relative to the ex I didn't find any
keys yet the nurse will Dash towards you
at mad speed when she sees you but needs
time to turn around corners if she see
says I hear you when you run perhaps
should stop running for some time
a her keys are relative to the exit what
does that mean the first sentence I
don't quite understand where keys are
relative to the exit I didn't find an
exit oh wait no the first door was the
exit I guess I just need the keys there
were like
several several locks on it I think so I
need to eventually bring them back there
well great I don't I don't I don't have
any direction sense
I don't know where I am I don't know
what this place looks like there's an a
to the
left a to the
left yeah this corpse didn't what I
found two corpses already and they both
didn't have the
key okay remember a to the left is
useless that's a dead
end
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
me oh
man please don't show up
Kelly maybe she'll only actively start
to chase me
when oh I have my first
key cuz so far she teased me
once I don't want to I don't want I
can't take this right now I didn't think
there would be an actual scary game
here okay H to the
right let's check it out see what there
is I hope I'm not returning to where I
just came
from oh to the left I can't remember all
these
things a to a to the left o to the left
o to the left leads to a to the left a
to the right leads to leads to O to the
left what what no wait what something
like
that maybe it'll be important later I
don't want to play this I'm a [\h__\h]
chicken I admitted
but I don't want to I don't want to I
don't want to maybe maybe maybe
no again again maybe maybe let's play
The Others if we're not satisfied we can
go back to this but this no I can't I
can't I'm like mentally not ready I'm
not
[Music]
there I know nothing was happening I
know I know she didn't even chase me
once but just I'm already so scared the
father of you know her chasing
me it's so unrealistic you know
Callie would never chase me I'm the
Chaser just kidding
no okay it's good we don't need that
yeah we don't we don't need to force
ourselves let's play one of the other
ones Let's Play Godzilla
[Music]
attacks I can do that phase two yay
destroy the city to score points run to
increase your combo Dodge attacks and
fight back hey press any key to start
isn't it amazing that I already have um
like one almost an hour of streaming
time with these short
games Goa
Bo wait what wait I don't remember I
don't remember what was the key that you
pressed avoid open areas there are less
things to destroy and you're more
vulnerable to attacks when you see the
big bomb warning stop everything and run
okay it's kind of
loud oh wow is so noisy ah helicopter
no
no how do I
attack was there it's just me walking is
attacking
right any touched
building they have
pcer
military uh this is like GTA but like as
dinosaur
gaura let's
go run how can can I
run is was there a running
option a space Oh it's different from
the other game I I still thought it was
[Music]
uh don't die you can't Killa she's too
precious I'm running I'm running oh this
is a big big one yeah let's go
GAA
W look at my
couble can I heal myself back up somehow
I wonder hey get out of there good get
out of
there what about this
camera can I can I turn the
camera [\h__\h] the
factories we don't need them run GA
run that t tickled a little bit that
only tickled a little bit go go go go go
run run run run run run come on you need
to get out of there it takes a little
moment when I press uh the running key
takes him only to charge so she doesn't
immediately run waa thank God we were
not in
there okay okay
uh oh when did our combo go
down it was like over 300 400 I think at
some
point
oh what the [\h__\h] was that stop shooting
me how could
you go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go go
go yeah I know I know I see the stamina
bar I know I
know
go
CH I should have more gooda voice lines
like when she's running or so she should
say
something personal suggestion to
improve there was one voice line in the
beginning you should have done more I
need to hear more
ga yeah yeah get the
combo I oh oh we're destroying all the
helicopters and and and and pcers pcers
what's that in English again wait I'm
dying GA don't die
run run GA don't let them kill you no no
you can't have me thanks I yeah
right no no run ah she
dead that was
fun my score is
this
5 uh 54 is my Max combo I destroyed
1,500 uh
things oh ah ah oh they I didn't destroy
any trees uh cuz I didn't go to the park
cuz I feel like that's an open area you
should be avoiding
right but pretty good let's do it one
more
[Music]
time let's
go alarm alarm it's too late guys
there's no
meaning the alarm will not help you I'm
already here for
Destruction GAA dinosaur GAA will not
protect
you
round I'm a dinosaur I attack
getou good just going for a walk guys
oh okay okay okay yeah yeah oh yeah
combo's still going combo is still going
oh they're all they're all pointing at
me time to go time to
go you're destroying your own City
trying to fight me just let me do my
thing
Gilla good has to play
this they all have to play these
games run oh best timing cuz they were
about to throw that at me uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh I'm I'm out in the open yeah but
my combo my combo though she don't no
yeah don't let It Go Don't Let It Go
okay okay there's like it's like about
to disappear there uh-oh oh I'm so out
in the open oh that's it but my combo
was the highest that ever was and oh my
score I didn't survive as long but my my
score might have been pretty good
still pretty effective perhaps new
record
M you can do so much more damage in in a
short time but I guess I took a lot of
damage too oh one more one more last or
last 5 million higher oh but I I I only
survived like half of the time so maybe
it's fine to not like um be too
careful zero
trees
yeah because the trees did nothing
wrong the trees did nothing wrong I'm
destroying only buildings and people who
have wronged
me
we we W yeah I think in the first run I
was like going more in
curves but now was like mostly going
straight so behind me was always like no
cover right so what do we learn from
that see I already got shot in my
back go a little
bit to the side sometimes slide a little
bit who wronged you boss horror games
the whole
world the whole world is wronged me
I'm angry so angry ooh those towers are
looking good don't you
think M they look like ice blocks I need
to destroy them like that ice block game
I'm going to die though oh oh God no
this is not a good run it's not a good
run yby yby yby yeah no don't die my
tail my tail need to get out of there
needs to get out of there no go down
a
no no one more that wasn't good that was
not good
enough I need a higher score I didn't
live long enough why was this one so bad
I I I I combined my tactics of the first
two
playthroughs
go no I don't think there's a heal mm-
they didn't say anything about it
e no keep my combo no no no
no people in the distance who are just
like watching TV they're like I feel I
feel the Earth rumbling what is this
could it be the legendary the mythical
dinosaur as the legend has foretold has
finally come to
uh uh
uh forour
sin uhoh my
HP
why
why why why why why why why why not be
nice punish us
yes uh-oh
come
on
a the combo wasn't too bad but je I was
really lucky in the first two
[Music]
runs Divine
judgment
yes GAA Knows What You Did Last Summer
it does she shall punish you all all
Humanity or another Fury
is gaura doesn't know what the hell
she's doing here she's just playing with
the
blocks she doesn't
realize to this to her all all of these
things are just
AIT little blocks none of this is real
to
her she's just playing she's having a a
good
[Music]
time she doing things the dinosaurs
do uh-oh my combo
no oh let's go to the big
towers meow meow meow that the I here to
destroy
you yeah oh yeah all of them
strike home
on oh w w wo wo wo wa I'm still out in
the open and they're barely getting me
actually
surprising and now I got a
shots now it's getting dangerous keep
the combo up keep it
going oh oh oh go
go I believe in you you can do do
it oh God there's so many there she's
going to
die C I'm so sorry I couldn't protect
you one one 1.2 I think my highest was
like 2.9 right so still not better
but seems like my best runs were in the
beginning pretty good pretty very good
quite fun
actually
okay oh this is stealth game and this is
the math
game let's do the the maap game let's go
by
order a evil laboratory of dangerous
experim experimentations numerous taces
were harmed in the making of this game
Taco does don't look don't look
taces tutorial important okay ooh oh the
hardest one has has seven steps okay but
let's start the tutorial
then tell me
welcome
well welcome new appren I can't do her
voice I
can't click on me to continue
mhm what is
this together we'll create the perfect
Taco DTI ah you know wouldn't you say
every Taco D is perfect come
on don't don't destroy their dreams
don't give them
complexes okay how do we make it 0 12 24
20 is that the perfect one this one
looks more perfect
though it will be incredible perfect
body eyes and
mouth ooh to do so we'll combine a bunch
of
ingredients they add plus 10 Taco units
of change to the subject
what okay ah okay okay
okay using pipes and do thats is that
really what they're
called you can multiply these plus
10 plus 10 but it says 1.2 0.5 Time and
Time
2 m oh well I mean I guess the best
would be the
highest let's look at an example to see
how it all works all right our first
ingredient is red adding + 10 body uhhuh
uh-huh then we picked a bubble do that
which applies
0.5 which is halfing it so it's
five time 0.5 half
something is is that
so [\h__\h] it's been too long holy [\h__\h] I
didn't think you could forget so much
math like like
languages I understand forgetting
languages and stuff
but why why why is this not like like
riding a bike H only we need you next we
have a green ingredient and uh times 1.2
do
that uhhuh oh dear do I actually have to
do math is this important to like
balance it or so do I not just always
want to get the
highest so it became 12 do do apply
their multiplier to everything oh so Al
it also applied it to the body to the
red stuff because of that we have six
body 12 eyes zero mouth
M I want a specific number
and finally blue
ingredient and noodly do
that ah okay wait then this F is the
noodly do
that which is uh time two the straight
one is 1.2 and
the um what's that character from Naruto
which who has like a thing on his back
like this what's what's it called the
thing on his
back some kind of container or so yeah g
g g well what's the thing he has on this
back a a
GD a gourd or gird sounds like another
nickname for
GAA a gird of
sand maybe thinking it as in percentage
makes it
easier
m i I guess I'm fine 120% wait so let's
say we have last say we have the number
six and it's 1.2
multiplied uh what would that
be um eight
or I don't
know it 7.2 H yeah I thought it couldn't
be such a pretty
number that will be difficult this game
will be difficult maybe it's more
fitting for Ollie but for Ollie it might
be too easy I don't know fin a blue
ingredient and noodly do that * two * 2
is easy and 0.5 is also kind of easy 1.2
H I'll have issues with
that so oh wait times two this one's
also applied to everyone so only is it
is only the the the the the the gar
container that applies only to itself or
is it because of the
order I wonder I suggest pen and paper
to keep track of everything
no I don't want to I don't I don't I
mean okay no I don't want to I don't
want to go that hard into it you guys
are my pen and paper it's the order okay
okay time to experiment uh click on the
ingredients and Doats to replace
them oh
oh don't worry about the results is the
tutorial okay uh wait
so where's the first do
dad I only see
two can I only have
two scroll up oh there's
more okay wait so so oh these
are there's there's currently one G do
that and uh and two of the straight ones
no squiggly these are 1.2 and this one's
0 uh
five so maybe change to the I no wait
this was a squiggle okay never mind then
let's let's do it the same way I
guess
uh wait but red can I change the color
okay so if I want to have it the same
way that we just heard it it would be
wait I don't remember though I don't
remember the the colors anymore I think
it was
red red blue green or red green
blue
M you guys remember which one the rent
was
for was it for the eyes a RGV ah yeah
but what about what what applies to what
the red applies to the eyes right oh no
to the
body okay green appli
to the eyes and then blue to the mouth
right see what happens yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah I I wanted to remember
what's what it's important important
okay so we in in Fe we did it the same
way I think as in the
example how you going to turn out even
though you're perfect just now
interesting color yeah it's a perfect
Taco DTI
color let's see click the syringe
okay okay T that you ready oh sorry I
didn't even give you
time a
cute
that's so cute ah tacis are you here
your mouth actually really looks cute
body 12 tackle
points eyes 10 tackle points and mouth
20 tackle
points it is the higher the better look
at that look at
the the thing here now that you know 6
12 12 oh that's the
objective 6 12 12 click the T to get a
new one okay sorry guys you have been
discarded 6 12 12 okay will it always be
the
goal 6 12
uh wait wait but wait how many
points
we
how how many points do we start off with
again like one red was it was it
so I I
think oh wait is it telling me it's
telling me what it would
be then let's go for the G one keeps it
pretty low or should I do it we'll see
we'll
see what did she say what did she say 61
12 12 it's written there I guess 61 12
12 6 12 12 40 24 what if I do the 24 and
then at the end half it again
oh free
m but in the real thing it's not going
to show me this result on the bottom
right surely it's not going to show
me
so H wait if we start
off oh no okay that completely gets rid
of
it it will it will you think it will but
then it's not so difficult is it you can
just like switch everything through
until you get it
no let's
say we go like
this times
two
uh
no wait ah
ah
time wait I'm too stupid for this I'm
not even thinking cuz like I can't
comprehend
it don't forget you can change the the
order oh should I change the
[Music]
order body is 6 out of six right now and
mouth is 12 out of 12 eyes just the eyes
need to be changed but I can't really
wait I did
it I did
it call it the Ina that's that's that's
it okay let's Brew
it smart yeah totally I didn't just like
click a lot of random things and and
hope for the
best
it suck it
[Applause]
cute oh the the Halo look is looking
quite a bit better this time oh my God
great work click on the button to above
to play again which
button this
one this
one probably that one okay then I guess
we select
difficulty
I guess we can go to easy now oh wait
fre steps oh later there's more than
like
oh okay here we
go let me
start let's see the objectives and
current values 12 6
5 m pretty similar I think to what we
had before 12 65 12
65 currently body is at 12 but if I
change the bottom things the top is
going to change too
right
12 what if I
oh uh 28 12
48 um
yeah I want to half it like these two I
want a half but I still have too much
blue time is ticking no it's going up
not
down blue needs to be last
why is it
uh is it because of the order that it's
written
here but wasn't it also always like
this anyway wa
it's mean infer body and eyes are
perfect now let still going to change
the mouth and that changes
everything let's put the El squiggle for
example and then we have too much of
everything we
could just change everything and see
what
happens uh I can't I feel like this game
is good for people who are
smart cuz the way I'm playing it is not
the right way to play it my brain is
like
overloaded sensory
overload 0.5 should be at the top
okay 6655 free 12
[Music]
free I did it just by randomly doing
things though
just by randomly putting
everything together and switching
it just doing whatever this time it's
brown what you going to look
like it looks like the one from before
now look pretty similar to your other
friend click the bottom above to play
again wa do you actually mean this
button it's kind of weird that I have
to ah wait I can just play I can just
click the takachi the takachi is the
button or would you be giving me the
same
prompt 1265 is that the same but
honestly I don't
really I don't really
um um this not this not a game for me
it's really cute but I literally can't
think let's try the hard one one time
and you guys can help me
oh
oh no way no way can you guys help me
let's accomplish it
together 36
25.5 now tell me what to
do tell me what to
do
W you guys tell me start clicking
randomly no where are the smart
chickens this may need pen and paper
yeah probably I mean even the game
suggested
it I feel like only a Harvard student
can solve this
one we might need
paper how about we uh you
know first of all get all all the colors
equally uh what if I just out of sheer
luck get it
right that's not that's barely changing
anything oh it's only changing the mouth
when I do
this click randomly this be difficult to
boot Force
yeah but let's try do you think I should
have an equal amount of potions though
six maybe less green
because green is really
low on six
only they they want a really low green
number see at least that I figured out
that maybe I don't need as much green
potions yeah that that that's quite
something that's quite a thought that I
had mhm
but then what do you want to have more
of blue or
red ooh M
33 128 no idea green is six which means
it needs 1.2 and
five green is what what does this
mean what do these things mean that you
guys are
saying green is
x05
x1.2
6 yeah but like where do I
what green should be second from last oh
oh at the
top second from last what made you think
that what makes you think that and then
one would be the 0.5 Maybe which was
which one this
one four 16
9.6
maybe
no no I I I don't know which
one remove the other Green Oh there's
still one more green
oh ah we got the ice okay okay okay okay
okay okay nothing here must be
changed uh this these two tubes should
be correct the green and these two tubes
are correct then
okay and
then let's what what do we focus on next
the red can change but not the do
thats oh oh yeah yeah yeah yeah thank
you for the red super chat thank you the
two chps at the top could be swept no no
no
no you don't
top no it's perfect the way it is now
I'd work backwards from Green change the
red on the top to
Blue wait that's the one right yeah uh
ooh and then maybe a different one too
right
no I don't know what I'm doing what is
this changing oh the the mouth only the
mouth is changing down
there oh dear look at
those de de seem M Sten or something
like
that well that can't be
right that can't be right like there's
no way it should have so many decimals
at this
point just that alone is telling me it's
wrong oh my God I don't know do you guys
know I say keep it 16.8 oh it is
now need more El squiggle for times to
okay how about we put El squiggle
here that went from 16 something to 18
and 24 that's that's pretty good we're
getting there maybe one
more change up
here
no
[Music]
no you you need 51 to get it to 25.5 by
halfing
oh oh
n 51 and then which one was the halfing
one again the straight
one it's so close now
though it's pretty close Okay
um change first to
squiggle
ooh
ooh ooh 134
88 48 48 is pretty
good
is
[Music]
this I don't
know 72 48 I feel like it should stay
around 48 but like what else something's
not
harmonizing 57.6 to eventually if we can
get 48 and the 56 h 57 if we can get
this one to 60 and this one to 50 and
then half it
that would be
amazing oh it's back there ah when I
scroll up high I don't see it anymore so
I thought it wasn't there
[Music]
um swap some Reds and
blues uh wait did I just switch it what
if I do this and
this oh
uh no I liked it more
before move potions I don't know
what change swap
some gourd
0.5 oh yeah uh
green needs to be lower and get to 12
then be half at the end lower people
were pretty pretty convinced it would be
here lower let's say it's
here but we already had the the green
one perfectly done
though I'm not solving this one N I
can't I don't think I can solve this one
it's okay we don't need
to I give up I give up that's plenty
let's play the midnight snack the
stealth game about sneakily drinking
villagers blood 2 minutes which is my
game yay I have freed you guys from the
math mess up the tacle oh okay okay at
least let's look at that
then just quickly like make all kinds of
random
[\h__\h] how about
this oh
yeah tatti I'm going to make you look
beautiful really beautiful trust
me come here Tak
DTI I'll treat you
well
it doesn't look so bad looks really
cute it looks so
cute body change was too high I know I
know I
know m one
more what if we make it all
green does it just do the other things
that are on zero stay like the way they
are
now let's
see eyes for
days his eyes are going to pop out
really let's see
zop looks like
myy yeah that one really looks messed
up and the other things didn't CH like
stay the same either
not oh what if I go all
red this is such a cute game if only I
had
brain then there was more to gain she
W
she how
about oh uh only El
squiggles which brings us to whopping
2,540 the highest possible I
think let's
go is that the body one
oo going to get a Fick Taco a Fick Taco
Dy Maybe
playing
doctor you look more normal than the
previous
one it looks funny though the the ears
are so
small and the I guess the the the bottom
flaps are kind of
long the eyes are cute though I'm making
ASA
Coco cute ah why are we ruining this
perfect takachi like he's already
perfect I don't
understand
okay that's that's really
cute all the games so far I really
enjoyed except for the Cali one because
I just can't handle these games let's do
midnight snack yum yum M midnight snack
m
can I eat you guys for a midnight
snack what are you going to do here oh
it's a me it's a
wa click to
start the Hunt is on oh these are
hunting me cuz I'm a
vampire oh oh I go with mouse
oh so what's going to happen if they saw
me H they're running
away
do I I don't want to be seen right oh
wait ah they're my victims oh I have to
kill them
ah ah I don't want to be seen by the
guys in the hats that's a vampire no
there's no
vampire
vampire Y no no no no don't tell
anybody sneaky I go sneaky sneaky
a will they ever stop charging
me never stop
wa I will kill you all you can't get
me now he wants to follow me to
y
y they got me but I will revive again
this will not change
anything don't think you're safe what
are they
doing oh I can end it by myself oh I can
revive where I want oh okay wa let me
let me resume cuz I just learned a lot
of things about this
game uh eh no I want to
restart so
cute so cute oh my
God all right let's
go
oh so after you kill the first one no
don't go Vamp vampire no not
vampire after you kill the first one
that's when the hunter
appears oh he saw the blood so then he
investigates
oh ah almost got
him and this game is cute vampire I like
it vampire vampire vampire that's right
actually normally during the daytime I'm
a phoenix at night time I'm a vampire
vampix that's what you call me I'm a
hybrid a hay bird hey Bird the game size
resid oh oh why uh what's the what
should it
be what's what's 16 to9 with
this you guys know
hey
bird
2,16 uh okay seems to have worked that's
a vampire no there's no vampire don't
tell him don't tell
him speechless when you see me
understandable oh now there's so many
already okay it has beun no no but wait
I can re
revive just like the Phoenix vampire
that I
am
no actually
surprised how did that was my voice how
they didn't see me when I was like right
next to him interesting there is a timer
that runs out so I guess I can revive
until the timer
is
up
oh
no run I like this music for the chase
y oh yeah but they did say that they're
not so good at uh cutting Corners
right ooh but I
am
it 5 Seconds okay let's revive here and
kill them
quickly nice I'm on the roll the night
is over oh
and my score I wonder if this is a good
score still only more or less my first
time playing it that was a call game
wasn't it I think that was about cell
what what what
what what what are you guys talking
about drank blood 36 times spotted 34
times 34 times oh by the civilians as
well oh
oh slow around corner ah that was the
Cali again for
real oh I'm mixing up things then okay
okay
okay do they have any disadvantage those
Hunters I don't think I care so much
about being seen by them because it's
not that many points that I'm losing
[\h__\h] that was uh
stupid
I didn't think you would look around oh
but he lost me wait I never was lost
before I didn't think that was
possible no you couldn't have seen me I
was behind the
barrel oh he lost me again
nice I'm not
dying a vampire that's
me no you can't leave you will die
that's aamp there's no use in
leaving I got this one
without nice I'll leave I'll leave that
one on live I'll get you
later a [\h__\h]
ah and the second one and the third one
ah try to get me play catch with
Wawa I can fly look at me zooming zoom
zoom zoom I'm really fast I feel like I
get like I get a little Dash when I
killed
someone uh-oh uhoh
uhoh uh-oh uh-oh
uhoh yum B let's go here quick quick ah
I don't care I don't care I don't
[Laughter]
get I almost I almost
[Music]
Qui where it was better than before
better than before I think yeah high
score hi
score hi bye score high
score
the music is so fun can you kill the
hunters from behind I never
tried shall we try is that
possible that's a
vampire well now I was in front of him
let me try
again no no I can't it made me disappear
this
time why did it like automatically kill
me let me try that again I don't think
you can kill
them a that's
[Music]
aamp dead on touch yeah can't touch
this what what what what did you
notice
okay pretty
good second Hunter is out that's
aamp y
y last time I I lost him quite of okay I
lost one but the second one found me
no no I resized accidentally the window
yooo run wa run wa where am I kfp
employees to protect
me
oh okay here we
go
[Laughter]
quick that's a vampire no no I'm a
phoenix I'm just a normal do you think
in the middle middle Medieval ages they
probably would have uh tried to kill a
Phoenix as
well scared by anything that is
powerful oh nice nice I thought that
would get me
caught ah wait no I trapped out of the
game no no I should play full
screen why are you guys so close
together that's not very
smart I don't care I don't care I don't
careing M Maybe
here that's
aamp oh only only ah no no that time is
over I died again no not at the
end
K not high score at all I got caught too
often
[Music]
damn sorry guys don't mind the
resizing it it does that when I click
around all right let's try to be a bit
more
careful okay so far only one of them saw
me yes yes yes yes yes yes yes W on a
killing
spree second Hunter
oh
yes get him he'll tell the others
vampire that's a
vampire please unsee what you have seen
yes today's your birthday happy birthday
congratulations let me kill
you another Hunter I think this is this
is a pretty good run so
far
uh-oh let's go down here ah I tapped out
no oh okay I ta back in ah
ooh triple o baby a
triple
okay R
my okay my first
death uh-oh I spawned
in the view [\h__\h] yeah okay that was such
a good run though no I'm ruining it with
those
deaths there's too many of them now cuz
I I killed too
many in this short amount of time no no
no no no no no no no no no
no okay it's over
almost
night over how many points do I get for
that 1,400
what again I'm like better and luckier
in my first couple of tries than in the
later
ones musina you like the stereo kiata
screams what streams
what what my screams are stereo right
now getting caught is winning your score
I know but this time I was so good in
the
beginning but then in the middle I got
caught like twice in a
row from me at the
game that was fun that was fun that was
fun you guys should play this this is a
lot of fun I'll recommend it for like a
short stream to the other myth girl or
generally any any Holo Ian girl I think
everybody should play it I I think I'm
satisfied now no oh Callie's game what
do you mean what what do you mean Kell's
game I I uh played it already I played
all of
them I don't know what you
mean let her catch you I I couldn't even
find her anyway like I saw her once and
like then I never saw her again it's
like I don't know how to trigger
[Music]
her no I I don't know there must be some
kind of bug or something the game is
bugged I can't play
it run around so she hears okay just for
you just for
you
Callie I want to see your cute
costume show me your
cute Kelly Kelly Kelly let me take a
close this corpse doesn't have a
key why is she not here she should be
here why does she not hear me
cie do you have the noise cancelling
earbuds from hyperx on is that why you
don't hear
me Kelly take the earbuds
off Kelly I'm looking for
you Kelly don't ignore
me is that one I saw already oh yeah
don't ignore me the other one why do
they not have any
keys don't ignore me Kelly this one
maybe I never saw this one before no no
really can
we Ka
bori
[Applause]
please bless me with your uh
present come
on what I'm running constantly she
doesn't give a
[\h__\h] stop listening to music
Kelly come and get
me give me hug give me a hug sister did
you guys see I was
um uh I was MC yeah I was
mcing
the the the thing on the official
channel oh
ke oh was Kelly she said I found a
survivor
is she going to be more strict
now I was I was I'm seeing Oh there's
another key here he
yo second one oh hello Cat which cat is
it oh chalky won is going to protect
me how do I suddenly get two
keys yeah did you buy the Blu-ray guys
cuz that was basically what it was for
to announce the the Blu-ray sales
go ahead and get a Blu-ray because it's
going to be way better quality than the
original stream or maybe if you went to
the actual concert then you you can
reminisce do you think you're going
to K okay K come out here come closer
close holy
[\h__\h] no okay now she's not charging not
not not chasing me okay okay okay okay I
see
why this suddenly so what the [\h__\h] my
heart my [\h__\h] heart can't do this to
me [\h__\h] I hurt my I hurt my
[Laughter]
knee oh Kelly please
stop she's like suddenly also with like
pretty bad audio uhy pretty bad
Acoustics suddenly in my ear so close it
freaks me out
man what was I saying oh yeah actually
Cy was there too um me cie IIs and Fu
were uh part of this program on the
official Ian
channel oh [\h__\h] she gave up okay oh I
thought it was it was over with me cuz
it was a dead end oh [\h__\h] I'm always
here in this area
yeah
uh wait I have two keys can I go to the
OG door and shut up
cie and put the keys in already I see
someone
running
stop please
please is so funny holy [\h__\h] I panicked
so
hard didn't you want to be caught I
don't know I mean now that I already
have two keys I'm I'm not I don't want
to give myself up immediately but
um I'm trying to have a
conversation running Ari I can hear your
footsteps so what what you going to do
cie what you got I'm fast I'm fast she
say so calmly
no no that's enough cortis she should be
lost
now hi CH I think she's really worried
about me cuz I'm screaming so much
running yeah let's let it happen chy
wonk is really concerned
M strawberry jam you were brutally
killed let's go meow I had two out of oh
two out of
three damn I two the free keys I wonder
if they're always in the same spots
sorry tky wonkey I'm okay I was not
brutally murdered don't worry I you will
you don't have to Feast on my corpse for
breakfast
tomorrow oh she's she's such a fluffy
ball
a almost made it I did but like she kept
on like chasing me in a way that I had
to stay in the same area the whole time
but it was really
funny Wawa is kill where were you when
Wawa was
kill she's still looking at me she's
like sitting behind me looking up to me
making sure that I'm okay I'm okay you
can leave now a small C is the cutest
thank you was the cutest F fan game fun
games for real it was really good
perfect for a shorter stream and like
has variety and all that I want to my
favorite I would
say I think it must be the pumpkin
party yeah cuz like that one I think I
did uh quite well at and you can go on
forever and ever it's a lot of fun the
first one that we
played yeah you guys
agree okay so since I was already
talking about the Blu-ray let let me say
it again in case you missed it guys
yesterday uh when I um was not streaming
some things happened on the official
channel so first of all there's a stream
of like I don't know half an hour or
so that in case you missed it you should
watch because it was W on the MC
microphone I I remember uh it was like
in the middle of the night or like early
early early as [\h__\h] morning for
me and I actually I didn't expect that I
would be MC even though they probably
told me and I just uh forgot about it
like cuz they asked me to be in this
like really early on and then and then
time has passed and eventually the
recording time came and they sent they
sent a a script beforehand but the thing
is with these programs if you're not the
MC usually you just like let things
happen you don't really have to
you know study the MC the the the the
the script so hard if you're the MC
however then you have to study the
script but I didn't expect to be the MC
and then so I just kind of ignored the
script
until uh yeah like a little bit before
the stream uh before the
recording and then I open it and I'm
like oh this will be fine because surely
uh I I thought aan would be the C or so
but H wasn't even
there yeah so I open it and I'm
like I'm
themc oh oh oh okay then um no time for
breakfast I guess let's uh look at this
and study it mhm but honestly like a lot
of the others didn't check the um
uh I I think both Iris and celly didn't
check the uh script either until we like
started
recording so I think it's quite quite
common um cuz it's really like you let
the MC lead it and you don't really have
to do much most of the time you're just
like reacting and stuff you know
mhm yeah uh yeah I was really hungry and
kind of tired but I wanted to do my best
um with the
MC and so I think it turned out really
good um I was I was watching the final
product and it turned out I think really
really good for kohai most
professional uh I I would assume they
looked at the script yeah but they had
other troubles like cuz it was the first
ever uh official recording they did not
know what to
expect and there were some technical and
audio issues like the staff wanted them
to record separately their all audio
separately so like one of them actually
left the room and you were like it's
kind of funny cuz you could hear one of
them from the distance through the
microphone of the other one while she
was like setting up the other uh
microphone setup and all
that bow bow issues yeah but they
figured it out it was their first time
so now in the future they know what's
expected normally when we do these these
programs they want us to all record our
audio like they record us like via
Discord but then additionally they want
a backup or like actually the Discord is
a backup cuz sound quality is bad so
normally they have us record our solo
audio on our side too and then we sent
it in but then yeah they they had some
troubles and in the end I think uh
because they like switched so many
things around they actually had to uh
use the Discord audio only for fua I
think you can notice it a little bit in
their audio it was uh significantly a
bit worse than
ours significantly a
bit no I definitely noticed I was like
ah yeah that's the that's the Discord
for
moo
MH yeah yeah yeah but it's a learning
EXP experience I don't even remember
when was my first recording like that
but uh now we know now you
know mhm it's a bit more complicated cuz
normally they just uh you know they're
just on one PC one no they do have two
microphones but it goes through one
thing and all that they said so it's
it's not what the studio staff usually
deals
with
yeah yeah yeah yeah so they were like
like please can you please record
separately two different audio sources
please but it was fun and uh watch it if
you missed it and then uh I also made a
little video with the help of cow carrot
thank you for saving my butt and making
it more interesting um the the the press
conference video is on the official
Channel as well as well as the Twitter
accounts and the script was really funny
there was no script I completely um
freestyled that video which is why I
asked cow carrat please please cut a bit
of my rambling because I can't I can't
stand my own rambling this is
boring but he made it more
interesting it was great it was funny
thank you
I wanted to sound like I was at a press
conference I was talking like kind of in
a lowkey serious way but like
sarcastically
serious the Sligh crash and that was
also
spontaneously coming out of my
brain the gator bit was my favorite I I
only like I was like taking questions so
to say from the audience but C carat
decided that they would be um The Myth
fandoms I didn't even ask for
that but yeah it turned out pretty cute
and then today will or like uh I think
in 1
hour if my calculations are correct in 1
hour the first door to the Advent
calendar should
open yay
[Music]
yay right cuz it's UTC zero and I'm on
UTC minus one oh oh oh no oh it's the
other way around in 3 hours oh so 1:00
a.m. for
me is it 1:00 a.m. for me now was 11
midnight yeah okay so 1:00 a.m. for me
okay never mind in 3 hours the first
door is
opening
uh I I uh I am involved in the first
video but it's not a solo video I
prepared something
nice yeah this is um a funny one I
thought we should kick it off with
something silly involving more than one
member you will see you will see so I
hope you guys will be checking out the
Advent calendar every day cuz I'm really
happy that it's back
and just like last year it will be great
mhm with all the help from all of them
and girls taking their time to make some
cute silly
videos
inde why are you so neat I think it's
because there's no more Kibbles in her
um in her food thingy but normally there
always are right I never let it go empty
but now mama let it go empty I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry it's
empty chunky
wonky that was crazy you pull it off
with no time last time yeah yeah yeah
yeah last time was kind of crazy we did
it like in free days cuz I had the idea
out of
nowhere mother I hunger yeah she looks
like she's
starving no I like her presence in the
room so she shall stay here she's she's
cleaning her face right now so
cute last year's video still on YouTube
yeah they still on there and on the
Advent calendar side I think you can
already go on it uh there's a view where
you can see all the old videos too in
the old
form uh what was it Holan
advent.com holen minus advent.com yeah
let me put pin this one now so everybody
is reminded
how about you guys bookmark this and
check it out each day so you don't get
spoiled by Twitter
whatsoever minus Advent minus but Advent
is included H minus ah
that's funny what that implies Advent
members is are included they're all
included you guys want to see what the
website looks like right
now oh it's kind of laggy for
me or oh my God it's so loud is it
supposed to
[Music]
be it's kind of laggy for
me qu lagging for me
too
M also kind of loud right can I change
settings volume there we
go Mr Harvard
student you can try to demo see if it
lags yeah man but the snow in the
background is
lagging like it's so slow I don't know
if it's supposed to be like
that it's like moving in two
FPS Works normal
really okay so it says day one opens in
2 hours 51 minutes and there will be 25
days
we and then uh how do you get
to the old
one ah if you go to the about section
underneath the video it says 2022
calendar archive Mr the 2022 Advent
calendar you can still view it here and
then click on the
link
yay it's so nice to see the old one with
all the pictures it's so
[Music]
nostalgic oh my
God it's genuinely so nostalgic oh my
God cuz it reminds me of the scuff like
the the the lack of time that we had and
we still squeezed out everything and
everybody was helping and I was just
scrambling everything together like hey
can you make a video what about you and
you can you make a unit video how about
how about you do this and that oh I'll
I'll make a video today cuz um we're
we're missing one and so on like me
jumping in
between
H yeah good time
that's
[Music]
Casina the one CI had to re-record cuz
she had no voice ah yeah right that was
a thing she sent me a video that had no
audio and then she
disappeared and it was time to upload it
though and then did I did I do like a
replacement video or did I have like a
different one ready from someone else to
replace it with and then move Callie's
to like a day later I wonder I wonder
how we countered
that oh I called her and she did react
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah she did wake up
see it always works me calling her on
Discord even when you can't reach her
via text or whatever and she's sleeping
she usually react when I call her on
Discord yeah it was just a little bit
delayed yeah now we'll see if we have
delays this time I think this time we
are trying our best to have everything
on time although I honestly
think it's it has quite the
charm with the scuff and like being late
and and unexpected and me being stressed
out you know all of that kind of had its
own
[Music]
charm I will miss the scuff can we have
some scuff I mean I mean there scuff
with the website lagging for me right
now I guess but that's not the kind of
scuff that I
want
[Music]
oh well I I'll leave this music running
actually cuz it's perfect let me go to
my small office chunky wonk is still
standing there do you really want the
kibble so bad are you so
hungry where's my small office
um a
here
oh
[Music]
you think it will come
naturally the scuff will come
naturally now now that you say like that
that scares
me I I hope nothing bad
happens okay
[Music]
chatow
small WWA become big Wawa no I'm
adjusting
[Music]
still um I think I have to give chunky
wonky Kibbles cuz she's being so
[Music]
suffering
all
right I'm
back
[Music]
yay okay
oh hon dance is the face of my YouTube
recap wait YouTube recap already a
thing
what do I get a YouTube recap too where
do you get your YouTube
recap how do you get your YouTube recap
I want want
to I want one
to how do you get it there's a
website YouTube
[Music]
recap I no shut up this is a
channel some shitty German
Channel that's not
what for YouTube
music I don't know how it works I I
Googled YouTube recap and I don't get
[Music]
anything German Channel what's
that it Vally showed up on my YouTube
app the game death is in
chat
oh can't see you what what uh what what
are they saying
[Music]
ah
wait ah the Super
Chat you're welcome they turned out
really fun I really had a good
time no such simple games and fury but I
I really had a blast
so D sh for making the
games make more make more make
more I would love to see
more but the Ina game too difficult Mama
Mia even on tutorial
[Music]
level okay guys I'm going
to read super chats I
[Music]
guess
sorry super chatos let's
see last time I stopped somewhere in the
middle of one cuz I wasn't feeling
good in the middle of the waiting room
right so you guys remember I stopped at
yours did I read it or did I not read
it oh I think I read yours and then the
next one I didn't read
okay reading the waiting room super
[Music]
chats I'm so
hungry I'm so hungry guys I didn't eat
lunch but I will survive until I'm
[Music]
done thank you for the red super chat
everything will be fine thank you
oh everything will be fine I did get my
salary today so I feel so much more
relieved hopefully from now on no more
money
issues cuz it was like two almost 3
months in a row so now please I hope it
stabilizes stonks
STS
stons W I think I hear cat in the
distance same here it's a real
pain you may Feast Upon Us Master eh not
going to eat you oh by the way did you
like my my my hyperx short I just want
to say I put uh probably too much effort
into it considering I'm I'm not getting
paid but I I really like how it turned
out please watch it my new short my new
YouTube
short I did you know cuz like we can put
pgs and stuff on our bodies right and so
I put it on my 3D body and there's like
all kinds of controls to like move it
into the right position I can't just
like like click it with the mouse and
place it wherever no there's like a lot
of like um ruler
[Music]
and from all kinds of axes like the YX
the
XX and the Z ax I
think thought it was a 3D model no that
was a PNG and I put the PNG on the 3D
model they the sliders yeah XY Z there's
like six no seven different sliders and
then I had to find the right placement
for my
ears isn't it so cute I put it in my
ears I was acting as if I just put it in
my
ears I was quite proud of
that I was pretty proud of it yo which
meows where there were some like when I
was meowing meowing meowing for
recording the YouTube short smoothie and
chunky wonky entered the room and also
meow I wonder if I can make that work
[Music]
now wow
wowowowowowowow
wowow
wow
wowow where did that coming
wowowow wow
wow wow wow
[Music]
owow this sounds so real to
meow I sound like your
cat
oh I heard it
[Music]
smothie oh she came in
running
[Music]
owow did you hear
herow she does answer me she's like who
who why are you speaking my language now
what's
[Music]
wrong
do you hear
[Music]
her help me
movie She we're having a
conversation I love you
baby I love you wow how they say I love
you and meow
[Music]
wowowow
looking at me
baffled what do you
want no don't don't eat the weird hair
no I watched the video of uh really
vient cat where I honestly felt like oh
okay so there's like worse cats than
this movie in terms of waking someone up
in the morning I liked it I think on
Twitter so you guys if you stalk my
likes you might have seen it but
I think no what wait no it wasn't on
Twitter it wasn't on Twitter and I
really wanted to show you guys I
think let me find it in my history cuz
it was so funny holy
[\h__\h] um my
history I watched it sometime
today it's so funny it's so good there's
like this
girl who films her cat waking her up but
this cat is like on another
level where is uh let me
cat e where is it was it you was it
Twitter cat waking me
up ah wait I think it's this
[Music]
one I think it's the same cat but a
different video aren't you meow was
[Music]
marvelous oh my
God but that's nothing that's just the
cute meow but like wait where are the
where are the the ones where he eats the
hair of the
owner ah there it
is no wait wrong video this one what no
no no no no what I click one and I get a
different one what is this with YouTube
I click one video and it opens the wrong
one no
why
I have that uh today like several
[Music]
times okay let me type this into
Marley's most viral
[Music]
wakeups I got it you guys have to watch
this please watch it
please
[Music]
he eats her hair
so so
violently and then at the end what what
it what's the end it's like she actually
loses hair because of this
[Music]
cat it's so
good
this
cat this is
amazing staged I bet you put tuna in the
there no I think it's
real yeah like this cat is a
menace
she just sits on her oh that's kind of
cute
though I will suffocate you
[\h__\h]
a
a wait is is it the one that I watched
with the
ending
oh it's so cute wait I think it's
actually the wrong
one yeah it's part
two ah craziest wakeups is the one not
most viral okay here's the second one
just watch it and and please tell me
this is if this isn't hilarious and I
don't know what it
is this cat makes me feel better about
smoothie hm
this one's even more violent
yeah hope this movie doesn't get this
crazy I hope so too but when I watch
someone else have issues like this with
their cat I
feel like really amused but if this
would be happening to me I would be
[\h__\h] furious this is only funny
because it's happening to someone
else I am enjoying their suffering it's
cute and funny even though it's
obviously like for the
owner it would be a huge
[Music]
issue smovie is an angel compared to
this yeah they don't they don't try to
eat my hair my
cats I I wish they would like sit more
on me but like smoovie when she's
annoying me in the morning she also like
gets like really close to me but she
doesn't sit on me not even then then I
wish they would sit on
me I wish then I hear about other owners
who get annoyed by their cat sitting on
them because you can't move or it gets
too hot and all
that but I wish I wish they would do
it mhm oh but I did have a surprising
incident yesterday with
smoothie um
[Music]
I think smovie was in like a cuddly mood
and I just like tucked myself into bed
just to watch some
Netflix and warm myself up under my
blanket and then
smoothie for the first time ever she
shows interest into going under my
blanket and staying there for a
while so she she goes in and I'm like e
are you serious cuz sometimes she like
shows interest a little bit but she's
not serious about going in but this time
she actually like goes in and then sits
down and purr Pur purr purr and curls up
like right next to my body like under
the blanket and touching my body so
she's like
basically almost sitting on
me by her own
choice normally I always go to her and I
like her and we fall asleep while I have
my my hand on her tummy and all that but
this time she came to me under the
blanket right next to my tummy touching
my the side of my
tummy no so I was I was like
blessed I was so blessed I was so
happy yeah cuz the room generally was a
bit cold but I don't think it's cold on
a level that she would really mind like
it's not like she can't sleep out in the
open with that
temperature
but yeah she did seem to enjoy the
Warmness under the
blanket very rare special
moment
yeah so
happy if I turn the heating off she'll
be under there I don't know about that
like cuzz generally I keep it pretty
chill these
days there was only one time when she
wanted to go on there but I'll try it
again I am I did try it again today and
it didn't work
today it only worked yesterday today she
she like was that like under the blanket
for like 5 seconds and then left
[Music]
again yes please make use of your free
human heater
Smoothie
Please okay let's read this all I I can
eat dinner afterwards uh thank you hi
zly thank for the red chat thank you zly
love thank you for your love and your
support zly D I appreciate it space
waterful for the red super chat just
with one icon but thank you for being
there and for listening to me ranting
and
ranting very much appreciate it oh see
you here hi hello hello I'm so happy to
see you guys in the Super Chat reading
actually picking up your
orders I always imagine it like you guys
put up an order for you know takeaway
and then when I read the super chats
it's when I'm making them and giving you
your orders and if you're actually there
to take them home
that's like wow mind-breaking to
me it's
[Music]
amazing so it doesn't get cold this way
at ziply you're here too see you guys
are always here you guys who sent the
super chats it's like actually
fascinating to me that you guys actually
are always
here it's not like you send the Super
Chat and then you catch up with the
reading in the VOD or so no you're
actually here how
come
amazing
amazing thank
you uh so AK did I give you a kiss I
think I did but here's another one no no
no no no n phel d j47 d j d oh yeah
welcome back welcome come back it's nice
that you're back I hope you had some
good time without me you little [\h__\h]
yeah
but I mean it's not like I was like you
know affected at by you leaving at
all no not at
all I guess in faor it's a pinky so I
can I can read it uh I I don't know if
you want me to read it cuz this seems
pretty emotional and
personal don't know if you want me to
read it out
[Music]
loud maybe not seems really
personal okay okay okay but I I see it I
see
it so welcome back and great timing cuz
I'm also back back to cooking yesterday
I
cooked yeah I I ate those uh little
cabbage thingies for the first
time basically isn't it just like tiny
tiny cabbage or so because it kind of
smells like it and it looks like
it is it not just like small small
cabbage small small
cabbage yeah the Brussels
sprouts I hate those I hear that from so
many
people isn't it just small
cabbage Rosen coal yeah
[Music]
in Regional of Brussel wait BR Brussel
brussel sprout Brussel
is is Rosen cool
Brussel is that why they call it brussle
because BR Brussel is a city in Germany
I
think
ha now Belgian wait Brussel is in
Belgian order never mind it's in not in
Germany it's in Belgium I'm stupid I had
a feeling something was wrong about what
I just
said but it sounds so German
because of the
O so they are from
Belgium yeah well in German you don't
say brussel uh cool you say Rosen cool
you don't say the name of the city I
find it interesting that in English you
do you do specify where it's
[Music]
from man me not eating my dinner at this
place I'm so [\h__\h] hungry though I'm
going to warm up the soup I think and uh
bake some more bread I hope the soup is
still
good on the second day I mean it's
surely edible but
like I don't know cuz like I did the the
cream after cooking everything I added
some cream like cooking
[Music]
cream H and that kind of cooking cream I
feel like is not as good as the Fresh
Cream obviously
I don't know if it's really good for
warming up things several times thank
you thank
[Music]
you oh my God I'm such a mess I'm a mess
mess mess mess mess in the stress stress
stress but I'm still the best dressed
dress to impress blah blah blah
something like that little
seraphin let me tell you about
serim unforg yes why am I why am I
singing
[Music]
S I need to buy new new pants for real
I actually want to buy new pants because
the the one the ones that I have they
don't feel warm
enough I know I said a band pants
but at least like one new pair to
replace the the Dead
[Music]
one and where was I oh yeah J SW thank
you for the red super chat bot gang here
in a week late but I wanted to say that
whole Shar tank was amazing thank you ah
I was laughing about the pitches for
days after really you're awesome
worldwide dancing Phoenix B good luck
with everything thank
you yeah some some genius stroke struck
me during this trip I'm so happy with
all the all the all the streams I've
created what about fleece leggings
instead I have like fleece lined uh
tights but they're actually like kind of
too small
a little bit so they don't fit really
well I want to find new ones but it's
kind of hard to find like the good stuff
in actual stores but
also I don't know I feel like it's hard
to find
them should order online again but then
the size might not be good again though
I don't
know H Telly H I need to eat
F thank you Jas swor I'm so happy I'm so
happy happy to hear that let's do it
again sometime Travy thank you for two
Reds oo just want to thank wa for her
hard work thank you it was really a lot
of hard work man this trip was packed
with fun streams from Shar fun with
v the Anya told was great to the long
awaited kiadis and Mory girls talk and
return to memes with
hatada what what kind of
what kind of names are those and lovely
K with your pko Senpai yeah all of those
were so great man I appreciate you
pushing yourself the extra M like you
always do still take care of yourself W
after all there's only one Phoenix Right
wouldn't want to have to perform some
sort of blood ritual with your chickens
to summon ke alter as a replacement or
anything sounds like you want to give
that a try
though hm
H kind of sus statement at the end there
but thank you so much for the support
I'm glad you enjoyed all the content I
created in my trip M it was so stressful
though like
sheesh I
actually
uh like started planning out for my next
birthday started planning like what
songs and what people I want to invite
just like before the stream I started it
because I felt motivated and um last
time I also started really early uh this
is kind of like normally you would want
to plan like half a year
before which is I mean what I did last
time too but hopefully this time not big
delay but I have I have an exciting
theme personally exciting for me and I
hope I can make it
work but yeah I I hope that this time we
can start everything earlier like my
proposal was really early for this
current one but then the notice that
it's actually happening was like pretty
late so from there
on the when the stones started rolling
it was really really really rough like
so so much things to do in such a short
amount of time and I felt so overwhelmed
by it and it was really really
noticeable during my trip as well like
squeezing in so many things in in one
and a half weeks I I was like hoping to
learn more coros beforehand
too I mean I started started learning
some beforehand but couldn't Perfection
IE them so yeah I was a lot more
stressed and anticipated so I'm hoping
that next time I can personally
personally also prepare better for it um
but that means I need I need the the
approval stamp that it's happening Also
earlier hopefully this
time fingers
crossed but yeah I had a lot of fun in
Japan nonetheless even though it was so
much stress but I think it was a a
really good uh
efficient um what's the word efficient
and productive
trip
yeah
nice thank you Trevor G I hope I can get
to Tes tiles Tales of arise soon but I
don't know I'm waiting for they're
okay that you can play the until the
ending
now but I did say I didn't want to
stream too long during the
winter cuz I noticed how it's been
affecting me pretty
negatively so I guess it can wait maybe
until
after after the mold divs after
January possibly I guess but then at
that time when I come back I also want
to play a lot of other games right like
Yakuza for
example there's going to
be many many things to play but yeah
we'll see we'll see how it goes I'll
decide everything
spontaneously if now in December they're
saying oh you can play Tales of arise
DLC until the end now I might start it I
might do do
[Music]
it we see I'll leave it to
Destiny a [\h__\h]
my I have a
pain stinging
paink thank you for the pinky stay
strong Tel myth drew a lot of people in
whole life including me if it for you
guys we won't be here I hope they
realize this and change how they treat
you if you need to went just went V just
go tento it's good for your mental
health thank you I mean
I yeah I don't know I I I I I I didn't
expect me venting a little bit on
Twitter space would um blow up this much
uh I don't think that
was necessarily helpful but
um thank you for listening to my worries
and my
concerns I'll work hard
on having all these issues go
away behind the
scenes
um yeah and hopefully 2024 will be
overall
better we'll
see don't want to get my own hopes up
but um I'm not going to give up and I'm
going to continue working hard so thank
you for supporting Z Duke you and all of
the others for such a long time always
rooting for me and the other girls thank
you thank
you you're the best you're the best and
since we were like playing fan games
today T you remind me of it wasn't a fan
game was was a mod though but like that
was so early on with the Don't Starve
Together ever
one good
times good times so old though the
classtic
[Music]
yeah there's a change when a concert I
think
generally uh the goal is to have
everything on time for next year but I
mean I do believe that more things will
be on time next year like less delays
but there may have to be
other
um sacrifices to achieve
that from what I've heard but we'll see
we'll see enough of that just leave it
to me I'll I'll work hard be behind the
scenes
mhm more Frey Studio on a guy you're
hired I I will hire all of your
chickens to become my studio staff
h no but I think um 2024 will be quite
exciting in terms of frd especially
because of the exent
suit I think you guys will be seeing me
and Fredy more often for like smaller
things like YouTube shorts and little
solo
streams just need to get it to work um I
I haven't had time yet at all I didn't
even open the packages because I had no
time
mhm but I don't know maybe next week I
can get to it look at it how it works
maybe get it to work I I I hope I
[Music]
can please hire me I've only 20 into my
bank account oh
no
[Music]
ah have you planned some content with it
yet I I really hope um there's been like
[Music]
some gray gray area regarding YouTube
shorts
using someone else's music cuz like
origin finally before YouTube shorts
were a thing it was like um generally
the rule to only use
instrumentals for like archived things
only use instrumentals that you have the
rights to and thus when YouTube short
started uh to be a thing I I thought oh
surely that applies to YouTube shorts as
well so when remember when I uploaded
some YouTube shorts in 3D of me dancing
ing I would like
um I I uh the the Mas blue jeans one for
example I used an instrumental of hours
but also for like the
singing I sang over it because without
vocals that would be kind of sad but I
can't use the OG vocals either so I just
basically I lowkey covered
it no uh no mixing or so not a real
cover but just for the sake of the
YouTube short I basically made like a a
little key cover so just so that I could
have something to go along with the
dance
and that was definitely a very very very
safe way to play it but then
afterwards more and more I saw like
other whole life members
using
original uh audios audio sources for
like for example the the internet Angel
song and yeah they're like using the
music library thing and then I was like
JMA is this allowed can I do this too
then what who I thought I have to I I
can't use someone's original
audio unless it's like whole live music
but it was this was this was other
people's music but still still Japanese
though
so uh like the safest songs that we can
pick or Japanese cuz you know rights and
all that
um but yeah then it was like yeah I
guess probably if you use the music
library then it might be fine so I still
feel like it's kind of a gray area like
where we don't really have a clear
instruction of what we can do and what
we can't but I talked the other day with
some management people and I asked if um
since Dad is now seemingly
tolerable I asked if I could
um do kop dance covers on YouTube shorts
like the
challenges um with the actual music
through the for using the music library
because K-pop songs I looked through the
the rights thing that we use it's like a
library it's called Jazz wck anybody can
look it up they have like a public
library it's like a Japanese music
rights kind of thing for Broad casting
Etc and normally we have to check there
and see if it's uh like there's several
check marks in terms of Rights for what
it can be used and for what it can't be
used and for Japanese songs it's like
all of them are okay okay okay okay for
broadcasting and live streams and all
that but then foreign songs like
American songs and so on are usually no
no no no h so that's why we have to do
it un
archived um but then Korean songs I saw
generally have the same kind of rights
as the Japanese songs but we're still
kind of careful there because it's still
outside of Japan uh like music produced
outs outside of Japan so it was like I
don't know maybe they'll bunk us anyway
that kind of
stance but I don't know if I saw I see a
lot of people the Korean music fandom
like that upload dance covers or song
covers and they never get
bonked so I also mentioned that
before and especially now with the music
library usage more and more girls are
using like original songs from other
people so I thought maybe it can be
reconsidered and maybe I can do cap up
dance videos with the OG
music that's something I'm hoping
for uh to put a lot
of um a lot of my time and effort into
next
[Music]
year I want to learn those little dances
and then make YouTube shorts out of it
just need some clarity whether or not I
can do it or not
[Music]
H hm
M
yeah please please please let me dance
K-pop please please please please
please yeah cuz I I I want to I want to
there so good I'm sucker for K-pop
yeah that's the kind of stuff I want to
use the accents suit for why is it so
hard to
say oh [\h__\h] I thought it would be over
there over there but no there's a couple
more EV dang H dang R Hulu thank you for
the red super
chat your birthday today's my birthday
every time my birthday comes I feel sad
that the year is coming to an end ah cuz
yours is at the kind of uh at the end of
the year I hope everyone who the Super
Chat spends the remaining Year Without
Regrets same with k then uh you will
celebrate me right from the November
22nd with
collab oh
[Music]
single
KF s
[Music]
to happy
birthday sorry I'm
late m H she please teach me Korean
I I I completely
stopped I feel like I know nothing
nothing is in my brain
now I feel like I could still revive it
there's still
hope but it's not like I even have time
to learn it at all right now maybe 2024
after December May maybe even during my
break I can take the time to refresh my
Korean
[Music]
memory yeah ghosting a Kore no not
ghosting it was a set amount of time and
I could have extended but I didn't want
to because it was stressing me out and
honestly I would not have been able to
do much more after that because that's
when
my the whole stress of like album
creation and then going to Japan and all
of that started so it was a good choice
for me to end it
there and continue with my solo
studies um cuz honestly like I learned
plenty during that time I just need to
like
really burn it into my brain and
yeah get so good at what I learned that
I can freely make use of
[Music]
it yeah I want to yeah internalize
yeah so I I I'm not giving up yet I
really really don't want to have those
Korean lessons go to
waste so please wait please wait for me
kareim Bros I'm going to try to get back
into it
no just need to move to Korea for a year
that would probably be really really
great but I obviously can't do
that
and Y Dan hul danim Tracy D J thanks for
the pinky thanks giving I'm giving
thanks to the best tal an unpaid Un
unionized Chef could ask
for you've inspired my hands why did you
mention the UN the
union Are You flexing are you like
trying to get on my good side by
mentioning these things you've inspired
my hands cook and my legs to travel all
over this year you've worked so hard
boss thanks for inspiring me to do the
same post Happy Thanksgiving I really
have no
connection with this holiday at all
but I hope you guys had a great
Thanksgiving
[Music]
anyway oh I wouldn't mind more Korean
super chats so that I can try to read
them
yeah but you're American
jeans
well you wrote it exactly with j e a ANS
so you should know my American jeans do
not mean anything at
[Music]
all
ah I really loved the jokes about the
the important announcement maybe me
already having my DNA results and being
like I'm I'm
American guys I'm American oh
no or even guys I'm French
[\h__\h]
no don't
[Music]
worry sometime in 2024 I want to take
that
test uh where was I uh oh yeah looking
for the top thank you twice by the time
you read this your pain is better oh my
my my weird ass neck pain yeah that is
better I'm just you know back to the
usual chronic pain let's
go but I'm used to it anyway so I'm okay
I'm
okay H I'll leave it a death cuz I'm
[\h__\h]
starving
yeah I should be like chunky wonky but
towards you
guys and me like
like I'm starving give me food give me
food give me food ah feed
me I'm hungry I'm
hungry ah
food I'm starving I haven't eaten for 1
hour just kidding I I haven't eaten for
longer than that but
uh that's what the drama dramatic
the this the drama from the cats feel
like I've been eaten for 5 minutes I'm
starving haven't cleaned myself for 2
minutes I'm so disgustingly dirty I must
clean myself
more haven't slept for 30 minutes I'm so
tired I need to
sleep cats
cats be
like suffering
24/7 Advent calendar yes Advent calendar
in 2
hours so hope you guys are ready for the
official launch and for the first video
of the
20203 whole life
English Advent but also myth and promise
[Music]
calendar
yeah and with that I will leave you
guys and oh yeah at the end I'll I'll
say one more time I was using hyper x h
headphones during the the stream and
they were comfortable and audio was all
all perfect so if you guys are looking
for some
headphones maybe scroll through the
hyper X catalog yeah skip ad no don't
skip don't skip me don't this is part of
my part of my stream and part of the
experience ah yes I guess oh yeah yeah
yeah to senses uh life I am part of it
so check it out check it out in case you
haven't
seen
um Cho sense is
live I will be
there yeah
yeah
mhm is it tomorrow it's not tomorrow
right when is less than two days let's
go
[Music]
no already ahead of you already have a
pair you already have a pair of hyperx
headphones for real
wow
tomorrow yeah the second 2nd December
H you didn't know well she just
announced it today the lineup so yeah
hyperx is half my setup h for
real oh I already have a hyx mouse but M
wao I'm using hyx right now
oh
oh had a hyperx keyboard it was
good oh I have a hyperx keyboard oh wow
there's so many actually I didn't think
uh hyperx was like that common outside
of
Japan not a whole all all right then
then you guys know what's up then you
guys know they have good products all
right then then then I don't need to
advertise it anymore right
okay guys in German we say I'll feed us
in yeah I'll feed us
[Music]
in tomorrow members
only he double wave
by it's like pick me up pick me
up ah oh
oopsie take me
up
yay one more time pick me
yay thank you
[Music]
bye-bye did I say in German we say he
does in well I said it now
[Music]
now