foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hello everybody
[Music]
afternoon evening indeed welcome
everybody to a special collaboration yay
I should have given you some like
applause soundtrack too yes Applause
sound effect would have been nice
I hear some of that that sounds good can
I hear some more
thank you thank you thank you very much
uh so let's start with some
self-introduction I'm takanasikiara the
owner of this channel uh from kfp
um first generation whole life English
whole life myth next to me please
introduce yourself
hi I'm Ina
also from oh really
yeah
same as Kiara oh thanks for having me
today
such a pleasure to have you here again
today for a really special occasion uh
but before we get started guys we have a
hashtag it's maybe if you look at the
top right you see it it's up there hello
connect is that how you would pronounce
it
I repeat Hello Kira connect
yes please everybody feel free to use it
on Twitter and tweet about not only the
stream but also maybe if you're already
playing the game or in the coming weeks
when the event is actually happening
feel free to use that hashtag
um to post screenshots of the game or
maybe some yeah
strategies or whatever
yeah yeah yeah and yeah we would love to
see that you can also of course add kfp
and Taco Time to it if you want yes yeah
all right um
[Music]
[Laughter]
honestly I did put it away for a few
days but wait I warmed it up before
again I sat on it I sat on it you got my
job and I'm using the extra chair right
now
yeah yeah you're back and it's nice to
have you back we have the big screen up
again
um actually I will
um
well this time Taco Tony came back
together for a very special reason me
and Ina had the opportunity to be part
of a collaboration with the game yeah
not only I'm sorry yeah not only us it's
a pecula senpai and LA perlasu from her
life Japan are in it too uh actually let
me down and show you is this the right
one that's the right one that is it
look at us oh my God it looks so cool oh
my goodness
so yeah we'll be joining uh the whole
live X of Valkyrie connect collaboration
so let's start with a quick introduction
on what what Valkyrie connect is right
I'll switch back to the other picture
um
there it is
stop uh Valkyrie connect is a free to
play of course
jrpg Japanese role-playing game on
smartphones uh and steam and iOS 2 as
far as I know yeah and we'll be
appearing in the game during the event
if you play fruity event you'll be able
to get us as characters drum roll please
hello
[Applause]
what a deal what a deal
yeah I think when people first heard
about us doing this collaboration I
think a lot of them pre-download the
game to get some like ink and currency
in order like to like pay for us because
they thought that we wouldn't be free so
that I I heard some of KFC was already
playing the game yeah but turns out
we're free so you can get us without
relying on the luck outside now
really nice especially because I think
you know a lot of new players will
obviously join to play this to to get us
as characters so obviously they don't
have many fans huh yeah yeah
I don't have any funds yet either
yeah it's okay we'll grind and get
ourselves you know yeah we're playing
the event grinding not for the currency
we're you know getting those points in
the event and
um this is the first time that we're
like appearing in a game like this not
only promoting it as a YouTube stream
but also as characters in the game with
like original outfits and even
implemented in other ways that we'll
talk about in a moment so yeah those
special outfits wow what did you think
about being implemented like this
oh man you know
I always think about like what if we're
in like another world we're actually
part of like an RPG like a lot of
classes would we be and like what kind
of skills we would have and I feel like
it's kind of like go look into that like
you can finally use your sword and
shield you know as well as like I think
you have like different weapons too
it's like me in the art we'll see a
little bit later but yeah and then I use
my Pentacles as well as my uh my book my
elk town and all that everything
everything your day everything is so
exciting and full attire
you came prepared let's say it like that
um
is that for me also like I think it was
um maybe it's
it's kind of applies to all of myth but
you know especially for me
um because like I'm like a part-time
Warrior
not only the owner of kfp but also
part-time Warrior so it makes sense for
me to be in a game where I can actually
fight and yeah yeah that's really cool
and and they gave us kind of a fantasy
look but we'll talk about that later oh
my God don't get me started
I can talk about art all day well
actually you know what we're actually
talking about it now now that I realized
oh nice yeah nice nice egg white nice
Segway yeah we're getting uh into it
we're gonna talk about the outfits first
now oh yeah I kind of forgot to say that
we're not actually showing any gameplay
today because the event hasn't quite
started yet it's starting on I think the
17th
right the 17th let me so wait I forgot
the time in UTC it was uh 8 AM UTC on
the 17th May is when the actual event
starts uh in the game you can already
play the game of course if you want to
but it will take a little
bit longer for three more days until
it's happening yeah depending on your
time if we can get some some uh initial
game playing done like a tutorial and
stuff so you can ready yeah I
heard there's a really
um useful event going on right now as
well where online you can get a lot of
when was there a lot of free
um not free but I don't know there's a
good event going on right now so it's a
good time to join better now than never
okay so let's uh put this away for a
moment and this away as well and we're
gonna look at this outfit first
oh that looks so good ah it does it does
I want to make it bigger but the screen
is so small but I'll make it a little
bit because I'm bigger and put it here
you guys see this gorgeous they're so
cool yeah
tell me your thoughts about it you know
uh I stayed at it for quite a while
you know like when when we were first
like
um deciding our outfits and stuff they
gave us like different colors variations
and stuff and uh mine looked a little
different but I was like I think I think
like this color combination with this
look really good and then they were like
okay and so this is uh this is why we
came up with and uh tummy window yes
tummy window
I love how they kept like
um in it they kept it in I would say
some other
the whole
aesthetic and not not aesthetic but like
it gives me Vibes of your original
outfit still like it's not completely
different when I look at it I'm like wow
that's that's Nino my Inon is turned
into a jrpg character and it fits so
perfectly
yeah
I love your feet too look at your feet
Muffy are you so small and they got some
stones on it and then they I think
you're wearing ballerinas I think those
are probably hurts way less than your
normal shoes
[Laughter]
probably this slide I'll go outside
often so I don't have to wear my shoes
yeah those are like really really really
really really tall platform shoes that
you wear normally so this is way better
for fighting obviously exactly but I use
a lot of spells and you know ranged
attacks so I don't have to walk around
this oh yeah yeah you're an arranged
attacker yeah looking gorgeous with that
magic I to be honest when I play like
Emma more princess or something like
that I like to use ranged attackers
personally so I would love to use you in
my team but a ranged attacker is always
a must anyway so yeah
there's actually comments from the game
staff uh well this design so let me read
it uh to you
do you want to read the comments
yes do it do it
okay comments from the game stuff number
one design point is the name is designed
around the navel is important I am
I see wait wait
holy is going into a dangerous territory
though below
too closely continue I mean they can
take they can take they can they can
take a look at it uh in game
privately yes
[Music]
number two the left hand is actually
casting a magic spell and doing a
capitol to takodachi oh
so you a pretty giant guy giant yeah
basically basically I can't believe I
can't believe the staff actually wrote
this cute
okay
um number three yes you could say we
followed the car
eat now rule of design I don't
understand
what does this mean
basic rules of design there's this whole
bunch of basic rules on YouTube
they followed it but they really wanted
to add their foot in there what's the
plan though what's the original word
it's a car part cardinal cardinal rule
pretty sure that's what they wanted to
say and it was the card in the car in
the room
should we laugh they tried I think they
want us they would be hurt if we
wouldn't laugh should we laugh
okay
um hold on I can fix this I can I can
find the left
oh my God I'm so sorry
everyone laughed
yeah
thank you staff Son thank you
thank you okay well yeah I think yours
is really really cool you also look very
happy and excited in your face
expression yeah I can destroy the world
with the smile I'm good with that and
your onion ring got a huge upgrade
oh yeah it's like I went from an onion
ring to like
let me try to make it bigger look there
it is look at that wow that's really
that's like even more priestess-like so
next up is
my mine here there you go
yes you might have already seen it and
it's in the thumbnail but yeah actually
um
our character designs are like based on
characters that are already in the game
so it's like they're combining our
designs with characters that are already
in the game and for me it's a character
called and for inai was a character
called soda the people who play in
valkyr Connect may actually feel like oh
oh this looks familiar
so uh as you can see my shield like kind
of has been turned into something like
Beyblades on fire
oh
I don't know what would you call it baby
Hot Wheels yeah it's really cool and I
think my my candy corn sword as people
like to call it got a little bit
extended and it's also on fire so
overall like they definitely made my
weapons look even even more a badass and
um
you know have you noticed out of
um out of all the four whole life events
that are in this
I did it
have you noticed I'm the only one who
has cleavage
the beautiful thighs of Aquarius chicken
but are you are you aware of the
cleavage though
well you know there's three of us versus
one so I think you're outnumbered here
outnumbered by walls but there there's
only free will so there's still an exit
I can still run away from you guys if
there was a fourth wall then I would be
in a room
[Laughter]
you know when you first put out the um
the banner with all four of us that's
the first thing
it's yeah it's anyways
thank you beautiful outfit you also have
tummy window I do maybe maybe it's a
Volcan connect artists or staff really
like tummies
oh good taste yeah and I also have some
kind of like wings that are they it
looks like my hair an extension of my
hair but I think it's wings you know
yeah it's kind of like a cape but not
really yeah so the comments from the
GameStop uh for my outfit are number one
the famous revealing plus leggy
leggy leggies legs yes it has dark socks
that are different from the usual yeah
mine are usually white but they still
have that that shape
um that might like my socks usually have
with the wing shape so we kept that uh
to resemble the original outfit
it is a bit revealing I guess oopsies
but but it is less revealing than my OG
outfit I think
[Music]
oh it is in some aspects
um
number two is this Kiara is most
definitely not bottom left of course
because we threw that word away a long
time ago but
no I've been I've graduated from bottom
left uh since day one in my opinion they
won
and number three is she can make
delicious Fried Chicken just by swinging
this sword at chickens oh what oh cause
it's on fire I'm literally cooking
chickens
when I swing the sword at them and
Grilling them
I thought you didn't serve
that's actually yeah you know you know I
kind of it's like how I got sick of
saying I'm from Australia I also kind of
got sick of saying vegan it's been
pointed out to me lately
oh I'm just I'm just going with the like
with the reality yeah I've got so many
complaints about it not being vegan so
we're just accepting reality at this
point yeah
but you know what Ina
it's just as much as I can fry chickens
with that sword I can also fry your
takodati what then
or they'll be happy with that honestly
oh
all right nice well we still have
something yeah look at the other ones
too while we're at it would you like to
uh read the comments from the game staff
for pecoran's outfit yes
[Music]
I want you to read it okay okay
comment from the game stuff number one
the theme is meat and clean princess who
is not a lore Criminal part looks very
cute yeah can we really say that after
what she said in
um the the little question and answer
video that I posted on the on the
Twitter yeah have you guys seen that
there were four videos one of each of us
on Twitter on the valcare connect
Twitter
um where we kind of introduced ourselves
uh while bouncing and vibing to a little
music yeah if you didn't watch it yet
you should watch it but uh yeah
I think this is very convincingly a say
still character it is it is but I feel
like she'll she's like if she was like a
magical girl she'd be the type who would
just draw things and be like fire
explosions in the back and she'll just
be like okay
[Music]
the comment is that this pet Corazon
doesn't look like she would say okay
oh yeah she would probably stay here she
would probably say it
[Music]
just say it cuter moist yeah
but oh my God I really really really
really love this outfit so much like
this is so cool yeah it's a huge
crystals bunny ears yeah and the Frills
oh the frills
[Music]
I want those shoes
looks amazing okay we have one more uh
really cool like I
um I like how she kind of matches color
wise a little bit with you with all the
purple and yeah and all that um
you want to say
it's one thing we see her hands
yes true
oh that's what they look like she
actually has some nails long stabby
nails on her fingers you see that
yeah those remind me of those corn
snacks you know what I mean
is probably in reality just Dad and she
painted them purple because she wanted
to look cool typical junipio
it's like it's like the the chunee
cosplay you know yeah yeah yeah yeah but
let's be real she looks really badass oh
my God she's cute that Lance would you
call it the Lance
yeah
yeah oh my god oh it's so cool I can
totally see that in the game which I
mean it will be in a game so I mean it
will be
so the comments from the game staff says
number one the theme of her dress is
kind of revealing as if she's trying to
say I
[Music]
am
yeah she looks a bit more mature than
usually yeah yeah her score even goes
like a little you know yeah yeah
the heels she has she has that somewhat
more mature
um Vibe around her mm-hmm
the comment number two says instead of
ymd we aim for an atmosphere that will
make people want to properly call her
Yamada son you know with the honorific
guys don't forget
sorry I keep on calling you son because
um we haven't really talked yet so kind
of unsure about it I used to call it
oh I'm I'm I'm I'm kind of scared so I
can't say
looking really cool I like her outfit
too the socks shoes and everything about
it the the one sleeve that's different
from the other one
oh yes yeah uneven asymmetric we like it
we like it uh I know a lot about
asymmetry oh yeah you do you do
all right besides that we also have 3D
models in the game but
I think staff Sam doesn't want us to
show it to you yet uh because I have
nothing to show you but remember you
were one of the lucky ones who've
already received a YouTube ad on the
game you have been blessed by the
YouTube algorithm I've been reported
that there are YouTube ads going around
right now about the um Hollow Curry
connect collaboration so you may have
already seen us in action in 3D but if
you haven't then
you may have to wait a little bit longer
they want to do the proper introduction
or something on Twitter or some or
somewhere there first so yeah be a bit
patient but thanks for seeing us in
action it's kind of like in a not quite
full body but like chibi style right
yeah
looks really cute yeah but it is the the
outfit that you just saw made into a
chibi model look forward to us to seeing
us
yeah yes yes so but there are some
illustrations that we haven't shown yet
and that we will be wondering
right now yes now right now oh one more
thing that's in the game is drum roll
please
[Music]
damn
wow cute
um
you can chat in the game actually and it
looks like there are some stamps
featuring us we have one for pecora Sam
by the corn picker
my call
is that how she would say it
I don't know I hate myself you need to
stop you need to sound a little more a
little more like
a little more like evil cute you know oh
like like uh like if you if you hear
like uh kick going eat my clothes
or heat wagaha is calm
hey
yes my dog yes my dog chat is already
already acknowledging it oh wow wow wow
she has so much Authority
wow wow and then we have leader as
you're saying wow it almost sounds like
what as your style says wow
[Music]
good
it's also like yours and and pickles are
kind of like a hello stamp
yeah
but I mean was very very versatile yeah
very emotional
foreign
and then mine is actually German so I'm
kind of worried that people will even
even be like it's besides kfp if anyone
will even use this stamp because it's
German and you don't know what it means
probably but let me tell you guys it
means thank you
thank you thank you yeah it's a word
that um I have implemented in my
chicken's brain uh like a billion times
by saying it a billion times in Super
Chat reading so yeah they know it good
good
so if you guys need some advice after
starting the game you could try asking
some veterans in the chat as well and
use the stamps to maybe look cuter
when you have chat and game that you can
use stamps it's always like
etiquette almost to you know use a stamp
yeah at the beginning or like at the end
or yeah you know talk to people it gives
us a lot okay
sounds good all right so that's the
stems guys have fun using those
and next up
ah
guys now this is some
may have heard about if you followed the
valkyrie connect Twitter and you may
still be a little bit confused about so
we will explain how the whole event
works now all right like roughly I will
try I'll try roughly now because itself
do you see this image everybody do you
see it Ina
I see a kiawa it's about gifting and
being gifted I suppose yeah this is the
dreams come true equals connect your
wish
event
and there is three different gift plans
it's all about gifting it's like I said
yeah
Christmas game early this year yeah this
is why I told my my fans in my stream
previously when I announced this that
there's something special besides us
being implemented in the game and I'm
very excited about it because I like
give two doesn't like gifts I love games
and also here we have different
Expressions on these ones
oh you're so happy it was so excited
yeah perfect
um perfect yeah
okay so this collab was made with the
over our arching theme of dreams come
true so we're going to show you the
different parts of that
oh yeah I remember they asked us a whole
bunch of questions yeah yeah forehand
yeah
yeah yeah that is quite a while ago but
yeah by playing the game you guys can
earn points that you can use to cheer
for us and based on the total number of
the points there are three different
level of gifts that we will be receiving
like actual gifts that's the thing like
first when they first told us about this
I thought they were just like talking
about like visual gifts yeah or maybe
someone is gonna draw something you
remember our Christmas collab where we
gave each other yeah like random gifts
that we drink
yeah it was like drawing gifts yeah pngs
but it's gonna be actual gifts I thought
it was something like that but no yeah
we're getting actual gifts and that that
was very confusing to me and at some
point but okay like Are you seriously
how do we even deserve so much but
apparently we deserve it oh
yeah so the first one that you see here
is the from the players to the talents
to the members gifts a part
um you guys to us yeah you guys if you
play the game you'll be able to give us
these gifts the first is this one you
guys decide for us what you want to give
to us there will be a survey to ask for
your present ideas and a few of them
will be chosen at random so come up with
something good
what do you guys want to give to us you
can also choose some some crazy things
that you wouldn't be able to afford
because I think volunteering connect is
paying for it
oh
[Music]
sorry I had to drink some water yeah
that's the first one
and then
we have the second one
something to us
pickle pickle
that's I I don't I'm not sure if I want
to open her present it's probably some
prank inside
honestly I'd probably scan it before I
open it but I'd still keep it we'll keep
it in the in the original packaging it's
probably smart don't open it
African one is from talents to other
talents yeah yeah got asked what
presents we wanted ourselves so the
development team
oh wait sorry well I'm reading the wrong
thing
really well that's what presents we want
to give to the other talents who are
appearing in the corner and at this
level those presents we chose will be
sent out to for example what I chose for
Ina to receive will be sent out to Ina
eventually yeah and mine's a Kiara oh
what about your feet but the thing is
you know when I when I was thinking
about these things like what when I when
I came up with the ideas I was still
under the impression that this was like
joking and and they're not receiving
real things so I came up with some kind
of Mimi ideas I'm so sorry mine was mine
was kind of half mean half pretty cool
but when they actually told me I was
like oh yeah she likes to
it but I was like oh dear I I gave
especially to that but also I came up
with an with a present that I feel like
is not very equal to the other ones
cheap but I'm like
like I can't change and I feel bad
I guess we'll find out what we uh gift
to each other yeah
and that's her like if we can tell you
about every single thing that we came up
with or not yeah everything yet but I
think we are gonna go over something
later yeah yeah but look forward to it
I'm also I have no idea what pecula is
gonna give to me for example I only know
yeah maybe maybe maybe I know what you
know gives to Me Maybe maybe are you
sure about that I'm not sure I don't
know do I know
but yeah I don't know the others uh for
sure so yeah looking forward to that and
then and then sorry I kind of already
talked about it but uh the last one is
um us receiving
presents that we personally wished for
that we said we wanted when they asked
us what do you want here's the budget
tell us anything and
um yeah Valkyrie connect will be sending
it to us which is
but it's too much like what what how
much do you want to give to us what the
hell yeah I was like that's what I
thought it was just like uh like in-game
um items but apparently it's uh real
items so yeah actually
um
not a little bit bad but they kind of
gave a pretty like budget so I gave some
crazy ideas and sometimes that normally
I wouldn't be able to get myself because
for example they wouldn't ship it to
Austria normally
huh
is shippable to Austria at like usually
too so no it's not you okay
[Music]
yeah but so many presents Ina how do you
feel about that I know oh man I don't I
don't know if I'm ready for this Brian
my heart can't pick all this all this
excitement I don't know when it will
come but I'm so excited about it looking
forward to it yeah I mean we gotta
reached we gotta reach the levels with
everyone's help yeah so please help us
help us
[Music]
because I know what it's gonna be the
one from the Stefan from well can
connect I really want it I really really
really really want it
okay so
please try your best guys to get those
points and make us happy it's your way
of giving gifts to us yeah yeah let's
get grinding
all right so
um
okay okay
um um next up we have
a little bit of a small quiz because
um we will try to guess each other's
answer to see if you know we know each
other well and like what we would give
to one another
oh yeah yeah you can see that kind of
stuff
um it
so I will stop the really dramatic bgm
now
yeah
because we have some ding ding ding and
Boo-Boo sounds that we can use as well
so
um I have four questions Ina what
questions and we have to try to get the
same answer
I'm not sure I can do this
um don't worry there's
nothing that's gonna happen if we get it
wrong I think I think as far as our song
in The Script there's also chat guessing
too yeah
hello carry connect oh yeah if you want
to if you're that fast
um
Okay so
okay yeah okay okay okay I can do this
uh here is a question number one uh drum
roll please
um
thing
okay so the first question is
what would Nina my innerness do if she
landed in an isakai World AKA other
dimension in case you don't yeah Chad is
saying sleep oh
it's such a waste no way you would say
that so you obviously know the answer I
suppose have you done this before
I don't remember I feel like I've
answered it before but I don't know
where I I had the same feeling because I
got the same question too but I don't
really yeah understood these questions
what if we don't remember let's do some
come up with one uh on the spot like
that that's the best thing anyway
because that will maybe really show what
you would really do so you know thinking
time
I need to think too though
[Music]
um
okay I have a I think I have an idea but
it's never gonna overlap with yours I'm
pretty sure it's not I'm sure yeah I
don't know there's like so many options
there is but I think there's a pretty
obvious uh really oh should I change
mine
I mean it's between very two different
obvious answers okay okay
I I you do you think you
I think mine might be one of the more or
less one of the obvious ones all right
should we say at the same time
sure okay
um
three two one
[Music]
I said
I said to Kai food you said just eat
food yeah yeah like eat the food at the
isekai because you just don't know what
kind of food they have you know
I'm a very simple person
eat or sleep and I was like you know
what I can't sleep yeah right that would
be such a ways to go to Ithaca and then
just sleep you gotta eat food exactly we
gotta eat or like look around first
before you sleep so no but I saw some
answers in the chat saying something
about finding a potion shop or so for
example
what if they don't have a potion shop of
course they have a potion shop it's an
easy guy no what is it guy is like in
like a Sci-Fi world like it doesn't have
to be fantasy world you know but since
we're you know in a jrpg game I wouldn't
imagine it's a rpg-ish kind of like a
world in the same style you know
let's still go for the food I mean
that's you can do that anywhere I agree
I took off the food get those it's a guy
cup noodles
exactly all right or if they don't have
cup noodles I'll be like wait brilliant
I can open a cup noodle shop oh my God
but then you're kind of like in that
isakai you're not really the protagonist
then you're kind of an NPC no no no have
you not seen those isak guys where he's
like I got isekai and I started making a
great living by making a cup noodle shop
but somehow ended up defeating the Demon
Lord volume one
I feel like you would just be like
blending in with all the other shops in
the main shopping street with your
potions oh no no you get the protagonist
stuff you know let's see okay okay well
we got another question number two okay
question number two uh
um yes uh next question is oh that
was sorry oh
wait oh oh I overroded um
could it be could it be uh
oh oh
do it ah
do I have it
I spy with my little eyes I have a
question Kiara
here it is question three okay oh it
says question three oh sorry but it's
still a different question okay it's
question two yeah it's question two
what did Piana choose to give to ninoma
inanus
oh
so this is where you actually know what
I
thought of giving to Ina
I actually I think I gave free ideas we
all I think gave like free audience I
think so yeah yeah but then the staff
chose what they think was like possible
so actually make or like give
okay I'll give you some thinking time
because I obviously know the answer
thank you
I mean you said you said it was a meme
answer right
at least for me or did you change it I
didn't change it but I think they turned
my me monster into something more
realistic
probably other answers were more meme
than yeah they chose the most realistic
one and made it even more realistic
and I give you I'll give you five more
seconds five four one two three
two
one
okay and now oh now we'll say it okay
um
um on one we say it
free
two
one a cup noodles a mouse
a what
a mouse pad
yeah I thought you're gonna give me like
the joke mouse pad like
I think which is why they changed my cup
noodles dispenser idea because I wanted
legit like like you know like a jeto hum
Viking like something that keeps on
dispensing the cup noodles
um that was changed into
um a collection of cup noodles uh okay
okay
like hundreds hundred a box of hundreds
at least at least I hope so I'm running
out of cup meals all right and how did
you know
well I mean you know
that's all yeah yeah that's true every
time every time we like before class
they're like oh actually I'm just like
cup noodles and I had a feeling you were
running out of it so
[Music]
um
I do I do so
the next question
is the other way around what did enan is
choose to gift to takanashiqui free
this is
honestly thought it was gonna be like an
inking gifts I thought of this oh then
when it translates to like a real gift I
was like oh yeah this is this kind of
work
oh yeah
[Music]
I kind of no but I'm not sure if I know
oh
similar to an item in our cover song
together
very uh item
okay item we we had in there
okay I think
okay I have
oh which one should I go for it
um
uh okay but
since time well I could have consider
that they're actually like sending this
to me so it has to be like it can't
possibly be the DJ booth like they're
not gonna send a DJ booth to me right
all right all right okay I think I have
it okay okay and on on one we say it
okay
okay three two one a Roomba
oh what did you say a room sunglasses
like shades
okay that means
what sunglasses are they gonna send me
like any sunglasses like or the pixel
sunglasses or
um I can send them to you later but they
actually sends me like what what
glasses and I was like oh this is pretty
cool
so they showed you like is this okay and
you're like yeah this this will do
yeah oh oh okay hopefully hopefully
they're um nice ones that will protect
my eyes from the Sun very well pretty
good okay
sunglasses you chose for me but why why
did you choose sunglasses in you
because I was I was looking I was
listening to our cover together and then
I was because okay at first I thought it
was going to be like meme answers for
like
oh it was like the shades that we had in
the cover song would look very cool yeah
it was also a little bit confused about
in the beginning so I get to we were
laughing when you see what I got for
pecula and foreign
I hope you didn't gift her Dynamite
anyway last question
um what what how come this you can't do
if she landed in the isakai world other
dimension
I don't know I don't know
look in my
instant guy let me look at my Discord
thingy did I ever answer this
no I feel like we've answered it before
somewhere I feel so good but I can't
find anything on Discord
um
no I don't know I I wouldn't find
anything now I don't know what my answer
was what was my answer what would I do
um what would you do Kiara
oh let's maybe Chad knows what I would
do
oh fast food Empire every branch
look pretty pretty convincing here you
know
okay okay and you'll never get this
though sorry are you sure
all right I'll give you a few more
seconds five
four
three
two
one
okay okay on three two one you say it
and I say it all right or I I won't say
it I'll I'll just do it I think meaning
because it's gonna be incorrect
find the cat camel me girl and flirt
with her
hmm
what find a cat girl and flirt with her
yeah
it's somewhat close you know what I'll
give you both
okay we're gonna make a cat cafe a boat
so it's gonna be all cats like cat girls
I was gonna find just a talking cat not
a cat girl I just want to find a talking
cat
what yeah that is true that's why I gave
you half a half the correct Point down
at the party you know wink wink no I
just want an older cat that can actually
tell me like talk to me have a
conversation tell me what's wrong you
know stuff like that a talking cat would
be nice
anyway okay so let me turn on the bgm
again
Nice Shot hope that wasn't too noisy by
the way guys if anything if it was noisy
it's too late now all right so
um I like your ideas about opening a kfp
guys but
priorities about cat girls
oh ain't no more I put chickens chickens
dressed up as cat girls
um
oh chicken little cat ears on the tail
okay well I think that's a good idea
because it will look super cute
[Music]
all right I don't know I have to see I
have to speak
thank you guys for participating thank
you enough
we got we got uh one and a half things
correct I think
which is actually impressive I mean we
were pretty good pretty good I think we
would get anything
all right so
um we are near the end now but I would
like to you know do some
some something that sounds very scripty
but I need to tell you guys about the
company
yes announcement so wow
um there's a Twitter campaign and a
special Twitter campaign going on to
automatically change your icon on
Twitter yeah you may have already seen
it um I've seen I posted it in Japanese
maybe they're still posting in English
or they already did I only saw it in
Japanese
um but there's a website where you can
register and your icon on Twitter will
change accordingly there's like four
versions one for me one for Ina one for
pecula one four and
maybe you guys if you want to join you
hit up the following website I'm gonna
put it in the chat right now that should
that should be the right link
did someone try
the one you're covering
don't cover it up
yes so you can do that and then there's
another thing the collab event obviously
that we talked about the whole time the
event begins on May 17th 2022 and which
is a Tuesday on 8 00 a.m UTC which is
GMT as well I think yeah
um you can get access characters in the
game for free of course so we hope
you'll cheer for us in the game yeah
yeah you want to say the next line you
guys in game
and as you said you can download the
game ahead of time
um right now there is a cool event going
on where you can collect a lot of cool
characters uh as well and and get those
little things and so on so yeah we
recommend it I think we I don't know if
we mentioned he we're we're voiced in
the game oh yeah you can hear us yeah we
did some voice lines yeah we did we did
um so that's that's another thing no one
didn't even mention that thank you Nina
smart one is this remembered
so you can fight with us you can listen
to us you can chat with using our stamps
you can gift us things thank you so much
yeah so I also want to say a big thank
you to Valkyrie connect for choosing us
for this collaboration it's a big honor
and so exciting right now
can't wait I'm so excited thank you
thank you thank you
[Music]
but yeah so for the Japanese stuff as
well thank you very much thank you thank
you guys for joining us everybody in the
chat and we hope you enjoy the game play
as much as you can get us those lovely
gifts it will be like Christmas
yeah and uh any ending greetings India
uh well the usual thank you very much
everyone
um for joining the stream and uh thank
you for awkward connect for bringing us
in the game I'm actually very excited to
see
you see how how tastina talks in the
game
[Laughter]
I'm sure it will sound super super cute
and the taco daddies will melt when they
hear your voice
yeah I can't wait I'm glad that
um you're also in the game with me so I
won't be annoying as well
yeah I'm so happy I was chosen to be in
there with you and also
especially you know I'm a huge fan of
pecula senpai I have always been so it's
like
what we eat together as four that's four
four is not a big number you know to be
able to get into that number you gotta
be pretty happy
everybody for making this possible and
yeah we'll see you guys
soon in our streams Ina's channel is in
the description of course and in German
we say
finish it
[Music]
is
oh yes yes
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you everybody bye-bye
[Music]
foreign