foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
that's true
[Music]
I'm not here
I'm only in your imagination
[Music]
foreign
where am I
where did I add because I walked
somewhere else hi oh oh so
[Music]
ah
um
[Music]
just the hips no wait wait wait wait
foreign
I'm not feeling so well
ah you know
like I'm
I'm fine but I'm not oh
[Music]
hello wise I I don't think the face
tracking is [\h__\h] one
that's the wrong one
[Music]
um
yeah now it's working
[Music]
I don't feel so well
yeah I mean
nice movie this movie is still lying on
the beanbag you know she curled up on
the bean bag so I put the the ring fit
ring
over here to make her feel even more
comfortable in her ring
and the thing she really likes it are
you hearing the bgm guys
I I so okay I got things to explain
so first of all I only slept like
[Music]
five and a half to six hours
um
uh-huh
yeah oh chats
chat is not complete yet
uh and
[Music]
there you go there you go beautiful
beautiful
uh yeah I only slept like five and a
half or six hours because yesterday in
preparation for today thinking that I
wouldn't sleep wouldn't be able to sleep
so early anyway I thought well
might as well like set everything up now
right and then I noticed when I was
setting it up of course
um
oh I'm not standing like that not really
uh of course
uh I was having these audio issues again
so I tried setting up the road cast as
well but then I noticed
that the headphone jack is not like you
know the simple one it's the thicker one
and so I was like okay can this thing do
Bluetooth
and yes in theory it can so I tried
setting up my bluetooth headphones for
it
but I got pretty far I did it
successfully but then somehow I didn't
hear anything still and I'm I'm still
like not sure about setting that thing
up like things I tried things but
uh I failed in the end so then I gave up
after wasting and like 50 40 minutes on
on the road caster uh I went back to the
grocery store and I was like okay well
I'll uh no no sound for me is okay
because you guys can hear it normally
for me it's like cutting up but not even
so bad it's been worse before
yeah
uh also oh yeah I was looking for my
ring pre-chat with those my journey I
was looking for the ring fit games uh
game game
thingy because ring fit only you buy it
physically because you want the ring and
I did that years ago and I can't find
the I found the package but I didn't
find the card anymore
uh unfortunately so I was like well this
game close enough
yeah and then I set up my copy you know
in my previous home 3D streams
it was always uh something different
that apparently we're not supposed to
name but it's not mokopi but it's like
basically about the same quality just
with actual gloves like this thing
doesn't have gloves so my hands are
constantly stable but in exchange it's
way easier to put on I agree with that
the Simplicity and the amateur friendly
setup and
uh it's actually really cute like the I
I
say though
disclaimer most of my movements are
inaccurate
also like here now I have my hands on my
hips but no now I have my hands on my
booby apparently
I have way bigger boobies than this now
now I have my hands on on my butt
no on the back of my butt
inaccurate but
now I'm running with legs actually
closed
but now the legs are spread apart I
don't know so you know the usual
let me
re-re-reset clothes here
[Music]
let me let me read I want to actually
let me do it again
okay yeah hey why am I like so spread
I'm walking normally
wait I want to recalibrate
I'm recalibrating guys
[Music]
I'll even do a free calibrating
it's not gonna get much better
it's okay
[Music]
so I really appreciate that
my other thing is a full suit and this
is uh hi I'm back
this is uh like just strapped so that's
really convenient
let's go
what's awesome
[Music]
okay guys
I know I'm stalling
um let's start I guess
well you guys can actually join me on
does anybody have this game
I love these shoes they're so cute
I have it open or right
yeah okay I understand most of you guys
don't have this game because y'all are
Gamers y'all are too good for this game
just kidding
no but yeah it's a kind of like my
everybody got Mario Kart for this game
it's fun though it's really fun it was
so much fun when I played it with
yeah I couldn't find the game card
anymore I looked for it I wasted so much
time
for setting up a lot of things
and uh yeah
well let's play globally
I tested it yesterday with badminton and
I'm
yay
uh single player
wow
all set what are we playing what should
we play
oh okay
[Music]
so okay now it's really really
uh yeah
still not too bad but the audio is
cutting out it's so annoying
but at least I got a rough idea of
what's going on do you guys wanna join
me in badminton to warm up if I lose I
have to do five push-ups or something
similar like I can also do these are
squats right ooh look at me squatting
yes
because that's you know to make it a
little bit more rank fit like
Katarina that sounds like a random
person not like a kfb well
you give me
I was counting on you
but okay
okay
unleash the tweet
tweet of what what
Street I forgot to still starting to eat
oh no janma do you want to make a
starting point for me just write in a
close retweet with a URL of the stream
starting now that would be nice
I'm left-handed let's go left to the
People Unite
Aya
okay let's go Batman
hi
it's so easy I don't even have to run in
this Batman game
I'm gonna obliterate this girl
and I wonder in professional terms like
well again like a
twisting oh
twitching
twister maybe you call it a twister
[Music]
I can play there's some standing
maybe I'll add a little bit more passion
to it
Spike
so I think
like the way she got me there
was a fast one [\h__\h] she always does
this second time
girl girl
no [\h__\h] way no
no
no no
imagine if I would have done this
challenge of not giving you my album
teaser if I lose until until I win every
game or so no oh she's coming
what the [\h__\h] I felt coming so
what
[\h__\h]
oh my God
how does he feel that how does she do
that
point
[Music]
I never was able to one more time
that was just not reacting I don't want
to play with her anymore
I don't want to play with her anymore I
don't care skip skip skip
that's not fair
you have to smash
no I I tried I tried sometimes stronger
sometimes weaker
all right
I'll do squats for now
if you hit the shuttle [\h__\h] at a high
point in its Arc it's a smash
is that what she was doing
[Music]
I don't know it's called that in German
it's just called a Theta bile which is a
feather ball obviously
okay here we go
it's not accurate I have my arms
straight it's a line uh parallel to each
other in front of me but okay
one
okay resetting
[Music]
okay
one
two oh
[Music]
I feel it in my cups I'm doing it
properly [\h__\h] hold it
hold again
okay
because I lost my joy-con strap
why don't we want to play
I think in football quite a few people
could join
four versus four when you go up against
players from around the world you should
warm up with someone this is one okay
do I need both
huh what
[Music]
enough space around me yeah
why am I so close guys
[Music]
position
is drifting
okay
two hand mode okay why not is this cat
ball or a football what the [\h__\h]
nothing more basic than kicking try
swinging uh uh the joycon on the right
side okay
all right
oh
it's angled
[Music]
so many thank you next try kicking the
ball that's not what I did oh okay there
was no ball
run run
what was that heads up
[Music]
I didn't
okay so the joy come up to kill the ball
upwards
[Music]
now I'm kind of sad I didn't take the
skirt version because I saw you get
striped panties underneath if you take
the skirt version of this swimsuit oh
[\h__\h] wrong
what did they say how do I don't know
it's like downloads motion right
good I did that the previous time too
but it didn't register as a downwards
say what
oh
my I'm so Joseph
their bottoms not panties are you sure
about that
[Music]
hey
I wanted the little one oh no
[Music]
this is good practice though it's a good
tutorial oh I got the close one and hi
how much longer do I have to do this our
next lesson there we go
[Music]
well
bikini tops could be categorized as
Browns too yes yes swing both silicone
controls down at once for a diving
header
oh
my God
that is
dream soccer try moving around the field
okay
dribbling dribbling dribbling dribbling
dribbling dribbling
[Music]
you've mastered football offer of course
I have oh Basics oh just the basics I
thought it said I've mastered footballs
oh
guys in 10 minutes the pre-orders for my
album are starting and jenma will post a
pin
the uh link whatever in my chat and in
the video description
okay one versus one versus Jake let's go
what does it mean that he's a summit
[\h__\h]
my phone my phone
[Music]
um
oh okay where does it go go then do I
have to take it do I have to bring it
let's go
position does this work quick
no okay just makes you face forward oh
well
I can't think
did I just no
[Music]
no
it was an accident
such an idiot oh my God
hey hey
oh it's the same wheel as in Zelda go go
go go go go go that'll take my ball
that's my goal right
it's fake grass it's so spiky
that you can use totally in real life
soccer as well no no
[Music]
thank God the stream today is very short
I have no one to pack to except for the
wow oh nice block
I already made three goals just one of
them is not for me
but it's by me
I can't lose but this is just a tutorial
anyway right
[Music]
but I won't lose
yeah that's going in
[Music]
Golden Ball appeared points of double
what the [\h__\h] that's not right
[Music]
went straight
my head hurts the head strap is finished
giving me pain
that's sand knockout game
you hear that
you never heard of The Golden Ball hmm
is that used in the world championships
how come I always missed it that's so
weird
now I play against some of you guys if
you can make it in
keep an eye on your stamina yeah open my
real lifestyle now now you're ready for
four versus four against people from all
over the world I am so ready
[Music]
search go you guys come in Bring It On
Bring it on Bring It On join me join me
join me
this doesn't sound like any of those are
you guys football
I'm playing with strangers mommy said I
shouldn't play with strangers
ah
[Music]
I'm scared
I'm here I'm here
am I blue
is that me
skip that come on okay I'm good with
cute hair oh no they look like they know
what they're doing I want to be pink too
okay but how's it gonna go in the game
running
ah the pig's got the box
oh oh that was quite coordinated of them
all these passes
oh no we can't let them have the upper
hand
[Music]
yeah yeah
so the patches
that was my chance to prove myself again
okay we're gonna stay here for a past
possibly
okay
what is that
all comes and live more than that
[Music]
I'm out of out of this
I dominated the ball
[Music]
no I'm such a failure
goodbye
and where it's going so Eduardo girls
KFC I just don't know if it's my Eduardo
any others in the chat
okay okay let's go
there she goes
your cat is called Eduardo oh my God
I I need to retire from soccer this is
embarrassing
[Music]
bring it to me
and back to you in the in New York City
uh I want to see real soccer players
I get closer and closer to you guys I
should stop doing that
soccer players fail at the
header does it look like this
participating in this
kitchen passion
okay Eduardo I see you I see you let's
do this no go yes
[Music]
I'm so sorry oh my God I'm so unreliable
Eduardo I'm so sorry for being so
[\h__\h] stupid here you go that's a good
one
[Applause]
[Music]
he is
I got it I got it let's go
honor honor restored now I don't have to
do push-ups
oh
oh my God
oh that was that was exciting yeah
[Music]
like the extra time bonus whoa
oh
[Music]
oh my God oh my God pre-order starting
now
they're standing in one minute but don't
worry guys it's kind of made to order
anyway so there's no
rash or anything yeah
oh I got another one
yes oh I get an outfit a track suit wow
it looks like a skiing tracksuit
the lead up to the goal was amazing oh
thank you kick up the Cycles
thank God I shot in there once all right
so
let's see
sales starting in a few seconds
[Music]
where is the URL German
playing taco nobody has the link
she's watching though she dm'd me that
the sales are starting in one minute
well where are they they're probably
just in the main
sales side which made me worry like are
European people gonna even be able to
get my album
link dead ah there it is oh why is it
dead
[Music]
let me open it for all four of the page
we're looking for cannot be found
[Music]
um
let's try this again maybe it just needs
another minute
yeah I don't see it on the
overview either
oh papa
[Music]
I mean
you see it what if I type in
Ashi
quisha
there
oh no
don't call
hey we're still a bit early it should be
can I sit down
more Sports yes in the moment I'm I'm
not sitting like this
that's so weird hey it's not even
registering me my registering my sitting
that's unfortunate
I'm sweating checking okay well I guess
we should do more Sports then
and she will update the chat if
uh it's something new comes up okay
Alexa okay what should we play what
should we play
[Music]
this album here here I am where am I
most why am I so far
first album
[Music]
starting free orders now now now now now
now now now now now
[Music]
where am I
please please get my first album the
physical this is the physical version
the non-physical version will be at
midnight and in every country as far as
I know
[Music]
drifting not that way
discarded congrats again thank you still
dead still 404. huh
hmm
we have to delete one of the two links
not is there two links in the
in the in the comments I only see one
is there is there for me you guys just
gotta check again I guess the link is
doubled
oh did not please have a look at that
the link is indeed doubles
oh yeah because she tried to have one en
and one Japanese link
here
[Music]
and then the other one
the end here waiting in football I have
not received any info about case or
general are we doing geek track
because
that is the concern how I I was asking
you know for the album to be in normal
shots too but all that's possible this
time is
uh on our own stores yeah unfortunately
maybe maybe I need a label like Cali or
something in order to sell in a normal
shop I don't know
I don't know
[Music]
now let's go
and it's a small item so I think the
shipping shouldn't be so bad and also I
was told that it should ship out like
maybe in October
um not as late as the usual merchandise
I love you switch
I love you
now we're gonna run inaccurate
[Music]
okay let's play something to celebrate
volleyball let's go I don't remember how
to play this but it's always going to be
the same I just swing it
just swing the arm oh
um Yoko and Alex
if if somebody is a kfb I want you guys
to Give Me A Sign
in the starting screen Maybe
yeah yeah I'm not standing too close
[Music]
um
uh
say hi
okay
I will never know I'm the server I don't
remember
[Music]
my timing was early okay but at least I
hit it I mean
what what oh god I was supposed to hit
that I'm so sorry
[Music]
I'm remembering the game oh
all right I thought I thought it's like
that no like uh I don't know which game
I'm thinking of but
ah that wasn't even my fault oh I see
the push-ups coming I thought you only
passed like once
I guess you can pass it to like slice or
however many times you want what
I'm not good at this
I was so ready for that oh I was so
early I thought it was uh
arriving earlier than expected all right
[Music]
thank you so much
so exciting the most exciting thing is
happening
in at the at the next half hour mark
teaser the album teaser it's premiering
on my channel
you can get a little listen on all the
songs
and then maybe get sure about whether or
not
you want that
you want that album for real for real
wow I didn't realize I could run around
okay we can still win Alex come on
sorry
I'm sorry yes yes yes
throw it down
oh
Spike wait what how do you know
[Music]
sorry
I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
Leah oh my God
I'm sorry
three I feel so bad
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't really care about losing I just
worry about this guy thinking what the
[\h__\h] why did I get paired up with this
[\h__\h]
oh man
[Laughter]
that was going pretty decently about a
little bit but then
how to spike
wow
whatever
oh no there's not more what do you mean
um
[Music]
I want to Bow both can't be so difficult
right
let's go
guys join me please I want to play
against you guys
you guys probably don't have kfp in your
switch name do you
oh my oh my
[Music]
head I didn't know bowling was a game
for I mean I have groups and all but
um
here we go at least one of them has to
be you
right guys
okay I'll do it right after I I forgot I
forgot I forgot or after it right why
they were probably waiting time when
somebody else or are they all doing I
guess you could do it so that everybody
does it at the same time and then you
see what came out round one I guess okay
wait wait wait wait wait top eight out
of 16 will advance oh okay I was really
good at bowling in GTA let's go bowling
Romance
uh
well it's really fun with the front wait
can I do it left hand
probably not
yeah
okay
[Music]
I'm a rolling motion we're holding is
that though
what's that L down
[Music]
oh
stay at least they don't count that okay
here I go here I go
[\h__\h] my finger
okay eight pins could be better but I'm
warming up
[Music]
I'm surely not the only one with one pin
left over right I'm four
okay but they're sevens and eight
oh wait uh all but wrong I'm actually
one of the better ones okay okay
[Music]
see that the skill
awesome oh that could be in the middle I
can see it can you move what what
[Music]
didn't cut well where
Honey hi
that was beautiful
guys yeah I'm proud of that one oh my
God I'm seconds
I can win this
I can totally win this
[Music]
okay round three
ball within the time oh so much time
what to do I could do my push-ups now
but I don't want to keep everybody
waiting right this is easy like how can
you not subscribe here
[Music]
laughs
it was she was not running with passion
that's the problem
whoa
[Music]
that was quite fast that was a lightning
bro
totally I'm gonna angle this one a
little bit
we go
you think this could work
it no I
throwing my ball and first though
I wasn't done though I didn't like
properly go down yet wow
but I am first what the [\h__\h] I'm not
losing this one
that let her believe
what do you think this these are Bots
but they're look look they're posting
reactions they must be real
I'm not posting any reactions I must be
a boss
round two
I made it 509 ball advance I will
advance
[Music]
no I'm not butcho I'm real I'm here look
at me I'm so real I'm realer than you
guys
do you guys have a pretty body right now
showing it to me no so I can't really
trust that you are real
hey
and fake it's true but you're real to me
even without a real body I'm sorry for
saying you're a butt
and makes me sad
thinking of that
to take back my statement
okay myself look at my finger my
money oh they know they know I did that
hi hi
no what what's your problem last time I
didn't finish it they just took the
took it for a real one and now now
they're stopping me even though I'm
doing the best pros of my life
hi that's perfect
ah come on the previous ones would have
been Stripes but okay I can I can
correct this mistake
okay I wouldn't have done it yet but
okay nice thing
spare anybody got some pennies to spare
to buy my new album perhaps
please buy my album please please
I recommend getting the physical
there's a girl that wasn't that wasn't
done
this game is so rigged
[Music]
pocket denial
next I'm still winning
even though there's so much
so much richness
[Music]
yes
I guess I'm just too powerful even when
a game is absolutely rigged they can't
hold me back
me I look so cute
girl she's me
[Applause]
[Music]
say hi to Nerf you you were too powerful
semi-finals three out of five let's just
go straight to the first place come on
okay please don't break my game
no not cool
but I will spare this [\h__\h] at least I
think I understand I think I know why
it's doing that
[Music]
yeah I know I know okay
I'll just stand now please let me win
anyway please please please please
please
please I just woke up working out first
thing in the morning is very unhealthy
you know
I can't
wait am I really still first oh my God
these spots are really bad boss
can they not afford some better Bots to
play against
[Music]
okay I can do this I would have liked
the strike but
it's actually ideal
can you support my propaganda please I
mean what do I have you guys for
today
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
nobody saw that right you guys don't
[\h__\h] it was just one left
what the [\h__\h] that will take my win will
it no I'm still I I can still make it to
the finals at least
oh my God no I'm still first okay oh did
you see you didn't blind me never
[Music]
mind
I'm shocked
you saw it are you sure are you sure it
said eight okay well yeah nobody looks
at the numbers though
all right what's up
balls like that
we should go bowling in GTA what the
[\h__\h] man this is
[Music]
finally it will be my comeback
I swear I swear
Roman tried to prep you for this oh
that's what all that was for all the
times he called me to ask me if if I
want to go
bowling with him was for this day I
didn't know I'm so sorry Roman I should
have gone more often with you final
round
[Music]
okay
hey
[Music]
here we go finally
I want to swing no how am I supposed to
solve this problem it's impossible
unless one of the pins
box the other one so I'll go for the
right side
go for her here
that's what I was trying to do for the
longest time oh it almost almost reached
the other pin
ah hit it hard
[Applause]
okay only once okay
all right guys uh
it's uh I won so no push-ups for that
but I'll do push-ups for the previous
one okay
first one number one the wobble number
one say whatever number one yeah and one
number one well one number one number
one well we're number one yeah number
one yes beautiful
you love to see it you love to see it
you just love to see it
nice
[Music]
repositioning
yes give me those bonuses
all right
uh I will do it will probably not really
look like what it's supposed to be but
I'll do it I'll do it okay
uh
[Music]
I will be honest those were the tiniest
push-ups ever holy [\h__\h] that was rough I
don't know what that looked like
she was not moving I was moving now I
was moving I saw okay let's sit down I
am I am sitting not not like that but
that's okay
uh we'll take what we get
I'm hungry and I'm sweaty
hello
hello actually
oh my audio is actually normal right now
how come
we'll switch
[Music]
to here
oh my God welcome welcome back to the
new studio [\h__\h] I'm gonna throw up I'm
so hungry I don't know about reading
super chats after all
but you know what I could do I could
rest a good rest and then I could come
back for super giant reading if I
need to
take a nap
to be honest I thought it would get a
little bit more sleep but yeah bikini
news
let me turn off the game we're done
we're done we're so done I did some
morning workout okay
we're done now uh let's let's uh perhaps
um I I think I did set a redirect but
um
I think I'm gonna stay here because you
guys want to see my reaction don't you
and I want to see your reaction but you
guys got to go to the actual Premiere
chat one second my chat is broken right
now
uh at least on my side
do you guys want me to stay or do you
want me to redirect you
[Music]
um
chat is so dead
yeah
you want to stay
okay I'll go but promise me
to open the premiere window because I'm
not gonna play it here
wait so okay my chat is just not working
this is the this is what happens when
you don't use hyper chat oh wait I was
using hyper chat but the studio one not
the normal one okay already here okay
when it happens
you should
um you know let's let's let's let
YouTube know that you're in the premiere
click into I don't know if they still do
this but click into the actual Premiere
window
uh where is it where is it
videos
so that it registers your view
I don't know if it really does that but
yeah yeah I'll pin it now
oh yeah a Premiere loading screen music
oh yeah the typical
the typical loading screen
uh I would like to pin this
um
okay
okay it's pinned now
uh
um
it'll be a little preview of
the album of all the songs
I will tell you already you have to pay
attention to the first couple songs
because the first couple of songs are
the actual new songs
and then afterwards we got to hear the
previously released Songs again a little
bit
this hurts
oh yeah you know what I'll switch actual
I think I'll switch I'll have some time
let me switch just to make sure I
actually also get some sound
mm-hmm
you want to hear the dark remix the dark
remix does not exist yet but it's it's
going to oh wait ah do you guys know
from the my voice is crackling oh I'll
fix itself do you guys know from the
um
here do you guys know from the pre-order
or what
is a crackling why am I the Kraken
all right shut the tracklist so you know
it's supposed to be a dark remix
is it still bad
what do I sound like to you guys
it's fine now okay yeah it was just
for a little bit
okay guys I
I changed into my 2D form well
almost no difference right now I can
take off these straps
good morning good morning
I lost the dimension yeah even though
it's just one dimension I feel like I
lost so much I lost my organs I lost the
baby that I was carrying
from Arizona
ah man
oh so I lost too much
I got no swimsuit that's sad I could I
could I could do
[Music]
uh nah we'll stay like this this is fine
this is fine this and out of all my
outfits maybe my default still looks
like the most broadcaster-ish my outfit
looks like you know what what what are
we trying to achieve but but but if you
want this to be a broadcaster outfit
then it's a broadcaster outfit
my swimsuit is not a broadcaster outfit
and are you guys excited excited what
kind of songs will it be
[Music]
um
the first couple ones will be new songs
death metal well you know uh the the
Sparks dark remix is
I won't say like you know what um I
didn't call it metal remix because I'm
not sure how it's gonna turn out if it's
really gonna turn out properly mentally
but I am going for a baby metal style uh
I don't know if it's gonna work out
but I asked Gojo gojosan will be the one
the one who made hinatory will be the
one to remix it and I asked him do you
do you think you're able to make this
into a baby metal style and he's like oh
yeah I love baby metal like that should
actually you know I know what I'm doing
so that's that that I could I think I
can do this I can do it he was quite
confident in it
he was quite confident
yeah
yeah and he's really good with songs
that are like that have a lot of like
guitar e-guitars
[Music]
and
um and instruments that go boom boom
boom and
um I hope that we can have you know like
some shamisen maybe you know these like
Japanese instruments to give it a
Babymetal Vibe even more
um
one minute switch tabs oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah let's switch dabs oh my God wait
I should post it on Twitter real quick
real quick uh
um ah
album teaser Premiere now
[Music]
please please
get your butts in here
two-time speed in the premiere huh
you're joking right
I'm still sleeping passing all this in
this me too me too but you're probably
in the an A Time Zone and I'm I'm here
at 11 30 a.m oh
just wanted to give you a I'm gonna have
it muted but uh that was a taste of
kusodega
bgmasai as who was it foreign
please enjoy the crystal deca
Premiere BDM that was loud right
and turn it down and then turn it back
up oh my God oh my God
oh my God I subconsciously unconsciously
I'm gonna be unconscious at the moment
but I did I did I did at the office uh
reference just now
deca
kusoteca
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
I'm so nervous you guys are not gonna
like the songs are you oh my God are you
gonna like that
let's go no it's not here yet I'm just
uh pre-hyping
[Music]
I'm gonna shut up now
um
hey should I wear like two times speed
no no no no
I'm not gonna do that that's you you
guys don't do that either just play it
don't believe
but then what if you still have it
accidentally on when the video starts
does that even have an effect to it
anyway Focus guys now is the most
important time of your little chicken
lives
foreign
that was my love letter to you guys oh
this one's good
foreign
you like that one huh
big variety I love this one
oh
my God
okay all of these all of the other ones
are previous songs but let's enjoy them
too
and then talk about it
wrestling intro what are you talking
about
the great Wanderer is not a wrestling
intro
we love the classics let's go hi down
home
okay please affection destroy you
've never heard that one before
you're gonna be okay
go ahead and do and do it
wait this was a full Kita production I I
forgot about that Sparks was fully Kita
baby maybe underneath the stop lights
move my feet to something new
I'm very behind
I'm I'm behind your mom
all the same
[Laughter]
all insane if you know
damn damn okay
no it's so scary oh
first album
wow pre-order open now
Spotify so uh pre-order for the physical
is open now but the digital version you
will already be able to hear the songs
digitally
um uh in at midnight in your country
yeah
talk about this oh my God I am so happy
that it seems like everybody found their
favorites and and every song is being
kind of like loved on its own
um I think like maybe
uh uh I should get I should talk about
them in the karaoke that I'm planning to
do as you can see here Wednesday the
stream tomorrow is the Freddy karaoke
with the super scuff 3D let's go
um yeah I won't be dancing much because
the dancing and even just moving around
normally is absolutely scuffed
um but still we'll have fun
so wait wait wait let me get the graphic
with uh all the songs the song names
let's just discuss a little bit
okay here is the track list is it what
you guys already saw in the in the
pre-order did you see this
we have
pineapple the one I've been teasing
all the time for quite a while
um it's a Akita most but you know it's
my whole team you know money money money
money money
and Johnny R and Kida and Kira made
another absolute Banger they were
together on this one but as far as I
know it's like mostly Akita production
like like
the base is Kira
and I really really love this one
uh it's it's ah I love it so much so
this is for me I chose it as like the
the main track that represents uh the
album because it's like a real some
summer Banger summer Vibe correct is
so that will be the target of the first
MV that I am releasing yeah they all the
new songs will get like some MBS there's
two who are gonna be getting like high
quality
um big time and these and the others
will be more a little bit more like uh
lyric videos yeah
uh-huh yeah pineapple
uh the little bit in the beginning of
the teaser before pineapple was
introduced the little bit that was
playing there was also pineapple a part
of pineapple
pineapple ah it's it's such a summer
Vibe and so I planned for the MV or the
to bring out all the summer Vibes with
ocean and pool and maybe maybe some
guests so you will see there will be a
teaser for it too yeah look forward to
it
um yeah so I love pineapple uh and then
love rash is you could almost say it's
uh almost the English twin of heart
Challenger
um I basically asked this is by also
Again by Gojo Sun just like heart
Challenger I asked to have a song that's
possibly kind of of inspired by I don't
know how to pronounce it but if if
Hannah fana uh
you know who I mean I really love fanaa
songs yeah
[Applause]
yeah yeah they they write a lot of uh
anime opening and ending songs
not faunas uh
yes yes and and the lyrics Yeah so
basically for all the new songs except
for sleep talking
actually also not so much for pineapple
but definitely for lovers the great
wonder and retrospective I
um got in a call with Moni and told her
told her what kind of topics I want to
be yes the dragon made opening singer
yes yes what kind of topics I want uh in
the lyrics and for love Rush it's
basically a love letter to everybody
who's been supporting me
AKA kfp
[Music]
and how
um I'm so happy to have you guys and how
you're helping me uh you know to you
know the in the innuendo one pineapple
possibly I mean
um pineapple was I will say to my
defense pineapple was handed to me with
the lyrics ready I had no input in the
lyrics
um and when I was singing it you know I
loved it nonetheless but when I was
singing it I was like
um
okay
you will understand more once you hear
the full song
but ignore ignore the innuendos okay
it's just a happy fun innocent uh summer
song okay okay yeah it's a little bit
Saucy I I uh let's just ignore all that
it's like you know the first time I
heard it I anyway just you know it's
like like with Madonna I listen to the
songs and I I just ignore the meaning I
just enjoy the vibe
spicy pineapple yeah
anyway yeah lovers is my love and film
for you guys then the great Wanderer the
great one though you guys were saying
EDM so I guess it's kind of idiom
um it has a very hard to say if if a
Furrow Vibe
um lots of uh Echoes and reverbs and
it's like futuristic
yeah and the great Wanderer was or is
about uh
uh what was it about
let me check my notes
uh
let's see where are my lyrics
here
yeah we rolled it we wrote it down we
wrote it down
what did I say about the great Wonder
lyric sheet I think it's written here no
um
yeah this one's a little bit uh
uh actually both retrospective and this
one are a little bit more on the
emotional sad side
and
the great Wanderer is basically about
being a YouTuber
because what I
um I don't know I feel like I shouldn't
let you guys find out about it but okay
I'll give I'll I'll say it I'll say it
it's a it's about
um the sad lonely and isolated feeling
that a YouTuber might have being in
their own Dimension not being able to
um see or touch you guys properly
um so you know it's like about you know
being alone basically so that can be
about V2 ring but also about any anybody
who feels lonely yeah yeah
yeah maybe if you listen to the teaser
to the chorus again uh
uh you could hear it maybe it says
eternally I'm walking by the lives that
flash before my eyes alone the silence
deafening since I'm reaching out to you
and then I think it goes on a bit more
connection sacrificed the lie I tell
myself so I'll survive one day
eventually the light will lead me back
do you see me
hahaha pretty deep right
[Music]
um
yeah
no
yeah it came out so nice
um I'm I'm really happy with the turnout
for the great Wanderer and retrospective
Moni my lyric writer actually helped me
with a lot
uh and for retrospective Johnny as well
too I guess helped me a lot with the
melody of the song
um figuring out a good fitting Melody so
yeah it wasn't planned in the beginning
but money ended up helping out way more
than she was supposed to
uh yeah yeah I'm really really grateful
for that and then uh retrospective
um is quite funny because it wasn't on
purpose
um
I'll be honest originally I think I was
going for paramore Vibe
um specifically like
um
not like misery business or whatever I
was going for uh what's it called what
was it uh the
um I think the one I sang it before in
karaoke I think money isn't chat let's
go
uh the it what was it
the one decode yeah decode was one of
the uh Vibes I asked for but then
um we changed the original Melody
singing Melody completely and
um
now I don't know about you but I saw one
person in the chat saying it too when it
was running
um
I I now
completely get Evanescence Vibes
especially maybe if you hear the full
song maybe you'll agree to me but it
went from Paramore to Evanescence
so funny to me and I don't mind it I
think both are great so I'm like okay
this is great too that's funny and I saw
you guys being like oh this is like
classic rock is it I don't know is it I
don't know about genres but apparently
it is
yeah and
um the lyrics for this
it is
this this this this this one I feel the
most uh shy talking about it
um it's about like
um
my my friend a friend of mine's
uh regrets and self-doubt and fears
um and concerns and worries and yeah uh
yeah
but it turned out the lyrics turned out
to be pretty dramatic
I like it though
um
yeah yeah
I have money did a great job writing
lyrics with my really rough
um
ideas
yeah the Presto espresso yeah this song
is the depresso espresso song the great
one there were two kind of but it hides
it kind of well in the EDM Vibe I think
but retrospective is quite the emo song
so I think the Evanescence Vibe uh fits
quite well
it's not so subtle yeah
yeah you keep cracking up at this box
I don't know if baby metal Vibe is gonna
suit it but let's go let's try let's
give it a try we'll see how it turns out
I have no idea yet
yeah and then sleep talking
sleep talking
is a special one because sleep talking
is kind of the the one song that got the
ball rolling I received sleep talking
like a million years ago that's your
favorite
you know I can't pick favorites but it's
also one of my favorites like oh my God
oh my God oh my God I love it so much
um basically I talked about this before
uh that you know you know how artists a
lot of artists out there they don't like
often they're just being presented a
couple of demo tapes demo tracks and
they're like here do you wanna use one
of these songs buy the rights to one of
these songs and basically this is what
sleep talking was but not even that
actually I was just
um after do you
after doya was created I got more and
more into talking with money and Johnny
because after do you all around to you
they created their team
um to like their music production team
and uh they like started working a lot
uh together was it asteroid
um and uh because of that they had like
a lot of demo tapes to show off what
they can do
um and I was just like after do you I
was so excited and I was like I want to
do more I want to do more K-pop Style
songs and as I was getting into the
talks of with money and and and and I
was like I wonder if we can do more
songs together and she's like hey yeah
look look at these demo tapes that I
have we can write Songs Like This and
like this and like this and so she sent
me like three or four
um demo tapes and one of them was sleep
talking I'm like oh [\h__\h] I'm is this
taken because I fell in love with this
just now I I I need this song to be mine
I need it and that was ages ago that was
like last year
million years ago ah no it wasn't in
summer was it an Autumn it was a long
time ago
now maybe Autumn last year
um
yoink now it's mine hey yeah then there
was like some process about uh you know
getting it to be my song and then with
sleep talking I started building my
album mm-hmm and yeah I love it so much
it's such a Vibe such a bob and the
lyrics were already like a package you
know with this one so it also has
nothing to do with me but I I just I
think it's such a bob such an addicting
Vibe and it's less like cutesy and
energetic like pineapple less that and
more a little bit mature and and I guess
it's so you know lovey-dovey I guess
early bird snatches the song yeah I make
it my own exactly uh I think it turned
out really really nice
um yeah yeah it's quite quite amazing
[Music]
um
yeah sleep talking I actually teased
this one too a while ago does anybody
remember when I tweeted about sleep
talking
yeah I didn't I did not
ah I teased a great Wanderer like two
days ago or so
but besides that I mostly teased
pineapple and then one time only don't
worry it was only one time I teased
sleep talking and the Tweet one time
and the great Wonder just because I was
vibing to it at the moment and getting
excited about the album release and I
was like whatever like it doesn't matter
ah
I just love fresh
because somebody was giving me an
opening I was like ah yeah yeah
something about this album is definitely
very rushed love Rush
Love Rush yeah and people were worried
about
people were worried about hey what the
album is rushed are you okay I'm like
don't don't worry don't worry
I feel an engine every day hold you
tight I'll never let go
yes so did you choose retrospective no
no not at all I don't think so um
I kept that one secret
so which one is your favorite just by
the teaser your opinion might change
still when you hear the full song but
which one spoke to you guys
sleep talking great Wanderer
a lot of favorites for those oh and
retrospective
sleep talking sleep talking
challenge
can't wait for all great Wonder
retrospective lovers pineapple
thank you thank you thank you oh thank
you
Hey You Gotta Give Love rest some love
too though guys because it's a love
letter to you guys okay okay
I think you like it more once you hear
the full lyrics and you understand it I
wrote This Love Letter to you okay take
it
cutesy song not for you well you will
have to like it it's a love letter okay
okay
just some Snippets yeah
so exciting oh man
ah man
it's in the contract yes
foreign
I'm happy though because somebody I saw
it in the chat you guys were reacting
and somebody was saying oh there's so
much variety yeah right I was that's
what I was trying to do to have lots of
varieties I mean you know I could put uh
fully uh like Kpop only songs in there
honestly that was definitely a
temptation to do that
um
but maybe I'll do that in the future but
uh for this one we have lots of variety
and that's also why it's called point of
view these are the different point of
views that I have and
um yeah and you can also look at from
your own point of view
um but yeah you know
different flavors different point of
views
[Music]
yeah so
fun summer Vibes cutesy Vibes EDM uh
futuristic Vibes uh Rocky Evanescence
Vibes and the cool chill uh sexy Vibes
yeah all the vibes
ah
[Laughter]
unfortunately no four blood on this
album it's my song though it's my song
I expected a new jeans well if I ever do
a K-pop album yeah I'll do all all and
everything I'll do new jeans out twice
I'll do everything
in terms of vibes
I am
so I think this also ensures that there
should be hopefully hopefully something
in there for everybody to Loop
um
hi
I know
[Music]
yes yes my ears are hungry for more
well well honestly you're getting it
soon midnight if you're in an Asian
country or so you're getting it in five
hours for example for Japan
so yeah oh I wonder if they'll if it's
like gonna be up on YouTube music as
well immediately because I think that
happened before
wait what yeah
Asian advantage
Gotta Wait 1918.
yeah maybe you can get your hands on it
somehow VPN VPN
uh I would kill for a future song but
you're also sing like you did for a
second performance that's so difficult
though man I really struggled with that
[Music]
um
there are some parts where I sing quite
low though I think in
retrospective I think
I think I'm not sure maybe
hmm
you have 20 hours to wait no [\h__\h] three
hours for New Zealand oh my god let's go
New Zealand superiority
homes
this is
what oh my god oh man oh can we do like
a hashtag where you guys tell me about
your thoughts
[Music]
um
when once you get to listen to it uh how
about
um
let's make it really clear what it's
about first album
I could I could do POV and so on okay of
point of view I like it but I want to
make it really clear uh what what it's
about so let's do takanasikaya first
album
first album I like KF point of view you
can add that one too if you want but
I'll look for it first album it should
have my name in it yeah
um
let me make a tweet I'm so hungry I'm
gonna eat you guys
I'm gonna eat you up
I'm gonna eat you up um
it will be up on Spotify Amazon music oh
actually there is this link where uh
the the point of view
cover link here this this one uh
what what services is it
some of them I don't really know
YouTube music Apple music Amazon music
and Deezer what the [\h__\h] is Deezer
what is that
um YouTube you
YouTube music
and
Apple music
and apple music
ah at midnight in each country
no
um
how do I say every country
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
please tell me your thoughts
in this hashtag once you hear it
uh
okay
Taka nashik
Yara
first album
ah it became a long tweet we'd have to
get rid of something
um
at midnight
everywhere how about that still
uh how about we're getting rid of the
police I'm not asking you nicely I am
ordering you to tell me your thoughts in
this hashtag okay
first album
okay okay okay
at that midnight stream point of view
this is a fret okay
um
let me see ya
yeah
super chats are gonna be a little bit
rough this week
uh because actually I I said I could do
a super jet reading tonight but then
again I don't really wanna
spam my Channel right now too much
because I want the algorithm to not be
overwhelmed you know it's really
important for me right now uh but but
tomorrow I mean the karaoke should be
relatively short
because I'll just sing these 10 songs
um and then I could read super chats
after that because it's archived
you know super tight rating on the
German channel oh interesting
uh
[Music]
um
yeah no I'm just I really I really want
this to be picked up by the algorithm
both the teasers and the envy and
everything I don't want it to be spammed
Away by other
um
submissions that I do you know what I
mean I'm like I'm serious about that
this is my first album I needed to go
well
um let's let it cook that's why I didn't
want to do the stream really but I guess
we could react together so that's fun
now are you guys gonna repeat the album
teaser a few times because you're
curious I would do that hey I've done it
or maybe you guys already are looping it
in the background hey
and share it on Twitter and elsewhere I
don't care where share it share it
well there's really not much time until
you can hear the full versions anyway
but
[Music]
hmm
because the quality goes up after a bit
oh yeah yeah that's true too the quality
might may have not been the best uh in
the premiere
yes add it to the heck list I use the
you still know the heck playlist okay I
can do what I can do
and shouldn't you add pieces to play
when people come to the waiting room
what you mean like a teaser yeah yeah I
will try I think teasers had to be under
a minute how long is this one or not an
air wait
YouTube
teaser video length
oh
here it says keep it under 30 seconds
but I think it can be longer than that
it's just uh
it doesn't stay here
um
maybe I'll cut it into just the first
five songs if it's too long
free my teasers three minutes 43 seconds
yeah
yeah it definitely and Kelly's done
longer hmm I'll check it out once I
pulled up my reservation for the next
stream I'll put it in as it is I'll try
I'll try
thing is it also has to be an uploaded
video so I might have to
maybe unlisted upload
a shorter one if that needs to be
um
just Loop it as your normal stream intro
yeah
we'll do possible no possible possible
okay I am hungry and tired and maybe you
guys are too so let's zoosa
um
5am here but worth it thank you guys so
much oh man this was at such a shitty
time I never stream at this time thank
you for still coming to say hi and uh
get through this morning workout with me
oh thank God honestly in hindsight thank
God it wasn't ring fit
bring food would have been more rough my
stomach feels upset hmm
yeah okay include a QR code oh okay uh
here now I already had to do like so
much for this album I'm like and
honestly I've been so overwhelmed with
um tasks uh on my hand
uh for the creation of this
um I still am
but yeah
Ollie puked With Friends
oh my God poor girl
um
take a break from projects well but the
thing is my next project is my
anniversary I need to
oh I need to plan I have some plans in
my head but I need to execute some plans
for our anniversary I don't want it to
be lame uh no more
that's also
stressful but maybe I just won't stream
so much next week so I can
you know work on some things
anniversary yeah anniversary is like in
two weeks oh
three year anniversary is in like two
weeks you
wow
wait I need to think again is it that my
third year ended yeah yeah yeah oh my
God
oh my God not that the third year is
starting it's ending holy [\h__\h]
four of your starts
season four let's go okay we're going
into the fourth year strong with an
album to Loop
um and to perform possibly in the future
in concert Freeview concert
yeah I mean not not a venue one I'm
never getting that
but also in conventions yeah I want to
sing in Toronto this weekend I want to
sing uh one or two of these songs
ah I wonder which one I should sing
maybe pineapple because that's like you
know
the one I see is the representative song
if I can sing too I sing another one
Toronto but it's not really Toronto
exclusive because by that time everybody
will already have access to the album
yeah the lead singer yeah yeah
um
I hate
waiting for you to come to Singapore get
some Singapore convention to invite me
and I'll be there
I'll be there so excited now you'll be
in Toronto yeah you'll be everybody in
Toronto will be the first ones to listen
to a live performance uh venue
mm-hmm let's go
start the emails email spamming
Australia one day what
was I not and I guess not
almost feels like I was in a convention
in Australia before I guess I wasn't
Australia plays I'm literally like
almost almost your citizen hmm
[Music]
yeah wherever you live just tell your
convention that you want vitupa
takanasikiwawa
and they'll probably look into it
now imagine to sing pineapple in fifth
Fest if there is something like that
next year
uh then I I'm I'm thinking like damn
which one do I do I'm like between
pineapple and sleep talking to be honest
uh pineapple is more cutesy so Japanese
audience would probably like it but
sleep talking is a bit different it's
not so cutesy and I think that step
would stand out more but I'll I'll be
I'll be considering both
retrospective retrospective would
probably be great with a live band
um
yeah it's difficult I I I will think
about it do you have Korea for them all
I have a Corey of a pineapple finished
and I'm currently uh creating one with
Kiana for sleep talking
it's in the works yeah okay I'm I'm
dancing I am tangenting Let's uh take a
rest guys
I need to rest
oldest like prep work for this album so
far has been rough
[Music]
oh yeah I think tonight is the Minecraft
Summer Festival
I guess we'll see now it's I'm actually
glad I'm not participating in that
ah I didn't even anticipate that it
would be overlapping with this event so
in hindsight let's go good choice
it's happening right now oh okay well
you guys can go watch that then
oh God
yeah I guess it's evening time in Japan
right now image
oh
[Music]
okay let's go let's go to bed
usual
guys please listen to the album teaser
again after this stream is ending is
[Music]
yeah
oh I'm passing out me too me too
me too
[Music]
is that alarm that I hear I wake up a
lot I think I hear a wake up alarm
[Music]
it's coming from
I'm [\h__\h] I'm so hungry I'm starving
[Music]
it's not wake up alarm now it's a go to
bed alarm
[Music]
my first time ever buying an album
thank you
wow
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you everybody for the support
thank you
bye bye
foreign