[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
so
right
[Music]
foreign
so
wait
[Music]
hello
hello you missed me i was
i was just gone for one day
[Laughter]
uh
i'm i'm feeling
a little bit under the weather right now
uh
don't know why
i feel a little bit
sick
i think that's weird
it might go away
maybe maybe the bread i ate for
breakfast was already past its
due date
um
one day is too much ah
feels like a bump
and in chicken it's a lot of time i see
i see
uh
no no no no no i didn't catch without my
hands
if anything
it might just be the way the other way
around but
um let me see
music
can you feel the music
baby
that remix was really cool they changed
like the
[Music]
how to say into not intonation but the
uh
the
[Music]
keys of certain words
um the pitch yeah
and it sounds nice
i guess we're doing tropical house for
now
it slaps pretty good yeah it fits the
rainy spell yeah
i'm like
i think fever night out of all my songs
has the most remixes
and they're all
really good too
[Music]
yeah no it's not the heat
or so
um i don't know i don't know why
oh
oh but i'll probably feel better because
like um when i start streaming often i
feel better later on
i should turn off the super chats i
forgot
god damn it
let me turn them off
it's dangerous man
turn that off turn that off oh
no
oh no
guys uh
guys
okay but i have a lot of tea and a lot
of water
so we should be able to go
on for a while
hopefully
let me pour some tea now
there's no oh [\h__\h] i should have done it
the other way
i'm stupid
[\h__\h] why did i do it this way i poured
hot water
do you guys when you have like a huge
jug
of
of hot water do you
make the tea like put do you put the tea
bag in the cup or do you put it in the
big
jug
because right now i wanted to put it in
a jug but now for some reason my hands
did something else so now i'm putting it
into the cup
in the cup
you could i feel like you could save tea
bags if you would just
make it in the jug but like put like two
in there instead of let's say there's
water for five cups of tea in there you
don't need five tea bags
for like in each cup you could just go
with two tea bags
in one jug
but
who cares
who cares okay let's sit properly for
once kiwa
okay
hi
[Music]
all right i guess i'll have to use my my
finger
ah
proper sitting yes
[Music]
trying
why there's so much cat's hair around
the cap of my honey thingy i'll tell you
why
it's because
it's [\h__\h] sticky
wow my cats are meowing so much today
that's the honey thingy
it makes yeah disgusting sounds i know
that reminds me of it
that reminds me of
um
when we were eating
uh dinner at some point with the myth
girls
um
i i pulled out the the ketchup uh bottle
and it was a fresh one okay completely
fresh never used before
and
[Music]
everybody was sitting on the table and i
was i started to put the ketchup
into onto my plate
and
it made all these disgusting
fartles
farto
farting noises
every time i squeezed a little bit and
first time first time everybody kind of
ignored it but the second time and the
third time and the fourth time it
continued on and on and on
everyone was like
funny funny noises you'll catch your
body make funny noises i'm like i don't
know why
i don't know why it's a fresh bottle
it's not like there's nothing left in
there it's just damn
the bottle was nervous so
[Music]
it was embarrassing
don't you hate that when like
like i'm generally a person
who
always
tries to
not
make such
i don't even i don't even
i don't
i'm even too much of a lady to say it
well i don't
i don't f-a-r-t okay
so at least i'm around people um but
also of course not when i'm alone but
anyway
what was i gonna say oh yeah don't you
hate it when like
you
you sit on a chair or something that
makes weird noises or or you do you move
something you do something that makes
weird noises
it wasn't you but it sounds like a
f-a-r-t
and
then you're like really worried about
what the person close to you
thought that was
so
sometimes i'm like i get nervous inside
and i try to recreate that sound that
just happened
to make to show that it wasn't my body
but it was obviously like a chair or
whatever so
chair makes weird sound number one i get
like i get i get nervous i get like
doesn't mean
it wasn't me so i make it i try to move
my chair the same way again to make it
again
but often it doesn't make the same sound
or the same way and then i'm just
then i'm thinking that they might be
thinking that i'm just trying to cover
for a real fart
even though it was it never was
relatable
really it happens
i'm not the only one
[Laughter]
that's exactly what they think that i'm
covering up for something
no i'm just trying to
ah
so embarrassing
i'm a lady you should no i don't do that
[Music]
pretend someone else yeah but when we
two are the only ones and i know that it
was a chair or something
then i also know that it wasn't the
other person so
i can't really pretend it was them
because they know it wasn't them but i
know it wasn't me but they know it
wasn't them so they think it was me
[Laughter]
i know it was neither me or them
but they wouldn't believe it because
they know it wasn't themselves
complicated man complicated
you'd never have to cover up with me
[Laughter]
make sure everybody understands
uh
ew
yeah i don't want to talk about
f-a-r-t-s
i don't want to talk about those
in detail
don't ask me these disgusting questions
or say these eewy things
i just wanted to
i just wanted to talk about farts that
are not fa-rt's
no i started the topic but then it was
never about real fa-rts
not
anyway
so uh i'm feeling a little bit under the
weather but
shut up
i am going to close the [\h__\h] window
now i wanted some fresh air but i guess
i'm not getting fresh air [\h__\h] you
ice cream truck
because what
firefighters because i'm too hot thank
you
[Laughter]
air open window to air out shut up
no
i was trying to get to air in to get
there
uh anyway i wanted to put the
tea bags into the jug next time
you know remember to talk about the
flies so i i got rid of the big fat
flies they're gone but now i have a [\h__\h]
ton of fruit flies
i have a [\h__\h] ton of fruit flies now
so [\h__\h] sick of them like around and
eating my
things
disgusting
fly for fly yeah and i have a flute
flute
for flute fry
fruit fly
trap
okay sorry that was too funny
i i have a i have a
fruit fly trap from a long time ago but
i already knew it wasn't gonna work
because last time i used it it didn't
work either
so i used it anyway because i'm like
what else do i have but it's not working
i even put it next to popular spots
where they all meet up
after school after s experiment
yeah that's mostly
but
all right well i'll do some home
remedies after the stream yeah
flute phrase
i love that word now
flute fry
blue fries
fruit fries fruit
flute fries kawaii cute
why are you saying fly for fun
i need to play the game again
well today we are here to actually do
something aka
um
read super chats but i'm also gonna get
rid of these
i uh maybe not this one cause that one's
fairly recent and cute
but
[Music]
which one i'm gonna go with this one hi
qui wawa
and now
i'm just gonna put this one
you know what was so weird
i
well
like looking at the concert
i obviously know all of that is pretty
so all of it is fake but
especially the part at the end during
black work shooter where i move around
on that moving stage
when i look at that it looks so real to
me
i don't know why
it's obviously not real
but it looks so real to me
it
looks so real
but immersion but that's the thing it
was really immersive
i love that that floating stage thingy
um
that was actually my request i requested
a blackhawk shooter i wanted something
special especially because it was the
finale
of the
concert
yeah
uh so
because we're reading super chats for
the birthday although i guess we're
reading the call-ins first
maybe there
there might not be
we might not even get to the
concerts i don't know
depends
uh but if we do then we probably already
have more than enough
things uh of
situations where we can talk about the
concert also look i'm pointing at the
hater
i'm pointing elena's chin
and poking lena's chin
continuing minecraft oh is that tomorrow
oh
yeah yeah
[Music]
star is playing it look
let's get started
with the
super cut those superchargers
did you guys buy the merch
get that
merchandise uh i think i should probably
read
eliza
at least now i don't have to worry
anymore about super chat disappearing
that's good
wrong effect
i pitched up my sneeze it was so high
that it wasn't even audible
thank you
bought the full set thank you well um
there will be uh
information about the
about the thing
soon
hopefully uh
kind of figuring it out still
within the management
because it hasn't been done before like
this uh but yeah it was my idea i wanted
to do the meet and greets
uh
yeah
yeah i got to go ahead but
they just didn't manage to give me the
details
uh on time
so please wait uh wait a total minute
hoping there's still some left before
the next paycheck oh don't worry there's
no way it will sell out because yeah it
doesn't work like that so please don't
worry you have a month you have a month
though mom a month from the uh birthday
uh on from the first day it started
selling
uh kind of like k-pop style meet and
greet what no
i don't know what you mean with k-pop
style meeting read i just mean what
we're basically gonna do is like a
i don't know what we're gonna use zoom
or something else but something similar
to that at least
um
and then yeah we're gonna have
one-on-one conversation probably manager
son is gonna be in the conversation just
listening in
and uh
and new cable cells for video call what
really they do that
[Music]
msn
skype
why not icq huh
yeah it won't be like too long but also
not too short i think maybe longer than
the ducami ones because the good thing
is that this time i can
space it out i could
i want to space it out to like several
days because who says that you guys
have time during the time slot that i am
um suggesting
so my plan is to suggest
several time slots for
the
meeting read participants once they are
accepted and found
and then
you can choose between the time slots
and and the days
okay
shut up i'm not going to put genma
inside
[Music]
me yeah i know 5 a.m or so you know it's
not good for everybody
at all
[Music]
yeah
but i feel like the chances of getting
into the meet and greet are lower than
for dokomi and so on
because definitely more participants
so
good luck guys
sorry i'm late don't worry i kind of
just started just been rambling
waiting for my tea to become drinkable
can we enter multiple times with
multiple orders
hole that that for example is something
that
hopefully the details will tell us
but what i can say is that the minimum
there is a minimum order which so far
they suggested 5 000 yen which i hope
they don't change because that would be
[\h__\h] if they change it because some
people may have already
you know purposefully spent 5000 yen
exactly
yeah
so anyway
uh i'm gonna remind
them to give me the deets the dates
[Music]
all right shall we start oh did you
listen to the voice pack because that's
the only thing that you can already get
immediately and i think the voice pack
actually you know i was i was thinking
so long about what to do for it
uh
not yet
i was thinking so long about it and
genma kept on telling me yo kiwawa
hurry up we don't have time we need to
decide on it and record it quickly
and the thing is that was when i like
that was when i was sick and
after i was sick i immediately went to
america
so
i had i actually because i was sick i
got the idea to make it themed after
being sick
ah
yeah um so i started recording it um
when i was
still having quite the problem with my
throat and my nose
so i may sound i was trying not to but i
may sound a little bit
nasally
in the first part but then the fairy
tale reading thingy i recorded uh the
day after where i was already feeling
better throat wise
so
yeah that gave me inspiration though and
uh there's like it's kind of like even
though i didn't use an asmr microphone
it kind of was edited in a way that it
sounds like asmr
the people who listen to it
no what i mean
there's some sound effects too
which i requested
yeah so it sound it's actually turned
out pretty good
i think
yeah
yeah you got sick and i am taking care
of you
and you know when i was trying to think
of an idea
um i was so glad i came up with the
fairy tale idea because that
that makes the voice pack so much longer
i was not sure how to fill the time you
know
i was faking and thinking what could i
do that fails a lot of time
and then at some point i had a light
bulb light up
above me and i was like oh
how about i just go i'm just gonna read
a [\h__\h] fairy tale
but i made extra effort
to
make two versions one is english one is
german
yeah
the voiceover
inspiration
now there's no no minimum time
but
yeah you can i guess make like a lot of
small ones and make it into a set or you
can make a longer one
but just one voice pack of three minutes
or so is like i guess
lackluster is that a word
so i wanted it to be somewhat lengthy
um thank you for the hard work thank you
yeah
there's a lot of things i did
while i was sick
that week i also recorded
the audio
for the concert
which is
why some of the songs maybe
i sound like a currently song for some
reason um yeah nasally
i think
i think it might be noticeable
during ladylike for example
yeah i had no choice
yeah
[Music]
i had to now that you know if you listen
back to it maybe you notice it um the
only i also recorded i recorded every
song
uh like i was kind of sick
but then i re-recorded black work
shooter
after i was back home
because
i realized i sounded so [\h__\h] in the
original recording of blackrock shooter
i can't have that being in the concert
so i was like i'm sorry i need to
re-record this
yeah
yeah yeah i was sick during all of this
[\h__\h] man
yeah i'm glad my rave recorded black orc
shooter the rest was okay
the rest was okay
thank you thank you
yeah i want a black rock shooter to be
good because of hooker papa
i'm so glad he got to see it you know if
he was um in japan at the time he might
have not even been able to see it live
because
he goes to sleep early
and
i don't think he would have stayed up
until like three a.m
to watch
blackwook shooter i didn't tell him that
it was gonna happen i wanted it to be a
surprise yeah
yeah he was still in america
during the concert so it was easier for
him to watch it thankfully
let's try this team
all right it's drinkable don't really
like to taste but it's a froat tea
okay let's go
uh wait let me pull out the thumbnail we
are reading the super chats from the
call-ins
[Music]
this should be from
is it from the top i would say this is
probably from the top
i'm looking for the tub
i haven't heard that one in a while
i don't think the world is ready for
your full power i was thinking the same
if
the next concert that i'm gonna do
i will record
in the hopefully in the
japan studio
and
it's gonna be perfect there's not gonna
be any stuff
and
everything is gonna be
even better i'm not gonna be nerfed i'm
not gonna be debuffed
yeah
it's gonna be
even better yeah one thing one thing
oh like there's many things i noticed
but i also want to kind of say like
even though a lot of the tracking like
the legs
the legs for example
were pretty accurate
i feel like
other body parts were like
captured kind of
what to say
i don't know
i feel like it was like
smoothed out so that
my
the range of my movements was
not
captured 100 accurately
uh
i feel like
i danced more energetically and
uh and did bigger moves like especially
i think it was especially noticeable
during the hip frosts of
the bigaku
i was doing hip frosts there which i
felt really awkward about doing that
while being watched by
uh amigura fauna
really awkward
uh but yeah stuff like that
and and many other
things
uh where i felt like i feel like i
danced just more
bigger more exaggerately
um
so i think um i have i have some ideas
why that could be
uh but i also think that uh yeah
if i record
my dances in
the whole japan studio i think
i think uh
it might be
more
true to the real deal
yeah um
a lot of them
uh
tracking was
like for example for a heart challenger
there's like this movement where i move
my arms really really fast like uh
actually
i can make the pose
okay just not with those fingers but
when i go like like this kind of
you maybe don't know what i'm talking
about but like fast movements like that
uh would often
like
end up in
like scuffness
yeah so
we actually tried our best to smooth
that out you guys have no idea
how much like
okay i wanted to read super chats but
now i think i'm gonna explain a little
bit
now
um
like
i want to
i told you guys i took
all of that in one day but there's like
uh
you know you you you could think that oh
then maybe it only took one hour because
the concert was one hour
but
it was like approximately maybe 40 to 50
minutes
for one song
because
there was so much recalibrating in
between
and
kind of had to
split the songs into several parts as
well
um
because
we even needed to recalibrate in between
just to make sure and sometimes you know
when i would move around i would go a
little bit out of the
out of the area that would capture me
perfectly because if i go too close to
you know the
edges
uh it would kind of mess up my limbs and
all that
so one song
would take
about 40 to 50 minutes
now that means like i was dancing indeed
for around nine to ten hours
yeah and and even even on that day we
were still figuring things out like in
the beginning we had this
um see-through plastic mat uh
on the on the ground to make it easier
for me to dance
which was really helpful and then we
recorded one or two songs of that but
then we realized
holy [\h__\h] this thing
which does not look
like it's reflecting anything actually
did apparently reflect things
really [\h__\h] sensitive man
so
we had to get rid of that and then we
re-recorded those songs again later i
think
so yeah we were still figuring things
out even then
and the mcs
those also took some time to set up in
between
yeah everything just took
took a lot of time it's not just okay
play the song dance okay done next one
nah
definitely not
and then
oh you wanna know one more thing
remember
remember um
when i was already with the with cali
and so on
and i wrote on twitter that i'm still
recording something or and yeah
um
i was recording some more stuff
at that point
because
here's a little something
we actually
recorded
every single song
again on that day
i danced every song again
because
we captured
the hand move where we tried we tried to
capture the hand movement separately
with different equipment
uh
thinking that that would help and it may
have helped for some
[Music]
songs and then it didn't for others
um
so basically we stitched parts of my
body together
in the post-production
incredible isn't it if you think about
it it's incredible
the things that are possible
yeah
it's incredible
and then yeah we stitched it together
from a frankenstein
[Laughter]
yeah frankie's
turns out that
it had actually it didn't
it wasn't as good as we hoped it would
be for some
songs so
um
yeah
yeah yeah
yeah we tried our best
yeah
and then even the face tracking
was made separately
originally there was no face tracking
so that was also stitched onto my face
it's interesting isn't it
yeah yeah only stitching i became oily
[Laughter]
it was a lot more work yeah than
it looks like and and uh
very tough
three parts to make a hole
there were even situations where
i feel like it was even more than three
parts
[Laughter]
uh
i'm your friend from indonesia hello
welcome thank you
it was really tiresome yeah
this is wester
where's your em translation and i'm
literally talking english
huh
well what the way why is there
why
why was there an end translation
huh
is this like in the court where you're
just writing down what i said for the
record
subtitles
e and huh
let's get started
i wanted to let you know about the
korean street food that you can try when
you go there they're called tornado
fries and they're an entire or fried
potato cut into a spiral and served in
the skewer i think i've seen that before
happy birthday thank you yeah i feel
like i'm i'm gonna check out a lot of
the street food
in korea
by the way uh the collab that i planned
with nabi has been postponed a little
bit more it will happen within this
month but kind of at the end of the
month
yeah
uh el canada well thank you for the rest
of the chat i'm trying to go for this
fast you know because there's a [\h__\h] ton
of them so you know school
happy birthday kiana a little early but
it's because i'm working in the mines to
get some money for the merch oh what
really
the mines
like i've seen some documentations about
working in the mines and it looks and
sounds really um
exhausting and dangerous
and tough
uh it's a pleasure to keep watching and
still having fun with you after all two
almost two years you got me out of
depression get me an engineer degree and
now a job thanks wow
you're welcome
but eh is it
i heard it's really unhealthy
but i guess maybe it depends on what
kind of mind it is i hope you
i hope you're not over exhausting
overworking yourself
be careful okay sounds like a dangerous
job
now be careful
of the spiders and
the
zombies
are around minecraft
and be careful but thank you so much i
wish you all the best and here's the
kiss ma
jeff star thanks for the pinky sticker
thank you
and general thank you for the rainbow in
the world of such darkness oh it's a
it's a poem
in the world of such darkness we sought
a bright light to soothe our wounds from
the battles we fight no stitches
ourselves no medicinal might with a
smile and a love you set us right to
those of us who were lost who you helped
find their way your birth was a gift
that we can never repay so smile goddess
and heed the words that i say happy
birthday kiana and have a great day
[Laughter]
it's pretty good
it's pretty good thank you
for being the brightest part of so many
lives kiara thank you for working so
hard for so many people you've
transformed lives in ways you'll never
understand and though i think the world
doesn't deserve a person as wonderful as
you we got you anyway and i think i
thank my stars every day for that
blessing have a wonderful year kiara and
a blessed birthday
thank you
thank you very much for the sweet words
all very very impressive poem i can't
write poems i mean i haven't tried in a
long time maybe i should try
[Music]
but you may have a challenge maybe thank
you for the beautiful rainbow
nicolas known as torres thank you for
the red super chat okay the mother of
chickens happy birthday a few days ago i
saw you were sad that some members
weren't around anymore and i'm still
here
but my work gets in the way i wish i
could send you a fan mail but i can't
find where to mail it anyways lots of
love from chile are you guys you're not
looking properly
sometimes you chickens
you just literally have to go to the
whole live home page and there's an
address there
it's in japan but it's there and i think
it's even written out in english too
we can't read though
come on if you can't read then
how are you even able to type in the
chat huh
i think it's fairly easy to find but
maybe you didn't think about that
possibility in the first place
little chicken
yeah try harder
if you wish you could write me a letter
then
have you been really wishing it if you
haven't even looked for it properly
sorry i'm really schooling you but
there's so many people who say like oh
what we can write you a letter what
yes you always could
let's go to the whole live home page
thank you nicolas though it's nice to
hear from you now i'm looking forward to
your letter which will probably
arrive at the earliest in half a year so
go go go
get to work
cruz thank you for a rainbow
oh my god there's so many rainbows what
the [\h__\h]
rainbow happy birthday to the
my favorite stream of youtuber idol
singer dance shapeshifter a dancer
part-time warrior and patrona i know
i've said it before but your students
helped me laugh through some tough times
and you've motivated me to better myself
and not settle
oh
isn't settling good like
doesn't that mean like to settle down
and
you
know maybe maybe not settle for anything
uh
less than what you want maybe that's the
meaning
i guess maybe that's the meaning yeah
i've been listening to your streams
while in the gym studying practicing art
cooking healthier foods gardening wow
i'm not where i want to be in life yet
but i'm happy with every little
improvement i've made and you have a big
part in that so thank you for i thank
you again for putting so much work for
the sake of making something great like
the 3d concert the original music and
covers for being so interactive with the
community and being kind and thoughtful
to us all might have been what gang on
your debut but i'm glad i stuck it
through some rough times in the
beginning and i hope to support you for
as long as possible love you and take
care patrona thank you
oh
yes can we get alta kiana back even for
a little bit pretty pleased with the
cherry on top you mean blue kiara
blue
[Music]
no
so annoying these chickens
rgb
hmm was it around
this
[Music]
i think it was
wow
[Music]
but i had like a
low voice right
oh
like
this
why well that's just that's why oh i
never did this with the blue one
was i just blue
it's murphy yeah
yay
[Music]
that was just blue
okay
okay well there you go
wow i'm blue
dabbing
so what now
i'm blue now
but i don't think i was ever blue in
this outfit before
why do i feel so weird
i mean even before i turned blue
[Music]
my sleep is so [\h__\h] too
i couldn't sleep at
night uh
and then i had to get up early so i only
slept like two hours and then i had to
get up early for something
and then i went back to sleep but i
think i got maybe like
five more hours or so
which in total would be nice but i feel
like since it wasn't connected my body
didn't count it as
seven hours of sleep or so um
[Music]
uh
and i had weird dreams again
no it doesn't doesn't feel like enough
now i feel weird die
[Music]
thank you i'll sleep more
tonight
i think
i have nothing
uh early in the morning so
we could chase dreams uh
what was it
nah i forgot
but it wasn't nice dreams
well things slow down for you now that
the concert is done
um
[Music]
on the outside perhaps but uh like the
what you see
not on the inside um
[Music]
i am
going through
um
a stressful tough time
and uh
yeah
but
i think um it
will be digital
it will be daijoubu
let me let me become normal again please
i don't want to be blue
i want to be blue
[Music]
ah so thank you cruz
hope you're happy now
making me blue
now we need papaku
[Music]
go go papa go
go go go
oh my god
but i have a
i read it out in english okay
uh it's been more wait this is from
drowsy cat by the way
drowsy cat says it's been more than 10
months since i watched kayla's breakfast
what already so long
it's been more than five months since
i've become active after being told not
to hide
maybe that was the clip the
the clip where i was like korean people
don't hide come to the stream and
comment
there have been many changes in my life
thanks to kiara thank you i like your
songs i like you as kindness i like that
you are soft-hearted but you don't give
up and move forward firmly
key slowly stuck in my mind for months
and became my favorite word ah
sweet oh there they are onion onion
happy birthday to my favorite kia i'm
sending it in korean not in poor english
that's okay thank you
to celebrate kennel's birthday i'm
sending a rainbow for the first time
happy birthday attention
i love you kiara i love you
thank
thank you for the beautiful rainbow and
for
you know coming out of the shadows to
support me
uh on my stream and um i want to say i
think
i'm i'm almost i'm about to book my
my flights and my uh hotel
because i got some things confirmed
some exciting things
[Music]
so
[Laughter]
i'm gonna book it soon
i need to go get a tissue brb my nose is
weird
[Music]
okay
so in my story um i found some cats on
on the way
thank you
[Music]
okay let's go
hello korean viewers good evening
[Music]
happy early birthday kiwawa it's been a
while since i started watching youtubers
mostly at the side playing the streams
in the background as i work or study so
i have not really decided on an aussie
for a long time however i think that i i
think i had decided on one recently
was it really recently
why
what did i do recently that made you
finally
decide what in your heart
was always there
are you here
okay no mike
only recently shocking shocking
statement
there you are
i feel sick
[Music]
today not a good day for reading super
chat those
i don't feel so good
i'm waiting for the answer
okay
[Music]
no i'm not gonna end it yet no no i
barely write super chats i'm gonna fight
though a little bit more
but
in order to keep on going i need
oklahoma mike's answer i didn't even
finish reading the super chat though
mary the answer is in the super chat
you shy
[Music]
i wonder what it was though
combo
[Music]
let the man think
no he's not busier sleeping i saw him
typing in the chat
ah
there is okay maybe i should have
finished reading the super chat
ah should be pretty obvious who it is
might not be able to watch a lot of her
streams live to time zones and rl
commitments i do make sure to watch the
vault whenever i can love your reactions
love your language course one two love
your antics love your creativity love
your commitment love your tension yeah
but that's things i've always been
i wanna know why it's recently
should i share uh how i came across your
channel maybe in a few more months time
what when i'm ready and legendary
why do you make me wait so long
you're just keeping some content for the
longer super chats huh
oh man
keeping the tangents just like me
just like me actually you learned
something from me
ah need to keep some tangents for the
times when you need something to talk
about
it is it is smart i'll give you that
here's a kiss for you
thank you for the rainbow and the love
and the support i wish you all the best
and thank you for
for being here and doing your best to
watch the vlogs thank you soon
now there's a million pinkies
oh my god motion thank you for the pinky
happy birthday to your boss another year
goes by and my respect for you has only
grown since then this will be read post
concert how do you know so i can say i
know all that that all the hard work you
put in for it will be rewarded here's to
another year of kiana thank you
another year yeah wow wow wow wow
[Music]
um i hope i can
make some of these
big dreams come true
in the coming year
um oh god i feel like
so weird
i feel so weird
i can't breathe well and i feel sick
and my face feels tired
hmm
on my yankee nine don't know
maybe if i
eat a pear pear
i ate some
bread with nutella for breakfast
which was
right before the stream
well i don't know the pair might be
attacked by the [\h__\h] flute fries
let me drink some more water
[Music]
maybe i should drink a energy drink i've
got some energy drinks in my fridge
because
the people who took care of my cats
left them there
[Music]
the energy drink
it would make me feel better for now but
then worse later on
no i don't no i don't feel worse after
energy drink normally but
[Music]
i don't know i don't think i'm even
really sick i'm just
lacking energy maybe
and proper sleep properly
thank you hatmo
groggy yeah
time for maldives trip yeah
oh it's always time for a maldives trip
[Music]
okay
continue shadow pencil thank you for the
pinky happy birthday pencil i hope you
have a birthday filled with joy and many
smiles you deserve it for being so hard
working and passionate about what you do
thank you
[Music]
kitchen i appreciate it thank you for
the sweet words
a gd down question for the pinkie as
well happy birthday kiara this may sound
repetitive but i wish you happiness like
the joy you have brought to our lives
and hope that you and us kfc will
celebrate more birthdays in the future
love your boss thank you
i love you too
thank you for the love
thank you
[Music]
a blue thank you for the double pinkies
my alpaca friend
uh
my one and only idol who i'm super proud
of thank you for introducing me to the
most wholesome and loveliest community
and thank you for helping me become a
much better person than i could ever
imagine what
you're not the only one who says
something like that it's
really interesting to me
that you guys
say
you became a better person because of me
i really admire how you always put so
much effort into your work and
everything you're passionate about
you're truly inspiring and worth to look
up to may all the joy you have spread
will come back to you on your birthday
lots of love
thank you alicante thanks thank you
thank you for the sweet words and
i'm glad that you're
you know putting
an effort into improving yourself too
there's always room for improvement even
though i'm sure you were a great person
even before that thank you for your
support and your love ma
about caddy
thank you for the uh pinky oh it feels
like a while i've seen you
happy birthday
to you
okay
so
[Music]
you've been watching me for a while now
how how how do you
assume that this would even be a
possibility you're not getting a raise
no no no no
but thank you for supporting me i'll say
thank you for that
thumbs up
thank you
me next time
happiest birthday to my dearest sweet oc
your brilliance light up our days and
fill our hearts with so much love and
joy you deserve the very best i hope
this special celebration will be full of
love and joyful moments for you love you
guyana thank you
the collins were really fun i got to
talk to so many of the japanese members
too for the first time in a long while
um
that was really nice
it was fun
yeah
it was also really chaotic but it was
also fun
and um
[Music]
and that for us oh my god
i i cannot handle
that
she's too much for me
ah she's too much for me
i even gonna pay back from selfie yeah
i didn't i did not expect that
i was a surprise
she has two handles right under her head
i see that's a good argument so now i
know how to handle her
like actually um
you know that was not our first time we
interacted we interacted during that
recording for the official program
um that you may have seen
the thing is that
during that i was really tired i don't
know if you've noticed but i was more
calm than usual during that um
program during that recording
because i was so [\h__\h] unbelievably
tired i got up at like i think
six am or something
for that recording
they always schedule these recordings at
6 00 am for me what the [\h__\h]
um
was i was so tired and i feel like
i couldn't give it my best and i i
wasn't quite so good at entertaining and
my throat was also not feeling the best
so uh
they cut it
they cut the sound but i coughed a lot
i wasn't even sick i think i was just
yeah i just didn't get
no hiccups i didn't get sleep so um my
throat was also [\h__\h]
i don't think it was when i was sick no
i think it was
before that yeah
yeah
but so that was the first time we
interacted and i feel like i didn't
quite do it justice
uh that comes up next
uh cause i'm gonna be in it for three
episodes right
the
following episode i was i was
way way more energetic
way more energetic because i got sleep i
think properly
um
i look forward to that
i feel like that one was way better
unfortunately i'm i'm regretful about it
i wanted to do better in the first time
too
[Music]
much
you seemed more major mature and
balanced love with us so
yeah it could be could be
but it was good that um rapunzel was
like the the host for that episode
so
most of the time because i was so tired
my brain was like zooming out zoning out
i didn't know what was going on
so thank god she was a great host
eventually for if i understand correctly
for my last episode i have to be the
host
i'm already nervous about that
but i'll do my best yeah
i'll do my best
but your answers are really good oh yeah
i never talked about it but the games
the games for my section
in the official program
i found out myself like there was like a
brainstorming um meeting
not really brainstorming it was just a
meeting and i didn't realize they kind
of expected me to come up with some
ideas um so at the spot i was like oh
yeah i i i totally came up with some
ideas and then i just threw out some
random things
and yeah they turned it into games like
the memory game of like um
looking at a burger and trying to
remember the ingredients and then you
know looking for new kfp members
uh and finding the right job for the
right people and all that
i came up with that pretty much at the
spot yeah
it was it was nice though because they
turned it into a proper game with the
graphics and all that
so
that's fun that's fun
it was fun i like how they
made it
into a game
oh yeah
louie has this corner
where it's about how to
socially make good decisions
in social situations
and
my answers
were pretty good but also
um they cut they cut some uh for i think
for each corner
they cut
one
um
one round at least i think
yeah and yeah i i almost always i had
like the same answer as rui
it seems like
birds are just
really good with social situations
it's because
in the nature
you see how
you see how pigeons for example
they hang out on the streets but they
don't get in anyone's way
even if they're like in the middle of
the street they always fly away when
cars or people
uh
approach them
no not because they want to talk to them
if if people would approach a pigeon to
talk to them i'm sure the pigeon would
read the air and stay but the pigeon
understands that it needs to move out of
the way
so
they fly away
i hit a pigeon a few months ago well
that's not a good comment to write right
now when i'm trying to make a point
[Music]
in any case
i'm saying
birds are
socially
adaptive is that the right word
[Music]
isn't it just instinct i'm making a
point here
[Music]
even if it was just instinct that's
exactly the point we're just by nature
instinctively
socially smart
uh-huh
no more discussions
no more discussion
okay where was i
did i read the
humanic superchat i feel like
i think i did i think i did so thank you
humidity thanks for the thinking
discussion time is over
skye thank you for two pinkies and three
red super chats oh my god what the hell
thank you
oh but you sent it for other people oh
happy birthday kiara happy to celebrate
your second birthday once again allow me
to appreciate your effort to give us a
freebie concert and so many joy in
previous times wish you keep having fun
and a wonderful experience and further
adventure also i asked my colleague do
they want to give you a birthday message
and this is it ah
from colleague susu
they say that in sims
it's it's hello in sims language
so-so hello
who baked herself with spices have been
laid on the table as a b-day fried
chicken she had waited from the previous
birthday to the next one will you enjoy
her on this birthday
if she waited on the table
ready for me to eat her
for a whole year
then i doubt that she's still edible
um
unless you put her into the freezer
maybe
even then
one year um
i would rather just
not eat you
or throw you into a soup
i think
[Music]
soup chicken
soup chicken is the saddest the saddest
um
destiny
to fall upon
a chicken a kfp chicken
it's like
where the unwanted
old chickens go
it's
why
because my mom said
if a chicken gets older
which means already at two years
you need to
kill them
fast
but i think at two years it's already at
the point where
you are
not really made for
you know fried chicken or so anymore you
need to be made into a soup then
yeah
too old too old for fried chicken
you become so
soup
soup can't talk
ah i don't feel so well
[Music]
i need to read super chats thank you
skye
thank you soon
wait there's more message from bt thank
you potential for letting myth have a
day to meet each other this day is not
only your birthday but also a milestone
for myth viva la viva la thank
you members finally meeting was indeed a
milestone yeah
from comic iced lemon tea she wants you
to step on her pretty please how am i
gonna do that okay you may not see it
but i'm stepping on you under the table
now
step step step step
step step step
here you can be my my foot pillow
my foot rest
me next please no
no i need to read them otherwise i'm
never gonna be rid of them of the
pressure and guilt to read super chats
thank you so much skye for being part of
kfp for so long and all your friends who
sent the messages too thank you so much
come sanny da
[Music]
i lurk every day nice to meet you i'm a
newbie and your pre-chef gave me lots of
warm welcome oh okay if he has good
chickens eva we were like and i hope you
have a great birthday thank you oh
newbie
you guys are so nice you welcomed him so
he feels welcome thank you guys good job
thank you for the support john thanks
[Music]
for
i love you thank you
thank you and a little bit of a korean
text as well
it's the same
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you for supporting me
thank you soon
thank you
[Music]
thank you soon happy birthday oh wait i
shouldn't be reading this but thank you
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
fire the elements
triple rainbow
not even making use of the
of all the messages you could write
holy [\h__\h]
triple rainbow super chat for dear lady
kiana i wish you have a wonderful
birthday and all your wishes come true
as always i'll keep supporting you
thank you so much
[Laughter]
thank you
triple the kisses for you thank you for
the support that's way too much thank
you for being so generous
it's way too much wow
thank you soon
[Music]
i hope all of your wishes come true too
thank you that's incredible
what a chat wow
damn
so many colors oh my god
thank you so much
[Music]
now we don't need to thank you for the
red super chat as well happy birthday
kiara i hope these next few days uh and
beyond you
ah and beyond you
where is the
where is the comma
grandma
you're feeling loved by everyone as much
as you make us humble timkins feel loved
you deserve the world boss
thank you
no no that is not not not character
limit no no
you forgot that's okay
oh thank you thank you thank you i feel
very loved by you guys i'm
i was quite
overwhelmed and surprised with
how much you guys have been praising me
thank you very much for the love
navida meeting you too
thank you so much
[Music]
thanks for always
always supporting me
thank you soon from the bottom of my
phoenix coco roll
yeah
shelves thank you for
i hope this finds it well and having a
wonderful birthday birthday you're truly
amazing for and through i'll always do
my best to support you that kind of
rhyme we hope you like the
frown kfb birthday letter we love you
thank you
what birthday letter i didn't see
everything yet because
you know after the concert um and in
between in between i was also kind of um
busy but i didn't see everything yet and
i wanted to watch the orchestra thing
uh when like things calm down
but uh yeah maybe i'm not sure what you
mean with the letter
what do you mean
huh you mean a specific letter
i still didn't get further um
art either
yeah i know about it but i didn't really
watch it yet
because i wanted to watch it when i
had like my the full attention for it
[Music]
is it on the on the website again or
just gonna assume that it's on the
website
[Music]
planning to catch up when you have time
yep yep yup
i'm still reading the fan letters from
dokomi
[Music]
yeah but i reserved this day to read
super chat so i have to read super chat
if only i could take a nap for an hour
on stream
and then come back
and continue reading then i would
probably feel better
but probably wouldn't just be one hour
it probably would end up being three
hours
no
no i can't do it
no no no no
anyway let me
continue actually
one
i feel like we're one to four
one fourth through the
super chats from
uh
the calling
almost
kind of
at least according to my scroll bar
okay let's go
thank you for the rest of the chat uh
happy birthday kiana i thought i should
give my favorite phoenix a birthday
present thank you i can't watch live
often or sent many super chats but i've
been a fan since you're fire emblem free
hearts play fruit uh free hearts free
houses have a great day and pat yourself
in the back for all the great content
you've made thank you that's a long time
ago
thank you oh it's i'm always happy to
hear when people tell me they became
fans because of the fire emblem
playthrough
that was quite something a long
commitment
yeah good memories of that one
yeah i miss it
i haven't missed it feels so nostalgic
now
yeah
thank you
happy to hear that thank you for coming
out of the shadows to give me a birthday
message thank you
steve thanks for the pinky happy
birthday kia i can't wait to see your
friday thank you hope you enjoyed it
thanks for the pinky
and
shisana
thank you for the rainbow
happy birth potential you illuminate my
life since i already joined kfb for over
one year i'm happier than before
i'm glad
thank you pencil i will always follow
you by the way after this over here my
terrible english seems to be getting
better it must be because of love i'll
keep learning finally lady kiwawa is
nice
no it's not because of love it's because
you're smart chicken
you can do it fighter
[Music]
you can do it papa
thank you for your love and support
let's make it two years now hmm
dino lord jacob dankeshen
moon dog thank you for the red super
chat happy birthday chihuahua your
passion and kindness burn bright like
the beautiful phoenix you are all of us
care if we love you for who you are the
past few months you showed us all how
dedicated you are
us as well
suspicious
english you're the best aussie to
support thank you
hi
so sweet thank you
even though it was a little bit a little
bit sus
very very kind words
you're so sweet i want to give you a hug
thank you for the love
yeah i'll continue doing my best so
please continue supporting me moon dog
[Music]
thank you
rainbow yeah it's a rainbow but
absolutely no message
with it
why i mean
right now when i have to go for so many
super chats i actually kind of
appreciate it
but you shouldn't waste your rainbow
like that you should tell me what's on
your mind and
in your heart
but thank you for the big big rainbow ah
there is a message oh
oh there is
and another red super chat thank you
happy birthday
we love you forever
there we go
there we go there it is
[Music]
oh
okay
thank you
[Music]
and so
sorry sorry sorry dramatic
dramatic yawning
ah
[Music]
no
no i will continue naked chicken duncan
thank you for the red super chat happy
countdown to birthday attention i'll be
working mostly tomorrow but i'll be
cheering for you in my head
did you
were you able to watch it live i wonder
i hope you got to watch it live
[Music]
dramatic hand mp3 oi
thank you spanking hot duncan
for trying to
squeeze me in in your on your
day of work hard-working chicken thank
you so much
it's um
7 p.m now
i'm just i i [\h__\h] up my sleep schedule
the other day
and last night it was even worse because
i just could not sleep
my brain did a big funk
that cook thank you for the thank you
hello i'd like to call in and order for
tuna and corn pizza
oh it's just a canada birthday call in
line sorry uh have a nice calling stream
click
wait i thought you were ordering the
pizza for me
i would like some tuna corn pizza
you know what yesterday last night i
even
i was
what was i doing i was recording last
night
until like
maybe
half past midnight or so and then
uh
i did something
and then
me cooked oh yeah i made the new
thumbnail put up the reservation it took
a while and then finally
i started cooking at like three
a.m i think
because i still needed to eat food and i
had nothing there that i could eat
immediately but i actually cooked pretty
fast it took me like maybe 40 minutes
and that's fast for me
and i cooked um
something
that looked pretty nice i think i think
i'll upload it on twitter later
so then i was finally done
no i wanted to eat but then i was
preoccupied
and
could not think about eating
and then later i ate at like i think 5
a.m
and then i still couldn't sleep i think
i was
i think now and then i took uh no now
then i fell asleep maybe at six
and then i woke up at
eight
for
an appointment
and then i tried to sleep again
afterwards yeah
i live like i'm in est oh man was the
hell fresh meal yes it was
yes it was yes it was
i still have leftovers from last night
so today i can
um eat the leftovers
sleep that like that really sucks yeah
it does
oh yeah i did take melatonin to fall
asleep after
the appointment because even though i
only slept two hours at that point i was
pretty awake quite awake
so i took some melatonin maybe that's
why i still feel tired but it's been
like quite a lot of hours since i took
it it's been like probably
eight hours
since since i took it if not more
now that then i don't think that's it it
shouldn't take that long to wear off
[Music]
eh no
no i've been fine before when i took
melatonin
[Music]
yeah it should have worn off already
oh man
anyway
thank you for the red super chatter is
the one who drew
the cute art for the
fridge magnets and the stickers
yeah i was thinking um
when i was
um
you know thinking about what to do for
merchandise i wanted some cute chippies
and i always really liked uh tadas
chibis
so thank you teda for accepting the work
request dan kishon happy birthday
attention wishing you good health and
happiness always thank you for bringing
us so much happiness and fun i'm glad
that i can be part of kfb love you buzz
thank you too
for being part of it i'm very happy that
you are
because this way i could find your art
please
continue drawing cute kiwawas
[Music]
actually they gave me a lot of different
um ideas for the
um smoothie and chunkers magnet art
so i was really happy to see smoothie
and chunky's drawn so many times i
wanted to make every single sketch into
a magnet i wish i could
just for myself
i could i guess i could
it's just really nice to see my cats so
much
yeah
bonkers
i know the rest i think was more like
sketches so i'm not releasing them but
yeah
yeah i can i think
hello hello
thank you
which makes me think i should put um
my merchandise here
as a
here
there we go
there
let's put it
in the tv
[Music]
not ideal size
okay i can't even read that
maybe bigger
all right it will be here after all
so cute
on sale july 6th what
birthday celebration
what
by the way the oven mitten it's one
i've admitted not two
i thought one would be enough because
normally i also only use one
it would have been a bit more expensive
i think if it was two
uh sorry
oh sorry
oh
a lot of you guys thought it was too
uh sorry
yeah no a lot of people misunderstood oh
no
it does say oven mitten not oven mittens
i'm i'm just gonna say that to to um
protect myself from any kind of
legal um um
trouble
sorry
yeah and it said front and back and it
wasn't supposed to look like there's two
yeah you should should have read the
small print don't sue me
[Music]
then
i always you know i thought
the shape of the tail looks funny
doesn't it
this one
show it again
looks funny
[Music]
hope you have the happiest birthdays
lady kiwawa excited for both your
countdowns and especially the 3d concert
thank you thank you thank you thank you
very much
hope you enjoyed both of it thank you
for the support mwah
docker tech thank you for the red super
jack doll
happy second birthday with highlight
boss yeah it's the second one already oh
my god i'm looking forward to more kfc
and kiara goodness in the years to come
and of course looking back with the
refund memories as well thanks for being
a potential
we can all believe in and pay money to
glory to carefully
[Music]
yeah we've made a lot of beautiful
memories until now haven't we
thank you for being part of that
lucy thank you for the red super chat
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you for two red super
chats
thank you for the happy birthday message
1.5 years it is my first pinky sending
super chat potential is totally worth it
because you always turn them into the
best content eg the comments at the
coming birthday concerts
thank you
1.5 years ah
that's also pretty long thank you for
not leaving my side thank you so much
i love you
[Music]
dominic kane
after most prime thank you put in pink
and super chat that's the thing look
once kiana whole size 11 whole size 11.
[Music]
now
i can't wait for your pretty concert
that you worked so hard for i know it
will be wonderful
i wish you all the best for your future
as well you deserve it bad girl
ah you deserve it too though
i wish i could
you know
have you have all of you guys dreams
come true
but but a lot of you guys are
working on improving their lives
as i've heard so
yeah i wish you guys all the best as
well thank you optimus prime for dinner
leaving leaving water down
[Music]
una manzano
matilda duncan seaweed
[Music]
almost two years watching your stream
can't tell how much joys and courages
you bring me
when i got troubles in my life thank you
for everything happy birthday my oshi
wish you always healthy and smiles on
your face viva
glory to kfb thank you
glory to kfp indeed thank you for being
here and supporting me for such a long
time thank you
i'm glad i can help you when you're
feeling down or troubled hmm
very happy to hear that
[Music]
king thank you for the
uh red super chat thank you
hello
happy birthday yeah normally i'm more of
a quiet cafe employee
yeah i think so i don't remember your
name in the super chats but today i had
to congratulate you you always entertain
us you're also really cool and you
always make me smile love
he said i'm cool
thank you for everything and i always
support you thank you too
i'm cool he says
wow i'm so cool you're cool sometimes
i should be mad at you but i'll take it
as a compliment
thank you
one of the cool kids yeah
thank you so much you should come out of
the shadows more often maxi king don't
be scared don't be shy
thank you very much
you danced for 10 hours you are cool
there you go are you hearing this
chickens
that is true you speak the truth
farfa another red super chat thank you
attention why is the fire alarm ringing
so loud in my apartment i think it's
fine
was it really
be careful
don't underestimate it
thank you papa though maybe maybe it's a
joke maybe it's about me being too hot
maybe i am the reason for global warming
yeah
yeah it could be
thank you
did i forget the kiss for maxi king maxi
king mwah
tibia and kay
thank you for the pinky comes
and it's korean let me translate it
[Music]
no
how does that work
i'll give kiara 100 thousand one and
take fifty thousand won
ah
well that is that is interesting logic
because it is
it is a pinky
so he basically paid himself
by giving me a red super chat but then
taking back half of it
i guess in some way
you could think that
i paid you
but not really because i never touched
it
in the end you just you just paid
yourself
[Laughter]
but you know what you know what i call
that
you know what i like to call that
an independent chicken
and you should be proud of yourself
for being able to pay yourself yo you
don't need anyone else you can pay
yourself
ah
smart
smart is what i call that
so you got me i thank you for the red
super chat i happy birthday attention
it's been a year since i met the dog
kama
what's that mean
is that what does that mean
we can celebrate at the same time
what
does that mean
what does that mean
no
d-o-g
k-a-m
and then a minus and then an a with an
apostrophe
i'm guessing suika is not here right now
to explain
oh it is his dog's name
oh
really
oh that's cute
you got yourself a dog
on my birthday last year
oh
sweet
ah
what a great day to get yourself a dog
um i want to see pictures why didn't you
show me pictures
thank you sweetheart show me pictures
yeah i want to see pictures
[Music]
happy birthday i joined the members
because i was fascinated by the
wonderful singing voice and dance at the
first bird festival i can't comment much
but i always watch it i'm sorry for
google translate even though it's my
first super chat
[Music]
you continue to be an inspiration and
ray of sunshine looking forward to
seeing your concert and everything else
you do love you hashtag we'll catch you
thank you
thank you very sweet of you
thank you i'm glad i can inspire you
i'm doing my best yeah
thank you for the sweet words i said
we'll cash out yolk indeed
i need to make a video about that
sometime soon
thank you
laura thank you for the pinky i wanted
to prepare more but i couldn't i'm not
good at english but i'm always watching
it
[Music]
ah
thank you a black friction thank you for
the red super chat
i love this bird so much happy birthday
for the second year kimono here's to
many more we'll always be here to
support you no matter what we are the
strongest fan base for the cutest oshie
happy birthday again thank you
yes strong honestly you guys are
really [\h__\h] strong
i i've always thought that
you guys are very powerful like
we may not have
um
the volume of other
fandoms
but you guys make up for it with the
power
and the passion
that
you guys bring to the table
makes me very proud
it's like yeah quality of a quantity
and you know that teaches people a
lesson to not underestimate chickens
yeah
one day the world will be dominated by
chickens
and the rose will be reversed
chickens will be humans humans will be
chickens basically
yeah yeah the day will come
and then the humans will be on their
[\h__\h] knees
and beg for us not to fry them
[Laughter]
let's go
i think we all um
we all agree we all are motivated
motivated isn't it
weak humans must be eliminated
it's a doggy dog world or a chicken eat
human world
[Music]
okay
thank you black friction
coconut oil
me
take no prisoners
i want to watch
not a lot of the rings i want to watch
game of thrones now
need some
some
i want to see some fighting
they'll never see it coming yeah
especially because of how good we are at
keeping secrets right
thank you for the pinky happy birthday
attention or she i got into whole life
because of my brother oh
thanks to your brother for like
getting you into that hmm i was a happy
i was happy being a casual club watcher
but there was one clip of you that
dragged me into the rabbit hole
thank you for the loves by the way can
you go back to saying ties please
was that the clip or was it something
else now i'm curious are you here alkaza
29 are you here
i want to know what clip that was
let's take a moment
it might not be there
the gold old pies i've been saying that
for so long and it took me so long or it
took you guys so long
to tell me
that i've been saying it wrong
and you go over your birthday merch
again it's down there
and the link is in the description
you have one month time to get it
because otherwise it will be gone
it didn't look a chat when people
corrected you
how convenient right
nah i don't believe it
i look at the chat all the time
maybe i was just thinking you guys were
writing the words incorrectly in the
chat
i didn't see that message
unbelievable
whatever you're saying wow
wow
kiana can read
all right non-canon ganon you're getting
into dangerous territory there
okay continue
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you for watching my
streams still thank you for being here
even though i'm probably streaming at
really bad times for you
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat
very happy birthday to kiara thank you
for everything you do for kfb 10 job
thank you
you and i appreciate it we're halfway
through now by the way
crispy thank you shin what's and thank
you for the red super chat
happy birthday i knew this day would
come it happens to the same day to my
birth what
[Music]
same birthday
i getting feel like counting birthdays
count with you who i most love i hope
you have a good birth time
[Laughter]
i will always be a good fan so that you
can be happy
yep
same
thing
thank you
[Music]
nice
energetic aura enlightened my daily life
and i love that you really care about
your employees yes that's us and me too
yes
as always you are our best boss sorry my
english is not very good no it's perfect
thank you so much
i'm glad i can make you happy and yes i
do care a lot about you guys i do
probably too much
a little bit too much
so thank you lazuru
for being part of the community
thank you for the pink super chat
obrigada
happy birthday angel with your happiness
and peace thank you i wish you the same
seventeen be pretty too dang question
thank you
now girl thank you for the red super
tattoo happy birthday hot wings hope you
have a wonderful birthday thank you when
you make your hot wings yay i'm hot
wings
thank you so much for spending the
birthday with me
domino thank you in the game i created
one park
for the red super chat oh
yeah i have to
get my german channel going sometime
soon
uh i don't know i just kind of wanted to
get it out there first because i thought
you know the dokomi
and the outfit reveal was kind of a good
timing because everything was german
themed
but i already knew that i would be too
busy to really like get it going
immediately
ah
we'll work on it
we'll work on it otherwise it will just
become a funny meme
in kfb
[Music]
remember that day when kiwamo made a
german channel and never used it
it will be a funny meme we can laugh
about it
but now i wanna use it
ah
yeah yeah
i will maybe i was thinking um to do a
german collab with eofy
on my
sub channel
because german let's go
there's a german channel yeah i made a
german channel wait are you really
asking like seriously
it's linked in my on my channel at the
bottom
[Music]
okay i've sat straight for long enough
now i want to get comfy
so number number comes
and your german is so good
good job thank you soon for your support
to sit european
become bencho hey
no
[Music]
how is your back uh i don't know i
bought this thing i didn't use it yet
but the other day i walked by
like
and how would you call it orthopedic
shop
i wonder if that's what you could call
it
which sells like all kinds of things
that supposedly help your
help you back in someone
and i bought
i used to have a cheap version of this i
think
but i bought this back strap thingy
that
um
helps you
to have a straight back but they told me
to not wear it longer
than three to four hours per day
i haven't started wearing it yet maybe
i'll wear it tomorrow during the
stream does it actually help um well i
mean
it reminds apparently it will remind
your back to stay straight because you
feel
um something pulling you
yeah it's it's you put it on like a vest
but it's basically just like a
strap
a stretchy strap
and
uh
yeah after a while the goal is after
like a few months
that if you wear it every day for a
couple hours
that your back
will kind of have memorized it
and do it on its own
just another thing to try to help me
yeah
and then they also recommended me to buy
like a bouncy ball
and then every now and then
switch
from my chair to the bouncy ball
just to get like the
the hips
moving a little bit
oh yeah like in the maloney yard
yeah i might get one
they look fun i've i remember sometimes
in school
we used them
sometimes like we had an option
to sit on those instead of the normal
chairs
i remember that you know
it's just fun
yeah it's actually fun
so
i feel like i wouldn't mind going for
that
help my core strength
yeah like a yoga ball
[Music]
i suffered a crushing defeat at alden
ring today console me
[Applause]
not gonna console you
[Music]
such a nostalgic name to me happy
birthday kiara i cannot wait for another
year of pure ganky energy and joy from
my favorite streamer am i really still
your favorite streamer really
that's that makes me happy thank you
[Music]
super bear thank you soon
thank you for the pink super chat happy
early birthday thank you thank you
thank you thank you at that point yeah
it was a little bit early thank you
[Music]
happy birthday chihuahua wishing you
another wonderful year of happiness and
joy although i can only watch the
archive stream normally i've asked for a
day leave from work so i can punch in on
time
another one who asked for a whole day
off wow thank you can't wait to see your
birthday for the life always support and
love you thank you so much
i hope you enjoyed it and sorry for
delaying it for an hour even with an
hour it was so
so last minute
i couldn't even check
the final footage
before playing it on stream and
like
even before that i only got to see like
some
some parts so
i wish i wish we had more time
it was really
not enough time
yeah
[Music]
sorry i was just reminded by management
that there's a meeting next week but
it's at [\h__\h] 6 a.m
no i don't think i'll make it
i don't think i'll make it
there'll be a director's cut yeah there
definitely will be i just don't know how
long it will take
um
but there's a lot of things i want to
fix
um
a lot of things
uh could have been prevented so
yeah to be honest i'm like um
i
i when i was watching it
live
you know it was the first time i saw it
too and i was so [\h__\h] nervous
and
um really under a lot of pressure
and then i saw so many things go wrong
probably i saw even more things than you
guys saw
and i
i thought
i
i don't know
i was um
let's just say my perception of it was
very very very different from
from your guys's perception
i don't know how i don't wanna you know
when i saw how positive you guys reacted
i felt like
i don't wanna bring
my negativity
into the room
there
so i'm i'm not going to
um
but yeah i am
didn't
i
i was
[Music]
i was very um
i don't know
i i don't know how to say it
[Music]
no i don't know man
so many factors came together also like
the stress and pressure and and
everything
and then
yeah
um
but
yeah
it's just looking at things that could
have been prevented made me feel very
regretful and
yeah i i definitely want to put out a
director's cut because
i strive
for
quality and you know i understand that
there's limits to what we could have
done but
uh or what we what we did
but there was still so much more that
could have been
prevented and improved
uh
so
that's that's what i want to do for the
director's cut
yeah
um
and originally i didn't want to upload
the whole concert as a director's cut
because i didn't think there would be so
much wrong with it
but there was so i think instead of
uploading single songs i think i will
upload the whole concert
from beginning to end as a director's
cut
there was even some things that you guys
have absolutely no idea and it would
like this for example was fine i guess
in the end because yeah you guys
it wasn't so noticeable if you didn't
know
but for example like uh for fema night
the floor
was supposed to look
different the floor was supposed to be a
disco floor
it apparently just disappeared when
rendering it
it's like really weird glitches
i don't know it's weird it would it
already looked really damn good
um
the disco floor i don't know why it
disappeared
it's so weird but you will see the disco
floor in the director's cut
yeah and now stop talking about it
because you guys are way too nice about
it and i don't want to
um
ruin that so thank you very much
everybody for being so
so sweet and
yeah
nice but i i i want to
improve i want to make the best out of
it
and um yes i was very very very hard on
myself regarding this
so please understand i was also under a
lot of pressure
yeah
but we're working on it
yes
we're gonna make it
even better
but i first want to give kanoru some
time because
kana uru has [\h__\h] to do as well and
um i think he deserves some sleep
because he
uh once again
just like a good ass concert
lost a lot of sleep
um
you know i thought i thought i gave him
more time than coulda gave him for the
concert so
uh i thought you know it would be fine
no it was not fine
ah yeah
yeah
i hope he gets some sleep back
it was not three times longer no
my concert was way more ambitious i
don't know
i feel like in some ways um whatever
uh
let's continue
i feel like i can get the super chats
done from the collins i can do it i can
do it
kana uru needs to be hired by cover but
i mean in some way we are hiring him
i am hiring him
he's just not i guess not a direct
employee
yeah but
might be my being better this way
oh yeah
yeah yeah
it's like you know how with yoonagoon
and spirit snare
okay i'm not gonna say that i um
discovered kano that was that was more
like um if anyone that was amen maybe
or just kannado himself but i've like
discovered so many people who have then
been picked up by the other members like
spirit snare is now the go-to person for
logos in whole live english
[Laughter]
and then until was picked up by gouda
and that's not the only the only cases
[Music]
then worked for
uh cali um
good eye for talent me maybe perhaps
because
[Music]
foreign
yeah but i'm happy i can help out like
people
uh
like to to get more
exposure i mean they're not only being
paid in exposure obviously but it's
really good like honestly they obviously
are getting more work
so this is a case where the exposure
actually was really worth it i would say
even my choreographer
you know how he said that i
specifically
picked out my own choreographer
because everyone else just works with
you know what the company
organizes for them
uh
and now i feel like my choreographer
has been eyed by others as well
because i saw callie
callie follows my choreographer on
twitter now
[Music]
like i'm connecting everyone
i am the connector
i don't know if she plans on
commissioning her or so i don't know i i
have no idea but i feel it's suspicious
that she followed her
connector
[Laughter]
ah
i don't know if my choreographer is
single
you guys hold the important questions
huh
yeah
the choreography
i think yeah the style
stood out because i feel like
probably pretty much every other choreo
was made by
the
the choreographers that you know cover
hires
at that concert
i might have been
the only one
who had like a different choreographer
so that makes it stand out yeah
[Laughter]
yeah yeah she uploaded some videos of
how the choreographies are supposed to
look like which made me want to say even
more
that
i was kind of nerfed okay
like okay i'm not as good as dancing as
she is
but
i think i can do a bit better
so i want to
uh
perform it even better yeah yeah
there's a clip side by side oh [\h__\h] no
no don't do that no it's not fair
it's not fair it's not fair i'm being
nerved and glitched and scuffed no
[Music]
but there were some sometimes um
where i like changed things up oh one
thing that you guys have been wondering
i think
um
every
uh okay kin yobe no ohayo
was a choreo by someone else that's like
just a popular choreography
on
uh yeah in the in the dancing community
um and uh
the one hello project song i did was
just the hello project choreography and
then my originals were from my
choreographer but the other ones
was just me
messing around
like a ladylike ladylike and for blood
and digital girl
yeah for digital girl i just i tried to
make up something really simple just for
the chorus as simple as possible so that
the girls could handle it but
they tried
yeah
i thank you very much um yes
but for ladylike and for blood i
i thought of something really quickly
um because i have no time i had to learn
the complicated choreos but i did not
want to
just completely
do
like random ass moves and
you know just wobble wobble
i wanted it's to have some kind of
system
you know like
repeating moves during the chorus and so
on
um
so
yeah i'm glad you like it
and when i was dancing for blood
the girls were like
you did lady like yourself yeah
yeah
i feel like if i had
or that actually gave
i normally don't do choreographies
myself
um
but i think if i have more time
i want to challenge myself to do
a more intricate choreo for whole song
because i think ladylike and for blood
um turned out pretty well i've been
praised for
it's quite a lot i i saw you guys be
like
i wonder who made the choreo for that
and i'm just thinking it was me
it was just me
don't
yeah
i'm glad you like it now i feel more
confident about making something myself
yeah
i really i really just thought up
something really quickly
um i think i can do it even better now
so i think i'll um
i might really challenge myself for a
journey of a thousand years
once we all get together in 3d
i think now i'm more confident about
making an actual choreo but getting the
girls to dance and oh man because i have
to keep it really simple huh
uh
because for dances little girl that was
just
literally four moves
and two of them were the same
[Laughter]
um
yeah i had a hard time um
i thought it was fairly easy but um
they they had a hard time
said it wrong they had a hard time
uh
maybe
yeah i think um if i give it if i give
them the choreo
one month in advance maybe
maybe
maybe it will work out
i'm gonna
try
also i want to make something clear
um
when we planned recording it the
original plan for a while
was you know just me ame and ina would
be together during the recording
that's why i planned to
have a song with us together because
um
yeah i thought you know that would make
sense because we're there i can teach
them a move in person and we can record
it together in person
and then at the time where
gouda decided to join
it was kind of too late to change my set
list
and all that
um
so that's why i just had guna and kelly
call in kelly as well like she was
traveling at the time so she couldn't
join us for the recording
yeah
that's
pretty much why
yeah
in the end gouda was there so i was like
kind of like ah damn it i guess we could
have
included her but you know it takes time
to plan i had to
commission people to make um original
instrumentals for
songs that are not my own
um
and
prepare other things to
record it beforehand and all that
so
it's not something that can be done so
super spontaneously normally
yeah the mc segment was really funny i
think so too
especially the charades one though oh my
[\h__\h] god i had so much fun
uh recording that
after i was done with recording the
charades turducken mc
i was on a high i was so
my mood was so so good i was like
laughing after the recording still
i was like this was so much fun this was
so much fun oh my god that was so much
fun
yeah they couldn't figure out the dance
though the subaru dance i thought i did
it pretty well
i was so desperate like i just couldn't
how do you first i tried to imitate a
duck which was basically just the same
as imitating a chicken
then i tried to like show oh me and you
you who are you
that didn't work either
then i tried to
make the
the duck dance but
how would i how else would i imitate
subaru just with my body
sitting down ah
interesting i don't think they would
have gotten it but it would have been
worth a try
yeah did you choose the words for
yourself no no i i told gouda to come up
with some words
uh some of them
uh whole life related please
the snail though
yeah
i think the imitation was great
but getting on the floor like that
was bound to result in
limbs
going all over the place
and snail
snail nailed thank you yeah i think my
snail was pretty good pretty cute
you have no idea though how embarrassed
i was about the skirt malfunction
i was
i was thinking
into
a
a barrel of embarrassment i don't know
how to explain it i was so embarrassed i
was like please please make this
and please end it please please please
make it go away please please what the
[\h__\h]
no it wasn't during the recording it was
something that happened in
post-production which
you know
uh will be fixed in the
in the
director's cuts because it is something
that can be fixed
yeah it just happened and i was so
embarrassed
i was so [\h__\h] embarrassed
yeah the original is staying up i'm not
gonna delete that no no
it was not on purpose of course not
of course the hunt
so embarrassing
[Music]
um i was watching the whole thing like
management
and me and ahmed and kana
we were watching it like not in voice
chat just like we were chatting on on
discord the whole time
commenting on everything
doesn't like sushi i guess that's okay
oh yeah they did they did uh shorten my
spots
uh i think yeah
thank you for that but where is my butt
like what the [\h__\h] i feel like it was um
from like certain
certain poses uh made it even more
visible
what the [\h__\h] is up with my butt
where's my butt
but i have but i have um
i've brought it up
i don't know if they'll do something
about it because this is you know just
kind of like um
typical
anime
um and and that to me
like the other girls also have no butt
except for louie but you know really is
doing his pants like
louise the the the the
shininess of her pants alone
do a lot of the work i think
andrew's whole body shape is like
what
[Laughter]
so but i used that as an argument
um
it was a whole bakery
i i used
that as an argument and said yo what the
[\h__\h] i want the butt to like what what
you can't do this to me i have a really
tight outfit like for the other girls
who have like fluffy
outfits and all that
it's not so noticeable when they have a
flat butt
but for my outfit
i need to be a bit more curvy in the
back because if you look at me from the
front i have quite the hips but if you
look at me from the side it's like
question mark question the question mark
nanny the [\h__\h]
right
what you know
the ina
honestly
eva that that was an optical illusion
though she said so herself we were
talking about it when it happened like
it's really [\h__\h] funny but
uh that's just the way the the the
cloves in the back
fall
she has a flat butt too
inna's back didn't stop the internet
yeah for me i don't know for me it was
more about the back to be honest the
exposed back was really
beautiful
but her butt
that's an optical illusion
yeah
but yeah it was a nice nice moment nice
fan art coming from that yeah
but then i also want fan out of my ass
crack though because the more i look at
it the more i think
that was my ass crack
oh my butt crack
yeah where is the butt crack fan aren't
then huh
no i thought so too first that that's my
spine
but
at this point i think it's my butt crack
i think so
yes
butt crack all right let's go
i mean
just
anatomically speaking
choctaw mata a minute
hi it's free ikiwawa welcome
oh wow i haven't used this like this
before but just added anatomically
speaking
it might not be so visible in this
version of myself
[Music]
how do we do this
okay hello
hello look
up
i mean i mean okay don't look at that
wait
look at that um how is that not my butt
crack
how is that not my butt crab and and if
you like um find where your butt crack
is
right now
touch touch your body
i think the placement like look look
look if you look um wait um
it looked like this look how look how
it disappears like this
that that's i think 100
that means that's my butt crack
right
are you seeing this look
i mean it needs to be improved
i mean look at that
you cannot deny this truth anymore kfb
right right
compelling argument i know
thank you
so much
[Laughter]
proven
proven and approved i am
[Music]
look at that by the way
the strap
i like that strap
[Music]
that strap
yeah my next round hidden though
but
[Music]
but then here it's like so straight
from
this angle it goes like
on on a hill and then suddenly the hill
is
so straight so that needs
that needs to be improved but at least
we know i have a butt crack which i
don't think
i have ever seen on any of the other
girls
should i say 3d for now
what
okay yes
hello
pretty chihuahua
always
let me put
i want to put some accessories oh i can
[Music]
wait a second
i'm trying to
do something
[Music]
oh there we go
there we go
right
it's really difficult
is that a cat that i see on the floor
nice hello chunky wonky
[Music]
like this
and why is it tilted now
[\h__\h]
damn it
ah
i'm feeling better i think by the way
[Music]
maybe this one's easier
whoa
[Music]
ah nice
ah
okay
[Music]
no
no yeah
ah
yes yes yes yes
all right all right now we're talking
okay okay
all right all right all right
hmm
i'm lady chihuahua kneel
before me
address me
properly
won't you
foolish chicken
oh
there you go
[Music]
remove the hats oh
you know i really love the
meow the cat bell
she's reacting to the cat mouth
[Music]
i feel like i was able to do it wait a
second where um
[Music]
i'm not sure how to do it anymore are
you i think
i should be able to do it
not
anymore
[Music]
oh but anyway let's add one more thing
okay
[Music]
i can put on even more hats if i'm
infringing yeah there's like a witch's
hat that i can put on for halloween
i could put on so much
[Music]
did anyone ever make that remix because
boom boom chat is the perfect intro to
start that song
no the christmas outfit i can't put on
at least not now maybe in the future
[Music]
okay now
i need to rinse up a chance
let me read
[Laughter]
and where was i i went on a big tangent
[Music]
hello
hello back to you
oh you're cute don't you
you're gonna run away right yeah
don't run away
don't you wonky
yeah
just wants my attention
okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
where was i
maybe thanks for the pinky
happy birthday
maybe no maybe not
i know yeah i did read that one now i
remember i remember because i read about
him leaving for from work
okay okay okay
[Music]
in
oh yeah my eyebrows that's another thing
maybe in the director's cut we will
release the eyebrows there was a
little problem with the eyebrows for
some reason
uh i wanted my eyebrows to be invisible
but
i think yeah there were some problems in
post-production that made my eyebrows
disappear
yeah
and i think i prefer myself with the
eyebrows on top
i think makes me look more uh expressive
i think
yeah
you didn't notice
ah
i want my eyebrows back release the
eyebrows [\h__\h]
apparently it wasn't that easy to bring
them back yeah
i noticed it like
like right away when i got the first
meow previews but
remember
she's like asking me why i'm a bunny now
he's like mommy i thought you were a cat
because mommy
i got her i picked her up
[Music]
you me you were gone during the butt
crack arc i'm so disappointed
you're gonna clip it anyway though i
know
um
chunky wonky
she's in my arms now sweet baby
we've been cuddling so much these days
corn cake
and maybe maybe a clip can make my butt
crack viral too
hopefully
butt crack fan art coming
soon
yes
so
uh
cute
and cute
chew junkies cute junkies baby
sounds
[Music]
my cat my cat my cat
also i'll let her go now i'll let her go
also
okay
let's make it back to normal
that was chunky wonky
you're welcome
now back to super chats for real
um
jesus morales thank you
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah he's saying that he's he watches my
um archives uh with the auto subs from
youtube
oh
that's
not good
um
[Music]
she's she's a bit zoomy again
excuse her
uh so thank you so much cotton for being
part of the community for such a long
time thank you
thank you
okay
oh wow get your hair done
no
oh no you can't jump up there no no
no you can't jump up there
nine
you know you can't jump up there
no
okay i think she understands
and thank you cotton
and
ah wait a few korean names
[Music]
and
that sounds very polite huh
thanks in chicago
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
my sweet sweet korean
chicken thank you for your support and
your love i appreciate it
i'll come to korea soon so please wait
for me why are they laughing
why are they laughing
what's so funny
because it was really polite huh yeah i
felt uh because i only know
and this one sounded similar but more
polite to me
so it's like saying it to a god or
something happy birthday god well i
don't know why you're laughing that's
just you know what i deserve look at my
crown
look at that crown
i'm a lady now too oh it's for elder
people oh
hey
don't ruin it for me i thought it was
for
i thought it was
for it
gods
well i am a phoenix cell
i guess i'm kind of old
[Music]
for the pinky
it just turned midnight in japan so
happy birthday kiara what do i hear
online reading great oven mittens and
all the presents you prepared are great
thanks for always having us in mind and
doing so much concert hype is max
yay you're welcome
yeah thank you now
now maybe next year i can
once again
mouth attempted
uh matching
something to the previous year's merch
wow
i kind of also wanted to do a big beach
towel
now but i did
i did do a a members only poll when i
was thinking about it and you guys voted
for the the mofo mofu blanket that's why
it was the blanket but i still want to
do a beach towel um
so talkative
i don't know she's gone now
so thank you dominique
the wise thank you for the red super
chat thank you
happy early birthday kiara it is still
the fifth from where i am typing this
that's all right you were trying to
you know be early at least you're lucky
and therefore i'm reading your super
chat today so everybody who sent it on
the other one i don't think i can read
them today we'll see we'll see
thank you very much
for the support i appreciate it thank
you
and
alex aka
[Music]
the trans and prosperity of this world a
brief span of prosperity
vainglories earthly splendors
why does this one
simple tiny word translate to all these
words
the trans and prosperity of this world a
brief span of prosperity vain glories
earthly splendors
we young
really
wow
impressive
yeah alex says
happy birthday
i heard that you're planning to visit
korea many fun and beautiful things to
enjoy in korea so i wish you enjoy
enough i will continue to watch your
stream to have fun have a nice birthday
thank you very much yeah i'm really
excited for it uh i need to bring an
empty suitcase
um and then i can buy lots of stuff in
korea yeah
makeup and clothes and food
souvenirs
i'm excited
thank you i hope you will give me a warm
welcome in korea i will i will do my
best to practice a bit more before the
visit so navi somehow now if you saw
mama navi mama
will teach me some more korean before
that and i now that my whole birthday
arc is over i want to
continue studying myself as well we
might even do one more duolingo session
uh
cause duolingo from the last time i saw
it uh has improved a lot apparently
um
was pretty surprised that they added all
those things
yeah
navi mama also told me that she has time
for me every day but she also told me
she wants to
maybe introduce me
to
meadows mama
maru's mama
is
uh also
in
korea it seems
yeah
yeah so
i
you guys suggested it to me the last
time too i think but then navi mama saw
the clip apparently and she was like oh
keanu i can introduce you
now i'm nervous
yeah yummy mama
okay why not why not why not make
connections with all those mommies mommy
i will build a mummy harem
she's a lot of fun
oh
nice thing
thank you alex
thank you
[Music]
i wonder if this is how i'm supposed to
read your name
[Music]
my sleepy employee thank you for the red
subject as well happy birthday tanjo
thank you
i hope you got some sleep sleepy
employee
thank you so much for your love and your
support and staying up late for me i
think it was pretty late there thank you
so much
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat ooh
super sonic chicken wow
happy birthday attention bye
happy birthday to you too someday
thank you very
[Music]
i regained energy but i need to go to an
idol meeting
hmm fight them k bar and thank you and
see as pony duncan for the red super
chat happy birthday thank you thank you
since we have apron and gloves will we
get cooking head for next can't wait for
3d life i could don't thank you but um
like these cooking hats are usually kind
of like
throw away one time only cooking hats so
i don't think i would make merch out of
that but
i still have ideas for example you know
the cutting board for example was the
thing i wanted to do before
i could also do cutlery
what else
sleep sleeping masks although i don't
know no maybe not sleeping masks but
that would fit in with the blanket
um yeah the shield cutting board i think
that would be a big big big um
candidate for next year
i wish we could do a knife because it
would be so cool if we could have the
shield cutting board with the sword
knife
it must be so
good i don't know if it's so loud though
[Music]
yeah
i'll ask next year when the time comes
oh yeah popsicle popsicle thingy yeah
yeah that would be fun too
butter knife i guess so we probably
would be able to do a butter knife
didn't someone have eating utensils i
feel like i saw that yeah but i don't
think a knife was included
i think i remember spoons
i'll let her open up oh
[Music]
that's cool
yeah but no knife right yeah
yeah that's the thing oh well
uh it's too early now anyway maybe we
got even more ideas
until next year so for now
it's uh
nothing we need to worry about
um
wait i think i forgot to kiss c and pony
mwah thank you neko fox thank you for
the recipe
happy birthday mommy for birthday cake
thank you
i did
i did get myself some
like really small cake
from the supermarket just like a piece
for the birthday celebration and i was
trying to eat it during the
um
during the concert while watching but my
eyes were so focused on the screen i
could barely take a bite
i did end up finishing it though of
course uh but yeah but i saw like um
i saw i think a japanese fan
ordered a cake like a prava whole round
full cake
with a writing on it happy birthday
takanese
and they ate it themselves but like it's
it's ironic i think that
i myself i'm just i'm just getting
myself a slice from the supermarket
while they're getting themselves a huge
cake for that
yeah
damn
give me a piece you know
[Music]
mama
course he couldn't send it to me
i just i think maybe i should have
gotten myself
a bigger food
oh and and then
after the concert i had mcdonald's by
the way
which oh my god no
i will keep this tangent
remind me of the mcdonald's tangent
soon
maybe tomorrow
i have a i have
i've made good memories at mcdonald's
the other day now let me go to an idol
meeting i'll be here
with you
do
[Music]
yay yay
i got
chocolate rice waffles
nice snack
so i'm feeling a little bit better
than in the beginning of the stream so
we might be able to go on a little bit
longer mm-hmm
chocolate
getting hungry
why cucumbers why
why
this is not enos chat you know
hmm
i'm confused
you know told them to stop but they
don't listen
i assume
she doesn't have her people under
control like i do
she needs to learn from kfp
she needs a usual
room wow
hello
sorry i'm quickly snacking
now because i mentioned mcdonald's now i
want to eat a burger
and some fries
give me that fast food
um
no i'm not gonna run
no
i'm never gonna do that again
and you know why because people
are [\h__\h] insane
measuring how long it took me to get
there
um
so sad you can't see my mouth moving
when i eat when i'm in 3d
i mean i don't actually open it and this
seems to be the proof
yeah
but it looks pretty cute when chihuahua
munches in in 2d
okay
um
suzuki
[Music]
hmm
donating to a streamer girl still sounds
wrong
no
but i want to join in showing my
appreciation
gracias
right
yes
happy canada appreciation day you're the
best i know super chats get cut to hell
so i'll try to buy oh yeah they do try
to buy merch for more materials of like
thank you
i see i see thank you i hope you will
like the merchandise i'm looking forward
to the blanket so much i wanna cuddle
with the blank and it looks so cozy
speaking of a spaniard accent
is that song
spain accent really
well that's
well i mean i am european after all
i am european
i can speak fluent spanish this year
[Music]
yeah i said that correctly
thank you thank you for the red super
chat
could you be one of my people
see
[Music]
your people
lady your humble employee always hopes
the time you and kfb spend together will
continue for a long long time
i hope so too
yeah
you see my
eyes being closed because i'm happy
because i hope so or wait
oh wait look at this and imagine that my
eyebrows
are my
eyelids it looks very similar
but maybe no i guess that's hard to
imagine
all right
i'm not sleeping i'm wide awake now i'm
feeling better
just hungry very hungry
anyway phoenix lady will continue doing
her best so that you can continue
supporting me thank you
thank you soon flash secretary some guy
called blake duncan
duncan 1737 thanks for the pinky
hey boss i've never fought that phone
with someone for so long let alone
donate but here i am only one
explanation it's
late and brainwashing
no no no seems like i fell victim to
your cult but i don't plan on leaving
happy birthday phoenix
no culp but thank you
i guess
um
no there was no brainwashing included
no
thank you so much i i also
for me it's um
hard to imagine too to see like people
follow me for such a long time and not
get sick of me so yeah i'm surprised too
thank you very much
thank you thank you
thank you so much yeah mao mao thank you
soon for the pinky happy birthday my one
and only austrian viewer thank you mama
i still remember how to read your name
i'm so proud of myself thank you for
your support fluffy thank you for the
pinky i just got it some good food
thank you so much for your fun and
energetic streams
and for having such an amazing
personality
oh
thank you
i feel like thank you i feel like i
could um be a better person but
i am doing my best
considering the circumstances that i am
always in
so thank you for the love thank you soon
not gonna read the name of the next one
uh pepsi danger
miniature pincher zhang wow
thank you for one two three four red
super chats
crazy
crazy thank you
oh my god 3d crazy eyes first time
are they even smaller or what they look
crazy
oh my god
so it says happy birthday when i was in
a hard time attention streaming helped
me a lot i hope everything you wish will
come true and i always say this i wish
everyone to be healthy all the time
uh i think the next one is the same in
korean i see i see
ah wait the next one is the same in
german and then the next one is the same
in in japanese you're covering all the
bases wow why so talented
well
not trilingual what's the one uh after
that
what's four lingual
set the expression we see in the usual
room
that's the expression that you will have
on your own face yeah polyglot
sounds like a god
quadrangle
tringle
quadrilingual oh where's going
you
[Music]
i'm trying
to sound like a
fluent
i'm not though
thank you very much
[Music]
happy birthday thank you a swiss word to
learn for you
when i think i heard of this one before
i don't understand why
it says as a sweet swiss person i'm very
disappointed that i have to send a red
super chat is it because their
value is
so much
higher so no i don't understand
i saw yesterday and now i understand ah
ah i thought it was about something else
okay okay you know yeah i guess it is ah
as a swiss person i am so disappointed
that it makes me send a subject
[Music]
what did i say
i mean it's what it's true though i said
switzer dutch is not really german
and but i like switch to dutch it's
funny
it's cute
no i don't i don't insult the swiss
people i would never do that
i want to go to switzerland
ah not it's just a real phrasing things
[Music]
nothing against switzerland
switch your dutch
let's blow our cover
you were trying to be undercover are you
were you acting as if you spoke
german proper german i'm sure you can
you can if you tried
i'm sure that a lot of
sweater people swiss people have
um
good basics
to go off of
to learn german especially depending on
where you live but
where in switzerland but
they definitely have something to work
with oh yeah i don't know
you can do it
learn german today
subscribe to takanashikiyara german
channel to learn german just by
subscribing that's all you need to do
one click on the subscription button and
kaboom uber
you now speak fluent german you're
welcome
[Music]
and happy birthday thank you for all the
great times you've given all of us i
hope you have another wonderful year and
i wish you even more success and
accomplishments i love you give me
forever bye so sweetheart karen you're
the best thank you for being part of the
community you've brought a lot of good
stuff to the community with your amazing
clips yeah you put so much work into
them
it's really impressive
oh big thank you for me and the
community too thank you
[Music]
oh no
no it's not almost
almost unknown
you have some parts of the rainbow and
people interrupted you
your bank stopped you oh no you got the
important ones down though
happy birthday tanjo i hope you have the
most wonderful birthday ever thank you
so much for everything you do you always
give us so much happiness with all your
amazing streams and incredible music you
really are the absolute best ever and i
love you so
much i want you to know that no matter
how much how much time passes you will
always be my wine only ocean i will
continue to support you forever love you
always looking forward to celebrate many
more birthdays with you
ah you're the sweetest thank you so much
i love you
so sweet
thank you for
trying to send a rainbow
yeah these are still the common supers
yeah oh did i get rid of the thumbnail i
did
ah
oh where did it go oh no it's still
there
now thank you unknown for always being
there no matter what i hope that you're
also gonna
be careful though
because you seem to always prioritize me
but you know be careful of your own body
prioritize your own health and all that
if you need to sleep more
or if you need more time for yourself
just for whatever reason you know
no no worries
you can always watch the vod later on
yeah no pressure
been really busy and didn't get to
prepare anything special i haven't been
in your streams that often but i tried
to pop up once in a while stay positive
tension i wish for you more birthdays to
come just here to greet y'all tincho
thank you
you should come more often then
please
why don't you leave me
well thanks for saying hi though
thank you
i appreciate it good to know that you're
still there somewhere
thank you
for the red super chat happy birthday
oh wait should i read this canadian ish
uh
because they're they're they wrote it in
a very special way happy birthday tenzo
here's my my big red art do what you
want with it
thanks fair
for
continuing to bring
me
me self and the others happiness have a
nice day wouldn't it be have a nice day
and ears too hopefully because i know
that's french then
here's to hopefully many more streams
together
let me read them again
happy birthday attention here's my my
big red heart do what you want with it
thanks for continuing to bring me self
and the others have happiness have a
nice day
here's to hopefully many more streams
together
that was a mix of german and i guess
scottish
but it's donated in canadian
maple leaves
eh
it's not canadian
you're not canadian either
eh
maybe maybe you are
better than my nose scottish accent no
way so i should always mix with the
german language to become scotish
oh
could be new scotland oh
what you talking about
i was conceived in canada oh dear lord
that's some info i didn't need
i wonder where i was conceived
i think i was just conceived in austria
but
look the tea is too strong
weirdly okay
here's a case for you here's a kiss oh
yeah
thank you
for the pink super chat nina no
happy birthday to you this is my first
super chat and i just wanted to send it
on a special day thank you for being
here for kfb and making us laugh so much
i hope you have a wonderful day and i'm
looking forward to your future streams
thank you
for your first ever super chat thank you
i'm glad you made it here
hopefully
you always watch my super chats you do
right you do my super chats i mean my
streams
right no need to always say hello with a
super chat but i'm just happy to know
that you're there thank you very much
thank
oh i love that little icon it's so cute
attention everything's furnished
um
[Music]
is
this is perhaps the best countdown
calling i watched early
can't stop laughing cannot wait to watch
your first 3d live concert thank you for
entertaining us for almost two years
let's keep frying chickens wait i mean
flying chickens yeah yeah yeah totally
we
we've already fried enough chickens
maybe we need to
focus back on the important things like
making them fly
we want them to have a meaningful life
before
they get fried after also
we want them to become fruit fries
see a little bit of the world you know
oh yeah about revival soon
it's september right
september will no
end of september maybe will be
the revival for the members who joined
immediately in the beginning
they become as kotoni and i think
they'll be able to fly
easily then
oh you can see when they're going really
far wow
wow
wow i used to always have like you know
sideways a lot of movement in 2d but now
i can even go back
[Music]
stretch
and stretch
wow
pretty good just need to add some arms
yeah i could i think already try it out
like i was sent some
thing
and that i can use for hand tracking
but the other girls tried it out uh
told me about it and said that it does
not work
but
it should
but i don't know
yeah
um i might be using it now but i don't
want to overuse it
uh because
wow
reasons
i still didn't do the pretty debut
so
yeah
i don't want to overuse it
anyway chunky chunk thank you so much
and
yeah
almost two years
let's keep on going chunky chunk
with those slippers on your feet
thank you
[Music]
thank you for the rainbow
somewhere
over the rainbow
there's a donut
she sent
me a lovely rainbow
i hope you can see it too
yeah happy birthday kiana my first
rainbow super chat for best bus
i'm glad that i can be here to celebrate
your second birthday together wishing
you a wonderful birthday and thank you
for your hard work and always bringing
us happiness
it has been over 1.5 years since i
joined kfp wow
so happy that kfp is now becoming bigger
and bigger i will continue to support
your love your attention
i also want to ask if i could get a cafe
staff number oh of course
[Music]
zero seven because that's the current
date that's just apparently what i do
recently
when people ask for numbers i give them
the current date that it's just a
coincidence that's it was always your
number it's just a coincidence that
today is
that date yeah
just a coincidence
thank you very much
for the beautiful rainbow and i hope you
won't get sick of me in the coming
months and years please continue
supporting and me and watching my
streams even if it's just the vods i'm
so happy to have you around thank you
mwah
have another call thank you
i see the end
just got off work we'll watch vlog i'm
late but i'm assuming this stream is
amazing like always and you blew our
brains with your performances and
announcements and existence heart
potential can't wait for your concert oh
thank you but you have to wait
wait i hope you waited faster
thank you very much for your sweet
birthday message and your support and
thank you for watching the vote always
thank you
hope you liked the concert
you think
thank you thank you for the recipe chat
happy birthday to the hottest idol
akka aka world number one tencho and
lady kiara mmm
you always inspire everyone with your
passion energy and persistence the
phoenix will keep spreading her fire to
the world thank you for brightening our
heart you deserve all the love love you
love you too thank you
ah
so good with words aren't ya
yeah start a fire today i will start a
fire every day
hell yeah no matter what they do they
can't stop me don't stop don't stop just
go your own way
thank you so much
you the guy doesn't
[Music]
happy birthday kara you always give me
courage and energy thank you from the
bottom of my heart i bring you from the
top of my heart take care of yourself
and keep up the good work i'll always
support you
[Music]
okay
oh
thank you
i'm fried screw thank you for the red
super chat oh oh feliz navidad no feliz
cumpleanos
[Music]
okay i know that's not the lyrics but i
just kind of
the moment i see feliz
the mom
i love that so much
freestyle hell yeah
um
not sure what it means
is like reminds me of the german word
kompe
which is like
uh
like a
like a friend kind of word
feliz compleanos
anos
[Music]
here huh but i want to ah hold on
yes
i know jaja jai is pronounced hahaha but
in my mind because i'm
austrian we read it as ja jah jah
actually we reading this yeah yeah yeah
yeah
but for some reason in my mind i read it
as ja da da da da da
ya
[Music]
thank you
happy early birthday countdown today
happens to be my birthday so i want to
share the love your birthday too oh my
god no we're free people we could
we could throw a triple birthday party
happy birthday to you too
congratulations
i hope you spend
some nice time on your birthday
ate some good food i wish you all the
best and happiness and all your wishes
come true oh thank you so much for
sharing the birthday with me such an
honor to you or me hmm
and did i give you a kiss gray fellaini
alvaro thank you for the red super chat
keeper happy birthday thank you for
being such a huge source of joy and
happiness
absolute best though thank you wow
i try
i'm glad i can make you guys happy
you guys make me happy too so i need to
give back some help right
um thank you very much alvaro
mom
i'm almost there
almost happy birth potential your
concert might be tomorrow but hearing
you talk with everyone today was great
i'm glad frida was able to make it in
the end looking forward to tomorrow oh
thank you yeah friend originally told me
that she's gonna be streaming so she
might she's not gonna call in so then
she surprised me at the end with colin i
was very happy yeah very sweet
everyone who called in
was so nice i'm so glad they made some
time to talk to me
and and kelly i really understand like
she really wanted to be there but then
she
yeah miss
did a mistake with the time for one hour
she was there like
actually i think i ended my stream
almost an hour later than originally
planned anyway
and then i ended and then immediately
after
she's like hey yo what the [\h__\h] what
what what what happened
[Laughter]
oh man
but i
understand you know she didn't do it on
purpose
and then she put so much effort into the
um
apology
into the wrap
so it's all good in the neighborhood
it's all good in the neighborhood she
wanted to be there and
i appreciate that
yeah
mistakes happen
mm-hmm
[Music]
oh man i really like
i really love maddie and tudo like i
respect her so much and
she's such a great entertainer she's
such an inspiration and she's such a
she's just such a great
person
[Music]
is so
funny she's oh she's so great um
actually she asked me about
a certain club
idea uh a while ago
that that came from her so let's see
if she's really gonna
do it with me
i think she at least wanted my help for
it
but it could take a while i don't know i
don't know maybe she already forgot
about it
but that would be nice too yeah i want
to
keep
didn't realize i thought she was done
streaming for pekura
i didn't realize and and i i just like i
saw her stream announcement before my
stream but i didn't realize it would be
like overlapping like that so i really
didn't think she was streaming i saw it
afterwards though
ah
she was actually cooking something i
really thought she was [\h__\h] me
i really thought she was like because
she said mabo doshi
she said marvel roshi
no sweet
which is like
like a
mysterious dream
uh uh like almost like a fata morgana
bubble
what's the best translation like
phantom yeah illusion she said that
herself so i literally i thought she was
like just
making
[Music]
was streaming too
yeah some of them were streaming i'm
glad they made it even though they were
streaming
yeah
very sweet of them
wait cooper was
oh no no no
huh cooper was streaming i was gonna say
but wait was she streaming during the
call-in
yeah anya was collabing i heard that too
what
cool was done anya was streaming in the
club
wow
it's nice of them that they came anyway
ah choco want stranger
wow everybody's streaming so late
but i wonder you know
i kind of for um
uh hold on ian and whole japan
i kind of like
um
did like an open and vibe thing like i
was like hey who wants to be who wants
to call in
let me know so i can make a list
a schedule
and then for japan
first
they didn't
um like because i did it for my
management
and they went through their management
first i didn't get hear back from anyone
and i was getting really worried but the
moment i messaged them
privately because i think the manager
their managers just didn't like
put it through properly
but once i messaged them privately
everybody was like oh hell yeah i'm
coming i'm coming i'm gonna call in yeah
yeah
i was really worried for a moment that
nobody was gonna call in but then
so many of them wanted to call in and i
feel like
if you really want to give everybody a
chance to call in who wants to call in
then we've come to
a level
where
these kind of calling streams
all have to be
at a minimum of three hours
uh
and i just kind of want to say that okay
this time it was fun but i think i
understand now
why subaru decided to just
do her birthday this year the way she
did do it
not by
like you know letting everybody call in
but just you know
calling herself very specific people and
getting messages from a lot of people
having them
um
like send messages but not actually call
in because it just takes so much [\h__\h]
time and
yeah it's also like
oh my god how does it know i'm up so
high
[Laughter]
uh
i don't know i just i just i think um
this
it's like a
kind of a
pressuring thing
like now it's like uh
um
if if not many people called and it's
like oh my god she's so unpopular and
they don't like her
and it shouldn't be like that because
also it takes so much time it's
exhausting actually
with no break in between and then it's
also so stressful like everybody only
gets such a short time i wish i could
talk more of them but then it's gonna be
five hours instead of three hours so
anyway oh i like how my bangs flow
i think
i don't know if i'm gonna do this the
same way again next year even though it
was fun next year we're gonna have even
more people so maybe even more people
wanna call in and then yeah it's gonna
be so long
i don't know
i might do it differently next year too
like only
either only have really close people
call in or
only en people but i know that's sad too
[Music]
no i'm just assuming that i don't know
id japan
maybe and i don't know one year later
you would assume that probably
it might be growth i don't know anything
it's just if you look at the past of the
whole life so far every year we've
gained members so it just makes sense
do two parts like louie ah but that in
the end also just makes it longer if you
have if it's so long that you have to
split it into two groups
two streams
oh no
yeah
we will see how i feel next year
but i understand subaru's choice now
i was also wondering oh why didn't she
do a
totsumachi
but looking at how long these tutsu
matches take nowadays because everybody
wants to call in
but if i invite only certain people to
keep it short then i also i don't know i
feel like it implies
you know that i don't like certain
people because i didn't invite them
that's not good either you know so
it's putting
me or all of us into a
difficult position
very difficult position
yeah
so how do we
how do we
how
how do we fix this
but that's also another thing that i
liked about super the stream is uh she
didn't i i was thinking she's gonna do a
concert for the concert you know because
why the hell not it's a birthday
and i thought you know everybody does
that now it seems to have become a
standard but she didn't so i guess maybe
that also lowers the pressure of having
to do that too
so but as a trendsetter after all
meet and greet lottery hey you can do a
lottery hey you want to sign up
do your whole life members i'm doing a
lottery
sign up for a ticket to get a chance to
join my call-ins
no
can't do that that's so no no
but i guess what what i could do that
i've seen people do before is have
certain people come in groups
certain people that make sense like
i often see like the gamers calling in
together
and um meal for example
or me or mikko and so on
yeah have have some people come in
groups like you know turducken could
come in the group and so on
yeah
i did that last year yeah didn't i
that did save time
remember
[Music]
i feel like
i feel like um
a year ago
this was still very different like
people didn't
um
expect everyone to call in
i feel like last year it was still like
mostly with totsamachi birthday streams
only like the close
people called into each other's what's
the matchy streams
and
within one year
it's
gotten really extreme
yeah
now everybody
even if they have never talked before
everybody calls in
it takes like three to four or five
hours
gotta keep one upping yourself all right
i feel like that's
that that's what
yeah it feels like an obligation almost
which it should it shouldn't feel like
that but i mean it's fun it's fun but
it's good
three hours of all these calls wow
but it's also maybe a good opportunity
to
make empty promises for collaborations i
was gonna say make promises for
collaborations and then collaborate but
i feel like these are all empty promises
[Laughter]
let's be real this is like the typical
thing to say ah yeah let's collab soon
and then nothing happens
it's like the typical thing that
youtubers say to another
let's go
yeah yeah yeah oh my god yeah totally
it's just like in real life when you say
oh let's hang out again soon
never hanging out ever again
yeah one year later oh man
we didn't get to collab oh we should
totally collab yeah
it's about time that we collab
versus who wants to organize a collab
you're right
right
like i'm um
most of the time i'm the one who invites
people for collabs and
gonna be honest would be nice to be
invited too so i'm not gonna take the
blame i'm not going to take the blame
no if someone wants to call out with me
ask me it took me a lot of courage and
and effort
to always follow up and ask people about
collabos so now momma knows maybe their
turn
coyote clearly is active yeah she asks
people for collabs
good job good job
anyway let me finish these super chats
cause there's only like five left um
matching eight did i read this one
almost happy birthday
i feel like i did oh yeah i did that's
that got me too tensioned
thank you masten eight for bringing me
on this tangent
it's already been four hours what the
[\h__\h]
how
moose thanks for the pinky
yay
happy birthday
thank you for celebrating with me
come sign me down
[Music]
is
i think it's kiara
name
[Music]
don't tell me the numbers
it's intimidating that i've still got so
much to go
[Music]
for the pinky
i'm done with these
something
we might need another super chat reading
stream yeah
yeah i guess so
i could probably do a few more from the
other stream because i'm feeling okay
i guess
there we go
[Music]
tomorrow okay
so
suppacha
thank you
thank you guys thank you
i'm okay
i'm gonna dip my toes into it uh but
before that let me
let me change my
looks
[Music]
there we go
wow
am i allowed to wear these i wonder
oh my god
[Music]
there's so much stuff wow
oh
[Music]
honey honey
why do we have this
why do we
not dead
okay um
i'm looking crazy
um but
please appreciate this
hard work
hard work has been poured into this
okay ah wait maybe
one more tiny adjustment
okay that's good
[Music]
i don't even
i have wrapped on this glasses on
and a huge umbrella
all right
i'm gonna make it smaller
nice
it's about to open umbrellas in there
and don't worry don't worry it's fine
yes fine
i need to protect myself
from
good question what do i need to protect
myself from i just had a feeling you
know
the petals outside yeah before they come
in
i'm scared of them i'm scared
falling cockroaches oh yes but flute
fries food fries
that's the real reason
obviously
it's protecting myself from the flute
fries
understandable
um
[Music]
okay
lunchbox thank you for the red super
chat
canada everything that went into this
concert is like we got the birthday gift
instead hey of course yeah that's how it
is
from the off collapse to all of the hard
work everyone involved has put in most
would just accept they couldn't have a
3d birthday but you went above and
beyond yeah
yeah no i would not accept that
because you know after getting my hopes
up i'm not and your guys hopes up too
like
you know the fact that i talk so much
about all the preparation
it kind of you know
puts me in a position where it's hard to
go back on it too
yeah when when management was like
saying like ah you know
it's looking difficult can't find any
studios in europe that are like
affordable
uh any any freaking every every studio
hit up every single one of them i feel
like
at least at least the ones that you know
they said would work
with like the the
technical stuff
yeah and then i was like damn it i can't
give up though because i got all their
hopes up
and i want to do it for myself too
i have all these like ideas all these
songs i want to perform and i really
just want to show off all the choreos
that i've had for so long
well
i took them out there
i'm gonna
lower the glasses a bit more
okay
[Music]
look i love them a little bit too much
hello
i love them too much looks stupid
dorky
[Music]
it still looks dorky
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] i reset it
oh no
i have to put it in position again
okay
[\h__\h]
it's a little bits
a little bit lopsided [\h__\h]
about now
okay that's okay
that's okay oh [\h__\h] it's not okay but
it's okay
thank you
lunchbox
is dangerously dangerous
thanks for pinky happy birthday quinoa i
can't even begin to tell you how much
i'm excited for this concert you and the
rest of me will once again achieve the
impossible you always work so hard i'm
so proud to call you my aussie viva
lucky i love you boys oh thank you
i'm very happy to be called youroshi i'm
proud to be your oshi
thank you so much for the love and
support
and the satisfied question logical
paradox
captain jerkbands thank you you and the
girls worked so hard on this so i know
it will be legendary also give a
generous tip to kana uvu who must be
burning the midnight oil with this
project
yeah he worked for the whole night yeah
yeah yeah i'm sure he was really
stressed out too thank you for the pinky
thank you very much
we did work hard on it especially almond
no i'm so sorry i'm in sick now like i
was looking forward to you know you know
her coming back now streaming getting
back to streaming
um but now
now she's
sick poor almond hope she gets better
soon
hi hapa thank you for the red super chat
no matter
what
[Music]
foreign
mmm
thank you for the rainbow
well you know you know that's why i'm
that's why i have the umbrella out
because rainbow usually comes after a
rain
and therefore i still have my
my
umbrella just in case you know you never
know when they come
prepared
so forever says happy birthday to the
phoenix who works a lot every single day
for all her chimpkins i hope we're able
to give you a little back of the love
you show us every single day you make
each day special just by being yourself
and i hope your birthday is as special
as you are you're a shining example for
all of us we all tend to follow your
example as we try to be better chimpkins
no don't bother my example
i'm uh
i'm not the best example i think you
have accomplished amazing things in the
zone by pushing yourself hard and hard
and it is that commitment that we all
love about our one and only aussie i
wish you all the best on your special
day chiara we all love you so much and
we'll always be here to support you
happy birthday thank you
thank you
no don't tell call me a role model now
uh
i'm not perfect
i wish i was perfect
but i'm not perfect
sadly
you guys are great the way you are so
you guys don't need to really change
anything either but but
i don't know
i intend to be better
better than me
okay that's good
[Laughter]
always um
go for the best
always reach for the
improvement
yeah
i think the only way i could be a role
model is when it comes to alcohol
and all that kind of stuff
straight edge
yeah thank you bro from wow you're the
best
you're so sweet i love you thank you
thank you so much
jay swagbuck also with a rainbow and
j swagbuck is an umbrella
just look at his
look at his profile picture
maybe maybe me bringing out the umbrella
was foreshadowing for jay swagburg as
well
[Music]
didn't expect that huh
happy birthday guys i hope it's a great
one i'm super excited for the concert i
know it's going to be amazing
and what brilliant
i first found your streams at the very
end of 2020 and back then i wasn't even
sure what an oshie was let alone had one
since then i've had a ton of fun
watching your streams at the end of 2020
that's so long ago you're still here
uh i'm following along with your music
and projects i'm proud to call you my
first and only aussie and last one
hopefully i'll keep watching as long as
i can i know you have
i know you have so much you still want
to do thanks for being awesome and once
again happy birthday
yeah
thank you
[Music]
bro i'm here since the beginning thank
you
thank you too
yeah did you kiss profile did i not i
feel like i did
frown foul
i feel like i did though
anyway jasper thank you so much
thank you thank you i'm i'm glad
i'm your first and your only one
thank you
[Music]
let's let's go until 20
23 24 25
onwards let's go
dancing
for the beautiful rainbow now my
umbrella makes so much sense
you're super talented happy birthday
thank you
so let's keep playing thanks for the
pinky one pinky now one after what it
should have been an absolutely stellar
concert i love the foam nail it shows
how my oh she finally gets to sing and
dance among the stars where she deserves
to be love all the merch and family
happy birthday
thank you
actually
the thumbnail
i was very picky about the thumbnail
pose
i asked um kana uvu
to give me some poses
uh that i can use for the thumbnail
and i i did send
a
sample
absolutely
gorgeous sample
and i'm gonna try to find it
[Music]
oh
oh there it is
this is turned around
wait
[\h__\h]
this way
so i wanted to be on one side i wanted
to reach out my hands to the front and
kind of you know dynamically
tilted angle to side
of this with the audience in the
background
which if you look at that now seems
somewhat accurate yeah but
[Music]
his first attempts were not really
accurate
but they're cute though i think i should
upload the other attempts eventually
i liked this one
this one was nice but i just thought um
composition wise it wouldn't work so
well as uh as a thumbnail
but it looks cool
take it carefully take it
take it off my hands
i like the pose yeah
but
uh for thumbnail it would have been a
bit difficult i have a special eye for
that
a special eye to judge
you know what works hell
yeah a bit too centered i said more on
one side please
same pose same pose but more on one side
and then he sent me one was what had a
different pose
and then finally it ended up being that
one over there but it took a few tries
but they're all cute and then one of the
the
ones that didn't make the cut i uploaded
as a
afterwards
thank you
tweet message thingy
so that worked out fine
mm-hmm
[Music]
for two pinkies happy [\h__\h] eternal
and second birthday attention but every
year you keep shining rather and
brighter you always work hard and do
your best to entertain us we've been
following and supporting you so long and
don't regret a single second of doing so
you always are sweet caring and a
lovable person to all of us your
cheerfulness and sweet smile singing and
dances can overturn even the worst day
i'll be at your service till my last
dying breath anyway i can't wait to
build quiet blanket fort i'm bragging
for oh
you need some pillows too though don't
you
blanket fort cute i came up with the
names here bottom working one won't call
them rock and
i said that already i think when i first
showed the merchandise i said it again
because it's important
oh yeah the armor pillows yeah
i'm pointing
i know they're not perfectly scented
it's difficult
nobody's perfect
[Music]
um
i
totally didn't stretch
thank you hold on for two pinkies
pudding down cushion
bottom fragger thanks for the pinky
happy birthday wow what is my first pink
and i want to commemorate all your hard
work for the concert i know it will be
great you were made for the stage
thank you for being born for joining her
life and most of all thank you for being
my aussie love your attention oh thank
you
i gladly am your
or she at your service
at all times
as often as possible
thank you very much
for your first thank you wow
so generous very generous
[Music]
this this form makes it too obvious when
i
change sitting position
don't fret me out
don't rat me out oh what'd you return to
well i'll come back
it's a rainy day isn't it
eh
congratulations on your birthday before
watching kfb i settled for a life i
don't want to challenge new things but
lately i have a lot of things that i
want to do thanks for giving me believe
that phoenix will always be there my oc
that's nice i think it's always nice to
try new things that you always wanted to
do or even things that you didn't think
you wanted to do
try it out anyway could be surprisingly
fun to you
and maybe your new hobby
yeah maybe also brings you
to new people meet new people
um but yeah don't don't get too many
hobbies number one hobby must be
kiwa
hashtag
yolk
thank you for being part of kitty
yeah
your boy stephen adams down question
that code thank you for the red super
chat happy birthday thank you mom so
proud of you for using birthday of
course you were gonna use boob day
proper
proper word it's not birthday it's
birthday
yeah yeah
thank you very much for the love the
good
hope you enjoyed the concert i wonder
what your favorite part was
i stopped watching anime because of you
oh you mean you're still watching anime
i am anime
i've reached the final stage of weeaboo
[Music]
a burning flame shining light a beacon
or bacon of passion just listing a few
of the many things that you are in life
uh thank you for everything you do for
us for making each one of us feel
special you make me feel special
in some way happy birthday my beloved
potential and comments on your concert
thank you
thank you thank you thank you yeah
ah
i know we did it huh it's over now the
the concert arc
the concert preparation like
now that i at least you know know the
choreos of my own songs all of them
next time i'm doing a concert i might
not have to learn
as much choreos
[Music]
um
but i will always want to do dances that
have a lot of choreos so yeah
i mean there's still a lot of like
vocaloid songs out there
uh
and anime songs too
of which i know the choreos already so
i can try to
fill those in
so i don't have to learn too much
any thoughts on getting your own mocap
set up yeah i've been thinking about it
a little bit
uh
but yeah i'm not sure
because i am getting like a suit
the the one that couldn't amen and ina
already have
the one that they used for streaming a
little bit but it's not
you've seen it during the arm wrestling
it's not
really good enough for a concert and
yeah it's just yeah janky
and relies on
certain things unlike what we used for
uh recording the concert that that was
really
different kind of setup
and quality
so yeah for some streams
i want to use it uh but it's also been
delayed
when i get it i think i won't get it
until end of august perhaps
so it will take a while but once i get
it i want to implement it in my streams
a little bit at least um
yeah
and then for
besides that
i will see if if the borders to japan
open up
somewhat soon for us
and then
maybe no need to get a setup myself
because the studio in japan i can use
for free
um it's just a flight but
the flight is
okayish price wise and i also get more
things out of it like i can
you know
just have fun in japan meet other people
and so on so
it's definitely worth it
um
you know i need to compare
possibilities
[Music]
yes
please i watched that stream of hers
yesterday i watched the vod of her
advertising
this
connecto machine i saw that machine in
the
in the round one
that we went to but it was before an
energy corral
it was before nanetti cordable but it
was it stood out so much to me i kind of
wanted to try
but there was a girl playing with it
some random small girl
but negating is not time limited she's
like gonna be forever in the machine so
i will play with her eventually
hmm
very exciting
she's gonna be in the
non-japanese machines too i assume right
it's the same
everywhere i assume
wish we had a round one i don't think we
have a round one in the street
round one austria
now
round one germany
round one europe
new arcades
in first round one in europe 2020
where
and
huh
why don't we get around one like in
central europe
please
[Music]
even canada and not even canada
oh is it only u.s and japan because like
the fact that u.s had one made me think
that it's actually more
common than i thought it was
[Music]
please yeah
we need round
please
i really want it i would go there so
often because it has all the japanese
stuff
yes
50 plus locations in u.s
holy [\h__\h] they should think about going
to europe please uh
no we don't have
arcades anywhere in austria
[Music]
take purikura
because they come with polikora and we
don't have folicula in austria
[Music]
doesn't even have to be
in the eu
how about london
they should make a round one in london i
feel like that could work
please i will travel to london for a
round one
arcades are not really a thing in europe
but yeah you sure maybe in italy because
i remember when i was younger when i was
like a tiny baby child
when i'm going on a vacation to italy
with my own family i remember we went
into an arcade
and now my image is that italy likes
arcades
right yeah
[Music]
refine my british accent my my british
accent
don't
don't need no
refinement
i've been watching some more task
mastery recently
so good
reform meant our refinement
sounding way less scottish
maybe maybe i want to sound scottish i
ever thought about that mate
a boot about
um uh anyway
thank you dusty
mr casper thank you for two pinkies
[Music]
for 661 days oh you've been blessing for
you've been a blessing for us chickens
and not just for the variety of
consistent great content you provide
like this concert but for being an
all-around good person seriously you're
as genuine as they come and like mrs
cronie said
that's a shining trait of yours ah yeah
that meant a lot to me
[Music]
that and the fact that you're like
incredibly fun i can't overstate just
how much fun you are in every stream and
on twitter thank you you're fun too
thanks for all that you do for us lady
wow
thanks for being yourself and thanks for
putting up with my silliness happy
birthday your glorious story
and i cannot wait to see how much higher
you store in the future proud of you
thank you
yeah i really enjoy
everything you write to me so thank you
very much for
being such a bright
bright
sweet chicken
source of entertainment for me too
thank you very much
dusty sends another pinky is that a
rainbow though no no no no just another
pinky okay
i can't wait for the concert while you
said not to get high expectations but
it's you in it so they can't get any
higher also looking forward to your
birthday emoji i've ordered and maya
please ask for my employee number thank
you love you oh damn it now i can't give
you 807. i already gave it to someone
else
[Music]
she came in with a big stretch
oh and now she
now she flopped down
she wants the belly pets
i can't i can't come here
if you come here i can give you belly
rubs
she needs a new number yeah [\h__\h] how
about um it's almost it's almost the
eighth no
it's almost a ninth how about
907.
i mean not how about that's already your
number anyway i'm just um it's not like
you have a choice
dusty you are now 907. hopefully no one
else has that number
a reverse ah
no can't do it it's it's oh it was has
been 907.
yay you like the number
gotta go hope you feel better i already
do thank you for watching
that was not lazy no
as long as you're not giving five 550
i'm not sharing
what you also don't even have it in your
name
i guess you just wrote it down on the
card huh
oh well okay dusty thank you love you
too
genie kunis thank you for the red super
chat rat
that's rad
happy birthday i can't believe it's
already been seven months since i became
kfb
every day has been exciting and and
before i even noticed that you have
become my favorite oh no contest wow
i wish you a great birthday and many
live concerts in the future that is so
flattering i love you excuse me thank
you so much
seven months huh
i'm hoping you'll stay until the full
year minimum
that's rad
that's red red
red i don't like that word it's hard to
say
thank you so much i hope i said your
name somewhat okayish
nice glasses thank you
it's what up my glasses
ah speaking of
[Music]
foreign
thank you for the rainbow wow
a chicken lives a mere eight years while
the phoenix is forever and then it's
warm the chicken cheers happier than
ever wait this is cute
the firebird moves with grace to a beat
and allures all with her song her
performances bathed in flames and heat
dancing all night long
a powerful presence that is never
extinguished
rising again from the ashes that refuses
to say she is ever finished that isn't
afraid to take her chances ah that one
didn't rhyme
the chicken admires the majestic bird
its wings too soft for flight and yet
inspired the thought occurred to live
with all its might
ah man i love it besides that one
chances
what is a chicken to the phoenix but
alive too fragile for its flames and yet
it's hard so filled with tenderness love
it all the sames
when the chicken sees the phoenix fly
over oceans vasts to lands afar as it
burns itself up the flames running high
the light shining brighter than any star
how beautiful is all the chicken can
think what more is there to discuss
here at the end i'll be sushi
you're too good for us
right it continues ah no the poem is
over thanks for putting up with my
crappy poem it was so good i like your
choice of words it's like
so sweet
although some of your rhymes didn't work
so well
um but the sweetness of it makes up for
it
i've i've seen certain other poems from
certain other kfp members who which are
very
to nebu
and yours yours is just sweet
i don't know how you do it but i love it
so thank you wait the rest is we
appreciate how much hard work you put in
for us and you've been an inspiration
for many of us in all sorts of ways
you've given us the drive to improve our
studies learn new hobbies find better
jobs meet new people and even get buff
that can be said for many of us just
talking for me your presence has been an
improvement in my life giving me a
better outlook for the present and
future what
i couldn't afford to send out all of
this if not for you oh
let's not talk about my sleep schedule
thank you for joining her live entering
our lives
i'm happy to be part of kfb i'm happy to
have met you like this oh yeah yeah yeah
you praise you praise that i improved
your life so much but we're trying to
ignore the fact that i ruined your your
sleep schedule
good choice
thank you so much
thank you with a beautiful poem i want
to hear more i enjoyed reading that it
was almost like
i want to say childish but
maybe that's why i like it because it's
so easy to understand for
probably even a child
because my english is
innocent yeah
i'm i'm i'm praising this poem so much
hey
wanted to keep it simple i love it
especially the first few lines
ah
it's so nice
and also kind of sounds like a
um nature documentary
the content of your poem
yeah i'm happy to be part of kfb i'm
happy to have met you like this
me too thank you mary pippin so much for
the double rainbow
thank you
i love you so sweet thank you for being
part of kfb
wish you all all the best
i hope you can fix your sleep schedule
without
without uh lacking kiwa content
thank you for doing your best to watch
my streams
jackets monkey donkey
thank you for a red and a pinky happy
day and thank you for all your hard work
ah
thank you for being there to appreciate
it otherwise it wouldn't be worth it so
he has chicken nuggets thank you for two
pinkies happy birthday kiana you've
accomplished so much this past year
constantly reminded me of why i'm so
proud to have you as my oshi just these
past months you worked so hard and
preserved your turn
to turn your dream of free of a 3d
birthday life into reality a big
highlight of this year for me was
meeting you with dokomi and finding out
just how sweet of a person you are oh
i hope i managed to convey how
incredible and important you are to me
also no one will be misled over who my
aussie is now with my name
oh you changed it
i mean if i was always your aushie
then
it was always just like
about [\h__\h] time
yeah but
thank you so much
you have finally become kiana's chicken
nuggets damn finally you know it's i
didn't even quite notice this time
because it just felt so natural maybe in
my mind every time i read your name
i just
changed it in my brain
automatically
into kiana's chicken nugget
two years later yeah what kept you from
doing it all this time
thank you though
finally that's much better
thank you
also whoever said only 200 left or still
200 left
it's way more than 200 what are you
talking about
i'm at like
out of
[Music]
[Applause]
kill me
i can't do this how am i gonna do this
oh my god
ah 200 left in pre-chat oh dear lord
um
how
delete them
[Music]
membership messages
no
i have them off
in this list
i know wait the numbers i see how it is
so for example it jumps from three four
nine two three five five
so even if i have the membership
messages turned off
the numbers don't adjust it just skips
them
ah
yeah 530 goes to 540 and then 544 557
and
558.9 562.
yeah yeah okay i see how it is so
i don't know the actual number now
but
it's still a lot
i think it's still more than 200
it feels it looks like more than 200
damn
only
well how many did we read so far
no no i mean with the other one with the
other one
don't get my hopes up
300 500
hmm
[Music]
it's almost been five hours i could have
been faster
three hundred all right i mean it's all
right we'll get there sometimes
[Music]
[Applause]
almost rainbow
it's just missing the red one i think
what thank you christina
the day has finally come do i say it
again well today you are no longer just
a majestic phoenix shiny elegant
precious etc
now you are lady lady kiwa
anyway this is supposed to be turning
into a rainbow let's make this long hey
it's almost two years little big bird
and you have done very well we are proud
of you and your achievements let's
continue to learn things together
because i feel that kfb has become a
little family that you raised well
i'm sorry i lied i will stay here
because the colorant is beautiful like
you i love you always be you
orange is nice yeah
i lied to you again red is also a nice
color like you what are you talking
about christina you confused me
i haven't seen the concert yet but i
know it was spectacular happy birthday
christina thank you
you're the best
still drawing so much of me
[Music]
it's like your love for me is eternal
huh
can't leave my side love me too much
understandable
keep trying yeah
[Music]
your love is even eternal i have a
chains on your hands
which one could it be
bonkers
thank you so much christina i'm so happy
to have you thank you
[Music]
i choose number three praise kiana
wait where was that choice i'll keep it
short you can't hide it ah visit the
collins
you're kind-hearted compassionate and
amazing in so many ways i have so much
to be thankful for since you're a
wonderful blessing in my life you're the
sweetest thing in the world i love you
so much my ocean shut up i love you too
you're so sweet
yeah
your tweets and your messages
are always such a pleasure to read thank
you for being part of kfp
[Music]
thank you
gary carter
thank you for the reds and two pinkies
happy birthday kiana i have a new niece
coming any day and her middle name will
be phoenix
really
that's pretty cool but
[Music]
it doesn't quite sound like a name you
know
wait
it's your niece
did you get to make that request
that suggestion or was it their idea
did you push it onto them
successfully
hoping that
denise would turn into a kfp member
one day
it's not uncommon in english really
really
middle names can be weird
heard that as a middle name before what
to me that sounds really weird i'm sorry
[Music]
it's like giving someone the middle name
washington
or
or cat
okay i think i've heard cat before as a
nickname as a nickname though uh okay
another good example how about hamster
giving someone the middle name hamster
washington is oh for [\h__\h] sake i guess
i'm not choosing good examples but it's
like giving someone the name hamster
okay
that's maybe a good example
because phoenix
is
somewhat of an animal
my cousin is named hamster what's wrong
with it
no [\h__\h] way
my name is my naming my man if you have
no
goddammit
okay but maybe there's just something
yeah i'm missing because i'm i didn't
grow up in america maybe phoenix is not
so weird as as i feel like it is well
i'm having healthy shoes right now as
well some as many unfortunate things are
happening around me but you along with
my two cats remind me to smile and to
keep going i'm so proud of how hard you
work for everything and i'm so excited
to see this life
that you've worked so hard on thank you
for being my aussie and being new and
thank you to all of kfb for being such a
great community i agree thank you
thank you for the sweet words i'm sorry
that i dissed the
middle name
but i hope you're
uh
niece
you said she's coming any day i don't
know if she's already there now but i
hope she will have a safe journey to the
world
um
and yeah i hope i hope she's uh gonna
join kfp
once she can speak
teach her
about kfp all right danke shin it's your
your duty now um
[Music]
is this the one the thing that you guys
were talking about
the letter thingy
thank you
i will keep this tab open and read it
afterwards yeah it's like 49 messages is
this what you
or is it something else
it seems to be medanga's uh project yeah
is this the testimonials i don't know
i think it's two or three different fan
letters from groups oh no
why so many thank you very much done
kitchen
[Music]
this is my first super chat happy
birthday
every kfb always love and support you
finally
oh
you're gonna ask for a raise or what
no actually not
[Music]
smile makes us happy thank you always
it's saya
thank you i thought you were gonna
put a secret message into that korean
text but you're actually a good chicken
aren't you
i'm so proud of you gucci king good
chicken who's a good chicken you're a
good chicken who's a good chicken
you're a good chicken
who's a good chicken
thank you
yeah thank you for your first super chat
thank you soon
fox 17 thank you for uh two pink super
chatters happy birthday and congrats to
one million on twitter quinoa i'm not
able to send you super jets often but
i'll always cheer my hardest in youtube
chat twitter etc for my lovely oshi
you're very precious to me blows away
with your concert like the majestic verb
you are everyone is gonna see how hard
working talented and sweet you are your
dancing skill will light a fire in them
and your warm and beautiful singing
voice will vow the ice that may linger
in their hearts thanks for melting my
darkness away love you oh well
damn
thank you so much [\h__\h] yeah so we didn't
talk about it but i got 1 million
twitter followers
on my birthday i was scared to mention
it because i thought if i tweet about it
that then people are gonna unfollow
for troll
reasons so i kept quiet
but i did reach 1 million thank you very
much i
i tweet a lot
and i also reply to you guys a lot so
whoever doesn't follow me maybe it's
about time because i feel like we
will communicate a lot there
um it's worth it following me
i'm like
i tweet the most out of all of whom live
english and even within hall of japan
i'm probably one of the top 5 tweeters
[Music]
my twitter game is strong hell yeah
thank you [\h__\h]
thank you soon very much
i appreciate you being part of kfp
and thank you soon for your love
mwah
ultimo mk2o friend
donation for two red super chats crazy
crazy thank you
happy birthday to the wonderfulest and
beautifulest phoenix boss idol in the
world the most amazing and special
person in my and everyone else's life of
course deserves a very special present
hands you an ultimate with a ribbon on
his head
seriously though you deserve all the
wonderful things that happened to you
and that you worked so hard for even if
you sometimes don't believe it but
there's no need for that leave the being
shook heads to us and celebrate yourself
and all your achievements oh thank you
[Music]
thank you
for your sweet words and you're so
generous wow it's way too much but thank
you thank you thank you for leaving dunk
came from every layer of my cocoa
[Music]
the
the deep the little ones and the higher
ones every layer wow
thank you
i'm running on the words though
i'm running on the words to say thank
you
oh maybe i should leave it there but you
get some kisses catch them
um
[Music]
time to go no
maybe we should stop
and then tomorrow after minecraft we can
continue
uh 104
is where we're at
okay now we're at 105.
105.
[Music]
suzukimasu
yeah i want to say thank you
from the bottom of my coconut from all
the layers
so
uh i'll better stop here
otherwise it gets
ingenuine
and if there's one thing i can say about
myself is that i am
very
genuine and honest to you guys
to honest
often
probably
but
that's just what i am and who i am i
want to be
honest i don't want to hide things that
don't need to be hidden
um
so
yeah
it might get me into trouble sometimes
but
i just don't like lying to you
guys the mcdonald's story you ask me
about that tomorrow hey
hey
ah now i want fast food
the [\h__\h]
i think i do have a hello fresh recipe
for burger
i was going to eat my leftovers from
yesterday but maybe i eat my burger
recipe but i'm lazy
but i have to cook i think i will cook
yeah i'll figure it out burger
post those pics i will
thanks for being honest thank you for
listening to me
grab my immersion grab food from
but but
but
but then that means that one of you has
to die
no
i can't do that no
i don't i don't want to sacrifice one of
you i love you guys too much
take me take me no
no
i can't do that
breaks my heart
no stop volunteering i don't wanna eat
you
never gonna eat you up never gonna let
you die
never gonna let you become my burka
okay
ah
no i don't want to be the reason why you
died
[Music]
okay
i'll go now
uh
so thank you
for spending the time with me for five
hours of super jet reading
i hope it wasn't too boring
point five k people rick rolled hell
yeah
only caught the end need to watch the
vote
it's okay it's just a super chat rating
there were some tangents though
oh thank you
thank you
i hope you guys have a nice wonderful
day
get some yummy food get some energy
and watch some netflix
and i'll see you tomorrow for minecraft
i feel like we're just gonna go
exploring because of the new update
um i want to get frog and i know there's
more animals but you know i love frog
i know inna just went also on the frog
journey but i also want a frog i can't
help it
i want frog
yeah
go on journey
ragiata
she didn't find one
it's just like with the electra
all right then i shall have the first
frog of the halloween server
[Laughter]
easy easy peasy i'm gonna find it
immediately
then i'm gonna flex it i'm gonna put it
in her house
i'll find a better swamp yeah are they
so rare what the hell
santa has one oh really
really
sana is sharing one
[Music]
nana give the channel a frog well that's
not the same she didn't find it herself
all right anyway thank you guys for
watching
and
i'm dipping
[Music]
i put up the reservation probably before
i sleep probably maybe not we'll see
eh let's hope i can sleep earlier today
i think i'll throw in some melatonin
yeah
auf wieder of the saiyan
matanos
[Music]
yeah
thank you for spending time with us no
thank you
yeah
i love you
[Music]
say goodbye to the butt crack
goodbye
all right
bye-bye
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
you