[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
yes
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
whoa hello
we're here we're ready
ready
as we could be
as ready as possible hey look you know
what let it be said that we tried man I
grinded in this game we've been here
we've been practicing as a team yes I
don't know you're doing pretty good we
weren't doing well I don't think we lost
yeah we had some good battles yeah yeah
we're too strong together
well I feel like the BC buff
I will be taking overs you're in C for
today so let me introduce you to the
stream today's stream if you're not
aware is the free Pokemon World
Championship
events
yay thank you for inviting us let's go
thank you huge thank you for including
thank you very much thank you thank you
exciting the first Pokemon unite World
Championship to be held in Asia we'll
start tomorrow from August 11th to 12th
in Yokohama and in the Pokemon unite
category teams from all around the world
will fight for their championship and we
will also be fighting for Championship
again Indonesia and JP representing
I'll be taking the Pokemon Wiggly tough
as full of support we also have Miss
Calliope Mori would you like to
introduce yourself hi everybody Mark
Clive here
um I will be playing as uh Garchomp
jungler
um I will be jungler or I uh I will feed
so
later sorry sorry mid laner I will be I
will be mid laner excuse me
and Iris Would you like to introduce
yourself uh hiris is Iris I will be uh
using Glaceon today uh glaceon's wearing
very cute clothes and I will be bottom
today
[Laughter]
all right next up we have takanashi
Kiara ah hi hello
um I am representing every European out
there who is currently awake at 4 5 or 6
a.m I've been staying awake but I'm very
awake still so I think I will be fine
let's come buddy muscle I'm doing alolan
nine tails because yeah what else
but it'll be great it'll be great
and we're going to have Amelia Watson
please introduce yourself hello Amelia
Watson number one detective today I'll
be your tank yes rely on me please
thanks then let's go stay with me
I'm going top with uh Kiara yes yes yay
shows My Bodyguard
well I'm there it's only a little bit of
time left before the world championship
I'm sure everyone
Championship oh wait yeah well for today
a few minutes
going down at this moment
so how about we watch the PV together oh
good idea okay I'll do a little
countdown and we can all share it on our
streams okay okay I hope I don't blast
your guys's ears
yes yes the first one
three two one go
our summer starts now
I love the animation yeah
they broke the budget for this one
whoa oh boy
now isn't that a legendary Pokemon look
at that cash money
I wish I was just cool when playing
Pokemon I know right
yeah we're just holding a switch procons
okay exactly
cute
[Music]
what do you guys think right yeah it was
really cute it's funny to show anime
this is wrong it says em first eh oh
was it changed I'm pretty sure we were
told differently
and we thought that that was a good idea
because you know
can you find out for us if this is
accurate right now and we'll just talk
over it for now yeah a lot of a Pokemon
unite World Tournament is a promotional
event for the Pokemon u9 category of the
world championship 2023 oh I have a
whole life English and whole life
Indonesia will battle head to head to
settle who will shine on top hopefully
it'll be us
the three matches on BJP versus id id
versus enjp versus en and the match will
follow the WCS rules therefore Mewtwo
will be banned oh wait are you guys
showing the slides sorry yes yes yeah
wait wait they're not they're the shoes
like it's like black wait wait
it's okay for me yeah reopen and in a
case of a three-day tie the team who
scores the most will be crowned the
winner no so okay try for points
tournaments go
the winner wins
wins and
we all get I think there's there should
be like something right consolation
prizes
next slide
please oh okay okay cool
the MVPs of each team will be awarded
with like real physical prizes the WCS
actually uniforms which are not for sale
they're more exclusive
wearing the Pokemon units Hollow air
and other teams will be awarded with 2D
trophies according to their placements
difference in color that's all you know
yeah you can just pretend there's
nothing different except for the color
if it's just our screen no one will know
yeah they'll think we're the winners
I really want that shirt though that's
true yeah I know well speaking of the
shirt our characters in game are also
wearing this shirt which you can also
purchase yourself from the shop the
digital version and the in-game store
we are going first seems like it yeah
we're going first apparently okay
that's great amazing
we were doing good just remember how we
were playing remember we're winning okay
oh no first thinking just because just
because it's the JP okay JP team it's
fine JP team pick pretty darn sweaty
though yeah no problem we can be sweaty
too just gotta get in the mindset you
know yeah
precipitation
here in the other participants for the
tournament from JP we have Caillou
yes
I suppose oh yeah oh and for a hollow
Live ID we have Ali Anya Renee Kyla and
Nicole
don't be full but they're cuteness
they're scary
they are scary I mean we're supposed to
be lore-wise you know like God's demons
oh my God we should be pretty darned
right now
including one one one human
the most mythical creatures I know in
Halloween I've really been wanting well
I guess we have we got on me we have
British members
hearing your British accent you don't
bring it out very often
I wish you would let your natural accent
shine sometimes
it's okay I'll try okay
next one
I think now I'm waiting to do the
introductions
okay okay for now okay okay so these are
can I close it
because we put away the slide please can
we close it okay
we're not as mentally prepared as we
thought
um
I was still debating on what Pokemons
[Applause]
um
how do we get into the room
uh they will send a code and we will
input the code make sure not to show it
on stream I love how the order of the
matches it makes it seem like the whole
alive JP and ID are like the the finals
yeah and I get to sleep early if yeah I
mean yeah
we're never gonna win if we have this
kind of attitude
and call me if you need help please just
say Maury and I will I will go to you
okay I'm using your lane matchup you
know who to call
Yeah the code will be provided to us
right
yes I think we're also gonna go into
meet the rest of the
chewy do we wait until there oh it looks
like they are I think they're going okay
oh okay we go there wait are they is
there a Lobby already the all regions
Channel it looks like oh to produce it
for introductions yes do we move too
okay we go we go let's go
[Music]
I'm nervous it's just you and me
do we go in I guess so let's check
what's going on all right they kick us
out yeah
we'll just go
I see me
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
um
I think that's why thank you Kiara thank
you yes
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
let's battle
foreign
you can go
away
[Laughter]
I hear the motivation gaps but it's okay
can I ask you
[Music]
[Applause]
so it seems that the battle already
started right the gong gongling
everyone here
[Laughter]
believe yourself
[Applause]
[Music]
are you going back
my tummy hurts oh no oh don't be nervous
the food you ate no right before nervous
don't be nervous I'll be fine food just
gotta Focus your food I'm hungry some
food I need some food
[Music]
yeah we're the first two matches and
then they do the finals
it's grew up big time then we good this
is that the code okay
we get a code
yeah that's your code okay I gotta hide
okay I hide yes hide code Lobby search
I searched the lobby
I'm in the lobby
oh I think it said something like we are
supposed to be
uh
uh like a top
or a bottle like there's a specific
order they want us to be in oh really
yeah it was in the in the like
explanation thingy but now that the
order is changed I'm confused too but
maybe we're in the right spot because I
think it said for the first one and Ian
down for the second one
let's go with that yeah
remember okay no panicking allowed okay
no panicking play it safe play cool call
for Cali as usual yeah okay wait so are
we gonna go for top objective first or
bottom or are we not gonna decide to be
aggressive I think
um should we decide on that beforehand
yeah it might be situational depending
on where the others are okay
um I should be high enough level at a
certain point where I can kind of guard
the bottom and then also take out the
bottom objective by myself if I do the
jungle correctly
it will be good
stay out of my jungle please
if they start to stop us and they get
our first our first uh
goal down and then they also get an
objective we can try to go and steal
their Farm in the jungle okay in the
wilderness await your command apparently
um JP team struggles against aggressive
players so we really need to play
aggressive okay
so nervous okay we can scroll to the
screen now right yep yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah aggressive but safe
it'll be fun it'll be fine I wonder how
our team comp is I wonder if it's
just like we're playing against the Bots
yeah so that we can also hear fauna
clearly when she wants something from
her okay
I know Dragon Claw is the meta but I'm
going with earthquake so that I can take
out the bigger Farms of swablu and
alteria so and also attack from a bit
more of a distance
who's going who's going Bottom with me
I'm going Bottom okay
better than their Glacier
we got this no problem here we go have
confidence
let's go just like practice just like we
practiced just slap oh God my hands are
so sweaty already
pop this really quick we'll use it again
later
oh gosh darn it oh see they're here ah
they are here we're still here
I am useless until level five well we'll
just poke a little bit okay let's go and
get this they're scared they're scared
they're playing safe playing safe I want
to go to the middle
don't let them steal it don't let them
steal it
um okay
who needs more help bottom or top
oh my God we're doing okay we're doing
fine right now but we're having really
fun I need to commit
um
their middle person oh okay go for the
middle
yes nice nice nice kill KO oh no oh no
yeah yeah
this thing traps you damn okay yeah all
right
quickly life steal
nice Kelly okay nice nice
stand a little garden take it down here
yeah let's go
score
okay
I need to level up the scissor dude's
almost dead though oh damn it okay I'm
lagging pretty bad no oh shoot okay hold
on
no one's dead right now right okay I'm
lagging I'm gonna go grab Center HP yeah
go ahead we can be able to get some life
steal as well yeah I'm gonna pop this
really quick okay the objectives are up
in 40 seconds uh no no she's up here
okay oh yeah okay okay should we should
we I got a decent amount okay they're
back they're back should I join down
there
[Music]
I'm with you
along with me
all right don't worry we got it
completely like stuck on this I think
it's my internet
oh you're stuck oh no oh they're Umbreon
here
moving okay again I'm safe I'm safe okay
[Music]
I just need to level up a little bit
should we go top should we wait wait
here don't attack yet
I think we should try to steal it
seven okay let's try steal it okay
earthquake you guys can go top you guys
can go for it okay good okay okay just
try another kind of like distract them
don't they don't die don't die um
let's go nice nice nice all right okay
good job
team let's go
okay let's not play too impressive okay
yeah I mean I'm back play safe places go
back if you have to
go back oh oops
all right that's fine
I know me too my heart's thumping if I
had my Harley monitor now I'd be dying
right now uh there's nothing okay
missing can score maybe I kind of want
to grab Center form again hold on oh
actually yeah
you think they're gonna steal it they
might but we could grab it we could grab
it we should actually leave because
daddy we got it nice you got it nice
nice yeah we have to protect it uh
they're all right I'm coming I'm coming
let's go top
we're coming
it's okay oh no problem all day yummy
where's Umbreon
it's fine it's fine don't worry don't
worry
I can't really fight um
it's okay just uh be the bouncy person
okay
I'm gonna back up
yeah ideally we don't want to fight on
there
there yeah if we can I'm trying to get
out but I'm lagging oh no I'm sorry it's
okay we'll be fine
oh God I can't I can't get out of here
all right I'm coming I'm coming
oh they're scissors real quick hold on I
can't do anything hold on okay
nice oh no I'm so sorry oh did one die
right now no no don't be sorry sorry
they also died too we're good
I will be back
okay let me get over here and help
nice actually
hold on let me grab a buffer bottom
glaze down scoring bottom okay hold on
um I think I'm about to go bottom should
we I think we actually want to grow
bottom I'm going anyway
I have really sound is pretty darn scary
oh God okay bye
I think I think we need to farm a little
I think we're focusing too much on
trying to fight them okay uh he's a bad
girl no they're they're trying to kill
me
but I can hold it I can hold her off
yeah you can try to hold bottom yeah
wait what level are we is everyone
higher than us no they're Nine and Nine
yeah
oh [\h__\h] okay I got surprised
if I snuggle behind me
okay okay nice nice
I'm gonna go back to bottom
is good
I don't know who's who who's winning I
know who I know dude I can't pop a speed
right now okay go back let's go bottom
other oh they just got they just got
ready guys okay let me ah they still
won't be done okay hold on a sec no
worries we're coming
[Music]
I should have known they were down there
I was not paying attention to the map
thanks guys I will be there in a second
oh I need to be a higher level this is
not how I should be okay no worries okay
[Music]
oh
shoot they're totally awesome then okay
okay hold on
I'm not high enough level yet yeah we
should be careful about team fights I
think I think we need to yeah
we should oh God okay get ready we
should defend I think okay should I go
down or up I'm just gonna get it buff
really quick okay we are going up yeah
but we might need it we probably need to
paint
already
the time this is going so fast stay safe
let's go let's go
dang it I don't think I'm close 100.
okay I have something to score uh we
should defend if we can too okay oh
they're they're totally yeah
why am I scoring here I don't know
it works no it doesn't work
I'm gonna stay right here
I know where did they come from
[Music]
okay
oh no there's like three of them oh God
I'm dead I'm dead I'm dead oh damn it
I don't know we just have to stop them
from uh depositing points and we can
still put in it might be even right now
um
it's true I'll defend I'll stay and
defend if you guys go okay I have no
points I don't know if that's enough to
go over I was willing to risk it for a
biscuit what the hell got me at least
hey I distracted them I destroyed where
are they right now I think I'm out of
this game so are they at the bottom no
they were all the way to the right at
their home bases
you probably can't
can I they're probably in defense yeah
[Music]
they know what they want it already yeah
that's rough
it was fun
I think we did well okay we had a
handicap because I was not handicap but
uh I uh was lagging really really really
bad yeah
it's not
that bad next match
we'll get them next time we'll get ID
good job good job
I'm proud of you guys I thought that was
pretty good yeah if we got the recoils
yeah I knew it's closed it was close I
think I need to farm more on that
yeah they hit before minded so
it's kind of rough but yeah anyway
let's try yeah maybe check chat for one
second yeah I I needed far more I'm let
me just going to accept my presents
right now Ambush
um
so we're leaving the lobby right
are we playing again immediately there
we go immediately we're warmed up we're
warmed up it's true but my hands are
shanky I know this is my controllers
controllers
I'm sorry oh is there already a room is
there a room
oh no not yet right okay we're gonna
start another one
what about now Chad
I thought it was just super quiet chat
[Music]
okay wait do we still have a chance okay
yeah okay
yeah we do we do we're only behind 200
points as long as we'll see how ideas uh
against him but they saw us by
oh
I know they know our cards
it's true they watched that is true they
have that
okay
then damn it all right I think I know
and I thought we'd be in that position
this next one yeah
yeah I think in that one team fights
were our weakness because we weren't
arriving all at the same time yeah gotta
make sure not to start and I was doing
this not at the beginning before
everyone arrived oh whoops I'm sorry
wait hold on is this the wrong okay
oh they went into the wrong one
um yeah I will try and help if I can but
I really need to try to focus more on
farming otherwise yeah you're a late
game on so you can focus on farms and we
can just try in the try to defend
yourself I'll try to help if I can
though yeah yeah
since you're looking at the time a lot
um oh yeah we just need to remember so
seven minutes for subjective unlocks and
then a two minutes Rayquaza so around
like 30 seconds or a minute before that
we got to be prepared yeah like at three
hours three Thirty don't use your old I
think
when there's yeah 3 30 left okay yeah
when 3 30 is left
how do I move my position wait
I'll be here are we supposed to be
bottom this time I think so they were
all on top so
it seems like it but I don't know
[Music]
we missing fauna right here oh yeah
okay
um
yeah I I get so tunnel visioned and I
don't really get what was like after I
get to a certain level I'm just like
what should I do now yeah yeah this is
May with the team yeah
group up
I have to also focus on leveling in the
beginning because Evie is weak as hell
in the beginning and yeah I have to wait
until I get to like at least level six
or seven to get ice shard
yeah I think it too
we were focusing a lot on fighting them
when we probably should have just been
staying back and foreign yeah
[Music]
yeah
we can try that too okay okay okay
[Music]
maybe she was only using it for that
stream I don't know but
they were going with like a pretty
pretty
meta-ish I think I forgot
I have got your back yeah show this show
the screen I forgot about that okay okay
I'm glad you're back so cute I'm going
to focus on being the strongest
good buff buff
whoa
good work no laughing No I gave up on
Lapras
[Music]
anyways I think Lapras is too too weak
for this
comp
and also also because Lapras did not
have much outfits yes
I really don't like Zoroark
oh yeah oh yeah the dog I think she's
juggler yeah I think she is oh God we're
gonna have such a bad time
confidence up
okay all right all right let's just do
it
all right I'm gonna be the strongest
right now
seven minutes and three minutes beware
all right yes
three minutes what happens with three
minutes
to be ready okay what 3 30. don't use
your own how long does it take for the
ultimate it depends on the character I
think yeah it depends but how many
you'll be safe if you wait 3 30.
[Music]
no arranged ah dang it
I want to get that form
steal it
okay guys stole it nice
scared
we'll be fine I'm going back to you
oh okay
they're being very aggressive yeah they
are
[Music]
okay
okay I'll come down to grab
wow you guys got the farmer what do we
do
um
here comes the Cali nice
run run run
oh
okay I got my Irish trade I'm good now
it's so strong
it's okay it's okay we're doing we're
doing okay in the middle so yeah and
just try to play don't die I'm coming up
top
actually gone bottom okay
speed up I need to keep farming actually
I need to focus on being the strongest
I'm gonna go for Middle Farm
yeah
I think they're all going for top is it
just me I think I feel like
Iris do you think you can hold your own
down here
I could I could I'll try I'll try you
can you can go up I'll I'll try to just
hold them back
scary
Kyle and bought
run go down don't fight right now come
come
oh that was close that was close yeah
nice you got the we got the birds
um I was gonna help them but never mind
oh it's okay
lagging again oh no oh gosh okay and
yeah
I can solo this
okay I wonder if I should break it
[Music]
should we go down here they're all here
all of them okay oh nice we should go
okay they're gonna they're gonna take it
maybe we should leave one person bottom
I'll stay back
okay yeah and I'll try and farm at the
same time
um but we'll have extra Farm after this
oh God I died
I shouldn't have sandwiches
yeah they're really coordinated
we still have the Rayquaza Center Farm a
few more minutes left till Rayquaza and
we can take it yeah make sure to farm
the Pokemon in this Lane in the Top Lane
there will be bonus mons of uh spawn oh
because they didn't give a good thumbs
yeah okay oh they're getting their Farm
they're getting out up here
wait what um
yeah they're on the top Lane I'm also
top but all of them yeah they're all in
Top Lane it's scary
okay I think I saw at least three of
them on top we can group up let's group
up yeah okay
um where should we go should we go just
keep on top I guess let's stay on top we
should we should Farm yeah probably I'm
gonna Farm it's done here they're gonna
come in and try to kill like anyone
okay
should we go oh
oh no they're they're trying to kill me
they're oh they killed me
this is scary
how are their levels doing right now
all right let me see uh I'm still a
level above Renee I'm gonna go bottom
I think we should all just group up in
bottom right now
let me know if you need me somewhere I'm
farming come down with us okay yeah
that's fine um
I think it's fine okay uh we should
probably go top okay
I'll wait oh wait they're all down in
the bottom Lane
do we want to go aggressively for once
maybe
last week
last week here comes the slow bro here
they come
oh oh no
are you kidding me I love being useless
to my team all right Rayquaza Rayquaza
yeah I'm dead no it's because of the leg
let it be known let it be known that was
because the [\h__\h] lag
cool all right well let's just dance and
see if we can make it count okay okay
yeah
oh my God I didn't die everyone should
be saving all their stuff so we can try
to win I'm saving us I'm gonna I'm just
getting some help oh okay um
oh we're really struggling yeah really
struggling actually hold on
oh here comes
okay
yep wait
yep
um all right just get ready for Rayquaza
okay yeah yeah I still have my ALT
thankfully
we do have a lot of points we could put
in okay you might need someone to stay
and defend I'm not sure
I don't know I feel like all of us can
just go requests yeah I think they're
all gonna go I think they're all gonna
go Rayquaza oh they're probably getting
the bottom objective I can't get that in
time
they're definitely down there oh
no they're here
I mean get get them get them get them
okay all right nice place we're not
there okay
okay don't lose all your HP to the
Rayquaza yeah okay because they're gonna
show up really soon
[Music]
oh
stop your Olds if you have them yes
[Applause]
do your best try to score
I'm so sorry they're so strong lagging
so bad oh God they killed me
here I got I'm gonna pick up the points
yeah yeah
thank you I need help Callie okay
oh they're all guard they're guarding
the middle they're all guarding the
middle maybe
is empty the topper the one and I'm done
okay hello fantastic awesome I'm coming
to the top keep it up
because I'm lagging yeah
if they don't score then we win okay I'm
going back yeah just just yes really
we're in the lead uh
we have two pads depends to defend at
all costs
um I'm staying in the middle pass
I need help on this pad I need help
bottom is the bottom just don't let them
score
all right come in
[Music]
now
leave
there's no way there's no way nice yeah
oh okay
let's see let's see no nah there's no
way did we I don't believe we didn't get
to turn in because did we actually I
didn't wasn't able to get it oh my God
yeah
[Applause]
[Laughter]
so I was
let's go
that you can live longer yeah everybody
I hope and debate I'm so glad you guys
thank you everyone for teaching us so
much
wait really and the doll yeah yeah is it
for every match I think it's for every
match right for every NBC yeah let's go
Emoji I'm so happy I'm proud of you guys
I think we did really well in the first
one yeah
yeah it was really close do you guys
know if they sell this shirt or not they
don't say no
um
sorry
if we maybe got in second place
hopefully we'll see after the next match
if they tally up all the points we'll
see how does that work so like if and
deserve that if
if ID loses somewhere first I don't get
away how does it work does it get less
than like 300 points which is unlikely
unless JP is
we'll see
okay
though some of the points oh
I want to spectate are we able to do
that
yeah I'm gonna set up once fana makes
the room we just join us spectators
on me
too much excitement
[Music]
but we did good nice job yeah we want a
man yeah I'm proud of I know we did so
well
yeah our practice is paid off oh and
this year I'm glad that we practiced a
lot yeah I'm glad I grinded like like 10
11 hours yesterday
I worked hard
thanks for helping us learn the game
yeah
yeah I hope I wouldn't have been able to
do it without you
it's for playing
also thanks for the the tips uh chat as
well to improve my jungle game I feel
like that second that second game was
much better
yeah
yeah cool good being strong middling
game let's go Ian strong man um
yeah yeah she is scary she just comes
out of nowhere and then bam bam bam bam
so scary can we get a run back with JP
now can we try it again
uh I know Kiowa you you want to sleep no
it's not because of that I'm not even
tired even though I've been awake since
I don't know what's adrenaline huh
foreign
[Music]
no matter what happens we've already
done so
[Music]
um
yeah I'm really curious to see how these
aggressive teams play against each other
so for us to get first place if it were
to happen
um then
what wait wait so if JP wins then we def
then JP definitely gets first place
right I think so if ID wins then there
might be a chance depending on point
difference and they could get like 800
points yeah I don't know it could be a
close match with these two teams
[Music]
I don't know if we'll amount to uh Mike
at third place because of our yeah it
was pretty close third place oh maybe
yeah oh it is
we still we still
we fought we won at least
yeah in the JP match was closed it was
pretty close we just kind of slipped up
at the end and yeah I should have been
stronger
the pain was holding me back it was the
bank
yeah
hey the lag really got me the last match
okay we're starting
oh we're starting okay okay I'm starting
okay I wonder how spectator looks yeah
do we get to fly around probably ah wait
I need to show that'd be kind of cool I
think that you I think that you can
almost I think we get to just fly around
the camera did you guys know that like
on the edges
edges of the what you may call it the
the map there's like this Magnemite
holding a camera yeah it's so cute I
noticed it yesterday it was adorable
cameraman
thank you
so who do you guys who are you betting
on
um
if he was not very aggressive so ID
might have it yeah Ida was very
aggressive yeah
we will see though
because they're both pretty strong
[Music]
it will be exciting I know I can't focus
though my adrenaline's too high
you need to chill
chat who do you want me to to focus on I
can follow someone specific
I want to see how she jungles actually
good question I mean yeah yeah
Kyla was was Middle Lane right yeah okay
because JP got a break between maybe
they've you know recovered
yeah true
so cute
the baby baby no they're so cute yeah
so efficient I didn't know the flower
was like a starfish looking thing in the
beginning
a starfish it looks like a starfish you
know the red right you're right starfish
with the flower or like a star fruit
yeah yeah
they seem so determined I know oh my God
I hope anyways they're really going at
it I love it go for it you can do it
yeah they're they're playing
aggressively
well yeah
the most important how is the level
going oh okay Kyle was fine there is
higher level than Kyla right now oh
yeah oh man better go to senpai's real
focus and they're gonna take it down
maybe it was ready for that yeah
the JP is using the grass a lot they're
like hiding in the grass
did push pretty hard to get in there
though okay
she's back in the rotation to get the
Buffs again
[Music]
right now okay
um
[Music]
they're strong
Anya is chilling Anya no yeah
come back there
two versus three on the top four
okay okay
and they got one ah it's still kind of
Tom
it comes out yeah let's see what they do
first yeah
resolved prioritizing oh Kyla's low
again
they did push them back
out of there we can see the point
difference it's it's interesting yeah
they don't show the point difference
when you're actually playing yeah they
don't they know I'm glad they didn't
honestly I think I would have choked
it's really hard
maybe going oh yeah I think he's going
for regular oh they're going for the top
yeah
almost down take whatever treats oh oh
I think they got it
yeah
I feel like we had JP put in most of the
work but
let's go about the final hit
though
this is exciting I like spectating I
know
I wish I could zoom out
um
it's dangerous cool but there's three
there's three enemies
oh what's going on here
I know right that's so weird it seems
like JP is winning but no idea is
winning oh yeah he's been picking them
off getting some kills yeah they've been
able to get lost
oh no okay
JP got that oh Reggie ice oh gosh that
was a good move
foreign
[Music]
yes
and they got Ollie
I feel like they would be very good
communicators the ID girl so they're
gonna just yeah true with their
Minecraft servers
y everybody is the top is we got it they
got it uh-oh that's gonna be um they
really need help up there ID here I
think everyone ID needs to be up there
because
[Applause]
oh no yeah Last Hope is Rayquaza I would
say so
the point difference
not too big still yeah the Rayquaza can
still turn it around but us being third
place has probably already set in stone
yeah
in second place
is it by points or is it by games one
I think everybody means one if there's
not a tie okay okay I think I think yeah
if I mean if JP wins this then I think
my points we'd be okay
if they get Rayquaza what is what I mean
as well
I was waiting
oh they got it
[Music]
one minute
yeah we'll see how Rayquaza goes
that's the main site yeah we're all
cheering for ID for a lot of reasons
I see how coordinated JP is I'm feeling
like proud that we yeah I know we hold
it together pretty good against them to
be honest yeah I feel like I died too
much
it was close if only I didn't die that
much I'm just like ah if we had gone
dang it uh I should have aimed my old
better
I'm proud of us I still think we did
well yeah
last minute our grind was I think we did
pretty good yeah
[Music]
funny it's only in our practices our
enemies weren't so good so so I know
a lot of them kids
you know oh no
they're really they're really going for
Reggie Reggie like you when Rayquaza's
gonna yeah they are respond really soon
interesting yeah yeah that's interesting
yeah
here comes everyone oh who's gonna get
it
oh oh they took they took videos in
Japan the other three they're three
other three oh okay
which one
[Music]
[Laughter]
I think they'll get it oh they have a
lot let's go oh yeah they're done
oh wait there's a hundred points up up
top Pickers oh yeah 400 points she is
gonna be so close
so close
yeah Kyla's only one guarding I think
and everyone else is going offensive
oh my God what is the right answer for
this one
be careful I don't know
ID defend Maybe
well yeah they are doing what the points
are yeah
yeah no idea
thank you I'm so excited
yeah good looking Brandon
yo yo oh my gosh they're so strong
he's carrying 50 points
they got the points in yeah
fubiki's gonna try and score these
points
[Music]
yeah let's go
it's like clothes for everyone that was
amazing oh wait so everybody won one
match yeah yeah now it's all according
to points
well guys we did our best yeah I'm proud
of us yeah me too we did well
I mean look at how scary and chaotic and
crazy that battle was that was pretty
insane
going up against these girls is quite a
challenge
that was huge
um
Japanese signs
and all pick one and only were the MVPs
yeah olly was MVP
everybody did well
I am I'm proud of everyone I'm proud
yeah everyone knew what to do pretty
much yeah there was nobody that was like
fumbling around like I didn't practice
you know yeah
you can confirm I did practice a lot
that was fun that was really fun it was
fun that was really fun yeah I think I
might try to play more this season to
hopefully get to ultra
actually this was I feel like we've
gotten closer you know yeah yeah it's
it's really like it feels like sports
like team camaraderie yeah I wanted to
play games together too like I don't
know yeah yeah
fun collab game I think it's a good
satsu game too yeah in general yeah once
you know what to do you just yeah if
you're not too sweatya
I think we joined the main Channel
we must capture the slides again
yes awesome excited for that
it will go well yeah we fine I just need
to
pair
yeah for the chat asking we don't know
the final tally yet we don't know yet we
do not know you know you guys probably
know it's fine but don't tell us don't
tell us we don't want to know we want to
stay oblivious
no mask yeah if you can do math you're
banned
he's smarter than a fifth grade a first
grader
at least being the top three
I think so
we're on the podium
a gold star for trying
like the Olympic bronze medal is
something very something very proud
an honor it's just like that right yeah
yeah it's as big of an honor as that
I'm proud that we won a game I saw so
many people saying we were not gonna
make it yeah
you're gonna walk all over us yes
we've been training we've been working
but I was ready to be the most beautiful
carpets there to be no no wrong and
orange carpet we're not rainbow you have
to be a flying carpet yeah it's supposed
to be a flying one where am I flying to
Flying to Victory
hahaha
lines of the other team's pad
for a dunk and the dog prevails
well chat did you guys enjoy watching
that did you know what was going on all
the time maybe it was at least fun to
watch yeah I never knew this could be so
sweaty like these kind of games yeah
yeah yeah yeah whenever I saw in games
like this like you know and I see like
tournaments going on and whatnot I look
at it and I always like oh they're just
spamming skills
it's just like an MMORPG I was like oh
that was fun but I don't why is this so
competitive now I get it yeah
when we like joined this in kikaku I
don't think we any of us expected it to
be dead serious I did yeah I didn't know
I thought it would be more it would just
be a fun
just a fun one Pokemon
friendly friendly competition
but I'm really depressed because I think
we trained enough to make it like
interesting matches yeah yeah
um
it wasn't too one-sided in any of the
matches I mean yeah the thing is like a
lot of Japanese and ID members were
already like really well practiced in
this game right I've seen a lot of
master
um ranks
so you know yeah we just started playing
a lot of us just started playing it yeah
like four days
yeah yeah but we put in the work and it
feels good at least playing in my dreams
like last week
pretty late last night yeah yeah did you
win in your dream or did you lose uh
well I was just like attacking stuff in
my dream but then when I was trying to
fall asleep I was like running around in
the game and I kept running into the
walls and it was really frustrating
nightmares
oh yeah
I can chased a lot in my nightmares just
like here in Pokemon United
so it was a nightmare no no not at all
I wish
while we're waiting
yeah it'd be kind of fun rematch rematch
I don't know I'm kind of scared to
rematch I kind of want to leave it have
you used all your power let us have it I
know yeah yeah I'm happy with the way
we've performed yeah
[Music]
it's so much more fun to like play with
like friends and like VC than one year
it was so frustrating yesterday when I
was like yeah you know queuing by myself
and then like yeah the random would like
you know leave me in the in in the area
alone and I'm just like why and
everyone's at the top in the beginning
I'm like what the why do you do that I'm
like that's how I'm Central okay I'm
Central I'm jungle and then I wait like
five seconds and then right before the
match starts somebody else says I'm
jungle and I'm like are you kidding me I
might as well not even do it
yeah I also had troubles playing alone
soloing Reggie leki so many times why I
was like why don't you girls wanna go up
there and get that objective why not
[Music]
feels bad man
feels bad but this feels good man yeah
I'm like playing with the five stack yum
yeah that's good I'm still I still don't
know if the held items I chose was the
correct answer though I didn't go with
like the most standard build I went with
I chose something else for the because I
wanted to make myself less squishy but I
was still very good I was still really
squishy so I'm just like maybe I should
have gone all offensive I don't know oh
they're going up now yeah I think it's
time okay the final result the results
we gotta go check the window let's go I
gotta set up the window though so hold
on
come up here
[Music]
wait a sec so so much
one moment and gotta set up the slides
fine slime slime
[Music]
hold on hold on hold on guys excuse me
I got it I got it I got it I got it too
I got it size wise it looks a little
while
it wasn't supposed to play this I'm
sorry I'm sorry how do I turn it off
oh my gosh sorry
wait every time
thank you for your good bottle Arigato
yay
[Music]
it was amazing
are you ready for it
let's go
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you eat it is
yeah
[Applause]
good job everyone
as a leader in leader please say you're
sold
I'm really proud of everyone many people
doubted the ENT but I hope that we
showed him we showed our abilities today
I think we did I'm proud of everybody
thank you for your team it was really
amazing amazing match yeah
as a leader only time please say
yourself
[Music]
where's already aggressive and we never
never give up right so
um
we can see a really good teamwork
communication thank you so much
[Music]
thank you so much
I'm really glad you enjoyed this much
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
[Applause]
maybe I'll eat them
thank you and not only this so um
in the JP lesion and the VP is
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
um
yeah
congratulations
great leader you go to MVP in the first
match and you're really supportive
everybody
[Music]
yeah you go to MVP and you contribute to
the uh comeback come back big street
right yeah
[Laughter]
thank you for your hard work thank you
so much
[Music]
thank you
oh shoot
oh so we on the stream now or something
last video that we showed the last video
just give me a second hold on
because when we like the slide thing
almost like you played it can I play it
one more slide we need to show one more
slide
one more slides really oh okay okay okay
okay
let me pull up the slide
time hold on oh is it slides it's not
not the video
slide and then videos
[Music]
if this one was so exciting imagine how
exciting the actual one will be true I
know right
you can also do predictions right now
it's true you can do predictions in the
in the game if you get predictions right
you get prizes yeah
I have personally that the team uh Peru
is absolutely cracked really really yes
oh no no I don't know
an orangutan because I like the things
you I predicted also on orangutan let's
go
let's go let's go
wait is there European oh yeah there are
European teams I should probably cheer
for them
go Europe go Europe let's go America let
me let me remind everybody that the
Pokemon unite category of WCS will
happen tomorrow
and here is a slide of all the
participating team members uh the
Pokemon tonight category will be
streamed on the channel listed in the
description tomorrow 9pm November 11th
jst
tomorrow and of course you can predict
in the game we're just talking about
something for it right you will win
prizes if you guessed correctly so
please check it out please watch the
stream and cheer for your favorite team
and we'll see you all tomorrow yeah yeah
I think that wraps everything up I'm
really proud of you guys I think we did
really well yeah
considering considering like you know
how much we didn't really know yeah much
in the beginning
yeah that's why yeah VP really it makes
a lot of sense
thank you I want everyone to get MVP
though
[Music]
yes I think I'm really proud of us
genuinely we might have got third but
they were close matches they were good
matches I wasn't a huge Point Gap it was
yeah it was pretty close so I feel good
about it
with Matt shall we play the ending PV I
guess we should okay
then jump away yeah sure thank you
everyone for watching thank you thank
you very much thank you so much for the
support it was really fun yeah we're not
where are we are we muting during the
video I don't know
okay okay
right
all right we're good okay I'm ready okay
three two one go Pokemon unite recently
celebrated its second anniversary allow
us to introduce congratulations yeah
that's oh this map
yeah this looks fun oh cool I didn't
even try that yet I wonder if it'll be
just as sweaty
the extra strong Mewtwo
the two strong is not allowed strong
Mewtwo
via an event happening now and starting
August 17th you'll also you could get
your Mewtwo today
um
I didn't know Mewtwo why Mewtwo was this
like tiny
World Championship
unless you get all your predictions
wrong
anticipating in this
mixed into the real teams
to get popular holaware for Pokemon like
stylish
I love the pirate outfits
cute
yay
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah thanks so much for everything you
guys that was fun yeah that was fun
for inviting us for this thank you very
much a lot of fun yeah I'm really glad I
was able to take part in this and
experience
this type of game yeah yeah fun training
with everyone I'm glad we were able to
train in the morning
[Music]
he's so tired
well I believe that's all we have for
today we can let everybody get some rest
yeah we tried our hardest
thank you thank you thank you very much
thank you thank you okay
thank you very much thank you for
cheering us on yes thank you for taking
us thank you for believing and nothing
thanks thanks
have a great day
bye
[Music]
foreign