[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
is that double
what's that is it
okay it should be fine now Nicki
[Music]
I have a racing helmet oh my God wait
wait wait there's still not everything
okay
I thought I had it
and there you are there you are welcome
to the stream Yokoso
hey
how you guys doing
cool helmet why thank you
oh wait
I haven't captured my switch in a while
for a stream I feel like I'm so confused
okay okay now there may have been double
for a moment
I know
but now
should be the right way to do it the
right setting hey I haven't put my
glasses on behind that so that if I look
straight you can see like you know
shininess on my glasses you could think
that that's part of the helmet
[Music]
oh is this mask baby I could also be a
a wrestler
could also be my wrestling helmet mask
but no it's a helmet here knock knock
yeah that's uh I don't know you probably
don't hear that but
still looking gray what looks gray what
what are you talking about
oh
hey I have like a a different helmet too
but I thought this one's maybe the
cutest
yeah I was like right before the stream
I was like no wouldn't it be nice uh
like funny nice fitting if blue made me
a helmet but there's no way that blue
made me a helmet on such short notice
without me asking and then I go Justin
just in case I go on my KF props hashtag
on Twitter and I saw
okay not great
and I saw blue has delivered without me
asking for it
and different variations even it looks
good it looks cute
[Music]
yeah so
f099 the game that
I maybe maybe made a little bit fun
about in the Nintendo Direct because I
think
people were expecting and I don't really
care much about this like original game
but I expected it too therefore that
like a new game would come out and then
they just showed this and it wasn't so
impressive and like in the beginning
because like you know
yeah but then turns out it's actually
pretty fun
right it's actually pretty fun
foreign
and we can play together and you know
it's pretty decent pretty decent how the
do I close this this is so annoying
I hear oh yeah
and a new week has begun
I wish I'll kick this week off with a
racing game we also need to play Mario
Karts in the near future though I'm uh I
I want to play Mario Kart in the new
near future
I'm not done with the tutorial yet
though guys I'm so sorry
I took a nap
it's so comfortable it was such a
comfortable nap I need to do the f050
okay
[Music]
completely slap above the safe rank
yeah I'm just gonna go with the pink one
I I haven't finished the tutorial but I
watched
um someone playing this for like two or
three hours already
this game feels like fever night yeah
yeah
yeah yeah so so someone no not Kelly
not Cali
nope nope nope
okay also the first time I'm playing on
the Pro Controller now uh try to finish
in the top 35 I'll try I finished first
in the
um
[Music]
go away
in in the in the in the 25
but it was difficult I crashed out I
several times that I'm so bad also it's
so difficult how do you why is
acceleration not on a and then boots
that'll be like the other way around why
is it like this
and why is my chat flashing on the right
side of my screen hereby
oh what is this what is this Blue Area
how ow yeah I shouldn't be doing that
gotta risk some things in life you know
and these are oh my God now a long time
long time still CPUs I think so ow I'm
so stupid we're gonna die
[Music]
am I the only one who thinks it's really
difficult to have the buttons set like
that I think they should be the other
way around
I can't crash ah
okay okay
thank God okay
I like the controls this stuff came game
to learn about it yeah even good people
apparently keep on crashing I better not
use my Boost because I keep on crashing
oh my God why I'm so wobbly
I'm so wobbly oh
okay yeah let me get rid of my speed
which will
okay
don't read chat while driving I'm not a
very safe driver am I okay let's go
get it yeah
yeah
yeah okay well I just can't get any
closer to number one than this it seems
my nose is itching
but no ditching my nose bitching
my nose itching
Hannah
wow
oh so many explosions
oh my my my super mega uh oh no oh no
yeah oh no oh
[Music]
tutorial
foreign
[Music]
can I change it can I change the
controls in this game
don't feel bad thank you
no you can Nintendo says no Nintendo
Nintendo
oh
[Music]
I know what number one wow
you're kind of not anymore it was a good
time being number one for a little while
oh wait that was a decent way of passing
the Curve
it's okay it's okay I don't need to be
number one okay this game is rough like
getting number one
it's difficult okay even more so when
you're not playing against CPS
laughs
I certainly was number one twice already
oh God oh God oh God oh God okay let's
be careful let's not use the rest of my
booze because I need it but I can load
up
right there yeah Nintendo never lets you
change right the button routing whatever
you know
[Music]
[Laughter]
when these Tunes are really awesome but
it's so hard to sing along to them
they're not made to be sung a lot too
okay oh
hey hey did you see that I know how to
do that yeah
I said karma
um can we just do three labs done four
laps I can't survive four laps three
laps okay
[Music]
why is my right like the windows I have
on my ride screen the chat and OBS are
flashing but not the screen itself
[Music]
is there like you guys know what this is
it's it's been like this sometimes for a
while now
like I have it several times maybe
change something more durable yeah maybe
nice mess thank you to have it racing
helmet
is it because it hurts
[Music]
hey but not the whole screen is flashing
just a certain
Windows on it interesting oh man they're
dropping so many balls
oh hey yeah sorry I was kind of far
behind because I was checking the chat
now back to where I belong in the top
10. let's go hi
off
[Music]
I'm more careful now not using my
booster much because uh it's kind of
busy up here wait
okay now I can use it let's go
oh
wow wow wow wow
the aspect that there's no items like in
Mario Kart in this game
certainly takes away some difficulty but
also adds
some difficulty because there's not much
you can do to like cheat your way to the
top number one
okay is is focus now
now whatever
big lead now yeah cause I was uh
collecting all those balls in the back
huh this is the aquilas Empire strategy
from Mario Kart stay in the back
be a hack
I don't know what that means
more skill in RNG yeah yeah there's like
like
in order to go from like stay at the top
you
you need to show skill not just items in
order to get to the top you can't just
like get yourself like a bullet
uh thingy item
and then go
pass everybody no no no
oh
[Music]
that's the very end yeah okay my last
try will be 99.
f 0.99
the names platstar that's a German way
of saying move get out of the way
oh
I think you can stay with this one I'll
get used to it
um
oh what is this I see a couple people
coming into the stream asking what this
is have you not heard of f099 it's free
to download if you have a Nintendo
online subscription
then you can download it and play for
free free and it's online I mean right
now in the tutorial I'm still against
CPUs but
yeah
Stingray is not easy for new players
really monster
uh you'll not be racing as rival Pilots
but they're all CPUs anyway right
yeah and I know about rivals
I don't know about them that's why I put
them in the inside captain
oh my god oh number one Wawa let's go
let's go oh oh some people would you go
right left there huh
oh this looks the same like
like the other map so far
yeah but who cares about Captain Falcon
when I'm here go away
right I yeah this is the the first map
that they teach you okay
easy
[Music]
one or this one I like I think get away
from me
this one I like more it's easier I think
than the other map that I just did
out out stupid oh off
okay
[Music]
that sounded awesome what what was it
what was it
oh
can we get back to our spot at number
one I'm happy with anything really that
is above 50 but you know
no no
no no no
styling oh I should be careful now okay
[Music]
okay charging time
okay
yeah
charge that baby back up
what I don't really use is the LR I
tried but my grip is already so weird
do you guys also hold it like really
weirdly for this game like my thumb
is on B
and my
index finger is like hovering above
uh like a like a cancer almost like a
cancer like a crab
above my oh hey not bad yeah like kind
of put like a claw but not Quan
yeah above the a
um
use it like that
what Controller Pro Controller
[Music]
it's nice yeah my thumb is Bob yeah I
feel like because
I feel like I need two fingers because
also my thumb is small
maybe I'll try though but we finished
the tutorial I think
hey
but because my Linux finger is on the a
I can't use the LR
collect enough take a buns and you can
earn tickets which allow you to enter
Grand Prix Grand Prix and mini cream
yay time for you guys to join yeah there
is no code like in Mario Kart no no
you just try to join and apparently from
what I heard it's not so difficult with
Cali
um people were having a good time
joining
uh
it's so flashy let me move at least
like one window over here
oh I think it stopped flashing nice
and come with you now ready to race
online new tracks and race modes are
also available
wow the Grand Prix oh no it's so
flashing oh my God that's so annoying
let me let me move everything on the
left side
for sure my left monitor is not flashing
so I'll just put it there
is
a flashing a checkered pattern no it's
like turns white I think
for like a millisecond
or black or both
[Music]
I didn't change anything no that's so
weird mama
[Music]
[Laughter]
you get a show
mama my middle monitor is not flashing
so it's okay
I keep my hands like that for Shooters
actually oh really
I wish they would just make a new FTR
game so that's what people are thinking
so it was like yeah a bit like
disappointment but now people really
love this game apparently so
yeah yeah yeah I guess we'll just you
know there's a special event in a few
seconds but I'm not ready for that and a
complete in half an hour we can try that
too
I wonder if the
like complete
now nothing's original like everything's
mixed giant everything's mixed
I'll do Stingray again and then we'll
like experiment maybe a little bit with
the machines
[Music]
okay
Revival
it's a coincidence oh my God motion you
little
be careful what you do
you better land behind me or else
don't you do anything funny on me oh
wait I don't what the I don't know
this
is
I don't know this one I don't I don't
know it I guess everybody turns I guess
I'll turn to
[Music]
okay
oh thanks for the balls holy
maybe I'm too scared to boost like
there's so many people well okay now
I'll post
okay
ouch ouch
emotion I see motion
I'm gonna die oh
I wish that gave me like oh there we go
oh my God
okay I will not boost anymore I need all
of that oh motion is right above me what
the
how the are you doing that
how
much staying right like around me on
purpose or what
I'm just gonna be slow
as long as I don't die wait wait I can
uh I forgot
oh yeah but sometimes you wanna you know
find the right timing for the super
boost because you know there's like
difficult posages
that might be in
more
preferable to skip
come on oh
stay behind me you little
[Music]
dude okay that was okay that was decent
okay go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go go
oh oh
that's dangerous oh that's
dangerous oh
oh
I love you
great will I expect an apology on my
table by tomorrow the 3 P.M
I wouldn't be mad if anyone else got me
but one of my viewers
wait there were so many that I
recognized humanix definitely like some
of you probably don't have like uh the
same name on your switch as you do in
the in the chat but I see Hogan
it's just one of us
[Music]
hard to tell hard to tell
sham that little crashed out as
well on 69 as if as if you're 96
Tony
yo Tony
who else is from us let me know let me
know
I plead the fifth
oh wait I did see a frost was that you
yeah did I see a frost
or maybe not
I didn't make it into yours I survived
oh I'm so sorry I played for this
and 10 fear oh my God
oh God the list is so long here at home
really wait let me check
this is so fun comparing who made it in
oh where is it going with a message go
I'm seventh
really oh yeah you are sheesh
oh my God so many people are able to
make it in
I made it oh my God but nobody is a top
five from us are they or
top five doesn't look so familiar Darko
could could be for most two
I'm 12.
oh
so good I'm 11. oh you are it's the same
nail oh oh
that's so cool seeing your names guys uh
soda and keyblade are you in the game
wait are you on the game three times
there's soda and soda's key and soda and
keyblade VT you little are you
hacking a game are you in there three
times
that's amazing let's play more guys
let's play more I only got 77 man so sad
it's actually not actually not so bad
hahaha try my best to stay careful
um
guys it's free if you have a Nintendo
subscription so feel free to join us
[Music]
and I have beat a couple other people
let's do it again okay
[Music]
mini play in four minutes oh level up
four minutes
can we get another one before probably
not right
[Music]
I don't know if I'm ready for anything
at all I'm gonna drop out like in the
first race anyway let's be honest
I don't I I won't enter yet no no no no
no no no okay let's try
what's everybody use why are there some
that I don't even see up here can you
like still ah okay I guess I'm going
with the blue one uh I don't care I
don't care you guys choose
what am I you made it in I'm in let's go
stay behind me
[Laughter]
stay behind me new skins can you get new
skins oh
are any of my rivals you guys
I mean again you will kill me this time
right it's on Pele oh my god let's go oh
okay let me go first
let me help me I'll protect you from the
damage
[Music]
what does that mean okay
is it like to remind you that there's a
boost upcoming
[Music]
this is fun it's like we're playing a
big game together I love it
great whale to kill Justin
holy greenwilder you're a beast
oh almost almost ready for my super
boost let's go
okay rock
is it cute
wow
Speed
Need for Speed uh Brown game
do most people not use their normal
boost that much and because they have to
protect themselves from crashing out I
don't feel like I see many people
boosting you know
maybe I'm imagining it
[Music]
the golden car a golden car is like not
a real person it's like you you want to
stay behind it and like bunk it to get
like those
oh
the the shiny things to up uh to get up
your wait what
they're gonna break me out
[Music]
please let me let me turn the front oh
okay okay okay this is my chance to
survive let's go oh Yoshi won the race
[Music]
oh my god I didn't even get very far
at least I didn't
[Music]
know
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I I got
I got one of my rivals down oh and Musa
was right in front of me
cheers look at you guys
what else I recognized some names are
really generic so I wouldn't really know
oh Sarah didn't
I thought your name was Geraldine what
the
Keyblade
I came in 44th fourth mini play
number four examples
eh you're not four here
I was Revival oh really
that's 52 82nd Jesus
[Music]
Yoshi wins
[Applause]
oh you guys can read his name good job
on your Katakana studies
I love your scene
no
she is
[Music]
our bar that low where we suck but we
suck proudly
sorry
[Music]
oh okay Minnie priests like going on
right now we'll just play the normal one
again
seems pretty easy to get into the race
so guys
just whenever you feel like it was I
just racing with the blue one in the end
I'll try I'll try the green one
maybe with the green one I can be a
little bit less
uh careful that
that different room again we'll make it
eventually
we made it in again
I'll crash you out
I think I'm in how do you know
Emily nini nini excellent
[Music]
how do you guys keep on being my rival
hahaha
it's on
oh
you can't fail your Boost at least can
you
come on
[Music]
everybody
what how is it already low battery
[Music]
[Applause]
ouch
[Music]
okay I'm gonna try putting my thumb
on both buttons
trying to control it like that not with
the crab hands
I may be cancer but I don't have to hold
my
hold my controller like a cancer
okay you can even AFK this one
good timing for oh wait did that get off
too early no good timing for
rubbing your nose
oh oh
careful careful
I may have a lot of durability but still
gotta be a little bit careful here we go
I'm way too far behind
governor
okay
my super boost
it's almost full again
oh God oh God no no please
somebody go behind me
[Music]
let's go
another one can't be
wait no what hey what does that mean
what does that mean okay final lab
didn't make it
adeku is also one of us I think
[Music]
bunny Cafe yeah you guys can change your
name so it's more
um recognizable for for playing together
if you want then I'll know
what's the next number one camera won
the race oh who is that
we got a winner at Red Is Dead
red you'll die
oh oh
oh let's go
oh wait the number one look at this
look here
y'all
Bonnie can't be
I was in the race apparently
are you aware that you were driving are
you drunk Gamers turkey
[Music]
I'm still at work where I want to play
surely you'll get another chance
sometime
when are you getting off of work
travel got far in the race the in the
race I was
better than Kiara who would have fun
we're first yeah we're first together
he's representing all of us
[Music]
parasite care of beer that band cave
beer lunch box Street spikes
eggs
[Music]
maybe from us too I thought maybe from
us
Rand died early on
stream POV don't go right
[Music]
it's a shame it's okay
mama
foreign
do we know
who it is
[Music]
shut up that's me that's
I need some proof whoever it is maybe
take a screenshot and then put it on
Twitter on the hashtag it's me it's me
[Music]
okay I I think um green one was pretty
good for me
oh oh that was fast uh I don't care
sand ocean
oh man mute city is so popular
different room again
It's gotta keep on trying
and free A's
okay
[Music]
so do I have which color do I have now
the green one oh okay maybe because I
didn't set it to where I was hovering
over
and it just uses the one you had before
okay
all right I need to charge my controller
maybe uh after this I'll I'll put it on
the cable
[Music]
s
okay straight line good to
um use my Boost oh I also actually here
would be good
yeah let me use it right now
[Music]
no not bad 16-9 yeah oh
big golden car
okay oh hey look at my rank
oh wait super super super super super
super super
boost eh
get that super boost
okay and back on track
and a little bit of a normal boost
get all those shiny buns oh I'm on 60.
I'm under 60 baby
[Music]
let's boost again I'm risking it
now's a good time to boost as well but
that's getting really into a dangerous
territory I know I know I know
but we're close to the boost again
okay okay
[Music]
I did it awesome
constantly have cat hairs on my nose
it's like a constant
handicap
oh I'm on around 50 yeah
oh yeah but why did I boost I didn't
really want a book goodbye
hey hey if I would have blocked that one
time I would have had a way better rank
but 61. I'm getting better
better
Perpetual cat hair oh I took down all my
rivals I'm better than you I'm better
than your hats man I think that's from
us this
is number one cave no wait that's a
different person right because they were
both in the same race before you guys
wow
[Music]
it's better than I usually do I'm 13.
yeah I don't know if you should be
watching the stream uh Lord fluffy
though really
that's her name
I'm six
there's two sixes the three sixes wow
hi
[Music]
Kiana
this one says my my Japanese hashtag
here
[Music]
Grumpy in 10 minutes rad you didn't die
for once
[Music]
hatman
yeah Triple G hey
who else do I know
[Music]
nice
nice guys good job
77 was you huh huh
[Music]
okay guys before I go in
Let Me Wait nine minutes that's maybe
even enough to still do
uh
let's do another race but wait let me
let me get cable and charge my
controller foreign
[Music]
I don't even have enough tickets okay
whatever
[Music]
it isn't even on the I do is it even on
the on the cable internet I have it on
the Wi-Fi and it's still going so smooth
Isn't it nice I have five tickets ah
okay I need free tickets I have five to
go
[Music]
I'll do another race though
oh
oh sorry guys that was a surprising ride
you guys could not wearing preferred
uh probably barely any kfb in here
oh no sorry I should have warned you bro
I'm sorry I'm sorry sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
tonight
you might want to use a power bank but
is my is it charging now I hope so we
haven't gotten the second warning anyway
right
anyway what the hell you guys wow it's a
coin
[Music]
yo yeah yeah
still not in you're making don't worry
yeah Pro con battery
not so bad yeah it lasts a long time
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is just what you have to deal with
if you watch me play this game now I'm
sorry really unbearable sounds
out
and super boost
is coming in only fans someone's called
only fans Captain meow
[Music]
meow goes out for me
69 baby
absolute cannibalism
are we fine with this guys can you guys
be nicer to each other please we are a
team okay anybody who makes it in the
top five represents kfp and therefore
represents the success of kfb as a whole
okay
oh sure
no Moon Dogs
maybe also from us
oh I'm just chilling I'm barely using my
Boost I should use it more
[Music]
than it is
someone else
[Music]
oh
be so aggressive guys please
oh my God
I'll be careful now Paul not KFC died no
ouch ouch her black box
it's like you're saying like a chat
message
oh
at the very end
I have made it so far no
oh
ah I was so entertained though
wow finite finite kfv
yo I see you guys edosan
Lance box again keyblade again
Big Boss that's me I got number 30.
did I go okay Stella kfp
Acer there's so many your heart could be
from us too 52 63 52 63 let me check 52
63 and 16 52 yeah 63.
oh
nice nice
I'm Mike I think I know that person too
and maybe a pilgrim
kfp number 918 let's go
hello new subscriber what champion
Rebecca who the hell is Rebecca who the
hell is Rebecca you stole the number one
from kfb little
okay what about the Grand Prix are we
too late
low battery uh oh
no we're not delayed is it charging
no oh because I didn't
maybe because I didn't connect it
is it charging not enough
I thought my job was done ah it's good
we good we're good oh level four
okay I'm not gonna go into another
uh one
I'll wait for the Grand Prix
and you guys try to get into but there's
gonna be like several ones too right
like there's not just one right so that
as many people as possible can make it
in but what happens when there's like
like all are filled up and then there's
like one left over that only has like I
don't know 80 people
it's a rest filled by CPUs
starts in two minutes
you can fit in enough nah I'm scared
[Music]
oh I'll rather wait
one minute after God that's what Kelly
did
one minute after it starts to get in
what what
oh it's open for 10 minutes to join oh
you don't have to join right in the
beginning
um
okay it will hold 40 minutes oh okay
okay let me try the golden Fox it has a
lot of recovery
okay whatever the rest is slow
but it means we can get faster faster
man everybody has such cute colors I
want I want to look like them
death wind
okay Johnny C could be from us maybe
maybe I'm in I'm in again
I think I'm in oh
have fun I ever had this one has wind
I don't think I had that before did I
oh God
[Music]
this is a first
cannot like
over over correct my movement that's not
good either hey they're picking up all
the all the balls give me some balls too
thank you
why am I doing that
not looking so good for me look at my
health oh
it's charging okay okay okay
oh no I really need a dad
came in clutch
get me is there wind up here too I guess
it wouldn't even matter
okay
I've Got The High Ground now oh yeah
more balls
oh I got the I got the bunk again
this one's difficult
fish
do cars get in real life also influenced
by the wind like this
maybe racing cars because they're
lighter and faster oh red
on the floor
red am I more of a gamer than you
yes at certain speed yes oh hello ah
I'm gonna miss it
I'm chilling I'm I'm chilling this is
fine
I'm having a good time
and get yeah
yeah cool it's difficult With the Wind
hook on dead I'm a better racer than
hookah although maybe he was like way
more in the front lunch box dead
oh I will be the last kfp standing just
how it's supposed to be what what's my
rank
[Music]
better to be alive
is that one of us
[Music]
oh
be down
yeah guys put kfp in your name so that I
can recognize you
you killed red
[Music]
seems like we have to have an outing uh
can't be outing to improve our teamwork
Taco that's one of my whole life fandom
at least
I don't know judgment okay if he came
for milk so many
menu Cherry camping
[Music]
Ted and behind me Hogan would you like
to you know talk to me about your
feelings about this race the taco was me
bang
if you're not trying to kill me
do you have any comments on on your
performance today
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's go okay let's get into the
grumpling
[Music]
Let Me Wait Wait guys let's try to get
in together okay uh how do I see like a
timer
okay let's join when the clock says
wait okay there it is when it says six
okay six minutes
[Music]
when it says on your side say it's not
on my side six okay
foreign
[Music]
I'm gonna have a tutorial prompt oh
okay
do I just I just ah okay I'm joining
I pressed ah okay
um I don't care what that said
quasel it may have said croissant I'll
go with green
oh
oh okay so we're doing like all of them
let's see how far we can make it oh
got some
kfp rivals
[Music]
okay good luck
let's go you forgot about the prompt you
just gotta click it away quickly
we can do it again don't worry
here we go
I think I've been fine by the way
without the crab hands
I think I've been doing it
was just my thumb
hello
it's like every time I touch another car
it like uh
gets rid of some HP online like an
energy
[Music]
yeah but hopefully not so much because
like if there's so many in one place
like what can I do
nothing
ah ko'd someone else okay then then it's
okay oh
already
on The High Ground let's go
oh I'm under 50. what
look at me
and I'm gonna boost another time to get
over this rough area the Cobble
we'll get a little bit off of the pedal
or boost boost charge charge can't be
dead unfortunately number 918
oh now I'm getting into a dangerous spot
here so let's boost
mmm
pushed again
my position needs to be kept safe oh and
we have a super boost better take it
while we are in the race
[Music]
okay for under 15. I'm gonna boost
nice turn
playing it safe
and let's keep that charge up oh God oh
God oh God oh God that's dangerous
[Music]
go go
you ranked out assistant
hey screenshot time hey
two Rivals defeated
on yeah oh ripped this kfbm
who was number one
got 38 74.
or 74 Gilder
[Music]
wow
I cut the whole thing
Red Rooster and aniki
[Music]
okay now we're how many people 85 what
oh God
you guys better suck so that I can win
please
does the the twirling protect me from
being like when somebody hits me taking
damage I wonder
[Music]
yes okay
okay whoa
oh oh kfps are fighting again
be nice to each other
okay here we go
let's take this chance to get a bit more
to the front
dangerous dangerous dangerous dangerous
oh God
[Music]
I'm not gonna make it really far and
just complete
but as long as I'm not dying I'm still
better than a lot of you
[Music]
was I on 70 and the rank up was 70.
oh
now it's 65
hey how much time do I have yeah bye
no no no no no no
[Music]
no
ah
I've been abducted yeah by the aliens I
was so close to catching up again
because of the super booze
um
what that's what that is dead players
who can blow people up
66. I mean not bad for a newcomer
[Music]
Acer
breath soul
no I want to go out let me out let me
out this is also like in Mario Kart
where you when you start spectating you
kind of can't get out
you're not gonna watch us win for you
no no a little bit a little bit
how do I switch between people
maybe also from us
[Music]
okay if we jello
mostly safe I like that name
okay okay
does that remind me of
GTG coffee milk
can't be Acer
campy lab
kiwawa had a little lamp
[Music]
red a red I saw you bunk
against the wall be careful don't look
at my stream
focus on the race Casper
Kevin cow gaming gamer
Kaze Cafe
downtown was pretty good and the ranking
pretty high
how do I get like to the top
they're number one it is like around
number one holy go go go
[Music]
what a pro look at him girl look at him
go
oh
you fell behind but you can still make
up for it go go go go
ah that car must not have much control
he's like so wobbly
I don't even know that car is it just a
skin on top of an existing car or is it
a new car
like riding a soap I ranked out yeah
because you didn't focus on the game
[Laughter]
it's a recolor okay of golden Fox
be careful be careful
[Music]
bye you can get back up I believe in you
I believe in you
[Music]
okay free lamb is oh okay lamb Go Get It
Go Get It
[Music]
real real
huh where'd you go
so confusing Matt hi
cute okay uh is it over yet soon where's
where's number one ah finished Viner
who's that
who the hell is that
not fair rigged rigged
kfp should have been number one
me
oh your lamp
good job good job good racing I respect
it
hmm I'm gonna stream 11th Cafe
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
I think there's just one racer that's
called hi Kiana
and let me out oh yeah I'll leave that
I'll leave now I love how my the only
number up there was 69 because that's
where the the only one that I finished
with
[Music]
okay wait somebody said press a
exit
I Believe In You focus focus on the on
the
on the race yeah better luck next time
me me
who points earned leaderboard resets in
six days
well well well
it's not the worst but if you turn the
66 around it's 99 so it's kind of a very
stylish number to have wouldn't you
agree Let's Race baby
get in here
now
that was fast some of you guys are
probably still in the Grand Prix as well
oh I see I see judgment kfp
between these two I'll go for mutually
um
[Music]
oh
oh Unix eon kfb
let's go you're in
[Laughter]
so many of you guys get a chance with
Mario Kart it's like so much more
difficult
well maybe we can synchronize running
right you really want to
fix your reputation now don't you you
want to win against me don't ya
[Music]
how did someone already die
be careful
[Music]
how far will Wawa get this time place
your bets now oh I got it I got oh
oh
[Music]
baby
I come alive
[Music]
the holy number
ah
okay here I come here we go down
oh oh I didn't even know I was going for
that
I didn't know it was ready
finally
finally is a final
[Music]
but that's okay
I'm not gonna use my Boost now
[Music]
doesn't matter
I'm not gonna use my stupid boost
until
46 hey that's my best so far I think
oh
my rivals all dead
red almost killed you well he's still
below me
look at these losers look at all these
losers yeah look at them
ah too bad for them
the problem is like there's no timer so
it's kind of hard to time joining
I like it I have an idea how we can do
it
I have an idea
don't just join now see we have the
special event Team Battle timer
or new Boost color unlocked okay Spin
Attack a total of 50 times oh yeah yeah
and when this says
uh 10 50. let's join
10 seconds
[Music]
yeah if you can't make it in now it's
not my fault you can't blame me
top 50 nice job yay
no I wasn't gonna join the no no no no I
wasn't going to join team Race I just
meant you know as a reference for the
timer
oh did you guys get trolled and didn't
mean it like that I just wanted the
reference of the timer
oh
hope you guys didn't join the
team Race all of my rivals at KFC
isn't that fun
it's fun
it's fun oh it's the only fans want a
reference to like fauna only forms
oh God look at all these people oh my
God
[Music]
holy there's so many people ah whoa
whoa that sent me flying really far
behind
to catch up
I'm so behind hi Cruz
Baba
[Music]
Baba okay really bad run for me
number one KFC is in again let's go
[Music]
oh I'm up here again now is my chance
better make the most of it
yes
okay
okay ah ah somehow I can't control
my car in this race ah
look at all these KFC yeah
spicy
okay
it's like it's like I'm a I'm a hockey
pin
oh my God and I'm playing like uh table
hockey
whatever you call it what the
man I'm gonna die
what the
what if I go up here with power down
does it still kill me
oh give me let me down
oh but oh I did get kind of charged back
up okay okay okay
well this is a really shitty run for me
but whatever
it can't be HL fan oh all this potential
he got shot what the freak please don't
give me finish the race oh my God okay
dead body is ashes
no I still finished alive so that is
quite an accomplishment but Giga chat
with chat
yeah
that was so bad for me
ah look at all these KFC
even from the
Mario Kart times creepy Jello milk
address cell wow GT
chicken
dog
Randy
alpaca
Saucy Rush look at all this cavity the
few normal people in here
must be like what what does this mean
what does kfb mean I love this we are
spreading awareness
okay guys don't join the team race or
whatever just I'm just using it as a
reference
foreign
[Music]
so when this turns
6 15 let's join another one
and go
do you know any Spanish and no habla
espanol
um
[Music]
uh see
um
[Music]
vamos vamos
tequila
is
[Music]
that's what that means now you can start
boosting in the first place
[Music]
no no no
no no
[Music]
evil one is fine either one is fine
why is everybody like sparkling oh is it
because they're super boost is ready hi
[Music]
come behind then go behind me
I got one
[Music]
okay here we go here we go here we go
oh getting dangerous I shouldn't I
wasn't looking at my Boost bar so much
but
[Music]
what Hannah
here we go I think this race is going
well but my ranking is still pretty low
it's difficult
it's really tough man
[Music]
get behind me come on you're not
supposed to be there
don't you know
[Music]
Moment of Truth
oh yeah you before me
[Music]
Al
ah he did go behind me Humanity
[Music]
I haven't seen in a while I feel like
look at them all dead all these dead
chickens I'm gonna make them into
chicken soup
don't look at me
bread bread that was the close one
you're not so good at racing games are
you
and roasting you I'm so sorry
can't be real gave me
look at all these kfp Giga chat not so
much number one anymore
but good try lemonade
we got a number two for sure and number
four and number five for sure
wow
nice
[Music]
because it was your rival wow you got a
really skilled rival there
and live for the bully this is so fun
happy for you but how do I get a rank
man this is rough should we try to join
the team battle
fast aggressive racing I don't know
that's not really my style but let's try
team Bell let's just join the team
battle
uh uh three two a one Thursday later so
sorry sorry not really well done
hope you can get in oh I see someone
space Banks
that's that's so difficult to join even
when you don't have much of an
announcement
announcement announcement the Vlog is a
Vibe looking my heart indicates with her
for a good time but till that's it pink
versus green a pink
foreign
over there
[Music]
what's green what the going on go
away
[Music]
get away from me
I got something like plus five did I
kill someone
[Music]
I guess I didn't kill anyone I just did
some damage there
okay
also it's like uh they want you to use
the
the twirling maybe to make damage
oh I'm so bad I'm so bad at this ah
do you want to hit that song
nice I at least I could skip the curve
there
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no no no Spin to Win okay
yeah pink versus green
[Music]
um
did I do that
oh here we go
we're close to the goal
[Music]
s
[Applause]
so how's that go
did I finish 69 again
[Music]
did we win
um
let's go bring him strong okay of pink
[Music]
I was 26 in my team I hate that
that's incredibly good
look at you losers
that's like middle
sheesh
[Music]
so toxic
wow
spins I did 140 spins really I don't
think so
whoa look at the Lincoln 75kos hat sure
you didn't KO 75 people but it's like
like the points that you get how many
points you get for 1ko
oh bumper 26 degrees
75 what
140 is the points
what
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah it's not the amount of
whatever I did just the points I get for
it
[Music]
uh-huh
interesting
[Music]
I get a red recolor
okay pretty damn cool
[Music]
when this one says six
um 25 okay that looks like a kfb racer
you think so
[Music]
proud of kfb
because you guys
are doing so well except for the ones
who aren't doing so well
and and and
it's fun to play together
guys sorry wait for me wait for me
okay now don't go without me I can't
live I can brace the no in a normal
world without kfp no no
no no
I distracted myself oh they're so comfy
I destroyed it myself
oh chicken
oh you still made it
you said it and like within five seconds
I
just tried it myself
oh man are they still they can't be
behind me what's up
I barely saw this race this um
or did I ever play it before this track
oh my God you guys are so mean
you guys are so mean no this is
definitely a first oh my God
oh
people talking
okay whoa
whoa
you guys are so mean
ah my nose is itching in look at me give
me super super blue so I can rub my nose
oh I'm so bad uh spicy can't be dead no
don't say no don't let the normal people
kill you
oh why did I boost that's so stupid
that's so stupid that's so stupid that's
incredibly stupid but
okay
I lucked out
cheese
give me give me the magical super
golden pretty oh wait I already have a
super boost oh
I am stupid and nobody's behind me it
seems
oh no okay it'd be winning can't be
losing
oh here's another charged wonderful
wonderful wonderful
foreign
[Music]
but even then my rank isn't too bad 77
that's like what I always get
I guess also now I'm not playing the
green one so I'm more vulnerable
oh
it wasn't the end the end is never the
end it's never the end it's never the
end it's never the end
[Music]
whoa good timing that I chose
some kfb died again and again and again
what the hell
guys midnight won the race
what's going on over there
ow
go
59 baby not so bad oh
survival
silent Ryan
pretty solid yeah I'm not liquid I'm
solid Wawa Kiara's bro what the bro
cherry
[Music]
made it in even though I said get in at
a different time look at
them
hey what's going on
wow it's midnight one of us
don't we have a midnight a member called
midnight
I feel like we do them
[Music]
we do
they're not in chat
Mizuki well that was fun let's do one
more
slang
[Music]
hard to stop anywhere at all okay okay
at uh five one five
at one five
actually let's turn the mini pre let's
join the mini parade at now
okay
uh tonight for all some of you guys
again
I'm gonna go green again
[Music]
you gotta
you gotta be able to read my mind guys
this is training for you guys to learn
how to read see if there's so many
characters who aren't able to read my
mind
unlike some of you
went to the wrong one
[Music]
really unfortunate for you but it just
proves that you are not ready yet you're
not ready for this
[Music]
is here
let's see if he'll get number one again
[Music]
okay
I shall take that invitation
I'm 23 right now holy
and not anymore but that's okay
[Music]
wow B Gamer
that must be one of us
so many of you are you having fun are
you entertained
oh sure
how much does the membership the
subscription cost again
yeah I need to charge I need to charge
Nintendo subscription
[Music]
20 bucks a year what that's actually
cheap and actually it could uh just
just this game alone
could uh be a good reason to get that
oh
[Music]
can I get a bit closer to 50 please
nah you guys are too good what's
going on
[Music]
he's just sucky at us brah can you not
look at my bra
[Music]
and hey you guys we're getting better
was my rival
that's so weird
all right we're in a mini print we'll
continue oh wait did I okay I
didn't get kicked out that's good
I forgot we're in a mini period not in a
normal race we tied
[Music]
oh get out of here
whoa V gamer has like everything super
fancy yeah what
must be playing a long time and you're
still down here with me in the bottom
ranks
must suck
to get down here on my level
ego check
Panda I love your skin too wow so guys
oh whoa all this place I don't know this
place why is everyone zooming around
confusing
bulldogan
oh
time to boost a little bit
no oh no no no speed
[Music]
oh my God oh my God
take that immediately get me out of here
now
I don't want to be down there
a pretty good pretty good
my okay I just came out of the super
boost no surprise
[Music]
[Applause]
oh danger stranger danger oh no oh oh
please don't hurt me please don't hurt
no I'm out yeah
[Music]
time to drop out
oh man
okay detonate for bonus points uh
uh when somebody's close to me right
ah oh it doesn't explode immediately
[Music]
once
yeah oh wait does it did it say who
killed me or did I just like die on my
own
well even then 71 not so bad I died next
to my bra almost
oh and this is like still
to be to be decided
wow wow wow wow that's how quick it can
end
don't kill yourself when you're not in
the race with me
maybe you get bonked for that
don't do that your rank will lower
um
I was 72. oh hey there's me oh
okay well there's protracts no no thank
you okay when this says 14 20 then we
join here
for real for real and
and
trust me trust me
you can believe me
I stay with my wild goose
did you make it guys are you in
are you crashed by key okay
oh no
yeah chicken cannibalism is a worldwide
International problem that we have been
trying to tackle and work against
actively
however
it is
just bigger than we are you know
but at least within kfp I would like to
keep the cannibalism as low as possible
you know
I mean if I can't keep kfp under control
how can I control the world
it's just things like this that keep me
up at night um
oh man I want to be in the top 40 or
something why am I always in the bottom
40 man so lame
skill issue
[Music]
oh the golden the Golden Boy
let's go quick
fly by your Falls
out of my way
oh that was mean that was kind of mean
and yet I controlled myself and I got a
bunk
and I did that
nice
did I do chaos alone I didn't mean to
I'm so sorry I said I love you
[Music]
I'm so sorry
whoa
ah damn it
[Music]
oh
how many more laps final lap okay oh you
get charged up here thank God
actually going kind of good because I'm
like playing a little bit more
aggressively actually
whoa
as you have seen with the kills
foreign
[Music]
I could have I could have finished up
pretty high up there
wasn't I like around 30 at the end or
did that already change quickly
[Music]
I gotta finish one more time under 50.
come on
okay when this says 40 10 40.
on the left side
and two and one and go
it was almost 20 yeah man
I'm gonna crash out I'm so sorry I said
I didn't do that on purpose like it just
happened like randomly I'm just trying
to protect myself man
in this wild wild west speaking of wild
west both are really really sandy
looking these roads I don't care which
one we're doing
okay wind Wendy the KO helped me
how does a kale help me do I get like
extra energy or something for killing
someone
[Music]
you made it
heals you oh oh okay Kiana
kfcoshiana
you made a little mistake there I think
oh God
I'm too scared to boost
oh that hurts
it's windy
thank you foreign
[Music]
I hope there's a charge soon because I I
did a stupid
I did a little stupid oopsie oh there it
is
[Music]
come on
hello I see you
oh we got lots of lots of boost ready
better use it it
it let's use it all let's use it
um 50 something around bad but I saw
five lines lies lies lies lies
ah
[Music]
does this game not have music
you guys hear the music right
[Music]
it's game nothing yes okay why did
somebody ask does this game not have
music
[Music]
put it in again
wow who's number one
Yoshi here again made it pretty high
Giles
stream Sparks
audience
yo you guys are strong
[Music]
fan is on
that was a high aggro attack to place
you got a KO in that one
eh I don't know I'm not good at that
Eleanor can be used I know about that
but when I practiced with that in the
tutorial it didn't really seem very
necessary to my playstyle
but I can try again
and when this sense
6 15. is that too little time
I think it's fun okay go
it's useful to place better it's not
that necessary I agree I don't like
using okay I'm having a lot of people
don't use it but maybe Against the Wind
yeah
[Music]
mute City please
thank you
small adjustments
[Music]
I use my you just take off your finger
off the gas yeah yeah
I do that a few times too sometimes are
10 seconds behind noodle
it's painted
[Music]
I did not anticipate the starts
Mamma Mia
oopsie it's fine we only have just begun
look at us being Beyblades
[Music]
oppa
big curve
[Music]
okay
hit them with those sexy chicken thighs
oh
yes guess
Nice kill Riga
whoa did something detonate there holy
how much kfb take does that take I
wonder
maybe I'm overdoing it oh
oh now about the charges over there it's
okay it's okay it's okay it's okay oh no
so many cave Pizza
I pray for you at night
you little why did you die in my
face
okay and I wanted the super boost not
the normal boost but okay now we get the
super boost
oh we're done already
that was short kinda
I killed him
I did
I thought you made it to 40th damn son
I did oh
violence in my veins
vile veins
[Music]
top five you made it away whoa
R4 could be from us soon I'm ranked 12
let's go nice
wow I got 90 in good job
okay okay I'll give you guys more time
to join the next one
oh I gotta have a ticket
I got another ticket okay when this says
two minutes
yeah yeah shut up when it says two
minutes we're joining this one
I wonder how long I should play because
I gotta Read Super chats too
hmm
oh am I ready okay I'm ready
yeah you need to switch online but then
the game is free
and go
good stream game yeah it is
thankfully they they prepared their own
servers chicken thighs
free as long as you have um
the subscription so it's like soil free
quiet free
you're in again oh my God see so easy
for you guys to make it in
more race tracks are being added later
oh yeah I heard that oh chaos bride is
my rival and some other kfps
[Music]
yay let's go guys Yoda school be nice to
me don't kill me
or you're going to the usual room
mm-hmm
I was first for a moment I swear
[Music]
I'm so shiny
oh wow who's talking
[Music]
somehow I surprisingly even though I'm
like usually the one who wants like HD
graphics like HD as in like like not
pixel I still find this
currently more Charming
and
like nice to look at like I don't know
why then for example like those like
really really realistic looking racing
games that you have nowadays like I
don't know
I don't know what they're called
[Music]
somehow the Simplicity of this makes it
really Charming
like on first look
I was like nah not so impressed
but I don't know I like it no I like it
now
[Music]
in front of me KFC behind me AFP I have
a
all my rivals on
front off
oh my God so much happening
[Music]
oh I got that
how far can we get it's the last one oh
the goal is there
yeah
I pushed some bastards away at the last
moment yeah Peter Griffin
nice I'm I still somehow can't get past
the 50 but that was satisfying
nonetheless I think I drove quite well
celebrities
oh oh my rivals in the end
wait I didn't look at the uh at the
thing three are behind me is one in
front of me oh yeah
oh yeah one only one is in front of me
all right
interesting
[Music]
anymore
you guys are welcome to keep all these
names
even after the stream and just represent
kfp when you're racing
wow did a lot of you guys change your
name for the stream well I use no way
you always have that name guys right
your number six
yeah I saw you I'm always kfb Rockwell
yeah represent
pretty fast to switch on switch oh funny
I'm always going to welder well yeah you
don't need the kfp
I changed mine
shame I'm bad at this game me too but yo
yo it's it's easy to be like decent at
least not die
if I can do it you can do it I love like
Mickey Mouse for a moment
just a casual look we're joining in on
the fun I'm happy about that welcome
welcome I die every game you're doing
something wrong like if I can manage to
not die
then you can manage to not die
yeah
yeah definitely
believe in yourself
be a bit more careful you're probably
playing too aggressively
I'm schooling noobs today
[Music]
I was doing right away but I played like
a glass Cannon
that's
that means when someone seemingly is
aggressive but they're not
how you seemingly aggressive in this
game but then you're not how does that
work in the game how can you be a glass
cannon in in f-zero
strong ah oh strong offense weak Thief
ah
[Music]
oops not quite not quite
didn't get it quite right okay let's do
another one I can't stop
[Music]
freaking fire
for a freaking that really
um
hits me right now for some reason pink
wait a second guys don't join
um where do I change these colors
all right Workshop machines
[Music]
these are all for the wild goose the
green one that I've been using
[Music]
I'm gonna go for red but I'd like to
have orange is there orange I want
orange
well it's like different achievements I
wonder which one is orange if there's an
orange
[Music]
I don't have any decals
and this is just a different color of
boost okay let's make it red
orange is one down Okay so okay so it
could be the next one
oh
all right
[Music]
change machine aha
wait so are they ah okay so it's really
like for the car that I'm driving that
I'm getting the achievements for and
therefore the different colors okay what
about this
oh I'll take this looks like I'm playing
a Toho game with my car
badges
finish your race I did that without
hitting any barriers oh I'm gonna
put all the stickers on you spin I'm
weird
ah there we go I can put all these
stickers on
cute now I stand out more
I want a new border I need all levels
for getting new borders oh man can I get
a cash shop
s
Nintendo switch online
did it save I hope it's safe
should we join the mini again or should
we do so no ones
foreign
apology accepted I was joking anyway
but I'm gonna I'm gonna drop out so soon
and then if you guys didn't drop out
then you guys are kind of stuck in there
but okay
um let's wait until three minutes
[Music]
okay
I'm not gonna miss it this time
and and
AGA with my new look
for real for real foreign for the orange
oh
wait is that an achievement that I need
the the purple blue orange
um
colors are really pretty
oh
so many of you
wow wow wow wow I love you but I can't
let you win
me
that means you hate me you didn't make
it and make it but so many made it
oh I'm on the very left next to Trevor
and red rooster
what about
Brad
[Music]
what what brace are we doing
okay
is there like some lore behind f-zero
like is there like some aliens involved
is there lore
I would like to know about the lore
don't tell me now because I can't read
it now obviously
tell me after
[Music]
stupid
oh I'm under 50.
no way I'm gonna keep that
[Music]
I'm back to 70.
did you see that I bunked him against
the the rails
no no no don't kick me out don't kick me
out don't kick me out you little shits
I'm desperate I'm desperate
don't play somebody somebody
except my destiny kill me already oh
wait I made it I made it
somebody sacrificed himself for me if
yes I love you very much thank you soon
[Music]
oh my God I'm still like apparently like
behind something okay okay
the 80 it was the 80.
[Music]
I'm so bad I'm so bad but at least I
don't die apparently there's people who
are worse than me
oh I'm 80. I made it under 80. and that
is an accomplishment as well that is
very big for me
who made it to number one
double kfp strong Oh wait we're in the
mini pre I forgot again
I never realized
we're still going we're going strong oh
that was a close one
the cut off
that one fancy sigmas kfp how is that my
rival he looks like so strong
[Music]
guess he wasn't doing so well last time
no habla Espanol
I'm fighting a Kiara 2.0
it's not me so give it your best feel
free to be violent
[Music]
okay
I'm ready to boost okay
buddy I'm just chilling on the side
where it's safe
wow
oh let's get up
no time to waste
how far can we get
not very far
charging
the yikes
Tula did it say two laps left
oh oh oh oh oh
I'm also in the danger zone leave me
alone
[Music]
no no no no help me please drop out
Alvin Elvis
[Music]
help me why tell me why do you hate me
so much ah
I never make it past the second round
or the first basically
unfortunate
foreign
[Music]
nah
did you you did you too late though a
little bit delay but that's kind of
sweet what the hell
oh my God
oh
[Music]
you're a sweet baby
love you
okay
uh man
let's do when this says 15 30.
oh should we join the okay let's join
the team battle in at 15 30. no okay
I'm sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
why is she like this
gotta keep you on your tippy toes
[Music]
am I pink again let's go
the only the words when it's a new track
you haven't practiced you're doing great
wow thank you
Pollo Loco no no
no
how do I say you loco
can is there like
um
friendly can I can I hurt my own people
Friendly Fire
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
yes
[Music]
oh
I want to be up here I can't do any
damage up here
[Music]
oh that's a bad thing right
yeah
I mean the top 25 oh not anymore not
much to see
what
[Music]
I want to hurt these people oh I got a
15.
[Music]
get out of here
let's go
foreign
difficult to like actually get someone
that
oh God why did I do that I'm gonna die
I'm gonna drop out I'm gonna drop out
just like I dropped out of high school
oh
[Music]
an egg won the race hey I survived let's
go
[Music]
150 points
did we win
[Music]
Big Daddy Big Daddy
nothing cool
oh
let's go
[Music]
Victoria okay okay okay guys left side I
promise at 11 20.
[Music]
cute helmet thank you I promise I
promise
three two one go
you actually drop out well yeah but then
I like like I still like a few years
later
went to something like high school which
is kind of of an equipment that explains
so much El mouth
double I am with you I'm so sick of
your words
yeah you knew that already
I just uh went to like like a like a job
focused school after and that when I
finished
you little shits honestly what job hotel
hotel
boost okay
boom boom get out the way get out the
way get out the way
[Music]
I'm not doing so bad actually let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's call it
please
[Music]
destroying each other again
uh-oh danger zone
and charge taco
charge don't go
[Music]
oh
I hate you guys I hate yo
hate you
rapping
you better not be one of us
I hate you
[Music]
even me I'm not playing I I'm I have a
mild
negative feeling towards you but I love
you at the same time
okay it's fine I am not affected by that
at all
okay normal race at eight minutes
my my PC froze for a moment that better
not be happening during the race
[Music]
okay oh now my sound is crackling oh I
haven't had that in a while
fighting
[Music]
do you hear that yeah I think I fixed it
now
okay should have fixed it I think oh no
please not those death wins
good good
are you playing an OBS no I'm not
[Music]
I don't know all of these people
I I think I know
muso
sand oceans harder
I'm not sure what this one's like but it
doesn't have wind so it's the worst
would you write that one said
pun
there is a new panties they're here you
don't need them huh man
your panties feel neglected
foreign
[Music]
it's okay this one's okay
[Applause]
the good thing is if it's a difficult
one
then not only you might be struggling a
lot of people might be struggling so in
the end
wow
[Music]
hey did I have that super boost done
ready before those crazy curves I should
have used it I was like so focused on
getting the curves right
that I
didn't see it if that was the case
oh
pencil
the golden car was literally kfp
trying to help me
an angel
I swear
[Music]
I still don't feel like I should be
boosting but I am doing it now okay okay
regret big regretty spaghetti
big regretty spaghetti
okay just survive now
now oh God oh God it wasn't the end oh
oh
okay I'm going to be careful very
careful and I'm getting my Superbowl
[Music]
why is there barely any like boosters on
that sometimes there's free sometimes
there's no no at all
[Music]
[Applause]
can I finish at 69 let's go let's go
I'm driving like a like a grandma oh my
God shut up
that is so not true
[Music]
hey 69 out of 99
that means I beat 30 people
um yes
[Music]
come on
and these are not our people kfp what
are you doing we need to win we need to
win we need to destroy the normal people
destroy love your helmet thank you it's
made by blue
b-l-o-o
blue makes a lot of my my little
attachments
kill enormous yes blow him up blow him
up uh free let's do a frame at three
minutes I'll give you a bit more time a
bit of a buffer
foreign
[Music]
don't worry I will not change my mind oh
my God that was close yeah
I'm gonna stay for the Grand Prix maybe
maybe
[Music]
I I am it's hard to find a point to stop
for me right now
so I don't know how long this is gonna
be
[Music]
mute
no I want to read some super chats yeah
yeah yeah I don't even have to cook
because I have some leftover pizza
from lunch
I went out to buy a dress for the
wedding today my wedding with you I know
uh
oh so that happens in this game too
huh okay now now I know now I know
and no I bought a dress for the wedding
that I'm attending attending in Japan
[Music]
yeah I was really unsure what to wear
because I also wanted to make sure I
don't overlap my colors with the bride
because in Japan they like to do a thing
that's called Ito now which really
directly translated just means fixing or
changing the color
and
like that's really what they say the
bride will like first wear a white dress
and then they will wear like usually a
dress with like pretty flashy colors she
didn't tell me what color
but she told me like what colors I could
wear
so I went out to go looking for
[Music]
some dresses that would fit the occasion
but
um
kind of difficult
oh did I do that
did I do that
[Music]
I typed that so perfectly did I do that
I'm on a roll baby
[Music]
oh that that one's that one's breaking
too oh but I I I'm scared
[Music]
oh
whoa
and yeah normally I mean I already had
some like dresses that could be good for
an occasion like that but the color
didn't really work
so and also the length and also the the
style because like shoulder is showing
and stuff like that and I know that in
Japan
um
people are pretty there we go nice my
best one today
[Music]
[Applause]
people are not I don't want to say prude
but like in terms of like showing skin
[Music]
um
yeah
what's the right word not fruit but
modest modest is the word I'm looking
for
so yeah I felt like
the dresses that I already have are not
fitting so I have to buy one yeah
and even my dresses I wouldn't say that
they're or anything
but yeah
[Music]
it was hard to find something I went to
a place but all the dresses they had
were like too fancy I felt like
um
especially when comparing to oh it's too
mini pre at
8 50.
When comparing to
like what Japanese girls wear at
weddings
[Music]
um
so I bought something
it was a hard choice because there
wasn't much that I felt was suitable
but I got something cute that matches
I got a good size
can you believe
XS wow
some like it really depends on on the
clothing sometimes I'm like XS sometimes
I'm s in Japan sometimes an m
yeah
for these dresses
I got an excess
did I join the mini play did I tell you
guys that I would be joining the mini
pre did I tell you
I hope I told you I was like
focused online I did okay focused on my
attention
and then I also bought a little bag and
then I also bought like some
skin colored underwear
because I noticed that it's a little bit
see-through even though it has like an
underskirt you know a lot of women's
dresses and skirts they have underskirts
but even then sometimes they're
see-through what the hell
get out of here get out of here get out
get out of here safe
[Music]
well yeah I think the dress I bought is
quite fitting and I'm looking forward to
the wedding I'm first and foremost
looking forward to seeing the girl uh
for the first time in a long time
I haven't seen that girl who's getting
married
since
how many years has it been
how many years has it been two
out
oh my God
oh my God oh my God it's going down and
I need to rub my nose
I was so surprised that she would invite
me honestly
I'm so happy she thought of me
oh one more thing that I'm really
worried about though
that I haven't I keep I kept on
forgetting because I didn't know what to
do
a wedding gift
am I supposed to bring something I
wasn't like told about anything
maybe it's a given I don't know but like
I think like it's a cultural thing too
like
maybe In some cultures
you don't have to really bring wedding
gifts
I don't know is it a must
hmm me being there honestly should be
enough of a gift you know my flight
ticket expensive dress expensive
everything expensive you know
train to train to the area where it's
happening gonna be expensive
everything's expensive should I
ask her because I already asked her so
many questions about is this dress okay
like she keeps on like helping me out
with me not knowing what to do
is there a wedding registry see no I
have not been notified about something
like that
[Music]
66 and not so bad
I was super focused on my tangents maybe
it's a good thing
man there's so many of you oh
what
number one
oh I think that's a whole library
because there's ayama in the name
usually money see that that I think oh
you think in Japan it's usually money
am I in the second or in the third round
right now
if I'm in the third then that's the
first time oh my God that's the first
time that I got so far
no seconds no what I feel like I already
drove more I'm so confused
confused I'm so confused
the Japanese Bros
even if I ask I can't really look at the
answer right now
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay okay
aggressive play style working right now
oh nice completely went off the gas here
and now gas gas time
and no gas gas time oh crazy curves
crazy curves crazy curves crazy curves
crazy curves
oh my God dangerous dangerous oh no no
no don't be don't be so mean don't be so
mean
I am I am
uh what's the name of that animal that
lume is not a turtle not a turtle towel
not an owl ow ow
[Music]
oh
is that the end no
mother I don't know
barely healed me up
ow
I'd rather
hey Dobby I missed this oh ah we're
gonna die together back here hello I'm
behind you guys help
[Music]
let me in let me in
fact I literally love you oh my God oh
my God like oh my God I'm gonna die
anyway you know I will do my best just
before me again but that's okay because
I'm I'm still ranked okay let's go
[Music]
let's go okay okay
foreign
[Music]
three thirty thousand yen
uh
[Music]
so first of all that's okay that's good
it's good because again it's weak
apparently giving like free 30 000 Yen
if it's a friend it's like pretty normal
but I'll ask her she might say oh no you
don't have to really you don't have to
you came all the way from Austria for me
and then oh even from you know that City
to that City for me oh don't feel like
worried about she even paid for my hotel
but that might be kind of a normal thing
uh for
oh my God what the is that
this is the first time I see this
[Music]
bring me up
Magnets
I don't mind dropping out now because I
want to have a conversation
I keep on looking away from the game
screen incredible
[Music]
okay so what the is this what the
not
why not huh
um I rank my
uh Trevor where the two trevors be
behind me oh my God what the is
this
hey thank you I love you I'm in I'm in
the rank now thank you I love you oh hey
hey
Transit stop go back
I think I'm almost
[Music]
I'm 50 out of 50. there's nothing behind
me
oh oh yeah right then the rank 40 wasn't
even that good because there's literally
not many people left
uh delusional Wawa
[Music]
but that one seemed to die oh were you
offering yourself to me like to like
Bonk you away maybe even sorry my
reaction time is slow too slow for that
I'm so far behind oh my God
[Music]
can't be killed evil Kiana
wow justice has been served what the
is this a car that's about to blow
up like a detonated thingy
don't blow yourself up in front of me
yeah
[Music]
okay hi
yeah
thank you
yeah come on
wait was that the end of the mini parade
actually
is this the end because it's a mini
[Music]
oh yeah
I was talking this whole time
I don't know if I did better or worse
because I was talking
[Music]
wow wow wow can't be
good job guys
wow oh shiny wow I think even crayfish
just from us no
you think it helped
anymore
[Music]
I think Trava deserves a get out of the
usual room free tickets
[Music]
yeah but there's two drivers like which
Trevor G and Trevor
thank you
this travel waited for me
but I don't think he is in the usual
room
she better pulled up the Tanz frame ah
yeah okay okay yeah that's happening
tomorrow on super the channel
Trevor from GTA yeah
then I cannot be very nice to you
because I hate Trevor from GTA
wow we survived guys high five
[Music]
oh what's that spirit's name it's snare
oh
points earned 149 weekly wow rank 40.
wow my work is under 50.
[Applause]
spent a total of 99 seconds Airborne
in one go
down oh as a practice course but not
available as an actual racing course
they'll surely add it later or it's not
made to be a proper
racing clothes rank higher than 50
unique Rivals oh did I already
raise 50 Rivals wow 89.
good boy that means
math time I always get Four rivals
I don't know
poor to ice Pro Tracks oh
oh
that one was also portrait Pro track I
saw them oh this one I didn't see before
is that like a like a snowy one
most difficult I don't want
okay last thing we do today we joined
this one at 14 30.
[Music]
hey is it like uh also like a mini prey
or so
what do you just get one
because I only see two anyway two
choices
okay go
just one okay
we will earn bonus tickets
sheesh let's see if I can survive one of
them I've I've seen before I've driven
it's before hello okay I've been
hi look at all these chickens in there
oh oh you can turn while in the waiting
screen well I want to see the white land
because I haven't seen it before and I'm
a white Beach it belong to the white
land
okay
we got it
I'm allowed to do bad because I haven't
seen it before oh it looks nice
wow so bright well blinding it's like
light mode
okay here we go who is kfp
good question
did I fit how I don't understand the
Boost you guys have to explain that one
to me
[Music]
oh God okay okay not so bad not too bad
oh oh oh oh okay okay okay okay oh
[Music]
uh what the is that
oh already explosions
okay okay oh super super super boost
LC laughing dead
to try
but you're not on my level yet
[Music]
too greedy
Ariana Grande
what the
um
hi hi hi hi my nose is itchy my nose is
itchy and that was not much of a
charge was it
okay careful careful careful
[Music]
damn this is rough
oh
[Music]
well good try
I got pretty far
yeah Mama Mama
yeah it was the itchy nose not my fault
and
look at all these failures
[Laughter]
good try guys you failed with me today
we died we if we died we died together
hand in hand Wing by wing
oh there they are oh
well wow the winners they are the
winners We Are The Losers
yeah
it is what it is sometimes we gotta
lose as well
yeah it's just cycle Circle of Life yeah
oh why wire unlock the White Lane let's
go okay
that was a lot of fun that was a blast
let's do it again and tomorrow I have a
stream on Subaru's Channel quite early
so maybe good for sea viewers we're just
uh promoting uh Tales of arise DLC again
is a sponsored stream
um yeah I'm not streaming again tomorrow
because afterwards I have some plans
with my friend
um but yeah that was fun today what time
I think it's 1 p.m jst stream is up now
so you could check
you could check
shibakiana it's been a long time since
we collab but apparently I'm taking up
like a teacher role in that collab
um she even put it on the thumbnail
because I played Tales of her eyes and
she didn't but she played other Tales of
games a few
so apparently my role is to like change
her uh teach her a little bit a little
bit about desert rights
[Music]
um
huh
once you have a proper chair for you
well it's uh digital uh I'm I'm at home
it's virtual so I will be sitting on my
own chair a proper chair
yeah I'm happy you got in oh you
overslept your alarm you wanted to be
there earlier well good that you made it
in last last second
yeah I'm her Tales of ambassadors Senpai
mm-hmm
I don't know if she's like with this
being pronounced
Ambassador as well
but I I definitely am
[Music]
that was lots of fun yeah thank you guys
for participating I also want to play
Mario Kart again sometime soon because
of all the new tracks that I didn't play
yet
so look out for that if you want to race
with me again but this one's definitely
so much easier for you guys to get in
it's Speedy like there's not that much
like loading in between either
it's like way more fast-paced I think
um
[Music]
I'm not marrying Subaru
ah the only challenge was you've been
boozling
and still you guys made it in you're
practicing your anticipation skills on
me
which you should be doing anyway
no no no no no no no no no no no no
marry her what the why
why marry her what the
no no no no no no no you guys are very
confused right now
get a hold of yourself
[Music]
nice raising guava respond to see you in
other kfb as Rivals yeah but it didn't
really feel like Rivals you know it's
felt like teething when I was your rival
twice oh my God it was like we're like
so on the same level so in sync
um
[Music]
okay
gonna race Cali I wish I wish they added
the function to make your own rooms but
I guess it's not that necessary but yeah
for playing with someone specific it's a
bit difficult I wonder if you can do
like local multiplayer though like join
the online game together with someone
sitting next to you
can you do that
Cali played it yeah she played it
yesterday or like depending on your time
zone maybe like still today
not yet maybe in a future patch would be
really annoying they added that later in
touch with 99 oh
[Music]
you have a friend leaderboard too oh
wait do I see Callie on there
[Music]
uh
uh loading where's friend
I don't see friend leaderboard
maybe because I didn't race against them
yet
[Music]
oh maybe because maybe she's somewhere
in here you mean can I see it when it's
a friend
press y ah
[Music]
did she play a lot longer okay okay ah
laughs
cannot accept this that was fake that
was fake it wasn't the Royal Kelly
she let somebody else play like it's
it's Sniper Wolf
[Music]
I just watched like a video about that
girl yesterday
that she was letting other people let
her her husband play the game for her
and just reading a script uh
funny
okay now she just does shitty react
content and like steals she doesn't even
credit people I watched a whole video on
that
yeah
always same reaction always same
thumbnail
never never credits the creators that
are in the React videos
[Music]
it just came up in my
um
recommendations because I was watching
another video from that channel
yeah
no no not the text film Zone but I I
heard that this dude was yeah like he
made a whole channel to like make fun
and react to Essence Sniper Wolf and
then therefore he called it JJ Jax films
[Music]
pressing stuff but this was definitely
one of the frustrating things to watch
um
that's because like
yeah I watched the video about some some
apparently cake streamer cool went to
Japan and like harassed everybody and
disrespected the culture and internet
and it pissed me off so much to see that
but apparently he got arrested so let's
go
that guy yeah him
man what what is wrong in your
brain that makes you even fly twice to
Japan even after like getting in trouble
once leaving Japan once and still
doubling on on to that to fly to Japan
again to continue your
what's wrong in your brain like
ah
what makes you think that that's
acceptable behavior oh my God
and in Japan especially I feel like a
lot of people already have
like
you know like not such a good image of
foreigners you know when they make
trouble so this just makes it so much
worse man don't don't ruin the
reputation of foreigners in Japan please
there's so many other foreigners even
tourists or people who live there who
are trying to blend in normally and then
one of these comes there
thinking that he can make fun stream
content by harassing people
oh please do not do no no no no image of
Foreigner very very bad please do not do
yeah
but I think he's gonna learn his lesson
because Japanese prison as far as I know
is very strict uh
the first time in his life maybe he's
gonna realize
you can't with people without
consequences
no
yeah I hate when people do like
that for streams like in public
that's even worse than all the
people do like non-public but in public
like IRL streamers that are just out
there to like uh ruin people's days and
be funny
oh hopefully he's done you with the
funny
are we joining no it's only it's old
today I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I am uh I've raced for almost
three hours I think it's enough it was a
lot of fun let's do it again
now
[Music]
um
knock off sooner
soon
[Music]
um
the moment he gets out he will do it
again I don't know I don't know did he
ever
get this far before
oh my God the Japanese people they they
all know what I'm talking about even
though I didn't mention the name and
just really roughly talked about a
foreigner
look
like doing
[Music]
yeah it wasn't Japanese news I guess
that he got arrested
um
in Japanese we say zamamido
Direct
ly
[Music]
that's what you get hmm
yeah I guess it's more like that's what
you get
it
I will read super chats guys uh do you
want to keep the music I go I go change
room though
[Music]
which room
yeah they should also add a function
where we can go through the audio
library
[Music]
I want to keep my helmet on
oh
I feel like the office is kind of messy
right now but I should I should we can
switch to like Halloween office again
soon I'll go here because I have my
bikini on
oh
okay
this whole time I was racing with my
bikini
because it makes me faster
and it distracts you guys
ah
yeah it was muted over here
there we go and we're Dynamic yeah yeah
that's all I wanted to say
oh wait chat chat you kind of dead over
here what happened to you
[Music]
wow
wow wow okay
um where are we with the super jets
actually last time we definitely
finished our anniversary super chats did
I not read after that I wonder I wonder
I wonder
[Music]
okay Marathon okay
dokie
[Music]
who would have known that such a simple
game is so much fun
quite addicting too
let me put something up on the screen
for tomorrow
mm-hmm
Subaru senpai's thumbnail
[Music]
foreign
if you want to watch it will be Japanese
it'll be short we'll just be talking
about the game so
maybe not so interesting for you guys
but you know
a rare
somebody one-on-one collab
um
on her Channel
I hope we can spread the tales of a
ride's love
[Music]
is a win so true it's so true I try to
be there okay it's really early I think
for you guys but
um
I grew up with f-zero
oh I don't think I ever played it when I
was younger when I was younger
the only arcade games I played were like
I think taken probably
uh what else could I have played I don't
remember
uh
uh help me I barely even like got to go
to arcades because I don't think we had
any in my city so I only went when I for
example went to Italy for vacation then
there were arcades
oh it wasn't enough oh it wasn't an
arcade game oh okay okay
but still
didn't play it on
ENC room I only have the 64.
[Music]
no racing games well
I played like
human racing 1080 snowboarding
no I probably like dabbled a little bit
in some racing games sometimes
but memory currently empty brain horde
where is this stream that I'm looking
for
oh oh
[Music]
found it
round one yeah see we don't even have
one round one in Austria
and yeah where I grew up there were no
arcades
now
[Music]
foreign
somewhere here
at least it's not close by a country
um would be so fun
[Music]
I'm not a Gundam
okay let me put up the thumbnail and
then we can read the chance
[Music]
something else for the color stream
um this
wow I love this art so much
and so cute I love every time there's
like my chickens included in artwork or
my cats chickens or cats it's my
favorite things to see included in fan
arts
hmm
[Music]
okay
so
how many is this I wonder
oh God it's flashing again I'll put it
here
soon hello one three seven five thank
you soon golden on me with a rainbow
thank you so much
Kiara congrats on three years happy
anniversary if you made it here you
survived kfp's Toonami of love Yeah high
five
yeah
sending this lead for your fraud oh wow
so considerate
[Music]
though I officially call myself two
years ago I've had my eye on you since
your debut oh I started a casual viewer
and didn't watch every stream but I
always liked you and have been rooting
for you since day one even as a lurker
thank you wow
it's actually like
hmm
it feels like it's more rare to not
catch somebody's interest right away but
then like over time over the course of
some months finally
you you're like oh you know what I've
been chat looking every now and then
maybe maybe I actually want to watch
more often hmm
years later I have to see every kiwawa
stream if I've had a tough year but you
were always there to brighten my gloomy
days I hope kfb can be your light
whenever you feel down as well you've
accomplished so much and we're all very
proud it's not much but please use these
funds for upcoming travel expenses I
hope it helps you in a little
I can't wait for the birthday concert
sorry it had to come late but I know
it's going to be absolutely worth the
wait
yeah birthday concert oh I'm planning
things
at recently pointed out that kfb doesn't
kiss you enough
we need to fix that but I'm too shy thus
I call on kfb chicken sandwich your
kisses
no you can do it too come here come here
give me a kiss on the cheek
come on come on come on I'm waiting oh
you're coming closer
you almost there almost there one more
step and
[Laughter]
see what I did there
[Music]
oh oh you were going for the cheek but
in that very moment
turned around
[Music]
[Laughter]
our tutus have met
spicy
thank you golden Umi for the beautiful
rainbow and for the sweet supportive
message I didn't know that you were like
a lurker in the beginning but I'm glad
that you have made it into the rabbit
hole of Wawa
I hope it's comfortable down there I
hope you stay
[Music]
thank you Patsy thank you
um
I'm gonna work wishing I was oh
you know
I think you are here now right second
47.
thank you for the pinky congratulations
on third anniversary and 1.5 million
subscriptions yeah wow
I'm going to Vienna for vacation next
month and I can finally drink my
favorite and doodler and it's the best
drink in the world Tantra is the best oh
I'm doing like yes yes
I like to flex and Doula because it's
like you know Austria doesn't do many
things
have you noticed the chat isn't dying as
often anymore as it used to
YouTube must have actually done
something
now you guys are just quiet the Abdullah
is one of the few things Austria created
in terms of like food and drinks
and it's a it's a
it's a sparkling
a soft drink
that's like herbal tasting
um
and it's so good and so refreshing I
really really really like it yeah Red
Bull too
one of the few things
[Music]
although there's like I like to say Red
Bull is from Austria but there's like
you know
um
[Music]
yeah well well the headquarters are
definitely in Austria
there is somehow to say yeah
discrepancies
about the origin it's called avocado oh
it belongs to us though
it's Alice
don't take it away
[Music]
um but yeah I'm doing a big recommend if
you find it if you go to Austria try it
it's also usually on the menu in
restaurants drink section as well
so give it a try playing boy you know
what's up you know what to do I hope you
enjoy your vacation and thank you for
the support hope you can catch my
streams even during your vacation but no
pressure
eating Mike Tyson's ass Duncan
Jackson FB thank you for the pinky I'm
in class so I can't watch but early
congrats for 1.5 million thank you
your class may have already ended
probably at the point where I finally
got 1.5 million right
all right
I wouldn't be surprised
[Music]
is also doing one uh soon like she even
already reserved two
streams or did I go crazy like when I
was I was looking at her Channel and I
saw two reservations
I'm like girl
are you planning to do this longer than
12 hours or is she taking a break in
between or what's going on ah one anarch
I have one archive ah okay okay
oh I wonder how she's planning to time
that and
cut it off
[Music]
oh you sent another one we'll find it
maybe
[Music]
she will sing retrospective or if she
would I'm I would be delighted
it'll be exciting
and ginger mats thank you Aurelius
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I'm gonna stay here for one year oh
interesting interesting choice now it's
easy to see your stream in time that is
true also I hope to visit Oscar during
your vacation oh my God you definitely
especially if you have one year time you
definitely should go around uh Europe a
little bit
you are surrounded by beautiful
countries mm-hmm
so I hope you check out a lot of places
while you're here I don't know what
you're there for for one year maybe for
school maybe for work but I hope you
have a great time and yeah food might be
something you have to get used to if you
come from Korea and you're used to
really spicy really strong strong flavor
things I think food is a bit different
here but but I hope you find the good
stuff thank you for the support and
thank you for trying to watch my streams
at uh even in Korea but now for a year
hopefully
more actively
while you're in Europe Europe gang plus
one let's go come Sunny down
hey
love singing here yeah oh that was so
much fun that was a song that I sang so
many times that it also was really
comfortable to sing
[Music]
huh
in Hungary I can recommend goulash
really
well I don't know if it's also called
goulash in Hungary I think so right
because it's a it's a Hungarian dish I
think and we eat it a lot in Austria too
there's like Austrian variants too
there's an Austin variation where you
eat the goulash with some semic noodle
[Music]
um it's like Austrian bread dumplings
I like that combination
it's really good it's really filling
though
yeah this dish is all over the world one
of those dishes that made it worldwide
[Music]
some milk noodle
yeah there's there's many great ways to
eat goulash and yeah different
variations there's like a sausage
goulash in Austria that we eat it's kind
of easier to make than the real goulash
which is made with beef
really soft stringy beef
[Music]
yummy Oh I wanna eat goulash
those two blushes are really different
though tasty both are tasty
yeah good stuff good luck with rice yeah
goodness with anything
um
top with a fried egg that's
that could
possibly also be an offspring variation
the the fried egg and a gherkin uh
okay
Fidel had a special name I forgot it now
a pickle yeah pickle
[Music]
gherkin
for tourists the one server and a loaf
of bread
ah you mean goulash in the in the bread
bowl that's also a thing yeah there's so
many variations oh man oh man ah
ah good stuff
yeah anyway you're welcome for hey ya
ever tell anytime anytime really
you chose a song that has big chances of
being sung over and over again soon
[Music]
Hello's music oh thank you for the Reds
but chat wow seems like we were already
really close 1500 I know no no that's
what that's how you mean it
ah 1 500 in currency thank you thank you
thank you very generous thank you soon
thank you for the support harlos hope
you're doing well
let's do something again sometime
Studio robbings of the pinky I never
doubted for a second you'd hit this
Milestone I hope you will perform The
Melancholy version of Sparks or there I
ask any Tori Amos song porn site girl
waitress no I don't know any of those
what the is that
[Music]
anyways
and I love ny2 what what's that mean at
the end
[Music]
I don't know Tony Amos but maybe I heard
it before and I just don't recognize the
titles
[Music]
yeah also good
um
they love New York too did I sing I Love
New York
[Music]
I guess so yeah and one of those
New York songs
yeah sorry I didn't seem sad Sparks I
just wanted to sing the songs that I
can't archive anyway
yeah Empire State of Mind that's the one
that's the one oh I love New York
concrete jungle wet dream tomato huh
[Music]
huh
somebody wrote that
[Music]
why don't you tune in during lunch at
work and you're singing Paramore let's
go you'll hit 1.5 million in no time at
all thank you that it was definitely not
no time but we made it
yeah I'm glad we made it and I think it
was um even even though it was a little
bit painful it was worth it
so all is good in the neighborhood
thank you spankenheim
a holiness
thank you
tinox
out of reflex I still every time look to
the right side even though my mixer is
not on the left side
[Music]
um
lunchbox
[Music]
always nice to catch at least a little
tento karaoke I'm sending this a little
preemptively but congrats on the 1.5
million Lala you deserve Millions more
it's okay it's okay I don't need 5
million subs or so as long as I have you
guys
um even even if it's just five of you
that already makes me happy
I heard this movie by the way did you
hear her
wow
[Music]
the more the merrier of course but
yeah
you guys honestly I said this before and
one of your chickens pretty much counts
for ten in terms of passion and Power
and let's get another word of p uh
um
come on
give me something
papaya no persistence
[Music]
hell yeah
so
baloney
um
so I don't have 1.5 million Subs I
actually have
15 million Subs good math good math
thank you so much Nathan
pineapple yeah I'm surprised not many
people said Pineapple
[Laughter]
but I guess it makes no sense
[Music]
Diamond play button on the way yeah I
can sense it DHL is sending it right now
and gonna try to sue me right after
stupid DHL
[Music]
okay we should copy that business no
that's not being evil like them
you are thank you for the rest of the
chat you're almost there Kento you're
gonna need a lot of new uniforms yeah
the factory is working overtime right
now oh and I oh by the way I realized my
name could usually could easily be short
for usual room true unfortunately it
isn't but that would be cool if it was
well I mean if you wanted to be that
you could just say it's dead
but what is it then
if you if you're saying it's not that
what is it
I'm curious
you're telling me it could be usual room
but you're not telling me what it is in
the Super Chat why are you keeping your
secrets
huh
well well well fine then well then keep
your secrets funny magic chicken or
something like that
thank you for the super dance
[Music]
it's the name of my old review channel
oh what were you reviewing
induction
what what is this
what are these pickup lines
even if I were allowed to marry food I
would still choose you over Pizza I'm
not saying something
[Music]
what I use pickup lines
foreign
[Music]
okay I have chosen drop the mask and
review my true form
and oh
oh find attached enclosed form and fees
50 bucks to complete the change of my
title from kfv blah blah blah to kfp
Kitsune
wait are you though the wow
thingy that I saw sometimes are you the
same person
why did you turn into a furry
you are
you ah
ah
are you a furry
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's unexpected
[Music]
only on the inside
what did you say that oh yeah only on
the inside
what does that mean
how are you only a furry on the inside
is it when you like want to be a furry
but you you don't have because I guess
the fur suits are expensive you don't
have the money to really be a fairy
[Music]
I guess you guys are I don't know I
don't know if you would call it chicken
the furry because it's not fur it's
feathers
I watched one of those videos you guys
sent me by the way there were so many
videos to fix my algorithm one of them
was a video about uh black chickens
interesting I didn't know that there's
like genetically black chickens like
everything about them is black even
they're like bones and their uh organs
everything is black except for their
eggs
surprisingly
yeah but their eggs often don't survive
more often than
normal eggs they don't survive
my algorithm well let's see
I didn't watch that many videos because
the ones I watched were really long ones
I might go back on them though okay here
here is my let me tell you my oh it's
not completely fixed but that's okay
here are my recommendations randomly uh
one is uh from Sashimi Clips narissa
gets a private session to see onigiri's
half naked model
oh uh a clip then there's one from Sushi
clips
has you made notices that everyone
believes she's a baby
so you know I have like a couple of
whole live Clips here there's one about
the crying which broke my heart anyway
like I watched it like other like I want
to stream
I broke my heart and then there's
something about Grand Theft Auto Four
hey it's a video with 40 views that's
being recommended to me oh it's like a
what the was that oh
it's it's a it's a playthrough I think
it's probably like part 29 or so
then there's a Airline review
video then there's uh an idol video from
uh like an old performance from years
ago from uh hello project Idol
from Suzuki any who's freaking cute I
want to watch that later let me open
that in a new tab
and then this is kind of more reflective
of my recent
recent recommendations
another video a new video so no surprise
it's getting recommended to me it just
came out from rotten mango
[Music]
um you know she does all these like
videos where she sits in in her room
podcast style talks about
uh weird cases
usually involving murder
you're getting those because of me too
she's like a really good Storyteller
that's the fascinating thing
[Music]
she doesn't show much footage or
whatever of the cases
um or you know she mostly just retells
everything
so that you can watch it as a podcast
too
crime was a mistake no no no no no no no
I I still
still clean cleanse my
uh my my recommendations completely I'm
fine with having some true crime on
there but then a little like yesterday
it reached the point where everything
was just depressing like either
some stream of drama like people who do
be stupid
and then some true crime and then you
know
just everything was sad just so sad
yeah it was scaring me
I did I did um
uh click on do not recommend from this
channel anymore for one case
which was actually such a good Channel
and I watched a few videos and was
really moved by it
but yeah I I at the same time it was
really
depressing so I didn't want to see it
anymore
no
no oh well let's go back to Super chats
[Music]
yeah
not good for mental health well I don't
know it was like in in some way it was
uplifting and at the same time it was
really just saddening because it was
like a Channel about telling about
um
all kinds of really rare uh like
illnesses on mostly like children and
teenagers
and I was watching a few and it was like
really
educational you know
usually like they were interviewing the
kids and their family and talking about
how they deal with it and so on how's
that uplifting because like they deal
with it really well and and it just
moves you to see
how they are
still so positive about life even though
for example their life expectancy is
really freaking low yeah spsk yeah
so I binge watched a couple of those
videos and then my whole recommendations
were full with them
and I I don't know I couldn't see it
anymore because it made me sad at the
same time
but they're good videos though
and good videos
makes you more aware
he's a saint yeah
[Music]
yeah maybe every once in a while is fine
but I don't want it to take over my
recommendations
[Music]
yeah and
what was I oh yeah pyra boom baby that
is an eventual Dragon zero Danish in
Santa Claus dankishun or Santa Clauson
yeah
Italian Guys cook
uh
certainly thanks for the pinky
incredible cut I look at today since
you've shown interest in metal recently
or not not really don't don't take it
like that
I'm not really interested
I want to recommend the stuff genre you
may like heavy mithril it's metal with
lyrics until it's Viper fantasy works oh
Blind Guardian is a good band to start
it hope you like it
whoa like medieval
medieval sounding metal
[Music]
hmm
there's no Metal Head Arc no no no no no
no no no no no
I will not let it happen
how I met I think I've like heard stuff
like that before at Medieval festivals
anyway I was enjoying
those medieval bands
um somewhere
probably in that direction and most
others were not but still
um
um certainly I'm sorry but like you're
not gonna start like a metal Arc for me
no oh I'm I'm I
I am not going there
but I wouldn't mind you know like making
or hearing more
metal remixes of my own songs that's
funny I like hearing my songs in
different versions
baby metal is a different story
[Music]
No I gave up on screaming when I tried
it was really painful like I used a
tutorial and it worked for a minute
because I did that like
yeah you know that
um
like this lady was teaching it by doing
that
[Music]
and it worked for a moment but then the
more I did it it immediately like I
immediately lost my voice and it just
didn't feel good and I would not be able
to learn it in a short amount of time so
I gave up
the told place
now but that would also sound ridiculous
but I could have channeled my inner toad
yeah Didn't I do that before
it's it's close
it's pretty close
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh toad is basically screamo
that poor voice actor
[Music]
oh my God
uncanny spot on thank you thank you
thank you
now do it with more Melody I can't it's
I don't know I don't want to hurt my
voice it already hurts right now
foreign
[Music]
I'm happy it comes across
my love for you guys
no I think I
I have to let it out a lot these days
yeah
it's just an emotional time with so many
accomplishments happening
um
and just yeah a good good happy time
even though stressful
when in stressful times I still have you
by my side
The View helping me reach my goals and
accomplishments it just means
even more
we're going through everything together
[Music]
police parasocial YouTuber
takanashikiara
[Laughter]
videos
[Music]
I'm gonna skip those those blue ones
okay the flush Jets I guess I went to
Idol meeting
foreign
[Music]
don't give up goddess morning will come
soon in Korea oh
I don't know how that cheers me up oh
maybe you were saying like Koreans will
come to my rescue
did they did they
[Music]
did they though I don't know hard to
tell
hopefully though thank you thank you
pill bug thank you for being here it was
really late for you and you were there
[Music]
I never discounted super uh super kiss
super chew I can't believe it man
[Music]
oh definitely of course yeah
a thirst in three years not a good
username thank you
uh P gangs
neither oh this is where I reached it
thank you for the pinky and it's good
it's coming first million and yo
thank you
man it took so long thank you guys for
staying by my side
ah
dragon's fire also congratulating with a
red Super Chat 1.5 million yay thank you
thank you thank you so much
for being one of them
Anton M dankerson bottom that question
for the rest of the chat thank you wow
150 for 1.5 let's go
foreign
you think so King of the private team it
depends like other people are like just
endlessly
it feels like they're endlessly like not
YouTubers I mean like other YouTubers
um riding the algorithm flow with their
clickbaiting videos
giving homeless people money and stuff
um you know
yeah it's difficult as a YouTuber
especially now that the hype is like
pretty dead
but I'm still working hard
still trying to get new people in
still trying my best to entertain you
guys every day
like it's my first day
if not more
no no no there's nothing wrong with
giving homeless people money you are
purposefully trying to misunderstand me
don't do that
it's about the clickbait
[Music]
that's just uncomfortable
when people literally just do it to look
better and for yeah
the
actually earning more money through the
video than what they gave out
in the first place
yeah sometimes it's even an actor yeah
so
it's just an act yeah they would never
do it if it wasn't on camera but then
again you know it it has its down sets
and and upsets because you would hope
that it inspires some people to really
do charity
by watching the video like feel inspired
by it but I don't know if it's really
that effective especially because most
people who watch these kind of videos
are teenagers
oh do not give a normally
so yeah
[Music]
yeah a lot of it is just
played up for the video too
you know
just one example of what YouTubers do to
get the views
[Music]
thank you
give money to Shadows instead or
homeless kitchens yeah that would be
great no
[Music]
oh night owl Alden flaming pants
1.5 million subsidence congratulations
thank you
thank you thank you I will probably
continue
[Music]
if you will continue or seeing me okay
pinky promise
mwah thank you so much for the support
and for watching that endless karaoke
Marathon yeah
[Music]
crayons 18. thank you for the recipe
Chad congratulations on reaching 1.5
million subscribers Kiana I knew my oh
she could do it also belated
congratulations on three years of Wawa
you had to spread expenses a bit so I
hope you can forgive my tardiness nah
it's honestly like
actually like you know to spread it out
it's better for me too
I wish for you to achieve all your set
goals this coming year thank you
I don't really know
like if we start the year from now and
not from like first of January if that's
what how we're looking at it
then I know
like what I want to do for the rest of
the year
but I'm not sure what to do for like the
like 2024 in general because I'm not
sure what will be possible if
things will change a bit more to the
positive
for en in terms of Studio usage Etc
because that will influence what I can
do what I can accomplish a lot I think
um but yeah I'm not sure like what
exactly my personal goals will be
[Music]
um
I think I already accomplished so many
of my biggest goals
so maybe I'll just mostly just let it
happen just come at me the way it
happens and hope for some
some lucky
Lucky Strikes lucky
um
[Music]
like you know stuff like being part of
the summer theme song stuff like that
that was just me being lucky for being
selected
maybe something like that can happen
again that would be really nice
[Music]
I'd be excited
yeah and in my fourth year
yeah I would really like to have
these like concerts on time or at least
not half a year later
I don't even know if I'll get to do a
anniversary stream like afterwards like
a 3D anniversary stream for the third
year
let me check actually if there's any
news on that hello
[Music]
getting two seems unlikely but like
everybody else in Japan is getting it so
I want it too
um
I'm not giving up
not giving up I have to go now thank you
for watching bye bye yeah
any plans on more song Duets since your
album is done oh song covers
well I definitely I touched with nerissa
about this I want to do one with her in
the future we don't know when and what
but we know we're doing it
um
there might be something coming that's
not a cover but like an actual song
together with someone
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah I will see we'll see what I would
love to do magnet but magnet I've been
trying to do that since my debut with
Kelly actually I wanted to do it with
her I think that was the idea
but magnet seems to be NG for us
a no no
sad
oh good
dude
[Music]
oh so good I just wrapped what's
happening we're just like thinking back
on if only we could do a song cover of
magnet but we can't
so that's unfortunate but it is what it
is
yeah anyway Koreans 18 don't worry about
spreading it out actually it helps me so
thank you so much for being considerate
and thank you for the support thank you
for everything thank you for always
being there thank you Koreans you're the
best thank you soon
[Music]
that's on 1.5 million Subs boss I'm
really proud of you never ever doubted
you always believe in Wawa You're So
Into You are seriously so incredible
singing almost non-stop for six plus
hours
you're singing is always so Heavenly I
can listen to it forever you're the
absolute best thank you it was
definitely a challenge you could add
that to my
to my anniversary challenges almost
because it was like more challenging
than anything else pretty much
[Music]
yeah but I did it to myself so
well I also did the other challenges to
myself so
yeah thank you it was worth it I had fun
it may have been painful but it was
funny too
um thank you thank you thank you unknown
I
I'm really really proud of YouTube
just like you're proud of me
for the pinky sticker thank you soon
yeah thank you thank you thank you
big big donkey
thank you
oh Castle
[Music]
's Kiana thank you thank you thank you I
appreciate it thank you for celebrating
this big moment that will be carved into
stones for history
Wawa history
glass sanctions
please thank you for the recipe Chad
sorry that I'm late but happy first
anniversary
seeing the Sea of supers imma keep this
shirt thank you you're cool caring and
wholesome I love you a lot I love you
too
thank you
you're a bit late too but I don't mind
it at all honestly those two happy
incidents were so close to one another
really really exciting I'm so glad
things are calming down
actually that one's a rainbow oh it is
imma keep this short so much for that
your anniversary celebration was the
best Vlogs funny also happy 1.5 million
Subs that's a lot of chickens
and chickens
um wait it's really spread out okay I
got it I got it thank you thank you
thank you I'm so happy you like the
Vlogs I saw like when I was going
through YouTube last night I saw some
um like translations I think Chinese
translations
of my
um Vlogs like subtitle and I was looking
for the comments and they were also
really funny
about my paragliding and my camping
vlogs
[Music]
if those are fully clipped if they're
translated then it makes sense you know
so
good work must have been a lot of work
to translate everything
[Music]
the little chicks
don't worry no chickens were actually
harmed in the making of that video If it
wasn't obvious I felt so bad anyway like
I I made that scene so quickly they were
already gone by the time when the the
chicken leg was on the screen the
chicken thigh
I just wanted to return them immediately
because I felt so bad because like they
were just like chirping continuously
and they wouldn't eat the food either
they were probably so confused
yeah
it was supposed to be an actual big
chicken but there was a misunderst
communicational error misunderstanding
between my mother and the chicken Giver
[Music]
they have some communication problems
and they talk more like with hands and
feet
and and normally chicken Giver has uh
adult chickens but at that time she
didn't
it was just like that time of the year
where she only had a lot of chicken
babies Chiclets
with no grown chickens
oh you think they could have been
aggressive
hmm really
I don't think so
yeah Chiclets
well that happened to all the groans I
don't know I don't know not my yard
nuts my chicken coop
I was wondering too
yeah but the small ones were so cute
anyway man it was cute to see such tiny
babies too
yeah I was still scared to touch them
I had my my mom transport them I just
followed her and it was just like you
know across the street basically
but yeah she she put them in the
container and then we carried them over
and I I think I had her put them into
the tent
because I was too scared yeah they
looked so fragile I didn't want to hurt
them I didn't know how to touch them I I
picked them up like one time at the end
to put them back into the Container
but I felt so so concerned
I'm so worried yeah they were so small
and delicate didn't want to hurt them
then my mom said as well and I have to
be careful
don't drop them or anything from too
high
so I tried to be super super super
careful
small small chicken
small and small chicken
[Music]
you think my noodle arms wouldn't hurt
them
hey I'm pretty buff now
[Music]
there is a DM me
Kiana I keep clicking on and off your
stream Tab while working and you look so
amazing with that helmet in your
swimsuit
I know it's a marvelous combination
isn't it
it just works so well
there is that if you want to play F 0 on
your stream let me know blue made some
helmets some variations and they're uh
you know anybody can use them if you
want they're made from me but anybody
can use them there's one that is not a
chicken but more like a
like a Golden Phoenix helmet too
honestly blue would probably make one
for you too
holy if there's time
[Music]
yeah jailbird version
and
where are we oh yeah deeply you get some
more kisses
thank you so much for the beautiful
rainbow very very generous
thank you for the love and support
tripod or trip tripod
Jacob 47 out thank you for the recipe
absolutely amazing six hours and one of
your best karaoke's converts on that 1.5
million you earned it thank you it got
kind of
rough at the end because my voice was
dying
uh uh and my energy was leaving me
but
thank you
I really tried my best
at times it looked dark and hopeless
but
Phoenix never gives up
yes it's literally in my lore that I
work
extremely hard
because I'll just revive anyway
[Music]
yeah
so honestly couldn't have done it
without you guys of course
thank you thank you thank you thank you
from the bottom of my cocoa
[Music]
pool
duck
so
God
clean
what does that mean
the name of a super chatter
Korean super chatter
let's translate this shall we
Korean bro
[Music]
something about chicken
okay so uh what the
uh
[Music]
chicken burger and chicken sauce and the
message ones I was counting on you
foreign
[Music]
stopped it immediately
did you hear the cheers
it's a live version
concert
hey I wanted to ask the one
it's so good
chat thank you I tried my best thank you
for being there and it was such a bad
bad time for Korea
[Music]
uh
oh yeah okay well
switch is dead
turned itself off
man that's lame
foreign
gotta bring out my own music now
I can't hear it
I did
oh you guys can hear it
or are you just
making fun of me
ah
there it is I heard it yeah you just
like the silence
okay okay there it is just for the
ending we don't have that much more I'm
just gonna finish this and oh yeah so
thank you Duncan thank you thank you it
was a pleasure to sing for you guys
always a pleasure to have people
actually listen to me hmm
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you I'm glad you could be there
was a legendary moment can you've been a
small step for teamkin one teamkin but a
big step for all of kfp
[Music]
thank you for the love that you give me
every day
unconditionally
I hope
humble 1713 thanks for the pink sticker
thank you for celebrating
[Applause]
already
[Music]
thank you for the first Super Chat
function from Canada Oh Canada Oh Canada
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
congratulations thank you for being here
[Music]
ah
thank you soon for continuing to support
me thank you thank you
thanks for the pinky how freaking yeah
you do the piano congrats on making it
to the big 1.5 million Subs you've
earned every single one of them Min
included
you mean me
autocorrect damn straight I knew you
could do it in the end now get some damn
rest five hours non-stop saying gonna be
rough it was more like six hours no
it was it was really rough
mean because I I didn't even take so
many breaks in between I should have
just taken a few more smaller breaks in
between but I just couldn't stop
uh I thought time would pass faster if I
just
if I just keep on singing
honestly it did kind of work but it came
with a cost
yeah
thank you gamer crate hey
thank you soon I'm glad you were part of
this beautiful beautiful day
um
congratulations on another Milestone
trench oh thank you so much for your
hard work for bringing us so much fun
and happiness and for enlightening our
lives with the bright Phoenix fire it is
a great pleasure to be your fan we love
you
oh thank you I am glad if my fans are
happy then I am happy
thank you thank you another big
milestone I wonder how long the next one
will take but I'm really really really
proud of this one
I'm so happy I was waiting for this
moment for so long
19 9999
well done
thank you thank you thank you
thanks for being there
sentence Centennial robots
oh wait there's a second page
second
oh
[Music]
I definitely underestimated how much
there is left oh
[Music]
Paige what the
I didn't
[Music]
foreign
that's crazy
[Music]
that's what you get for being so
supportable
no no no no this wasn't my sixth most
Super Chat extreme no it was the
anniversary one I think uh
yeah no anniversary was uh fifth
no no this one isn't even on the top ten
but
um it has two pages because there's more
smaller ones
yeah but still sheesh
and subtle chicken that is
major minor thank you
space wonderful Junction crawling
seeing
Ultimate mk203 Edition now I write your
full name for once with the numbers
jackets monkey dancing Trapper Scouts
thank you for all the Reds chat Marathon
ended up being a regular live stream LOL
good job that is true yeah
well you got your daily Wawa dose for
sure on that stream
[Music]
yeah
thank you for the support Evie
the best thank you
and Dr shaky Jones
Rainier thank you for the recipe chat oh
is this also from Hungary
with another Hungarian bro
comments reaching 1.5 million
subscribers into your amazing thank you
I probably already said this before
about you in the past like oh you're
from Hungary sometimes I forget these
things sorry like
yeah
I remember it like your names and stuff
but the the sometimes the currency
stands out to me more than other times
yeah have you met hokan before
hahaha I wonder
now you and Hogan and the Korean bro who
went to Hungary you can like have a meet
up
no you haven't why not oh wait polish oh
sorry my brain literally I
literally know hukan is in Poland for
some reason
I I just combined it in my brain sorry
I know
I run
up see I'm just ah
everything is scattered in my brain
maybe I may need to need to come into my
head and clean up
[Music]
helmet on too tight yeah
I do have
[Music]
Fred candies that will help too to get
through it
it's not that much more actually yeah
yeah I'm pretty much done
all right
okay
[Music]
yeah good stuff thank you Rainier
give me some of that Hungarian goulash
please
really hungry for goulash hahaha
yes I know where hookah's house lives
silver Randall thank you for Pinky
comments on 1.5 million Wow Let's
Marathon to 1.2 1.25 million was
actually the second stream of years I
ever watched wait I did a marathon for
1.25
really
I guess I did yeah because I was like um
next one would be so far away
I don't even remember that oh
I was the second stream of me that you
ever watched wow
and it was so fun I kind of never left
and this time you grew from the set from
the 2dv2 to 3D video to 3D flash tuber
you release a lot of songs in an album
I did that I did wait there's like
another Super Chat afterwards a red one
I see it I think there's nothing in
between yeah
got
000.
to watch you just think about this
number
where did I get 250 000 to watch me do
you mean 25 000
[Music]
and a bigger cake learn the new language
and how to fly yeah huh made a lot of
friends some corny pizzas yeah and I
hope a lot of good memories hope that
future will be even better
Oh you mean the 250 000 new subscribers
true true
that makes sense
yeah thank you
yeah that time damn how much time was in
between
that last marathon until now must have
been a lot of time it feels like forever
I don't even remember it what did I do
what did I even do
[Music]
2021 I mean end of it but still wow
that's before I got Freddy right was it
well
[Music]
um
second third yeah that was before
before
[Music]
that just shows again
how big of an accomplishment it is
because like it was
the growth was slow
but I really tried everything I could
to make interesting content that would
get people to join me
but yeah
[Music]
wait where is the beginning of this
again oh there
so yeah
you are one of those chickens who
believed in me and stayed with me and
supported me during that time so thank
you very very much Silverado thank you
mwah
we did
do a lot of fun things and I hope we can
do more
and you'll be there right yes yes yes
thank you for everything
and the big big support very generous
thank you soon
yeah
[Music]
we are the Smart Ones that know good
content when we see it hey you do you do
so true
I had to leave Japanese for Japanese
guys oh did you learn something huh
multi or cold 308 thank you decide
thanks for the pinky congrats on another
Milestone Kiara 1.5 million also the
karaoke has been fun make sure to get
some good rest afterwards we love you
thank you did I get rest I think I did
yeah yeah I forced myself
no no wait I streamed
no it's my stream but I felt rested I
was okay
I did stream didn't I and you guys were
like are you okay
yeah no I'm good
I'm fine thank you don't worry about me
yeah surprisingly my recovery was quick
yeah thank you for worrying about me you
guys are so sweet always thank you
pillow five thank you
okay
from today right same person
yeah Phoenix regeneration
um yeah
welcome to egg welcome
congratulations for 1.5 million chickens
the clucking must be unbelievably loud
how do you even
so true I just zoned out at this point
but honestly it is admirable that you
actually made it through over a six hour
ago great job you deserve every single
sub and many more thank you I agree I
agree I deserve more I agree with that
but you know it's hard hard to get new
people into the boat
well that's okay
that's okay
I am I don't want to complain I think I
deserve more but I'm happy with what I
have so all is well
as long as you are part of it I am happy
thank you segelius for
being one of those many 1.5 million
chickens but every single one of you is
special
yeah two million which that's that's you
know one big reason why I need to reach
it but if it took me like two years
to get 250k
[Music]
oh
that actually makes me sad
that makes me so sad
I mean you never know you know some some
YouTubers get lucky and they get
suddenly like a big push not only
YouTubers I mean I think I've seen it
with V2 boost too
yeah
[Music]
sometimes you get a big push
from somewhere because you're lucky now
that could always happen you know
maybe we'll get another pandemic
um not really ideal but yeah
[Music]
sorry sir no pandemic please
that way it makes it harder to go to
Japan again
for your vision boost
um
well it's again probably too late to
sign up and I didn't sign up because I
was busy with album anyway and they want
like something new
I can't really give that to them
um
well difficult if it's not too late then
I could still try but
to sign up at least
um
[Music]
yeah Europe is
seemingly not so
open or like interested in btubing yet
as an audience but
yo
[Music]
it doesn't have to be a European
audience but I do stream at European
Primetime so
[Music]
YouTube started pushing shorts
I saw a video of like laplas explaining
why she's going to Twitch
and it made me think a little bit you
know there's
definitely a bigger European streamer
audience
on Twitch
it made me think like if I got like to a
point where I'm really hopeless maybe I
should try to who knows like you know
I'm not like permanently but like every
now and then
um
but I don't know you guys don't want to
go right
[Music]
let's see how it works for Lapras yeah
yeah
let's just watch for now
see if um
it's like something worth considering
hmm
but even for her I would say the case is
different because she's still targeting
a Japanese audience
and
I know that like Korea twitch is doing
really well in Korea right now but Japan
surely there's like an audience but I
don't think it's the number one place
for Japanese people to look for streams
necessarily
[Music]
not I don't think it's that far yet
could be wrong but
um
you left because too many ads
um there's too many ads on YouTube too
but
not on like ongoing streams I guess
um
[Music]
yeah yeah the devot not being not
staying is of course the shittiest thing
about it I don't know why they don't
even like consider changing that maybe
they don't want to have so many bots on
their database because then they have to
to buy bigger servers I don't know
and it's their thing so
yeah
anyway anyway
thank you for the pinky congrats both of
us oh you have 1.5 million Subs I
received a result from my bachelor faces
yesterday or
and Bachelor computational archeology
now
[Music]
no more neat title from my friends I
want to send Super Chat yesterday but it
was sponsor stream I couldn't send no
problem
when I have to look that up
is it like what do you look for bones in
computers
what is that describes computer-based
analytical methods for the study of
long-term human behavior and behavioral
evolution
somehow that is very clear as a
description but at the same time
I'm like what
what
German German please
um
is that even a thing in German
it's probably not a finger driven so
um yeah it kind of is
[Music]
I don't know
right maybe you can explain wait wait
wait wait wait wait
I was John Bieber is John Bieber in the
chat
stand up
will the real John Weaver please stand
up there you are you draw bones in 3D
but so explain more
well the real John Bieber please stand
up please stand up please stand up
they draw Temple and Bones in 3D
like for what like
huh do you get like a reference and then
you create it so that it can be
documented or
or for like for recreating it from like
museums or
[Music]
take pictures in every angles and then
put them together
in 3D yeah but for what
like what's the greatest purpose
digitalizing
[Music]
oh oh
to get
VR Museum okay so stuff like that yeah
[Music]
oh
we are museums huh is that the future
interesting really really interesting I
saw like
the reason I saw archaeologists uh like
a while ago
[Music]
a couple days a weeks ago I'm like
like first I thought it was like a
construction site but
the people weren't really dressed like
construction people and there was like
really a small group it was definitely a
construction site
but they were like
they didn't look like construction
people and they were only a few and they
were like it just didn't look like like
quite like it and I'm like could this be
but why here
hmm
yeah but then I saw like like a logo and
it said something like that there's
something like archaeologists or so
um
yeah I guess they have to do that maybe
before they construct something which
makes a lot of sense
they should do that everywhere
uh
because I watched a video that was
making me think why don't they look
under the Earth before they build
something
that's another one of my curse
depressing YouTube recommendations
[Music]
should be a norm kind of oh I would say
figure figure
to skip that
well
yeah Evan
yeah is it clear now why it happened
because weren't like when I watched the
video it was like several reasons that
it could be and they weren't sure
[Music]
why is my streams always so depressing
yeah because
um
yay oh okay so it wasn't mine but it was
trapped gas interesting weird
up anyway I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I'm so
sorry
yeah
I'm so sorry
[Music]
it's just interesting when when humans
are just
stupid
at least
it will guarantee that I would never
create such a such a situation
hopefully like any anything anything of
those shitty things that I've been
watching
just like I will not get a life
insurance because someone will murder me
if I get a life insurance
just one of those stories
[Music]
[Laughter]
that will happen
I know that's not how it works I know I
know but it's just
a weird coincidence and it keeps on
happening
okay uh James MacBook thank you for the
red super chat so much endurance
congrats yeah
I am
enduring
a lot the enduring Queen
I hope Cali doesn't have to endure so
much
but
it was also fun you know until a certain
point so thank you thank you Jace
Watford for being there seemingly from
beginning to end you poor poor lost soul
all of you must have suffered so much if
you watch the full stream
listening to me sing for six hours
at the end rather painfully I don't know
how you guys do it
like oh at least I guess since it's
singing you could put it on the
background while doing something else
that's at least one good thing about it
[Music]
you probably did that anyway
but it's just the the length was
unnecessarily long
hmm you have it on while napping oh naps
are so good
[Music]
we also talk between some songs
making it entertaining that way you
think so I should have talked a bit more
[Music]
why do you always act like we hate your
streams no I don't I would hope not that
you don't hate my streams but this one
is um rough but you know I feel like
everybody was gladly suffering through
it because it was gonna be worth it
the final moment you would want to be
there when it happens right is special
special moment and we were all in days
together yeah
so thank you Jace wackberg
you were in it with me
rpwnktunction
[Music]
hooray
so I'm not gonna continue reading but
just heads up
Super Chat reading stream had no super
chats GTA stream had no super jets and
then the Badgers gate
I had only a few
and then there's today so I'm like
pretty much caught up
um
not bad
[Music]
okay
so tomorrow
this is happening let me check when is
it actually happening now 1pm is that
correct
um
uh yeah 1pm for me
all right
[Music]
I'll try my best to
be insightful and helpful
and
knowledgeable
um
[Music]
be a good tail set bye
I will be I'll make good advertisement
for tails off
hmm
that's our ambassador yay
yeah my Tails go higher
[Music]
um
would be Japanese Oriental but
definitely Japanese
[Music]
well I'll try to wake up beforehand no
don't really guys don't like
chill
like
don't worry about it it's short it's
Japanese it's early
[Music]
please
don't worry about it you can watch the
VOD
this is not a big deal it's just this
monster stream
[Music]
about it you know I already like the one
that happened on my channel was
important that you guys came but this
this one is you know super new channel
so I think Super the channel already
brings in a lot of subalu viewers I'm
not so concerned about the rear ship
there
um
but
but yeah if you want to say it okay okay
I won't stop you
all right all right all right okay would
be nice to have some kfb there yeah
but don't if you need sleep then make
sure to get sleep okay if you need rest
on
don't hurt don't hurt your body for me
I mean if you're European time zone or
SCA time zone then it's good anyway
I mean yeah European is well during the
like work time but you know
still look not in the early morning
I'll I'll gladly have sca and European
viewers there but if you're n a viewer
then stay in bed
[Music]
okay I'll go finish eating my pizza
and take a shower I think
I'm gonna go to sleep with my keto
cartoons
by the way two days in a rows movie left
me alone but then she stopped leaving me
alone again so I continued to wake up
for her uh but it's okay it's okay
fine
yeah
I'm getting a break from her soon
hmm maybe she will be a changed woman
when I come back a changed cat
[Music]
clingy but then she rewards me with the
best cuddles one could ever ask for like
before I go
can I just
[Music]
show you the way we cuddle
okay
[Music]
this is important
okay where is this yeah
yes so
okay
okay so I will um how do I die okay
let's make let's make bird point of view
stream
foreign
[Music]
POV
oh
okay
so this is bed this is my bed and I have
box
for chunky wonky
who sleeps in there all the time
[Music]
happily
right next to me all the time and then I
sleep here
middle
don't look at the Boba look at what's
really important here
and so I I have blanket and
you know like this but then I have an
extra blanket that's basically just
there for chunky wonky to
um knead it need k-n-e-a-d
because it has a special texture it's
like fluffy I know she loves it so even
in summertime I keep it there at the
bottom of my bed
and then sometimes you know I'll keep
these areas a little bit free usually
will make yourself comfortable either
here or here or here when I'm lucky but
I'm lucky it's here but that doesn't
happen often it's more like here or here
so she will like come over and then make
yourself comfortable and you will lay
down and ideally sometimes she doesn't
do this but often if she like is smart
she lies down in the perfect position
that like the blanket
[Music]
the blanket sometimes it's a bit messy
like this on purpose so that her her
paws
can reach it here okay
just so that her paws can reach it when
she sees it
and her paws can reach it often she'll
like naturally automatically start
um
kneading it yeah
yeah
and then she goes well needs it for a
while especially when I hear that I
can't resist I have to like
go this way and like turn completely
sideways
um and okay at this point to usually
usually we switch it up a little bit let
me change this
like I move her a little bit
we work together on this we're like in
sync you know
[Music]
I put my my hand on her tummy when I
turn around
so I'm I'm here okay
[Music]
um
happy
Wawa oh God ugly
but just so you know so I'm lying
sideways and and oh this is so difficult
but I have my hand here that's where her
tummy is that's where her butt is I know
I know sometimes sometimes she farts
sometimes but it's okay and then her
pawns are here and so this whole time
I'm getting the full fluff between my
fingers
this is her head okay
and and she will like lift her leg for
me you know so I can I can actually like
usually my whole arm is like getting the
fluff
um
I'm getting the whole fluff and a little
bit of fluff on my cheek and my and my
whole face you know
and she's purring and she's kneading and
ah it's just the best cuddle session
ever and I fall asleep we both fall
asleep like this several times and then
eventually I I don't even notice this
sometimes when I wake up and I move back
up here and she moves here usually
at some point when she falls asleep and
notices wait wait did we fall asleep
like this let me move over here I don't
want to sleep here anymore
yeah but I'm like so happy in this
position
um
it's the best
it's the best man
and because chunky monkey is in a box
it's a bit more difficult to pet her but
recently I noticed that the box I can
like kind of fold it down so the front
the front part I kind of like lower it
and then I just
I put my hand on her tummy she will
sometimes lay in different positions but
you know
foreign
[Music]
that's me
they said though I sleep even like this
or like this
yeah so my arm can go easier over there
since I noticed that I can like kind of
fold the box down and she's very happy
she purrs endlessly
um
I'm sorry you look like that me too me
too
[Music]
Bliss
Bliss that's also uh a video that I
watched yesterday thanks to your guys's
recommendations that also was a really
long one and really fascinating the the
origin story of the windows wallpaper
Windows XP wallpaper it's called Bliss
the name of the photo is bliss
the story was really interesting
I didn't even really realize that it was
a real picture I thought it was like
kind of Photoshopped together because it
just looks too perfect right
[Music]
well
some perfect places really exist in
reality
it just looked too clean and perfect
yeah the default one with the Green
Hills
and the Beautiful Blue Sky with some uh
clouds
um
no I'm not using that now is my
background no no no no but back in the
day XP you know
yeah yeah it's yeah I think it's new
California yeah
uh it was a four-letter word City or so
um and now nowadays it doesn't look like
that anymore it only looked like that in
between like some wine Seasons because
that Hill is used for uh wine
um uh grape thingy
harvesting yeah and Vineyard yeah so
like once they took it down and the guy
who took the photo just drove through uh
luckily and was like oh this place is
nice I'll take a photo so he just stops
his car on the road on the side of the
road takes four pictures and then
continues to drive and he was there for
completely different reason anyway he
was just like driving yeah Napa Napa
Valley
he was just driving
for his job from one place to another I
think
and this just like stood out to him
in the middle of his trip yeah
I just took randomly just a couple of
pictures and then he registered it to uh
just like like something like stock
photo website basically
and then Windows uh owner what's his
name not Bill Gates Right what's the
book
oh
was he the Apple guy or
was it again
[Music]
Steve Steve Jobs
Apple guy Steve Jobs okay so in this
book it he bought that
um stock for the website to add to his
own like there was one for Windows as
well
that he owned Bill Gates well then yeah
he bought he buys this one and then this
was automatically in his like photo
library yeah so it became one of the
options
for XP wallpapers and eventually became
the default one because they liked it
yeah yeah
yeah it's an interesting story
and the guy who like explains it all he
even ends up going there IRL in person
just to see that place
and somehow it was really overall the
video is really like interesting and
inspiring
a little bit emotional even
mm-hmm
yeah now it's a Vineyard again so it
doesn't really look much like the photo
anymore the shape is the same but it
looks different
[Music]
um yeah okay that's it for me my my
tangent reports I hope you enjoyed them
I will now enjoy cuddles with my cats
and then in 13 hours and 20 minutes
you'll see me at somebody's Channel
[Music]
see you tomorrow if you want to be there
be square whatever thank you thank you I
love you guys it was fun today let's
play again and Germany
bye bye
me
what's up good night have a nice day
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's rolling on the carpet
no oh she's stuck
he's stuck
[Music]
she's so good at guessing when I'm done
nickel grenade
oh
she needs a hug bye