foreign
[Music]
God
yeah very nice ladies that was a
wonderful God
good job Happy Thanksgiving
I love that that's actually really good
Kiara I'm glad you came up with that
that's a good one
well done and welcome everybody to
today's well to this year's this month's
I don't know how often we would do this
but it's a food review stream welcome
welcome everybody
wow yeah we got all the yum yums yeah
close enough yeah okay
just in time for you guys to share your
delicious tasty things with us right
yeah I mean we get to see some of your
cooking we get to see a lot of mommies
cooking because I know that not all of
y'all made this stuff
I see I see you gotta help your mommy at
least when she's working a lot of
cooking for you guys for you for you
hungry hungry Mouse that's right dishes
afterwards yeah if you can't cook yeah
just wash the dishes
what is it there's no such thing as I
can't cook everybody can cook you just
have to follow a recipe precisely it's
true exactly it's true I concur so make
sure make sure that you guys are doing
your part okay
no slacking off and then you can at
least learn you know at least everyone
can cook eggs right
yeah that's that lazy yeah yes yes
thanks do you guys like the eggs do you
guys like Kiara's little chef hat
[Laughter]
I was like you know what I I don't have
one too let's let's just wear the chef
hats for um hygienic reasons nothing
else just a chef's hat I miss got a
tiara she's the she's the queen of the
kitchen
um okay I'll say you guys gonna cook for
me or something yeah
that's right all these yum yums they're
yours
dang it what have we done you're
probably doing this before eating
anything was a bad idea yeah I'm hungry
too I said before like I ended my stream
half an hour before this I think and I
said I will go eat something but I did
not
it'll be hard this will be very
difficult that's okay it'll be it'll be
a great way to make you super hungry but
just don't overeat because I know a lot
of you is thanksgiving's over so a lot
of you are feeling that
they're overeating After Effects not
great get a snack though get a snack
snack yep love the smackerels
um so with that being said this fine
specimen that we have on the screen is
from You lyrics actually shall I read
the menu for you ladies it looks so good
it's freaking tasty I'm pulling these in
real time so you may hear like a
snapshot being taken don't freak out
everyone's like oh snapshot Snapchat
it's me just pulling them in real time
because we need to be able to read the
menu so we got some squash soup and
embotido stuffed peppers what the
question yeah there's something right I
think yeah they're from they're in the
same family I think yeah the Mane is a
sizzling bulalo steak
I don't know but it looks good
Brazilian it kind of sounds like ah I
don't know yeah maybe let's see chicken
yeah
someone said Filipino Filipino when you
said the the next thing I was like oh it
kind of sense yeah yeah it looks really
good honestly this like this kind of
shocked me I was like wow that's a good
one a lot of you guys have shocked me
because like you put so much work in
like I feel like you'd open up like in
all recipes like website or something
like that and this would be at the top
as a professional chef and photographer
I must say that the arrangement of how
the plates are placed here as well as
the angle is perfectly in Harmony and
arranged so that it pleases the eye and
makes you very hungry it has like a nice
bread right that's what I call it a nice
spread indeed yes in the perfect uh you
know space in between yes I must
especially say that the soup
the way uh there's like this squirrely
[Applause]
um yes I love the cream
it's beautiful it has like leaves around
it yeah yeah
I'd want to eat the potatoes in the
little bowls they look really tasty
potato
I would like the corn that's corn yes
give it give it to me I didn't even
realize um that this was like a a
Filipino dish because like just from far
away it kind of reminded me of what we
eat in America anyway but now I'm like
looking closely and it's kind of
slightly different
wait what is that green square is that
like a
maybe just an empty plate I thought it
was like a big bottle of olive oil yeah
me too big olive oil oh my gosh I have
no clue what the
maybe it is it looks like an optical
illusion now oh my gosh I don't see what
you're saying it's like above the
chicken
oh
is that like burnt sausages on top
that's the only one I don't want to get
yeah yeah
kind of look like burnt sausages now
that you say it I'm sure though I'm sure
it's great
let's see
oh that might be a banana oh banana leaf
plates
yum yums and then on top on top maybe
it's a burnt bananas yeah but they're
probably good
everything else is good so there'd be no
reason for it to not be good very good
sausage yeah it could be blood sauce I
saw the chef of this in the chat but I'm
uh I couldn't catch an answer about the
burned sausages yeah it's still very
easy though you lyrics very good thank
you so much for sharing I love it we
love it yeah nice job good job thanks
next up we have I hope it was tasty Lord
yeah that does look really good
all right so the next image that we have
here
um that I have not yet put on the screen
I have a I have a question for you
um for you guys what is the best dessert
that you can possibly think of ever like
what's your favorite pastry warm cookie
oh I say warm cookie with like vanilla
ice cream oh yeah that's good that works
too very nice
one of my favorites
what's that one
um you know apple slices fried uh in
breading you know like onion rings with
some vanilla hot vanilla sauce and a
cold vanilla ice cream right next so
good oh I've never is that a real thing
or did you just come here yes no we eat
that here my mom needs to make it home
[Music]
that sounds so good I want some well
right now I'm thinking cupcakes and you
know what kind of cupcakes I'm thinking
is
um
I mean it looks here it looks like they
put their heart and soul into them so I
mean thank you Pia P who says I ran out
of bread and butter but bread and butter
pickles should do the trick I don't
understand
yeah
I want to know if this tasted good
I feel like the cake had like pickle
juice in it it might kind of taste good
because it's like kind of like a sweet
Savory but not with the pickle on top
yeah that's
yeah
I don't know I felt like since we had
something so obviously delicious the
first time it would only make sense that
we get something a little cursed this
time
submissions I've seen so you guys were
pretty good this time and not not trying
to bamboozle us yeah
all right proud of you guys you guys did
well now is it mayonnaise but what is it
Mayo looks like mayonnaise dude you
can't
you can't dude
maybe okay what if what if the bread was
kind of or what if the cake was kind of
like more bready but then on the inside
there was like ham and cheese
that's pretty good actually but less
mayonnaise okay less mayonnaise please
For the Love of All That is decent and
tasty we can make it work but like this
it doesn't look like it's working
necessarily maybe if you take off the
pickles maybe then it's normal put a
blowtorch to the Mayo so it gets kind of
like crunchy on top oh yeah well there
are ways you can work around it
hey well let's get away from this cursed
territory and go towards something
that's kind of amazing
so question what is this everyone
what is this here you're already
bringing this one out now yes I wanted
to bring it out as soon as possible
because I want everyone to see kfp okay
it's
good totally 100 again
yes here I have a question for you
ladies is it cake
have you seen that show yeah yeah yeah
yeah that host and I could have like a
cringe battle honestly it's pretty
insane I want to challenge him take over
his show
um it's definitely not cake sure
yeah well satashi says yes it is cake
the chicken is vanilla cake with crunchy
cereal and a chocolate wafer bone the
rest is laid with chocolate frosting and
fondant 100 editable
yeah there sure is here let me see I'll
go ahead and grab it just so that we can
get the proof you know I'm sure that you
guys want to see the proof believe it
until I say it whoever is actually
coated in cereal yeah a yum yum cereal
and it looks really good because um I
don't know it literally makes it look
like a fried chicken but you know that
it's like sweet and tasty you know here
we go
there it is being cut open oh oh wow it
looks good oh damn
there's like a six layer cake yeah they
put so much effort
and the fondant ah actually you guys
remember the
um the myth and uh that collab Cafe we
did in uh Korea and Seoul
yeah yeah yeah so I when they first
showed us the the dessert menus that
we're getting I thought it was so funny
that my dessert menu was just real Fried
Chicken
maybe it's secretly a cake and it just
looks like a fried chicken and in
reality there will be cake inside just
like this but no it is actually Fried
Chicken so so much from being dessert
good idea though yeah for like a cafe
it's freaking amazing I love it yeah big
skill used here this person has some
skills you should go on that show
although in that show honestly like from
what I've seen the the one that is uh
you know the odd one is usually like so
obvious though I know right I feel like
it's never really a big mystery but they
play it up like it is
I mean it's still good it still looks
like really like skillful but still it's
very obvious and they act as if it's not
so obvious right they're like whoa no
way and I'm like come on oh I have to
think hard about this one yeah what
could it possibly be yeah it looks
different in person you know who could
sing perhaps mayhaps so positive
positive thinking yeah
well yeah that's someone said in the
chat what gave it away was the bucket
yeah the bucket looks um like less
realistic like a chicken fondant sticks
out like yeah yeah it's like elevated
right perfectly yeah but still looks
fantastic honestly yeah yeah it looks
really good if you're not competing in a
is it cake episode
very nice good job good job now next up
we got something on the Savory side so
oh this right here is what is described
as um a hollow mini gumbo
um with all of our like things combined
I guess with alligator Amelia Watson
shrimp gargura chicken takanash Kiara
calamari Nina my internet and Carolina
Reaper peppers with a side of deadbeat
skull cheddar bay biscuits Maury
Calliope it's so good
it looks so good but wait does that mean
that in the curry there's chicken shrimp
and alligator meat because that kind of
like is like a weird mix I thought that
the alligator was like with like the
biscuits looked like alligators more
more than skulls to me
I didn't know real real alligators in
there huh yes yup it pairs it is a thing
but it's just a weird
[Music]
well of course you say it's good you
made it well okay now here's the I've
actually tried alligator before and it
kind of does taste like chicken
ah you know I would not eat this
it looks good but the presentation is
also good I like the skulls but I would
not eat this
well I mean you gotta give things a try
every once in a while are you do you
always eat gumbo with rice I never knew
that and I don't think I've ever had
gumbo what's gumbo
spicy
spicy is like a cherry and a curry yeah
oh spicy yum yums well that's already a
problem uh you don't like spicy food do
you Kiara not really even though I'm so
spicy
yeah I guess that's a good point I don't
know you make a good point all right
let's see well we have this from You
lyrics and then so the next one that
we've got here
is oh let's see it's still kind of spicy
but but you may recall Kiara a special
trip where we went to Hokkaido right
yeah and we had something very very
delicious
Brown
not not the raw milk
um we had something else that was it was
you could decide your spice level right
um but for the most part it was very
warming and soupy wink wink nothing much
not quite we're getting close to getting
warmer we have here some soup curry
from dokudo this looks so cool
we I think they're sweet potatoes
um yeah we don't have Thanksgiving in
November here so I made soup curry and
matcha again
Maita with rose petals very nice wow
and the left on the left back side looks
like um carrot or or Sweet Potato Sticks
but on the right side that looks like a
couple chat pumpkin
yeah I think it is
[Music]
I love soup curry so good the chicken
too hot oops I dropped my phone
yeah yeah yeah Curry udon's the best
once you're finished eating my neck yeah
come to Japan Ahmed I'm gonna come to
Japan yeah I'm gonna try I want to try
we'll go eat some soup curries together
yeah let's go together show you the best
places to eat good food amen oh thank
you yeah we need some some good places
for sure
I'm sure that Kiara has her faves as
well but it gotta be gluten-free though
no no no
we're gonna Risk Everything amen yeah
oh YOLO another thing I could say about
myself
oh Phoenix true well very good this is
this is super yum yum and to me honestly
the tea really sticks out is something
that I just want to drink right now so
with rose petals that makes it so fancy
it's like a fancy touch yeah so it makes
it a little sweet rose petals kind of
have a sweetness to them don't they yeah
slightly
now we've been showing a lot of like
really kind of
um like more intricate or like something
that takes like a lot of effort slash
looks fancy well presented but how about
just a regular ass freaking steak dinner
with some potatoes and and wine Morkie
glass
potatoes so draconic says today is my
grandma's 93rd birthday so I made her
favorite meal to celebrate Scotch fillet
Steak Diane with chips and peas that's
my plate in the photo kind of went
overboard on the peas LMAO that's okay
you gotta eat your breakfast European
I'm just kidding why is the fork on the
right side oh my God
that's really I I can't look at this it
turns my brain around yeah I'm supposed
to be on the other side no
no unless there's different rules for
steaks but no
oh my gosh
Oh Lordy
man that's that's okay
[Laughter]
so now that Kiara has like made made her
her viewpoints on food very fairly cut
the replacement very apparent let's go
ahead and take a look at um a couple of
submissions that Kiara picked here
so let's see this so there's so many
there's four different pictures here but
it looks so good
um so let's see here we got
um save this oh it's a PNG
pee and Jizzle all right one second
I don't think it looks delicious though
right yeah I like having too many
because I really like it the yum yums
are there now here we go it's kind of
small here let me make it big oh yeah we
got a lot of stuff here so we've got a
Ramen weiner Wienerschnitzel lasagna and
Easter bread did I say it wrong [\h__\h]
the w
[Laughter]
oh yeah
um
is that at first you said like wiener
schnitzel Ramen like in the ramen
probably wouldn't be so bad a crazy
mashup what the heck I mean like a Ramen
before with a tonkatsu topping maybe
yeah so that's similar tonkatsu similar
to shinit cell it looks so good
especially the ramen I'm like looking at
the ramen like hey I want to eat that
now yeah give me yeah the ramen looks
good like making ramen yourself I feel
like it's quite a challenge because
there's like so much if you really want
to do it properly there's so much to
prepare and so many ingredients and so
much skills yeah it's really difficult
yeah dang well this is really great
um it's making me this is what has
triggered my Hunger
um yeah my tummy I'm hungry
also by the way if you guys ever go to
our restaurant to eat Vina schnitzel you
have to ask for Lincoln Berry Jam to go
with it I know it sounds crazy but it's
so good right so good it's so good I was
I did not believe it until I tasted it
and I was like oh wow this is the way to
eat this yes yes
you had Venus schnitzel at Ikea um
yeah yeah yeah they do sell so it's kind
of hard to find outside of um you know
the countries where it's really popular
but they always have it at Ikea yeah
because you also eat it with short Pula
the the meatballs the Swedish meatballs
you have it with lemon Barrel Jam too
yeah can my cat
what's up
[Laughter]
[Music]
what was that again Easter bread I don't
really know what Easter bread is but it
looks yum yum
it's kind of like uh um European more of
a European thing yeah looks really good
look at the cat looking at what the cat
looking at lasagna
Garfield hey Garfield that looks like a
good one because it has it has not only
a lot of cheese but it looks like it has
a big amount of what's that white sauce
called again I forgot wait
white sauce is white sauce
um
there's so it looks like it has so much
Bechamel in between and I freaking love
a huge amount of bechamel with my lasaga
um
which so looks very yum yum good stuff
good stuff really hungry thank you for
sharing this with us and making us even
more hungry
um would you be able to eat any of this
no
no no
oh
my God are those scrambled eggs on the
plate with the Schnitzel maybe I can eat
that no no potatoes buttered parsley
potatoes yeah
let's go we can make a gluten-free
version of schnitzel I'm sure of course
oh yeah yeah probably must be possible
thank you I think gluten-free for the uh
for the next spread of food we again
have a beautiful four picture spread
over here oh my gosh look at this look
at this Thanksgiving Masterpiece from
moon dog
yeah wow these are the leftovers they're
wait those oh no there's so much
leftovers two days I guess that's just
taken apart the bottom left one yeah
yeah
it looks like a big old turkey it's a
good looking bird even though the cold
cuts starter plate already like looks so
freaking good I would chill out with
some wine and eat this with the ladies
yeah just just talk [\h__\h] about life eat
some some cheese on crackers yes I see
like a lot of effort was put into this
lots of herbs on that bird I love it
yum yums
here I mean stuff I'm gonna take my put
my hat all the way yeah my hat's in the
freaking way what is that that's just
the carved turkey or is that a like
lobster on ice
oh huh Let Me Take A Closer little
look-see it's oh it's the cut up it's
the cut up chicken turkey there's like
stuffing there's brussels sprouts
cranberry sauce but yes the cut up
chicken looks really yummy it does
really good and one thing I'm gonna try
this too yeah
it looks like they had all kinds of
different pies for dessert like it looks
like they've got
um uh an apple pie
um a pumpkin pie and uh it looks like
there's nuts here um it's the Nutty The
Nutty pie I think it's
um what is it what is the peacock I'm
such a dumbest yes I'm fine
here I'll go ahead and throw it up on
the screen because it does look pretty
yum yum here we go
oh this one's a JPEG I don't know why it
just keeps switching on me here we go
behold the many different pies that they
have here and there are quite a few of
them oh you guys had so much desserts
I'm looking forward to Christmas dinner
now what the heck
starting to get angry
angry are you getting to hang out and
they're not sharing with me
I'm sure they would if they could
but what can you do right what can you
do you guys
I had an apple pie yesterday with
caramel ice cream on top it's so good oh
my God it sounds freaking amazing oh man
what the heck those are tasty hey
caramel ice cream that sounds freaking
incredible oh my Lord oh yum yum oh yum
yum sealant accent for a second freaking
incredible eh you're freaking incredible
oh my god
really really freaking amazing food you
guys speaking of desserts lovely yum yum
desserts uh Kiara you recommended this
one as well
it is a delicious uh strawberry looking
cake that we've got here
one moment now I didn't even I didn't
know what this was at first I thought it
was some kind of like alien concoction
but not it looks very interesting right
yeah strawberry Charlotte they baited it
culinary school
s made yeah it looks like a bunch of
cinnamon or what it is called these
rolls cinnamon rolls yeah
looks like a brain though this would
make a great Halloween dessert I feel oh
yeah especially if you add like some
color uh uh food coloring yeah maybe
like a light pink one to give it an
overall pink tint yeah yeah I love it I
bet it is
like monkey bread we pull it apart maybe
monkey I don't want to see a cut from
inside like if it looks like this from
outside with the rolls facing the
outside I wonder how it looks from
inside oh yeah good question I would
like to see it cut open yeah that would
be cool
oh wait what was it called can we uh
it's a strawberry Charlotte
strawberry Charlotte is what it's called
oh
it looks so different and
those completely different
why why do they make a difference wait
oh
strawberry short this one looks more
like a Tiramisu but strawberry cream
yeah I know I know the one that comes up
with your Google but it doesn't look
like this
yeah it doesn't look completely
different one one stock photo that looks
like that I see okay Charlotte Royal oh
okay oh yes yes yes yes yes oh yo it
looks so fancy if you cut it up inside
most of them is like cream oh pretty
what the heck I'm going to make this one
day yeah Kiara you could make a really
good one I bet
oh man bacon Master oh so it's just
swirl cake that you cut up and then you
put it around like a bowl a bowl of
cream or something cool oh
that looks so good what the heck thank
you for sharing thank you Yuri this is
really cool
so the next one that we've got here is
um a special a special
um
selection that features a friend who
isn't here but I wish was here
we've gotten an Ina lunch box oh yes yes
in a lunch box you know in a lunch box
do you see the fact that the tentacles
kind of reaching to go outside
oh my God
yeah it does kind of look like a bug I
bet it's yummy though I bet you got the
yum yums hayate takoyaki lunch I made
the other day the little eater is so
cute yeah
oh yeah you're right there there is a
meatball there's a bunch of stuff in
there
if you bring this lunchbox to work your
colleagues will be so impressed yeah
Senpai is gonna freaking love you
trust trust Senpai is gonna love you for
real I wish someone would make this for
me
we're gonna make your own lunchbox I
know right I really want to learn how to
make my own bento box but you know what
would be so cute
way ever
it's like five again or so yeah then we
could
um like make a lunch boxes and then it's
exchange lunch boxes wouldn't that be
sweet yeah yeah like secret santa but
with lunch boxes yeah secret Bento I
love that cool just gotta make sure that
the one that Amma gets is gluten-free
exactly whoever is in charge of ahmeds
needs to be careful but that's okay this
one's also mine this is another one that
you recommended Kiara this is from
Hunter
um I cooked too much to show all my food
but here's some of the better looking
ones wow we got a chef here okay
all right this looks freaking amazing
the fire in the background's so
aesthetic yeah it's a french onion soup
oh my bee looks cheesy too there's fluff
is some salmon or so oh my God they're
cooking this outside you guys can't see
the full like Grail yeah sure but it's
outside on a grill oh barbecued soup I
would hope to not have open fire like
this inside yeah I know that's true
true oh my gosh so you're like an actual
Chef huh
[Music]
chef with an S no chef of a culinary
student fine dining cook ah that
explains it
yeah that explains it this is your time
to shine
that this is a person who knows what
they're doing if you look at the plating
on the top left
true that is true what is that balsamic
vinegar drizzle
yeah they have like the fancy guns yeah
very yeah there's a lasagna right it was
only very popular I love it looks like
it's got green beans in it it looks like
a green bean casserole but I'm not sure
yeah maybe
what's easy or yum yum very nice job
thank you so much for sharing Hunter I
love it wow I want I want to do some out
here
I'm hiring you
you got the job
very nice and next up we've got this
here which is another
um Kiara recommend that's got a big old
Kiara on it it looks like a Kiara over
ice a fried chicken
I didn't chose it because of that I
chose it because uh especially the top
left is they seem to have recreated one
of the burgers on the kfb menu you
should write it out sure we have kfp
Kotori Burger
um very nice Kiara omu with fried
chicken
and then we have a I'm gonna butcher
this see off bulky with fried Gilda
and tonkotsu ramen which is what I'm
interested in home cooking oh I guess
I'm eating Ramen today
[Music]
oh my God those eggs look freaking
delicious
yeah
they got the best color ah they look so
they're cooked to like Beyond Perfection
I freaking love love eggs
how did they make that keep one of face
it's almost right so it must be egg
oh and maybe maybe they used food
coloring right maybe that looks like it
took a lot of work
I'm gonna say because the yolk sometimes
can be pretty orange on its own so maybe
the hair is normal
but they kind of food coloring for the
Hat oh true yeah that is that could be
possible either way the top left the
burger you can keep that photo until I
one day make that contest of people
making uh menu items from the kfp menu
I like that all right you got your
submission right there we got a winner
yeah let's go you got to keep it there
my dude the next time we got a bunch of
stuff here that there's just a lot going
on but gosh does it look freaking
delicious so
we got simple zucchini and basil and
Parmesan spaghetti oh yes and then we've
got I've never heard of this one koshadi
Egyptian national dish
it's freaking good yum I would eat this
I'd eat the heck out of this that looks
amazing
um anchovies
yeah oh those are anchovies I'd still
eat it though
um and then we got rainbow couscous
salad with harisa baked chicken I love
couscous
salad with grilled chicken oh my gosh I
can eat that I can use you can eat that
cold and warm it would both be good I
think
yeah freaking amazing and then lastly we
have chicken mushroom and kale pie which
is their specialty Jack's specialty
those mushrooms look sick and very flaky
bread I love it
no you don't like mushrooms huh yeah
but I love everything else that's on
here and I'm really curious about the
Egyptian Nationals yeah
yeah I'm curious too I want to know I
wanna know more I'm gonna go look it up
later I want to find out where I can eat
it
oh I'm sure you can find some place that
has Egyptian food in in Japan yeah
somewhere somewhere somewhere
right yeah and yourself oh that's a
really good point actually Kiera you
make a really you know you make a good
point there uh I ought to do that it's
better to cook things by yourself
sometimes instead of looking endlessly
for a restaurant to give you exactly
what you're looking for
that's good yeah well since we've been
looking at a lot of really good food how
about
um a little more on the a little more on
the basic side what is that something
from V faction people often tease low
calorie meals but I'm here to show you
that they are good indeed spaghetti
alvery Dente avocado toast minus the
avocado water soup and a hearty helping
of three whole eggs a nice balance of
protein carbs and Air
you faction
yeah KR is not impressed
Kiara doesn't like this one
hahaha
or not you should be angry too because
they're not taking it seriously
I mean it looks like they put a lot of
effort into put a lot of effort into
this one
you can't you gotta you know understand
not everybody can be a Master Chef just
doing their best you know
I mean well I do understand some people
eat raw eggs okay yeah for the for the
is it the protein I had raw eggs um at
Mel senpai's house we had raw eggs with
Sukiyaki and she made a really good
tsukiyaki we dipped the meat and then it
was good
I mean that makes sense but the
restaurant
I'll get it I'll get it away from in
front of your eyes and replace it with
some yummy Pizza are you amazing you
made us laugh thank you oh yeah the
pizza
from L5 Guardian the first is the best
pizza ham and pineapple
what do we think about this here the
pineapple you like pineapple and pizza
right now but love it love it love it
love it's cold because I don't like warm
fruit oh yes I agree I agree I meant
honestly
gotta include that fact in the
conversation that warm fruit's kind of
yucky let's be real
but but I see this person has been
definitely practicing their pizza making
skills I want to get into that too
because there's like a whole whole
science about it right and getting the
the dough rides and airing it and like
breaks for ages yeah spinning it I guess
and getting the right flower
the most important is the freaking
flower that's Mori oh yeah
that's right yeah the flower I can never
figure that out I just go to the store
get a pizza that already has stuff on it
and take everything off
[Laughter]
marinated by everything that was on it
oh it's kind of like everything pizza
but I take off like everything yeah take
off to everything yeah it's already got
all the essence in there of a lot of
delicious stuff
now this is really interesting because
they made muffins out of out of a
Thanksgiving dish that I love which is
stuffing would you guys eat this what oh
yeah they're stuffing muffins my sister
and me made muffins out of stuffing a
thing we do every Thanksgiving
have you never had stuffing before Kiara
Thanksgiving stuffing
oh my gosh this looks like the stuff is
the stuffing it's bread marinated and
Bone juice
bone juice that okay well the way that
Ahmed describes it is not organ juice
okay that is not really the best way to
describe but it's the bread is is light
and fluffy and mochi mochi
um and here let me see stuffing recipe
just so I can read out to you so it's
really quite delicious celery onions and
butter tossed with bread cubes
and then topped with broth basically
which is the which is the bone juice
it's the it's the yummy turkey stuff
like yeah I kind of assumed that you
stuff your turkeys with vegetables nah
you help it with the bread and then you
take it out I guess so yeah usually you
get when you buy the turkey it comes
with like a packet inside that has all
the gizzards like the heart and like uh
all of the organs and stuff and then you
take it out you're supposed to make
broth with it so you make the broth and
then you use that with the stuffing and
you put veggies and stuff and you put it
inside the turkey and you let it cook
while it's in the oven
he knows what she's talking about wow I
actually didn't know that's how you
that's how you make it
you put it in a turkey or do you put it
somewhere else I don't remember I mean I
just eat it off the plate
stuff the turkey oh
normally you don't eat it but then you
there's people who take it out and make
this out of it and eat that separately
it's like a way to use the extra parts
oh I want to try yeah no it's super good
like every time that I go to some kind
of Thanksgiving party or Thanksgiving
event if the stuffing isn't on point
that there's something pretty much
determines how happy I am with the meal
to be honest this looks yum with the
cranberry sauce right next to it I
really want to eat these
very well done well made I have to I
have to get myself adopted by some
American family for one Thanksgiving
only and join their Thanksgiving dinner
at the police chat I'm sure someone will
somebody will now this is homemade bread
[Music]
it looks like you can pull it apart and
it'll be really like not stringy but
like soft fluffy
and even had garlic like a garlic sauce
inside really tasty
um
oh man that would be perfect do you not
like garlic Liam I love it so much I am
I am you know back in the days when
people used to use Facebook uh I used to
use Facebook too and I um was part of a
garlic baguette lover
they were just like every day they would
post pictures of garlic bread and garlic
again and everything garlic with bread
and ah that just sounds super yummy I
feel like I'd lose my mind every day
having to look at that because I
couldn't eat it
yeah man now the next entry here is
something I thought was so sweet and
shows the true love and devotion for
their Oshi so we've got from here it's
from X key potato who says hello there
these are some cakes and desserts I made
to commemorate lamy's three birthdays so
far the big yukimin one is a chocolate
and Tequila mousse cake the one with the
bowl so cute it's so cute and the
cupcakes are her mascots next to the
dessert they each represent isn't that
so freaking cute look at this
looks really good what's opera cake I
never heard good question I kind of want
to look it up
I really like the top the top left one
is so cute it looks so fluffy like a cat
buttercream almond sponge what the heck
oh it's so adorable you put so much love
into this and like you did a really good
job you must know your stuff
yeah amazing
that's not like decorations make it look
like it's literally like from a store
like so professional and aesthetically
please oh wait and it's got a snow globe
I wonder if it's made out of like sugar
oh yeah oh yeah maybe that would be kind
of cool that would be next level that
would be next level but I love the
little like beads in there as well that
look like snow and the mascot the
Devotion to making the mascots look so
cute
so adorable you really did great and
you've even got the acrylic stand and
the plushie wow the the oh she doesn't
know what it tastes like the ocean the
the devotion oh [\h__\h] no I don't know oh
she devoted oh she devotion oh she
devotion cycle really so amazing I just
I I love it
um and to be honest I feel like you guys
also you other
um like deadbeats investigators kfp
members you guys do cool stuff like this
too I was gonna say where's mine but
then I was like ah nah you guys do cool
stuff like this all the time I always
see this kind of stuff in the tags so
thank you guys speaking of things
involving us
there's uh I found a pretty cute little
dessert submission here I don't know if
you might know that when I'm I saw it
yeah these ones so check this out I
think it's dong is it dongle yeah
[Music]
I like to make food but I don't know how
to take photos I made some Holo dangos
AME is lemon flavor Kiara's caramel
flavor and Cali is Grenadine flavor plus
some blue tea and purple soda grenadine
you don't know what grenadiness oh it's
like um it's kind of similar to like a
cherry
um a cherry you had to drink cocktails
yeah it's yum yum a pomegranate I like
Paramount oh I like caramel I was I'm
surprised it wasn't orange dough but I
like caramel too yeah yeah I mean yeah
so close enough I would say honestly I
feel like caramel fits your personality
for whatever reason
yeah that that's what I think well
because you like so many like like
sweets and like baked goods you know I
feel like caramel's used more often than
orange but I don't know yeah I think
that fits it works
it works either could work twisting
misses okay Wawa's favorite drink is
orange soda oh yeah that's true
okay yeah that's true that's true now
[Music]
cute little faces drawn on them yeah but
I I don't think I've ever eaten dongle
that are like like a fancy flavor like
that oh I guess it takes some level of
skill to be able to like know how to
make it because I have no clue where I'd
even start so yes what looks like the
Yum Yum's here no Starbucks flavors yeah
ah you're right oh my God yeah you
mentioned that before Ahmed that we're
Starburst flavors now that you were here
it's so true I don't know what it is but
that sounds good oh I'll send you some
yeah
well whenever Nick next time whenever
you come into my neck of the woods I'll
have some ready for you so oh yeah I'll
get some Starburst I'll make you try
them on stream I want to see your
reaction because they're yummy all right
now you'll be offering me candy in the
woods oh yes
this is uh it's like I'm a sacker so
this is a cheesecake made from scratch
and it's a Blackberry no-bake cheesecake
this is quite looking good
oh my god seriously so delicious the
comment here says reminds me of a
Jackson Pollock painting
oh cake I can imagine it tasting amazing
but it looks like it's crazy yeah it
does look like a painting
it's so good though
see this is the kind of dessert that
like I see and I immediately want to
just take a slice out of it I love this
kind of chaotic stuff can you see the
screaming faces
I see butterflies
yeah it's pretty I really love this it's
extremely extremely a chicken's brain
what the [\h__\h]
what on Earth
where where are you seeing that
chicken's brain I see it don't you see
it sure yeah oh wow it's horrific my
eyes
oh man well anyway this is
what does give is that
yes
I'm gonna remember that
so for this next one I love all right so
recently
um Ahmed did um a turkey baking stream
so I thought I thought of Amen when I
saw this because there's a little omelet
coming out of a turkey
this is from Nagi detecting yeah
where's the anatomy difference between
the turkey and the chicken no clue
bigger oh just bigger right just that
yeah there's no no size comparison then
it's hard to tell but I guess they're
small this is wider oh yeah there's a
little bit in there I actually I'm kind
of weird about eating turkey these days
because I actually have wild turkeys
like near my house
yeah I have a family of wild turkeys
that comes and just visits me
they might attack you no they're so cute
well whenever I come outside they like
kind of gently walk away there's like a
little turkey family they're so cute I
won't mess with them though forget that
yeah no no I'm best to not mess with
nature because you never you never know
when a when I was like maybe four
Millennia or so I ran um over to like
the the lake where there are a bunch of
geese and um I was throwing bread at
them and like I threw it like at their
faces and they came out from the water
and chased me and geese are frinches
yeah I tell you what Natural Born
Killers I love bugs yeah well of course
you do Kiara you love all the birds I
took more pictures of burps during my
trip to Rome than I did of Rome oh my
God why am I not surprised
but it was a combination of verbs in
Rome uh sitting on uh you know ruins of
archaeological things so you know that's
fine pigeons and seagulls and stuff yeah
yeah oh cool these cookies are so cute I
saw them they're by Katie thank you so
much sugar cookies
look at that it's it's mithras first
sounds like she's wearing a crown but I
think it's just a plate yeah I had the
the snowflake um
it looks so good I want to sink my teeth
into them me too the good one looks
funny cute yeah it does I want to eat
all of them I want to bite someone's
head off and take a picture of it oh
cool that would be kind of casual I'm
crazy yeah it looks like I'm dead she's
like huh like she's scared like no Cali
you can't you wanna what nothing nothing
my eyes grow wide ah speaking of grumbus
check this out we got a classic steak
potatoes and
and there's something going on back
there is this are these veggies red
cabbage rabbits red cabbage
those are dumplings they have potato
dumplings noodles
this looks so freaking what now that you
say that they're not just normal
potatoes I'm like okay all right this is
kind of interesting yeah I want to eat
this a lot here red cabbage with some
you know like
um like uh meat from what's it called
sour broth
yeah and and the bread dumplings this is
a really popular famous combination here
especially for like Christmas or so they
eat it are you supposed to like cut off
a slice of The Dumpling and then put
cabbage on it and then put meat on it or
something because that's how I need it
you can if you want to get all the
flavors at once in your mouth hell yeah
hell yeah hell yeah yeah I want to get
like a little bit of a little bit of
like each
each thing at this at one time and then
yeah just just shove it shove it on in
into the mouth oh yeah I meant like uh
yeah I think I did mean venison Venison
and uh elk or stuff like that I don't
know
oh not elk but what's the the female
version of the elk yeah okay then there
and uh
like similar similar kind of animals
not beef no not the beef no that's not
meat looks like beef to me but I'm just
a I'm a dumb underworldian American song
no because only if it's only the thing
that makes moo and pork is only the
thing that makes only
that's the best way I've ever heard that
described Kiara yeah
I freaking love that very good
um next up here what we have since we're
on an international roll right now is I
think that this is Filipino dishes again
but they labeled them for us very kindly
wow yeah Ube cake I want the Ube cake
but that's the only thing that was store
bought apparently oh yeah and the cream
cheese brownie I guess but I had a
desserts yeah the Restless though I
don't like scallops but the rest I will
eat yeah
before
yeah it looks like a noodle
good stuff that was really delicious
it's like a pie or something
um
it's a fish
oh looks really tasty though everything
here I would gladly try everything
because I love trying things right I
can't guarantee I'd like everything but
cream cheese brownies I can guarantee
I'm like
yeah thank you so much looks yummy I
hope there's some stuff that normally I
would not be able to eat here so it's
special definitely you gotta try things
in your life now this I had to choose
because of the bacon wrap the asparagus
you gotta get the bacon wrapped
asparagus this one's from General thank
you very much looks freaking delicious
it looks simple like you can just you
know wrap the asparagus season the steak
throw it in the oven wait a while and
take it out and eat enjoy that's true
that doesn't look very healthy but it
does look yummy yeah
there needs to be some potatoes you know
I was told I was I was taught that a
dish always needs to consist of you know
the Meat part but then the vegetable
part and also I think it was some some
kind of like I mean
um
yeah yeah yeah something like that I
don't know how to translate it anymore
but it has like it needs like three
parts of you know like a little
Illuminati triangle
yeah okay yeah
it's got to be balanced balanced like
all good things but this is still
amazing I wanna eat quite good yeah I'm
thinking to myself where's the rice
where's the bread where's the potatoes
you know they're on one of those diets
they're just like kettle or something
you know
oh cute oh I don't think they'd be
eating would they be eating the red I
don't know how keto Works honestly I'm
not doing that but
I don't know if you can eat red meat
maybe you can I don't know keto Bros let
me know what you're supposed to do keto
Bros keto Bros
um and then here we've got what I can
only describe is this is definitely
homemade that's not an insult it's not
this it's just got that homemade
this pizza has like a really fluffy
fluffy crust on the pizza yeah it was so
good
oh this definitely has lots of carbs in
it for sure I only a keto diet could eat
this because keto is apparently no carbs
no carbs at all dang it so I guess you
could eat you could eat some red meat
but dang this is like carb City but you
know what I'd eat it I got a salad up
there I can't really I think it's a rice
bowl yeah
the Caprese salad they call it a salad
but of course it's mostly you know
cheese and tomatoes the Tomato counts I
guess basil yeah basil Kelly what did
you just say basil no before that it's
Capri salad who said you said it's just
cheese and tomatoes I I said it's mostly
cheese it's amazing
I mean I love it don't get me wrong I
just think calling it a salad is a
stretch
that's all oh
salad it's a nice starter yeah but you
know the bezel with a good olive oil
[Music]
pasta or something I don't know how to
say that
the antipasta I like that I'm gonna
start off with a little anti-pasta
because it's not the pasta so it's you
know like the opposite of the pasta
fruit that's a good point never thought
about it that way so here we got a
Tomahawk Steak now this looks freaking
amazing
weapon is that potato salad yeah uh yeah
I mean Tomahawk Steak with chimchuri
deviled egg potato salad and roasted
brussels sprouts I'm sure you know what
you're doing here I can't imagine what
it tastes like but it looks good
what's a Tomahawk Steak what's the steak
taken apart by a tomato
uh that's a great question maybe it
originated from that I actually don't
know
uh I think it's a name for indigenous
people North America possibly like a
group of people but they use the
tomahawk as like a weapon it's like an
ax I knew it oh maybe it's just called
what people are saying it's the shape of
the the steak if it's like an app
yeah so it's the LMAO the shape I guess
so okay
right the meat looks nice and tender
is that what I don't think
oh maybe [\h__\h] I don't think I have ever
had a brussels sprouts before what but I
heard that children hate them and they
always get uh forced to eat them by
their mothers in America they're dumb
because brussels sprouts bang I that's
right I feel like I would like them yeah
a little bitter like they kind of have a
kind of bitter aftertaste but you're
supposed to dress it with stuff that
cuts through the bitterness but it's
tasty yeah it depends on how you kind of
cook it as well like I I cook mine for a
long time so a lot of the bitterness
goes away I dress mine in like a little
bit of Can't Believe It's Not Butter
um and I Can't Believe It's Not Butter
yeah that's I mean that's the way to cut
down on the calories man look just
trying to do the little things I'm just
laughing about the name it's funny I
Can't Believe It's Not Butter I mean
because it's not bad
it's something it's something that makes
the food taste okay oh but oil yeah yeah
something yum yum maybe in German it's
margarine yes something like that oh
yeah yeah let's check out these little
cookies
look at how freaking cute these are
gosh I can't even I love how they kind
of made you know it looked like stitches
on the side yeah on the edges it was
like it was like stitched as if it was a
sweater or something yeah so adorable I
bet they tasted great too everyone's
little mascots look so cute where's
Council make a council one next yeah
yeah Council rests yeah yeah those guys
in the cookie batch next please I love
baked goods that are themed around it is
time for Christmas cookies ladies true
oh my gosh dang got a new Christmas
cooking cookie baking stream or
something like that I think that you
guys should make
um a famous Christmas cookie that we
have here
um it's called vanilla
if there's vanilla in it I'll eat it
it's very Vanilli it's so cool
where the crumbly it falls apart easily
but it's so good one of my favorite
Christmas cookies anyway what do we have
that was amazing so this is a big this
is kanzeni the noodle dish
um
these good old memories taste good so it
looks like this kind of looks like
Sukiyaki actually this looks similar to
what me and Mel Senpai made last night
you put a bunch like uh cognac noodles
um I love the long white mushrooms a
bunch of meat and um
you throw them into a hot pot and then
you cook it cook it a long time with
sauce and then you put it on top of rice
it's really good we've got like a
homemade got homemade burger patties it
looks like there's these are veggies
inside of a burger patty it looks really
good I would eat this with cheese on a
burger
this is yum yum thank you so much for
sharing these good old I don't like most
of these ingredients but it looks
fantastic you don't like mushrooms oh
God I keep forgetting that mushrooms are
good oh what's that
what's that book look at this
it's orange featuring my dad's cooking
so this is a 30 piece Dad let's not get
it twisted all right um roast duck oven
baked second pick is how it's sliced and
presented we got sauteed prawns
mushrooms and onions with avocado in the
first pick Chinese roast pork belly and
orange chicken
yeah that duck looks like it went to the
tanning salon for just the perfect tan
the perfect tan it looks so good oh my
God chicken
looks different than like turkey or
chicken skin to me it's like super taut
yeah it's tight I was gonna say yeah
like much tighter they do the squats
with the Ducks do the squats into the
two squats oh man and they apply night
cream every night before they go to
sleep and that's why they're tight
incredible are you on this one I'm gonna
eat it orange orange
and purple very good yeah this is very
orange themed bird Cuisine that I
thought you'd appreciate Kiara
I do yes I do do you do you say do you
enjoy the orange stuff I do you know
very good and then we only have a couple
left so here we've got
oh
this this looks healthy and delicious so
this is called Casa lemena a popular
dish for my city in Peru it's made of
potato vegetables and chicken
accompanied by salad it's easy to cook
and 100 recommended it looks like a
sandwich you eat with a fork yeah yeah
or like a little lasagna mix sort of
thing so what's the yellow made out of
the Yellowstone I think no yeah I think
it's potato
yeah
something like that I don't know it
looks good
I want it to be potatoes
oh mashed potatoes pepper oh
puree
freaking nice very good heck yeah looks
interesting definitely did not see this
ever anywhere else ever before right
this is egg yeah
thank you
looks like a chicken to me chicken face
huh you're coping hard right now no wait
no wait you said this by Christina
Manzanita right
yeah but now I can't unsee it so
that it's a pink and the little eye
right next to it
yeah
let's go with that let's go with that
I'd like to get the cursed imagery out
of my head so
oh
you just you're just too deep into the
amokus yeah I blame where are you
looking see I'm all good now let's bring
it up
here
stuffed peppers
stuffed peppers before Oh many times
this is so freaking I mean you mean bell
peppers right yeah my dog or bread so
it's ground beef onions rice and
seasoning all tucked inside the bell
with a nice tomato based sauce for that
juicy goodness okay without the pepper
yeah it's so easy to make and my mom
used to make it so many times when I was
younger and we and my my my siblings we
did not really like it that much but now
I appreciate it
yeah I love bell peppers very good
extremely yum yum this you can tell
these are the yum yums
homemade yum yum homemade yum yums
seriously so so freaking good
thank you very much for sharing and uh
let's see I'm gonna go ahead and grab
one more the bell pepper the reason why
they do this is because they have the
perfect Hollow shape you know so around
you have so much space to put something
inside that's why people like to stuff
bell peppers oh yeah that's a that's a
good point actually man I'm not very
good with the spicy
um but if it's like like a sweet banana
pepper it doesn't have to be spicy yeah
true exactly now you're so gross you're
so right I wonder if there's a picture
bell pepper and they've ate cereal out
of it or something
[Music]
next time next time I run out of dishes
um to use for my experience I'll see if
I have a bell pepper
now this is the last submission that
we're gonna look at this is feta cheese
wrapped in bacon with healthy fresh
greens I thought it was crab legs I know
right it kind of looks like crab legs
thank you very much yeah yeah that's
good yum yeah you gotta have you know
healthy Greens on the side if you're
gonna have
bacon wrapped feta cheese I guess
yeah this is a thin slice yeah that's
true oh man actually I bet it is
probably pretty pretty low pretty low in
the unhealthy category so yeah yeah I
can appreciate it
being big in yeah oh good point why
what's Canadian bacon
healthier or something yeah I think it's
a different fat content maybe that's
what I always thought maybe not bacon
this looks very tasty well done and
that's just ham
this ham oh Canadian bacon is just ham
yeah different
yeah
yeah people saying Pizza
interesting I'll look into it it's yum
very nice thank you for sharing and this
isn't really a submission but I found
this in the tag so
um oh they're laughing at this guy but
they don't know that he made the noodles
baked the bread harvested the eggs and
collected the water himself
called out
bread does not look homemade uh-huh
oh maybe you never know maybe they're a
Master Chef maybe they they work at a
fact if the noodles were homemade they
have would have a regular shape and
would be like all messed up and fake
yeah
maximum benefit of the doubt right here
I love it and also harvested eggs well
how about you try making those eggs
yourself first before you start flexing
on us well hold on a minute
yeah Kiara tell him
look at kfb they make eggs all the time
it's true it's true first thing just
harvesting you're stealing my kfp eggs
man yeah you can't ice cream for someone
else's work you can't hell yeah it's no
good
been well this has been very fun you
guys I had a good time looking at
everyone's yum yums with you
you watch it you watch it
I slept I wanted I wanted to make a joke
it's joking
but yeah it was a good time I'm glad
that you invited you too because I feel
like you guys are like I wanna I don't
know maybe not cooking well actually I
think both you are pretty good at
cooking never mind I take it back I was
gonna say you guys just seem like
cooking aficionados are like really
strong cooking appreciators you know so
I had to invite you guys over
well I mean throughout this whole stream
I have been carrying my um
oh true very serious about this stuff
we're getting ready to dig in of course
it's so good
did you smell it yeah it's delicious
Fried Chickens making me want fast food
but I cannot yield I gotta stick to the
doctor review this turkey
um oh oh wow it smells like turkey
juice like all over her lap Yara you've
been holding them this whole time
oh yucky gotta clean that up man
yeah
those are called Virtual Worlds we can
clean it with a finger snap yeah I guess
that's true enough yeah that's true
wobble gobble gobble well anyway guys
thank you so much for coming this is a
lot of fun thank you for coming to my
house for a food Fiesta thank you for
having us thank you for all the
submissions too everybody thanks you
guys and there's a lot more that we
didn't get a chance to look at so if you
guys look at hashtag Holo yum yum you
can see everybody's delicious and trees
I still need to browse all of them and
I'm gonna go drop some likes on them
find some inspiration on what you're
gonna cook for dinner next time or if
I'm hungry yeah I need some inspo so I'm
gonna go look at more of you guys
submissions in a minute here
um while I'm chilling waiting to get
ready for the the Singapore panel so
yeah thanks for giving me something to
do you guys and uh thank you very much
ladies I hope we can hang out together
again soon that would make me happy yeah
that would be cool
yeah that was one thing I wanted to say
but it doesn't quite fit anywhere
I'll say it
around clearly well clearly all of you
all of you don't own an air fryer
hahaha
yeah where was the air fried stuff you
guys I didn't see anything
oh maybe it was buried somewhere in the
submissions but I could not find a
singular air fryer dish so true what's
going on it's a conspiracy
get it together
get it together you guys well do you do
all the airfryer no you don't either
what is it dude you just put something
inside of a pan and I cook frozen stuff
with it because it's faster
but the actual like big meaning behind
it is that for example if you you know
fry some fried chicken in a [\h__\h] ton of
oil it gets very oily and you use up so
much oil but in an airfryer you only
have to use like one Spritz of oil and
you save so much oil it'll be much
healthier so that's the thing about the
airfryer
yes and if you can Grill it or bake it
or cook it then you can usually make it
in an air fryer
cool yes okay I guess I need an air
fryer yeah I know I don't think you need
an air fryer indeed well when I get when
I get my house I'll get one because I'm
curious
get a big kitchen so you can place an
airfryer yes air fryers take up a bit of
space to kind of turn the teeth whoa
chunky fryer
yeah okay I'll get one then I believe
you guys I believe you're recommendation
well I mean if you guys recommend it to
me I don't know you speak very highly of
it so I'll get one it's the
sophisticated Choice Kylie it's the
superior Choice okay I trust you
yeah well anyway guys we're gonna go
ahead and hop out do you guys have any
announcements that you'd like to make to
everyone
I'm back welcome back
you all uh we're happy to have you back
thank you thank you how about you
anything to announce
uh no sorry
no problem there's not always things
going on we're both on YouTube music
week we are we are come check us out you
guys both me and Kiara YouTube music
weekend whoa get ready
gonna be very fun
um
and uh just so you guys know I was
planning on playing Pokemon Scarlet
today at um at 10 A.M jst but then um I
remembered iris is debuting her brand
new outfit so go give Iris love yes
today the 26th oh yeah so we'll give her
some love guys I'm gonna move the stream
until uh after her reveal is over so um
so yeah just so you guys know
um that's tomorrow tomorrow wait isn't
it tomorrow
ha
come on calendar
no where are you yeah calendar
well thanks I'm glad I'm glad I know now
yeah good that you found out now
otherwise you would have moved it for no
reason right that's okay I'll just take
an extra long nap I need the extra hour
anyway okay
okay yeah okay guys well I'm your Maury
I hope you'll remember me and everybody
please continue eating yum yum foods and
enjoying life because eating yummy foods
is part of enjoying life
[Music]
we'll see you guys later bye-bye
peace peace
foreign
[Music]