[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
do
ah
please hold on
[Music]
press any button
do
[Music]
almost there
huh
[Music]
okay
where's my screen my my wii u screen
flickering
the [\h__\h]
where's it flickering
you good
you're good wii u
phyto
okay hello everybody
[Music]
oh
hello
sorry for the wait uh
i mean it's not real uh
that much of a weight
right it's just fine it's not a big deal
hello welcome to
the beginning of
the legend of zelda the wind waker hd
[Music]
yay
i
wanted to play this
for quite some time i told you guys one
day i will play wind waker on my channel
i told you
and here we are finally the day has come
i've prepared for this
i bought a wii u
um because you know i played it on the
gamecube but
uh the wii u has an hd remaster that
really does look better
and um
supposedly maybe it's easier to capture
i don't know maybe there's other reasons
i think you guys gave me some reasons
why i should get the
wii u remastered version but
i have a pepsi with me hoping that it
will
keep me energized at least for a while
probably it won't do much it's not an
energy drink
um
ah
i had a pepsi in my fridge because i got
it for free for ordering a pizza
somewhere sometimes they give um
sometimes pepsi is like
comes for free with those pizzas
okay of pepsi
yeah so um
i downloaded and installed the game
um i tested capturing the wii u
but what i did not do is
test the game itself
um
because i didn't have the time
and also because i wanted to
have that moment every moment of the
beginning uh with you guys um so uh we
might be up for some
uh
bad surprises if
if it turns out i should have tested it
out just uh
but but it's probably fine
should be okay i mean you see a wii u
screen right now i see something else on
my
on my
what's it called gamepad
what is that thing called again gamepad
i see something else there
now now i'm actually um
a bit uh
should i cover up that camera i'm a bit
worried now
maybe i should cover up that camera
thing that the gamepad has
uh the wii game we pad the wee pad
gamepad um
yes
let me get some tape uh
i have tape somewhere why did i have
tape
i know i have tape somewhere
wait wait wait wait wait wait where did
i have to just in case i mean the game
is not gonna show my
camera right
oh dear what's happening is it turning
itself off turn yourself on again
people people there you go
there you go come back to me why does it
switch i still have like profiles from
the previous people who owned it
um
there's a little bit of an interesting
um situation
i
wanted to originally buy a new one but
then i realized oh they don't
sell any new wii u's okay
so i first looked for
um
like
secondhand ones from to buy off of
private people because i was hoping to
buy it in a set with the game from
someone and perhaps with some extras
um so i i contacted someone from the
second hand website thingy
like a marketplace
uh sorry the pepsi is coming up
um
and uh and and and then uh you i guess i
told you guys so you maybe remember
uh
like
two or three days later that person
wrote to me oh i gave it to someone else
now because they picked it up personally
because i would have i was gonna have
that person send it to me and they
already said okay
but then they gave it to someone
directly so i was like okay [\h__\h] now i
have to think of another way to get a
wii u i was looking a bit more for the
marketplace but i was like [\h__\h] i don't
want to deal with the all these stupid
ass private people
they're not reliable so i was like [\h__\h]
it i'm going to a secondhand store
or like not really secondhand store it's
just like a game store but you know the
wii u apparently is only being sold
secondhand or like
or or selling it from
like maybe not like
there might be new products but those
are things that new products that people
bought before but just never opened up
so yeah um
we're kind of like gamestop but not
quite as professional
i think gamestop would have been more
professional so i went there and i i
um
bought the wii u from an actual shop
and
you know paid full price for it i think
i don't know what was the original price
of a wii u
actually i'm i'm interested
to know that what was the original price
does anybody know
like in url
oh
what
oh there are a lot of different prices
300 for the black model
oh well then maybe i did buy it cheaper
oh i guess i bought it cheaper
oh they are cheaper now i thought they
would sell it more expensive now because
they want to make use of the fact that
you can't buy it directly from nintendo
anymore
oh
so yeah they had a white one and they
had a
uh they had a white one and they had a
black one and i didn't even know that
what the [\h__\h] the white one has like
how much space one
mb or something like that
uh like basically not even enough space
to have one game on it uh in some cases
apparently
okay it's one gb no one everybody feels
like one envy um and then the the black
one has actual
and actually enough gb
to put some game on it
uh
was it 16 i think it might have been 16
32 maybe that's another version
i think mine has like 16
well maybe it does have 50 i'm not sure
but i just know it has enough so
so
yeah
so i was like it what the [\h__\h] that's so
weird but okay i'm gonna get the black
one then i guess
8gb on the white one
42gb on the black one that's such a
weird choice i wanted a white one if it
weren't for the size um
and then uh
yeah i bought it i was gonna buy the
game too but i didn't have it but then i
realized oh
oh
you can buy it from the e-store
so
uh
i i got the wii u like week ahead of
time or so i think
uh and then
uh sorry that i did it last minute but
it all worked out fine in the end but
yesterday oh it's gonna turn itself off
again
yesterday uh in the night time yesterday
i took the day off because i was very
busy this week really and um needed some
time for myself and i also played tales
of her eyes for six hours yes yes six
hours
[Music]
and then
after playing tens of rice for six hours
i was like okay i probably should
prepare zelda now and then go to sleep
and first have some dinner
and
so
i
packed out my wii u which wasn't packing
it out because it was not packed at all
and
i turned it all out and i
it was very fast really easy until the
point where i turned it on and i
realized oil
there's there's other people's profiles
on this wii u
they couldn't care to do a factory reset
really
there's actually a whole family's
profile on here and it's it's it's not
only the fact that it was annoying to
factory reset it myself because it had a
it had a pin code on it that i obviously
didn't know that i was not told
and you can't you can't go into the
nintendo estore if you don't have the
pin code and you can't do a factory
reset if you don't have a ping called so
don't ask me how i did it but i did it
and then um that's not the only worry i
have
isn't this a problem with you know
datton shoots data shots uh english is
uh data protection whatever
because i was able to see
that families like email addresses i
i saw a full um email address of the
mother or whatever
um
yeah
that's kind of [\h__\h] but i mean they
will never know because i will not write
that lady an email obviously like hey i
got your got your wii u from shop but
they didn't they didn't do a reset so i
know your email address now
[Music]
um yeah that's uh i think that's that's
not well even if that in by law it would
be fine which i don't think it is
even then i think
you should
you should reset it so i don't know
other people's like
profiles and email addresses it's kind
of weird
yeah it's kind of weird
yeah um so anyway i i have figured it
all out and i downloaded
i bought and downloaded the wind waker
today
so okay
uh my only
um
[Music]
concern is some people told me there
might be some sound issues we'll see
about that actually yesterday when i was
just on the wii u screen the sound was
fine so
i don't know
uh
okay and this will be our new series
uh it's probably shorter than skyward
sword so i think we're good it's not
going to be it's not going to be five
years of this game don't worry
uh
[Music]
godzilla
everything is good everything's cool set
to stare what
i didn't really check anything like that
uh
what
is that the stereo and nuts around
let me check that
one second
let me see that just in case
yeah some of you guys sent me some
troubleshooting stuff already in case i
have problems with the audio
i'm just hoping things will go well on
its own why does the wii u load so long
for like opening up system settings or
opening up uh the home screen again it
loads like a full minute
oh my god okay uh
where's uh
where's your sound settings
um
are you hearing this
i mean if you hear this shouldn't it be
fine or do you think it will be
different once i'm in uh
once i'm in the game
we shall
here it is
yeah it was correctly i fixed it that
was that was something else
[Music]
oh
oh it does show something else on
what the [\h__\h]
wait a minute
shut up
oh i wonder if my
is the game gonna be german
what shut up
shut up
your menu
i'm not showing you on purpose right now
by the way
ah
tape on the camera if i know there'll be
a hardware malfunction
yeah that's so true i suppose um
wait a second
[Music]
yeah wait is the game gonna be german
because the switches that we use jim
wait why does it always bring me back to
that stranger's profile i didn't
actually end up doing a reset actually i
just added my own profile and i can
literally see the other people's
nintendo network ids
this is so wrong i should not be seeing
this
who fought who who
delete this user can i delete this user
yes delete delete
delete your existence
ah my i don't know how this is annoying
after putting in the pin code you have
to put a password for nintendo idea
[Music]
but my own or the one from that person
yeah i think it means the one from that
person i can't delete them
it needs my pin code but that their
nintendo network id which i don't know i
know i mean no i know their nintendo
network id but i don't know their
password
uh
shut up
let me go back to my there we go
let me go back to my own profile
i don't know who these people are
i don't know
mm-hmm on my password
but i can set the
uh i can set the language
of the wii u to english no
i'm gonna be [\h__\h] if this is german
maybe i should have oh [\h__\h]
shut up
stupid
um
why did it kick me out of there anyway
okay we're opening system settings again
wouldn't you guys like to i mean he
doesn't talk anyway
wouldn't you guys like to see wind waker
in german
um
yes yes
it's so confusing that there's two
screens to look at
where are the settings that i'm looking
for
audio video
maybe this one because i don't see audio
settings i just see ah default audio
there's tv audio and there's gamepad
audio
which one should i
look at
let's see uh
how do you read a guy with this gamepad
surround aha stereo there we go
okay i'm feeling dizzy why am i feeling
dizzy
and then just in case of the tv one as
well i guess tv our audio video
ah
uh-huh should i change something right
here here it is stereo
okay
okay back that's fine now the language
where do you change the language
out here
espana
italiano netherlands portuguese
that language setting will now be
applied to the wii u gamepad
this may take up to four minutes okay
then let me get some
tape brb
let me go get some tape
where did i have to take tape somewhere
[Music]
what
so
[Music]
i found it
found it
oh it looked exactly like that face
not a whole dog
i found some tape for sure
so
let's put several layers of the tape
okay it's still setting the language
sorry i did not think of that
normally when i when i get games on my
switch they're always english because my
switch is already set to english and on
my steam it's the same thing
it's just been like that for a while so
i didn't think about it
[Laughter]
all right and then hopefully the game
will be english right it should be
english then right right right
you don't need to tape the camera we
gotta do stuff like that just in case
you always gotta go safe
security red
ah
um
use the wheel gamepad oh by the way um
i
i i know that
uh
if i play with the gamepad sometimes
you guys
won't see
certain things
like the inventory and i i thought we'll
just test it out today if that's like
bothering us but if it's a problem i'll
get a
pro control of
but as far as i know i mean it's not
that important
um
[Music]
yeah
i was like at the store they offered me
like a pro controller but i wasn't sure
like
at that moment if i should get it or not
if if
because it was like 60 bucks as well i'm
like
is that worth it why do i need a do i
need a pro controller
the switch controller doesn't work right
i i assume
um
it's not a problem use the game pad um
i do also might want to get it just
because the gamepad is huge
it's so big and chunky
um
i i don't know how i will feel about
using it for several hours today but
it's um i think it's
kind of chunky and big
language set to english done
okay
nice
i set everything that needed to be set i
think
surprisingly comfortable
i guess so
i don't know
uh it does have great battery oh i mean
i have it connected
so
yeah it's okay the cable is really long
thankfully
okay what the [\h__\h] why are you telling
me about that miiverse [\h__\h] the miiverse
don't care about the miiverse i want to
play there we go
no let me play
what are you doing stato stato
estado let me start
laughs
[Music]
everybody
[Laughter]
[Music]
me
this is exactly what you're supposed to
do with uh with this case no tactile the
what's it called in english
is it called the windwaker
oh i think it was a very obvious name
because in english itself and japanese
it's also causing no tattoo which is the
title oh this is the wind waker
[Music]
sorry
oh
[Music]
i have a cat hair in my eye
okay
it's still there but
[Music]
i never noticed that before there's a
wind waker like you know where usually
there's just just one
one
one line
[Laughter]
okay
yeah god
oh my god
oh my god i'm so excited
this is but one of the legends
of which the people speak
long ago there existed a kingdom where
golden power lay hidden
[Music]
it was a prosperous
land blessed with great oi i want to
sing and breed but one day a man of
great evil found the golden power and
took it for himself
[Music]
with its strength at his command he
spread darkness across the kingdom
but then when all hope had died an hour
of doom seemed
[Music]
evil's vein he sealed the dark one away
and gave the land lie
[Music]
this boy who traveled through time to
save the land was known as the hero of
time this is the story of ocarina of
time right right it was the story of
some previous game the boy's tale was
passed down for generations until it
became legend
[Music]
but then a day came when a fell wind
began to blow across the kingdom
[Music]
the great evil that all thought had been
forever sealed away by the hero
once again crept forth from the deaths
of the earth eager to resume its dark
with
the people believed that the hero of
time would again come to save them
oh no
but
the hero
did not appear
faced by an onslaught of evil the people
could do nothing but appeal to the gods
in their last hour as doom drew nigh
they left their future in the hands of
fate
left on red
what became of that kingdom
none remain who know
the memory of the kingdom vanished but
its legend survived on the wind's breath
[Music]
on a certain island it became customary
to guard boys and green when they came
of age
[Music]
they aspired to find heroic blades and
cast down evil
[Music]
the elders wished only for the youths to
know courage like the hero of legend
outside island
[Laughter]
[Music]
but
[Laughter]
oh my
hey god is my favorite spot to gaze out
at the sea when i play with the ghost i
call it ariel's lookout
in german they call this island
preludian which is you know like a
prelude
[Music]
so do you remember what day it is today
wasn't it someone's birthday
even hers or mine
you still have a sleep aren't it's
probably his you know he gets the ring
garbage
[Music]
oh i didn't realize i was i was moving
my head in the same
vibe as she was
[Music]
i'm just gonna stay here forever and
listen to the soundtracks
[Music]
don't eat her don't either don't eat the
girl
go away
go away bird
[Music]
it's leaving no it comes next no no go
away go away
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh no it's gonna get eaten
bad ending
when the [\h__\h] is it so close to me
did you forget
what did i forget
big brother it's your birthday
that's why grandma has been waiting for
you to come back to the house she's been
waiting for a while now she's gonna
[\h__\h] die waiting for you
it's a good thing i came to find you
you should probably go home and see what
grandma wants don't you think
[Music]
oh my god oh my god it's so weird that
the right stick is above the
buttons that's really um weird gotta get
used to that it's so far away
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh
[Music]
oh my god
the boats chop thingy
oh that bridge i remember
that's up there i remember yeah yeah i'm
not looking forward to going up there
scary scary
oh the pots the people wearing the pots
um
ah the water the water that has no
texture but i love that i love the
the style of this game you know
this really [\h__\h] long uh ladder for
me what the [\h__\h] it's always it always
felt like an eternity to go up there
but i want to swim you know what i want
to swim
oh you're right that was stamina oh
[Music]
i'm so happy
okay ro
how do you jump out
oh jump wait
was he not able to jump or does he jump
wait how how did how does does he not
jump
doesn't he jump automatically when he's
like oh yeah right right
uh when he's close for example over
there he should jump automatically
[Music]
can we reach them
oh my god oh my god i'm so happy i'm so
happy this is so beautiful oh yeah
that's that pink it's so cute that pink
come here piggy how did i pick you up
how did i pick you up oh it's so cute
it's so cute the black small pinky is so
cute it's so cute i want it i want
[Laughter]
[Music]
so cute as mine now
you and me picky
bffs
[Music]
hello
oh yeah that dude was a huge [\h__\h]
head
oh hi
press set l right uh there and use a to
talk to me try it set l
except
that l
ah
ah focus
that's correct your smartphone
your my friend have just targeted me you
see when you press that l you can target
certain objects i for one use it quite
often to talk to folks who are far away
from me
of course even if there isn't anything
around to target you can press that l to
face forward you know it's quite handy
indeed
there are a myriad of other ways to use
targeting as well quite an ingenious
little thing if i do say so myself
of course that's not only the tr the
only trick in my bag not remotely i
could teach you a few more things if
you'll just climb up that ladder over
there and drop by my room
alrighty um another time grandpa i'm
gonna go to my grandma
the snot child disgusting
[Music]
disgusting child
ew
[Music]
let's destroy some parts
oh beautiful
[Music]
uh how do you crouch again
how do you crouch i know the secret
why you crouch you cannot crouch yet did
i not learn it yet
[Music]
we're going backwards
so we can all see that face from link
[Music]
into the black hole
oh [\h__\h] this is confusing now
now that was confusing
[Music]
i know there was a treasure but i forgot
what it was
[Music]
hell yeah
hell yeah baby
come by the link
we got the money cash money
what settle
sido
family treasure
i
so i think when i was younger i played
the beginning and some
in between parts maybe a little bit but
i never got to the end alone and i also
don't
think i ever played until the end with
my brother
in either way i
think it's been a long enough time to
um you know play this again i normally
don't play games again but i don't
really consider
me ever
finishing the game
i i don't consider me playing it uh
to be
enough of a reason to not playing it
ever again
yeah
because i don't remember it that well i
think we will see we'll see we'll have
definitely a lot of struggle moments
anyway even if i played it
uh okay
[Applause]
[Music]
oh it's us too
and some nice hot soup
and the chair looks nice
oh she has another picture of my sister
up there
i think she likes my sister more than
she likes me
[Music]
wait a second go down
don't go down no go down
are they too damaged you know they kind
of are
what the hell
okay it's an old game
i just look at everything more detailed
nowadays
hello
oh you got my coops already
i don't like my blue clothes though to
be honest i like them no
i've been waiting for you
[Music]
try these on
time certainly flies i can't believe
you're old enough to wear these clothes
i got the hairless gloves they look like
they might be a little warm for this
weather
his his face she really doesn't like
those it's probably embarrassing for him
um
and yeah
they are too warm for this weather
understandable but come on dude be proud
of it be proud of the tradition and your
history and all that
[Music]
motel
she's his mouth
[Laughter]
don't look so disappointed dear one just
try them on
today is the day to celebrate
oh there's more cute pictures over there
all
it is the day that you become the same
age as the young hero spoken of in all
the legends
you only have to wear them for one day
so don't look so down be proud child
that's right yeah he was in ocarina of
time he started out as a child for a
moment i was like on it wasn't he older
but then i realized oh yeah right there
was a time skip oh yeah
yeah
in the olden days this was the day boys
were finally considered to be men they
were taught the ways of the sword to
prepare them for battle with their
enemies
but we don't live in such an age any
longer always are the ways of peace
beautiful
nowadays i suppose orca is the only one
one on the island who still knows
anything about swordplay
or the shield
hanging the family shield on the wall as
decoration is another tradition that has
been carried down from those days
oh you look amazing in those gloves
oh
reminds me of
some other greenlings
as all this make sense to you
yeah
nothing makes sense
isn't that nice chihuahua they suit you
perfectly a perfect fit
well tonight i'm going to invite the
whole town over for your birthday party
so i better start getting ready
shouldn't i
your grandma is going to make your
favorite soup for you tonight mmm
i just know soup
soup birthday food
okay i just know you're looking forward
to it
now go get your sister our arrow
what was her name in german
don't remember
[Music]
i don't like soup but for birthday i
don't know man
at least i don't know something that i
can bite into
[Music]
a-r-i-l yeah that's that was right
cute pink cute pink cute pink cute pink
i
will
catch
you
[Music]
[Applause]
smelly big smelly pig
what are they feeding you
smelly big smelly big
it's not your fault
[Music]
now
everything is
[Music]
oh my god it rhymes
let's go up those endless
ladder thingies
oh no it's going to happen now isn't it
was now that's so early for it to happen
she's being disturbed by the birds again
[\h__\h] birds
at least back then now birds are better
birds have changed over the years
ah hi
big brother
did grandma make that outfit for you
but wow you look like you'd be way too
hot in those clothes
i guess they're pretty neat though
so anyway yuawa can you
close your eyes and hold out your hand
oh she's gonna give me the looky thingy
i'm going to give you my most tragic
belonging but just for one day oh wait
it doesn't happen now we oh does it like
oh no
uh we go up to the thing and then we
look and then we see she gets
i think that's what that was the order
maybe
uh
or or it happens first and she gets
put up there and then we
i'm a bit confused something happens i
know
you got the telescope
oh it's so cute
with the birds on it
and she looks so proud in the back
oh
the founder of horotoni
yeah oops
never mind set it to y x or r and use it
by pressing whatever button you send it
to do it now and see what you can see
oh yeah no
something happens now because we're
going to look and then we're going to
see and be like
[Music]
so well do you like it
i'm learning about a special gift just
because you're my big brother on
aren't me
lucky
oh why don't you try it out right now
try looking over at our house from here
all right um so we put this oh
now let's put it on ours
[Music]
are you looking at the red post box
oh oh the postman
oh my god oh my god
and now he's gonna be like oh my god oh
my god what's that
yeah i'm looking at it
this is not good enough for you
oh i think it's gonna
it made the sound
ah i'm looking at the post box what else
do you want from me hold
on zoom out
i thought i should zoom in
are you using alpha zoom in yeah yeah
yeah i'm there now it works
oh my god oh [\h__\h]
the postman looks kind of weird doesn't
he what is he doing what's his problem
[Music]
is her name tattoo in english too
probably not or maybe it is
[Music]
get the [\h__\h] fat ass verb
save tetra
we don't know yet but we're cheering for
her anyway
oh oh oh [\h__\h] oh yeah right in his face
noise
but now she falls oh [\h__\h]
i hope she lands softly
okay
could have landed in the water would
have been maybe better but okay
this is so terrible that girl fall into
the forest she needs help
it's too dangerous for you to go in
there and worry about something you can
use to defend yourself with
[Music]
yeah thank you for that hint
what is she doing to make all these
birds come to her
she's a bird boy spurrah
[Music]
i think we can take the shield were we
also able to get the sword or any kind
of sword already
what was that afterwards
[Music]
but i suppose i can
see
the other way around
is he gonna give me the sword now or any
sword
oh oh man
i remember i remember the training of
this dude being very
annoying for me i always have these
problems with the skyward sword we have
the same problem but in skyward sword we
have motion control controls this time
we don't have motion controls
but i hated this guy
but maybe it's not that bad anymore
maybe it was just now that i'm a gamer
maybe now i won't have problems back
then i wasn't the gamer yet i was on my
way to a game i was a gamer apprentice
and now i'm a real gamer
[Music]
yeah okay thank you guys for giving me
confidence
[Laughter]
oh what is the matter
you have an urgent look about you and
something happened
whatever it is from the look on your
face i suspect there is no laughing
matter what do you think he will
i have you come for some serious
instruction in the way of the sword
yes sir
[Music]
oh no
very good your first lesson shall be the
horizontal slice
face me and press b
do not fear for my safety i'm ready for
you
um okay
press only when
okay i shouldn't do fancy
fancy things like running around him
it's okay
would make things easier but okay
oh very good next is the vertical slice
hold that out target and then press b
does that automatically make it vertical
[Music]
how is it
i don't see it yeah i'm i'm trying to
see a difference here sir
okay whatever
it just does whatever though
he just does stream is back
oh
why are we gone for a little bit welcome
back
and this is pressed tagging the zl and
then tilt
from a forward
uh
and then press b
huh
[Music]
[Laughter]
you pressed by targeting with that l
tilting l toward me and i'm pressing me
that's what i'm doing
oh did i do it now okay
[Music]
so just for a moment
okay
you shouldn't
[Music]
there we go
spin attack hold b briefly to build up
your strength
and then release it okay
[Music]
wait can i do it without attacking first
that little
attack first hmm
this is a parry attack target would set
l until you see a and then quickly press
a to perform a defensive strike
uh-huh
what
huh
oh that is so cool
a circle and then me okay okay
uh target is that allen watch closely
now finally jump attack draw your sword
target and then press a
why did i have problems with this when i
was younger
maybe it was like later
a little bit later he still gives you
other lessons doesn't he
there are and wait wait was there a uh
was there um
was there a version for this game on the
wii
or am i imagining things because i
lowkey feel like i played this on the
wii too on the gamecube and on the wii
no okay then maybe not i feel like i was
using motion controls
huh okay
uh
draw your sword target and then ah
yeah
whoa
come at me once more
and yet and yet i sense a certain
anxiousness into sword you hold an
eagerness that goes far beyond to be a
desire to be wielded on the fields of
battle
i don't know i do not know what has
happened
but i have faith in you somehow i doubt
you will misuse that sword you may have
it kiwa i'll give it freely take the
blade with you
[Music]
use it one thing carefully you don't
want to let down the kind old man who
has entrusted it to you
[Music]
i want that big glance in the back that
you probably used to kill big big sea
animals with
well it's huge holy [\h__\h]
i want that
don't tell me i'm too small for it
it's dangerous to go alone yeah link is
left-handed
just we played skyward sword and they
had him be right-handed then which
triggered me
i
because it was motion controls man and i
am left-handed too
and i had to get used to
wielding a sword on the right hand even
though i'm left-handed too and even
though link is left-handed but it's
they made it right-handed there the one
time that i as a left-handed person
could um play a character that's also
left-handed they make him right-handed
too
isn't that disappointing
[Music]
but i did end up getting somewhat used
to it um
[Music]
yeah he's left in breath of the wild
right
i think he's properly left-handed in
every game but skyward sword
that's weird oh so it's a weird
coincidence that all the heroes of time
are left-handed all the he runs up all
the heroes a lot of time but all the
heroes in the legend of zelda are
left-handed
it's like
[Music]
how does that happen huh what a
coincidence
so let's imagine
maybe maybe maybe
maybe maybe maybe you know how um
yeah
over the years uh i think
the people used to um um train
everybody to be right-handed right now
they say don't do that anymore but i
think back in the day my mom told me
that people just made everyone be
right-handed but maybe in the legend of
zelda universe they train people to be
left-handed like ever maybe everybody's
no wait he's right-handed isn't he
that dude is the old dude is
right-handed hmm
but maybe they train people to be
left-handed if they want them to be a
hero because they know that the legend
is that every legendary hero is
left-handed so wouldn't you want your
son to be the legend too maybe if you're
hopeful
so you train them to be left-handed i
don't know wouldn't that be yeah a nice
theory
i feel like it would make sense in some
way
the lord the lord
hey take off my
my hat take off that hat
my tinfoil hat this is all real
let me drink some more pepsi
[Music]
um
well i like this museum too um
since the olden days the sword has been
used to fend off evil
its blade is infused with a desire to
become strong and righteous
mr alky i will be strong
[Music]
i am strong
i don't need to be strong i am strong
[Music]
you guys said
oh wait
i was uh being on a
okay so the jump attack
is uh
wait all right
[Music]
sorry just testing
and uh
then there was one with the surprise
while you wait and then pure way
[Music]
what was that belt again
what's the night's crest
does that intrigue you young one
it is still too early to discuss such
things with you but if you happen to
cross 10 of those show them to me that i
can tell you what they are and what they
do but i will only speak if you get 10
of them i really don't remember what
that was
we learned some good useful stuff
uh first frost attack frost's head was
uh was it b or a
b
[Music]
depends on the enemy which one we're
gonna use i guess but i think most of
the time we can just button smash
[Music]
hello do you want me to go up
is he waving at me
yeah he is
all right
all right i don't care about the
stranger girl
i'm coming
what does she teach me again
i like your place
so soon my my my if you're already old
enough to be wearing those clothes
that it's going to be very important for
you to gather as much wisdom as you can
from now on if you're to make your way
in the world that is kiwawa
now i've been studying a wealth of
topics since long before you were born
i'm what you'd call a big brain
you're a smart little fellow yourself
aren't you
that is true of course i know it's very
noticeable
iq1a
i've been thinking it's time for me to
pass some of my wisdom down and maybe
you're the one i should pass it down to
[Music]
everything that you see tacked to the
walls here's something i've researched
for really and before you ask yes i do
know my filing system is odd
i think it's okay i mean i don't really
have much of a system either for my
things
organizational issues aside however it's
all extremely useful information you
would do well to read it all very
carefully
reading leads to knowing you know
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] what was that
is it the guy from below
honestly the hooligan i'm referring to
is my younger and much less intelligent
brother who lives downstairs
he hates studying all day every day the
loud just exercises and practices with
his weapons does he exercise his brain
no the brains are muscle too i think
i think so
anyway the only thing he does study is
the art of fighting right now for
instance he's been studying fencing and
whatnot as if that's all fatty used to
anyone
he simply does not know how to do
anything besides exercise i ask you
what's a brother to do
[Music]
i don't know how about you challenge
each other
to like
some kind of contest
and then prove each other
that you're you want to prove each other
that you're better but you'll figure out
soon enough that
both is needed at least in this world
body strength and
brain strength
nowadays i would say you can mostly get
by with brain strength or like one of
either
[Music]
one of either will get you by if you use
your body strength a lot then you're
probably a bully in school
if you use your brain strength a lot
then you get bullied but then later on
you'll have a great job probably do we
really need to read all of this
oh my god must you know
lesson one energy of life
stamina okay don't know who's stamina
[Music]
oh
remember that just because one can play
at any time on the gamepad it doesn't
mean one can hide from one's parent
parents huh
i'm an adult
i can do whatever i want
i know my own paint coat from my gamepad
[Music]
[\h__\h] parental control
materials the more things one tries to
experience in love
[Music]
does this game always have so many notes
here what about all these gamepad notes
were they not here
your pose again when i was going to take
time i don't know what you're doing here
plus race plus right here okay
[Music]
oh not to regret the things
one fails to do in life a very important
lesson
okay uh-huh
improving human relations when you
talk to people is this what you're
saying um
[Music]
when you talk to people more talk to
people
um
[Music]
uh
don't worry i'm collecting my rubies i'm
keeping them safe
[Music]
do not give up don't give up never gonna
give the game up never gonna let them
down i read it all
[Music]
okay bye-bye
that was really um
i think
i think i
i never went up here when i would play
the game as a child and to be honest i
realized that was okay
not really much useful knowledge
was given to me
are you
looking for ah you want the black pink
i stressed all wild a lot of pig oh see
look that black one there don't you see
him
this is perfect my wife was just telling
me how she really wanted a pet you ready
to grab it now you can't just run up on
it things are too alert you want me to
capture one for you because i already
captured it before slowly
[Music]
okay no he doesn't ask me i guess
there's no quest whatsoever give me some
brownies
give me some ropes
yeah what the hell is this
what is this grass
[Applause]
all right now we can go very unrealistic
right yeah it should be giving me rupees
in the real world
when i
slice up the grass
it totally gives me a rupees
it does
no no no wait what was it
no
[Music]
i already got the chest you're too late
hello piggy
[Music]
ah these pigs are just so adorable i
don't know man
can we zoom out there we go
all right we're going up now we're gonna
do
uh what we should be doing we're gonna
save the girl
i was always confused as a child and i
still am somehow
uh
about
whether or not tetra is zelda
or some kind of zelda
um i guess she is it's just some kind of
zelda
or
spoiler i mean i played it before
yeah she should come she is right yeah
yeah she is
i i it's been too long i think i
remember something
do it
i'm a bit bad at this
swoosh
swirl attack
oh this way it works
rubies
is there anyone here who has not played
a wind waker
i mean i think everybody knows there's
always a zelda in the zelda game
otherwise it couldn't be called the
legend of zelda right
so
me what
we're not going to spoil much more okay
but
but um i mean i mean you know
eventually you would have noticed that
there's a lack of zelda in this game
hello
[Music]
there's a sneaky music going on here
weren't there enemies here
are they probably going to show up once
i get closer
[Music]
this is so cute oh i love that so much
ah
sonic make sweetie
[Music]
i love it
um i don't know if we should be
careful
i only see one but there may have been
more
but this is the first enemy that we're
facing so it can't be such big of a deal
i have something in my eye again though
that's a problem
a small link so cute sneaky squeaky
i will be fine hello oh
you just fell asleep now
oh you
want me to sneak by
i wish i could do like one of these
allen ring things and stab him in his
back
when he's on the ground i can't do
damage that's so lame
[Music]
wasn't there a finishing attack too when
they're on the ground maybe i still need
to learn that
okay first enemy
failed
small enemy
i failed do it
yeah there we go
oh let's let's go through here
oh ready groupie
you still have something in my eye
link
his face
is so funny
he's like is this lady okay the lady
that's controlling me is she okay
yeah
could i not have been controlled for
something more competent please
can you go up how am i supposed to get
that rupee when it's up there
ah okay whatever oh come on kiwawa more
progress
actually i might be kind of thankful for
the auto jump i know sometimes it still
can
fail and if you don't aim carefully you
might jump off a cliff or something but
mostly i think
it's pretty useful
thank you for the membership thank you
oh there she is
where should we go just
uh here
ah
[Music]
more enemies
more enemies to fell no problem
[Music]
good job i'm a part-time warrior
i'm a part-time warrior
and a part-time hero
come on
i will i will catch you
probably oh i didn't sorry
moment
[Music]
i'm a hero
look at me
wow what did that gun up well whatever
so where am
i oh that's right that giant bird came
in
this moose control
oh thank goodness we're
when i saw you get dropped under
somebody i fought for sure
oh
summit
or that bird dropped me on top of a
mountain
well wasn't that nice of it
well don't just stand there let's go
time to repair our dab to that burden
full
more bass what about this boy
don't worry about him come on
yeah i like i like her she's cool
she can
mostly usually protect herself she's
cool she has an attitude
oh
harassed by birds again
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
dude
insane
stupid kid get a hold of yourself she's
gone
there's nothing you can do
my sister it's my birthday she's my only
guest in my birthday party
no one else will come
what you want to come with us on our
ship
[Music]
do you understand what you're asking
we're pirates you know pirates the
terror of the seas
what do we get out of bringing some
helpless little kid along with us i'll
tell you what we get a headache
i know you must how you must feel with
your sister having been kidnapped and
all but that doesn't really have
anything to do with us now does it
oh and how do you figure that out it's
him
[Music]
just talking are you where do i look at
off putting it on someone else's
conversation
i forgot how i did his voices was like a
few seconds ago and i already don't know
how to do it anymore
too many voices in my head
please all i mean to say is that if you
big bad pirates had come to this quiet
little island that poor girl wouldn't
have been snatched away by that bird
and just what do you mean by that
just be quiet for a moment i'll tell you
now as my work entails delivering
letters i spent much of my time
traveling amongst many different islands
as a result i hear many things
haven't any of you heard word that young
girls have been getting kidnapped lately
from all regions of the great sea
no matter whether you've heard it or not
that seems to be the case young girls
with long ears like yours have been
getting kidnapped never to be seen again
and unless my eyes fail me the young
girl who was just kidnapped from this
island also has long ears does she not
much like you do miss fearsome pirates
oh no putina senpai is in danger hide
funnier senpai
we need to protect her
put it outside gabon
my point is that the bird mistook the
poor girl for you and that's why it
grabbed her
now correct me if i'm wrong but i
believe it was young kiwa here who saved
you from the monsters in the forest
wasn't it
[Music]
is this true
oh and while i'm at it
i may as well tell you that bird that
kid that both viewed kiwa's sister has
made its foul nest to the north on the
heights of the forsaken fortress oh no i
don't like it oh no
the forsaken fortress
isn't that the place where
[Music]
what are you going to do
under the circumstances i don't think it
would be unreasonable for you to give
kiwawa a little help now would it
yeah just give me a lift
uber uber ship
huh i don't need you to tell me that
even if i were to consider it lately
i've heard nothing but even rumors about
this forsaken fortress
can't possibly mean to go there with
nothing but that jeep of the sword
that's not brave but stupid
i mean come on even a sing something on
the island like this has to have
something you could use as a shield you
know something to protect yourself with
anything
tell you what if you come back with
something like that it'll let you stow
away on their ship
oh and one more thing once we leave you
won't be coming back here for a while so
you better go say goodbye to your family
while you have the chance
i don't want you getting all way behind
and homesick on me
oh
[Music]
yeah i won't be gone for a while
[Applause]
uh well
i know exactly
where we have something that could
protect us
you guys might have an idea too
[Music]
but first let me get those rupees behind
those trees and i want that one up there
too how do i get up there again
[Music]
can i even get up there right now
probably
a pig lets me fly wasn't that a chicken
where are the chickens
up there up there
grab a pig and fly are you sure about
that it was chickens i think
well where are they
[Music]
chickens
or seagull or something
what what
[Music]
to stop running
comply
i'm the hero
you must comply
[Music]
stop right there
hands up in the air
okay
good choice otherwise i was gonna make
yakiniku out of you
there's no way this will work
[Music]
pigs don't fly i mean look at this
nothing flies here
i was gonna give you the benefit of the
doubt but
it sounds like a whole lot of [\h__\h]
to me
or pig [\h__\h]
there you go freedom freedom is yours
all right um grandma
no you don't necessarily want to give it
to me if you're worried but i need this
does the shield
please hey
what is it chihuahua please tell grandma
what's troubling you and where is arrow
oh no
is she still playing outside with the
girls
yeah yeah
don't worry grandma
it's gonna be all right
[Music]
grandma yep
grandpa
okay wow
this is so sad
[Music]
i mean sweet but sad
is this what you're looking for
how did you know
take it with you
anti-climatic scene
down you're the hero's shield this is
the legendary shield said to have been
used by the hero himself
hold that eye to defend yourself while
holding the sword you can move around if
you defend while targeting
wow
oh
i guess it is true
oh don't make me cry
[Music]
amusing and the grandma it's gonna be
okay
arrow really has been kidnapped hasn't
she
oh
she's crying
[Music]
i heard a voice crying
and come on
[Music]
what kind of monster could take such a
sweet young child
oh how safer i'm the hero starting from
today
it's my first duty to save my sister no
no first studio was to save tetra on the
second duty is saving my sister oh my
god i'm so sorry oh it's it's
that was
it was dangerous
[Music]
oh almost fallen down to the table
grandma
[Music]
oh well
bring your back as soon as possible
don't worry
[Music]
we'll bring her back
right away
oh there's more people now
wait before
we go with them
let's check the um
the shop
harry's shop
oh
[Music]
welcome to beatles shopship i deal with
pretty much anything and everything
do you have anything you don't need if
you do show it to me i'll pay top rupees
for your junk
or do you see anything you would like to
buy
or just use lots of browse
bait bag this holds bait is quite useful
uh
huh what kind of bait
oh
oh for animals
should i buy anything
do i need it for
and the paper prepare
pretty ah the bag is useful
buy this first okay
i'll buy it i mean i'll leave it
eventually probably for something
[Music]
eight pouches for storing bait
nice
you're the greatest i'll never forget
you i'm going to make a members card
just for you when you buy lots of things
to build up your point something good
will happen yay memories guides
nice
my shop is kind to its customers no
other shop will do
this sort of thing for you i'll have you
know
now we have one point saved up
30 points okay
uh i guess should i get the bait too
can i only buy paint or
can i also like get it somewhere
for free
i can watch his memory streams you know
i would love to watch his membership
streams
he's great
only buy
okay
and we'll buy one
i don't remember
what we had to use it for though
[Music]
okay now i'm good now bye
i will
be gone for a while oh but i love this
is like this is like van life but with a
boat
look at this hammock
just lives in this boat
sounds like fun
okay
[Music]
wow that's a the crap the crab pit
what does that mean
old shield are you sure you can still
use that thing are you going to get
splinters and cry hey you're so mean
well whatever if you're ready then let's
go
are you ready
am i ready
is there anything i should do before
leaving that i can't do later maybe
thank you for the membership welcome
adding a toe
falling apart
it looks fine it's not falling apart
pig quest
kidnapped the pigs we need raisins
i already got 100 rubies
in the very beginning
rehoming the pigs ah
yes let's do that
let's do that
um do i have to talk to the lady first i
wonder let's talk to elena first i think
it's up there at that house
easy peasy lemon squeezy
i'll help you lady
hello you lost your pigs
how did you do that
okay walmart you look cute there's a
look at that outfit i suppose i should
congratulate you on your birthday
shouldn't i well to tell the truth i
could congratulate myself too we just
finished building our little hutch and
product today isn't it a delightful
addition to the place i was actually
thinking of getting a pet and keeping it
here the boys would really like that i'm
sure boys love pets
huh
i wonder what kind of animal oh wait
ah she wants the the black pig what
about the bringing all the pigs here
what okay it's life these days listen
dairy
yeah
okay maybe maybe there was only the
black pig quest
okay okay okay
[Music]
i'm on the roof
i'm on the mother effing roof man
[Music]
i'm on the top of the world i wanted to
no i wanted i wanted to go down
yeah but not fully done i was scared of
fall damage but okay
wait for me
if she doesn't like this then i don't
know what else
[Music]
i am absolutely in love with these pigs
it's eyes are dead though
there's no light in this pig's eyes
but the only going sounds so cute
i'm going going
there you go
right
what do you say
[Music]
why did you bring that little pink
little hole in here just for me
oh thank you thank you so much i've been
thinking of getting him past pig for a
while now the boys will be so happy when
they get home you sweetie wait isn't
this kind of
kind of mean that you know i get the
credit for it because her husband that
was the husband right
was already like eyeing the pig and
hoping to get it for her for his uh lady
and i
just
do it instead and get all the credit for
it
in front of his eyes too
he couldn't catch them yeah but like i
could at least i don't know work
together with him catch it for him give
it to him and then let him get to get
the credit
from his wife
hmm
i don't know feels kind of
kind of i don't know like i'm like i'm
in interrupting or getting between them
also i have a snack i'm going to eat a
little snack milk
a sweet snack and i have some salty
snacks for later we are very prepared
for the stream today i'm i'm low-key
tired but at the moment it's still
um
under control
[Music]
only 20 i expected more
okay now she wants more
okay and why not do it why do i not look
well what do you mean
[Music]
um
maybe i'm being so realistic but i have
another worry
the quest is for me
to bring basically literally all the
livestock that they have running around
here
to her
just because she wants them as a pet now
so she will have a monopoly
on all
all the livestock here
that worries me
[Laughter]
she will either
just consume them all herself and they
will have no more livestock here
or she will sell them for [\h__\h] ton of
money
and be like you know
uh
a mogul yeah
maybe i'm worrying too much
[Music]
um i finally heard ariel's voice cry
from far away is it is it really true
yeah unfortunately
get me that [\h__\h] pig
you run fast piggy
i would already have you if uh
the a thingy some would always work when
i'm close to you
unfortunately
i often just roll into you even though
there you go i should be able to pick
you up
oh sneaking
ah never mind we don't need that
sneaking is for losers here's one more
piggy
uh there was one more
uh let's go let's go let's go
i
really like being on this island
ah there it is see am i not stealing the
pig from them
i want to stay on this island for as
long as possible because we'll be going
on a long long long journey
on a pretty
lonely journey sometimes
you'll feel maybe a bit lonely
stupid pig
[Music]
what is this guy doing there by the way
oh wait would you pay me if i win your
garden
no
yes he will
okay
leave it to me
get rid of all the kusa
yeah and i don't want to kill the pig
got to be careful but you're kind of in
the way there piggy
[Music]
i want to do all the side quests that
are possible here
before we leave
and enjoy the
o.s.t here
you got to move now
oh i didn't
[Music]
what did i get
huh
didn't it sound to you guys as well like
he was implying that it was a quest and
he would give me something
huh
[Music]
oh so is the reward whatever was in the
grass
[Music]
you chose to swim instead of getting
picked up by me
[Music]
there we go all right
cute wobbling out of the water very cute
[Music]
all right piggy
have a new home for you
is so cute
and you have new friends here all
together
yeah
i brought you another one yeah it's so
cute
[Music]
and i have a 20 should i talk to her
again she's gonna give me another 20.
i did find another one you realize it
yep yep yep
[Music]
ah happy birthday
see i should have done this not on my
birthday because then maybe i would have
gotten a birthday present and these
rupees but okay
okay i think this quest is done
so
let's go
or is there something with these shitty
children too
you want something
are you somewhere
no
none of your business
[Music]
you know my sister is
she's gone
i love those crabs
those crabs are so cute
sorry guys i'm really enjoying
everything
in this game because i was looking
forward to windbreaker so much
you don't understand
wind waker is my childhood game
even though i never finished it i just
played it with my brother and watched
him play it
but you know those are memories
those are beautiful memories
i really like the
graphics too of this game i know there
were a lot of people who were like
cartoon what the [\h__\h] but i love it
i love it
[Music]
it's so cute
it's so iconic you know
um
all right we can go
i'm ready
wild graphics too
um
but you know and i wouldn't want to see
breath of the wild with these graphics
obviously that
wouldn't have made much sense but for
wind waker i think this is
this is beautiful um
[Music]
go
oh this music is great too oh wait
didn't i forget something
[Music]
aren't they gonna be like oh i forgot
something
take care of yourself
oh
grandma grandma
come on
oh
oh it breaks my heart
it brings my [\h__\h] heart
[Music]
we're having a moment
are you sure you shouldn't just quit
right now seriously think about it
i can tell you're just going to get more
sentimental from here on out
there's still time you know
are you sure we shouldn't just turn
around and take you back to your island
no
i'm fine
i'll do it for her
do it for her
do it for grandma
stupid
cheddar
[Music]
the big blue boys turn the [\h__\h] full to
starboy we heard for the dolphins
there's a trip you're really creeping me
out standing there like that so quick
here stay out of my way way out of my
way
hello
[Music]
always get stuck doing the hardest work
it's a real world dealing i'll tell you
it sure sounds like english happy to
probably not be the bottom rung on the
pirate ladder you bet he is
i won't don't sweat it i'm sure you'll
do just fine so long as you don't
disobey him
uh what who
what are you talking about
oh look at the
sun is already setting oh
we're already so far out
sign an air skill level right
that's one way to get up you got on
there so what's the deal as i pop your
back on your island or what now that i
think about it though i think i've seen
an outfit like that somewhere before
yeah i'm the [\h__\h] hero okay
you guys better stop making fun of me
right now
right now let me get to the top
yeah big open sea
so many fish in the city
voice acting presented to you by kiwamo
hello
[Music]
yeah and i don't know why william
turn around right now climb down
or i'll push you don't care if you die
you'll be our dinner tomorrow
put you in the hot pot
yum yum yum
he's a freak
[Music]
i
remember wasn't there some kind of
popcorn here
well stop right there this is miss
tetra's cabin most of us real pirates
aren't even allowed in you there's no
way we're letting an outsider and don't
you even think it
i
am
um
wondering like how
this little girl
she's supposedly very young too
got this whole crew like how did she
become the captain of this
ship
how
oh that's where i came from oopsie
so i think we gotta go down here and uh
do some kind of parkour or something
like that
another one
okay my knees hurt but
this is a hero's life
oh wow now hi dance mommy hey today oh
i'm real sophia nicole no i promise i'll
go easy on you so you do as i say okay
all right now first off you have to take
the test all new pirates have to take
it's a bit of a doozy so get ready you
want everything i'm about to show you
real careful like so you can grab it
until you no doubt must be swabby
first off you got to press this switch
this is the only easy part
just walk up or to it and tilt
this two step on it presto switch
pressed
hey
you see
impressive isn't it now check it out
after the platform dries out from the
floor you gotta jump on them
[Music]
okay so i was able to jump to this first
one by myself well the next one is too
far right that's why you gotta do this
watch
watch me
if you jump right at the rope you can
grab onto and use a swing
swing until you get close enough to the
next platform you've played
the other day wasn't it yeah you
probably already know how to do this
hey
piece of cake and do you think you get
how to doing you have to swing from
platform to platform and try to get to
the entrance of that room over there
here's the problem though suave the
platforms only stay race for a little
while so if you don't get there by the
time they drop you have to start over
yeah better be quick just like me
it will probably take you at least one
year before you're good enough to make
it all the way here one rough here one
tough year full of bumps and bruises
of course if you manage to do it fast
i'll reward you now give it a try it's
got to be good for chuck or two
okay nico why are there two buttons
absolutely deactivated
uh-huh okay
okay
uh let's give it a try i guess
it jumps automatically and wait does he
hold on to the things automatically
he does okay
[Music]
yeah how much time do we have
easy
what do you mean puzzles somebody just
in the chat said puzzle took them here
at ages what you did it already
oh man that unravel play through with
coyote must have really paid off
i wonder how many people in the chat
watched it even though it wasn't on your
channel
maybe next time because you didn't
finish it you can continue it on your
channel so kfp sees it too
good idea
that's what i planned anyway thanks chad
i'm proud to have you as as my underling
[Music]
i i wonder if it's okay to just give
that to him
i don't see why not adopt i'll get
busted
all right slammy i'll tell you what you
can have the treasure in that chest over
there it's your reward from the great
and january sneaker
good for you if you fall don't want to
wait for the time to run out yeah yeah i
thought so
[Music]
what channel
coyote channel
uh
whole live sixth generation
gamecube version has much wonky or
physics for the revs yeah
i think i remember having more issues
too yeah yeah yeah
i guess it's better now that's good
[Music]
let's get the treasure
oh nice trash is it a hard piece could
it be a hard piece or like a
i don't know something else something
good must be something good
[Music]
oh a bag
i have to get from enemies in this handy
pouch
hey kiwala we've reached a forsaken
fortress already oh no
this is
[Music]
gonna be
bad i have a feeling that i'm gonna be
struggling a lot in the fortress
that guy could also do it
yeah i don't like the fortress it's
scary i remember it being scary
and tough especially with all the
stealth going on
and then you get then you get [\h__\h]
brought back to the very beginning if
they find you so
i'm gonna be so [\h__\h]
yeah
like it's
it's like a huge hurdle in the beginning
of the game the rest is like
chill more or less like
um there are some chill parts but then
then they suddenly throw this [\h__\h]
stealth fortress at you right in the
beginning and throw you back to the
beginning every time you make a mistake
that is so frustrating as a beginner for
the first time playing that game
oh
here i am up here
okay i'm coming up
i guess you're oh [\h__\h]
oh we're really here and the big ass
bird is over there on its nest
give me back my sister
give back give back
what were you doing with nicole
don't tell me you were playing some
stupid game for treasure when you
doesn't matter
or whatever there is something you need
to see have a look over there
that's the cursed isle known as the
forsaken fortress
there are all sorts of strange rumors
about this place what i do know is that
long ago it used to be the hideout of a
no good group of pirates we used to
compete with
aha
but they were just small time now the
place looks like it's pretty dangerous
huh i knew it look
over there
oh oh oh
rap
let your hair down make it easy for me
please
over there by that window
have you ever seen so many seagulls
flock like that before
oh
the seagulls oh they followed her
that that's so cute
or it's different seagulls but they just
all flock to her always because
she just smells good or something
i'll bet you anything that's the place
where dave got your sister locked up
[Music]
but it looks like the whole place is
under a really tight guard
let's go metal gear solid and barrel
this won't work we'd be spotted before
we get anywhere near the land near
landing there
all right aren't they gonna shoot me
what do we do now
[Music]
avoid
it
and barrel
[Music]
[Applause]
why would they not notice that something
flying in the sky like that
there's no guarantee they wouldn't
notice that
just listen to
zelda link struggle endlessly
playing fighter
bye dog
look don't struggle if you really want
to get into this dangerous place like
that this is the only way to do it trust
me
we pirates do this all the time don't
worry about me a piece of cake
are you sure they probably never did it
before
oh my god someone shuts him up
[Laughter]
oh my god
oh
we're pros we're going to launch you
good three
two
one
[Music]
that's why this becomes a stealth
mission we can't fight
it's so [\h__\h]
forsaken fortress
i'll be failing a lot probably i'll need
your help guys
oh man
[Music]
[Applause]
did i just hear nubby
your sword landed all the way up there
shoot i'm sorry i apologize because my
aim was off oh yeah we can hear a tattoo
on me
why why
then look on your face priceless
i slipped a stone into your pocket just
before we fired you over there it's no
ordinary stone either
i can see what you're doing through this
stone and so obviously you can hear me
through it so if you see a you better
press that button
if put the stone on your request set
i've put this i can't read today i'll
put the stone on your quest status
screen use right on the item screen to
take a look it's pretty basic
hey but listen carefully i need this
back after you save your sister so don't
go losing it you understand oh
oh you want it back
all right i almost thought you know they
just would leave me here and then
go off with their ship and never come
pick me up
on
this i never cleared this
by myself
if anything i would let my brother
play through it or like i think i just
always used his save file probably
mostly
where it was already past this
and if i want to play on my own
whenever i would start from the
beginning i would just
let my brother play this
all right then down to brass tacks the
courtyard is a wash with searchlights so
they'll see you right away if you just
go charging in better think it through
[Music]
let's hope that
i just remember it oh uh way worse than
it actually was
ambero
um if i'm a barrel as long as i'm not
moving i can be in the light i think
[Music]
i wonder how the reaction time is though
like
is it is it very a bit
okay this is okay
i want the money
what what was i lag i was moving there
was some lag of him sitting down what
the [\h__\h] scary
okay okay where are we going um
are we go why why are you still moving
oh my god
uh where where are we actually going
first i wonder
where should we go first over there or
up to up those uh up the ladder maybe
[Music]
it's a pain
oh i remember the camera being a little
bit shitty sometimes
can't want to do go to stairs stairs
stairs
okay it doesn't come all the way over
here
ah those stairs okay
all right
here we go guys
the first big
dungeon can you call it the dungeon it's
an outside dungeon
the first big hurdle
that we will have to overcome
no problem so far and barrel
i had uh
quite some experience with barrels
okay that was generous
in atelier raiza
lots of barrels there as well taro taru
tarudes
i'll just i'll just stay in the barrel
oh i'm getting a good look
mm-hmm
i mean in general maybe it's better for
me that it's stealth
because you know you guys know i tend to
panic when
you know i i am
wait where do i go first door or further
up
you guys know i tend to panic when i
have to fight and all that
uh
i like to
go slow step by step
yeah
but i will panic anyway probably but
i'm gonna go up here now is that where
my sword is i can turn off the light can
i
if i kill the dude that's up there
oh my god
oh you scared me
pikachu style
listen up kiwawa there's a monster
running the searchlight up there i know
i know no no
all you have is a shield oh
my [\h__\h] to deflect the monsters blows i
forgot about that you're right i have no
sword how was i going to fight them
thank you i actually need your hint uh
see if you i could make ah drop the
weapon and then steal it yeah yeah okay
i remember them having a
weapon sam
huh
oh how do you use the shield
oh [\h__\h]
uh
and there's a bucket there too but i
should know how to use my shield too
[Music]
ah there we go
can i not hold it without just standing
there
still
said l and then that that are
why
[Music]
okay i guess i can't move
oh he went back i'm still here dude i
[\h__\h] dropped it
i dropped it for some reason
break that [\h__\h] up again
[Music]
only one hit the [\h__\h] is that
i need to make him lose his weapon
oh lock on oh
okay okay
why does he jump like a frog
okay
i'm gonna die
but why can't i still only get one
handed it's just because it's that kind
of weapon
oh
can i even kill him
i'm gone
ah there we go there we go
try me
huh what am i supposed to reflect
[Music]
wanna punch him with my fist
come at me bro come at me
swing them through wait i was pressing b
okay
oh my god
it looks like a hit
all right we got a health back so
anyway
[Laughter]
i am confused with the buttons i was
playing playstation yesterday
i was playing playstation
okay well it was a tutorial okay
hmm
by the way that was really a lot of fun
okay so we're going to first to close
those things i was saying it was a lot
of fun to play tales of her eyes
yesterday um
even though like
i didn't want to play him because i'm so
close to the end and i
i'm not allowed to stream the ending
but i
i didn't wanna i didn't wanna want it to
end you know
cause like until the next big tales off
game
it's gonna be a long while
and i don't want to not have an option
to play
a tails off game that i haven't played
yet you know i want there to be an
option to play it if i wanted to
so i was just dragging it out installing
installing
oh compass wow
but i am
i did uh
i'm gonna look at what we have should i
go down or should i
go
i mean let me go to the other side
mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy mommy
mommy mommy mommy
i wanted to go to the other side
[Music]
never stay in first level
oh this is dangerous how do i get back
up there's a map there but
casper
oh it's not that kind of barrel
it's a yeah
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
i think that my strats can actually hurt
me too
um casper returns
to give me a [\h__\h] heart attack again
[Music]
i'm sorry i'm sorry
i'm sorry
oh big
dude where do we go
i can open this but where does that lead
me outside
where should i go
big door or over there
outside
the door outside should i go outside
okay
i think i think
oh god
okay
i think we uh should
go back to where i was and try to uh
climb up you know
try to get the other lights first
i think
stop moving what the [\h__\h] is the matter
with you
um
okay anyway so back to tesla rise so um
it's in an attempt to
stall even more
i
um i didn't finish the game yesterday i
may have been i could have been able to
if i didn't uh go for hurdles and side
quests and all that i did a [\h__\h] ton of
side quests i did some main stuff too
um
i am main story-wise i'm without
spoiling too clearly i'm at the point
where you reach
um
you reach that new zone
uh with
left or right
or
up
we go down again after going up
i reached that new zone with with um
with
you know all the dead water and
yeah you know what i mean i don't want
to say it too clearly
zone with the stuff
there was a lot of story in between a
lot of talking and uh
dan moment where they did a really funny
uh
cut to their reactions
[Music]
yeah there was a lot of talking
before
uh
before you know doing any fighting or
anything there was really no fighting
but
[Music]
okay this is a different room i don't
know should we go first here there's a
there's a chest here could be good
what do we have down there
[Music]
a kitchen
i see no enemies but i see a cell
with
oh is that a bottle
[Music]
okay let's try to get to the other side
without failing this time
okay
okay okay okay okay
what do we have a map maybe because we
got the compass already
oh yeah
okay
we got some important stuff already i
see the map on my gamepad now
at the moment though it doesn't really
i don't really need it although on the
first floor there's still two chests
good to know
okay okay
[Music]
all right
um
[Music]
you want to proceed it's that door what
door
oh that door
that door
i didn't see that door
[Music]
exterior
yeah oh
huh we came from that door now
is it that door
okay wait
okay ah my height goes doki doki
um anyway so i found all the huddles so
far uh
but now there's like extra huddles all
over the map
apparently
and uh i found some new areas that i
haven't even been to before
entitlement rise by the way talking
about total rise
i found some new areas
i don't know if they're if i never had
access to them or
if they
were always there and i just
for some reason never went there
oh
and that's how i found that temple
i don't the temple
surely wasn't there before
i think
well
[Music]
temple seemed new and i was 20 levels
under leveled but you know when i
stumbled in i thought oh i can surely
you know go back if
if it turns out that
it's too difficult
let's just check it out yeah well then
turns out i couldn't go back
[Music]
okay
i couldn't go back
oh butterfly necklaces
nuts
cussy pendant i have to i think uh
collect those
i think i can sell them or get something
for collecting them
okay is this stop now okay good
yep there's one left
um
should we just jump down here
let's just jump down here
out
um
and go to the to this door is that where
i came from
i don't need to take out the last one
all right why should i go next i wonder
oh ah this is where i fail to jump
that was dangerous
i took out the important lights yeah
the other one doesn't seem to
be important indeed yeah it doesn't
do much
i think oh no wait that that is still
the one on the ground
well i guess it doesn't really matter
anymore hmm
[Music]
of course we got prims
no problem with nintendo
no this is where i fell down
no no no [\h__\h]
no i fell down in the room before but
then i ran through here [\h__\h] okay well
we're here now uh
i want my sword where is my sword
i know it's somewhere
outside oh god
[\h__\h] you
let's go outside no
sword is up yeah
i want
i want to i want to know the route how
to get there fastest
um
[Music]
do you have to go up there again again
panic fall
do i really need my barista
yeah
no i don't need it
do it
risky quality very risky to not go with
a barrel but okay
uh
joko
on that side there's still the light
but we don't need to take it out
i don't know where to go
second go all the way until you go to
the big door guarded by a big guy
holding a lantern
let's go this way
oh
my god scary
[\h__\h] help
i'm so stupid to make that jump
baby
why why why why
why
i can't
if i had one of those sticks then i
wouldn't mind going past the big guy
but
yeah
it makes me
leave the stick whenever i go for a door
or something
all right
gamer of ian yes i am still a gamer of
ian
i am still the gamer of the end don't
take away my title
if you roll the leg you'll jump further
okay interesting i don't want to do that
test it out here where it's really risky
though oh don't wait
no no no no okay
[Music]
all right we are
here now
getting closer
but
do i have the option to take out the
light
yeah yeah you can stop showing me that
we could take out the light from here i
think
or
oh there's a shortcut there for later
let's see
yeah yeah let's take him out why not
so we have a bit more freedom to move
around
[Music]
hello
surprise
oh [\h__\h] i dropped it
i dropped my spaghetti
why is dropping on that iron man
i tend to push that a lot for some
reason
hello
yeah
okay
yeah easy
easy clap
they're all turned off now
[Music]
i did my extra homework
yeah
anyway so tails of her eyes
i think
um i still have some side quests left to
do
so i still have some some time for
stalling and enjoying the game a little
bit more i'm literally trying to do
every single side quest right now
because i really don't want the game to
end
i know
[Music]
oh shipwreck
but it's been
quite some fun yesterday and also the
dungeon it was
really [\h__\h] difficult that temple
uh what
oh no [\h__\h] way i wanted to push it
does that respawn
you better tell me it respawns
no
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] let's go go back outside
uh but i think that's where my my
my sword is right
does
yes okay
wha it's a grab man
if i push
no don't go up
push it
[Music]
why did i not
how did have they managed to destroy it
last time i pushed a because it said
grab and then i just did a roll into it
what the [\h__\h]
ah
okay
yeah that's the big door i remember it
hey we didn't get oh don't jinx it kiara
nevermind i wasn't gonna say anything
i wasn't gonna say anything is he gonna
come here
wait wait
wait
this looks very familiar to me this is
like
watching pogba play metal gear charlotte
and barrow
oh
just a box
oh [\h__\h] those mice aren't they gonna
they're gonna rat me out aren't they
[Music]
they'll be so [\h__\h]
oh i remember them running into the
barrel
[Music]
i
think it's just a barrel it's just a
barrel go away
[Music]
you know your snoot can be used for a
delicacy people like to eat snoots like
yours i mean i wouldn't eat it but
[Music]
how close can i get
i just don't have to i just have to be
careful to not be um
seen by him right otherwise as long as
i'm behind him i can get as close as i
want i think
oh sure safe oh my god i still didn't
get
caught
besides falling down a few times i've
handled those situations
maybe a little bit panicky but still in
a way that i didn't get caught so
i say
i'm winning
sakura susan
i thought he already saw me and was
going to follow me down okay okay okay i
don't know no i don't think myself no
i'm not caught i'm welcome
okay
let's be careful let's be extra careful
with this dude or he's gonna come over
here
okay we're gonna wait a little while
i'm not going to get caught
[Music]
feel free to get as close as you want
i thought it was already over that's why
i panicked and ran try to run away
[Music]
but there's no running away once they um
find you
you get immediately
catapulted
don't you
cute butt
cute tail
i better better look where i'm going
both sides though
okay just a box it's just a barrel
all right
all right all right okay
whoa stealth over nine thousand
ee kanji
just a tadoo taro
taro raiza be like tadou
oh their flag is a pig snoot
now that also reminds me of uh alice
playing alice oh i should go down here
and make the the shortcut huh
i can still go back up right there's a
ladder right here
i think i'll i'll go down
yeah sure they got the peppa the paper
grinder
okay
now don't fall down
oh don't destroy it
perfect
[Music]
100 points for me
oh one more thing i did for a test of
her eyes
you know when i was streaming it um
there was one outfit that i couldn't uh
one dsc outfit that i couldn't put on
because of like kind of like i don't
know copyright issue
uh because it was like
okay oh you scared me
[Music]
huh yeah i know
you mean what's the matter well cancel
out the towel well isn't there a narrow
leg you can i know no no
no no no no no no
no no no
oh but i was gonna go the wrong way
right now huh
[Music]
i was gonna go this way i forgot
how how do we do this
link
yeah
how oh there you go okay yeah i was
saying um they were
there were
some outfits that i couldn't wear during
my playthrough so i realized oh my god
wait i can wear those outfits now
finally so i put everyone in those cute
outfits that couldn't show on stream now
linwell is wearing that idol master
outfit so cute
she looks so cute in it yeah
the only one i didn't uh
make the dlc outfit wear was kisara
because i don't like that specific one i
just gave her something else
i don't
know
where that one was from again some some
game but
i don't really like the design it was
some kind of purple
full body suit but not the sexy type
like oscar langley
or ray
no not the evangelion plug suits i was a
tekken
ah
i don't know she looked better in all
the other outfits so i kept
a different one
but i am using the ponytail
the hairstyle she looks so pretty kisara
is just too pretty for this world
[Music]
huh
can he
can you jump back up
huh
or can i just
is this connected if i jump down here it
was that connected
be careful link your little [\h__\h]
oh my god
all right
three hearts is nothing i hope i get a
heart container soon
at least we're not doing much combat so
the heart thing is not that much of a
problem i hear you seagulls i hear you
but i think
my sword is right there just uh do we
have to
what is that thing on the ground that
looks like something that would step
through my body
it's probably not active do i have to
run to it and then fight him
[Music]
the hero sword back now i'm in business
take care not to drop it again oh dear
okay stealth is over
[Music]
no match for a hero
oh no need to be scared
that that sound that ost though i want
to listen to it eonam pj and magikakami
okay
we're back in the game what's in here
hello oh [\h__\h] come on
[Music]
oh isn't that like the the rich girl
oh oh
yeah
all right the [\h__\h] bird what are we
gonna do
should i remember this part i don't
remember
we're gonna fight them here in here
[Music]
he's bringing me to the top
[\h__\h] we were so close
oh
mommy you're dead
what are you gonna do with me no he's
gonna
ah
he's gonna eat me
and then
uh
oh yeah yeah uh we won't be back here
for a while right
[Music]
he's gonna eat me and i'm gonna get
picked up by certain someone
i remember again
ah totally [\h__\h] we're gonna rescue her
now
i eat no
at least we got our sword back i guess
[Music]
god knows
just floating
ah
best friendo
oh
freaky ass boats that can speak
koala
whoa
can i do like a something like
uh uh oh
that's not good
doesn't sound so good
pull
there's been voices are so hard for me
to do
and i still have something in my eyes
make it go away
you like the white voice
right to the monitor morning
[Music]
what does that hear that squeaky sound
oh [\h__\h] why what's happening
only when i turn on the effect though
[Laughter]
pull all yourself together
this is actually pretty good maybe this
voice
i'll have to do this voice a lot so i
prefer to use the
voice changer
well
have you come to senses yet
you're surprisingly done with it
did i startle you
i suppose that is only natural as why as
the world is i am the only boat upon it
who can speak the worlds of men words of
men i am the king of red lions do not
fear
i am not your enemy
i've been watching you since you went to
the forsaken fortress to rescue your
sister
i understand how your desire to protect
your sister could give you the courage
to fearlessly stand up to anything
but such a bold attempt was foolhardy
i suppose you saw him the shadow that
commands that monstrous bird
i am not monstrous
his name is
he who obtained the power of the gods
attempted to cover the land in darkness
and was ultimately sealed away by the
very power he hoped to command
[Music]
he is the very same guardian the emperor
of the dark realm the ancient legend
speaker
i do not know why the seal of the gods
has failed but now that ghana has
returned the world is once again being
threatened by his evil magic
tell me you allah do you still wish to
save your sister from him
of course i couldn't just leave her
there
and will you do anything to save her
i see
in that case i shall guide you as we go
forward advising you on what you should
do and where you must go
ganon cannot be defeated by human hands
let alone by what little strength you
possess
the key to defeating ganon is blocked
away in a great power that you can wield
only after much toil and hardship
do you understand
i'm not a woman
in that case we depart for the great
scene
but i am getting ahead of myself
this is actually a bit embarrassing for
me to admit but
although i am indeed a boat that
possesses the power of speech i possess
no sale
oh what is boat without the sail
literally what is it a rowing machine
oh no but he has no no rowing thingy's
paddles either he has nothing that's
just a raft oh no a poor boat oh oh we
need to get a safety sale
and a boat with no sail can sail no seas
i have brought
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm so excited
i'm so excited i'm so excited this is so
[Music]
listen to me first okay and then you can
squeal i brought you far to the east of
the dark gaze of the forsaken fortress
on this island is a town of merchants
who deal in a wide variety of goods
if you search hard enough surely you can
find one who will sell your sale
i'm sorry to ask this of you but without
a sale i will be useless to you
this island of merchants is home to many
valuable goods
the information they provide you may
come in handy during your endeavors at
sea so listen carefully to their words
and hate them well but remember there is
no time to play come back here
immediately as soon as your errands are
done
ain't no time to play
yeah
but
i wanna i wanna do side singing
how did he get you here we gotta say
that's a good question don't question it
too much but
i guess
maybe he has little tiny duck feet
under his
uh you know under his bottle
and he just waggled all the way here
[Music]
underneath there
someone really cute windfall island wait
what was its name in germany
[Music]
which is funny and i never realized this
as a child but um
sometimes we like to call uh
the thing that you
carry your money in a port monet too
because i think it's it comes from the
french word probably maybe it sounds
french
yeah your wallet
and it's called
this place called port money maybe yeah
um
also because port ports is like also
you know
somewhere where you can
land
but also you know wallet we're gonna
hear you spend your money
don't come here without a port money
we call it that in the netherlands tomb
[Music]
i'm so happy
[Applause]
i remember this dude but i forgot what
his issue was oh i i hate those children
for some reason i remember hating them
ah
are you hearing the bgm do i need to
turn it up oh yeah that was elvis yeah
oh hello
oh if you please young boy there please
help me
please listen to my tale of woah
my suit oh
your daughter she was a non-rich looking
one probably
my only daughter poor maggie she was
captured by a bunch of villains and
taken to the forsaken fortress one of
them could those schedules
are they just roaming around looking for
young maidens articles evil creatures
who delighted miss chief well kron
having a kingdom daughter doesn't get
you a single ruby you know please please
save my poor daughter i beg of you here
i stand banging
i hope you'll give those scoundrels
why would you think
that i maybe because of my sword and my
shield i guess but like i'm young as
[\h__\h] and uh they don't seem to have that
green clothes tradition in any other
island here besides our own island
so it's not like that was a sign
you must have for some reason already
seen my sword in my shield
you think oh this child he will save my
daughter
i'm okay
they'll pay for what they've done new
year's pay
don't worry about it when i save one of
them i'll save all of them of course
of course i will
hello
this peaceful place is here island the
people here would never even dream of
leaving your little paradise and setting
sail on the voyage at sea you know what
i mean
why this town is full of faces that
don't even show the slightest interest
in sales of a ship
are we sailors the only ones has no one
else set out under great see
i know what well i i have i guess
i have with a big [\h__\h] pirate ship
which i'll know when i'll ever see it
again if i they'll ever show their face
oh wait why is that thing not talking to
me
that necklace
does the
does the wi-fi not go that far or the
the blue what's it called again blue
tube
if you could indulge me for a moment
please admit that i'm looking fine
well looking this fine would have won me
to miss windfall crown way back when
i'm still looking better than all the
younger girls i know
you
look okay i guess i mean you got a lot
of volume in your hair some people might
be really jealous of that
[Music]
for a guy that's also her age she might
be looking very attractive
hello what are you looking at the ground
floor
you're looking for a sail i have no idea
where you'd find one i look like a
sailor to you
look i'm feeling dumb right now so shove
up romeo
in the mouth
[Music]
it reminds me of them
what are they are they called ice
cleavers
from i only know them from super smash
brothers but
they're probably uh
they have their own game i suppose ice
climbers not cleavers [\h__\h]
yeah yeah
yeah
uh
my story is a strange one i came across
cursed seas from the land far away a lot
where the blizzards blow violently
heading for this town called windfall
oh dear for me my ship was torn apart by
vicious winds and this island is where
i've washed a sore
there was one other person with me yes
there was but i dare say he was
immediately arrested based on his
somewhat suspicious look said for throne
ride into jail yes just looked up
somewhere on this island island
need needless to say i'm really worried
about him would you be so kind as to
help free him from captivity
indeed it would be appreciated
[Music]
what
is he's locked up somewhere in this
island
and then what you will sell me your sale
oh wait what oh i [\h__\h] i thought you
had a brother or someone but you just uh
move okay okay
[Music]
tango he's talking about tingle where
there's a cafe here i never noticed that
what the [\h__\h]
oh i is have been in here
oh my god
those those borders
on the table and on the wall and
everywhere
you know what that looks like
the inside of a cake it's like it's a
chocolate cake with cream inside and
strawberries
and and buried
jam in between
[Music]
that writing i know it's just gibberish
but it looks like japanese i see coffee
kohi
and something that looks like a cake
and
ho ho
yeah it looks like katakana
a little bit
and some kanji
you don't wanna
i know it's i know it's not i mean
can you read that
tell me you can read that if that's not
if you can't read it then it's gibberish
okay
i never wasn't here before this is
fascinating welcome
oh my a very small customer aren't ya
well that's fine of course just feel
free to look around wait all those
coffee beans in the back oh
[Music]
i'm on the table now serve me
serve me
i'm a customer customer is king
all that what i've been doing that
monsters from the forsaken fortress i've
been going around kidnapping grills for
long years i can't believe it after all
two girls from the rainfall i've already
been cutting them poor maggie in my life
just breaks my heart to think about
those two
oh their fathers are desperate to find
anyone who can rescue their poor little
girls what kind of world has this become
so much free and suffering
yeah you speak so fast dude
it didn't serve me i have money
you can serve me
huh
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
why are you not serving me
[Music]
is there a secret here maybe i wonder is
it worth falling down maybe not
[Music]
oh
pop
[Music]
[\h__\h]
is that really not possible
[Music]
okay what do we do wait we gotta look
for that tingle where the [\h__\h] is that
person
can go
where is he how do i find him
where is he where is that jail are we
supposed to look for jail
nothing
where is praising
this prison
that looks like a mayor's house
[Music]
maybe he can tell me where prison is
oh
i see i see
no
[Music]
a rich looking girl school for quarter
towel is difficult you see my one and
only daughter milo was taken away from
me to a frightening place called the
forsaken foot
how do they know
where they are it's not like the birds
told them hey i'm taking your daughter
to the forsaken fortress bye-bye
[Music]
thank you for the membership welcome
they read the script
good question
bird left a note
on the fridge probably
i've always wanted to rescue her but it
seems to be a difficult voyage to that
cursed place
oh to see my sweet meal again my
precious little daughter wears so over
welfare i can't recall the last time i
slept more than a wink
really
i sincerely wonder about the wisdom of
asking a boy like you to do this but
would you lend a hand to help rescue my
precious daughter
brave boy to take all those tasks i
assure you if you do rescue her i will
pay you as much as money takes
as it takes i need more toy fortune for
your safety and then you're probably
just gonna pay me like with 20 bucks
in the end
and then you'll be like well
uh we have no contract whatsoever
don't complain to me now i already have
my daughter back
you know
okay so we kind of accepted
a quest but we were gonna do it anyway
so
and
where the [\h__\h] is prison
where the [\h__\h] is prison i don't
remember prison at all
[Music]
the first floor of this mayor house
by the grave ah by the dancing elvis
okay anyway oh [\h__\h] but wait if i break
anything here is this the place where i
have to pay
was that a different house
i'm scared but there's no one here
what was the consequence again of
breaking [\h__\h] here can i even yeah
um
[Applause]
i know we all want to break these kind
of things that's sparkle
oh but we're
yeah i further i
would have to pay i think i remember
something there it was not very good huh
i mean
oh
what
[Music]
are you gonna tell me that every time i
walk by you
i already know i'm i'm doing it
hi doug
[Music]
hello look at all familiar buddy are you
some kind of tourist or something if you
i'll show you around why don't you join
me for a list
i already took i already did a holster
all on my own
kind of too late now
oh oh he's not taking me anyway
can you just offer me what an empty
promise that was
hey elvis
[Music]
oh
no that's not it that's just not it that
the problem is even though that's not it
this isn't it evil
[Music]
oh dear pardon me pardon me guy
i was so fully and holy absorbed in my
dancer that i didn't even know this
little old you standing there oh
i'm taught
i love dancing more than i love three
meals a day you will come to know me as
the world's charismatic dancer extra odd
now
ready go one two one two
say guy you know what i was just
reminded of
long ago i met this little delightful
guy who performed the most dazzling
magic dance a dance that turned nine of
the day right before my very eyes oh i
can remember those fabulous aspects but
i just can't seem to get the intricate
rhythm down
do you think you know the rhythm guy
[Applause]
no
i don't know anything
please keep me out of that
prison
[Laughter]
well natural maybe he needs to go to kfb
dancing school
[Music]
this is why
uh watching chihuahua play rpgs is fun
[Music]
voices
he's green like me
he must be one of the heroes who have
come of age
is he a link from a different dimension
[Music]
a link from a different
tl oh that game which one could it be
[Music]
it was that [\h__\h] easy
free the criminals
thank you all so very much harris
jungle's heartfelt gift bags
[Music]
you can insert a message oh [\h__\h] that
[\h__\h] what
ah
[Music]
rip me verse can i even use that
i think i remember
that but it was that even possible in
the gamecube as well
oh mr ferry are you familiar with the
main verse with it messages put in this
bottle can be sent to fairies the world
over but that doesn't matter anymore
because the mean verse is dead
r.i.p just don't write anything
unpleasant okay not that i have to
remind you mr fairy
splendid tingle is returning now to his
own special island will you come find
her
you have a very red nose are you a
rudolph
no i was forgetting something important
don't talk about my nose i am i have
some confidence issues about it oh mr
ferry you want to come to my island
don't you don't you don't
i got a dinner shot what kind of shark
could it be head out to the scene and
check your shirts on the map screen to
find out
you open it on the map screen
if you ever need any help with your
charts just leave it to tango don't ever
forget it
oh one more thing if you like to give
your tingle balls that little extra oh
not all the tingles crave you should
check the back of this cell check it
right out
bye-bye
look at that they're they're forcing me
they're forcing me
hmm not gonna know something laser
intingle bottles by using miiverse are
you sure
people say it's dead
is that your tingle bottle
why would i do that
pick up tingle balls if you find lying
on beaches or floating in the state to
read letters other people have written
[Music]
and launching the bottles don't receive
okay i set it to don't receive
you cannot currently receive tingle
bottles because even miiverse or online
interaction in games has been restricted
by parental controls
you think that is the problem
you think that's the problem
i mean yes i may have restricted the
miiverse yes i remember doing that
but it's more than that
mama says no
uh no
uh
there we go
[Music]
is what i thought they're also going to
be useless or at least at
some use of some use rather left guys
right
left
oh [\h__\h]
right
right oh
[Music]
did i go in a circle
oh
right
there's something left there is that a
trap door that will make me fall down
yeah don't turn if you see what i
thought so
[Music]
what is that sound
money
[Music]
at least link looks like a the cutest
toddler ever when he's crawling like
this it's so adorable
i see the word no no i'm not going there
but i'll get that blue real big
it's a time again for our whoa
for our uh
economy guy
what do we call that position again
to tell us how much a wind waker rupee
is worth in us dollars remember that we
did that for skyward sword too
and for uh
what was the other thing that we did
where we did that
look we did it for something else too
did we only do it for sky ones did we
got it
this is our first uh zelda game
on my channel
economy
date unknown
at last i have succeeded in stealing the
picture box i have designed for so long
succeeded yes but sadly due to a slight
mistake on my part that was also caught
i've been imprisoned but i do not give
it easily i've refused to give this
wondrous box to my captors
i've decided to hide it here in the
depths of my cell and and then make my
escape by tunneling out yes that is the
plan is is that tingle or someone else
[Music]
is the picture box useless now too
what are cryptographing
no this one's not useless
[Music]
side quests ah
i don't want to deal with that now
though
okay we're free tingle so will the dude
[Music]
let us
buy the sale now
should i take a shortcut by going
through a wooden door where will that
lead us
is that a shortcut for going out
[Music]
i haven't been sleeping well that's okay
me neither
[Music]
oh okay it's a shortcut okay good ah
gasps for you little [\h__\h]
that's a cute bell though with a ribbon
very cute
oh
don't even ask i have been
i've been on it okay i haven't been
playing around don't you look at me with
those eyes like that
seminar
let's try again
to see if that dude tells me
what i want now
[Music]
they playing pranks again
oh what voice
killed him that is news our team rabble
great you are one stand-up individual
indeed you are now i apologize as i have
bought another favor
i am actually considering starting up a
little shop oh it's not a shop yet
here on the island island but i'm having
trouble finding my venture
i have but one aspect to my name i
wonder if you might buy it from me
perhaps the people on this island have
no interest in venturing out into these
denture scenes so my chance of selling
it to them is rather bleak the blinkist
i can describe
i'd really like to ask for 200 rupees
for it but that's a favor for rescuing
my friend perhaps we may strike a deal i
have 300 actually he doesn't know huh
well 88 okay i'll get off your holy [\h__\h]
yes
went down from 200 to 80 i probably
would have bought it even for 200 if i
had to
me
yes
wait why am i buying though you didn't
tell me didn't you [\h__\h]
am i even buying the sale
wait what am i buying i can't
wait am i on it
is this um mind control
manipulating my brain
making me think
that i'm buying what i need
because he emphasizes it so much
oh well it is okay
ah yes yes yes thank you very much
indeed i have received precisely 80
rupees for it i can use these funds to
finance my new business oh dear me
what a happy day
very well young masters i promised
please take notes
oh yeah okay
you made me worry that i was being
scammed
didn't show it to me didn't even name it
but the way he talked about no one else
here having a use for it at least was
reassuring yeah yeah
scene
[Music]
i could have just said it yeah not eat
but eat what is eat
[Music]
oh yes yes yes you have made a good
purchase today my young master yeah i
have indeed and you have saved my life
and business as well treasure dearly it
is the finest sale in the world treated
as such
okay
i hope my weird dragon boat will be
happy about it
let's bring it to him immediately he
said no playing games
i'm literally playing in games right now
i wonder what he would say if he knew he
would be mind blown
what you mean i am the king
what it's like telling a cat that
they're a cat
what what do you mean i am the kid
oh yeah
oh that look in your eye so you found
yourself a sail have you
very well then i shall teach you the art
of sailing
come next to my hole and press a to
climb aboard
hoist the sail you got with a to get
moving
the sail will catch the wind which will
push the boat forward
the up that appears behind me indicates
the wind direction
use l to steer if you wish to move
quickly you should keep the wind blowing
directly into the sail
you can also always press b to put away
the sail
try it when you want to adjust your
speed
did you understand all that
[Applause]
oh one more thing when you are out at
sea with few landmarks to go by you will
be at mercy if you c chart i have marked
the place we should currently be heading
for on your c chart if you get lost at c
select map displayed on the wii u
gamepad to open your c chart
every time they say stuff like when you
game bad it really ruins the immersion
you can also pause the game with plus
and confirm your position
now a westerly wind blows hop in and let
it carry us to the east
yep we're leaving
what east
um
where
is i don't know how to read a compass
uh
is this north
[Music]
if this is north and this is east
open the map
oh yeah
okay well i was correct okay
so if i if i have the red one looking
straight then that's not
[Music]
louder
was not able to jump
[Music]
yay
wait
[Music]
i wasn't able to
do i need more momentum in order to jump
oh right now it works
[Applause]
[Music]
oh i remember those spots
i can uh fish there for a treasure can
we already do that or
[Music]
uh probably not yet we need some kind of
tool i think
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe maybe it's selling the club oh
[\h__\h] i go so slow against the wind oh
sit
am i faster without snow
wait for me
don't go there that's dangerous
don't wait for me beetle
i wanna say hi
does he sell other things ever if you
meet him on the sea i wonder
how do i enter
you have to leave my boat
[Music]
be
here we go
hello nice to see you i have my own
little ship now we're both living boat
life instead of van life oopsie
sorry
i'm so excited
oh you have the same [\h__\h] but i just
wanted to say hello
bye bye
bad live boat live for
bros pick me up pick me up
oh yeah yeah oh no no
no no no no wait
[Music]
here we
go he's a lot nicer in this game if you
don't buy anything oh yeah in skyward
sword it was really
stupid about it
uh this way
[Music]
is over there
ah hello
i want to deal with you
i'm almost there
oh is that the bird's place
the bird people
isn't it yeah yeah and that's a cloud
around it
oh
i think it is
[Music]
bunny
in german again does somebody remember
that the dragon's at the top
they're on the horizon
yeah i see it that is our destination
dragon roost island
almost makes me wanna start dancing
tango
[Music]
i already turned it up so loud
okay
uh
higher top this island's peak lives the
spirit of the skies a great dragon by
the name of coco senpai
[Music]
no no no no no
no no no
[Music]
you must go see this dragon in the
request from him a jewel called the
vince pearl
[Music]
this is not the
uh burp island after all that was a
different one
ask the people of tom no it was maybe it
was rita tribe who inhabited this island
about how to see the dragon
okay
oh
oh i almost forgot wait just a moment
ah
it went like i already have it dude you
don't need to give it to me i already
have it
[Music]
this is the wind waker it has a baton of
sorts that was used long ago when the
people played music in prayer to god
in those days simply using it allowed
one to borrow the power of the gods but
i do not know if this if it still works
even so i thought it might be of some
use to you perhaps you should try using
it
what i don't know what that means
uh-huh by tilting up down and right in
that order
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm a musician
up right left and then down
what
what's happening
[Music]
hold left on this
oh
[Laughter]
yeah
why does this not stay that though
don't have to keep on holding okay
[Music]
okay
that was not bad for your first time
using the wind waker not bad at all
you can also conduct with it in six for
time
by tilting l
uh you would do well to remember that
[Music]
does that change the wind direction
by using this magical conductor's method
you can borrow the power of the guns
you're right to the night don't tilt
oh conduct
okay okay i have to
okay
[Music]
oh the shop has followed me
stay there
[Music]
nice one
and uh i don't know this one
[Music]
another yellow one how much was the
yellow one worth again
[Music]
you are the economist after oh
is that not wrong did you just change it
for me
[Music]
was there some secrets here
uh or was
it let me read here maybe it's a hint
huh
oh dear
oh
yeah
is that something i can solve right now
like i can't
do i need like an arrow bomb arrows
[Music]
what's that sound
i can't reach it yet okay okay
what about that over there no we should
just go inside okay
i need fire arrows or a slingshot
ah fire arrows not a hotel
[Music]
they
seem to
not want
people like me to come too close
i don't know
why is everything blocked with these
huge stones
i guess they don't
really need proper paps for themselves
because they can oh nice
they can just uh
fly out from the top or somewhere
[Music]
of course that would happen
i was trying to
push a to stay on the
on the side
[Music]
it did not work as you can see
at a time screen britannia yeah yeah
yeah
kind of similar
oh i saw um some other live english
members where
uh putting town scraper on their
schedule and i think maybe fauna already
or is it it's sunday maybe she's playing
it today
and as her members stream
yeah
are they already plated
both of them
i wonder if they liked it i mean it's
it's not much content in the game it's
just you know i thought it would be nice
to have something
uh
cute and calm and chill for members only
streams to talk uh
with the members while doing stuff and i
didn't fall down
all good
oh shortcut
how
yeah okay that's what i hoped would
happen nice too
and that hurts a little bit
[Music]
that's the problem with jumping
automatically
[Music]
i started a trend
kind of
good morning i didn't talk to these yet
they can talk
i have nothing for delivery thanks
though oh is that the postman
hello
i always thought you guys looked really
weird when i was younger
but
i guess you guys are fine you're nice
ah they shake when there's something
yeah yeah right i remember that
oh yeah all the jumping straight into
lava
good times
thank you
for reminding me of those good times
yum yum yum yum yum uh i forgot what
voice i did hmm just a little voice
well okay what was that you
it is i'm pleased to see you're okay
i must say you've traveled far from one
with no wings
[Music]
and your sister is she
no
i tried i've come so far i was right in
front of her
is that so well don't worry too much i'm
sure she'll lag in there
i have an idea of
would you like to meet our chieftain
i've told my people here about you and
all of us rachel are very concerned
i'm certain the sheep chieftain will
befriend you our attention that is by
the way lends you the aid of our harry
give me your
hey settle down i'll fly on the head and
let everyone know you're coming
come inside you all i'll be waiting
why can't you not carry me
why you gotta make it so difficult for
me
[Music]
wait a second guys
uh
let's go inside
turkey
[Music]
yeah well i don't carry them up but
we have an elevator so there's no need
for carrying people up
is there
they don't have an elevator dope so that
would be would be a nice service
to carry me up
mom
well have you discovered the cause of
the great values anger
[Music]
no
ah so you lucky where are you
quill has told me all about you
a troubling tale indeed
i insist that you let us know if there
is anything we can do to help you
we shall do everything in our power to
assist you we're so sweet of them
however in the meantime we have a
problem of our own to deal with
when you arrived on the island did you
notice the raging dragon perched atop
the mountain
as you can see i didn't really see him
raging but yes i definitely saw a big
dragon
we are the rachel tribe are profoundly
connected to the sky
we make our livings in the airways
we do so by the graces of the sky spirit
for lou ah he's probably gonna teach me
how to
um
how to change the wind direction because
the emperor is the sky spirit would make
a lot of sense
ah
oh the
the oh it still runs i can't help it and
they're coming
when rita reaches adulthood he or she
journeys to the top of dragon bros to
receive a scale from the great dragon
it is a scale that enables darita to
grow his or her wings
[Music]
recently however the once gentle value
has grown violent and unpredictable
sadly we can no longer approach him
if this continues to fledglings were of
age we'll never be able to receive
scales from the loo on dragon roost
it will remain ringless
made unless almost one might say and in
time our very way of life will be
threatened
that sounds tough no we don't want that
i will help you you help me
as tension of the rito my first
responsibility is to solve this problem
my apologies but i must ask you to wait
for our assistance until this is done
will you do so
i will do more than that
no wings
potential
potential what do you think of
consulting eval with regards to your son
prince komali
son there's another girl
huh i only remember a girl
get a son
as you can see chihuahua is a gold young
lad
i feel certain that prince komali would
open his heart to him and speak freely
of his fears and worries
i forgot about the sun
that maybe
[Music]
let me be direct my son komali is of the
age to earn his wings yet he is weak in
some ways and in light of the current
situation he may just give up on ever
getting them
say you will you share some of your
courage with my son
will you meet with my son
i think i can
help him with that i don't know
i don't think my courage will help him
only me
only me calming down the dragon will
help
but okay whatever you say
we shall do our best to solve our
problem as quickly as possible so that
we may better help you with yours
i have something i wish for you to give
to my son
a young girl named medley we're giving
him a maiden
oh um is holding it for me would you
find her and take it
[Music]
i am the maiden giver
wow what an honor
no wings but he will not be maidenless
[Music]
can i take the bacon
if i take the main and i want the maiden
[Music]
how about i take the maiden and use it
to get the wings for you
and then you can have the maiden
afterwards
okay
[Music]
a delivery bag
another bag
any kind of item
one of the upper rims okay
all right
wait where do we go first girl or boy
[Music]
because upper rims first girl first
oh girl face
ladies first i like that
[Music]
there she is i always thought her beak
was creepy but it's okay you're cute and
pretty yes
try to kiss me with that shuba nose
track
[Music]
okay now that i look at her i mean
she looks cuter than
when i saw her when i was younger
[Music]
wow you really do have green clothes and
a strange shaped hat
yuki wawa aren't you
oh me i'm attending to the great sky
spirit value my name is
medley well to tell the truth i'm not an
attended court yet i'm actually still
studying to be one
oh what am i thinking here this is from
the teacher
he wants you to give this to directly to
the prince kamani
[Music]
you know what if you
if the dad would have just directly gone
to him whatever is written in the letter
he could have gone conveyed directly in
words but okay this is like sending a
sending a a a text message
to your son even though you live in the
same building
even though you could have just gone to
his room and talked to him
so they've just received to find the
lumber bag
okay do i really need the delivery back
to deliver it to kamali can i not put it
in my other bag
yeah
the round lay in the back on the first
floor is prince come at his room you
have to go down a couple steps to get
there
when you need to cut prince come on
please don't get offended by his mama he
has no bad intentions i promise
um by the way
listen
i have a small favor i'd like to ask of
you
could you please come to the entrance of
the dragonview's cabin later
i'll explain everything then okay girl
will be partners in crime
uh where was kamali did they tell me
because i don't remember
confession
so early oh my link is just so charming
everybody falls in love with him
immediately
first floor okay
all right
ash just told me you know sometimes when
i read things
out loud
they don't enter my brain
portal brain
when i read them quietly
it works better forgive me
this is the right way nah
the way that this room is here that
looks like it's going to prison
must be here
big room yeah but that leads outside
hold it
oh wait that's that's probably not where
he lives either
it was the right way really
and it looks so
so much like oh of have to somewhere
where someone lives
that you just want to
put behind bars i don't know
like that door too doesn't look so
friendly
[Music]
hello
ah
oh
yo nice room
oh the bird doll's cute
nice clothes i like the style
and the colors and his room looks very
cozy lots of huge ass feathers that he
probably picked from that
uh
bird that stole my sister
hello
is that a magic 8 ball what does it say
well
who are you supposed to be
i need to ah give you something wait a
second uh
items
[Music]
oh
this one
[Music]
here
a letter
from my father
oh
oh sure telling me to be brave is easier
enough for him
it's not like he's the one who went
through that horrible experience it's
not like he still has to go get a scale
from value
also he could have told me directly what
the [\h__\h]
he's so
so so lonely nobody comes to see me and
then he just talks to me for a letter
you're in this letter too you know
poking your nose in others people's
business your nose aren't you at least
you have a nose
[\h__\h] you
sorry but i really don't feel like going
to siva lou right now i mean how am i
supposed to get a scale from him when
he's so upset
what
are you trying to say that you can calm
down down
that's just a big fat lie it's easy to
say you can do anything
bragging doesn't cost a thing
i'll tell you what if you can find me
someone who can get past all the
obstacles on dragon roots to get value
then i'll listen to anything you say
okay
sure don't believe me then
i'll just do it i won't come back before
i
i have it
no that voice
that voice was supposed to be
not not just because i was tired but
because he seems like a little boy that
um is more on the quiet side at least
right now when he's sad
hmm
now she's here already i've been
actually
wasting some time here and there running
around and humming the melodies
but i guess we've been progressing
pretty nicely
yeah uh so are we supposed to meet the
girl now uh
how where uh where do i get there
male starting minigame at the top oh
ah this one
you can try
[Music]
well no i have not seen your young face
before nope don't believe so
i wouldn't be here in response to a
posting for some part-time help
yes
yes give me all the part-time jobs
wait i need to i need to take a fruit
can the older reading
has been
killing my throat
a little bit
[Music]
okay i hope that helps
it's hard
oh dear my roads are worth it
maybe my hops the first heart container
what a month
i see now
[Music]
forgot that window i got was filled with
chicken people excuse me chicken people
those are not chicken people if anything
i don't know they're hawk people or
whatever
hmm
hello hot wings i am
you see a tingle uh i guess that looks a
little bit like tingle yeah
match the c on the envelope with the
same icon on the shelf for the letter on
the onto that shelf okay
okay okay
um
[Music]
hey to friday okay and it's simple but
probably very fast and confusing
so at least ten letters okay
[Music]
i'm certainly not gonna first try that
am i
i mean at least 10 letters is okay but
that probably doesn't give me the
biggest reward
i was gonna throw it there i was going
to throw it there but then it swooshed
swing slip slippery slip
oh [\h__\h]
what is it 18.
what did i get for 18.
one rupee for every two has nine rupees
okay
that that was definitely not the reward
that i'm supposed to get
but it's also a money-making minigame
huh
20 miles you'll see some nice financial
gain okay okay 20 20. okay okay
uh okay
[Music]
that's better with the
well not with the joystick but with the
other thing
because i have more control
okay
[Music]
i get something
pink huh
i can't mix oh wait wait wait how many
do you want for
it
there's something bigger right
two more a 25 okay okay again we can do
25 i will jump okay okay 25 25.
[Music]
this is not the one this is not the one
we had some good um
a good brand before oh [\h__\h] man this is
not it
it was like a good combination of
yeah they're not even close
like it was so many of the same ones and
then the close by ones and all that okay
no that's okay at least we're not losing
money or anything
it's gonna have a lucky run with some
good combinations
of letters
like for example this like holy [\h__\h]
start off like oh that's a good start
do
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] that was such a good one
okay
[Music]
um
come on
[Music]
huh
[Applause]
i only spent 400 rupees now why not
always keep on missing one
one more
oh my god
[Music]
[Applause]
hi
[Music]
ah
uh
[Music]
[Applause]
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yes oh yes
[Music]
oh
what a [\h__\h] lucky one
[Music]
those were a lot of lucky ones though
yo those repetitive ones
oh my god oh you i don't even have like
time to look up to the left uh top left
to see where like how many i have
really got to stay focused there oh my
god i did it
i did it what am i getting
[Music]
i thought i get
a heart container
i just got more money
mm-hmm
your new helper arrived i don't see
anyone
[Music]
now do it again for the hot it
do i actually get it
birdie
later
not now
i don't even know how i can get to 30
holy [\h__\h]
i don't think i can do that
[Music]
i don't have the confidence for that
later in the game you can try for the
hard piece
yeah maybe off screen maybe if i get a
lucky run and like an extra lucky run
and with some practice
maybe then
can i break things aren't gonna go up
somewhere
no
nothing okay
okay what about this though
nothing okay sorry guys i
made a mess over there
how
do i get to where i want to go
[Music]
25 for hot days
after the dungeon though
[Music]
what did i work so hard for now
okay we have to get 25 again at some
point
first floor ah okay thank you
thank you it's always great to have some
people in the chat who know the game so
well they remember everything what was
this place ah
that was where i met the girl
for training yeah
okay
uh
first of all
and i guess so here
oh yeah right yeah
right we already entered
the hot place
is she here somewhere oh there she is
hey this place uh makes me feel very
uncomfortable
[Music]
hey you actually came i'm really sorry
for bringing you to such a dangerous
place i had to i wouldn't have asked if
i didn't need help desperately
you see this place there used to be a
spring here surrounded by a beautiful
pond it was beautiful and lovely but
then a great balloon he became so angry
and in this red she shook the mountain
and just pulled the crash down plugging
the spring you can see the result
oh but where is my mind tell me how was
prince comadi
oh that doesn't sound right not at all
i may be partially to blame for the bad
turn that prince come on has taken
see prince christ's grandmother was the
great balloon's former attendant
she was an amazing woman i was honored
to have her as my teacher she was kind
and brave and unsurpassed in her
dealings with the great balloon
i'm not yet worthy of being mentioned in
the same breakfast head
if only i'd possessed some milk or
strength i'm sure prince cormadi would
have felt more secure
[Music]
i'm sorry to ask this but i need your
help
i want to go to the small shrine that's
near the peak of dragon roost but that
ledge over there is so high
if i could get some wind under my wings
i'm sure i could get up here there so
will you help me
oh do i have to
control the wind already here hmm
oh no
okay how how can i give you wind
oh i throw you oh
[Music]
um the atmospheric cards are really
messed up so pay close attention to the
direction of the wind
all right i'm ready don't hold back now
all right this is
this is the mechanic of this dungeon
using her together
and
and then solving the dungeons somehow
but see like yeah yeah sorry about that
i'm fine
that didn't really hurt what was i
saying oh yeah once more let the wing
toss away please
we're
hopefully not gonna
uh have her hurt herself too much
but the wind just goes from side to side
holy when does it go to the front
left no
there we go
fly high burp
oh thank you i think now i'll be able to
come dragon bruce and meet with the
great walloo don't worry i'll be fine i
mean just be an apprentice attendant but
i can understand some of the great
balloons language
i'm not exactly bursting with confidence
but
look if anything happens to me
please look after prince come on
don't say that
this is all i have to give to you i know
it's that much but please take it
[Music]
don't tell anyone that i'm climbing
dragon roost it'll be a secret okay
good luck to both of us
what about me
can i take the water from here
i'm sure that would be helpful
i'm sure we might need that water
somewhere
put it where it's dry
hmm
smart tool
well there's water there's a bottle
it was a little bit obvious
that recycling oh the bombs
okay i was thinking when i walked in
here someone has to water these bomb
plants
there we go i just need one that's all i
need i think and then throw it on top
and there we go
[Music]
oh hot spring is filling up oh and i can
swim to the other side and follow her
if she would have just waited a moment
for my big brain act here
also she could have done it herself too
genius
oh this must be pretty hot though
i know
first dungeon well i kind of considered
the the castle as a dungeon too though
uh i think i'll go to an idol meeting
really quickly
and then we'll
enter
this
lava dungeon i don't like lava dungeons
but
we gotta do what we gotta do
okay
please wait please hold the line oh time
to save i didn't save even once
good idea
continue
okay
okay okay brb
um
uh
hey hi this movie
hmm
i'm not sure if my humidifier is on or
off
i'm out zone okay
okay
i am back back back back
oh
yo sure
you're soaked
no no it's moving i'm a smoothie
smoochie does not exist yet maybe
sometime in the future
okay oh
do i need some more water
what is this is your water in here
by any chance
no [\h__\h] i lost money with that
i know wait oh wait i thought i have to
make the ground uh you know
uh solid blood
yeah that was it that was that i
remember it now
oh three two one
damn it
helmet
[Music]
don't know if that was a bomb or it was
a sneeze
[Applause]
that was such a good pro you're kidding
me
oh come on
oh my god
okay
that one i understand
where are we
what one time one fall in the lava
sends you back to the beginning of the
dungeon
now
the whole dungeon except for this part
after this everything will go smooth as
butter
oh [\h__\h] you
thank god i'm not using my own bombs but
bomb plans thank you for the membership
oh come on
[Music]
this game is ringing
hot
huh
oh my god
if i stand in front of it it'll just
throw it too far
i have to throw it from the side
oh [\h__\h] up maybe i don't know maybe from
here though maybe yeah
no this is too too far
no why i don't get it
let's not talk about it
on your
dragon roost cavern
not very musukashi
that's it's okay well
oh
my god
well at least i have my sword so
everything's
[Music]
and nothing cool you brother
oh butterfly nicholas he's fashionable
he got that bling bling
nice
[Music]
you guys want to hear some
some live updates
uh
so i had like um extra
what is that thing
i had some extra doctors
doctor's appointments
um
[Music]
had some extra doctors appointments
right that's why i was busy had some
extra stuff to do one of it was a
doctor's appointment and
it was kind of like
um
that doctor you know
i talked to him one time
because it was just necessary uh before
starting the
in this new physical therapy whatever
yeah but then i was like i'm not sure
about this like it was like how do you
feel about it i was like i don't know
i don't know i mean i guess i'm gonna do
it but to be honest i've i just came
from a physical therapy so i don't know
how about
how i feel about doing the physical
therapy and and and then they were
actually
not only gonna do a physical therapy but
after another physical therapy they were
gonna do
a different kind of therapy um
that's like more
like all kinds of different things like
like training
and i don't know you know i told you
about this
therapy right the special one that they
have that they wanted me to do that they
prescribed me basically kind of
uh what is that plot
um
i guess it is what are the water plots
for
i don't see any reason for them being
used here
but that pot is weird
oh
okay
maybe that's just letting me know that
this mechanic exists and i will use it
later
it won't work now
i need to unlock the ah it's like a
teleport
okay okay
so anyway because i wasn't so sure or so
convinced about it the doctor was like
okay let's have another appointment
[Music]
let's have another nice appointment
and then i missed the appointment right
i told my members
that for the first time in a million
[\h__\h] years
i
set
my
uh wake up alarm wrong which i really
that never happens to me that was really
an
absolute exception i was surprised
myself and i was so pissed up at myself
and i apologized a million times and i
felt so bad about it but anyway are
there bones
no
okay
um
but
for sure
it happens yeah and i got another
appointment
and that was
uh fine i
i made it and the doctor he wasn't mad
or anything he was like
he was really nice the other doctor lady
that i told you about that was so rude i
didn't like her
the other doctor that's actually more
like a
psycho doctor he was fine
so he kind of like
talked to me
um
she tried to basically convince me
uh that the therapy is good for me like
um
because this and dad
no no where are we going no not to the
beginning
oh thank god okay beginning of the room
[Music]
yeah and told me like about how pain
works and how chronic pain works
um that like even if in theory if you
actually oh don't you man don't have
pain
you
feel it because your brain sends these
signals
uh to your nerves that you are feeling
pain even though you aren't because
you're crying no
your system is just already that used to
it
um
and basically tricks you now
that sounds like believable i wonder if
it's really the case always though with
chronic pain that it's just basically
your brain tricking you
i i i don't know i don't want to say
that what the doctor said is wrong but i
just wonder if that's really always the
case
um
i don't know it is interesting though
[Music]
he didn't say that
oh what is this
okay
[Music]
i know
there must be an enemy here i knew it i
felt it oh somebody
bling blings
but anyway i thought i thought what he
said was interesting and i listened and
all that
and
he basically drew a whole map of
what can be the cause of pain like
uh
it kind of went
ah
uh strongly into [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] up do i need a do i need a pot into
the direction of yeah
direction of uh
could be very much a psychology
psychological issue
um for many reasons like your
environment
no stress or work or whatever
and i said that you know i'm sure that
this that can be the case but i'm not
sure if that's the case for me because
i've been having this chronic pain for
so many years where my life has changed
so much in those
[Music]
so much in those years
a big sword oh okay
really
like um
my work has changed so i don't think
it's because of the work even if that's
sometimes stressful to me
um
i don't i don't think so because my
previous job was not stressful not
really yeah and had a good time there
but still
i had the front of the tank you know
what i mean so
now there weren't many other oh yeah
chew jelly
oh okay okay
we can make potions with that or so i
think sorry i didn't read
ah
let's go let it go
but yeah i don't know i won't say that's
100 not it but
but in any case he basically just uh
told me
about all the
reasons all the things it could be
and then was like
uh
we'll we will help you
create
a strong body
to at least physically
fight
or like
help the muscles
you know blah blah blah blah blah
but then the catch is
actually he said that in the very
beginning
um
that my insurance
[Music]
doesn't even
cover that shitty special therapy they
have here
they cover the physical therapy but they
don't cover that's the first time i ever
ran into an issue like this
ever but this is only because i am
self-employed if i had a normal
insurance it would be no problem
but i have a self-employment insurance
that costs a [\h__\h] ton of money so i
would expect it i'm so mad
i would expect it to cover something
like that but it doesn't and i think
it's ridiculous
am i supposed to make them go boom by
throwing something at them
does that even work
and i could pay for it privately but it
i it's actually pretty expensive
honestly i i was like
no
i don't know if i want to strike it
because i feel like i'm going to fall
down
no no no it's not just 60 years so
it was like i don't know 130 or so per
session per session and there was uh
how many sessions was it
like 10 sessions or so
that was like i'm not gonna if uh
no no thank you
i mean it sounded interesting i was
gonna do it but not if my insurance
isn't covered what the [\h__\h] am i
supposed to do here oh no
really that's so scary i'm gonna fall
down
isn't it gonna go off immediately if i
hit it i can't even hit it it's too far
away
[Music]
huh
this is really a matter of uh
aiming
really
yeah
no
no way that the hitbox is that small
no way
[Music]
anyway
the one thing that my insurance does
cover is normal physical therapy so i
will do that somewhere else uh
starting next week
um
but
that's actually the one that i was more
like
doubtful about because that's just a
normal physical therapy and you guys
know i literally just been no [\h__\h]
way i literally just finished one
nah that landed on top you're not
telling me that that no no no no no no
no
that's [\h__\h]
you're no way i'm too close
don't [\h__\h] me
yeah
no i just feel like it's [\h__\h] like i
can do
also now i started i even started
i even started working out and i think
like
i
i'm gonna do it anyway okay but
i don't think it's necessary you're
[\h__\h] me guys are you trolling me
are you trolling me guys
are you trolling me
i wanted to do spin attack
[Music]
so it's not the stones okay it's not the
[\h__\h] stones
i think we can all
see that now
just felt wrong
uh
where was i okay so yeah
that's why i'm also very busy next week
um this is a bit different from my last
physical therapy uh because it's not
even one-on-one that's also a reason why
i was thinking like
yo if it at least was a one-on-one
physical therapy then they can focus on
my pain individually i was in a group
physical therapy
before like years ago
and it's just it makes me feel more
uncomfortable if anything i would
appreciate it being one-on-one but they
didn't
and they were not gonna do that
[Music]
but okay that's why i'm kind of busy
i'll be kind of busy
this is the room i came from
did i go in a circle
wait do i still have a key
no i don't know okay do it
i don't have a key bottom right okay i
didn't see it i looked at my gamepad oh
i finally used it for that door already
wait oh wait do the keys no are they not
one time only used
what
oh no they are i thought i used it
already
[Music]
i could have done that special attack
unfortunate
jelly yum yum yum yum
the normal keys you're supposed to use
more often than once but but only on the
same door
only on the same door
[Music]
well thank you for opening that up for
me
oh you're still lie
not anymore
all right
i see that's not working
it doesn't
there's a button there did he drop a
sword oh he just dropped the stick does
that work too really you're telling me
my sword doesn't work but
okay no that doesn't work either
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
does it close again no okay thank god
getting closer
i think we're we're pretty fast you know
yeah
so a lot of people in the chat saying
too that i'm fast
speed run
oh i hear the bird
[\h__\h]
i missed again bye-bye
hope i didn't need your item oh there he
is falling down
we're all ready
huh
no we're not at the top no no no way
that dungeon is much longer
[Music]
one hit
strapping nothing
um
dungeon is very straightforward
yeah yeah that's very straightforward
i hate those
parts where i have to stay on the side
yo
i always do it too fast and then i fall
down
oh that was close
i forgot about that
are we good to go
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
wow
i did a jump attack i forgot how to do
that yeah
oh
god it feathered i didn't drop that
before he said only sometimes
a certain strangest emanates from the
quill of this beautifully shining golden
petal
winged girls are said to be infatuated
with these treasures
really girls
it looks like a feminine feather
[Laughter]
[Music]
deja vu
maybe we can get another one of those
feathers
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
let me see if there's a heart
well i'm sorry
give me a hug
need a heart
[Music]
the [\h__\h] are you back
oh they respawn they always respawn
you gotta keep your guard up why the
[\h__\h] are there no hearts now
i'm there then i know
guys give me your hearts
please i'm dying
please
guys please hide
[Music]
do these drop cards sometimes or only
money
hallelujah stones i love you
oh god this is okay this is enough
maybe
yeah yeah i know i know i know
[Music]
maybe
drop me some heights now
okay the game hates me
the game hates me guys
what is this gotcha
what is this shitty right up huh
that's like a [\h__\h] baby
there we go how does the
[\h__\h] ladder not fall apart
and burn
explain that to me
are you gonna drop a feather
um is it gonna disappear
[Music]
i was too scared to go down
i still have the one from before right
ready
yes i have the one i have the one okay
okay now what the actual [\h__\h] there we
go
let me wait you're goody
don't fall down anymore
uh-huh
okay
faster faster
faster
that is hot
don't
don't don't
huh
ah
i'm supposed to hang right okay okay
i get it i get it i get it
strong strong tiny hands link
pretty impressive
it's his tiny [\h__\h] hands not my fault
look at this baby hands they can't hold
on to anything
yeah we were going too fast anyway we
need to go a bit slower
[Music]
we need to enjoy the game tool first
and appreciate all the details therefore
we play everything uh five times
now grab that feather
yes thank you
right on top of me
okay i'm not doing the same mistake
again go
can you [\h__\h] move it's your problem
i'm gonna wait now
yeah i just wanted that feather that i
was promised
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go oh wow
no i'm not doing it on purpose
but
i'm just not good with this kind of
stuff
thanks for the membership
link link
link link link link
link
i'm sorry what i said about your tiny
hands now hold on strong if you don't
want me to make fun of you again
hold on strong and
don't let go
go up
what do i need to do to make you go up
there we go
i was uh moving the joystick
up but he didn't want to go up
carefully
carefully where would we bring that to
the stone
okay okay
okay
thank
god can i just jump
okay okay
i prefer it inside right now normally i
don't like dungeons
because they make me nervous
but now i want to be inside why are
there peoples
on this
and like
hold on to it and crawl into it no
and that's so sucks why are there those
holes
now look into it
is that just decoration no it goes to
the left side
ah maybe i am able to come out of these
holes later
okay
let's see
do they fall down aha i thought
uh
oh yeah
it should be fine if i do that yeah yeah
yeah okay
[Music]
it's not tetra what the [\h__\h]
why is it though the ship talking to me
you are have you seen any filthy
flipping rats around
i know they are annoying but keep your
wits about you there are only rats if
you spread bait near the nest oh they
may share the store of treasure with you
why don't you try it
[Music]
sorry
um you say there are only rats but what
if i kill them will i still give me
treasure
[Music]
what are you going to give me for that
i must say
they're pretty nice for giving me
something back oh
i can even get
more bait or i can get a pear
which one should i go for it's not
really good i thought they were gonna
give me something better than this
you never saw that why not did you not
listen to the to the boat's advice
more bait
yeah
what do you mean i have to pay
40 rupees
how is that
[Music]
wait they they must be working with the
boats though because the boat told me it
would be a good idea to give them some
bait
they're ripping me off together they're
a team
they're in it for the money what the
[\h__\h] was that
what do you mean batteries i'm connected
what do you mean
what the [\h__\h]
nothing
cheapskate
bring me moist no i don't think i'll
ever give you anything anymore if i have
to buy everything off of you that makes
no sense
why would i give you a bait to
to buy more bait off of you
huh the
logic
[\h__\h] character knew it all along
my money is backside oh i should spend
it i guess
i don't like seeing my money maxed out
but there's no way to spend it here
got the compass
oh
i'll put the bait back
uh
i'll
i don't want to empty it
[Music]
i don't know what let's just put this
here i just don't want to accidentally
use it
okay oh why are there those things do i
need to fire
i don't have a key
huh
[Music]
no i want to throw it
what
the [\h__\h]
gamepad
having problems
wait i can hold it while i climb why
don't i just directly climb i don't need
to i don't i don't need to oh
okay i can climb
i can climb up this like
stone
but i can't climb up the ladder okay
okay
uh fro yeah
and now it went out it didn't
did that happen because i threw it oh
because time was just up
okay time was stuff
all right that must be a key
kagi desho konnaka
[Music]
don't fall down link don't fall down you
little [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] dropping hearts i want that that's
not fair
maybe in here
my own
maxed out
a key for another key
to open the door
where you can get another key to open
the door for another bikini
which will eventually open the door
and there you go the key
[Music]
you know what that is for
for a door
no amazing huh
[Music]
is that another
might i say okay
no this is not a key
this is a joy pendant
but i forgot
like a butterfly
okay
i bought i need the fire again
to
uh get rid of this door
oh
perfect
there we go no key this time the key is
fire which is funny because my element
is fire and i'm the key kiara
okay i'll stop now happy birthday not a
[\h__\h] ball
happy birthday to you
happy birthday see you
[Music]
happy birthday
to you
thank you for the red superchat though
so i jump in there just to make
link i hate you
i hate you for the auto jumps you stupid
[\h__\h]
i don't have to use it to activate it
right the sound was the activation i
think
it would just bring me to the beginning
i suppose
i think
it is that okay
what was that sound
this is scary what the [\h__\h] is that cage
[Music]
oh mini boss
is that it
probably need this
[Music]
are we playing hide and seek
that's all right with me i haven't
played that in a long time
guys by the way you know what i'm trying
out because my um
friend recommended it to me
[Music]
there is this uh service in my country
where uh
you you probably have something similar
to in your country guys probably i
assume
where you can um
make an account
and then you
um
you choose some
[Music]
recipes
and then they bring you weekly depending
on how often you want it to happen they
bring you the exact
amount of ingredients like by the gram
um
depending on for how many people you
want to cook it as well
hello fresh yes yes it is hello fresh
exactly
i thought that would be pretty
convenient because i can try out new
recipes without thinking too much about
it
what i need to um
get for it and uh
and i don't really like going to the
supermarket these days i always get my
groceries online anyway um
and uh
and yeah i thought it was perfect
because they gave me the right amount
because sometimes i just don't i i i
waste a lot of food and i don't want to
waste so much food and they give me
inspiration
for
no it's not about being lazy it's really
not literally not about it's about
anything but being lazy i wish i could
go to the supermarket
um
something is missing because this door
doesn't open
is there still an enemy in one of these
[Music]
[\h__\h]
the last one the very last one
so now i'm excited to try using that
i picked some interesting recipes and
they have so much choices
yeah i'll report back to you guys
i learned some new recipes for that too
because like i i know a few
i know how to cook a few things but it's
really not not much i want to you know
widen my
horizon of recipe books
there's one more here
oh
give that to me
here we go
phoenix in the supermarket just be a
fire hazard yeah that's exactly the
reason
thank you
thank you for oh
oh
how do i fight you guys again
get me i don't want no i don't
[Music]
[Applause]
my cooking streams oh i don't know i
wasn't really thinking about doing that
but
[Music]
uh
um
no that didn't work how i wanted it to
look
can you uh come over here
they left the sponsors down but i
already bought my subscriptions
[Music]
i can't fight in a tiny ass platform
like that
come on
[Music]
one more
yes
[Music]
okay that one missed but the other ones
did not yeah
how many times do i have to miss them
huh
[Music]
okay these are my new favorite most
hated enemies
why are they so [\h__\h] annoying
wonderfully you're such a genius
go [\h__\h] yourself
[Music]
i tried for the water i had to lock it
up oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] annoying
monster oh i'm so triggered
i'm still trying going duh
i tried parrying but that didn't want um
[Music]
i think i need it
what the hell
don't blame me
switch is so much better than this [\h__\h]
anyway you
wanna be switch
i [\h__\h] wanna be
ignore i can't ignore it i need to go
around the way yeah
it's in the [\h__\h] way yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah i stand by
my statement
um i remember this room i stamp on my
statement the switch is better
it's a given but this is just a wannabe
switch
looks a little bit like a switch is
trying hard to
do what the switch does
actually all right a switch wait does it
switch over i forgot does this switch
have this touch screen it does but
it does have a touch screen what does a
switch have
that the gamepad doesn't have
or the other way around what does the
gameplay have that the switch doesn't
know
it's a prototype yeah
[Music]
a camera
a virtual console
rio has a camera
okay yeah i tested it and it's [\h__\h]
so that doesn't really even count as a
camera
but okay i asked you what it has okay
switch has no stylus what's a stylus
what's that
did i say switch doesn't let you use
your touch screen when docked
or does this one
that you use i guess it does
faster cpu i think with all the
technology so switch can still look
better that wii u has a faster cpu
way better virtual console not a hot
door oh we've reached the top
oh yeah but we have to fix it from below
i think
it's problem
real sticks i mean real sticks
i mean the switch joysticks are kind of
lame
oh wow
and then you got
you got caught
oh i don't even have full health but
where's
[Music]
give me the hat
do i need the one of those big swords
for you maybe
[Music]
oh she must be so in love with me now
doesn't she actually kind of act like
she's in love with me
oh
i feel like i feel like she does have a
liking for this link
hello
kind of scary place to be yeah
very loud up there
you came to rescue me oh thank you
i actually didn't come to rescue you i
didn't even know you needed to be
rescued
i have to tell you when i found out this
is terrible some creature is doing awful
things to create fellow's tail that's
why he's so angry
oh
the great littlest tail hangs down into
the room right below there
[Music]
now before it's too late oh he stopped
because i told him to shut up
i'll go and tell everyone what's
happening
hiki no i use this to get out of here
it's what i used to get this far
oh
oh a grappling hook i thought we were
getting like a
a floaty thingy but okay
oh he's noisy again
do i need to tell him to shut up again
climb up on that little lunch over there
so i can show you something
uh-huh
uh-huh uh-huh
uh where should i put this
uh
do you want me to
use it off here
oh you don't want me to use it at all
yet right you want me
to learn it by you teaching me oh i
don't know i don't rather rather
i understand
[Music]
let's see if this is easy to use uh
which button
oh just y again
[Music]
okay
more of
that gimmick
how exciting
we're not gonna say goodbye to her
that's sad
i wish there was like an auto
auto aim for that
because in stressful situations i don't
know if i can
uh
what
if i can aim that well well how am i
supposed to open that up
oh hit it sometimes i forget my sword is
just strong enough or not
uh okay so i guess we go that direction
because that's what makes sense
awesome
i can log on
what when i locked this is what it does
that's for fighting enemies i guess
maybe
yeah yeah for enemies i was saying like
for walking onto these uh targets
faster without shaking so much
okay it works it's fast enough i guess
after stealing ayanna
stealing from enemies
oh yeah like their weapons for example
let's try it all right i was gonna steal
his weapon but i mean
no need i guess
you want to go get it
fall into the lava perhaps
be careful there buddy
people kill if they're done
people die after
okay wow i'm trying to say cool things
always ends up like this
do i need this
[Music]
do i want this to fall down by any
chance
maybe
okay i'm scared
okay okay
oh is this like a
no there's no water i was hoping it
could bring me down safely i don't just
want to jump down here
let's go
okay no fall damage
[Music]
necklace
here we have the water parts
do we need them here
ah for going back up i guess
but now i don't need that
okay
is this is this where it is no we still
need a ah
that thing this only the boss key
oh
i can do this
i thought we were going up for some
reason
[Music]
huh can never go to a bus without having
the basket oh but look at where we are
now
that looks like the entrance oh
no boss caving
[Music]
and
oopsie
nothing to catch here although a fairy
would be nice did i like miss some kind
of
optional fairy
i feel like by now it would be nice to
have one
just for safety
can you turn around
can i jump backwards
okay let's go
ah don't
go
away ah
it works but i feel like i should be
able to turn
let's try it
it should be possible stop with that uh
okay
okay okay
see the hitbox man
[Music]
um
this is where i learned to turn i guess
i need to sneeze again i think
that that are that are there we go
[Music]
i don't know
ah okay i got it
oh
got your uniform
congratulations
i was close i was like [\h__\h] dallas too
short
what
wait a second is that where i came from
did i go into the wrong direction
huh
all right look at my
map that's not where it came from
no no
the room over there has a key and that
might just be the boss key
i would say
okay
oh
it's on fire not you again
okay i should be able to kill you and
fight you normally right
just if you if you don't have the chance
to go back into the level because that's
when you heal i know i know oh wait
never mind i use you as a weight
can you drop it
on
this
can i even kill these things
[Music]
okay
i waited too long
fast fast fast
i think you're so stupid
i pressed a to open it not to roll into
it
did you notice for the thumbnail of this
series
i um as the counter for the episodes
i made um like a little boss key thingy
did you see
[Music]
yeah
yeah put some effort there
and we have uh unfortunately no link in
the thumbnail because someone better
than link took up the middle spot
looking like a cartoon link but not
quite link that was uh drawn by
sean um
was really good at like recreating
certain game styles thank you
yeah
link is just
not there it doesn't exist i am the
protagonist
and for me i'm the protagonist
legend of kiara
the windwaker and the intro was by the
name uh from cow carrot cow kelly
uploaded that on twitter so i downloaded
it uh
yeah that's cute
[Music]
i
i pressed x i wanted to
shoot this thing at it but
too slow
all right
right too slow
all right uh
am i going the right way oh i'm just
going back now was there no other way
yeah
i don't know this was just for the
bosque i didn't see the
boss door
but it's on the third floor
it is on the third floor
so i have to go to the second floor
first because now we're on the first
floor
oh the myth place plushies arrived oh
you mean the mascots
yeah yeah i got the i got my own one
the kotoni one
it's really
chunky i love it
yo
really chunky wonky
yeah
challenge
um
other news what do we have
i'll tell you
a little secret
um next month
there is a lot of stuff coming out
um
i need to go oh
[\h__\h]
no stop
so we have my original song coming out
next month finally
i was working on that one for a while
uh and
i mean maybe that's a shortcut
now thanks for the shortcut i think
that's where i wanted to go
no wait that's not where i wanted to go
damn it it knows where i came from when
i entered the room
it's so close yeah um i think i told you
guys that mean and elena wants to put
out
uh a song cover a little song cover just
to know you know we wanted to do one
anyway and it's a perfect timing we
thought to do it during the vacation to
also kind of fill
fill some kind of
content lagging content in case we can't
stream
but turns out
that is not the only thing the only
musical thing
uh a certain sound now i'm not gonna say
i'm gonna keep the surprise a little bit
longer i guess
i press a instead of
why why why did i do it again why did i
do it again
[Music]
no someone unexpected
for you guys apparently because you guys
are not mentioning her in the chat
um
ask me
for
a song collab and this is i think the
first time that ever happened
me being asked
and not me being the initiator so i was
very excited
like the the thing with me and uh
uh
what was i going to say
oh yeah just go higher by the way
the thing with me and elena was is kind
of like
on
in me and energy as well
it's kind of like we both wanted to do
it
but
me being asked for
something like that it's the first time
so i'm
i'm quite happy
about it and uh actually
this person
suggested a certain song
now this this i can say this
i press the same button as i did before
maybe it wasn't the same but the right
but i'm confused um
uh
uh this person suggests the song
yeah
and i was like uh
i really wanna
i really want to do a song collab
with this person but the song suggestion
was
you go higher ah with this thing
the song suggestion was a problem
because uh this person
suggested connector
from
uh
maggie was it right i forgot already
yeah
and
i said uh
can you guys imagine why
what that works oh my god i'm surprised
actually
can you guys guess why i didn't want to
do that
oh my god
okay
yeah because i'm energy i was like i
mean it's not like we're planning to
cover that song anytime soon
but for me
when i think of that song i i think of
nancy like you know
and i feel like it's like cheating if i
do a song cover that also sounds so
official
it sounds so official
if it's like only a kadaoka stream where
we sing it together and i feel like
that's a little bit of a different story
but if it's a song cover i don't know
myself yeah
right i'm faithful
i'm faithful
but
is this gonna work or is it gonna be
lopsided oh it's okay um
um so i told her
that mysterious person
i told her yo
i'm so flattered thank you for asking i
don't want to do it but um
i'm sorry i need to tell you actually uh
there's a reason
why i cannot do this song and the reason
is energy and i sent her a clip
of the whole uh connect story like the
the time where we
miraculously
sang that song randomly at the same time
when we were both doing separate karaoke
streams
uh
yeah i told her the story and i was like
you know
sorry i don't know it feels wrong
it just feels wrong to me we can do any
other song but not this one
and then she was like oh i'm sorry i
didn't know that happened no of course
let's let's do something else
yeah that was funny
what
giant mod what the [\h__\h] what does that
mean
well what is that question
huh i won't tell you yet
but it will come out next uh next
next month yeah may in may sometime in
may i'm not exactly sure when
uh don't we need water
what misa
i know we don't need one huh
oh my god we're right at the bus do you
have it
yes
really
it's money okay it's only 10.
this is also money
no no go away
i hate you
oh
one of the nights chris
okay i'll take that that's uh that
actually works for me
[Music]
can i get a heart too please
there must be a heart in one of this
yeah uh there's gonna be a lot coming
out in in may the sun
okay
[Music]
will be on my channel
uh
for no particular reason i don't know
another one
i only have one bottle
oh man
uh and the one with this mysterious
person will be on the mysterious
person's channel
um
do i remember what this boss was like
i remember one boss but i'm not sure it
wasn't really wind waker it was that
skyward sword
that was probably skyward sword
i don't know some just something some
stuff with the
like ripping
ripping out something with the
new weapon that we have
said
i'm scared i'm gonna
i'm gonna dye my hairs i have a bad
feeling oh [\h__\h] i didn't save can i
still save yes
oh hallelujah
uh
[Music]
is the big version of that [\h__\h] worm
um
somewhat yeah okay i hate you already oh
no
ah
okay i guess when it's so close to me i
will have to like so
[Music]
oh interesting what do i do in this case
this is what i was supposed to do but it
just didn't uh
work this time
[Music]
or am i supposed to land on top of it
when it's stuck like that
ah because if i ah okay i think i
understand the tail
uh
and then we will drop on him
can you do that again dude do i have to
stop for you
there we go okay
uh
wait
okay
never mind but i understand do it again
i didn't see it
do it
got it tony quickly had it
let's do it what are you doing
[Music]
i know i'm not supposed to land on it
but uh
wait wait what
what
[Music]
however you would be able to change your
perspective to see what is around i know
i know i know i know i know i'm a bit if
i have a bit
[Music]
oh
i finally got one
hold on dude
what are we doing up here oh yeah okay
okay
okay okay we wait for it to drop there
we go one damage i suppose we have to do
this three times step in the sunkai
and then
i go down again i can uh maybe relax
oh are we doing it on a higher level
i'm coming down
i even roll
up
[Music]
but he's so fast now
i mean the eye is also target but it's
really hard to get the eye
oh okay wait i did i did it while
walking
[Music]
i did it while running
a little bit stressed out
[Music]
i should have just stayed out there you
guys said it's easier when i stay up
[Music]
what what's happening
i'm here
[Music]
now would have been a good chance to do
it like right away again
he moves so fast
[Music]
trying to stay calm
i can't get the eye right unless he's
like really close to me
okay i have to do it while running again
ah
dangerous
[\h__\h]
okay okay i got
[Music]
what is this camera what is this camera
i couldn't like properly move it
is that
it
nope this is not it um i would like some
healing though um because i'm so [\h__\h]
now
okay can i take that can you can you not
be an idiot and maybe take that [\h__\h]
pot
okay okay i suppose that uh we're not
doing the same thing again
um
where are we
[Music]
are we still doing the same thing
you get the i know
oh oh and then
yeah okay we're not doing the same thing
anymore that's good because i thought
that would be too boring
i'm sweating though
my hands are sweating a bit
okay okay
okay okay okay that wasn't so bad i just
had to figure out the system in the
beginning
i did fine no one can tell me that was
so bad
yoga
[Music]
especially in the second phase which
should be more difficult i actually had
less problems
does this give me a full heart
in this game increase by one yes okay
we get full hearts full hearts
oh yeah i don't even need the money
we have calmed the big great balloon
[Music]
thank you everybody
already two dungeons done
the i i consider the first thing being
like a half of a dungeon let's say 1.5
dungeons
that was for power dungeon and this was
a full dungeon
you should be done screaming
watch the skit calm down
calm down now
oh down
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
is he gonna give me the ball
[Music]
are you impressed by my extreme gamers
skills yo
nice to meet you i'm the whole live ian
gamer takanashi kiwawa
well prince connelly don't you have
something you want to say
oh
i heard everything from medley
chihuahua
thank you so much
i'm sorry i mistrusted you
i hope i can be like you someday kiwawa
you're welcome buddy i just
oh that looks like a dragon ball
right
i don't even watch dragon ball i never
watched it but i know that looks like a
dragon ball
wait that is funny because there's a
dragon on top of their island
[Music]
is that on purpose
is that a reference on purpose
[Music]
to you
i wonder if they're doing that reference
somehow
a salmon egg from splatoon night hodo i
don't get that reference
maybe it's just like a tiny small hint
it's not even that tiny for me it's not
very obvious
here
i want you to take this kiwa
giving you the thing i value most will
give me the courage i need to stand up
to bad things
i got the dragon ball
isn't there more
isn't dragon ball about collecting
dragon balls like a certain amount how
many are there
is the gem that rita's claim was passed
down from the great goddess why why why
am i really okay to getting a seven
uh-huh
should i really be having this
yo
[Music]
uh who's talking
boy
a great mother is grateful to you
[Music]
wow
i feel so enlightened
use the wind guards
wind
that's what he said but i don't
understand
i wonder what it means
[Music]
who's talking
the wind got swing i wonder if what he's
talking about has anything to do with
the wind track i remember windshrine
[Music]
the highland text
who's talking three types of dragon ball
some give one with some they're free
they give wishes oh i didn't know what
they did
dragon ball make any wish come true
any
i almost forgot only once
the great balloon also names yuki wawa a
true hero but he knows what he's talking
about
yes uh-huh
almost anything not everything certain
extent
you don't like dragon ball don't you
i agree with him as far as we're
concerned quebec you're really a real
hero well i'm going to go and visit
balloon
i'll come and see you sometime with the
best pair of wings ever
hey prince komadi
thanks so much
see you again someday
[Music]
queen i like her she's so cute
job me good job me
um i couldn't even continue on playing
but i need to consider that i have some
attack serene i don't know how many it
was
it probably should end it here how many
dungeons are there how long is this game
again 24 hours what did google say 24
hours was maybe the
was maybe lynx awakening wind waker game
length
at 29 hours
approximately that's not even that long
so with me vibing and chilling maybe
like 32 hours how many streams is that
30 hours how many streams uh
i
five and a half hours
only five hours because i was transiting
for 40 minutes so five hours of um
[Music]
six streams
approximately six streams
if if they're all about this length
yeah
[Music]
um
so um
the thing is uh next week there will be
no wind waker because i'm kind of busy
um i can't stream that often next week
that's why there's no schedule because i
also am very busy next week um and i i
have to use the few days where i can
stream to do portal too
in preparation for collab with
kobo and that takes up two days two days
of streams already
and then uh
there was
if possible member stream
and something else i needed to do i
forgot
um but yeah my schedule is already
pretty filled up and i kind of
you know
we will start the wind waker weekends
properly
uh in the week after i guess
i wanted to be the wind wiggle weekends
saturday sunday
i also have like some
other things to do like
recordings
next week
and there's there's something cool you
know i never get called for uh collabs
from whole life members i always have to
do it myself but i do get called quite
often for official
um live things on the official channel
and uh yeah there's something i need to
record for that next week
yeah it also takes up a couple of hours
and i'm looking forward to that uh i
don't know when you guys will be able to
see it i think it will it might be a
while
i'm not sure when they're releasing it
but
um
yeah and it's gonna be japanese content
but but i think there will be people who
can maybe
translate it i don't know
but i'm looking forward to it i'm
you know the management acknowledges
i remember they when they asked me for
it jenna said that they uh they thought
of me because but let me
let me i think i can i think i can get
the
the offer because i can also turn it
down of course but why would i turn it
down but it's usually it's like hey we
have this uh from management do you want
to partake in it
and yeah
uh let me see i want to say
what they said
oh there it is i won't say what it is
but
ah here it says
they would like to have you on the who
as you have strong japanese skills and
are very good at variety talk
yeah i
yes am
writing is my thing
management
acknowledges my very strong japanese
skills and my variety talk
yo
management acknowledges me and it makes
me happy
there was another like random thing like
genma was like hey can you help us with
this thing here we need to test
something out and we ask you for it
because
you're you're the one who always answers
the fastest out of whole life in english
[Music]
hey legit ask me because i'm the fastest
we're testing something out i'm like oh
sure
all right like it's a it's something
that needs my
needs whoever is helping out with it
their attention and i'm like ah leave it
to me
i'm most reliable and and answering i
gotta say the fastest
no ghosting in kiwawa town
um
you're like
oh yeah yeah but
also very reliable i would say
yeah
i don't know
[Music]
today is sunday by the way um as i said
there will be no schedule but oh by the
way we're still reading superchat i'm
just saying for everybody who's leaving
the stream before the super chat reading
comments but let me just tell you
tomorrow
so you know yeah the spain um
food box thingy i wanted to do that
because we we're supposed to do it uh
last week but then i replaced it with
koi woody sample uh sampling collapsing
with six sent by when it comes to
japanese whole life numbers
it's just it's just natural um yeah uh
so that will be tomorrow that will be
tomorrow
[Music]
night
so i'll be putting up the
reservation
uh for the next week's streams as soon
as possible always
uh
in exchange for
not having a schedule all right
um because i need to
i have some things planned but overall
i'm not sure how next week is gonna go
so
there will be a little bit of
uncertainty but just just chill
everybody tomorrow there will be a
stream i'll tell you that
but yeah not so many streams next thing
okay
ah this is fun though i was really happy
to
go into this wind waker world again for
the first time in a long time it's so
beautiful like honestly the way i look
at it now this is how i perceived it
back when i played it on the gamecube
but i did look at some screenshots uh
comparison screenshots they did improve
the graphics a lot it's just like you
guys probably know that feeling right
when you look at old graphics that are
remastered and you're like this is
exactly how i remember it though
everything just
looks
better because
you
this was all that that was already great
graphics for
back then so you remember it fondly you
remember it as back then you were
impressed by it and then
now i look at this remastered and i'm
like isn't this exactly what it looked
like
but yeah it's good that we chose the hd
remake i suppose it looks it looks much
better when looking at the screenshots
that's that is true
um remember remember to say thank you
true
very true
look at the gamepad i'm looking at it
continue i'm actually going to tie the
screen oh well
isn't better graphics i mean yeah i
guess it's just rendered i see that as
better graphics
i would say that's better graphics okay
[Music]
else the shading
what do you mean it's still cell shading
you mean because there's some like these
soft lights here and there
oh i think that's beautiful
and i didn't have this soft light here
in the original i think
[Music]
music was also remastered oh
sounds the same to me
i don't know what it is then
thanks for the stream thank you guys um
i'm hoping to have you all again here
when we continue the wind wiggle
weekends there will be a little break
but
uh i think we're all looking forward to
it excitedly is that a word
i'm really excited to play this game
yeah when do i go when i got
let's see if after i
clear it by myself for the first time if
i can with full confidence say that it's
my favorite zelda game i i mean
the ones that i've
really
cleared played and cleared all by myself
fully so far are i think only the ones i
played on stream
the other ones i
only really uh
you know
touched
while my brother was playing him
but i mean i i do have a lot of them in
my memory for example twilight
princess which i i do consider um
playing too after windbreaker i wouldn't
mind playing twilight princess but um
is there a twi uh twitch a switch port
or is the wii u port the port is that
even the port
i think my brother played it on the wii
not on the wii u
we used to play it on the wing no
switchboard so the wii u is like the
best one
not gonna buy a wii just for 12 printers
it better be good on the wii u yeah i
thought there was a hd remaster too
oh sorry what it would make sense to
play it on the wii u
um
would be cool
because i want to make use of my wii u
now that we have it
i know there's not much
that
is like exclusively for the wii u that i
would want to play and make sense at
least not not much that i know of
better buy as soon as you get to each
other version yeah yeah
oh yeah yeah
i guess i will
um buying some wii u shopkins yeah but
i'm not sure like i looked at the wii u
shop
and i was like
which ones
makes sense to buy which ones do we have
on the switch and i didn't want a one by
one look at
uh
look it up online but good to know that
twilight princess would be worth it also
i really like how i can be
like my wind waker smells good
well i can like try to eat it
i want to play around with this thing in
my
in my thumbnail so i have a funny idea
for the next thumbnail i hope i don't
forget it until next time i should make
it ahead of time
today
yeah
[Music]
it down my nose or pick my nose a little
bit
i'll pick my teeth with it
i love that we got that uh
done
that wind waker when i was playing
skyward sword right or was it for
uh
for link's awakening i think it was
skyward sword
[Music]
a multi-purpose
very multi-purpose
[Music]
chicken nugget on the end of the
windwaker like you're using it like a
fork
why would i
eat chicken nuggets with a fork though
i just eat chicken nuggets with my hands
who doesn't who eats chicken nuggets
with a fork
mmm chicken nuggets
[Music]
and it's already 9 p.m what the [\h__\h]
how many super chats do i have to read
do you guys know how many streams which
one's gonna have to read the ones from
last time and today right
i think i wanna um
order food to arrive later
just so that uh
[Music]
i make sure it arrives
i cooked the past two days
also i had my banana pancakes again
today i made banana blueberry pancakes
again today i cook a lot of breakfast
these days
youtube's accepting credit cards in may
when you have to spend time ah you don't
want to put too much into it ah but the
nintendo eshop uh
[Music]
the wii u shop and the general nintendo
shop uh um
credit
is connected like you can connect it and
i guess then it doesn't matter if i
charge it with a lot of money
yeah
wait wait what
charging
runs out earlier then the wii shop
actually is still
uh usable right did i understand that
correctly
yeah
until
free to spend it
but they stop accepting credit cards
in may okay
yeah yeah so i just charge it move some
money now
don't have to buy all the games yet
eh button can i not just if it's
connected anyway can i not just charge
my normal even if that runs out in may
can i not just charge my normal nintendo
account since they're connected and then
just buy whatever
[Music]
actually doesn't matter does it
yeah it doesn't matter unless you don't
have like
like how would that even affect you only
if you
have no access to a normal nintendo
store to charge your money there
which is easily creatable
[Music]
that's weird
i don't understand why do they close it
to begin with like ah
always keep the online store open that's
so weird why would you it's not like you
have to create physical copies and send
them to someone and ship them to someone
it's just a download
why can't yeah
why why you close it
why
why clothing
[Music]
likes a wheel
keep up the servers and
i with how much money nintendo makes i
doubt that that hurts them in any way
keeping up a wii u
thingy server or they could at least
like
at least make it so that
like okay kill the wii u shop just make
it so that the nintendo eshop is usable
in the wii u and then all problems are
solved is that not something they could
do
[Music]
is that not possible
just combine them merge them
let me buy the games for wii u in the
normal nintendo show
gotta be so
why gonna be so complicated
i see you want the money from my wallet
it's okay i will give it to you nintendo
last night
[Music]
okay
okay guys you listen to this oh should
we keep this on the soundtrack while i'm
while i'm reading super chats for now
you listen to this because i have to
think about what to eat
i guess i could go to the
i could go to the inter interruption
intermission stream uh screen
for now
and i don't have to feel bad about not
talking all right give me like
four or five minutes
of chill time
and then we'll read super chat ok
so
gives me time to make food in five
minutes
what are you making
what are you doing what kind of food is
that five-minute food
not that simple yeah well if it was very
simple i would hope they would do it so
i guess it's not that simple why are you
looking like that link huh okay so shook
fun stream
thank you i'm glad you enjoyed it
oh yeah cup ramen i guess okay you guys
need to eat more
nutrient food
food that has more vitamins and
nutrients okay not cup noodles
put your and put my stream on your phone
and cook something more
complicated something bigger
make some proper food
all right not cup noodles i don't i
don't tolerate cup noodle uh
any room
for my chickens
[Music]
wrong wrong one here here here
we go
[Music]
foreign
me
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
oh
i don't know what to eat
i don't know what i want to eat
[Music]
we talked about chicken nuggets so i
kind of want chicken nuggets but i don't
want to order from a fast food
restaurant
and i actually don't
chicken nuggets from
more proper
burger places
i want the
industrial chicken sockets
but now we're ordering something else
[Music]
okay
me
[Music]
foreign
i don't know what i want
i'm looking at everything i can't decide
[Music]
not order an oreo shake
no
[Music]
um
i had pizza in like two days ago i want
pizza
[Music]
one day ago
okay i found something interesting
[Music]
oh
what is
[Music]
this right [\h__\h] fast food it is
wow
oh
[Music]
show okay
okay okay i'm almost there
i mean i can only order for now
is it because it's already so late
i don't want to eat it now
[Music]
then i would have to eat it on stream
oh
yeah yeah sunday
i mean it's not going to be here right
right away
maybe
maybe 30 minutes or 40 or 15.
okay let's do it and then i can
either
end the stream or
or eat on stream
we'll see
okay
[Music]
it should take some time anyway
would i
[Music]
where's my office
oh my god
jonathan
no
i'll get you out of there i'll get you
out of there jonathan
[Music]
where's my chat
here's my chat
you know speaking of offices
amma's office
did you see ama's new office where she
has like a newspaper in front of her
body and she has like her legs crossed
and all that
i think it's so cool it looks so good
it looks so good
i love that
the moment i saw it i was like holy [\h__\h]
that's so cute
it's so funny
i want to think of something like that
like something original like that
don't wanna
copy that but every time i see like
people coming up with new poses for legs
like also good uh good i had something
like that before you know with her with
her lying on the sofa
with her legs
crossed on lying on her tummy
in her sofa like stuff like that
it
it's so cute
i want to think of something like that
i can't think of anything something that
covers my body nicely uh
but the problem also with my all my
hairstyles
is that
like
there's some difficulty with like if
they're if it's something i have to put
on top of myself
then it will always like
have to explain this
i don't know how to explain this yeah
also that i'm too animated i move too
much but if
if it's something like what ammo has i
think it could work
but also like it's better with short
hair that ends above your shoulders
um because of reasons that are hard to
explain for me
and with longer hair that's over the
shoulders
i can't explain do you know what i mean
they have hair that i think it ends
before their shoulders
so yeah ah thank you
thank you come sanita good night
cuts off weirdly
i need a short hair hairstyle
short hair hairstyle
yes
yeah it gets cut off by the overlay for
example oh anyway since food is on this
way i should
[Music]
ah
i should
i should read the budget sorry i got a
message from kobo
i confused me
asking for what time for collabo
good question
[Music]
gotta go boss good night thank you for
watching
[Music]
yeah i don't know if she's planning on
playing portal before our collab i
really recommend it i told her she i
recommend it but
i don't know if she takes it that
seriously
like i probably wouldn't have taken it
that seriously either if it was just an
option
and i didn't know that um portal is so
much fun
[Music]
and it would really help
but it's okay even if she doesn't play
it i'm gonna carry her because i played
portal 1 and i will play portal 2 next
week alone
i will carry her if need be
yeah we'll hand hand hold her yes yes
i'll carry the whole stream and look
like the super cool
senpai that i am
all right i think we have to redo a
lingo super chats oh there will be a lot
of korean ones uh
[Music]
where is it here it is
yes
yes yes there we go
[Music]
okay are are any of my korean friends
here to pick up their super chat oh i
see some oh
hello
sorry to keep you waiting
[Music]
i have to be fast anyway so let's do
our best special
myself
let me drink some water
thank you for waiting oh wow where are
so many of you here
at this time
[Music]
all right
star team starting with jenkins monkey
dancing
and jacket's monkey
twice cocoon
pepsi danger
thank you thank you for sending that
help by the way as well it was very
helpful although
the reason i
stumbled into that dangerous temple
was because you told me there's a hoodle
in that area and um
you should have warned me that there's a
dangerous temple there that i shouldn't
walk into yo why did you not warn me
why did you not warn me
i spent like
millions of healing items there
worth so much money but then after that
i did like a lot of side quests
and gained back a lot of money
so it's okay but wow wow wow wow that
took up like almost my full inventory of
healing items so at least um
at least my
hp goomies um
wow
pretty sure we warned you about it on
stream even if you did that's like a
million years ago
but yeah
i made it through all is good it was
pretty tight hand though pretty tight
hand
there's another owl here i know i knew
you'd help me find my friends whoo-hoo
this i was different it's scary who it
hoots differently to who
might be zugo oh yeah [\h__\h] duolingo it's
a dogel
you're right hoodoo
i love who though who is so cute
[Music]
i love you so much
my sweet holy
i love you
i love you i'm sorry i can't be waiting
for so long
after you get all those uh
they give you a queen hoodle
accessory and i put that on top of
a
ring well now instead of the small
hoodle and holy [\h__\h] is way bigger than
her own head it looks ridiculous there's
like a huge huddle
on her head now and i suppose that after
you get those final additional noodles
they will give you a king noodle maybe
which will be even bigger
probably yeah because they give a queen
hoodle and then they add some more
noodles in the map to find
probably the kingdom then
no
is that really the final reward that's
not quite worth it an accessory i hope
they give me more
maybe although rinwell i think gets like
some like um skills
that you can activate
through the huddle quest
i think
like uh not i don't think they're called
skills like traits or you know what that
was that uh
when you use the sp points
i think yeah she gets a pool exactly
that where she can use her sp points for
some extra skills so i guess that's one
thing
titles
titles not really titles
but the extra status thingies
some of them you only get from quests so
a violent everglade in dankester
and now i know
like the
i don't even need to try to read your
name because the
the way
the korean letters are aligned in your
name
it's just i know
by heart that this is you
barely anyone else has so many
korean letters in their name and you
usually always have a cute whole life
member as your profile picture
so it's really easy to recognize you
skye duncan thank you for the pinky
sorry about i'm gonna miss your korean
stream but i need to have sure have
enough energy to do some workout oh
that's okay twin shroud will become the
most delicious chicken in kfb oh
not a hotel
the most delicious that is quite a high
goal for you to set for yourself but
good luck with that i'm sure you can get
pretty delicious mm-hmm
thank you maybe you saw the archive
anyway so it's all good don't worry
about missing a stream or two
i appreciate you being here and trying
to be here and catching up on the
archives and all that thank
[Music]
now in order for me to not take too much
time reading trying to read these korean
super chats
i will
uh use papago
[Music]
and oh it says
otherwise i have to use my my brain too
much and even if i may be able to read
it i don't know what it means so
[Music]
the hair ornament is pretty what ah the
one in the thumbnail
i think
um that's why i chose it for this stream
as a thumbnail but i think um this was
supposed to be like a korean
version of korean style traditional
style version of my main uniform
yeah
[Music]
ah this is
a
similar name but not quite
the song meme comes on
the pink super chat mak sung min song
thank you a good comprehension really
it's so sweet thank you very much i'm
trying my best to study i don't have
that much time with currently being
really busy in whole life but
with the little time that i have every
now and then i want to do my best to
study a little bit um
yeah
thank you for
supporting me
yeah i will do my best
[Music]
i am
and this one says oh this is easy
very easy just keep on repeating words
because i don't understand anything
anyway
thank you thank you
oh dear so many korean names
oh dear oh dear oh dear
oh it's really a lot
[Music]
oh that one was a pinky thank you for
the pink super chat
it says
it says in english king sejong
compliments the manager very very what
is king sigil is that
a real translation of the hair accessory
i wonder what that is
does somebody know in the chat
maybe they mean the clothes
i'm not sure what compliments me
oh
ah king station who created hunger
oh compliments me because i learned it
or something
maybe
oh
[Music]
i would have never known that if it
weren't for the chat
oh thank you guys for being here
thank you
[Music]
why wireless
are you in the chat i think i saw you
but maybe not maybe i'm imagining things
for the pink super chat hole
he says
it says we want wages what do you mean
you have wages you just pay them to me
what's the problem
these new korean fans come in here and
just scream
we want wages we want money
pay me pay me you think it's that easy
you have to earn it
you earn it by paying me
also kind of uh
it doesn't work like that you say you
want money but you're paying me money at
the same time so it's kind of con
contradictionary don't you think
contradictory contradictionary
contradiction
i
don't i don't know how to speak english
kim hilsa
another one thank you very much oh
trying to teach me uh
some korean here well
more and fumbling
the point of them is that they come out
from
her mu if you add lines on the top of
the muhammadan will there be humahuma
and tomohome as long as they look like
they're from whom any font can be right
one you've learned before is one of the
cursive scripts yeah we
and there was some confusion about that
one sign i think it's a ch
or the j
that looks different
looks different in duolingo
but apparently it's yourself
just the thing about the font
they they both mean the same thing yeah
kind of weird but okay
i'm trying to remember it as if thank
you for the red super chat normal normal
oh so sweet since it's so nice to see
always working hard don't overdo it take
care of your health and i want to see
you for a long time
you are so clean
thank you for your kindness
wow
thank you
[Music]
thank
no good gentlemen
thank you for the pink super chat i saw
you in the chat my raccoon friend
with the laser eye
i think is more similar in pronunciation
to
[Music]
um i know it's supposed to be pronounced
like
kind of like that i but in my brain when
i learned it
uh i just tried to remember the letters
and
then it turns out very german
um yeah but i'll try to pronounce it
correctly just in my brain in order to
remember what what the letter stands for
it needs
[Music]
just to write it out but to pronounce i
would say
[Music]
something like that
i'm still very very very
uncertain and unsure about everything so
i need to study more to be more
confident
now i
i don't have enough confidence to really
use the
the little korean that i
am able to read because also it takes so
much time
to think about it but thank you i'll do
my best please keep on following me and
my progress
yeah yeah
fighting fighting
you're doing good thank you
mom if i had more time
i could get better much faster but
i don't even know when i can do those
lessons probably not in may
no time
not in may i mean april april is almost
over anyway
but yeah
may also looks difficult but maybe maybe
i can start at least can't do it every
week but maybe
sometime well while i'm in the maldives
it's probably not gonna happen
thank you chunk rain
thank you very much you're always here
even if it's not a korean learning
stream thank you thank you thank you
very much
of course when i study korean
and so many more of them show up but but
but but
you're always here i see you
thank you for being part of kfb
my loyal
korean chicken
[Music]
crazy green bird obsessed with milk and
cucumbers yeah
i like cucumbers
i like
milk when i don't have to drink it alone
but cucumber milk i've heard for the
first time
kind of
i don't wait but okay you do you
duolingo you're just trying to teach me
some words or somebody
i think said on on twitter that or
somewhere else i don't know
maybe it was trying to teach me um
[Music]
uh what's the word vowels or so
because like
it probably was trying to focus on wow
violence is the vowels
because it was like
right
it just sounded like a lot of gibberish
that was probably on purpose to
not make it too difficult but that was
it had the opposite effect it made it
very difficult because i could barely
hear the difference in the words
it all sounded the same
what
[Music]
yeah korean kfb bros are dope
y'all are you all are
[Music]
um
that one is so easy i should be able to
read it but
i'm scared
it's me
uh meaty
[Music]
i can read your name your name is so
easy hallelujah
it's a it's for babies like me
[Applause]
that one is easy
okay okay okay
all right
[Music]
get your [\h__\h] together gamepad i need
your music
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah it's a christmas miracle not really
but yo yesterday
yesterday for some reason i felt like i
really missed christmas i want christmas
to
come quickly quickly quickly
[Applause]
by the way i really stutter so much i
hate it i notice it so much
like
when i speak english on stream
why do i speak like this
how can people not always like
stutter while they talk
how do you do it
i stutter so much i interrupt myself so
much and i do so many uh
i hate it
i hate it so much i i i wasn't so
bothered by it in the beginning but
maybe it's because
i've been doing this for a long time now
and these things stand out so much to me
now i hate
[Music]
foreign
it really bothers me and i try to not
talk like this
it stands out so much to me
i hope it doesn't stand so much out to
you guys
[Music]
i hope so
what i do a lot
a huge habit i have is i start a
sentence and then i'm like oh i go back
a few steps by saying because
and first even though i already started
the sentence i i go back and i explain
like i go a goal and and tangent about
like the origins of why i'm saying what
i'm about to say or something like that
it's so stupid can i shut up for once
you didn't notice
not because yeah i'm not staying that
long can i not can i not
oh
but i don't think i do that in german do
i
i would have to observe myself for a
while
um
thank you guys
as long as i'm more bothered by it than
you are then it's okay i guess
ah i like how you speak are you sure
about that
maybe it's like i think i remember paul
moos saying
that she stutters
[Music]
uh but i was like yeah what do you mean
you stutter
what
the whole chat was like what what do you
mean you stutter i don't
what are you talking about
but i think it's more noticeable for me
oh
[Music]
like from homer i had no idea what she
was talking about
for me
i think it's more noticeable but it
might just be a big part of it might
just be because of
me not
having it as my native language
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
not even that hungry right
now oh it looks so good from like the
outside
oh maybe i'll start snacking on
the
fries
[Music]
where's the dress where's the thingy
where's mine
that works hi snowman
oh
where's my mail i'll get my mail
i want my mail
[Music]
foreign
oh
yeah i have no space to eat here
uh
the game pad will be
[Music]
i like eating fries
sometimes without anything and then i
have some times where i want to eat it
with a lot of mayo
it depends but recently a bit more on
the mayo side which is very unhealthy
but [\h__\h] it
who gives a [\h__\h]
mayo thank god i have mayo at home
i usually don't but the other day i
bought some mayo fries and mail yes i
love it
i used to like it more of ketchup then i
had a face where i started eating it
with mayo always and then i had a face
where i started eating it with nothing
now i'm back with mail
[Music]
no i mean
no normal mayo you guys why are you so
shocked about it
[Music]
big thing in europe and japan maybe not
no surprise or not you guys don't do it
in america i thought you guys love mail
i thought you guys love mayo too
low mail
but yeah japan definitely loves mayo
they put mayonnaise everywhere
that is true they put it on okonomiyaki
they put it on yakisoba they put it on
a pizza
which i really i don't like having mayo
everywhere
i'm not like that okay
especially not on pizza
no mayo on pizza
not for me
[Music]
worse than tuna it's funny that you say
that because
one pizza one of the most popular pizzas
in japan is tuna mayo
[Music]
um
don't you i my burger's gonna get cold
if i don't eat fast but i don't wanna
eat it all on the stream that stresses
me out don't see y'all
don't you guys
i should not call it here
tomorrow is a snack box stream so it's
gonna be relatively short anyway i have
a lot of time to
have a lot of time to um read super
chats
[Music]
[Applause]
you know i feel bad if i mute myself and
don't talk to you
[Music]
is inna streaming today
i know she had issues but she said she
wanted to fix it till sunday right
[Music]
she is did she fix it finally does she
make it
i don't envy her
she's more tech savvy than i am if my pc
were to break down like that
holy [\h__\h] i would be so lost she has a
whole new pc
oh [\h__\h]
she had to rebuild i know she tried a
lot of things i don't know what the end
solution was
[Music]
or maybe today
it's not fixed either
oh
oh but it's in one hour
it was supposed to be in one hour
frankenstein the new one oh dear that's
so stressful
like was she even able to work on other
things when her pc was broken
[Music]
there was a whole week of no pc
oh no
[Music]
it was issa clyde
oh she has a stream reservation up okay
[Music]
um
it has a laptop
[Music]
um
okay oh man i hope she doesn't feel too
frustrated by it i i probably would
feel very stressed frustrated and
stressed out about it
because you know
you guys are also always very supportive
but
you know there's a there's a point where
the whole oh hollowing anchors
joke gets really
like it feels like pressure
when things
don't go well for one day and you have
to cancel a stream or so okay
happens but when that continues for like
a whole week for example
and you can't stream for that long
not only enough happened to other whole
live english members too
like similar things
that is like
um
people actually also get mad at you for
not being able to fix things but like
you know we're also no technicians it's
not like we can get tech support from
cover because they're like on the other
side of the [\h__\h] world
and
yeah things just you know we try to you
know have things
go well but it doesn't always go wrong
sometimes things always go bad for
several days in continuation
and it's really stressful but
yeah just you just have to be patient
both the audience and the person who's
um
going through it
yeah
just have to be patient and and deal
with the fact that okay there's not
gonna be a stream for a few days it's
just how it is
it's not like there's no other people
streaming that you could watch
there's more than enough
yeah a party outfit reveal well at least
that was just one time but i was really
i was so nervous because that was a huge
thing
i was so nervous that it would happen
again
[Music]
and that people would be like kiara why
do you [\h__\h] it up two times what is
wrong with you why did you not prepare
it properly why did you not test it out
properly why did you don't fix it why
did you not have something
on the
as an um
side thing too in case it doesn't work
then you can use your laptop leave blah
blah blah
well thankfully mostly
i have not had
technical issues in the past months
thankfully
[Music]
i love potato fries
i love
potato fries
[Music]
i can
while i'm eating potato fries i can
still talk to you guys
but when i eat my burger i have to
[Music]
probably dip out
them
and they're a mix of crunchy and soft
which is
pretty good
[Music]
i'm excited for the burger dough
no i think i wanna
watch something while i'm eating it's
more
relaxed and that's the one thing about
[Music]
when i have
dinner i always it's like a ritual for
me to watch something while i eat
i cannot
eat
anything without watching something
unless i'm with other people okay
same
yeah
you guys are watching me but i have
nothing to watch
[Music]
my
i just realized actually the food came
earlier than i expected it
[Music]
only i had a bit more time
ah maybe maybe i should
and she'll
i know
but tomorrow i have so much time to read
super chats tomorrow too
it's not like we're having a long stream
tomorrow
i'll do a show
i can't decide things i'm so bad at
deciding things
[Music]
why am i so bad at deciding things
um
it's already been almost seven hours so
i think you'll need to feel guilty about
it
[Music]
okay
okay i need to make a decision
so we're doing it tomorrow
and
i remember meeting here have to continue
reading at meeting is pink super chat
and maybe as another uh guide there's a
moonlight butterfly
super chat right after moonlight
butterfly and meeting it
remember
[Music]
we have tomorrow yeah after i'm done
eating i'll put up a reservation okay
okay guys
spanish snack box who's looking forward
to the spanish snack box it better be
good because i don't have anything extra
to fill it up with
i have no extra snacks no spanish extra
snacks prepared
me
really
excited any people from spain
[Music]
any people from spain
who are here
um probably don't have many viewers from
spain
spanish speaking viewers yes but people
from spain i live in spain but the s
[Music]
that's been what i want to see okay
i've been to spain once me too
i'm from barcelona oh cool
[Music]
cool barcelona i've never been to
barcelona
oh
[Music]
i should go someday
i'm from spain but live in switzerland
whoa
noise wow
it's way too late
hmm switzerland is expensive
that's the image i have of expensive you
make a lot of money but you also spend a
lot of money in switzerland
what time is stream tomorrow a good
question
uh
so next week uh most
or all
most streams all streams will be at a
shitty time for sea i warned you
i'm sorry
and
so the
snack box will probably be at 7 00 pm my
time
which is gmt plus 2
which is
2 am jst
[Music]
and 1
pm
est
according to this
yeah but tomorrow i'll eat i'll cook
something probably i'll cook it after
the stream so
don't worry we won't get interrupted by
food again okay i mean we will because
it will be a bad food but
finally bros i'm sorry
i'm sorry
it's uh once i'm less busy we'll mix it
again okay you know you know i always
mix my schedules
to accommodate everybody but next week
looks tough
okay
thank you guys for your understanding
we're trying to wake up until no you
shouldn't be no
no no
no
please don't don't do anything that
you know is bad for your health okay
don't do it too often okay
but thank you thank you for trying to be
there
messier will not fall this week we're
not that weak since stand up fight all
but thank you guys for watching wind
waker i'm so excited to play more soon
tm
and yeah
everybody have a nice
last few hours of your sundays
love your weekend
and let's jump into a busy week okay
let's get through it fighter oh
no
no korino
[Music]
caught you off guard
good night kisses for my chickens
who's that cute chicken
who's a cute chicken who is that cute
chicken
kfb
is a cute chicken
don't say
big mistake big mistake no no no
bad chicken
[Music]
i might tweet
after i ate food
in case you're waiting for me to tweet
something
bye
[Music]
you