foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
what's up hello
hello
everybody I'm here with qawwa I'm ready
to eat I'm ready to eat oh my God that
snake right in front of you is that what
you're gonna eat uh no that steak is
actually going out for
um oh I feel a customer this is actually
my my uncle's kitchen Uncle Remy and
I've stolen it to do a tasting review of
The Amazing snacks that you sent me
thank you so much yeah she said me so
much like a crazy amount
yeah yeah it um was quite the uh
purchase
I think the when I was buying the stuff
in the supermarket the lady was probably
thinking I'm having a huge party hey
there's nothing wrong yeah we love it's
a lot of stuff a lot I'm so glad it
arrived safely but I heard some some
things melted yeah yeah there's a the
chocolate bar has contorted itself it
was it's kind of interesting to see but
oh [\h__\h] but it's fine I think it's like
it's hardened again so I think it should
be okay okay I hope it still tastes
somewhat like it originally did I'm sure
it'd be fine now it's probably is it the
purple ones yeah the purple ones yes
but it looks awesome okay I'm excited
it's bait
is very ready to have a pot I'm ready to
have a party you know Mama opened the
box and she was so confused she was like
hey hey you gotta you gotta you got a
delivery and I'm like oh my God okay can
you actually opened it before you even
could like do it yourself yeah I think
because I was either
brushing my teeth at the time it came in
the morning and then I was really busy
that this I was like oh can you open it
for me
um because I get a lot of delivery stuff
and then she was like okay and she's
like what
what huh what
that was just so much stuff did you have
to pay customs don't think so you just
kind of arrived
I don't know okay if I did I'm not aware
of it but if you did then your mom did
it I guess
who knows yeah but there's mom
um so we're gonna get started we have a
lot to get through so I'm gonna scoochy
scoochy over a little bit scoochy
scoochy over
by the way you're absolutely welcome to
be honest on your review
um I'm sure that your taste buds are a
little bit different than the same taste
buds but the things I chose are mostly
snacks that I would totally eat on a
daily basis
okay I feel like it's gonna be good
though because I'm not a picky eater
um so okay I have very high hopes I very
high hopes me too me too I'm excited to
hear what you think of the okay raelian
snacks the Australians next we just
exchanged Australia stack books to
Australia snack box that's what we did
that's all we did that's all we did
um no hand cam because yeah no not yet
okay
um so I have photos I took a lot of
photos guys the very first one is
probably the one I'm most excited for so
I'm gonna start with that we have wow
it's a kangaroo guys literally it's just
an Australian box
for an Australian box because I swear
jumpies are Australian are they not
there's an Austrian flag up there yeah
on the top left right yeah I think this
brand they make all kinds of like snacks
but I chose to give you this one because
of the kangaroos oh you already snacking
on them I just opened them oh
the smell is amazing
oh I think this is the one she sent like
it's kind of like a single serving size
I think the small one small one it's
gonna be gone by the end of the night
nice oh
crunch
you can never go wrong with jumpies guys
amazing
[Applause]
the flavor is uh
yeah we call it pop like a bell pepper
[Music]
wow another 10. why is it nice 10 out of
10. can you can you describe them a
little bit more it tastes like
what does it taste like it kind of
just we have something silly here but
it's not coming to mind
it's like a rose
[Music]
um
roasted MSG
oh sweet it tastes like barbecue
Pringles
oh barbecue Pizza Pizza Pringles that's
what it tastes like oh it's so good that
sounds good right there like hollow
inside right yeah I love Japanese I so
jump I think I was actually gonna send
you jumpies I don't remember if I did or
not
um because I thought they were like
Australian because you know it's a
kangaroo so but I didn't wait what what
is the company that's making them I
don't know I thought it was I thought
the company was called Japanese
oh Kelly's Kelly's it's Kelly's ah I did
look up and I saw Kelly's is from
Austria yeah yeah all of the Kelly
snacks they're all from Austria which I
was like I didn't know until I stood in
the supermarket and I was like looking
at every snack and looking up is this
from us is this from Austria because you
don't really know and then I saw Kelly's
is from Austria and I'm like hey yo whoa
whoa whoa
what I'm so proud no Kelly with
k-e-l-l-y Ellie Kelly oh Kelly's amazing
um I if I see him I'm going through
relatively quickly it's because we have
so many guys okay okay all I've had
today is a plate of mango because I was
saving my stomach for this and Mama good
idea she was like how many snacks do you
like can there be and I'm like Mom you
don't understand there's so many
I was gonna put in one more thing
actually but I'm glad I left it out then
oh
anyway
um yeah
can I get
the good thing is I kind of want to
guess what these are because I cannot
read a single word on any of these
I'm guessing from the picture it's
pretzels right
yes pretzels and they're really famous
in Austria or Germany too I think and
they're like kind of to be honest as a
child they're they were like the boring
snack to me right but they're still very
enjoyable it's just like a kind of like
a cheap snack to give to your kids I
would say snack to give to kids yeah
because like you want more fancy stuff
but the soleti as a child I was never
quite impressed by them but they have a
good potential and they're uh salty so
it's good yeah it's good for when you're
sick apparently I love salty food okay
tell me how to pronounce the words as
well
so Letty
what what is that what does it say but
it's it's not actually a word like not
really a German word
that's that's original oh
story yeah that's a German name for
Austria
it's not like Pokey no no no not at all
pretzel stick
I don't know we have salty pretzels for
sure but they're in like the shape of
the pretzel like the small ones
um but yeah it just tastes like a
pretzel and for that I give it a 8 out
of 10.
we did the two points girls I mean it's
not I'm not judging this particular
brand I'm just pretzels itself I'm like
it's good but it's like it's kind of you
know it's just depressed yeah
okay that's fine yeah that's why I was
saying like as a child I was never
really impressed but yeah you get in
Austria you get these pushed into your
face all the time isn't the kind of like
when the parents the kids are like
complaining of like they want chips or
like potato chips yeah but they're like
no it's not healthy so they can eat
pretzels instead yeah I mean this is not
really healthy either but I don't know
they're always at parties they always
put like a stack of them into a glass
and they're supposed to eat them you
know oh they're not bad though they're
really good it's not that it's brown
also I have like
so many rubber bands next to me
literally eating like one of everything
um I have Ziploc bags and rubber bands
at the ready guys it's great nice oh
yeah no I I remember someone in the chat
apparently knew it too so when you're
sick you have to eat those with
Coca-Cola what
yeah I mean not that you don't mix them
but oh you know you drink Coca-Cola you
eat saladi salad
because the salt and the cola apparently
is a good combination for when you feel
sick I don't know why wait you feel sick
like when you're like a cold or like
when you feel nauseous
I think it's when you feel nauseous oh
because I was gonna say Coca-Cola and
pretzels don't sound like a very good
cold sickness
I'm pretty sure when you feel like
throwing up yeah yeah I see I see I see
that makes more it's a traditional
Austrian medicine yeah I see I was gonna
say because if I was young or younger
and I was like sniffling coughing
sneezing and Mama wrestled me with it
saw me with a can of Coke she would have
slapped me across the face like what are
you doing what are you doing
tell her it's an Austrian remedy
anyway yeah that's the fact that it's
in remedy should bump it up to 9 out of
ten Austria okay the thing is pretzels
are just kind of like you know it's it's
because it's just eh that's why it gets
an A but for a pretzel it's pretty good
well you will change your mind once you
get sick and and this will be the one
thing that cures you
next one is
again oh Kelly's oh I'm getting all the
salty ones first
yeah this is uh also a salty one yeah
these ones oh I like these ones they're
pretty addicting to eat my puffy quite
Airy peanut Puffs are these peanuts oh
kind of like that yeah they're really
good how do you pronounce the flavor I'm
guessing that's the flavor goodness
no that just means um crispy and Airy
mm-hmm
peanut butter jelly peanut butter oh
I really like those oh now I'm kind of I
want to eat them too give me some Bales
ah there you go there you go I'm feeding
it
thank you thank you it smells sweet
interesting
yeah well I guess it's a sweet salty
kind of thing
that sound was oh beautiful whoa
oh
interesting oh
wait I need another one
oh
[Music]
who in the chat had these before
curious I think they're also in Germany
definitely at least
me this is cup those are addictive me me
oh so many oh so many are you guys
German wow what
this is I've never had anything like
this before
um the texture
um it's different to like because we
have
um like Cheeto puffs here
it's kind of different because I think
because it's made of like peanut or
something the puff itself the texture is
more
not more flaky but it's not as like
crunchy crunchy as like
it starts off like very very corn-like
it reminds me of some corn like Korean
corn Puffs that I've had before
Starbucks not actually having that much
flavor the more you chew it gets more
salty
and then you have the aftertaste of
peanut butter yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
hear this thing but it's good oh my God
it's good it really is good I like this
one I mean you may have to need to grow
up with it to really love it but I like
it it really is the more I eat it the
more it's like this is just peanut
butter in puff form
yeah oh my God
in general yeah
who
it's sticky yeah it literally feels like
I just ate like a mouthful of peanut
butter you get like that it's like
sticking to my teeth as well no
[Music]
clear clear and clear your mouth oh yes
it's somewhere down here I don't oh
actually I'm gonna shut my shirt that
now I'm gonna go get it
um okay let me rate this one this one
gets like a good nine out of ten Wow
Let's Go
um it's a good I didn't hear that I
think Mama rat would like these as well
because she's not a really big fan of
like really salty stuff but she likes a
crunch so this is like sweet and she
really likes peanut butter and stuff yum
thank you very much
um I'm just tying up this huge bag that
I had three Puffs from
whoa okay oh my God this is amazing oh
I'm trying to see if anything wait okay
at the bottom there's some words that
I'm thinking means peanut butter I don't
know if you probably can't read it on
the image
um and I know her yes tell it in off
Harry no not at all it just means made
in Austria where is Peter 's peanut
flavor me it's not even on there what oh
no
I want to learn some some words
um oh
spin area
yes I wanna I Wanna Be I Wanna Be fluid
by the end of this journey
then this should not have been a snack
Box review but a German language
German language kind of wrong there yeah
yeah but it's fine not gonna get really
far I'm sorry through snacks damn it
okay
um so the thing that uh Kiwa was talking
about was she sent a
drink over the thing wait again number
three okay okay okay
I was actually gonna say this for the
end but I actually do need a drink right
now
um I couldn't yeah take a picture of it
so I just found an image online I hope
this is the right thing I think this is
the right one this is the right thing
yeah okay okay good I'm gonna go get it
real quick because it's in the okay I'll
be right back okay okay
oh yes I have some explaining to do
about this one
but I'll wait until she's back
the oil
is a drink in itself
um I don't realize I was meant to get
like sparkling water for it I literally
was just gonna drink the whole thing
like I was just literally just gonna
drop oh my God okay I need to explain
before you drink okay
so number one thing is this is a syrup
but the original drink is dotted syrup
it's a carbonated soft drink
that kind of has like an herbal taste to
it right and and normally we drink it
like freshly from the can or or bottle
or whatever but not as a syrup the syrup
I just sent you because it is it gets
pretty close to the original taste I see
and I thought it would be safer to send
and also you will have more out of it
yeah but ideally you would drink it with
a carbonated sparkling water oh but now
you don't have that so it will basically
I think it'll just taste like a normal
water mixed with like elderflower kind
of syrup but that's still elderflower is
a very Austrian kind of like
drink flavor yeah we like to use that a
lot it was like corio oh okay
interesting I don't feel so like it but
it's definitely not like the original so
don't think too much uh about it it's
it's just like a little I see I see it
smells really nice
yeah
if it's too weak then don't feel uh um
scared of putting more syrup in next
time
oh
I need my water hold on okay maybe you
put in too much syrup then
she may
really I would drink this even without
carbonation I feel like with carbonation
definitely will taste better but yes yes
carbonated water too but uh oh that's
not quite how it's supposed to be no no
no it should be sparkling very very
bubbly like extremely bubbly but one day
I want you to drink the original
Oh I would drink oh this is really nice
oh did you add some water to it add more
water to it good oh it's quite strong oh
my God yeah I have to like figure out
what the best balance is for you yeah I
was actually really surprised I because
I thought it was a drink I was like how
did she ship this over I'm because I
didn't realize I was like wait oh my God
she shipped an entire drink over wow
yeah I was I was considering like
sending a A can uh I can can oh that's
good yeah but then I was too worried
about it like exploding and ruining
everything so I bought this plastic
bottle and then I wrapped it in this
like soft hellofresh wrapping fabric
right right yeah yeah the whole box was
a hell of fresh box what was it
material from hellofresh actually was
very useful to keep it soft and safe
this is really nice okay Anita this will
be my little drink from now on it's
really nice
snack box needs a drink everything else
yeah like Ella flower and a lot of other
like um
herbs uh made into a like a soft drink
yeah see without the combination it
literally just tastes like iced tea like
some sort of iced tea which is really
really nice
well I can see that
God I did not drink that straight out oh
my God
oh my God I by the way they have a very
um famous like advertisement uh because
it will like in the middle of the
advertisement there's a dude who yells
out
oh
[Music]
and then they go yeah
no yeah kind of like that yeah and he
yodels he yodels there oh
um so since it's a syrup you'll have a
lot of it and joy in the coming weeks
and months yeah this is actually perfect
because I feel like this is so
refreshing it's such a good drink for
summer and it's getting really warm here
um it'll be perfect oh thank you you're
welcome thank you thank you all right
next food item
oh I didn't write it hold on go back
this is
a
wait I need to change this goal
is it 10 out of 10. wow okay I really
like I think you liked original way more
though the original this is a different
flavor oh no I'm not it's it's this
flavor but like it tastes different
anyway oh I see I see drink it how it's
meant to be drunken anyway thank you
yeah I really like it I really enjoyed
this kind of flavor it's kind of like
yeah it I don't I just I really like
it's really refreshing so very nice nice
very nice
okay next item was I was so excited when
I saw this beautiful
I thought you might like the the
tackiness of it
attack you oh my God kiwawa no it's so
amazing okay let me try it is also an
Austrian chocolate brand
or sweets brand yeah and they make these
chocolate
umbrellas
let it try pronouncing it okay
mm-hmm looks
and
[Music]
very good you know how to pronounce the
C
uh um
yeah it's like um chocolate
umbrella chance oh my God at the end
makes it into a cute small word in
German if you add hyen at any word like
Beijing it's like a small Bay oh oh
there's a ton
yeah it's like a ton yeah
I'm dying I'm dying I'm dying okay I
need to open it and wait how do I open
it do I just rip it
okay oh yeah
like you would open a normal umbrella
and I think it's just normal chocolate
like really normal milk chocolate I
think
the umbrella makes it guys oh my God
yeah yeah it's a popular
um like chocolate for children and so on
this doesn't look like normal milk
chocolate
but I love our milk chocolate oh it's
Austrian meal chocolate okay that mouth
yeah
[Music]
um
she
why is your chocolate better than our
chocolate what the heck
because we're European chocolate in
general we're like that's that that's
what we do that's just what we do
so so so plump by the end of this
I'm so happy that Austrian chocolate
gets some recognition here because like
you know when people think of oh the
best chocolate in the world people
always say like Switzerland and so on
and yeah yeah they have great chocolate
but Austria is not losing we have great
chocolate too and this is not even the
best
I love how I'm going this is just basic
I'm not gonna lie we have like the fancy
quote-unquote fancy chocolate that we
get as gifts this tastes exactly like it
and the fact that I'm eating it out of
an umbrella is blowing my mind
dang
I'm winning Austria is winning let's go
I'm not kidding I'm literally not
kidding
[Music]
nice this is just the beginning
the beginning
now you have just an umbrella stick I
don't know what you can do with that but
yay
that's some good chocolate man
oh
I feel confident I'm staring at this
packaging and I'm like why am I tasting
like freaking
what's like a fancy brand guys that we
have here
lint
lint is kind of it's not that fancy it's
like
it literally tastes it tastes like
something like you buy a box and it has
Belgium written on it it literally
tastes like oh oh and you know it's good
because like even the color itself was
lighter than normal milk chocolate but
it's just you know you look at this
packaging and it has unicorns on it and
there's pastel colors and it's like
obviously made for kids blowing my mind
blowing my mind okay it's because the
unicorns make it magical magical oh
Gillian that's it Gillian chocolate
Gillian chocolate it tastes like Gillian
chocolate it's crazy okay Jillian
Jillian I I always thought it was called
guylian but anyway it's Gillian
chocolate oh yeah that one that one
it tastes like our basic chocolate is
better than
oh but that's wow that's Belgian huh
yeah it's Belgian yeah yeah
but it tastes good very cool unicorn I
rate 10 out of 10 because unicorns and
good chocolate very nice you're too kind
fails
um no I have
I mean I will say I I'm a very open
eater like I don't really do like a lot
of foods but I do critique if the
chocolate was similar to like normal
milk chocolate I would have given it
like a seven big just for the unicorn
but it actually tastes different so
yeah
so I haven't eaten this since I was
probably like 11 so I don't remember the
flavor actually
yeah I'm still 11 though
[Laughter]
um seven ain't that bad either yeah I
mean like points for marketing but it
does actually taste different than
normal chocolate so I have to do that
too wow amazing
do I have to make it so yeah and the
thing is
um oh my God oh my God are you listening
are you still here okay so so
uh famous I think German no all right I
think it was actually actually I was so
surprised
yeah yeah there's a reason for that okay
what is German I guess okay it's German
so so
um
famous tea brand
um that you can find okay overseas yeah
uh they make for winter time they make
several different like winter teas I
know it's like summer over there now but
I really wanted you to taste the flavor
of all the winter teas so I opened the
box because I bought several ones and I
didn't want to send you free boxes
because I wanted some for myself too so
I just took the hop out of every box and
I mixed it into this one it's not only
hooten's album that you're getting here
also getting the different winter teas
and I love them all for lunch
yeah okay we've got uh oh gosh okay let
me try and pronounce it we've got
foreign
yeah yeah that means like
um Cottage on the on the on the Winter
Cottage oh so it's like a magic cinnamon
tea interesting yeah you can see kind of
the ingredients area yeah we've got
Carmen zobo
come inside yeah that is Magic at the
the fireplace oh fireplace okay and then
the last one is winter summer yeah that
is Magic in the winter so all of them
they make you feel like you're in the
Christmas Market in Austria or Germany I
love them so much yeah is this winter
tea is this like Christmas tea oh
obviously because of the patches yes
recently I've been drinking it during my
streams all the time and I keep on
wanting to share this flavor with
everybody but nobody will understand but
you can drink it and then you'll
understand oh yo it smells so good
yeah
I would also recommend like adding some
honey into your tea when you drink this
oh interesting should I make it now if
you want and then you can maybe drink it
at the end of the stream when you know
it's already like
properly
flavored because you can't drink it
right away you have to wait like a few
minutes oh really okay well I'll make it
in a stick because I still got my other
drink which one would you recommend the
hitomberg or winter is the boat the
birds
oh
take whichever one smells the the best
to you it Carnival smells the same yeah
okay I'm gonna try the winter one wait
does that have a pumpkin okay that one
is
um a reliable or reliable I'm gonna get
the winter one I always have warm water
yeah I have I have a picture of boiling
water next to me literally what
hypothermals you're so prepared even
though you didn't know about the Tea
um no I saw there was I I guess it was
tea but I just always have warm water
next to me
okay yes I'll make this in a second in
my humongous mug that okay was there
still a a cute sticker on the package
yeah it's got Bobby stick around it cute
yeah I closed it with that you thank you
did you get the letter too by the way
a card there's a card
I yeah I sent you a card somewhere in
there too oh
your mom steal it
may have I
[Music]
it should be somewhere there oh
oh
it was a cute card even
it's not so important but the card was
cute but the message was not so
important oh there was actually I added
some explanation in there for the things
that were in the Box in case you needed
some explanations yeah
intercepted by Customs intercepted by
customs
oh no wonder I was like yeah because you
mentioned did you get the sparkling
water and I was like wait wait wait
what interesting yeah okay I'll go see
what happened to that after the stream
but thank you so much okay thank you no
problem so we'll rate this one later
yes let me just rename this one so I
know it's this one t okay thank you very
much we write that at the end of the
stream okay next
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah oh yeah these are extremely famous
um one of the most famous products out
of Austria
we honestly I feel like they're like
pretty basic yeah Wing is the capital of
Austria that's where that uh chocolate
is
um made at uh and they have different
flavors too but this is the basic flavor
and it's called Manel
Mana
yeah they're Wafers chocolate a Wafers
whoa
very nutty this is gonna cause a mess is
IT smash yeah they're crumbly
hold on let me get tissue okay
[Music]
wafer I mean this will be like is this
like the Tim Tam of of of of Austria
I guess so they're also a popular
souvenir yeah okay I go oh gosh I
wouldn't say they're the most special
but uh they're good they're pretty good
I like them more as an adult than I like
them as a kid oh I see okay
oh
[Music]
I heard no crunch where's the crunch
microphone what are you doing do your
job
should I turn down the Noise Gate yeah
that should be a crunch good crunch was
that not a crunch I don't know it was a
crunch okay I had no crunch
[Music]
oh we got it
I heard a little bit of a crunch
um
they're good yeah yeah they're pretty
good I mean I wouldn't give them a 10
out of 10 personally either but they
they are like pretty much besides Mozart
balls they're the most famous souvenir
and chocolate I was waiting I am waiting
for I'm waiting for tarma to zoom
tarzomb balls I'm waiting for those guys
I may have played trombone champ
yesterday Tarzan
May Mozart
okay give these a rating um they're
wafers
the inside game is like a hazelnut uh
chocolate
um it tastes a bit more nutty than uh
Nutella um
not that sweet but I think I would give
this one a seven out of 10.
I honestly don't understand why they are
so famous in Austria I don't I don't
understand
hazelnut chocolate because the chocolate
is really nice because sometimes you
have Wafers and the chocolate inside is
just very mid
[Music]
yeah it's probably just because they
have a long history and they're like
pretty basic so it's like safe to give
to everyone like people who don't like
sweet stuff too much they probably could
still eat this and people who like to
use sweet stuff also would eat this so
like safe guess unless you don't like
nuts not a hot dog okay
thank you thank you very much okay we
still got a lot to go next one oh
they're also vegan oh my God
yeah wait what really apparently
apparently wait a second
trade Coco
soy
okay ingredient sugar wheat flour
hazelnut low-fat cocoa powder soya
maybe
nuts and milk solids
hmm interesting
um guaranteed
[Music]
all right next item
I'm these are the ones that I saw that I
literally don't know what they are and
I'm kind of that's okay
druggie kexi
yeah
um cookies cookies with a chocolate uh
coating but if you look closely you will
see that some of them are darker color
than others yes
so the darker ones are dark chocolate
and the lighter ones are milk chocolate
and I prefer the milk chocolate ones but
in order to eat the whole package I just
always eat two at a time one dark and
one milk that makes sense
I like the cookie texture I feel like
these have a really special texture
um yeah they're not my favorite snack
but they're pretty cool
yeah because I was looking at it and it
has like the cracks as you guys can see
in the picture and I was like I'm so
confused I don't know what this is but
okay I'm gonna try a dark chocolate one
first and then I'll try the milk
chocolate enjoy okay dark chocolate
foreign
[Music]
oh my God
that would be perfect with coffee I'm
not even kidding oh yeah
oh nice
oh oh
okay let me try the milk chocolate one
oh
let's see if she's a dark chocolate type
of person or milk chocolate type of
person
hmm
no hold up I think milk chocolate
would be even better with coffee but the
doctor one is actually really nice I
actually really like it I'm glad you
like both
literally again I just keep thinking
like oh mama rat would like this she
would definitely like the dark chocolate
ones because she's not much she's not
really a big Sweet Tooth but she really
likes something with a coffee this is
gonna be perfect oh
by the way the package says
um Venice it means if only I could stop
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
what an Australian okay you're speaking
German or am I speaking Australian hmm
you'll never know
I'm glad you like these ones I actually
got inspired when I bought these and
bought myself a package too and then I
snacked on them forever because I bought
like an XXL large package
amazing oh that was really nice cookies
forever I was like it's raining Madam
the rating is
I will give these a
8.5 out of 10. oh better with coffee yes
better with coffee I think with coffee
don't be bump up to nine 100
but I cannot relate yeah oh yeah you
don't drink coffee do you yeah
drink tea
I mean I feel like they'll also be a
good accompaniment to tea you just need
something to wash it down otherwise too
many at a time can be a bit too heavy on
the taste like yeah yeah absolutely
absolutely I agree hmm you're getting it
babe you could get Austrian I'm getting
it
do you perhaps share any Austrian blood
not that I'm aware of but in the soul in
the Coco roll I am yes
I'm there
I am one of you do you get very salty
when you play games
is that is that an Austrian thing or is
that just a game timing that's a sign
austrians we love songs and we have like
uh back in the day in medieval times or
whatever we um were the big ones with
the salt industry and still on well
maybe I am who knows I will say this
some this
[Music]
Elden flower tea drink thing is going
great with these snacks
oh I'm glad to hit it okay
[Music]
um next thing
yeah
oh my God
so these are the famous Mozart balls
they're famous and very popular number
one top souvenir for when you go to
Austria and bring something back
um the thing is there's different brands
they make it a little bit differently
depending on the brand on the company
but they always have like similarities
oh personally I do not like them
you don't like trezones balls
no I don't like his balls but um they
are famous so I had to give them to you
what's the feeling they have marzipan
inside that's the filling
yeah you have to give it a try
I would have sudden disappointment
come on
I don't know I would have something in
common
yeah 10 out of 10 for packaging though
honestly like when I saw this I got so
immediately
filled with happiness maybe because I
was playing trombone Champions today but
honestly I was this is this is great
amazing marketing 10 out of 10. I'll
give you five your face Mark even if it
tastes like [\h__\h] it'll be five out of
ten just because of the packaging is
that even this is not even the best
packaging they also sell them in like
violin packages and so on
oh I am crazy
two out of ten okay
let's open it so it's chocolate nougata
marzipan interesting yeah
I hope that didn't melt really no um
this I think they're okay not bad nice a
little bit it's all right
hmm oh
[Music]
is that cherry
Cherry oh
what what's the why is it red in the
middle
oh that's red red
can you give me like a flavor of
something
no
[Music]
bread bread
is that not just the chocolate
oh the new gun oh never mind it's red on
the packaging I thought it was red on
the inside nevermind
all right
she went
oh
you dislike marzipan that much I don't
blame you
[Music]
wow
[Laughter]
hmm
yeah okay that's okay I understand I
mean damn is it the marzipan
um
austrians like marzipan very much to
they use them in desserts a lot and also
chocolate I'm sorry it just like tastes
like Cherry medicine that's why I asked
oh because I could smell it through the
packaging
I like I'm sorry I could smell it smell
it through the chocolate I opened it and
I smelled it and I was like oh I can
smell medicine why do I smell medicine
that's why
[Music]
was it really this bad
oh
oh all right
well you tried I tried it
it's liquor Mozart is very sad that you
don't like him preserve his balls oh
look at the ingredients wait there's no
English on here oh wait yes there is
okay
okay um
citric acid
hazelnuts okay it doesn't say anything
on here that made chocolates filled with
marzipan and praline cream
huh yes the mouse pen
what I don't like it turns out I don't
like trism's balls either okay
he's crying right now in the corner
I am sorry to zoom but but just like the
Mana waivers this is just a thing I I
had to send you for the sake of sending
you an Austrian snack box it's not like
I like them anyway I see well I did
promise like five out of ten
nice
nice 5 out of 10 straight for packaging
okay
oh I appreciate it that's very kind
Mozart is like uh looking back at us and
sniffing but he's okay he's doing all
right all right
I'm trying to figure out what I'm gonna
do with the rest of this package maybe
someone will like it I don't know maybe
um if you want to throw it away no of
course not I mean I did throw mine away
kind of I did but you're gonna ask if
someone likes marzipan yeah maybe
okay am I touch shrugs
it sounded like you were quite disgusted
it's just that marzipan flavor
oh yeah yeah okay
thank you very much resume maybe next
time
next snack
oh
my gosh
I have not eaten those ever since I was
a young child but these are
um yeah from our Capital Vienna uh uh
what's uh
foreign
six flavors
um yeah filled hard candy and six
different flavors oh it's not like Haiku
yeah yeah like chewy candy okay
okay I really don't remember but it was
chewy but you tell me okay
what flavor do you recommend there's
pineapple lemon orange I'm guessing
Peach black is that Mulberry orange
orange okay we eat orange oh my God yeah
wait is it a Blackberry or is it a
mulberry a conto ah those are maybe
Johannesburg maybe Johannesburg yeah
Johannesburg what's that
[Music]
Johannesburg a black currant a Black
Horn
I like black coloring um and then
there's raspberry strawberry and is that
a peach
is that a peach Ponto
that means
apricot yeah
eat an orange one though huh
I'm still a bit sniffly but don't bite
right into it who knows maybe it's not a
chewing oh okay okay that is a hard
candy softly oh it is hard okay
don't lose your teeth for it it's not
worth it
yeah it's hard it's like do I have to
stop do I suck it will probably take a
while yeah
I'm not bit into it okay oh oh
how do you like the the girls
suckerberg
to my teeth hold on
[Music]
it do be like that
oh
ah
[Music]
this is a very weird texture of candy I
don't think I've ever had a candy like
this before
I never eat like hard candy ever though
only as a young young bubble bubble
child not hold up
to lose my milk teeth
[Music]
after my stuck to my teeth
so it's hot candy
but the outer shell is like hard but
it's not
hard to the point where you can't bite
into it right
that's some good peppers like a Jolly
Rancher it's really fast and just butt
oh my God my teeth you sound like
someone who's eating a hard candy
but hot candy normally like you suck on
it until you can bite into it like you
you physically cannot bite into oh I
think I'm still talking about rock candy
Maybe
um maybe I'm talking about rock candy
oh
and the inside is it creamy it's like a
little bit sour really nice
but I don't particularly like this
texture because
of like hard candy because once you bite
it I it's everywhere in my teeth I
cannot ah um
but you're welcome to give these out to
like friends
oh
you can be like hey I I have Austrian
candy one so oh I got the good stuff oh
my OBS is
oh okay
let me just restart it real quick all
good now
we bet hello I'll be back
yeah it seems like we're partially back
people maybe need to refresh hello
refresh everybody
yeah Mozart's Revenge
actually trisom he's on to me yeah my
Ubi is gonna die for like two seconds
oh my God we're not going back out again
what is happening
hold on
it's like red what is going on no it's
not YouTube I think it's OBS what is
going on internet
it might be a little little bump here
and there guys but
um
I'll just give it a little bit of time
give it a little bit of time
you mess with the wrong European
[Laughter]
yeah it should be okay I think it's a
combination of trism hating me and also
just my internet is a bit weird at this
time
um Australia be like Australia be like
that sometimes yeah refresh guys you
should be back
Oh yay don't mess with the true Zone
balls is what I found out
I think these are good to give to your
friends if you meet them yeah I think so
too very nice a very nice little
souvenir amazing
um
yeah no I was saying for those uh but
when it cut out I was like I don't
particularly like this kind of texture
because it gets all stuck in my teeth
um is what I was gonna say but the
flavor is really nice it's a little bit
sour not bad
so for these I give it a
six out of ten
it's good but I'm also not a big fan of
like candy candy like this kind of candy
candy so me too me too yeah so six out
of understandable have a nice day yes
very nice okay
didn't but wait there's more
[Applause]
is this just Pocky Mikado so this is
awesome
Australian German or european
um I just generally European Pocky I
would say uh-huh the reason I got it for
you is because I personally don't like
Pokey but I love Mikado I love it so
much I eat it all the time it has a
different kind of texture different kind
of flavor but it's basically a European
version of Porky yeah oh interesting
okay I am in it's not Austrian but I
just got it because I snack on it all
the time first of all
hockey should learn this packet is so
thick and full what the heck it's like
yeah
I think they're thinner oh that's me
okay I haven't opened it I just felt it
and I was like what the heck okay
I love them so much I can never stop
eating them
um different from Pocky though
and we only have like three different
flavors it's so boring but they're still
good okay let's have a look foreign
[Music]
there's just a lot of them okay you
gotta eat two at once two at once okay
okay yeah
they kind of oh no they broke hold on
they're a little bit stuck together
because they've been melted
they're so good okay
I've got four
oh that's good too the more the merrier
okay okay
okay I've got four five I'm just gonna
go for it okay okay
[Music]
I think I can see what you mean
um
[Music]
need all the chocolate and the
crunchy all of it all of it you really
think this is that different to poke
yes 100 percent
huh
I I really unfortunately dislike Pocky
but I love this oh I feel like the um oh
the cookie and the chocolate both yeah
the texture of the cookie and also the
chocolate and and cookie flavor I feel
like the Mikado is more natural tasting
I'm so sorry okay no I can understand
the stick itself it's more
yeah I got what is that in English
um
it has more picture yeah I think maybe
it's just it it feels Fuller than Pocky
Pocky when you bite into it you kind of
feel like there's nothing there this one
it feels full
um
it's more dense that's the word it's
more dense yeah somebody said and that's
true it's literally tailored to European
taste buds
um
the thing Pocky has that I'm guessing
this one that you mentioned doesn't is
that it has more flavors right
yeah that's a sad thing like I wish we
had so many flavors for Mikado like as
Pokey does because I feel like it would
do well but all we got is uh milk
chocolate which you have a dark
chocolate and white chocolate
oh
but sometimes simple is best
based mm-hmm
I'm cleaning my teeth let's do candy I
don't do the same company perhaps but
the it's very different taste
try it guys come to Europe and try it
it's good it tastes really good okay
um
like oh my God
oh next I want to eat them oh wait I
need to write this first ranking ranking
Humanity
I gave her the 50 out of 10. um
if I'm supposed to rate this as like a
stick with chocolate on it yes it's a
9910 it's not bad
[Music]
I'd probably give Pocky like an 8 out of
ten but
yeah or even a 7 out of ten so this is
definitely a lot better than Pocky I
will say
it tastes really good
if you like the snacks what's next yeah
what's next
um
oh I lost my position wait oh
Rock Cocos yeah I hope you like this
kind of stuff because I hate it
yeah it's real rum and uh coconut uh oh
this may be a Miss also there's I feel a
really big lump that I feel like a lot
of them might have melted together
inside this bag okay
oh yes oh they've kind of just stuck a
little
stuck a bit together interesting a bit
okay I can still break it apart okay it
is an Austrian company and I have a
funny story about this but not so funny
but
when I was younger you know you know
there's a snack called maltesers yeah
yeah yeah is this a chocolate
I guess so the thing is like when I was
younger like 10 or so
um I went to a friend's place and they
had a plate of what looked like
maltesers so I tried but it was these
things and that is so disgusting I hated
it
says pink have I ever had alcoholic
okay my door just opened on its own
that's fine spooky
it's coming for you
leave me alone
oh [\h__\h] I'm being haunted by the spirit
of trism understandable
I'm sorry true Zone
um I was gonna say I don't think I've
ever had alcohol have I had no I've
tried alcoholic chocolate once and it
was disgusting
um so I don't know if I'm gonna like
this but do you like rum in general no
well then you're probably not gonna get
happy with this one okay
oh
yeah
I hate coconut and alcohol so I would
not eat this
all right you maybe like Robin coconut
oh oh that's disgusting I'm sorry
I ain't judging you I need the tea okay
get the tea
let me get rinse my cup real quick I'm
gonna make the tea that is disgusting oh
my God I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry
[Music]
yeah yeah I I was just looking for
Austrian stuff you know this was one of
the things if you like Ramen coconut
then you might like it I don't like
either
you also not like coconut
[Music]
it's not the coconut it was just coconut
we didn't find I really like coconut but
it's the liquid center that is
disgusting oh gosh
I'm sorry that I feel like this might be
going into the trash just because I
don't think there's anyone like we would
enjoy this
that influenced any of the snacks taste
it might I mean it was supposed to be
liquid right but still maybe the heat
didn't do it any favor I don't know
maybe
I don't know there's there's something
about a liquid Center that it's like
like a pure like you know when they say
liquid Center guys it's not like oh it's
like a runny caramel no it was pure
liquid it was just literally rum inside
of that like straight up rum
anyway let me
ah T winter
's supper okay
oh it's a binky bag okay
yeah I think it's like uh six minutes or
so you should wait till six minutes oh
my God approximately yeah
okay
I've got my warm hot water
um
yeah it will get pretty dark I like it I
like this tea really yummy 10 out of 10.
Christmas smells so good okay I'm gonna
let it sit for a couple minutes maybe
this will help you
um to get a little bit more of a winter
Vibe during Christmas yeah yeah true
true because we never have a winter
Christmas ever yeah so anyway I'm
excited get these out of the screen
disgusting
you're not even gonna rate them oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow not even you know I have a series
where I snack a try all all snacks from
all over the world right
I mean there's been some bad snacks but
I don't think I've ever rated anything
zero no no no no no no no
okay if the it's this it's the rum
Center that really is like it was just
straight up rum it's like you bite into
it and then immediately because rum
because alcohol burns alcohol yeah
imagine small Chihuahua thinking it's
maltesers and eating this as a young
child oh my God so if you bite half of
it the rum like trickles down and
touches your lip and then it's like it
burns okay yeah oh I think I had the
same reaction as you back then I just
threw it up
it's bad very bad okay
um I'm sorry if you like if you like
this good for you I'll ship you these
ones okay but I'm good thank you very
much
okay what's the next step give me
something good give me something good
what is this oh
hello
candy I'm guessing German but I I felt
like mixing in some German things
because Italian food is very popular yes
and these are my favorite ones from
Harry bull actually
[Music]
player
peaches
the texture and the flavor of them it's
like hard
[Music]
[Applause]
to be relatively soft ones you bite into
it
oh sorry I was trying to open it okay
I'm pretty sure how able is all over the
world but maybe this particular flavor
is not everywhere I love them it smells
so good as soon as I opened it it's just
peaches oh yeah yeah they're so good
okay
yay
yum yum yum yum yum that's what I needed
yeah oh that's good something to get
that [\h__\h] rum flavor out of your
mouth yes oh my God hell yeah
they are quite popular good taste to
chat
yeah it's a peach gummy really strong
Peach smell and Peach flavor I also have
a code here
where I can win a free water bottle I'm
guessing
it's a water bottle
oh my God how about mascot is called Sig
can you check if I won a free water
bottle
sure I I can't see the code though take
a picture and show you
there's one out of 333 that's quite a
lot hmm
yo free water bottle let's go
I'll take a picture and then maybe oh no
okay it's not the name of the mascot
it's just a company that makes the the
water bottle oh I see now though ah okay
what is his name
what
you don't like my th pronunciation
[Music]
how do we spell it what horrible
it's right there what do you mean
stream of luck that gold bear
oh I think we can already be sending it
to me yeah right now yeah
I mean it'll probably be your free water
bottle but hey
if you don't want a water bottle with
have a bow on it come on
oh now oh okay happy bowl.com
I I have never won seven days before
like this before but I usually always
um like just ignore these kind of things
because I don't think I would ever win
anyway
oh wait
where do I put in the code
oh you're already sipping the tea I am I
got an impatient
it's really nice wait I know it will get
stronger later
[Music]
I'm putting in the coat now
everybody
um uh uh and here at least in Austria if
you like um
how do you call it you you put one
finger above another
prioritize both no that's both lying and
and hoping for something good to happen
maybe you should just um put your thumb
into your fist that's also a way of
wishing someone luck oh fingers oh crop
fingers crossed I'll cross your fingers
crossed fingers crossed come on
do we get a free water bottle
did I put in the right code let me check
um
[Music]
I don't believe it we should have won
the world
Peach candy
more gotcha yo we need more horrible
candy so I can have more gotcha there's
so many that I love but I don't I didn't
want to spam you too much with candy so
I just got this one that I like the most
thank you
like it 10 out of 10. I love it
I don't know there are certain times
that you know
times in my life where I crave something
sweet but not like and something sour as
well and something hard something chewy
this will be perfect thank you so much
yeah you're welcome all right
peaches too
oh okay
so that'll wear oh I still smell the
freaking
I need a garbage bag do I have a garbage
bag
you need to exercise exercise
[Music]
let's go
sort of guess what it was I see marzipan
on this yeah yeah but it's it's several
flavors uh and they're a tiny version
normally they're like
yeah but this is like this is like a
sampling kind of one um
German by the way and it's one of my
favorite chocolates
oh
oh yeah so it's like a it's a I really
like that it's in a paper bag as well
oh
oh that's so cute yeah okay my favorite
out of these would probably be the white
one yogurt jogger yeah and and maybe
also the yellow one what's
[Music]
birth flakes
I cannot spell flakes yeah those are
it's like um cereal in there oh
breakfast cereal but not the just a
normal
um
the normal yellow one interesting
and yeah yogurt is yogurt and then the
light blue one is uh just normal uh milk
chocolate milk
and yeah the green one is nuts nuts okay
and then the dark blue is nougat yeah
and then Martin you can't ignore the
March upon one
okay
so do you recommend I try the yellow or
the do I do should I try yogurt oh
God if you like this one okay well
should I have the yellow one I don't
know okay let me try the yellow one has
some crunch crunch
oh you get a smooth oh yeah okay I kind
of want the crunchy one okay okay let me
try
um that's perfect
[Music]
this actually this package doesn't even
have my favorite flavor I'm so sad oh
what was your favorite flavor
it's one with like a big butter cookie
in the middle oh see almost like I
realized even from like the Unicorn
their chocolate is like different the
color is like a really light brown
compared to our milk chocolate which is
like a dark brown which is really
interesting
your milk chocolate looks like it's been
discolored that's how light it looks
um oh it's just very milky yeah that's
crazy is this like oh this is
oh wait no there's four what the heck oh
okay yeah four tiny squares four tiny
squares okay let me just eat one
or maybe two I like two okay
oh I heard the crunch
mm-hmm
it's good chocolate once again I thought
she was not bad oh I really want to try
the yoga one
[Music]
they have that one too
oh okay I just had one square of the
yellow one that's okay
what is this
okay what the heck oh by the way there's
a special way of opening these how have
I been opening them wrong I think I have
oh no but I mean normally I like
um like on the back there's like this
fold right so you open it in the middle
so that the fold would open
I don't know how to explain it
just crack it folded crack it somehow
crack it fold yeah you fold it in half
half in the Middle where the fold is
um
I don't know you can oh
that's so cool
Twisted puppets that's so cool okay okay
okay oh this one's good German
technology technology okay this one
melted best okay
oh
[Music]
no crunch because this one's smooth
mm-hmm
oh yeah
[Music]
I'm having the other one too oh it's
good yeah
[Music]
fixing what we lost with the with the
rum chocolate God damn rum okay this is
making up for it and that chocolate
brought my average down [\h__\h] should not
have included it
but I will say my mouth is very like
sweet now yeah maybe it's time for
something salty again yeah I'm gonna sit
my tea
oh that's so good so actually I I gave
you a two different light drinks of tea
with different types of tea and stuff
syrup
[Music]
so much variety
it was funny good you included it oh
yeah content entertainment values make
Bay throw up oh my God I was actually
really close with that rum okay
Oh I thought the worst one was gonna be
the Mozart balls oh man oh
okay
that was really nice the trees laughter
this is not pre-recorded pre-recorded
boss bro no pre-recorded laughter Oh if
if the loft is pre-recorded that means
the buff was also pre-recorded
all right this is live
all right next one next one next
um I think the normal one but the yellow
one I would rate
um seven out of ten and then the yogurt
one I would rate an eight out of ten
it's very nice
very nice very nice indeed
yes oh my God we still got so much left
oh my God next one
I'm actually scared of this
um so actually this is the children's
version of a famous uh snack that we
have I got you the children version
because the original version would be a
much bigger package and I didn't want to
like waste too much in case you didn't
like it but it's chocolate bananas
oh it was but as a giraffe yeah I can
see that
um oh did they melt
um no the packet was kind of open a
little bit so I don't know if this is
actually edible oh what the [\h__\h]
hmm
I don't think this is actually oh
it's kind of it's producing juices
what the package was kind of open and it
doesn't it's not not only the outer one
the inside package was open no inside
package it's just like a box
so
the the box is kind of open I don't know
if I can either I'll buy you a new one
no it's okay
all right maybe I can let me just break
open the other ones is it meant oh this
one's okay okay oh I think some of them
are okay some of them I feel like I've
gone a little bit bad but yeah I'm gonna
try to take a little bit tastes a little
bit I'm scared because I don't like
banana flavored things
yeah
what
yeah anyway I'm gonna have a taste
[Music]
it's more artificial banana than natural
banana flavor
oh no I'm so brave such a warrior this
is
let me go
I have never had good tasting banana
the inside is like fluffy I don't think
I can eat much of this because I'm
pretty sure they've gone bad but oh it's
like it's like fluffy there's like that
hint of banana and the chocolate is like
not too
oh
you liked it so much
I'll try to come back
did I blow your mind that much
I'd like it because you said you don't
like banana I don't okay no he's no I
need to send you like disgusting banana
flavored candy from Australia if you
guys know what I'm talking about banana
musk oh my God that thing will haunt me
in my dreams
gone by the way oh is it it might be on
my end
Australia be like Australia be like
Sandhill again again they're not in a
good mood today they're really not it's
okay it they're jealous because you're
not sharing the snacks maybe me hams hmm
hmm I actually the thing is like I never
tried this children version I'm not sure
if it tastes different than the adult
version I think they're probably just
different shape but I can't be sure
but I'm glad you like the banana oh I
see the room
[Laughter]
I'm back shares
back yay
I don't know what that was honestly it
might have just been my internet she's
bad back
banana Musk
banana monster
you don't want to look up banana musk I
just got bananas
it's like the most artificial banana
flavor in the world it's disgusting but
this actually
it's like this is chocolate no it's just
banana
it's like a fake banana in candy it's
disgusting anyway I really sad because
oh my God I actually would have eaten
this
I'll get you more
yeah this is like me again ever then
I'll get you more oh okay I because it's
getting more of the things that you
rated 10 out of 10. I mean I don't think
I'd eat this too often but I can
definitely I would definitely eat it you
know but what what this box if you can
see it's it's like a pop-up box right
and inside nothing is sealed so it's
just inside of a box and the box was
like kind of open so that's weird though
I didn't see it open before no it must
have ripped because it's like one of
those like it's those really easy
openable boxes as well oh it might have
been from Shipping that's okay that's
okay oh
um I would rate this for a banana snack
honestly
a seven out of ten which is good what
banana snack
wow very nice
[Applause]
very nice costumes bro
they had it at Customs bro
kind of yikes I think they looked at it
for a while because when I sent when I
brought it to the post office they said
until it arrives it would take like five
to seven days but it took way longer
than that so it must have been stuck in
the customers yeah but anyway okay
amazing okay still good still very good
next item
got a couple left
um
oh okay I think I can show these too
together because it's just this same
thing can you see that edge that's what
happened to it
yeah like milka is uh famous here and
and it's like well you know this is
purple cow and that's really famous and
they have so many different flavors it's
like our go-to chocolate it's not like
it's kind of cheap actually but it's so
yummy and go I'll go to it's like
cheaper than Lind milk yeah yeah I
really did but I know it still tastes
good
um so we're talking about the strawberry
one and I love both of them they're my
favorite ones you know we actually don't
really have much strawberry chocolate
here and me being a strawberry
connoisseur I must
I need to try this okay it's like one of
my favorite strawberry flavor strawberry
chocolates here it gives you like a
fresh fresh strawberry flavor so good oh
my God I can smell it already oh yeah
and this little tiny red bits that are
like a little bit crunchy it's like
dried strawberry
I guess like similar yeah
you're eating it
oh that's not good
even though it melted once
oh that's very good I'm I'm only gonna
have one little bite
because I've consumed more chocolate
today than I have in the entire year
okay I would recommend you to not even
open the other one and save it for
another time because it's basically just
um really yummy milk chocolate with some
white chocolate mix in between I see
okay it's nothing special you will like
it though strawberry is so good right
oh the tea goes along with it ah is so
good yeah I think America is not
actually only Austrian but it is like
pretty much the most popular chocolate
here
tonight
I'll bring you more flavors next time
what's like when you get chocolate
what's your favorite like extra flavor
in the chocolate that's the thing I
don't eat chocolate like ever I don't
ever have like a craving of like I want
to eat chocolate right now
um it's always like a if someone offers
it to me oh it's like a oh it's just
lying there then I'll have it or if I
have it with my coffee so I never
actually I don't remember the last time
I purchased chocolate for myself
so yeah
um yeah so I didn't have a chocolate
craving like ever so interesting
interesting yeah
maybe that's because
right yeah
I will say this like strawberry one is
kind of like it's I've never had
anything close to this it's very nice
okay I feel like we're really good at at
making
um like uh uh in chocolate uh making
fruit flavor tastes somewhat natural
because like from other countries like
no hate but this is just what I'm used
to it's just the flavor that I'm used to
so when I eat chocolate from Japan or
America it tastes like artificial to me
no no I feel like I always tastes more
natural but that's I guess just what you
used to perhaps yeah maybe that's why I
didn't really particularly like
chocolate that much just because it's
you have been provided with lots of good
chocolate so you can eat that for a
couple months Yes actually honestly I
feel like it's just gonna disappear
before I even have any a lot of the
times when I have chocolate is because
Mama rat brings it home and then I'll
have like a little bit and then it'll be
gone in like two weeks and I'm like oh
okay well
but I definitely want to try the other
one I want to try the other one as well
okay okay take your time
thank you strawberry one is so good
thank you so much oh by the way the
thing about that lower chocolate uh it's
not it's like
um it's supposed to look like the the
spots on the cow it's called yeah
it's a cute gimmick exactly
it very easy okay we've got I think
we've got one more snack because I don't
think I can oh I've got two more
actually no yes we've got two more one
of them I cannot eat at the moment
um oh what this is the last snack that I
can consume which is my favorite zombie
snack in the world did I save the best
for last oh my God
it's why it's a big pack I'm so excited
okay it's my favorite thing ever like I
I I cannot stop eating these when I open
the package it's so good
I know exactly what kind of snack this
is Fluffy potato chips
they may have gotten crushed but that's
okay it's okay
that's totally fun
oh
magical crunch yeah I know
they're so salty but sometimes I eat the
whole package and then afterwards with
the inside of my mouth is kind of like
it feels like really rough because I ate
too much I can't stop myself
[Music]
um
oh she's she's eating she do be eating
welcome to my mukbang guys
he's salty but
ton flavors too but I just like when it
comes to potato chips I just like the
original salty flavor most of the time
you know rather than like bell pepper or
whatever honestly I do too but it's so
hard to find a well-salted like just
original flavored chip a lot of the
times it's undersalted so this is up to
you this is very nice oh she likes the
salt she's an Austrian I like this
okay oh that's really good that's
dangerous actually okay
I'm surprised you know I thought that it
would be totally normal since you were
not raised in in Europe that you would
have different taste buds but I'm glad
you agree with most of these things
actually all of them like even the
things that I didn't like he also didn't
like yeah we have trained taste buds
let's say that yeah wow okay it says let
me guess
um gluten free gluten free
[Music]
what does that mean yeah that's just uh
I don't know how to translate it but no
additional like Flavor things yes yeah
yeah yeah oh yeah stuffing
Farms is open no no color oh no
artificial colors yes and Rain sun and
Blue menu
yeah something with sunflower oh made
with sunflower oil or seeds or whatever
yeah oh
oh natural hey yo oh man all natural the
all the flavor oh the goodness is all
natural baby amazing thank you so much I
love this this is going to be gone by
the end of the week I promise you hell
yeah I'm glad you like my favorite uh
salty snack it's so good oh my God
I I try to not buy it too often because
I know I I will eat it within a minute
no I don't know at all if not by the end
of the day no the jumpies will probably
be gone by the end of the day but I'm
being good okay so I'll save those for
like you know snack in the week
I think I remember
um there was one time when I still lived
with a roommate uh after I came back to
Austria from Japan and I was streaming
and I had these and I was eating them
while streaming and I could not stop
myself when my roommate heard me and
screaming about it so she took them away
from me and gave me vegetables instead
[Music]
did you actually use the chicken food
I still have it I still use it yeah I
tried to like use it whenever it makes
sense like on potatoes and and chicken
yeah you like it I like it yeah I'm
feeling like I need to put on more
though because uh I guess it needs to be
more intense yes yes load on the chicken
Salt load only what was your first
reaction when you ate it
and yummy like fits really well good
good match with potato
I see it's not just normal salt it's a
chicken Chihuahua salt
it was really good that you sent that
because like it's not it was not just a
like unhealthy snack box then but also
had some oh oh yeah right then
you say the last thing you can't eat
right now okay right now yeah yeah yeah
good Segway into yeah the very last
thing I actually I don't know what this
is
[Music]
wasn't it like four small ones they send
you one big one you sent me one big one
oh
I thought I sent you four small ones I'm
confused oh
the [\h__\h] is 225 grams
that's a lot uh well okay well Dabo is a
very famous company here that makes Jam
especially Jam also some other stuff but
mostly jam and
um it's it's a really good high quality
um uh uh apricot jam
[Music]
should I try a little bit honestly there
is versions of this that people just
snack directly without anything else oh
because it's so yummy you can at least
maybe get like one tiny spoon yeah oh
you should get a flavor I'm gonna I'm
gonna do something that is very gross
guys I'm gonna
get my pinky I'm gonna scoop some from
the lid
okay
just put it back into the fridge
afterwards
whoa whoa well that's very nice
yeah I actually don't eat because I
don't eat breakfast I don't eat a lot of
breakfast foods but I saw this and I
thought it was Gem and Mama rat's a big
fan of like fruit Jam so oh I was like I
have something for you I think I just
gotta double check what it is and then
I'll come back
if you have crabs it's more fitting than
pancakes crepes with this yummy grapes
oh my God
I heard something very different okay
grapes yeah
great I see I say I see
um so where's the mommy then is
apricot it's a fancy type of apricot
yeah
is a very
um fancy type of jam I guess marmalade
or something
yeah it's not marmalade
it's just fancy cam
it's it's a bit different from Jam yeah
but it's still Jam kind of confit to the
English oh is it isn't it just wait is
it a comfort tree oh I'm stupid
it's just a very fancy gem no no
yeah I'd like a high quality show I
don't know
yeah yeah yeah yeah enjoy okay thank you
and what's fine
associate
[Music]
um
mine produce
no
help me chat
[Music]
yeah smoothly Blended something like
that oh no yeah no chunks oh
[Music]
fine is press through oh it's been oh
it's been past received
there's also a version with chunks but I
think this one is maybe without chunks
oh I see I see I see thank you I'm
definitely gonna enjoy this
[Music]
there's actually one more thing but I
don't know if I'm allowed to show it on
stream
um and also we have it here so I didn't
think it was yeah you sent me um the Pez
candy
please show it I don't it's Disney oh
um Disney what's that Disney yeah
the whole thing is Disney it's Buzz
Lighty let's show them oh yeah let's
show them a different one there's
different versions you can find one on
the internet and then it's one of those
we have it here which is also why I
didn't think it's it was that necessary
to show you because I used to have this
when I was a kid but it is Austrian
apparently I was so shocked really
yeah it's Austrian apparently I looked
at them that's crazy oh my God this
contraption yeah and the candy is like
it's just very cheap but really nice
children's candy it's the thing where
like you pop open the top and then like
it dispenses one piece of candy to you
um Pez candy yeah I didn't know pepper
pastry and what the heck
ah oh man I can only find like versions
of some characters that are probably not
yeah I mean everyone knows what Pez is
because it's like everywhere but yeah I
didn't know it was Austrian yeah and I
gave him one that has Buzz Lightyear
oh my God is this the new Buzz Lightyear
it's the new Buzz Lightyear oh my god oh
I didn't know that pest was uh from
Austria and still so famous all over the
world damn Paul Lopez when a yo that's
an idea hey yo Paulo Pez went come on
come on when yeah wait good idea oh my
God I want to be a candy dispenser yeah
that'd be so cool hey yo it's your candy
from us yeah but that was also the one
thing that she added in there did you
also eat it when you were a child yeah
yeah yeah yeah
um
and it's like I don't understand like
the dispenser was it feels like it's
supposed to control how much you consume
but it's you just keep going back for
more and more and more even though it
dispenses only one at a time it's so
stupid but it works it's just like yeah
right yeah it makes the candy more
interesting
oh this should be a thing all right
management are you listening let's get a
collaboration going with Pez yeah hola
Pez holopess went
so okay we're not showing it but you
guys know what it is and I think uh as a
child we would rate it 10 out of 10. I
would rate an item
for now since I only had a little bit
would be an um would be an 8 out of 10.
um but yes Pez is like 10 out of 10. I
haven't had Pez in like years so I don't
I don't really remember the flavor but
my memories of that time was a 10 out of
10 100 it's time to get nostalgic Bales
let's eat the the snacks from our
childhood that is true I mean not right
now it's okay but anytime yes but thank
you my table's a mess
I think that's it
that's it apparently the name pets comes
from uh the German word fefa mints and
the letters p e z are in that so it's
peppermint peppermints peppermint pets
pets pets
yeah page some letters in that word
apparently thank you for that random
knowledge yeah thank you
I'm so full
I
but I don't feel full from like
substance I just feel bless probably
because of how much chocolate I've had
in the last hour and so yeah yeah yeah
but anyway thank you so much I'm gonna
clean up I'm gonna throw those
disgusting rum chocolate out and very
sadly the bananas as well but thank you
so
so this was so much fun thank you you're
welcome we finally finished the exchange
yes yeah I I tried this next you sent me
and that was also 10 out of 10 bucks man
there's so much Variety in there yeah
Santa let me throw it but I really did a
great job at that too I remember it was
like a like three or four in the morning
for me and I was like I can't I cannot
I'm so sorry but that was my
representative at the time yeah I had a
different Australian with me all good
all good well thank you for doing this
with me yeah thank you I had a lot of
fun there's a lot of I have a lot of
snacks now
yay I'm glad you like them so much I'm
very proud now I feel very
um what's the word
I feel very like someone put a stamp on
me and approved of of me on my country
right you feel validate validated
validated
thank you well um I think we might leave
this stream here for today thank you
guys so much for joining yeah and hope
you enjoyed seeing me puke a little a
little bit I think that's the closest
most disgusting noise I've ever made on
this trip
um on a public stream anyway and
yeah those that that's not it those are
not it oh my God
anyway thank you guys for coming to the
stream thank you Kiowa again for the
amazing books do you have any
announcements before we finish
[Music]
um steak coming up in five
steak
down the stake there
the what
what I just made an announcement to the
waiter staff
oh yes
I'm so sorry I have I don't I have not
been aware of what is happening around
me
it's all right stay coming here at five
it's very very well well well well done
done and extremely well done guys anyway
thank you we'll leave it here for today
um you're streaming you have any streams
coming up tomorrow nah no
nah okay actually not streaming for
three days oh take a good rest yes thank
you thank you for the rest you work very
hard take a good rest you too you too
Belle every time I say Bales people are
like who's Bales yeah who is bills I
think you're one of the few year members
who still call me Bills
yeah and I think it rolls off your
tongue very well
really I think sometimes I I still think
of you as Bae but oh for completion's
sake I somehow always play Bales it
feels more complete yeah yeah
um for me I'm streaming tomorrow I'm
playing Taiko tomorrow and then I'll go
study stream at night time if you would
like to join me thank you so much for
watching and we we will see you next
time okay
okay thanks for having me yeah thanks
for coming
thank you
[Music]
foreign