hi
everyone hi y'all
hey you hi you
gosh wow what
[Music]
for the intro yeah
you're muted on discord by the way oh
don't know if you're talking to your
viewers but i can't hear you
i want to hear your voice
[Music]
hello hello everyone i had everything
muted [\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
we played a little bit of this game and
i got so scared i almost cried
and you only got scared because it got
dark because i was alone if one of you
was with me in the dark it would have
been funny but it was just me by myself
and it was very frightening
my pc does not like this game all of a
sudden whoa
oh no whoa red frame drop whoa
oh
this is just the internet possibly uh no
it's whenever i whenever i'm in the game
it's just
yeah uh let me let me i'm gonna adjust
some settings real quick okay
i'm gonna leave the lobby and then come
back okay okay
no problem by the way guys i bought a
lighter
and i bought some socks oh because there
was none
so you bought stuff yup i did i did
salt i bought salt yes salt wasting are
we cooking
who is that what does the salt do uh i
don't know maybe you can use it in
exorcism
i'll bring up their mom and i'll buy a
thermometer
where do we buy items
uh in the server lobby in the lobby ah
bye
see the bike yeah yeah
how are you guys moving around i'm stuck
uh at the at the screen
or is that is that good huh that's kiara
huh
i'm a justin oh uh
do we not have a tripod is that why the
camera thing didn't work
probably no i just i tried to put down
the camera but you can
you can pass it onto the floor or
something
oh yeah the the the camera in the truck
never showed
any anything besides outside
uh did was the green light on on the
camera did you see
cali did you turn the green light on uh
yes i turned it on
i'm gonna buy a tripod because i have
exactly twenty five dollars
perfect oh perfect okay that should work
well then
oh wait no i need to be level two and
i'm probably level one
yeah we're all we're all eleven level
one ghosty hunties okay
after this one we'll be level two i
think oh yeah
i've gathered a list cannot go with
shopping hold on i'm joining back
i'm coming back coming
up let's see if this helps
also chad says that the salt can be used
to track the ghost
via uv oh
so if they step on it and then they like
leave a trip
yeah or something like that i don't know
we'll figure it out see i see a heat
wow we're so cool this is like
this is like a an anime or like tv show
or something we're like cool
ghost hunters and this is our home cool
now
what very scared possibly
yes okay uh by the way we're gonna we're
gonna use the proximity chat right
yes we're gonna we're gonna mute us on
discord once we're in the game
okay i'm ready
to say i'm ready okay i gotta wait
should i find a job
should i turn v-sync on or off what does
that do
i don't understand why my game is all of
a sudden now like
maybe it has to do with the fact you're
also streaming well
why this game what yeah
strange oh well if you are
ah maybe that's what it is maybe
[Music]
yeah that drops performance when it
doesn't consistently hit 60 frames
so yeah maybe oh my now everything is
going wrong oh i love this game oh my
god that's cool we got time we got time
no problem i'm just going to sip some
music
um um i got five dollars in the dream
take your time take your time
oh this is bad what happened
whoa did it get worse everything
everything is going
very wrong all of a sudden oh no what do
you mean
welcome to halloween
there's always gonna be a little stuff
i'm gonna restart my game
i apologize if you want to play around
without me please
please go ahead no i can't wait it's
cool
wait who's this no problem i want to try
and learn about some of these ghosts
[Laughter]
you goodness are you good
are you
oh no
you're like my game turned into like
a strip a strip on the screen what
happened
oh yeah she's gone
i think girl is the next post
where is the next ghost this is not
going to plan this was working fine
about 10 seconds 10 minutes ago i think
the ghost got to you
your pc no not the only
it's okay not everything's going to be
perfect i mean look at look at the
character
models and how they might be a good game
[Music]
[Laughter]
these
wow let things change to this
[Music]
no shut up i'm not flat it's not it's
not funny i'm crying
on this cup you guys can keep down this
watch from here
shut up shut up chad what's what's with
your hands though
you know what about my hands i have
hands
very weird i don't know when
when you're like that you look like
you're gonna do the naruto run you're
gonna like it
[Music]
[Laughter]
did anybody else like tweak their
settings at all or is this working fine
on
on everybody else's i didn't change
anything
i tweaked it a little bit but i don't
know if it did anything
uh okay how are you doing this is weird
how do you fold over like cardboard okay
well i'll try this let me jump back
whenever you look down with your mouse
you're doing that pose yeah
look at the naruto run the only thing is
we can't be very fast
oh my god very
slow naruto run
yeah naruto naruto
roto you gotta go fast
[Music]
[Laughter]
how's it going now good night um here
i hear the voice of amelia watson
that's amazing
[Laughter]
okay let's view it let's try this again
okay yeah okay sending us messages to
help
solve this problem once again it's going
it's going it's going it's gone it's
gone
so bad what what what exactly happens
is it like yeah every time i every time
i tab into the game and i start moving
around
uh every i drop it just goes
it goes bad um did you restart the game
stupid question
yes i turned it on and off again okay
um all right so how about 60 frames per
second
and one 920 by 1080.
uh i think that's what it's done yeah
maybe double check
okay are you sure you don't want to play
around without me
i feel so bad like this this i don't
feel bad we're chilling
all right oh good um and also make sure
the game and obs are at high
let's play hide and seek all right sure
whatever um
where do you think i am oh wow you hid
pretty quickly because of tori hold on a
sec
it's fine we've done this before um
sorry everyone i don't i'm sorry this is
that
take your time don't worry
you underestimate me i will find you
hang on hang on a sec
all right you you hid pretty well i give
you that much um
oh you crashed i wonder huh
getting colder colder hotter hotter
water
hotter
cold cold cold okay hot hot
hot not me you know are you the dude
we're supposed to find wait oh wait oh
my god
emilia is doing technical support right
now in our discord so not in the collab
but she's
in the district helping us with
technical stuff
isn't she just amazing
amazing amazing okay
where were you you have to tell me wait
this looks better on my side already
wait
[Music]
trapped in the closet i close the door
like that
okay peekaboo coming out of the closet
for you cali
thanks
yeah it's only when i tab into the game
everything all of a sudden just goes
really bad
um
[Music]
i'm gonna stop right there we all know
what happens
when you try okay
it seems better because i'm i'm tabbed
out and then when i tab in
it
also it's obvious that's dropping into
the
red yeah obs is jumping into the ring
um uh you guys play player game
without me if um while i figure this out
if you want
i i'm not sure if i can do it without
you
but you're the most experienced one when
it comes to ghosts
oh no somebody unless it's not that bad
should we just try one like this let's
try one like this
let's just try it let's just try let's
just try let's just try it
okay and he says kathy
who the hell what so i'm gonna cry i'm
singing a song
sorry should we select a
house yes please yes ooh the farmhouse
the farmhouse
with the moomoos are we using in-game
chat or are we using
uh yeah in-game yeah okay
okay okay
ready up ready huh
oh oh you're ready
i want to buy a flashlight to
put in the thermometer
okay good not ready
also is everybody like does everybody
watching know what phasmophobia is
have they played it before oh yeah good
out please a pro explanation about the
game
uh pretty much uh ghostbusters except
it's us
we gotta hunt down the ghost we gotta we
gotta search for clues before the ghost
gets us and kills us in front of our
team
um it'll be easier to explain as we go
along i think
yeah who is this uh-oh sir hold on okay
loud whoa
okay
okay so in-game voice yeah cali is very
loud in game
hello oh just kidding whoa okay
loud it's gonna be a loud loud loud
everything going seconds you know it's
it's
it's going it's going it's working okay
yeah mary davis flashlight mary mary
davies
mary davis mary david
come get this camera you have the tripod
right so you guys you guys can hear me
now
okay you couldn't buy it ah okay i
gotcha
is the audio okay
[Music]
see sweet secrets about about them
because they won't hear us
like we can talk about how how beautiful
singing voice
every every girl has they can't even
hear us
and how beautiful kiara's eyes are can't
hear
okay all right oh yeah
i gotta grab something while it's loud
louder
the camera that i have is that one for
taking videos
how do you turn the how do you turn the
game audio down the wall before taking
colors is the one
you have you have to leave the match
okay i can lower them a little bit okay
so i happen to be
down in the room where we think it is
okay let's try that we'll see that how
that is
this game is scooped it's it's all
flashlights
okay that should be a little better
please let me know okay a lot of
flashlights though
the one over there is the uv light
before you're seeing fingerprints
okay you guys are right you guys are
right you guys are right okay i just
said double check thank you
are you good okay let's play the game
apply
resume how's that for audio are they a
bit better
hi i'm here too i'm adjusting more
settings yay
okay it's okay
so i turned my brightness up for this
game but we'll see how that goes
does everybody's lights work lights
lights
hello lights
guys mary davis has a pool in her
backyard and a telescope
mary davis bougie davis
uh so right now we gotta we gotta we
gotta
probably scope out where the
what this hello oh shoes
blue solos
oh i see guitar that's a guitar do we
have all the
all this stuff we need what is this
well we don't have smudge sticks but we
do have a camera a picture of her
is this a light switch
so we gotta find like closets to hide in
right
maybe upstairs this is a big map
let me
did you hear that footsteps i'm just
kidding
so if we gotta find dirty water it's
probably gonna be in here well maybe it
might be in the bathroom
in the
where the bed is i'm going to play you a
diddy
i had this desk chair i literally had
this exact desk chair for like three
years
oh my goodness that's a full pc right
there look at the size of that
oh sorry i i left hopefully they don't
have any voice calls with anybody
because all they're gonna hear is
oh sorry let me turn off my let me turn
off my uh
refrigerator size pc my full pc
hi did we find anything here's the
garage i found the garage
apparently it makes her really angry
when we say her name
mary davis can you give us a sign bloody
mary bloody mary bloody mary spin one
okay callie all right so the breaker
isn't evening
basement i believe roger
my garage what happens in my garage
stays in my garage
are you looking at us hi no
no no it's my eggs right your leg
nice legs they go all the way up
so okay ghost this is a double car
garage
my mary baby where are you
mary baby
hello hello can i go upstairs
yeah we can go upstairs we can go
upstairs and
said nobody ever but okay
mary davis give us
hey guys
because the ghost doesn't like people
together right likes people alone
i think we blew the breaker i think we
blew the breaker
so we gotta
where's the breaker uh breaker breaker
in basement over question mark
you have power
i'm in the basement i'm in the basement
the lights
are on cali is quiet all right
thank you callie's quiet because cali's
far away when she's next to us she yells
i found it i found it i found it i i
already turned it
back it's red now
wait it blew it the burger went again
okay it's green it's green
huh and now it should be fine i thought
i turned it off
by the way
who wants to go upstairs
all right coming with you whoa
uh cold air cold air hold on you know
you know
you know you have cold breath do you see
that cold breath
in the stairwell there's cold breath
here you see that you see that
so we have cold breath so it's here it's
is
yeah in the stairwell definitely here
but when it went
up a little more
[Music]
i heard something callie's the type to
antagonize the ghost
give it like three let's give it three
minutes before she starts yelling
profanities at the
tree
is that the radio who turned the radio
on
is the radio upstairs
hello mary davis how are you mary davis
give us a sign you stinker
mary yeah
okay here's the plan everybody
you owe me hey uh i'm upstairs
uh roger i'm upstairs at freezing
temperatures in this closet right here
guys
freezing temperatures in this closet a
up a up holy mackerel
oh i have the spirit box i'm a dummy i'm
sorry
whoa whoa okay okay level two
and my phone too i'm gonna turn on the
spirit box
mary davis
mary davis can you give us a sign
how do i drop an item again g
[Laughter]
okay let's go back i agree i'll stay
here
it's all right it's all right it's all
right i'm in a closet closet for safety
can't get me in here yeah you hear that
mary davis
hear that mary davis you're that mary
davis
i'm immortal you're not um
[Music]
mary
um
it was real cold here wait how do you
rotate this
how the hell do you rotate this thing
how do you rotate the camera yeah i'm
definitely thinking she's in the uh
is it upside down it might be upside
down
oh hi yeah can you see can you see the
camera hi over check check check check
mic one two
uh rotate camera left mouse and then you
can place it with g
uh roger okay
fixing that my bed
hello how do i place this camera
how do i place a skip
uh well i already forgot
all right thank you everyone i figured
it out
i don't think it gets much better than
that you see okay
can you see me do you see me
so we have we have we only have freezing
get in the closet
i guess um
if you guys can still contact us for
fine right can you hear me in the truck
uh okay ghost or
do we trust them you guys telling the
truth
you only have 35 no i'll be okay i'll be
okay don't worry about it
we can we can tag out at 10 door
so ghost orb so we have freezing
temperatures and a ghost orb
yes
hi i'm in the closet oh my god
are you okay
are you okay i'm trying to uh read which
okay
um
uh yeah okay
[Music]
up
hey uh uh my uh
check check one two where is everybody
over uh
one more time please over the radio over
here
entryway okay i'm coming downstairs i'm
scared
who where's that radio coming from
very dangerous
do you want me to sacrifice myself
i can i can go in there and i can start
screaming mary davis and see if i can
pick up any other clues and then
i die which you know whatever and then
oh wait maybe someone with more
sanity wait let's narrow it down
let's narrow down some candidates first
and then we can
figure out what to do from there okay
okay that sounds good
pop up the journal no need to die for
but it's fun oh not yet i see
yeah yeah yeah anything anything besides
freezing temperatures because the ghost
orb summoned
some people in the chat said that but i
wouldn't trust it that much
did anybody else see ghost orbs or is
that a bunch of baloney
huh how about you ghost hunt recruits
i don't think it was there i didn't see
any flashlights
i didn't see any orbs i only saw the
temperatures
um yeah well temperature we can still
rule out some
so uh yuray
a demon mayor banshee phantom
wraith wrath we didn't have emp
emf 5 though we only have emf 2.
so we can rule out a few more too
actually
so race race yeah
did we try the spirit box uh i can try
it some more i didn't really do much
with it
it's still up i think i still have it i
think
yeah since the the ghost only responds
when you're alone
we probably have to send one person
there
i volunteer as tribute okay
but you're still only at 24
22 23. look at all that activity
okay goku i'll go get some
uh some evidence and i'll report back as
long as i can before i
you know good luck
thank you
you're gonna have to come collect it off
my dead body
i'm not a coward i'm not a coward it's
just yeah i'm gonna
come into the house too but i'm gonna
stay far away from you so you can talk
to the ghost i'm just gonna watch them
ah content i get you're the cameraman
welcome to my ghost adventure show i'm
your host gal guron
the toughest predator in the okay the
lights went out we're fine
come close here right next to me come on
come on i don't bite are these lights on
nope okay the lights are off
okay here's the game plan
i'm your host gargoyla
mary davis mary davis you are the next
host of my gargura show
would you like to say a few words to the
viewers
let's let's start this first round of
questions mary davis thank you for
coming on tonight mary davis
mary davis are you uh are you
are you adult mary davis
smile stinky
you hear me come in come in come in then
come in hq
i'm not going out there they're dying
down there
okay
mary davis mighty brave of you
is the door still locked can you get out
it's kind of ironic how cali always dies
first even though she's death
hello come in the door is locked still
should i come out i'm gonna come help
you
i'm coming to help
should i take a picture can i take a
selfie let's take a selfie
see does anybody have a do you want to
give a flashlight
no i did not uh take my flashlight
i'm
yeah hi i just want a picture how do i
take a picture
oh yeah okay
smile oh that's not your face this is
your face
cali smile
oh beautiful beautiful
that's what i'm talking about
we got two left it's fine who's next
i didn't get any evidence do you want
the spirit box somebody else could have
the spirit box
there's a closet upstairs upstairs yeah
go upstairs go upstairs
there is a closet to your right
there's a flashlight on the ground i
think she's dead
oh no
yara
ah
uh how good are you guessing uh guessing
on the
answers
[Laughter]
huh okay okay let me let me think let me
channel my inner army
can i get a cell phone there's one more
picture
a smile
there we go that one's going in the
that one's going in the the photo album
okay i can't close the door your body's
in the way your body's in the way
okay
well what do you think it is
unless you want to go in there and do
something right now okay um
only have like the only solid edison we
have is
is the freezing camp with the
possibility of a ghost store
oh okay do we wanna
um let's bring up the journal
i like how we're just chilling i like
how we're just chilling
next to uh our friend's body like hmm
let's breathe let's bring up the journal
it's so warm
it's a bit cold you know freezing temps
her body is still warm
it was toasty for a little longer
okay oh if only we had the salt we could
have
probably tried something because rats
have toxic you have to
talk salt because we don't take a
uv like you think we can maybe we had a
uv light didn't we
in the truck i think we i think we did i
think
okay turn the lights on
chris chance to attack in the dark i
or it can be tracked by
footsteps hey
well if i had to guess one i'd probably
say
check if there's any uh fingerprints
you're going in there alone if there is
any yes
if there is any and i die then you know
i believe in you okay i'll uh i'll
i'll keep you uh okay
okay you got this xena you're born for
this you were made for this
top detective uh sorry i mean if you
plug your ears on my top detective you
know you got this
she's a goner she's a goner guys she's a
gunner i'll give her
30 seconds
30 seconds tops okay let's see
how you doing champ i can see you i see
your footsteps okay i can see the cold
air
i'm doing okay okay
i think they can pick up the camera and
do like uh
also
i am i am watching the camera i just saw
your feet run by so we think it's either
a wraith
or a mare i mean the mayor makes sense
but the spirit box oh i have the spirit
box don't i
uh is that her
uh i think i think on the the door if
you find the the prints on the door will
be rather easy to see
uh they're usually right in the middle
of the door it's a big hand print in
green
roger that sounds like a very good plan
what's a good song wait the girls can
hear
all right
well we heard i heard footsteps when i
was upstairs in the closet
so it can't be a wraith because i did
hear it stomp around
so it's not a wraith
a mare okay
i mean we can we can guess what's in
there
i feel like i hear footsteps
there's no there's no activity showing
huh
can you tell me um
okay
the mayor yeah yes
uh mares have increased chance to attack
in the dark okay
so turning on the lights uh lower the
attack chance but
it's been dark in that house for a while
yeah do you want to guess mayor or you
wanna
okay um
it can't be it can't be a people think
it's a it's a yuri but it can be a yuri
because
a stronger effect on people's sanity but
my sanity was was pretty much zero and
it went for kiara instead unless
oh
home yuri you're a how do you say it
you're right
okay i think we left them dead for long
okay yeah we didn't get to use the
spirit box because i'm a dummy and i had
it
that's okay it's okay i should have
brought it and then use it
i dropped it do you want to try it or
i think we should at least get another
game so they can
have it okay let me uh put what are we
gonna guess
mayor okay did you fill in your journal
yes
all these pictures callie yes yes yes
yes yes
okay okay
there you go
you guessing banshee i like how the
the uh welcome back
let's see if you're right
damn you guys are good at this game okay
okay chat is actually good at this game
girl you died no no my sanity dropped
wow though that was right they were like
oh it's
here
okay so that my my stream doesn't like
the the
this screen this loading area doesn't
like but it seems the game seems to be
fine so
sorry about the the lagginess here
kiara yeah i tried to leave the the menu
but i accidentally left about one second
oh okay okay where's giada yeah
she'll be back okay
yeah so uh i guess we should come back
maybe maybe listen to chat
because they seem to actually know what
they're talking about
sorry if i ever doubted you maybe um a
[\h__\h] thing
like the whole group or just one person
because like if it was like an average
between everyone then it started
attacking a lot more
after like we were just dropped really
low right kobe
oh it's the group the whole oh okay okay
that makes sense
oh by the way you you got some uh
the the the journal was in the kitchen
so we should have
eventually moved it upstairs so they
could ride in there and also we should
have been looking for the ocean
board oh job boy okay oh yeah
did you say luigi how do you pronounce
that but we should have been looking for
that because it probably would have
been luigi it's the linguine board
okay so journal next time we move it
where it belongs
that sounds like a plan hey can i buy a
flashlight
yeah if you have thirty dollars uh
i think i have i think i have ten bucks
and some bus tokens and some pocket list
so can anyone lend me like maybe 20
bucks
yeah i'll buy one if someone has extra
money then
they can buy it you don't have to you
know i'm five dollars
don't worry it's fine we're all broke
i'll just wander through the darkness
again that always works we already have
a ghost writing book right or is that
a different thing that always appears in
the trunk i think
let's see what we can buy let's see we
can buy i think i'll buy a tripod now
oh i love tr in my right ear
yeah okay i bought the tripod so we can
have the camera up higher and see more
things now i'm gonna add a candle wait
what is this note
yeah all right gotta select a job is it
my turn now
yeah i think it's nothing okay so which
one did we do before
just now
that was like a house a farmhouse that
was the farmhouse that was uh
no that was a normal house it wasn't
there's like two houses and then one
normal house
ah tanglewood street ridge view it
turned out to be
a u-ray you yuray
to go to texas hell yeah
cowboy do something too big though we
shouldn't do something too big because
we're never gonna finish it
let's go to such a sense
is it a house in texas
i don't know if that was a lucky guess
on your guys's part but that was good
our house with the basement the owner
called this morning hey what does
dangerous goes is haunting the area
sounds dangerous you'll have to be
careful with this one
yeah no [\h__\h] sherlock everything you're
going to leave as soon as you can
more info when you're looking at my mind
you may lower sanity what else do we
have oh i don't know how it normally
lowers so i guess that makes sense this
one sounds dangerous
yeah wow you couldn't tell you that one
recommended items thermal and then the
one that's
in seems like around ny two-story four
bedroom with the basement the owner
called this morning
dangerous ghost island in the area
bringing us
thermometer okay so i wonder team should
be small you guys want to do the one
the one-person one okay because maybe we
can actually accomplish it
we're going to text okay yeah texas
oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
wait wait wait uh i have to add the
tripod oh yeah
okay tripod there we go hey
also how do you guys use the items that
you buy yeah
you have to have to add the equipment
list yeah
okay got it got it okay do you think the
ghost responds to yee haw
howdy ghosty
oh yeah now you added it okay good okay
okay we're good enough there is no salt
though there is no salt cali
show the night you have to ready up by
the way these are not just
in chicken oh i got it if she dies
we got it ready and go
hurry howdy
is that a can of tuna what is this
oh salt i don't want that responsibility
no thank you oh you're missing someone
uh callie i think oh yeah sorry i was
talking again
nice tripod okay richard brown only
responds when people are alone come on
you should use
it's comparable activity refer to your
journal does anyone have a crucifix
no no no crucifix
[Music]
this is a sad song
oh my god
richard brown wait is there a limited
amount of salt what is something
endless self is amelia here
i'm getting yes
sorry is there really a way to turn off
push to talk
uh i don't know go into the menu maybe
yeah yeah
forget that maybe next time
by the way guys okay okay okay
if you need more i just need you to roll
on some gotcha and you'll have more with
this a ghost
event i think with
how slow we are doing these things i
think this might be the last game
huh okay yeah maybe so we got we gotta
figure this one out let's do our best
yes our goal is to have everyone alive
yes let's go
is nobody bringing the tripod
i guess i guess we're not bringing the
tripod all right
because i otherwise i can't have a
flashlight
ah i see you think that'll summon the
ghost
hello let's get some light popping out
here
i have a lighter
uh what's the name again how do i light
these things come on
what's the name of them it's richard
brown richard brown
what are some what's with some richard
nicknames richie
i like these candles
[Music]
i bet you some people named richard go
by bob like some people have nicknames
that don't even don't even like
you know them as bob your entire life
and it's like what's your real name and
he's like
richard
how do i light this candle my guy
was that me
hey guys
um
so i was in the kitchen trying to light
this candle and i think richard flipped
the cup on me because i i called i made
fun of him
yeah he flipped the cup at me i don't
think he's at the dinner table i think
he's hungry
richard brown all
yeah he's definitely there he's in the
kitchen he's definitely there he flipped
the cup at me
oh okay
should i use the sauce okay
guys is there alex here with your brown
southwest freezing temperature
that was me by the way that was me that
was me my heart just jumped into my
forehead
i dropped something
light yeah yep yeah light the salt is it
working when i tried it
i got it it was cold here
i was making fun of him richard brown
maybe he'll maybe he'll talk around
are you old richard brown are you here
look i'll put the book down
is this a picture of you richard brown
do you have a monocle
and a moustache god that scared the [\h__\h]
out of you scared me
when i saw that did you see when you had
the flashlight on the face i thought it
was the coolest that was like the
coconut brown
in which direction should i put the
camera
oh standing table okay so
wait we have freezing temperatures
freezing temperatures
how do you guys think we're doing are we
doing all right i turned on the camera
richard brown would you like to be a
guest on the podcast
richard brown
richard brown are you adult
richard brown are you shy
when's the last time you showered
up
is that a four that's a three we had a
three on the uh
we got a three three on the emf i don't
think he liked it when i asked him if he
showered i don't think he likes me
insinuating that he might stink
richard brown shampoo with bread
richard brown richard brown richard brad
richard brad richard brown
richard brown is starting to sound like
not a word
maybe we can ask him some questions are
you here
richard brown richard brown are you
stinky smelly
are you here ugly richard brown
okay okay i thought
he's here
[Music]
yeah he's here he's on the ems he's on
the ems
chad is saying you should turn off the
lights but i don't know how i feel about
that
yeah i don't know and this was a it was
a three
on the emf maybe we should turn off
elections
richard brown do you know how to spell
oh you do know how to spell oh you
better prove it
prove it pick up this pencil and write
you coward
hey girl i'm gonna leave you alone
he threw something on the floor
richard brown what's this all for
oh never mind i know what the salts for
uh ricky richie richie richard brown
richard brown richard brown richard
do we have any other we're gonna die
i think we really need to be alone
wait i want to find the lead can we find
the ouija board
oh yeah that might be fun yeah i want to
talk to him stick together he won't come
after us either so let's let's go yeah
let's take it
let's go um where would it be
i'm in a bedroom i'm looking for okay
cool
maybe we can let someone
slow
huh
welcome to math with hollow live eaton
i'm back in the house
to take some photos does anybody go in
the basement with me let's go see if we
can find the ouija board if the chat was
like 50 50 on whether or not it was go
starts or
if it was brad
all right i'm going to look for the
luigi board
cause i'm going to talk to this guy
and then i cannot wait to bring that
spawn sometimes
he's up there with them so he's busy
he's occupied richard brown
where are you brown hello
where is i don't think it's fun because
it's i don't see it
oh no that's a piece of wood okay dang
it i wanna i wanna use the ouija board
it's in the bedroom
oh that's a shame let me turn this light
off though so we're not gonna blow any
breakers
how how did you find that out
fingerprint fingerprint
nice nice fingerprint thread wait wait
on the door we have freezing
temperatures and we have
uh i mean
back here back here come on come on
fingerprints
come upstairs upstairs it's either a
wraith or a banshee
i don't know if you guys can see it but
oh how did you see that smartphone uh
banshee
one person at a time then she fears the
crucifix
they tell me again that green
yeah i want to take a photo of it
you have the spear box yeah
oh a bit more a bit more
[Music]
it flew off the table
did anybody get emf five
so he's here four at the highest richie
fourth the highest we haven't had any
footsteps so
it's either a banshee or a wraith um
please
tell us are you here thank you all right
thanks you are with so what does that
mean
um richard brown please write something
one person at a time maybe maybe let's
just talk to him and not use his name
maybe he doesn't use his name please
write something
has anybody heard footsteps
please write a message
well it likes us to be it likes us to be
alone right and the the banshee
also likes to be alone
it stalks people who are alone where's
kiara give us a sign
give us a sign okay so if it's a banty i
i feel like it's a banshee because the
alone part
okay should we test it out yeah probably
give us a sign
fingerprints emf um
yeah oh chad guess
richard is this the keys to your
automobile
richard i have obtained your keys
richard what are you doing
please scream
scream hey kiara
are you okay right again
i'm a poor guy
[Music]
it's a banshee it's a banshee it's a
banshee the door's locked the door is
locked
it's a [\h__\h] it's [\h__\h] it's [\h__\h]
okay i think it's a banshee personally
i'm just saying i think it's
wait did we hear footsteps did anybody
hear footsteps
i didn't hear any personally but okay no
footsteps
i'm thinking uh ina died she died in
front of me i got it on camera i got it
on camera
oh my god dude
what yeah there's the body
oh no oh no
oh no that's no good
um on the live camera by the way what's
wrong
i don't remember a dude
i don't i don't really know how the
other ghosts look like so i'm not sure
but the chat was like oh
banshee or something like that did we
ever get ems level five
i think i i think i did hear footsteps
i think i think i'm gonna say that that
was a
what the neck who's got the camera i
want to see this
i gotta get a picture of this does
anybody have a camera yeah i'm curious
oh goodbye goodbye i only have the video
camera
oh yeah yeah we already know my dad
and take a pic i can't i can't take a
pic i only
i can only take a video and you guys
want to guess so
i don't know what do we have what do we
think it is banshee wraith
uh you said banshee
[Music]
i'm thinking it's banshee
screaming don't [\h__\h] scream typically
a banshee would scream
i guess not a ghost banshee but i so
when anna died did we hear footsteps
because i i'm pretty sure uh
i think i heard footsteps
i didn't hear anything okay
i can't remember if i heard footsteps
now does anybody else wanna
nah but about the emf the band she would
have needed ems fifo as well no and we
didn't get that
oh we didn't get we did not get emf5
but we did get the radio so is that
spirit box
did he did he say something over this
video
actually i'm not sure maybe that was the
other house
oh it's the spirit box oh oh that
spirit box my chat says
uh we did get we did get emf level five
so it must be a banshee
okay okay yeah it's benji let's let's
do we wanna we wanna do we wanna go with
benji yes
yes i am for the panty i too am for
banjo
let's go let's put banshee in the box
do i have to bring back the items do you
know
the tripod do you have to bring it back
uh
i don't know i maybe you wanna go get it
i don't wanna bring a tripod i can't
bring anything for you
i don't have to okay do we have these
items i wonder
uh okay uh chad says no okay they also
say not here
huh i too witnessed one
we all did nina died in front of me i
watched it
yeah sad enough wait wait girls wait
wait wait wait
aren't banshees only female and this
name is male
huh is that random does that matter in
the game i thought banshees were only
irish branches can be male maybe
an irish banshee in texas
i wonder uh it's fine
not okay maybe not in this game okay so
i think we can say banshee doesn't
everyone have it in the journal
um yes sounds good
okay are you ready ready
ready yeah yes sorry i forgot to press v
[Music]
okay
how do we do it everybody did we get it
right there's some jobs ready
what is a wrap all right
a race
is it called why am i level one and you
guys are level two
because you you died uh in the first
game so early i guess i don't know
uh yeah i suppose that makes sense
do you guys want to play one more quick
one i can do one more do you want to do
one more
yes maybe if it's fast one okay one for
me it says yes
yes yes let's see what i can buy
i have 45 dollars okay money
i still have maybe smudge sticks i'll
get the smudge sticks
smash sticks like two i have 25
[Music]
dollars
i want a head-mounted camera
that sounds fun doesn't it we can't vlog
squads let's see
gather evidence it's possible so the
ghost removal team can deal with it
afterwards
let's see i want to look for a small one
oh i don't really need any of this
okay how about tanglewood street house
size one person
a small three bedroom single floor house
the basement got an email from a friend
he says there is definitely some kind of
paranormal activity here
head there and gather as much evidence
as you can so a ghost removal team to
finish the job okay let's go
okay i'm ready spaghetti
i am also ready spaghetti
i'm
oh it's the truck hit him up move him
out
okay let's go yes
[Music]
wait guys guys guys can we turn off push
to talk
we have to like leave the lobby to get
to the settings oh we have to leave
correctly
yeah forget that forget that next time
okay donkey
let's go
all right lads what do we got
hey ina ina
what does this look like on your screen
what does this look like
it responds to everyone
[Laughter]
all right um a photo of dirty water in a
sink i can take a picture of that that
seems
easy enough i'll do that dirty water
it's gonna attack us no matter what you
guys it's going to come after us even if
we are all together
so yeah just be ready excellent
i got this spirit with boxers
i'll be checking the emf i got the book
too
and i'll take the um uh and
the salt oh okay i got stuff
i thought
uh for the do you have a lighter for the
smudge stick
i do i do excellent nice do you like it
would you like me to give it to whoever
has this much space
no i think i think we need we might need
one
no that you i don't know how to use them
i don't know how to use them either but
we'll learn i have maybe one of us can
have the sticks and one of us will like
them i have the lighter so we can do
that then
hi friends welcome to my cribs
patty clarke
is this a light how do i like this
so where they hide in the ouija board in
here where would it be i want the ouija
board for this last game
patricia clark give us a sign i'm gonna
check the basement for the ouija board
where's the luigi board
okay
good point
in this position
where are you here did you guys see that
uh uh it's gone now it's gone
oh oh it's kiara okay
wait where were you with the ems why
i was i was exactly here
oh okay let me let me put this here
maybe i'll write a book for us
give us the next amazon bestseller book
right here
right here on the table come on let's
huh it sounds like
is it my radio
i don't know maybe i'm putting it down
you hear it now i let some kid yeah i'm
gonna leave some salt
that's my radio that's my spirit box ah
okay
oh oh
oh what is that was that always there
wasn't that
it's not oh it's myself ah okay okay
i thought it was hunting okay i wonder
where else i should put it
maybe i'm gonna bring the camera into
tripod
brb the lights came dimming for anybody
else
patricia clark can you speak to me
patricia clark
please write something
please write something i'm preparing
that's my i'm diving headfirst into that
closet oh
boy i tell you i tell you right w
patty clark
patty
they say turn off the lights for spirit
box response so i'm gonna turn off this
light here
okay patricia clark
speak to my box
[Music]
is it here
oh handprint handprint we have
fingerprints they got fingerprints
fingerprints
fingerprints fingerprints
everybody put fingerprints in your jar
no
give us a sign
the lights the lights are dead the
lights are dead right too
it said kill in the box and say kill on
the box and therefore i'm going in my
box my books here's my books
okay everybody it said kill so everybody
put uh put
put put spirit box in your in your
journal please
please make sure you also have
fingerprints
so it can be either a spirit a wraith
or a poltergeist
[Music]
are the lights on do we want to turn the
breaker back on
[Music]
all right i put down the notepad
okay write something
um spirit ball experience
ghost riding okay there's not much
okay if it writes something in the book
it's a spirit okay
okay god got it roger hold her guys
pulled her eyes
you can throw huge amounts of objects at
once okay
ghost orb
yes i have uh the boxes on ems too right
now
i'm gonna go get the lights and hope i
don't die
wish me luck to the right
wow it's dark in here ms4 emf emf
ems
[Music]
oh hi ma'am sorry
hey where like
i'm in the basement i might die but the
lights are back okay can we turn the
lights on somebody
find the wall find the wall follow the
wall follow the wall okay what is this
this is the fridge the fridge
might be getting ready to hunt i am in
the basement i require resistance
follow the line of the wall follow the
line of the wall wait what is this okay
okay
it's good guys turn the lights on boom
turned on
i really want to see if we get dirty
water in the sink maybe there's some
there they're pretty rare
so wraith poltergeist or spirit
so
where is the phone
[Music]
have we had freezing temperatures
has anybody seen a ghost orb
no but i repositioned the camera to the
basement so maybe
i don't know where should i shuffle
where should i put the camera around all
right
it didn't see anything when i pointed it
to the kitchen
okay okay i relit the candles
do you want to use the i mean we already
have spirit box evidence we don't really
need it
um unless you wanna
uh [\h__\h]
throw something patty give us a sign
hello daddy give us a sign
patty give us a sign
patricia throw something
patricia i'm gonna go check them
is this recording
[Music]
and ghost has stinky breath he blew in
my ear
nobody
kelly
poltergeist
maybe a poltergeist
oh ineffective in an empty room that
makes sense
did you hear that
he did the thing he did the grudge it
went
hey ina can i request a sanity check
over
hi uh uh
[Music]
thank you over there was a
slight peak of activity just a moment
ago
so how do we how do we hold up oh
they're screaming
okay i love you patricia
i'm gonna close this door
patricia clark give us a sign
give us a sign patricia
patricia patricia i love y'all
[Music]
are you married patricia what is it like
are you married
you have children patricia clark
where do you come from patricia clark
hey patricia nice pool how old are you
do you live in the void
what's your favorite food
you're kind of lame i'm not gonna lie
kinda lame
kind of kind of stinky not gonna lie
kind of lame
i can't promise i'll bring it back
give us a sign give us a shout
out are you a chicken
[Music]
let's go let's go
can you get out is the door open
cali come in cali over
callie you read over callie
kelly is dead i see
[Music]
there's footsteps so it's not a wreath
right
oh
okay guys there's footsteps so it's not
a wraith so it's either a
poltergeist or a spirit
you got ghost riding i think someone
said they rode kills
no no no that was the spirit box the
spirit box said
kill yeah
well my sanity is draining so many
um
very powerful and dangerous they're
discovered at one of their hunting
grounds after unexplained death
but the poltergeist noisy
this ghost is noisy because i kept
hearing it go like
and stuff like that
i keep forgetting to talk into the thing
okay let's let's uh
okay okay i'm gonna make my way to the
dining room
okay do you need help i can help
uh do you actually have a flashlight i
could use good eye look at the camera
let me see your camera
what's in the camera i don't see
anything do you see
you seen this body i see nobody wait
what oh you gotta switch you don't see
that
no you mean you don't see that i don't
see anybody
what do you what kiara why why do you
not
if what okay okay
not on your screen
so we need ghost writing
we need to get it to write in the book
okay
either orb or ghost writing
move the book around but yeah yeah we
gotta move the book around okay can it
can't it write in the book while we're
holding it
i feel like since we placed the camera
and saw no ghost art it must be ghost
riding
that's that's true that's a good point
ghost
so ghost riding so spirit then
okay yep i would say it's a spirit
because
we didn't see any ghost orbs at all it
must be the writing so it can only be
the spirit
that's a good point that's a good point
i forgot your name that's a good point
patricia
it's risa patricia write in the book
picture
okay
do a flip put it on the
floor you can hold the book they say you
can hold the book if you want to move
around
oh my
i gotta say uh very good camera angle
placement i must say
hey is there something written in that
book what's what is it oh it's your
finger never mind
oh wait it's your thumb no
activity
zero zero
are the lights off
maybe put the book down maybe try maybe
try
yeah let's try putting it down does the
ghost
move by saying its name
you have to put the book down for it to
use it oh okay apparently the book has
to be down in order for the ghost to use
it
all right they're very busy doing their
ghost work what do you guys think it is
i i also i think kiara has a really good
point as in we haven't seen
uh we haven't seen any uh
any orbs or anything oh you think it's
the the laundry room and not the kitchen
but cali died in the kitchen
try the laundry room you guys want to
try the
the laundry room with the book
over
laundry room yeah maybe the ghost
ghost has moved perhaps
and say her full name patricia clark
hey we got tasks done
huge spike huge spike guys guys hello
hello hello
hello
someone's gonna die
hello ghost team ghost team
do you read over ghost team
this is hq hq to
to to go squad do you read over
is everybody okay over
i think but you can die
i mean oh no okay um
lens
any ghostwriting okay so
uh okay i'll come to you
she died at the door i see your hand
okay
oh she died at the door
wait this ghost is fast then wait what
okay did it write did he write in the
book
did he i have the book yes
no no no no books here books here books
here
no writing no writing no writing no
writing and no orbs
we can you
oh
patricia clarke will you write in this
book please it can't be that hard just
pick up the pencil
slap it around throw it across the room
push me touch me do something come on
inna
all right i think i think it's just i
think it's just me
okay oh hi hi hi hi
so it killed where is this ghost it
killed her here
should i bring the thermometer
all right so i blew the breaker sure if
you want
okay i'll bring the thermometer
i
well she doesn't like being alone she
doesn't like lone people so she won't
touch me
wait yes you will this is a bad idea
what am i doing
i'm scared to go home
i gotta go place the book in the laundry
room okay
okay okay yep yep yep
wait we're gonna be okay i'm brave i'm
brave i'm brave i'm
i'm brave i'm brave i'm brave follow the
wall line follow the online guru
okay we put the book down right in the
book
right in the book you stinky stinky
spirit activity is going up a little bit
be careful
yeah right in the book stinker yeah do
what you want
all right i'm out
i was
[Laughter]
[Music]
i i don't know i put i put the i put the
the book in the laundry room
um yeah do you want me to go turn the
lights back on in the house so that we
can use that i do want to just go and
go in blind go in dark or do you want to
guess what do you want to do
um
oh there was some activity i want to see
if she
wrote in the book move the camera oh
move the camera okay
if it only hunts one person at a time
[Music]
i will be the base
no we don't know who it will go for us
you don't know where it'll pop up
so okay oh there's oh
there's a bike maybe the road in the
pool yeah we gotta go check the book
okay let's go together okay and then if
if there's a hunt hide in the closet
save yourself huh yeah they're allowed
okay
you see that
that's big hand print
big what was that
sounds like a microwave are your hot
pockets done
why are you leaving you know
what's going on yeah some of these uh
pizza rolls are done what's up what's up
what's up
i'm gonna drop the lighter okay
okay did you hear that beep was that you
yeah i heard it too microwave i think it
is the mic oh it was the microwave she's
making hot pocket
better be a pizza pocket oh my three
write in the book yes stinky [\h__\h]
apply the stone clue where's the book i
threw it down
here
did she take the book
i swear i threw the book down
aye aye
right um
um the book uh the book has glitched
into the wall
oh the book is gone i don't see here
the book is gone okay does anybody else
have wait i picked it up i picked it up
i picked it up i picked it up oh wait
check this out see if they're um
right in the kitchen
is it that way here hello
there's a salt footprint apparently yeah
you like girl you can check over here
they guide me guide me where are you
right here in the laundry room can i go
into the garage
like that no
it's a spirit it's a spirit it's got to
be a spirit
oh yeah apparently you don't need uh
who had the camera
i think so
okay okay um
you wanna check do you wanna do
poltergeist okay rapid step on the fault
right
all right
hey the phone's ringing again that's a
loud spirit though maybe it is a
poltergeist
because it keeps making noise it's loud
that was richard okay
i'm gonna guess poltergeist
oh hey it moves something did you see
that did you see that
did you see that
in the camera yes also the book do you
like how i placed the book
where's the book it's right there you
see that white thing it's right there
oh i see i see oh standing up right
yeah i think it is poultry guys it's
moving along
it through something it's a poltergeist
yeah it's poster based do you have
poltergeist here
oh here was nothing
you ready i'm ready who pushed the
button
ready we going you ready
you're a two person i'm a fifteen
percent
it's gotta be it's gotta be poltergeist
welcome back i've prepared some jobs for
you yeah
[Music]
that's the first thing i got right good
job
good job yay we did it we did it we did
it
high five yeah high fives all around
us i died right at the door though right
at the door i was about to leave
we saw your buddy oh
i tried no i tried you know what i
watched you go right past
eno that was cool
you found it so quickly no i i
remembered that it was an open door but
i didn't even close the door but then
it had itself on you i guess love is an
open door
indeed nicely done guys
that was fun at least we got what we got
one we got the big one that was a tricky
one
yeah yeah nice chicken chicken in the
calories
around nowhere to run yeah let's all
go
[Laughter]
all right i think uh two hours of ghost
busting is enough right
all
i expected it to be much much more scary
but the chat says
because we were uneasy it wasn't so
scary i guess it gets much
scarier i mean it wasn't too scary i
mean that wasn't bad for
level one level two
that was fun that was good
again okay yes please let's get better
ghost hunters
but anna has to play it too yeah
next time i want i want next time she
won't be a ghost
what's that detective time i have an
idea
four players but we want ammo to be in
there too how about
i play together with cali right like i
visit her at her house
we play just as one player there's no
other reason i just wanted to so that
amic enjoyed the game there's no other
reason why i would want to do that
oh yes cali can be the mouse and you can
be the wizard it'll be perfect
perfect what is this
[Music]
that way me and kelly can mentally
support each other
when when we're like scared in the
darkness
[Laughter]
big brain big brain alrighty i think
that's it yeah
yeah yeah does anybody have any
announcements for the week
yeah my new song is on all streaming
platforms go check out
yeah it will be it will be there
it will be there soon for spotify but
itunes and whatever go check it out
please
i'm i'm collabing with polka senpai this
weekend
um well i still have to put up my
schedule so
oh yeah
i think tomorrow i'm instead of bitching
kitchen we're going to be [\h__\h] and
movers because i recently
hey on theme i like it yeah
look forward to it everyone okay
[Music]
all right everyone thanks for watching
thank you
catch up on the flip side indeed
bye
you