[Music]
faster
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hello
hello cheerio
[Music]
lime Marines
sounding more like Texas
ah come on
ah it's it's Saturday you edit it
catch your day ain't it
no it's not
what was that what was that what was
that that was good no
I saw or die in it
wasn't that [\h__\h] good breath
what's up
pretty good right oh
[Laughter]
peanut butter on the road peanut butter
no no peanut butter I don't like peanut
butter
I need some
BTM I need BDM ooh I need big Jam
where's my pj um
where's my opinion
I need it right now where's my video
[Music]
I don't know how to stream anymore
um
hi guys it's been a while
it's been indeed
a while I I don't I don't feel like I'm
streaming yet am I streaming
you should now hear the bgm that is
looking stealth cute that's what I title
it
um I'm I'm here
um I'm back home and hopefully
I will stay for now I don't want to go
anymore anywhere any any time
uh I'm sick of it
[Music]
within one month I traveled to Japan
twice back and forth
[Music]
and I went to the UK and then the last
trip I got sick however
it was like in the morning
I'm trying to remember if I already
found something like on the night before
we flew
but I can't remember but I was
definitely like in the morning when I
woke up I noticed like some some like
small I sound congested it's like so
much better like especially the last
night fixed all my problems
uh but yeah I noticed like oh oh my
throat feels a bit scratchy but like I
know I noticed scratchiness is like when
when something's you know
you know starting
[Music]
um
so I I told rmt we met at the airport
early in the morning was before before
10 a.m it's quite quite too loud okay
[Music]
yeah and then like rnt I I I I I'm fine
right now but I have to scratchy feeling
in my throat that is telling me that I
am getting worse
[Music]
no the flight was was I'm just giving
you a rough time it was way earlier we
we arrived way earlier than 10 a.m I had
to get up really early
yeah and she's like oh okay
and I'm like yeah sorry by the way if
you get sick because of me but she also
just recovered from a sickness but she
uh
she was already fine
and she said like ah I never get sick
like even when I had the sea virus it
wasn't wasn't so bad so she wasn't
worried about getting sick from me at
least yata who uh
[Music]
but those people who do how could she
pass it to me that like I started
feeling it before I even went off to the
airport
um
and we met at the at the airport sea
virus
famous last words
so her name her name is rmt that was my
old roommate I used to live uh with her
before the sea thing
um
uh and then I went to Japan for a year
and then I came back and I was in her
life at that point uh but I I wanted to
move didn't want to stream immediately
yeah I didn't want to stream the whole
time
in the same apartment because kind of
awkward yeah I did it for a couple of
days weeks
but I moved quickly and since since then
we haven't been meeting much I feel like
yeah this was the first time I met her
this year
uh we don't talk much either like on
text messages just messages or whatever
we never meet but we're still like you
know we still know we like each other
and
you know we're we're good we're good
so I was I was really happy when she
um wanted to go to London with me I
think it was my idea though because I
was like oh look there's there's a lot
of Lord Lord of the Rings musical
in England yeah close to London uh
starting here do you want to go with me
and she said yes let's [\h__\h] go
because she loves Lord of the Rings
yo I'm already going deep into the
tangents it's been 12 minutes I am I'm
so deep already oh my God
ah
um
yeah yeah I've got a lot to tell you I
think I'll tell you the whole thing
today because I also got a lot of
pictures
that's what we are here for hey you're
here to listen to my beautiful story
about the UK about I how I came and I
went I left the UK
not too much of a pain for you
um well London ah well okay a second
step by step
let's take everything step by step right
oh sure
okay
um I've got pictures I I just have them
all on Discord I gotta like download
them
uh but here we go Walkers
did you saw some of these oops some of
these pictures you saw on Twitter
already
[Music]
let's begin
some of my tensions I wrote down but
some for some others I'm gonna have to
think really hard about what happened
[Music]
um
so I lose my tensions yeah
[Music]
oh yeah okay okay I don't think I really
wrote anything down about the travel
crisps not chips yeah yeah crisps that's
what I kept on saying
with sparkles crisps on Twitter salt and
vinegar I didn't eat those I didn't buy
those I didn't eat those yeah but so we
went on the plane of course we had
separate
um seats because we went with one of
those cheap ass Airlines honestly uh I
feel like it's almost impossible to not
go to such a like close destination with
out like one of those cheap ass Airlines
it wasn't Ryan area it was with air with
air whiz what do they think they are
Wizards
but I mean it's kind of I mean in the in
the in the medieval times over the Roman
times probably people would consider
this Wizardry
um flying people all over the country
like that
so
[Music]
okay I'm gonna hold back my comment
no but uh I I I I I I like the the color
of the seats
that's the only good thing I can say
though
nah um I don't know no I mean it's
pretty shitty I mean
uh there's no free drinks of course you
have to buy everything and if you if you
want a seat like they assigned I feel
like it's even worse than Ryan there
like with Ryanair I didn't have this uh
experience Ryanair and wizard in case
you're not from Europe are cheap ass
Airlines for like short distance mostly
destinations
low-cost carriers in Europe
uh yeah right air ranks higher for me
just because I feel like at least for
Ryanair
like what I noticed whiz air the seats
um there is no reclining option at least
they're like rather feel comfortable and
from the get-go I feel like they are a
bit more reclined than other seats in
their default position
[Music]
my voice is pretty much normal I think
at this point maybe a little bit maybe
it's just a little bit sicklish still
um
Ryanair killed my relationship what
because they put you on different seats
all across the airline on different
sides it's killing relationships I can
imagine no oh no flagon wasn't so bad I
I had some flogging in the morning but
fun I'm like mostly like 100
yeah I do notice I sound congested a
little bit but I'm fine I can sing
[Music]
yeah so I think I'm a Ryanair you can at
least recline the chairs a little bit
I think
last time I flew I think I could but
yeah who's there you can't
like what
you can't even do that okay with a
client chairs
it's okay though it was relatively
comfortable and uh actually [\h__\h]
lucky I had a window seat normally you
don't get window seats for free on this
Airline I don't know what happened
recline air oh my God
yeah what happened to Quality of Life
yeah it's okay I mean I tried just short
flights or whatever
so uh oh yeah I was really tired on the
plane but I I tried to sleep a bit but
couldn't whatever bleep I bought some
drink and a snake snack uh some like not
potato chips but something something
Savory to snack on and yeah ah
[Music]
all the interesting thing was like you
know the plane looked pretty damn full
and we were a full row and the I was on
the window seat there were two dudes
next to me
and the middle dude after take the after
the flight took off after like a few
minutes early on the dude he left
and went to the back of the plane and I
thought maybe he's going to the toilet
but
um he never came back
[Music]
where'd it go like he was so the
determined when he left
did he take his finger I feel like he he
took like his handbag stuff or whatever
but didn't uh take his suitcase so he
would take that later when he actually
like you know left the plane on the way
from the back to the front but yeah he
just disappeared and then the dude I was
really tired
but I didn't
would be appropriate you know this is
the problem if you're in a row of three
people
and there's an uh free seats and there's
a seat between you
you know you feel like you wanna kinda
use that second seat right but there's
like the cities between you and another
person so
you like taking it for yourself
feels kind of like like who do you think
you are like you assume the suit is now
yours let's at least [\h__\h] share what
you would usually do is I don't lay down
on it uh if there's like if this if this
is a free see-through row I don't lay
down on it sometimes I like um let me
it's paid time [\h__\h] let me paint
I'm gonna probably explain a few things
on paint today
[Music]
wonderful
ah the wrong button there we go
German paint
[Music]
where are we where how where is the
ending here it ends
[Music]
we don't even need this big dope I think
wait
[Music]
let me cut it uh
where is it
here
[Music]
I'm so surprised I never lost this
tablet pen before I should have oh sure
trying to move the mic Okay so
Saint
Saint okay what I don't know why this
one is bigger but they get thick and
bigger bigger and bigger
okay uh what I would
sometimes do in this situation because
like I like to like kind of like
make myself small because I can't really
make myself like really big right in
such a tiny seat so I'll make myself
small instead because I like that it's
kind of comfy so I put my legs up
and just a little bit because if I
couldn't do it if there was a person
here I can't do this really
but since there's no person here I used
the opportunity to sit like this and
then just um you know
okay
enjoy the little extra space without
taking it all up this is what I would
like to do or or slash and I put like my
bag here
I guess but that's the most I will use I
will make of this princess
very ladylike
hiding my crotch out of fear no
no men spreading oh God I
I have many experiences with sitting
next to a guy uh and and them like men
spreading the hell out of their manly
Hood next to me but hey
and I I tried to I tried to understand I
tried to ignore it okay but sometimes I
wonder why what would you what would you
do if I was as wide and tall and big as
you huh you're lucky that you're sitting
to a small person like me okay you're
lucky that I only take up like this much
space sometimes sometimes though I also
like to take up a bit more space
whatever whatever you're lucky you're
next to me
okay
what extraordinate
[Music]
okay so however I couldn't do this I
couldn't do it this time the dude the
dude he he's he like he was weird
busy I like in my in the corner of my
eye I saw he was like constantly doing
something like he the moment the guy
left he froze his like bag here and then
he froze his laptop like here like kind
of uh angled uh and then he's like
click click like an important person he
was like kind of in like a suit-like
outfit too I'm not like oh wow what a
busy man okay but minutes three minutes
later he moves it around again and he
kept on throwing his things around and
and putting even more things on the seat
before I even put anything there yeah
and and he was just really busy like he
was looking around like he was kind of
anxious I don't know what was going on
yeah but then then eventually
he takes off his coat he takes his big
bag and he puts it here he puts his coat
over and then like a baby
he lays down
[Music]
like this you know you see what I'm
doing here
and with his hand his hand was like
under his under his head and he just
suddenly with so much so much like uh
energy he just
then suddenly laid down there and then I
look over and I'm like oh
okay
like his head he had like a really like
fluffy head like so much
[Music]
I'm like oh okay
I guess you're using this new seat that
we now have okay enjoy I guess not like
I wanted to it's okay it's okay I have
the window seats
um I feel like it's pretty easy to like
at least like lean on something on the
window seat so that's good I didn't Pat
him no
yeah I just I don't know it just it just
clings it yeah like look at the audacity
the other City to take and claim this
middle seat right
and then you know what happened then
eventually later lady comes by while
he's like doing this and asks anybody
wants to buy snacks and I'm like yeah
hear me um I like to buy a Coca-Cola
[Music]
and then I got it was something called I
feel like elephant bites or something
like that like it was like he's round
um pretzel crackers it just spoke to me
you know I looked at the menu and this
spoke to me with uh black and white
sesame seeds Sesame I think it was
Sesame it just looked good to me so I
buy I buy this you know out of the menu
that has quite a few options yeah yeah
just keep this in mind manual has quite
a few options and I choose specifically
this and then I I'm like you know I'm
I'm here
I have my table out I'm munching this
happily I feel quite happy about my
choices about my life choices then she's
gone right
he wakes up
he wakes up he puts out his table he
looks around anxiously he gets the lady
to come back he buys something
he buys the exact same thing
and I'm like
trendsetter that's such a trendsetter
[Music]
like damn I'm I'm such a [\h__\h] there's
nothing wrong with it but I just felt
weirdly proud of myself
yeah icon
no I know I I like I saw it and I'm like
and like really gave this smug smile I
don't think he saw it I'll have what she
said I wonder if he said that I didn't
hear it I didn't hear it clearly but I
just felt so proud and I I I I I I
didn't look at him directly but I looked
like I my my head I angled it towards
his Direction and I had this smug smile
kind of expecting a comment from him
like
like I don't know like thank you for
inspiring me like you have made my day I
I am looking forward to the trends that
you said it you know I just expected
something some kind
of comment
there's nothing and he just ate it as if
it was his idea
I just ate it and ignored this like
this situation
you don't understand me you you don't
get it guys you don't get it yeah
[Laughter]
um
it was my competition
you know he didn't even look like a guy
who would order a Coca-Cola and the
Elephant crackers
[Music]
honestly
yeah oh my God you're so right it's
because I'm watching too much Seinfeld
oh man yeah
marked it I feel
I feel I am
credited for because he was oh my God I
was enjoying those crackers but he was
like eating it like
three times as fast as me and he
finished it immediately
both his Coca-Cola and his snacks
what I'm saying is he enjoyed it so much
he should thank me
I don't know man
[Laughter]
is it too much to ask for some credit
I can't I can't it's a stand-up routine
hmm
Phoenix God complex no I'm saying
there's so much on the menu why would
you take the items exactly combination
of things that I took
it's obviously because you had taken
inspiration from me
and then he went back down to sleep in
that position and take up all the space
it's okay though I had all this kind of
content I was pretty happy that at least
I had a window seat
I love George Costanza
okay uh
uh
[Music]
how do I make new
ah there you go
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's see the menu it makes me nervous
oh man
[Music]
being able to Brave the same air as me
too
of course
ah okay that was my my very important
this was just this is It's been
30 minutes and this was just the
airplane ride
so
eventually
you guys don't get it
eventually we were done with the flight
uh we got off I was waiting for IMT who
was in the back of the plane and
um UK has changed you
know it's like this before
[Music]
Oh man
yeah he ruined my whole holiday I'm just
kidding
I would love to live in a Seinfeld
episode
foreign
[Music]
I'm happy he had a good sleep
um we landed at Gatwick Airport which is
I guess it looked like like judging by
the planes that were parked outside an
air an airport just made for cheap
airlines to land because they can't
afford uh or don't have space in
Heathrow yeah but it's not so far
actually from the city like
if you compare it to Narita in Japan
Narita is not even in Tokyo is like so
[\h__\h] far if I compare that I feel
like gatwick's closer to like London
than 90 days to Tokyo
I prefer Gap will go for Heathrow by far
oh wow okay see and it was really easy
to get from Gatwick Airport to the city
but we didn't look up anything
beforehand we like the whole time our
whole trip it was like so unplanned the
only thing we planned beforehand is the
reason why we booked this trip uh and
that was for the
oh yeah fames like straight in hell yeah
for for the Lord of the Rings thing um
it beats him so loud what okay let me
change it anyway
[Music]
okay
so
next we arrive and we're like okay okay
what do we do first of all we need a SIM
card right should we buy a SIM card
because like
back in the day oh it's [\h__\h] wobble
Beach
back in the day
uh before
before before England chose to brexit
the [\h__\h] out of here
um
[Music]
stupid
um we were able to just go there and
have internet now we do not have
internet it depends actually I looked it
up and it seems like depending on your
provider you may have
free internet still like for Austrian
providers maybe maybe I'm not sure but I
certainly didn't and my friend rmts
certainly didn't either
um unfortunately so we had to buy some
like I checked the the rates if you were
to roam without like some specific SIM
card and uh I I I don't know how to
calculate if that's a lot or not so
we just bought SIM cards we arrived and
there was like a like a YouTube what ah
and L here a vending machine for SIM
cards and it had two different uh
companies SIM cards I think one was
Leica that I'm sure UK people know the
other one I don't remember maybe you
guys remember we were first eyeing the
other one
um and we're like okay they have what
they have like
maybe 10
GB and then a 25
GB I think maybe something like that
um
free I'm not sure I'm not sure but then
Leica had uh
I think like 50 and 100 GB but the 100
should be was as expensive or cheap as
the other carriers 25 GB
and we were like why would we buy the
other one is there something like
something that we don't know like is
there something that makes it work to
get the other one
because like on the packaging judging by
the information on the packaging it
didn't seem like
there was any difference between them so
whatever we just bought this the 100 GB
one but of course we only uh
um
at the very last day I I used up like 7
GB in one day because I downloaded a lot
of things on my phone like videos but
besides that we only used together
sharing by having it on the whole day we
only used like maybe one GB per day
the 7gb was an exception
normally I I wouldn't use so much but I
just downloaded a few videos on my phone
because I was like whatever we have so
much GB left it's the last day it
doesn't matter
okay so uh yeah yeah I was surprised
that we got into the fames linked uh
train and it did have Wi-Fi because like
we couldn't I didn't have you know like
a little little pin to open up the hole
on the back of the phone to put the SIM
card in so I was like uh we first need
something maybe in the hotel or so but
until then like at the airport we could
use the airport Wi-Fi to find a route to
get to the hotel
um so we just saved the route and then
hoped that we would arrive eventually
but uh turns out the train had internet
too and I in hindsight I noticed so many
places that had Wi-Fi in London
so so many
okay
[Laughter]
so many things were so difficulty
pronounced and I would I would talk and
I would ask British people like where's
this what's this and they're like what
are you talking about I don't know what
you're talking about and then they say
something that I'm looking for and I
don't even hear like that they said the
thing that I'm trying to hear because it
sounds like something completely
different to me when they say it it was
quite rough my auntie she was also like
uh question one question we were both
like question my question mark a lot of
the time
[Music]
we were in the train we were looking at
the station names and nothing sounded
like it's written
nothing sounded like it was written at
all it was really confusing but
like how I would say it
was funny though it seems so
sophisticated but yeah we bought the SIM
card then we moved on like slowly slow
it was early in the morning and we knew
that we would have a hard time checking
in so early
um so we were just you know taking our
time and on this day
our plan was to in the evening
go to
I've been told it's not Newbury
[Music]
although I feel like that's obvious it
should be Newberry
I I think it wasn't Newberry
I pronounced a little bit different
it's it's pronounced a little bit
different I think I don't know anymore
yeah to the Watermill fear theater to
watch The Lord of the Rings oh
oh musical day musical opening day
hmm
new Brew Newbury oh yeah that sounds
kind of like how they said it oh
yeah we booked the opening day and
pretty good seats too when we were
booking it there were like so many seats
still available it was quite early I
think
um we could have gotten even better
seats but we went for something like you
know pretty decent but not the best of
the best like not front row we weren't
like in the third row I think
anyway yeah yeah oh my God oh my God I
have so much to tell you guys
not just my not the telepathy can I not
just telepathy it to you that would be
so much easier oh my God
no more mountain of super chats but
mountain of tangents this one yeah
um
for real like I was considering vlogging
it and then voiced it over
maybe next time I go on a short trip I
might do that
ah ah so okay
uh SIM card didn't use it yet because
didn't have the the pointy thing this
thin pointy thing
um we took train before that we bought
these snacks okay and water and we got
into the train
um get weak and
for that honestly Gatwick Airport holy
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] there's like a million uh
automated and non-automated uh uh uh uh
like immigration like passport check
thing is
and they're all manned to the
non-adomatic ones like it was like all
all there was so much and still
there were hundreds and hundreds and
hundreds and hundreds of people in that
Hall it was shocking like I didn't
expect Gatwick Airport to be so [\h__\h]
crowded it was insane yeah took us quite
a while to get out of there
but once we were out there it was fine
and then we went to the the tickets
buying place and uh it was really
crowded there too and the staff were
like like
you know there's there's all these like
ticket counters
next to each other
and and there were like people in front
of them buying the tickets
uh yeah it's like you know and then then
there's like a fence and it goes like
this is like a snake
and then there's a like a staff here
from the airport uh from the train
station and he's like okay go here or go
there and when when you don't
immediately move or when you're done
buying your ticket and you walk away or
you know uh it goes too slowly or or
when you're like I saw a group of people
and they didn't immediately proceed to
buying the ticket they all got so
[\h__\h] angry all right the step was
like don't the [\h__\h] just don't let
this buy the ticket move on faster
faster don't don't
even when they're just like there for
like one second and there was this
British light eh
who was like interesting uh she was in
front of us and she was like pushing a
trolling or something
and she was like kind of like slow not
this not not like super slow like a
grandma but she was a little bit slower
than you know others and and he's like
you know basically hurry the [\h__\h] up
just don't waste my time go faster and
she's like
don't [\h__\h] stress me
don't stress me out
that's what she said to him but she just
proceeded to walk really slowly and I
was like go girl she's actually like
telling him that I love that because
like they were unnecessarily stressful
about the situation
[Music]
if she said it in such a British accent
how it was amazing
I was it was inspiring but of course we
didn't want to anger anyone so we were
very quick to move around and do our
thing about the ticket uh was easy
pretty easy we went on the train uh it
was also pretty easy
uh and then we just chilled it was
comfortable
uh finally we get to the station
where we wanted to get off and we took
uh we took
a taxi didn't we
Taxi
I've taken a bus or so I think but we
just took a taxi uh
and then we went to the I feel like
there was something happening there that
I wanted to tell you but it's okay we
don't have to tell every [\h__\h] detail
um
[Music]
I think we just turned uh Uber we just
used Uber our finger
um
I hope you use the underground the two
the two the tube I don't think we use
the tube at all mostly we were using uh
buses all the time or we were walking
um
yeah all I noticed it was pretty cold
like damn but I was actually quite
thankful for it like I I knew I was be
gonna be colder than here in Austria a
little bit but not like ice cold
but I appreciated it because a little
break from the really hot hot hot summer
in Austria and in Japan was was like Wow
amazing I really appreciated it like it
never felt hot a single time except on
like the last day or two where I just
felt hot from being sick I think
yeah the weather was great honestly the
weather was great for me as a break from
the hot summer elsewhere but I did like
a a thought to myself like
eh
this is like my first time summering in
like kind of the north of Europe this is
your guys summer
then if
it's never hot over there
this is your summer
oh my God that's crazy maybe there's
some like exceptional days where it gets
really hot I suppose but oh my God
then I mean for me it was nice to have
that in the middle of a hot hot summer
but for you guys if you're there in that
area
oh that's a little bit oof but I guess
you guys are used to it yeah oh my God
I don't know if I should be feeling
sorry because no no would it be nice to
have it be a little bit harder I don't
know
I'm already exhausted from talking so
much
I'll try I'll try I'll try my best I
didn't bring tissues though and I wanna
I wanna blow my nose
pepper
[Music]
I got this Dragon advice moving did you
hear you're probably done here but I was
walking over to the toilet and I saw a
smoothie just lying and chilling and
being cute
[Music]
so of course I had to touch her ah she's
so cute
okay
[Music]
it's mostly gone mine like uh running
nose
it's walking now it's not running ah
anyway
um
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you I caught up to it
oh man
uh okay okay well we're the train we
arrived let me skip forward we arrive at
the hotel uh
we booked quite a fancy hotel
[Music]
we booked a pretty fancy hotel I don't
know if I should say it but I think I'm
gonna say it because we're gonna find
out through something else that I'm
gonna tell you eventually
um we booked the wow I mean if you if
you're in London you're gonna probably
know it because it's so [\h__\h] Central
uh my criteria was a place that has a
pool because I wanted to keep up my
swimming reps
and here's the thing uh rmt has a gold
membership
in Hilton Hotels the chain of Hilton
Hotels not only Hilton Hotels but
everything that comes with Hilton Hotels
um uh and she's she still had like a lot
of points she wanted to use them so she
said well you can go for something
fancier if you want and I'm like yeah
hell yeah
um we booked the wild off
we booked the [\h__\h] wild or which is
thank you uh I don't even know what the
area is uh that it's in in London but it
seems like a really really
cool Central Area
and I only have one experience with
staying in the wildlife before in Berlin
uh for a work trip before and I didn't
have to pay for it thankfully but I I
had it in really really fun memory
because it's gorgeous it was really I
got a huge room the bed was enough to
fit uh 10 people or like basically you
could fit all those whole life members
in swimsuits from the summer night music
video and have them pose
uh
[Music]
like death on your bed uh that's
basically how big the bed was
what the [\h__\h] was that empty
oh my god
um
uh or or yeah yeah so the huge huge bed
huge room bathroom was amazing and the
breakfast was insane incredible I felt
very welcome the staff was crazy nice
and they made me some yummy French toast
and this and that it was really nice so
I really really enjoyed the Berlin
Waldorf so I had it in good memory I
thought this would be the same
that's what I thought
I'm just gonna say it
for a hotel
that you pay
never under 100 bucks per night
if not 200 bucks per night
this was [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
me and RT we've stayed in many Hilton
hotels uh we we know how how hotels work
we we worked in hotels we know this and
that uh and Waldorf is out of the Hilton
Hotels like the top you know
uh this was so disappointing we were
laughing the whole time you know we're
like you know we know hotels so we know
we know how it should be or how it could
be we were just so amused by all the
things that were weird about this hotel
oh it was just amusing it was [\h__\h]
four days
uh if she wouldn't have used points it
would have been like 700
euroso Palms I'm not sure but a lot I
think Euros I don't know
but you
but he's really happy about when we
arrived
um
we arrived uh on the
[Music]
opposite side of the street so Waldorf
here and then here on the corner there's
like a crossing here
here's uh where the taxi led us out
and
it's been a long time last time I was in
UK it was in Winter before Holo
um here's a like a musical theater
building here
here's the Waldorf right next to it
we arrived and instantly I recognize
this place
I'm like all right crmc
it's daytime and last time we were here
I think it was nighttime only but this
looks so familiar to me is this not
where we watched Mamma Mia
on our England London trip many years
ago
and she's like oh I don't know I can't
remember that at all I'm like
this looks like it this looks like it
and I remember that over there at the
corner of the street there was a
restaurant where we had a really amazing
uh dinner before going to the Mamma Mia
musical
um I'm like did we honestly book
a hotel right next to this like venue
where we watched Mamma Mia
and it's a yes like I I I like still had
to do some research and be 100 sure but
yes my memory was right correct this was
the place so this rated really nostalgic
for me
quite nice quite happy yeah
we go to the Waldorf and we're like hi
uh while the hotel has a nice Bellman
Bellman on the ones that greet you at
the front door
um help you maybe with your car or with
your luggage
um very friendly uh
very friendly funny
strong accent a guy with a top hat
foreign
[Music]
nice nice English man yeah and he's like
welcome and I think it was like uh maybe
roughly around 1pm
check-in time is 3 P.M
like in most hotels
so he's like oh welcome where did you
come from you're like from Austria we
just arrived
um
we would like to check in and I already
had a feeling that you know our room
might not be ready but first of all this
is a wildlife so they should be you know
doing their best even more than in other
hotels uh I I am sure that even if the
room is not ready yet if we requested
they could prioritize it as I have done
this before when working in hotels tell
the housekeeping to get this one ready
next so that these people can check in
it's not that [\h__\h] difficult okay
because other hotels they they make it
very difficult I've noticed it like
recently every time I stayed in the
Japanese Hotel like a cheap uh typical
small hotel they did not give a flying
[\h__\h] about me requesting to have my
hotel room a little bit earlier it's not
it's Landscaping you know you're gonna
do a million rooms obviously some are
gonna be done before 3 P.M
you have to start somewhere so some are
going to be done earlier but they're
like no no there's no way you have to
come back after 4pm no not I mean like
maybe half an hour earlier they're like
No 3 P.M 4 P.M no 4 P.M I'm like uh
bye bye thanks
why it's not that difficult but whatever
okay whatever
so this Bellman
he was really nice but he's like are you
oh you want to check in well that's not
going to happen
uh check it so check-in is at 3 P.M so
what we can do is we can take your
luggage and you can leave it there and
you can come back later at 3 P.M okay
all right we're like
um
maybe we can try and he's like well you
can try but you're not gonna get a room
you know we have no rooms where you have
to come back later we can take your uh
luggage of course yeah please come back
at 3 P.M he was way he was way nicer way
Charming uh way more charming and I'm
portraying him right now have a hard
time to portray charmingness with this
accent
um yeah uh
we're like
[Music]
I want to give it a try like rmt would
have probably already like given up but
I was like I want to give it a try like
I am tired we have uh like somewhere to
go in the evening but we're really tired
from a flight we both didn't sleep much
we were very tired we want to take a nap
so we want our room if possible
so we go to the reception there was a
queue
okay reception uh there were like I
think two people checking in
there was like somebody checking in here
then there was someone here and we were
here
and there was someone here who was
interesting
[Music]
he's got a tie that's important
he's got a tie yes okay so this person
uh I think not important disappeared
fast this person he was angry
he was angry he was one of those people
who stayed in an expensive hotel because
they have the money and they think
they're important and they have special
rights and they have places to be
they're extra important they think
they're important they may be important
but especially the most important thing
is that they think they're important
I I didn't like these kind of people
when I worked at hotels
they think they're extra important
so it seems like he talked to the this
guy before who is just trying his best
yeah who also has a tie but that's
because it's their uniform
he's just trying his best you know and
you have to
um be very nice as a receptionist in a
Waldorf Hotel yeah so he he was here he
was asking for a room and he's like he
comes up to him once this person leaves
very angrily he's like what about my
room Mr Dunya and in my room are you
I've been I've been waiting yeah I'm
sitting here I'm waiting for my room
what's with my room and he's like yeah
we are trying okay let me check it's not
ready yet but we're gonna notify you
okay we're working on it we're working
on it we're trying our best here okay
um in 10 minutes we'll just give us 10
more minutes we'll try our best and he's
like I've been waiting for so long
a [\h__\h] male carrot so annoying okay
how annoying and me and RMC were looking
at each other we were like ah these kind
of these kind of people are the worst
like he's obviously trying his best you
know but this game was the impression
that maybe we're not gonna get a room
huh but we can at least ask for getting
it done soonish yeah but we're like oh
man
poor guy like we've been in this
position many times before poor guy yeah
this guy is being a cabin yes
eventually he is able to shake him off
the receptionist and we're next and
we're like oh dear this poor guy like oh
man
that was a really
annoying looking interaction
um
difficult customer difficult guest so we
go up and we're like hi um
we would like to check into
ah yeah if it if it's okay you know
so we're not expecting much at this
point he starts the check-in procedure
and somehow without trying too hard we
just get a room
we just get our room what I'm thinking
is like you know usually the process is
especially for members with uh guests
with like a special membership status
but generally possibly everybody they
assign the rooms
either the night before or in the
morning and possibly it was in the
morning yeah some staff will assign the
rooms early on
um and yeah some some rooms will just be
done earlier than others you know and
especially also because maybe he wasn't
he was asking maybe for a room type that
just needed more work while we were just
getting a standard room you know
possible that our room was just just
already done but that's not the the kind
of room that he would want you know so
we got a room we were surprised we were
happy we checked in and we immediately
closed the curtains turned off the light
and jumped into beds to try to take a
nap this was like before 3 P.M we
um had to leave like maybe at 5 00 PM or
so I don't know to get to Newbury
really far away uh
um
because it took two and a half hours and
the play was at starting at 8 30 I think
um
the Lord of the Rings Musical
[Music]
so we uh tried I was like so tired but I
couldn't sleep
rmt fell asleep but I just could not
sleep that was so tired I'm like [\h__\h] I
needed like I think we had like an hour
of nap time
an hour or two maybe even
um
yeah
but by the time the alarm went off I was
about to fall asleep
under pressure
I'm so sad I'm like I guess I'm [\h__\h]
guess I just gotta yeah try to stay
awake
so
yeah
we get to get ready we uh make our way
to station uh
[Music]
doesn't matter some fancy station though
I panicking
I know this name from The Bear right
Paddington Bear
yeah yeah yeah yeah
and we were kind of hungry but we were
kind of rushing to the train uh because
like we looked up a certain train that
we wanted to take we were rushing but we
wanted to get something really quickly
that's where we got the chicken nuggets
the 20 chicken nuggets that I posted on
Twitter uh
and we got we went to the station and we
bought a ticket but I we experienced
this every time buying a ticket in the
uh in the train stations is a bit
difficult for us maybe also for other
foreigners because it seems to always
give you free options
and two are for the same price well this
one is a bit more expensive
uh I forgot why maybe it was first class
I don't know but it's like only a few
bucks more expensive but these two are
the same price
[Music]
wait it's
how what does proud look like again
what what does pound look like again
[Music]
like this she looks like [\h__\h]
yeah it said peek and off peak but it
didn't like specify there was like like
here there was an info icon we click it
hoping that it would tell us you know
more about that but it didn't we didn't
know like which one to take we thought
it wouldn't matter so we just took the
off-peak one oh I think I think this one
was the yeah yeah this one was more
expensive like six bucks more expensive
because it was on Peak and this was off
peak and this was also off peak but kind
of like
station name was a little bit different
for some reason I don't know why we just
took the off-peak one because it was 30
bucks instead of 36 bucks I don't know
why like how could we have known that we
should have taken the on peak one
because we get on the train uh with our
chicken nuggets
we take a seat
and at some point the train announces
before taking off but like really really
shortly before taking up so not enough
time to buy a new ticket
uh announces that this train you cannot
use the off-page tickets and we're like
What Happens we're gonna get arrested or
what cause like now it's not enough time
to leave the train and buy a new one
because it's about to leave and we can't
afford being late uh using the next
train
uh what the [\h__\h] so we started looking
up things like
um
um what happens if you have an off-pick
ticket uh and it's like on Peak and do
you have to pay extra and it seems like
there's fines
um so only if the conductor is in a good
mood
he's just gonna make you charge uh chat
you less like just the six bucks maybe
but it seems that there's cases where
there's like bigger charges but how the
[\h__\h] are we supposed to know yeah yeah
I'm guessing they're barely enforced
because that's just me for people who
have no idea who here who are here kind
of for the first time and uh yeah you
can get a 100 quid fine yeah yeah or
more I don't know
um
how are we oh the thing is like I asked
the lady in front of the train like is
this but for different reasons because I
just wasn't sure if this was the right
train so I asked is this with this
ticket can I take this train she takes a
look at my ticket that says off peak and
she says yes but we were both focused on
the destination I think
she did say yes she could have noticed
to off-peak and tell me yo it's on Peak
I didn't though
yeah most people get away with it don't
even buy tickets yes so we were like
anxiously waiting in our seats I think
it was a long train ride but it was only
two stations and we were like anxiously
waiting waiting and waiting for
connected to show up and we were holding
the tickets in our hands and that was
just gonna be very honest I was gonna
say sorry we made a mistake can we like
pay up six pounds
you know because like we didn't know I'm
sorry
but until the first station he never
came and then after the first station
one conductor walks by our seats really
fast not even looking at the people in
the seats
and just asking anybody who newly joined
the Train on this station
and I'm like and RT's like don't say
anything
[Music]
but nobody in this train so far had
their tickets checked anyway since the
beginning of this train ride
that's nice and confusing and what
well we didn't it was just the truth we
didn't just join on the station so we
didn't say anything but
it was confusing so he walked by and
then that was it and we're like okay
we're going off the next station so this
should be fine
uh
[Music]
they didn't check you from London
because there were
tickets oh that's another thing
that's another thing uh like I noticed
explain this to me
um in the train that we took from
no two famous link
um there were the gates where you could
not go through without putting your
ticket through you had to go through the
gates but on this huge Paddington train
station
I noticed okay here here is train here
is train here is train here strain these
are the platforms
um here like a lot of shops and people
people people
so many people shops it's hard to see
but like we were like snaking through
and I saw like over over
here and maybe over here and maybe over
here I saw like the ticket Gates uh-huh
and it looked like you could only get
over here through the ticket kids but
here we didn't walk through if we had a
ticket but there wasn't any Gates that
we had to walk through so we didn't use
it we didn't see it like you know I
thought maybe it's only for specific
trains or so I don't know
so we didn't use the tickets
and then we arrived at the station that
we were gonna get off at and uh there
you had to put the tickets through it
seemed like
um
and rmt actually because she thought we
were done she threw the ticket into the
trash with other trash before we could
even leave the gates
and then we see that there's Gates and
she's like [\h__\h] I just threw my ticket
away and she's like
[Music]
she runs back to the trash and doesn't
doesn't get back though then goes back
to the staff and she's like
[Music]
but the thing is our bus connection is
leaving in two minutes
stop stop we're like panicking we're
like we're like screaming and and blah
blah blah to the um to the guy that was
standing there the staff guy and they're
like sorry
I'm like
[Music]
you know we're just like stressing out
and and he probably didn't really
understand what the [\h__\h] we want but he
just knew that we were um you know
panicking
um
yeah everyone just waiting
uh but he just let us through normally
uh and we ran to the bus which was
already standing there and was supposed
to leave now uh and we ran over
and we look inside the bus
and there's no one inside not even a
driver
[Music]
and I'm like
this is the Red Bus though look
look at my Google Maps and it's on here
it says the same thing this and that
this and that there's no one here okay I
guess we don't have to yeah he's just
chilling still probably until the very
last second I look over and he's walking
over from from the train station he's
walking over like really slowly chill
yeah you know
and I'm like okay yeah yeah he was using
a break so he goes into his bus uh he
opens the doors for us and we're walking
and we don't really know how this is
gonna work like even in Austria
depending on the city you're in buses uh
bus systems are kind of different from
depending on the city do you buy the
ticket outside can you buy a ticket
inside um do you buy the ticket for a
certain amount of stations or is there
no certain amount of stations like this
is always the same price for no matter
where you go Etc
so uh what we say
is we want to go to this place
um gosh we'll order it again
what was it again
I don't remember but we said it and I
tried my best to pronounce the pal I
think it would be pronounced
[Music]
yeah that's not so was it really
or did we just arrive in Newbury
no no no no we arrived in Newberry I
think the train station was Newberry and
we had to go even further with the bus I
think
I don't know I don't know but
um
it's like I'm gonna go here this bus
goes here right I need a ticket for this
and the bus driver is like where
I'm like this this bus goes there right
he's like
um
[Music]
I don't know
say it again and he's like
and I show it to him because maybe I'm
like not pronouncing it correct and then
he says it he's like like he sees it and
he says it and he's like yeah it kind of
like beats me
I'm like what's going on
but I'm like well look at this is this
bus right like this bus number with this
like destination rain he's like yeah I'm
like okay that should be it well
probably
I
think so
[Music]
so we get in we sit down a few more
passengers get in and then one single
uh
one single guy walks in and asks for the
same destination which is really a
destination like out of nowhere like
it's in the middle of nowhere and we
seem to be the only ones going there
uh so I'm like oh he must be going to
the musical as well and and uh he's not
from here either
uh
because I I heard the accent was not
from here
and he also asked are you going here and
again
the bus driver is kind of like being
mysterious about it I'm like what the
um but he gets onto
um and when he's walking past us I'm
like are you going to the Lord of the
Rings musical too he's like
oh yeah yeah I'm like oh oh where did
you come from he said he's from America
and I'm like
did you come here from America
for this it's like now then you know
other other plants uh this just so
happens to be at this time and I'm like
and we're like oh we came from Austria
today for this thing but we kind of
expected like at least a few people to
come like from like pretty far
destinations not just us
but we came for this okay so this
american guy doesn't count okay he
cannot be counted as you know coming the
furthest from the furthest away for this
okay cannot be counted so far we're
we're the most far
so we're I'm like checking the whole
time on Google Maps so that we don't
miss our station eventually we finally
reach the station by the way it was like
a really nice area like we looked at the
houses and the streets and there's like
a lot of green and the houses were cute
and so on it was a nice place to live I
think
um we arrived it's in the middle of
nowhere and after this follows like
15-20 minutes walk
um I say oh we're getting off but the
guy who confirmed to us that he's going
here for the Lord of the Rings musical
is like on his laptop focused on
something not seemingly wanting to get
off so I reminded him like Hey you have
to get off here we're going we're gonna
uh we have to go up here
he would have missed his stop
how long he would have been in the bus
if it wasn't for me the hero of all
people
um
[Music]
yeah yeah it was so nice of me right I
saved him
American roof
[Music]
um we walk we walk we walk
um me and rmt kind of in the front while
this American birth is like walking like
a duck behind us
um yeah he kind of dips out in the
middle he's like I gotta do something he
sits down in the middle of the grass
with his laptop and I'm like okay don't
get lost
don't get lost see you there I guess
yeah me and Auntie keep on going
um it was it was pretty there were so
many pretty houses but it was like so in
the middle of nowhere but more and more
closer we got to our destination and
right before we reach our destination
and the gates
I see this
[Music]
range range free children I see this
this was so mysterious looking to me
like those kind of ducks I've never seen
ducks like this before I didn't even
think there were ducks at first because
they were huge they don't look that huge
but they were huge okay
um
and they were so fluffy and fake and
chunky and they had a funny pattern I
wasn't sure what it was
now I know now I know yeah
Ducks apparently
um
and they were chilling right at the
entrance kind of greeting us you know I
was I was fascinated mirror aren't teen
wasn't just me she was also fascinated
by this these ducks we took like videos
and and pictures of them and then we
walked in and like up until this place
it was already magical
but I gotta say hell yeah
foreign
I understand why they are doing it here
and not in the middle of London because
I noticed like London has like a million
musical uh venues and everywhere there's
a different musical going on we're like
what the [\h__\h] is like is this like a
thing is London like like a musical City
it seems so they're doing a musical
everywhere
um so they could have done it in London
and make it way more accessible but they
chose this like really Countryside
random ass location which is kind of
like a barn
and when you arrive you see this
[Music]
oh my God
and this is just a small snippet of it
it's got like this little little
um slow running River with some brick uh
uh uh uh Bridges and they got lights
decorated everywhere
ah and then you have this outside garden
there's a lot of grain and flowers and
the Ducks
it's just so cute yeah it's a Watermill
yeah yeah it's about available oh my God
I don't know if it's actually working
though but yes it's so pretty it's like
oh we were like what the [\h__\h] this is so
pretty
fascinating and then uh oh yeah I took
another picture it was really pretty
right
I took so many pictures
[Music]
Hello
look isn't this so pretty
hi
so pretty this is one small of you you
know
[Music]
we left London immediately after
arriving just like everybody told me
leave what to do in London leave
I wanted to make a joke you know so many
people were telling me
um telling us to leave
and I was gonna say like
you guys that can that that might sound
a little bit racist guys be more careful
I know what you mean but you telling all
the foreigners who are coming to your
country to leave
now a little bit differently
but I understand I understand you're
saying that out of the lack of
um uh confidence I I explained it to rmt
though she was very confused guys why
you all tell us to leave
[Music]
um
xenophobic yeah
no no I gotta you guys are not confident
about London
um
still I mean it wasn't that bad
so we walk a little bit further and we
see the entrance and the little stall to
buy tickets
which was also really cute so let me
show that to you as well
[Music]
this is kind of the entrance
uh there's they put up this little stall
and where you can buy like a the the uh
not menu uh like what's whatever like uh
what's going on today kind of thing
about the Lord of the Rings Musical and
yeah
the thing is we booked some deal where
you can also dine at the restaurant uh
there's a restaurant with some uh food
and we would get a a main course and a
dessert a choice of some main courses
and desserts
yeah nice pictures thank you
see there's even
more who are here it's so cute so we
walk up there and there's too late
ladies sitting there and they're so
friendly like these people are all so
friendly and I was really excited to
tell them that we came all the way from
Austria so I tell them right away I'm
like we came all the way here from
Austria
but I thought that there would be more
people you know but there's there's like
what what
for this I'm like yeah I was so excited
excited
and they're like oh my god wow you
you're the from like the furthest way
like apparently no one else came from so
far away uh the American guy doesn't
count you know
yeah yeah
they were so happy that was so like
helpful and we were gonna ask you know
um how long it takes because there was
no official statement on the website of
how long it would take
um but it was important information for
us because we needed to get back to
London and this is so far away it took
us two and a half hours to get here
during the day now with the night time
of course there's not gonna be that many
connections either right
um so I expected it to be at most two
hours and if it was that it would have
been fine
they tell us
three hours
or even a bit long
it was three hours and 20 minutes or so
I think
I'm like what IMT is also like what [\h__\h]
we're [\h__\h] and they're like
where are you staying and we're like
we're staying alive that we have to go
back to London after this we didn't
expect it to be this long what the [\h__\h]
yeah I mean of course the slowest
material that's really long but
[Laughter]
[\h__\h]
uh [\h__\h] and we're like what the [\h__\h] are
we gonna do how are we gonna cut it back
do we have to stay here oh my god
um
um so
um they were really really eager to help
us the thing is like the bus that we
took which covered quite a distance uh
from Newberry the train station to here
and then even after that we had to walk
20 minutes it was quite a trip okay
um so the bus wouldn't be available
anymore
so we would have to get to Newberry
I don't know how the [\h__\h] like only the
only option is a taxi but we were
worried that if we like uber wouldn't
work we've been using Uber all the time
but Uber wouldn't work here I was pretty
sure so we would have to get a normal
taxi so they wrote down the taxi number
and
um I made a reservation for us uh for
the taxi at uh like 11 pm it would pick
us up at 11 PM
and then bring us to
uh even Newbury or Redding not reading
piwawa uh which is the the other stop
turns out we would have uh we should go
to reading because I think it was just
it just made more sense in terms of
connections and all that
but it would cost a bit more it was 65
pounds
but we had no other choice really
um
reading I'm sorry about that
oh you know where that is
reading is unfortunate why
live in Reading
Station food yeah it's a lounge station
yeah yeah
yeah so 65 pounds were like okay well at
least we share you know then it's not
that much but wow okay Scott and I at
least we'll at least we'll get home we
were thinking we might not even be able
to get home at night so yeah could have
been worse it could have been Swindon
what
what's that
uh but yeah okay we solved the problem
more or less so it was okay
um
we get into the restaurant we have our
food
[Music]
let me show you
we know the UK is known for I'm sorry
you guys don't have the best food
unfortunately but I mean
I mean okay it's enjoyable I was excited
to see what they have here in like such
a Countryside place must be like really
Countryside food
um
what wrong way
[Music]
turned it wrong still
ah what the hell
[Music]
look at this
I mean
doesn't I mean okay the veggies were
like in a separate like bowl and you had
to take them out yourself they were
there was like nothing they were just
boiled I think there was no sauce for
the veggies or they didn't look really
seasoned at all they didn't taste very
seasoned either so the veggies were
pretty meh
um potatoes were just simply boiled
unpeeled potatoes which is fine just you
know just gotta eat it with the sauce
from the the gravy from the meat yeah
it's fine it's fine the pie I know you
guys like pies very much don't you end
up in the pie I was wondering what was
in the pie but it was just the same
thing that you see on the outside of the
pie
um this is this is pork uh I think me
and rmt got the same thing actually this
this was pork with some like gravy-ish
sauce it was pretty good I think yeah
the meat was good the gravy was good
um the veggies were just really really
plain and I got
pie I
I had like something like this before I
think
it didn't really I didn't really enjoy
it much
but like the inside was fine the the
whole gravy stuff I was fine but the
dough the texture of the pie I don't
know if it's like always like this
but it wasn't like particularly
you know I don't know if it's supposed
to be more like an apple strudel kind of
kind of uh texture but it wasn't if it
was supposed to be that probably not
supposed to be that but I don't know it
was yeah it felt very very dry I don't
know
but maybe it's supposed to be that I
don't know I really don't know
um
was tea served with this well I ordered
tea but it wasn't like automatically
served no
you got a Soggy Bottom I think the
bottom looks kind of soggy and that was
good honestly
I couldn't finish it by the way it was
too much and we still had a dessert ah
it was uh I don't know it wasn't like
the best food but I just enjoyed it
because of the atmosphere and the fact
that we were in the middle of nowhere in
England
eating something like this it just felt
so British to me I enjoyed that
uh let me check the next photo for
Reflections because that might have some
but no it's probably fine
yeah the dessert I I was 100 sure if
they named it after uh Lord of the Rings
thing if it was a reference or if that's
just a name of a dessert that UK has
um this was called a fool
I thought it was like a reference to
Gandalf say fly you fools and all that
yeah look at this it's basically a lot
of like whipped cream stuff with some
chocolate and uh pears pears and crumble
crumble stuff and a big strawberry that
was really yummy I was like oh my God
British strawberries I need more of this
this is so good
um
yeah yeah it's called a fool
it is a British dessert it's actually
called a fool
Oh I thought it was a reference they
should have made like references to Lord
of the Rings for the menu but I think
they ran this restaurant even without
the musical so yeah but they could have
done like a special
menu in my opinion
[Music]
f-o-o-l it appears to be good
a little bit too much whipped cream I
was like
feeling a little bit sick but it was
good it's good what's good
cute so cute let me clean up a little
bit
ah so we had dinner and then um they
announced that it is time uh you can now
proceed to the Garden take a seat in the
garden because we're gonna start soon
this was gonna be as you know a three
hour thing with one break in between and
it starts outside and then you're moved
to the inside and it ends again in the
outside which is kind of cool because
like you know it's such a Charming like
atmosphere
turns out we were really the only ones
from like overseas basically who came
for this and
um a lot of people seem pretty local
there were people from all ages they
were like young kids uh like around six
seven years and then there were really
old people like 60 70 years hmm
and the amount of people wasn't that
crazy either it was like a comfortable
amount of people you know
uh so we walk out of the
I just want you guys to get a feeling
for this atmosphere and this place so we
walk out of the uh restaurant and we
walk over to the Garden it looks like
this
you see like there's like uh in these
stalls there's like benches placed and
then there's some more benches uh in
front of them and then there's a stage
around stage in the middle and you walk
over there you take a scene and it's
like a comfortable nice atmosphere
everybody's just like you know having a
good time a lot of people seem to have
come in groups uh on their families and
I've been wondering all the old the
really old people maybe they're like
related to the performers who knows get
a little bit closer in between the
Stalls you see the stage in the middle
and you see a banner in the very back on
kind of the right side of the stage it
says happy birthday
and there's lights in the trees and um
on the left side wasn't kind of like the
I guess the sound people
and they're like they're having beer and
stuff outside very comfortable yeah uh
we were just standing though we were too
kind of too shy to join other people on
there uh uh seats and tables because it
seemed like everybody was already
settled in we kind of took a long time
with dinner
um
yeah oh yeah I already deleted it but um
let me talk a little bit about this so
just like the movie or the book uh it
starts with Bill's birthday party and
that's where the musical starts too and
[Music]
oh my God
I got really emotional right in the
beginning because
the the actors they like eventually they
slowly they come in they join just like
one by one they meddle they just meddle
in between the people it doesn't like
suddenly start like bang here it's this
is the beginning no it slowly starts by
them just joining the birthday party
kind of like making it feel like we are
here for the birthday party weird part
of this world right now and they just
come in and talk to everybody
um and they're like you know in the mood
they're acting they're in character and
they're dressed up of course in
character
um and they're just like Hobbits and
they're doing Hobbits things and they're
having fun together with the actors and
also having fun with the uh with the
people who are there and talking to them
and some of them came in with
instruments and they were like
testing their instruments a little bit
and you know they were commenting about
things and then this and that you know
just getting comfortable getting settled
in giving it a slow start and giving us
immersion and we were like observing
everything
um like oh my God this must be that
character that might be this character
this one I don't know maybe just a
random a hobbit but oh my God they're so
they're so cute they're so hyped they're
so excited like ah maybe it's just
because it's the first day but they're
just having they're just all in a great
mood you know
and then they start and uh Bilbo comes
out Bilbo stands out so much because
Bibble is significantly other older than
all the other Hobbits that are there and
he really looks like Bibble I have to
say like a lot of the actors didn't
really look like their character which
is fine but Bilbo was so recognizable he
was old and and he was kid he had an
attitude
and he got this little these little
glasses and he sits down and
um on the stage and he's like you know
starting the thing
and it's really like it starts like this
whole musical it's um he uses up all of
the free books slash uh movies
[Music]
which
is why it's so long but at the same time
it should have been longer because at
some points it seemed rushed and yeah
yeah but overall I mean they tried their
best to keep it a reasonable length
right so
[Music]
yeah but they started with
them it's so cute and I just I got
teary-eyed right at the beginning
because it's just so
it's so cute and it felt like oh my God
this is like one of my favorite ever
movies uh brought to life and this is
like I'm I'm in this world right now
they're so cute
a lot of them are not like small a lot
of them were really tall
but you know what can you do
um so like visually it wasn't perfect
visually
um but they they did it with so much
love and heart and passion they were all
so into it and like I swear
they had like they had an ensemble and
the main cast
uh but even The Ensemble would act
sometimes uh and not only play on the
side uh they were like all dressed up
and
um
even the main actors the main like
lineup even they every one of them
played an instrument some of them played
some really crazy instruments some
played like five instruments like you
would see them always on a different
instrument there were so many
instruments everybody played in this one
these people are insanely talented it's
crazy yeah
[\h__\h] like holy [\h__\h] and I noticed later
once we got in
um like after the birthday party was
over they said okay let's go down
the ring and he disappears right they
recreated that too that was funny they
like made some smoke go up like boom and
he kind of like jumped down uh the back
of the stage
it was a bit funny like I mean obviously
you can't make him like disappear for
real so this is the most they can do
it was funny though
um
immersion yeah so everybody takes their
place inside the actual like theater
um no
this is I I wasn't allowed to take
pictures like at the play so this was
just before it started
I just wanted to give you an idea it was
cozy it was small our uh upper arms were
touching each other uh in our seats
um
yeah this is the indoor stage yeah most
of the things happened indoor most of it
just the beginning and the ending was
outdoor
um so it it felt really small I was like
how are you gonna do all these things
on here in this small stage uh
like on the left side
you could see like under there were some
seats up there right but uh behind the
fence but under there ex like
immediately under there where uh the the
the the the instruments some of the
instruments that you couldn't carry
around
um like drums and stuff uh they would
play those those there and in the middle
is where all the action happened
happened and a little bit like up the
the ladder
uh they would come from like behind the
ladder
um or sometimes from behind the audience
you know and the doors could open and
they
um played some like
video-ish things on top like on on the
whole back wall I guess and especially
on the back at the top part
um like they for example would use that
round shaped
uh like wooden thing for I think like
sauron's eye for example for the volcano
um sometimes they would use the shapes
that were already there sometimes they
would just ignore that and put it all
over
um they would add some props but not a
crazy amount of props onto the stage
and
yeah I mean it was it was like hmm
some things were
lacking and sometimes some things were
really good I want to talk about it all
so guys can we go through the whole free
movies really quickly
[Music]
you have to remind me of everything and
I'm gonna tell you how it went
and and with that probably the only
tangent I'll be telling in this whole
stream is this whole like first day
that's all I'll be telling you
[Music]
like a checklist so first thing was
Bilbo birthday party right
um
at this point we were not 100 sure yet I
think no
no we were introduced to all the hobbits
but not all the other characters
um Marion Pippins were really cute
Pippin uh pip been was a Pippin I think
Pippin was played by a girl but she was
so cute
perfect in her roles he was like she was
like really
scared all the time I'm excited and blah
blah really it's like a lot of
expressions in her face
um
yeah they were they were really really
really excited and yeah so cute
um
but she was a girl but she did really
well in her role I must say yeah
yeah yeah yeah
so so cute her facial expressions were
like the most
cutest thing ever hmm
yeah uh which might be a thing like oh
honestly it could have been it could
have worked really well as a girl too
like the whole Hobbit Team the main
Hobbit team that you know you
are around surrounded by in the books in
the movies you know the four Hobbits
they're all boys and honestly it could
have been a girl like why not
it would have been that unfitting that's
what I thought when I was watching her
play her role yeah
besides that nobody else I think
I think trade
trade new
by a different
gender I think
um I think they were all like you know
um
yeah
it was interesting though
very interesting I felt like Sam was uh
also very different
but also like was actually perfect for
his role Sam and Frodo honestly Frodo
Frodo wow the choice for Frodo like his
um he looks like the actor from How I
Met Your Mother
combined with the photo actor in my
opinion
but yes Sam I really like the Sam actor
uh Sam was gumsy but he was busy playing
instruments so much of the time like I
felt like
um they had to like like cut him out of
a lot of the Chit Chats because uh they
were like you they needed him for
certain instruments
yeah but no he was he was uh more there
in the second part of the play after the
break that that's when he was used more
I felt yeah
um
hmm
overall I wanna I wanna say that like
um the music they came up with was
really fitting and nice the only feeling
that was weird to me was when
um
not collateral uh what's the other chick
the one that marries
uh the the cool guy
forgetting all the names right now
iron yeah that's Arvin was really pretty
and had a strong singing voice but the
only thing that bothered me is that all
the songs that she would sing by her
style of singing and voice made it sound
like Disney musicals
and that just kind of kind of felt off
to me but it was only whatever she would
sing did column sing yes in character
and it was it was good it was good
um
[Music]
down
all the scenes just write them down in
the order and and I'll tell you how it
went so first we are in in the Bilbo
house and uh Bibble gives the ring right
to Frodo and then he's gone and first
like what the [\h__\h] and then uh Sam is
there and Gandalf was there kind of
arrives uh Gandalf was played by a
really old guy thankfully and
um sorry my arm team she was like after
Awards saying that she felt like Gandalf
was uh like forget forgetting his lines
sometimes it seems to her like he was
forgetting her lines but
um honestly
I feel like that was on purpose like no
he didn't really straight up forget his
lines but he just like stumbled a little
bit over his words and was like
babbling felt to me just like an old guy
and
it didn't feel wrong to me hmm it it did
feel authentic to me for gandalvia so
that was fine for me personally I think
kind of was fine Bill po Bilbo was 100
authentic kind of was maybe like gave me
only 90 percent Gandalf vibes
[\h__\h]
[Music]
um
how was Saruman Saruman was scary
uh properly scary
um a little bit Posh and kind of sassy
had a little bit of a sassy attitude
he was also a bald
very bold shiny bold but uh he he played
his role really well it was like a
little bit of a sassy sarabando
[Music]
okay if we're not gonna go through it uh
scene by scene because that's difficult
gonna take a while just just throw out
some scenes and I'm gonna tell you how
they went I want to talk especially
about the balcock scene
um
that was the most disappointing one
because of course it's like difficult to
portray that in such a small musical
theater
ah
but basically what they did they opened
up the back and then Through It came it
was overall really dark that darkened
the whole room quite a bit through it
came
[Music]
um
like
this big blanket people were underneath
you couldn't see it but they were like
pushing up with their hands
creating like ups and downs in the huge
stretchy blanket a black stretchy
blanket it was overall dark but they
played a little bit with the lights
um but
it was just like a really vague like
scary thing
and and Gandalf was standing in the back
on like a little bit I think I think it
was kind of elevated I may be mixing
something up
a nice way to go I don't know it was
kind of disappointing because like you
were expecting this this huge thing
but this is just like that's how it is
in the books really the rmt loves the
books but she was also disappointed it
was so vague it had no shape it was just
like a big ass blanket
and then he gets consumed by it
basically and it's gone I'm like okay
I guess that's yeah how you gotta do it
like it's difficult but it made me think
like me and rnt were discussing during
the break how are they gonna do the
spider it's not impossible to create a
spider right they can just make a huge
spider prop shouldn't be impossible I I
was hoping for it rmt already gave up
hope that she was like if this is how
they're gonna make the ballot they're
not gonna put any effort in the spider I
was so hopeful and also the trees the
ants
um I was curious how they were gonna do
that too this was just a spooky blanket
yeah
dialogues are meant to be made of smoke
and Flame
so sort of accurate oh
okay
all right then
blanket is 100 accurate hmm
anyway
uh that was that was that so it was a
bit
um
but it was okay they also like a lot of
the battles they they skipped some
battles and
um or shortened them and made them not
so important and uh not much battle like
one thing that I wasn't so happy with
was the Orcs they had a total of four
Orcs throughout the whole movie
um uh Musical and and they were wearing
kind of like gas masks
they were kind of dressed like in
hip-hoppy clothes
and wearing gas masks every other outfit
uh was fine in my opinion from the Alps
the outfits were nice from the hobbits
the outfits were nice
um Gimli and Legolas everybody was fine
in my opinion just the Orcs were like
what it was four Orcs in Hip Hop e dark
baggy clothes with a hoodie on and a gas
mask underneath
I was thinking could they really not
just make like a somewhat orky mask or
paint their faces green and I don't know
give them some orc ears and stuff yeah
they were like steampunk Orcs And
um yeah I don't know that was a bit meh
yeah
it was a bit strange yeah
uh in terms of other enemies though they
also had uh
what do you call them and the ones on
the horses
[Music]
that was basically
um they recreated the horse heads and it
was like
I can't remember so well yeah the ring
wrap Rave refs they they were kind of
good because they were scary and and the
the horses Horseheads where we created
quite well it was like skeleton
Horseheads
um and they were like hippity hoppity
across the stage and going like
looks pretty good as this is scary hmm
[\h__\h] my fruit I'm talking too much
[Music]
yeah the screams were good The Sounds
overall like I I really cannot
compliment praise enough the music and
the instruments uh the like what really
impressed me is they had no like
dude who is like directing everyone in
terms of music and I saw no one with a
sheet of music and they they were so
much so much music going on even when
they weren't singing you know they were
also creating background music and stuff
there was no they didn't look at Sheets
of music but they were all so like
synced up I didn't notice like any like
big mistakes or flaws in um the music I
only heard like a violin sounding a
little bit off sometimes
but besides that
yeah that was impressive they knew it
all by heart and they were so into it
like when the when the
um in the middle there would be actors
right and on the side there were some
Ensemble sometimes Sam who wasn't uh or
like any uh even when when for example
Arwin or Galadriel and so on were not in
the scene right now they would be on the
side playing instruments because
everybody you know had like their
expertise instruments and and they were
watching the play and each other while
uh playing their instruments because
they had to uh adjust it to what they
were doing right but I saw Their Faces
Sometimes I would focus on them rather
than what's going on in the middle of
the stage because they were so into it
when there was a sad scene they looked
sad when there was an intense scene they
looked intense when there was scary
scene I looked scared when there was a
happy scene they looked happy and
[Music]
yeah they were so into it um it was
really really good
um
everybody had great singing voices
especially like Galadriel and Arwen they
really showed it off
um
I don't know everybody had good singers
the moment when when when Gollum first
came out was really cool like he uh we
were sitting quiet in the front so it
took us a moment to notice
um there were two floors right Gollum
just appears hanging on the the fence
somewhere in the back uh of the like on
top of the fence of the upper seats
behind us and people were like laughing
and were like oh what's going on and we
look behind us and we see Golem hanging
up there uh uh just climbing over the
fences from the very back to the very
front there with that he made his way
onto the stage and a lot of the time he
would just be hanging down the ladders
um you know giving him a little bit of
like a
the when Salmon Frodo are on the
mountain and and the Golem is there too
you know the way they would give the
feeling of the elevation of a mountain
is like he would sometimes be up on the
ladder looking down to them you know
stuff like that
um yeah yeah
uh so yeah he was like constantly like
climbing onto something uh when he was
on the ground he wasn't fully Crouch I
would have wished he would fully Crouch
all the time he was just like kind of
bent down a lot of the time he was
pretty tall and he was bald uh he was
I've got him as and he was very muscular
and fit looking but you gotta be if you
look a musical actor you don't have to
be but like the way he acts like
climbing everywhere even his climbing
um
some of the poses he would take up up
there on the fences is like uh it gave
me like this um what's the word not
ballet but what do you call the like
people who are like good at climbing ah
correct yeah Acrobat
it's acrobat Vibe and I I could really
see it the way he would like like
stretch out his leg in the air and flex
it really acrobatic like this was a
really acrobatic Golem perfect actor for
this role as he's really good in
climbing and portraying emotions from
his body
um by you know showing off certain body
parts and this and that
um so he was not like insanely buff but
you could see that he's doing workout
um
but it still fits like he was a really
good Golem he was doing the voice very
well and he was doing like this like
schizophrenic acting really well
um
[Music]
they did they did act out the the biting
Frozen swinger often yeah
you couldn't see it clearly and
obviously Frodo didn't lose a finger but
it looked pretty good and ah the the
scene where you know um Gollum Falls
was also really good like they
um
[Music]
interesting because
um you want him to fall down a really
really really low
uh
deep deep
um
mounted right so you can't fall down
though because this you don't have much
space so what they did is you see this
uh stage
um there were like some people holding
him up
when
Gollum is like
in this position
and uh they they they hold him up and
they carry him around and it's like
you're watching from above because when
you sit here like you see his bald head
from front view right so
they're trying to create like a um
optical illusion
where they go this way so you see like
you know what I mean it's a perspective
thing
and that was that was pretty good I
liked how they played with the
perspective there yeah
um
and it was kind of slow and dramatic and
there was music going on dramatic music
yeah and they carry him around slowly a
little bit and eventually I think they
went behind the doors
and he's just gone one more cool thing
in terms of like
um I don't know how to say that in
English
and
um the way they did things
[Music]
method staging yeah staging
um you know the big battle they seemed
to have like I was confused because like
I'm like what's actually going on but
rmt knows everything by heart so she
confirmed that they kind of combined
like two or three big important uh Wars
battles
um the one where Gandalf shows up and is
the hero and suddenly he's white not
gray anymore
um that one they combined it with
something else
uh
yeah yeah so what they did was pretty
cool uh you see the stage
you see that like round thing there
right and the doors and all that
[Music]
um they're fighting down here
and and you know you want to give this
feeling that he appears really far on
top of the mountain right he appears up
here
[Music]
with his staff and there's not much you
can do up there but it was pretty like a
cool moment because he's there they
they're like oh [\h__\h] and he does some
fancy thing and he saves the day now
it's difficult
like retell everything it's been a
couple days already
[Music]
oh one thing that I was completely
missing for example was the King's
Daughter
uh who fought in the battle too right
she would she didn't exist
and rnt said they also combined two
other characters into one seemingly
how I did I don't think she meant the
daughter they combined her somehow but
to me she was practically non-existing
in the play
they didn't
um like mention her which I guess it
worked perfectly fine without having her
there it wasn't too important so nope
sorry the romance of Agra no oh they
were so Aaron and arrogant we're so
lovey-dovey oh when they kissed I screed
I squealed
that was cute
um collateral oh you know how I was
really scared of collateral in the movie
collateral was properly scary in the
Musical 2 and the scene where uh Frodo
offers the ring to her she she went kind
of insane yeah she acted out that part
really well
um she was really spooky they made her
really spooky yeah
that was really good
um oh yeah the spider the spider they
actually
actually it was so cool because they
darkened the whole room and then they
opened those doors in the middle and
[Music]
ooh
Louie red eyes in the distance
and
slowly it comes closer to go out of the
door and when it's like getting closer
to get out of the door you see the the
legs
showing up holding like the door is here
it's like you know squeezing fruit
really elegantly like um you didn't see
it well but there were definitely like
people holding like several people
controlling the legs because like each
leg moved pretty individually I don't
know how many legs spiders have eight
six there are plenty there were a lot of
legs yeah and there was a child like
six-year-old child or seven or so maybe
eight nine I don't know hard to tell uh
sitting like on the um lap of her father
kind of almost next to me and I was
wondering if she would be really scared
because that was actually pretty scary
eh I always ate okay
this was pretty scary this was really
good and it came out and it was like big
and fluffy and I I first I thought it
was kind of scary but the more you saw
of it the more I kind of thought it was
cute because the eyes were so cute
but that's just because I don't know you
know it was properly scary but it was
also cute you know
and they did so well oh
and it's it um it took Frodo it it
rolled Frodo up not really in like a
proper cocoon but he was like rolled up
on the ground and it did that and you
know then it [\h__\h] off it was a cute
spider really good it was huge it was
huge actually that was like the biggest
prop they had I think
thank you and the most uh
uh like effort
they put into a prop in my opinion
I really like the spider yeah
um I have the trees for the trees Mary
and Pippen they interacted a lot with
the trees and the whole you know slow
thing you can't make it like insanely
slow right because this musical has a
time limit but they did uh put like they
did they did put some effort into being
slow
and um they kind of made like green
green leaf projections all over the
stage
and they use the ladders like when when
you would want to show that Mary and
Pippen are climbing up the tree they
would like you know climb up the ladders
or they would be down here and they look
up to the ladder by looking to make it
look like they're looking at the ends
the ants were the only ones that didn't
have an actor that you could see like it
was just like this voice and the
projections
um but it was a good voice and it felt
very like big and oh
hmm
was Tom Bombadil and goldberry in this
version
I I want to say yes because
um wait who was Tom Bombadil again uh
I'm pretty sure yes because we talked
about it not being in the movie but it
was in the book and and he was indeed in
the musical
uh what was that again
[Music]
the Magic Man
yeah yeah I'm pretty sure
[Music]
like he was there he was he was there
there was somebody there that wasn't in
the in the uh movie for sure
that was really cool
um Albert was really
was real too
uh
um
Legolas
was
I wish they would have put a blonde wig
on him you know but they didn't use wigs
at all uh so that was a bit
disappointing for me
um personally
I wish I would have used some wigs
um but Legolas like his face structure
it did give me Legolas Vibes even though
they're very different from Legolands
but I felt like okay that could be an
elf
um
and and to be honest not enough Legolas
Gimli interactions and Legolas overall
was not that active in the musical like
he was also one of the people who seemed
to be used a lot for the instruments
um but he was he was yeah I would have
wished for more Gimli and like was
overall uh oh one more thing that was a
bit mad with like the weapons
um
like the staffs the staves were fine but
Gimli is
gimli's ax was Tiny and
I felt like they could have hired a
better prop maker because it looked like
it was like a really cheap
creation kind of plasticky
um like the phone was uneven I don't
know it was It was kind of meh
um a lot of the swords were like only
like less than half of the size than
they should honestly most of them were
at zero point 25
percent of the size they should be
[Laughter]
yeah like a little bit bigger would have
been nice for the weapons uh
uh yeah also
um
maybe this is just me because I I you
know I go to conventions I see the [\h__\h]
and that cosplayers can do if cosplayers
can do this stuff then I feel like music
a musical like this that is doing
several performances and has such a big
big big like book and uh a movie behind
it should put a little bit more into
[Music]
[Laughter]
a little bit more into the the prompts
um but what I saw was like Frodo you
know he he's got this um sting or
whatever uh the the sword that lights up
right when it should light up when
there's Orcs around
um it was [\h__\h] tiny uh which is okay
it was like a tiny dagger that's okay
that's okay but when he first shows it
off it didn't glow right and I thought
they might they could easily put LEDs in
there
like a few LEDs make it uh glow blue we
were waiting for that but it never glue
glow glue clothes
um they could have easily done that in
my opinion
um they missed out on not making a glow
because like they even said it like
there was a line where they said oh it's
glowing oh there's Orcs around
and they show and they look at the
dagger and it's just normal
but what I liked was um The Capes that
they got from the elves they are really
shiny and and pretty and silver those
were nice
um also they they you know they they had
all those items oh this is
because you know I'm a [\h__\h] a [\h__\h] um
pathetic fan I didn't read the books
because I'm a lazy [\h__\h]
um
so I didn't know that there was one more
item that the elves gave to them
for what reason did they not show it in
the movie I don't know but there's this
box right the box of Earth or whatever
the earth box
um
and they keep it until the end of the
movie oh they generally try to stay
closer to the to the books which I'm
sure you guys are happy about
um so at the end
they talk about you know we go back
outside we go back outside to the garden
and the cute thing is that all the
benches and tables are turned over and
the hobbits encourage us to together
with us the people
uh turn everything back around because
you know we're back in the Shire so we
wanna after they re wrecked Havoc or
whatever
um we want to build it back up right
which doesn't happen in the movies
because they go back home and
everything's fine everything's nice
untouched
I didn't know that it was actually like
[\h__\h] up
and and yeah there's a reconstruct
reconstruction going on that you as the
visitor are being involved in which is
again very cute
um
and everybody's just happy to be home
and we build it back up it doesn't take
much time and the play continues or that
was like literally part of the play uh
and and then that's where you know
they're like [\h__\h] um what are we gonna
do like this is this is uh like so much
of our grain is gone and then they bring
out the box we're like oh but we have
this don't we have this we can use this
right
and the cute thing is that at the end
[Music]
um the staff by the way was really
really really sweet they they looked for
us uh after the dinner to give us some
more advice about how we should go back
home and also after the play they found
us again and um they found like it felt
like they looked for us specifically to
give us this
it's a little package
uh of seeds
it's a little package of seeds and
they're like just spread it somewhere
and we were very wild with the shires
together
yeah and I'm like I'll take this it's
cute I will use it somewhere sometime
I'll keep it for now
it's so cute they gave this out to all
the people yeah
isn't that so cute
yeah so anything else important that I
should mention from the play any scenes
that you guys want to hear about my
throat is dying so I should take a break
soon I'm sorry guys I thought it took a
longer but
staff was really good don't take it the
wrong way but it was
um really emotional and uh yeah the last
fight a lot of the fights were as I said
kind of shortened and not as big as they
should be because there were only four
Orcs
um but they took him apart really well
uh it was really dramatic in the end
especially that last like
um time where the like sword goes
through him
um and yeah it was it was really good oh
my mommy is watching by the way oh maybe
I should give the seats to Mommy
she has big big guiding did they kneel
for the hobbits at the end I think so I
mean they definitely celebrated them uh
they also combined like at the end uh
the I feel like they kind of combined a
lot of the ending scenes like the
wedding and and and the goodbyes and
everything
um
but yeah uh
uh what was I gonna say
um
[Music]
I got four mirror yeah yeah he was
played by a good actor and and and he
did really well
he had really this Boromir vibe from the
beginning I I actually we didn't talk
about it but I liked um
um the scene where you know they're at
the elves place and and they
um gets Gimli and Legolas Etc on their
team and it's really it's really well
done Rivendell yes Rivendell uh where
they create the fellowship yeah it's
really like motivating
um
um I hope Saturn was really good too
really scary really intimidating
um the volcano too was nice at the end
because the projections they used and
the music was really dramatic and red
and wild and wow
um
yeah I don't know
um overall I would give it a
[Music]
um
difficult either eight or nine out of
ten
[Music]
wow you know some things felt really
rushed but you know it's it's hard to
not have it be rushed when you want to
squeeze so much content into one musical
um
ah the actors were great singing was
great the songs were great the
instruments were great
um some of the props a lot of the props
were meh
um but the like
um the way they used the stage was good
that the floor was turning by the way so
sometimes they would like turn the floor
and that added to a lot of the
performances and and in in in what's the
word ins in in
ah
um
they weighed the way they create a scene
yeah
immersion two I guess but that's not
what I meant um
so the rating and then would I say like
the thing is the problem is it's far
away from everywhere so if you're in the
UK I say it's worth it go there
if you're not in the UK
is it worth it going there for this in
particular I say if you live in Europe
then it's easy to get there relatively
easy relatively fast
so as a European yes if you combine it
with doing other things during your trip
like don't only go for this obviously
but go for this and then add some more
things then it will be worth it if
you're outside of Europe
[Music]
if you're already planning a England
trip then yes it's worth it but just
like coming from America or Japan or
whatever just for this
if you're like a huge Lord of the Rings
nerd like if Lord of the Rings is your
[\h__\h] life
yeah
yeah then I think you want to see it
uh yeah but um
I think you should combine it with
things
the guy the guy uh we did like share the
taxi in the end which made it a lot
cheaper for us so that was good yeah
I was good
I won't lie like we had good talks it
was a nice guy nice American guy like
uh I don't know just a really nice
American guy
he didn't make it he did yeah
we were all really grateful for like you
know being able to share the taxi ride
um
[Music]
it's a good motivation to start planning
a trip to the UK
and
I was surprised I thought this would
um like I mean I guess there's only a
certain amount of people that could be
there because it's a small barn but I
feel like I'm giving a huge promotion
right now so uh you're welcome but
please enjoy please go there check it
out um I don't know how long it's
running like maybe two months or so a
couple weeks for sure
um if you are in Europe or like the UK
please check it out it's
they really did a good job to immerse
you in their their world
and they put so much passion into it you
really can see they love what they're
doing
um I love it I love it yeah I would hope
that they play in the future maybe
overseas but I doubt it I don't know how
these things usually go
uh but yeah I'm in the South I'm tempted
please go please go and tell them uh the
Austrian Girl
inspired you to go
they don't know that I am a YouTuber I
didn't tell them anything they don't
know that I'm giving them this huge uh
advertisement
I'm in the Northwest four hours it
doesn't [\h__\h] matter in total it also
took us furthermore for more than four
hours it's easier for you go there go go
you're in the country then go there's no
excuse for you to not go
um they don't know I'm Kiana
I'm visiting next year if it's
successful now
I would hope they do like a rerun or so
yeah
wow I don't have anyone to drive me
there you can get down with trains and
buses that's how we got there
but make sure to like at the end it's
really late so you might have to take a
taxi or you stay close by in the area if
you find something
um I'm in further north it's five hours
doesn't [\h__\h] matter you have to go
there
certified Banger yeah you know SS
the thing is you know Lord of the Rings
fans
um
Maybe
I'm a pathetic fan but maybe I'm a
better fan because I even appreciated
[Music]
the Amazon thing
so
also appreciate the hell out of this but
quality wise this was better of course
I'm an adequate fan
ah so I would
want to bring the pot
shouldn't we be happy about anything
that comes out except the Golem game
um I told rmt about the Golem game she
didn't know about it but yeah
um yeah should be happy about anything
that comes out in relation to Lord of
the Rings and and this was just like
so cute because like there never was a
musical before I think at least not like
a officially permitted one that's what I
think this is
like not
it's definitely they definitely have
like the rights to do it hmm
yeah it's crazy how that ended up
I think I think I need a [\h__\h] break I
wanted to tell you about more uh you
know what guys I know I said I'm gonna
play GTA on the weekend but obviously
I'm kind of [\h__\h] so I think the coming
days
um will be a collection of uh that's not
streams I'll do another test Downstream
tomorrow we'll talk more about the UK
I'll do an advent stream on Monday we'll
talk more about the UK until I'm [\h__\h]
done and until I can talk for a long
amount of time again
I feel it's getting rough uh with my
throat it wasn't actually like in the
past few days honestly like the first
day on Tuesday Tuesday
uh it started early in the morning and
throughout the day I noticed my throat
got really Scratchy on the second day on
on the first night I had a lot of like
coughing fits but on the second day I
thought okay I'm gonna cough a lot but I
didn't I just uh
had some throat pain so I got like strep
Sills and some other stuff from the
pharmacy and just went through my day by
using those a lot and then at the end of
the day
um I think I already felt better in
terms of throat pain but that's when my
nose started running so the third day
was my me catching up to my nose all the
time
and I was like damn this is like going
in phases maybe I have covet because
like I feel like this was uh the same
thing before
for me it's always like I only have one
thing and then it goes on to the next
thing you never have all at once I feel
like
but I don't know
um I don't know if I had it
I'm sorry I don't know but after the
nose running uh on the last day I just
the last two days like this overall felt
kind of weak and all that
um
no uh
today honestly before my stream I felt
perfectly fine but talking so much and
entertaining you guys it's making me
feel a little bit weak again
uh yeah but overall I got sick and I
healed within four
or five days
I'm mostly fine so it's okay I'm also
gonna be perfectly fine for singing
um for 30 minutes I think I'll be fine
[Music]
I just need a little break before that
I'm gonna drink some tea I'm gonna eat
dinner maybe
I don't know what to do about the we
didn't even talk about because I was
gone we didn't even talk about Advent
uh New Gen in like I think for me it's 5
a.m or 4 a.m
right
well let's talk about Ian free real
quick wow I mean we're gonna talk
tomorrow again so I could tell you all
about what I think tomorrow
uh not much I can tell you now
[Music]
um
um I'm excited for them
uh I'm I there's maybe someone I'm most
excited for but
but I'm not gonna say who
ah oh but I did want to say one thing
um
yeah about the new burp in town
[Music]
um so before debut
uh I talked with management I talked
with narissa
uh and so basically
[Music]
is going to be in my temp
[Laughter]
um the thing is like there's currently
from management no plans to like add a
new member and it's not gonna be like
um every time there's a new bird there's
gonna be a new member because they agree
with me that that's that's not what we
want like currently the way it is now is
nice yeah like uh like uh like um yeah
she's my what do you mean my temp she
will uh work for free uh
she she's yeah an intern attempt an
intern
she'll be my intern if anything she's
very happy about that position
um she 100 understands the like issue
there it says listening right now
actually
and yeah um
why are you listening she just messaged
me on Discord yeah
um yeah the thing is you know if if we
always add
anytime a new burp joins it's just like
at some point gonna have like 15 members
and that's not what I want from holotoli
and that's not what management wants
either it seems like management is
really happy uh with or like the
director really happy with how Horror
Story is right now how it's very well
balanced another thing you have to
consider is if we put narissa like into
horotoli then it's free en members
that's kind of unbalanced too you know
free and members to Japan one ID it's
kind of unbalanced I like the five day
where they are now there is a grease uh
she's like you know perfectly fine with
it and I said though that you know maybe
in the far future like not saying never
but maybe sometime but not gonna like
immediately you know
have her be
part of the you the idol unit that is
for the Tony like surely we can like do
things together uh
[Music]
and as I said like kind of have her as
an intern hey
have her do some dirty work for me hey
[Music]
um
that's that's how I think it would be
the best for now and uh we all agree we
all think that is the the best way to do
to go around it uh yeah
gotta earn your feathers yes but also
not necessarily what we're trying to do
here like it's not like oh you have to
earn your place no there currently is no
place in holotori as as like a unit you
know because before holiday was kind of
just like a like a gathering of burbs
um that really like are uh friendly with
each other that like each other that go
along well but now it's a little bit
more than that now you have to consider
the fact that we're doing some
activities together that we have like
things planned out together and yeah
so you will see but yeah
um
we can't just just because some new burb
is in town now we can just like
immediately throw the girl in there
especially because like I mean it
doesn't even have Freddy yet obviously
and who knows when she gets pretty so
that's also something to take into
consideration
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah but I'm thinking like uh for
example let's say let's say horotori
does something or I just do something in
Minecraft for example
and there's something I don't want to do
so I'm gonna say narissa
dear unpaid intern
um I got some work for you that you
can't turn down because you're my burp
kohai
I got some work for you
[Laughter]
my part-timer no it's more like an
intern yeah
[Music]
for me thank you
yes yes yes yes
power harassment yeah
um
I want diamonds
I want diamonds at least
for never right not yet hmm
[Music]
yeah so that's that uh that's all I will
say about them for not because they
haven't debuted yet none of them so yeah
but I wonder if I should I don't know if
I'll be awake for it I might just wants
to Archive
was it four or five am for me
I feel like I don't want to miss out on
the hype so I wanna be awake for it
I'll be awake at 1am for the karaoke
but I don't think I can stay up until
five so I think I'll I'll even wake up
for it and then go back to sleep
or I'll
no I will of course go back or I'll
um
just watch it when I wake up
[Music]
sound European pain [\h__\h]
the pain of being European
um yeah I need to get full sleep anyway
to heal that tall
yeah
but you guys please watch all the debuts
are finally getting our sweet sweet
third generation which took so [\h__\h]
long but they're finally here they're
really edgy the designs are really cool
like damn damn their designs are so good
I'm personally like artist wise and art
style wise
uh I'm like the most excited about was
it
you'll be right
yeah cause her artist is kayapada said
I [\h__\h] love Kiana said oh my God
[Music]
just by default she's so hot
when I do
[Music]
that's so hot
yeah
but also like nerissa as a bird like her
burp design is so dark and edgy and and
we were like writing is saying to each
other that you know my new outfit kind
of visually matches well with her so
um you know if you ever stream together
I Gotta Wear this outfit so that we
visually match well
yeah she's so edgy though like she would
be like those like visually most edgy
one if she were to stand in line with
holotoli
yeah mine is the bright hair but color
wise like black and blue you know
matches so well actually
yeah
hey coordinating outfits already yeah
oh I do not know about the collab then I
mean
as far as I know for now it's default
but who knows there's always a chance
they'll change it
depending I think they'll just do it
while watching the situation and decide
judging the situation
uh
honestly it could be anything
[Music]
do it the classic japanese way you know
where Ian we don't have to do it that
way
[Music]
especially like ever since Miss debuted
uh lots of things have changed in terms
of I mean you know Jen my soul there
chenma hasn't changed except I mean I
mean she's definitely
her position changed a little bit but
um I feel like a lot of the non-managers
I mean we got a lot of new managers
oh but like you know a lot of managers
change you know there's like a lot of
new people Indiana's growing and such is
like also changing the way we do things
a little bit
uh things are you know improving and
just a little bit different these days
so we can do things differently
yeah I never like said it but there's
there's been a lot of internal changes
yeah
[Music]
um
in a good way yeah I think like mostly
should be in a good way
I mean look at
look look at them
[Music]
how much stuff uh that management got
going for them like you know all those
trailers animated trips several animated
trailers
really cool stuff
how about the twins oh [\h__\h] genius of
course
like yeah that's my reaction when I
first saw uh it was uh twins who were
gonna join us I'm like yeah [\h__\h]
genius
yeah yeah genius genius
all right so they're always gonna like
have someone to bounce off of
compared to like swimming alone
you always have someone to bounce off of
and you can like always be energetic
there's there can always be someone like
commenting on what you do and there's
never Quiet Moments
um
yeah you always have a partner
I mean then in exchange maybe there's
not so much intimate moments I don't
know who knows but I feel like it's it's
just a smart way to do things
and let's say one of them doesn't
feel like streaming or can't stream
then the other one can pick up and you
know
so it's genius like
[Music]
it's gonna be very interesting yeah I'm
curious to see how it goes oh
but I think it's gonna go really well
[Music]
but I'm not gonna say anymore
[Laughter]
unless animals
[Music]
I I've I've uh actually the first time I
talked to them was actually pretty like
recently
um and since then
uh the one I talked to the most was
Marissa uh and uh I think second most
the twins I didn't talk so much yet due
to time issues and so on uh time zone
issues and all that with the other two
uh so I I have yet to really make myself
an image of them to be honest
um
[Music]
yeah I haven't I haven't talked oh no I
was in Japan guys
no there is that it's just like you
can't judge by what I'm saying where
they are you can't judge it um
they might just be like awake at any
time
who knows and that was like in Japan
recently yeah there's no leak no
literally no leak shop
no like I'm not not flaking [\h__\h] but I'm
just saying I didn't like get to talk to
them much so you know I I it's like with
counsel my problem was I just
I feel like for the longest time I
couldn't Bond much with the council
because yeah time zones really
um
that I really felt that very strongly
so I
I was hoping that for the third gen this
won't happen I've been
to keep up with them but um I've been so
busy I've been in Japan and I'm in
London
yeah I feel like I'm again missing out a
little bit on interactions to be honest
with you
them
yeah I feel like I'm behind
on interactions especially as I said
with shiori and Bijou I have like no
idea
what kind of girls they are really
I have no idea I only like I mean you
know because like the others like often
would be in voice chat and I'm uh I I
talked a little bit
like chat messages like replying to like
technical
problems with advice and stuff like that
but that's it that's about it
[Music]
now I'm back yeah I'm late I'm starting
late but I'm back now I I want to
interact please I want to get to know
them uh I want to learn about them
um
it's perfect because
in a couple hours so
[Music]
right I'm seven hours I think
let me know you
and then Debbie first ah sure but like
I'm I'm behind the other girls talk
plenty with them already I think not
everybody but
don't intimidate them too much now
[Music]
like so
um because of my time zones I don't want
to be so like a like a no what's the
word
on like distant whatever
like I was with
um isolated too yeah like I was with
Council
like now it's better like there's enough
time has passed enough collabs have
passed that I know Council well enough
yeah but for the longest time
uh me and Council we didn't get like a
start we didn't get any
interactions right
[Music]
man man
yeah I felt kind of regretful about that
ain't no start hey don't start
you had a great bakelip yeah yeah
I I got the bake collab early but still
Past after that like
no no interactions really
[Music]
ah
oh
[\h__\h]
I was just sending private messages
okay I have to stop somewhere uh so
let's stop it here that was basically oh
oh so we we we we we uh hopped into the
taxi we drove back we arrived in London
very [\h__\h] late uh and then had the
best sleep ever after a really
exhausting travel day
um
talking more and more about you know
what we thought about the musical and
this and that
one stream for one tangent can you guys
[\h__\h] believe it for one day
[Music]
sorry guys
for the musical I want to I want that
you guys know how it was because I think
there's many potential candidates in the
chat who would want to see it too
[Music]
and I want to advertise it you gotta go
there and check out the musical
because it's time Limited
please go and watch it
I sold it to you
I wish you guys could have seen it with
me
together
[Music]
it was so cute
I'm glad I was there on opening night
yeah I'm gonna drink some tea now and
and [\h__\h] off
um I'll tell you more tomorrow let's do
another short stream tomorrow uh around
the same time and on a Monday I'll do an
early one because
of reasons
I have plans in the evening
um
Monday that's all for sea people I guess
yeah
Let's uh have fun guys with Ian free
debuts very exciting uh let's freaking
support [\h__\h] out of them let's get some
hype going uh I'll see you though in
three hours for a little karaoke
I want you guys to send me
recommendations on my tweet that I am
about to write after the stream ends
I'll I'll write a tweet
to announce the stream and you guys can
reply with songs that you want to hear
that are summer summer-ish summer Vibes
please not for blood
it's unarchived mine is on archived
because I want to sing English songs
um
yo
yo yo yo
[Music]
not spoolie is that summer
[\h__\h] I need I need a break from talking
okay guys
in uh thank you for listening to my
stupid dance that are too detailed that
no one gives a [\h__\h] but I wanna talk
about it anyway
um yeah more about UK
tomorrow if you want to know I'll try to
talk I'll try to squeeze at least two
days of stories into tomorrow's stats
[Music]
bye bye cheerio
bye
bye-bye
[Music]
um
see you in the Shire
Cheerios Frosted Flakes
[Music]
thank you
okay okay
unfortunately that was not part of the
Musical
oh
[Music]
well then I'm not going no
no
they made their own songs yeah
[Music]
experience ruined
boom boom
foreign