foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
foreign foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
this is
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
key
Daddy
[Music]
okay
hello
[Music]
Kitty
I didn't burp that was the sound of me
drinking water a little bit too
intensively
[Music]
oh
hello
hello it feels like
it feels like
and it feels like I didn't see you guys
for a while which is not true it's just
we haven't had a one-on-one uh not
one-on-one one on chat stream for a
while
um the last things were collabs and uh
two collabs and then before that a day
off so
it feels like I haven't seen you guys in
a while one on chat hello
[Music]
it feels like Hisashi booty oh and um
some things happened in between so maybe
we can talk about it oh
hello collabs are fun to watch as well
yes
stream orange
yes there's a new
song cover collab we've never
on her Channel
um if you missed it then why why is
YouTube not notifying you because I also
even put up a community post to notify
everybody about it even the non-twitter
people
um but I think it's a really really
um
pretty song and our voices together also
sound so pretty
um so I want you guys to listen to it I
have a in my head the whole time right
now
and it's occupying my brain my
um brain is filled with the Melodies
um
I was asleep for the release listen to
it at least 10 times thank you
yeah yeah lives rent free in my brain um
Nana likes wait why you guys are
likes you a lot right why are you asking
that of course I mean I hope so
yeah um it was her idea to cover that
song
um but I was of course immediately in
um because I I really liked um the
Toradora openings and endings as well
um yeah and of course obviously odenji
orange is a perfect name of a song for
yeah us to sing uh it's just very very
obvious
yeah I love vanilla salt too
uh but I think I like especially now
that I I sang it
um spent some time learning the song and
all that and recording it
um am I even like odenji more than
vanilla salt now
because uh now I have more connections
with it
um
[Music]
is not salty enough oh I am I am salty
enough sometimes I have my salty moments
well um yeah let's talk about it a bit
more later after we get into the game
perhaps but I want to get started
because
um my hope is to finish this game
uh within today what did it say again
three hours in length
says Google uh so for kiwabo that's
maybe five hours
I'm hoping to finish it today
um I know polo one is shorted in Portal
2.
was it the other way around
I think Portland one is shorter I don't
think so what is it yeah I think so
um
yeah puzzle show puzzle Cho is back
today
um I know this is a Legendary game I've
never played it
um I kind of know that it's like first
person and you work with portals and
with the portals you solve some puzzles
or whatever and then there's a lot of
funny memes or so coming from this game
the only one I really know is the cake
is a lie that's the only thing I really
know
um or maybe there are other things I
know but I didn't know it comes from the
game
yeah super liminal I guess would be
um
comparable I feel like I did
not well it's super liminal but also not
terribly horribly bad
um it's just I don't really have that
much experience with these kind of big
brain games so
um I need some time to like sometimes
I'll overthink things and sometimes I
don't think too far
um so sometimes I I think too simple
sometimes I think too complicated
um and it's always always uh the wrong
thing in the in the wrong situation yes
um so
let's see let's see uh how difficult
this one gets I'm looking forward to it
uh yeah let's get into it uh
[Music]
um
I I hope I can do well and not embarrass
myself too much now let me uh
I'm gonna take a look at something
hmm
I mean
[Music]
oh yeah you like the thumbnail isn't it
adorable one sec I need to do something
[Music]
um
oh yeah sorry
[Music]
um
an issue
with something
but it's uh not important for you guys
at least at least not really
um
the song what what song what song
no no no it's not a song no no no
something something behind the scenes
thing
don't mind me oh I'm okay
let's uh get into it
oh
chapter one why is what is this weird
old looking interface I know the game is
a little bit old but the graphics look
great but this interface looks like
weird like what is this Windows looking
interface this this looks so weird what
is this font huh what is this button
it's like Windows is asking me something
I'm roasting it but what what okay okay
you guys aren't defending it okay
[Music]
oh it might be loud
I know the song
the opinion it's notifications on
reminds me of sunshine Super Mario
Sunshine oh hello oh what a
ugly toilet one second I think this
might be too loud maybe I need to lower
the volume a little bit
Papa
okay I won't let portal a little bit
let's see how this goes up and again
welcome to the Aperture Science computer
Aid admission Center we hope your brief
detention and the relaxation
and we are now ready to begin the test
proper before we start however keep in
mind that also fun and learning on the
primary goals of all Enrichment Center
activities serious injuries may occur
for your own safety and the safety of
others please refrain from me
happening
in three two what was why is it moving
okay
I am robot
sorry that was really loud my robot's
voice is always so loud subtitles
subtitles how do I turn on subtitles
options
video
uh audio
uh where is it
captions
close subtitles dialogue only
do I need to I don't even need to reset
right okay apply did it apply is okay
applying is that okay
should be fun that was actually so loud
I think uh
more quiet yes yes okay for sure okay
let's go oh it's
why do I stand like like some kind of uh
animal like what is that stance why am I
on my tippy toes
oh is that like shoes
am I like why can't I see my legs
where where's my body I don't have a
body
ah those are like
she doesn't really use them the right
way though
[Music]
stance is so weird but okay it's like
those bowling bowling shoes ah that
prevent foul damage oh and what happened
to the cup though what does it say
what is this I want to read that I can't
my screen is too small I can't read it
well this is my bed I like the bid it
looks like a cocoon
cocoon like a butterfly cocoon and here
I am the butterfly
okay so this is uh I see two portals
uh nice we're gonna work with that
where's can I make portals where are my
portals
hello hold on
e to pick up an object okay yeah it's
killed by I've seen this Cube before
okay okay okay so there's a button so
we're gonna put it on the button
chamberluck after completing each test
the voice is breaking up this Aperture
Science material emancipation grip will
vaporize any unauthorized equipment that
passes through it for instance the
Aperture Science weighted storage Cube
okay
okay first mission done I'm so smart
[Music]
where are we going elevator
aperture Laboratories
uh what are we even doing here
this looks like some some logo some
companies logo
besides the aperture Laboratories
yeah other subs too small
Subs are smaller than chat room I can't
change the size can I
ah
what is going on what is going on
wait I need to check something again
it's bothering me
where is
what is it what it what
what
[Music]
um
[\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
why is it YouTube chat so [\h__\h] uh
useless
hyper chat my beloved
uh
and I want to see what's
happening
true
I can't see okay ah there it is
what is this
uh
there's something that's bothering me
since the
collab yes today
the what the [\h__\h]
foreign
I don't get it why
I don't I
I don't
oh I didn't mean you guys I meant the
[\h__\h] it keeps on
it keeps on freezing it's really hard to
go through the chat but
um
um I have already brought it up with my
manager just so you know uh
but
I don't
know no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
what that no what is happening
one second one second please
I'm trying to gather evidence
what the [\h__\h] are 12 hour timeouts
foreign
no
no no
no I hmm
let me fix this
I'm sorry for everybody who already got
bunked
but what the [\h__\h]
oh
um what what rain rain too slow what was
I gonna do are you all right
sure
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
what
it's
this is really confusing
[Music]
there we go
um
okay
I did something that had to be done for
the moment
because I saw no other way
Aperture Science heavy duty
what
explosions
uh okay so we go through the portal we
how do you pick it up again
uh
what's the button for picking up again
[\h__\h]
I was too occupied Mouse click is not it
jump is in Bank thank you
where's my portal
oh
what is it close in front of me
explain that to me is it a Time limited
okay but wait okay
wait another changing
no wait that's the room I got it from
now I'm so confused
yes
oh it's so noisy bunk all right all
right
now wait wait
[Laughter]
please move quickly but it took me a
while
exposure to the button are not part of
this test effective prolonged exposure
to the button
what does that mean I don't understand
the thing of word
wait that's not what where do I go here
ah it open up all right
check mark
we did it
yeah
my brain is melting it's been melted
from the beginning I'm like one of those
new emojis that you can only use on the
PC right now did you see it I used them
on Twitter if you look at uh that tweet
from from your phone then it will be
just a question mark But if you look at
it from the PC you'll see the new emotes
it's not part of any test protocol but
it is an unintended side effect of the
Aperture Science material emancipation
grip which may in semi-refaces
emancipate Dental fillings crowns tooth
enamel and tea
oh [\h__\h] I thought my dentist Arc was
over I
have to go to the dentist anymore
I've been to the dentist
a couple times recently to end my
sentence what the [\h__\h]
open
oh
oh [\h__\h]
my portal all right all right all right
all right okay you took your sweet damn
damn sweet time which tweet uh I used it
in two two different tweets
uh one rabbit recently what are we doing
here
I was making poor oh my God
with it you can create your own release
what is the operational end of the
device
the inside of my gun liquid even
partially most importantly under no
circumstances
well that's very helpful thank you for
nothing
to ensure the safe performance
I do not allow you to look at me
that's Santa that is a clipper go away
all right then what are we doing what
are we doing am I done oh really that
was it I didn't do anything
I just picked up a gun
laughs
[Music]
let's speed around this game what I
thought I can make portals anywhere
I guess okay now I'm not in the elevator
okay okay
understandable have a nice day what is
the next riddle
I'm so ready please proceed to the
channel
mind the gap I always hear that in
Japanese trains
whoa is that lava
lava
where are we going
wait I can't go up anymore
but there's a camera
do not destroy a vital testing apparatus
[\h__\h] then I am did she say that because
I'm killing the cameras
I both make it was there too I only
killed one
oh it comes back
what
what now I have
um I split it I have now oh look at me I
now have
um I know I have three cameras I made I
made three cameras out of two cameras
smart
look at me it's like a mirror oh oh look
at the sexy posa
oh is that an orange suit
like I'm in prison
am I in prison
I'm not that uh
uncute I'm pretty what if I portal
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
what's happening
[Music]
forever
whoa It's So tripping what's happening
I'm gonna get sick oh God okay don't do
that anymore
oh that is that is confusing where are
we going
I just want to go over there what if I
put a portal there and you go through
here
like
who are you having tested me me what are
you testing me for for my cuteness I am
100 cute
so it's positive you don't need to test
me I'm positively cute yes
all right next up in the portal world
stupid camera all right oh we have a
kill oh no no no no no no
um
where does it come out oh here oh
and then e and oh why is it glitch like
that as part of a required test protocol
my mom will not monitor the next test
chamber why not be entirely on your own
good luck I'm not gonna be alone I have
my chat with me
I have you guys to help me even if they
don't help me
of you guys you help me with everything
because obviously everybody played
portal before
look I'm the only person who didn't play
portable for
um
no don't leave stay
where's the camera
huh
Drop It Like It's Hot
why is it not
also what about not monitoring me huh
there's a camera what is it why is it
not falling down
why isn't Autoport
are the point objects may be vital to
your success do not destroy testing
apparatus
do not destroy the testing operators
okay we have two buttons
we have a red portal there
a cube
uh-huh
a camera
oh that's what you meant
yeah but am I gonna get in trouble
am I gonna get in trouble oh it's orange
okay well whatever
[Music]
oh foreign
but I need one more oh yeah
okay wait uh I will go here and then I
go here and then I go here and then I
take this and then I put this up here
yes
what opened I just opened all right oh
no wait that's is that where I came from
because this is already on the floor
over there the orange check marks
as part of a required test protocol our
previous statement suggesting that we
would not monitor this chamber was an
outright fabrication why would you like
to Knob as part of a required test
protocol we will stop enhancing the
truth
it's true enhanced truth what is she
talking about what a weirdo soundline 60
FPS and 30. and now I'm in 60 but I feel
like I was 40 for a moment where are we
going on it
spoopy
okay
she's saying she's lying enhancing the
truth is lying wait yeah what a weird
way of saying it
why the [\h__\h] you're enhancing the true
why no [\h__\h] you don't answer your truth
that song you know that song why the
[\h__\h] lying
science
that looks like creme brulee
permanent disabilities such as
vaporization please be careful she's
speaking in riddles okay uh what What's
happened
it's playing tennis it's playing ping
pong
creme brulee
I'm red
oh no oh okay is one of many Enrichment
Center goals the Aperture Science High
Energy palette scene to the left of the
chamber can and it has caused permanent
disabilities such as vaporization creme
bruinely dangerous okay oh that's pretty
horses
vaporization I got vaporized but I don't
Vape
uh uh uh What uh
what me
what what what uh what what what ah
do you want me to
oh it goes through and okay
let's jump straight to Hometown here oh
yes I am wait what is that though
what is that it's the light I see the
light
oh wait sorry okay I got distracted I I
uh yes uh people of uh Australia are
very proud of me
by the way I had a very busy and long
day
um but currently I'm energetic so let's
hope
um I'm energetic until the end of the
game and don't get tired Midway through
let's hope for the best currently I'm
doing fine working devices are required
equipment is
I will go up there
oh Google
[Music]
there you go good
um
I understand everything I understand
everything I think uh except for how to
get up there
uh
no
I don't know
so these areas I can't go for a word
what okay okay that's what I wanted
that's what I wanted that's what I
wanted that's what I wanted I didn't
realize there was something here that I
could stand on okay I was looking for
the orange portal on there and what is
that a creme brulee
the creme brulee turned into an orange
portal a beautiful
oh
oh I have to jump
I'm bunny
I'm usagi
um
did you guys watch vitamins Empire's
stream today perhaps she had a
drunken Pond rock paper scissors
tournament stream again with some
announcements oh my God I'm Moving On My
Own
[Music]
unsatisfactory that is that doesn't
really sound very good to me
[Music]
oh the floor is lava another what are
these signs by the way are these hints
and don't get
oh but there's no crust so maybe it
means do get hit by the lightning ball
do put the lightning ball into this big
knee uh we do go underwater but don't
drink the water on this cake
see this one is
don't do this but this one doesn't say
don't do this the [\h__\h]
why is it not telling me to don't get
hit by the ball
what's up that's enhancing the truth
isn't it
all right what do we have uh
oh
what's up sorry just had to tell my
manager something ah Jen mom beloved Jen
my beloved all right we will figure this
out there is um some substance down
there that doesn't look so yummy looks
like they're toxic so I'm not going to
jump in that okay
uh where is this going oh okay so I
suppose First Steps put this here
Maybe
so it will come out of here
and is that on the same level no it's
not
uh oh maybe I don't know what uh
well first here
so it goes right there and it goes from
there and then maybe we make it go
through here
but then it just goes for here again
okay we created an endless loop
um
uh
wait wait think what what if I uh
what if I go oh over there no we
probably don't want to go there
[Music]
and the light is just we saw the light
before somewhere where I had to make a
portal
oh wait I ah okay so
um
uh
yes we have to wait for the right moment
because it switched some at some point
it switched directions why did I switch
directions
I mean it's good for me it's what I want
it but okay
I don't know what made it happen uh so I
don't 100 understand but I did it anyway
so how do I get over there uh
I'll wait first so here
wait how do I go there ah no first go
there
uh complicated thinking not so not so
complicated and then and then we go
oh God that looks so confusing
when when I look into that and I see it
from the bird's eye perspective that
that freaks me out
oh God oh God yeah that's so that's so
confusing I'm looking straight at it and
it's a bird's eye perspective
so much we're not jumping into that [\h__\h]
oh
show her and delicious orange
do I have to redo it no okay do I have
lives
Maybe
is it too close to normal or not close
ah this is perfect maybe okay
I can just go from the side
oh
she's here
please note that any appearance of
danger is merely a device to enhance
your testing experience
okay
all right I figured out something by the
way
um that some of you have experienced
some issues with getting timed out for
12 hours since the Monopoly Monopoly
yeah Monopoly collab and it happened
today too I was hoping it wouldn't
happen but I saw it happen that's what
bothered me it seems to be a bot
uh that we have the Enrichment Center
regrets to inform you that this next
test is impossible
nothing is impossible so what I did was
um I unmoded the Bots
um and it will be fixed I don't know
maybe it's
um maybe maybe there's a glitch in The
Matrix or something of the bot yeah
sorry about that I know there's some
people right now in the 12 hour
time out sorry about that
I'm sorry guys if you're uh if you are
if you were being um
timed out like that and cool man maybe
make a side account for the time being
[Music]
what are we doing
um
bring this
but these portals I can't bring it
through here right
yeah yeah okay okay
and I will make a new queue
if we were you we would quit now
who is way I thought you were just one
person but no more I'll figure it out
what does this say don't smash your head
with the cubes and
well it's telling me it falls down here
okay no one will blame you forgiving I'm
not giving up [\h__\h]
shut up waiting at this point
around
and desert you oh
oh yeah no oh yeah oh yeah I see you oh
tank oh
yeah and cake will be served immediately
okay so that's a lie you
remaining
[Music]
pessimism
that's okay though I already had cake
today and that was definitely not a lie
open up
um
[Music]
no no
no no no no giving up game is weird so
far and I'm I don't know what's
happening why are they talking to me
like this
one
momentum
I I'm trying to listen to
Stan
uh first of all bye
and that's what you deserve for staring
at me too much
mmm
can I jump no okay okay uh
can I jump through that
okay noise I can make a big jump oh
good to know I can jump pretty far
actually but this is this looks rather
impossible
uh
uh portal orange portal is there
uh we want to go there
so
think
[Music]
what if I make a poor little just fall
down here
what if oh there's hey wait is that a
hint
oh wait look at it like this
oh oh okay
what happens oh God
you appear to understand how a partial
affects forward momentum did I have like
a huge momentum from falling
oh I guess so because I was still
falling rather than jumping
interesting this one now
oh dear a lot of stairs I'm gonna get an
asthma attack wow they're going down is
fine why did I go down
all right where did I go now I can't
make a portal here I can't make a portal
here
where is this going oh it's probably
going where I want to go so what no
maybe higher can I do the same thing
again
do it right oh now I'll have more
momentum oh where did it go I'll have
more momentum because I was even higher
I was so far I'm doing pretty well don't
you think
don't you think guys I'm doing pretty
well so far
big brain
tutorial over really that was fast the
Enrichment Center promises to always
provide a safe testing environment the
dangerous
promises to always provide useful advice
for instance the floor here will kill
you how to avoid it oh thank you for
telling me the floor is lava is this
where is that where Dad come from comes
from
it's not really it's not really lava it
doesn't come from this does it
it's not really lava okay oh God oh God
oh God
is that a lot
of lava is older yeah it's just a kid's
game okay true I I didn't play that in
play that in elementary school
okay but this this floor is just a gooey
toxic [\h__\h] that lava I don't want to
fall in there what are we gonna do
and also
oh wait oh it switches it moves it moves
doesn't it does it yeah so you make a
portal there but I don't want to go
there you make a portal
on the other side does is that where I
want to go yeah okay okay okay there's a
button
how do I touch there we go okay do you
want to go there
uh I wait until it makes a portal here
and then I go through right
it's coming
I'm on my way
and now we're gonna do this but where
does it go
can I look at it
oh wait wait what
oh I think
it went still where I wanted it to go
was that on coincidence did I was I
lucky that the portal was at the right
spot at the right moment
it worked yeah yeah that was fast
because I guess it just switched from
here to over there
and when it was there it went over to
that side and activated what I wanted it
to activate no no
good timing yeah first try
low effort
uh-huh do I go through here again
uh no we want to go there
I'm coming yeah
wow wow wow wow I feel smart so far I
feel like I'm doing better than super
liminal
I think now
it's part of an optional test protocol
we are pleased to present an amusing
fact amusing advice is now more valuable
than the organs
um
oh I can make 2.0 now
word where are we going what am I doing
where are we going where are we going
where where do we want to go uh uh uh
here
wait how do I
what
uh
I can't put it there I need I need to
see it from a different angle I think
that's why I want to go I think
water
oh let's see the button
uh press
this one here
oh no wait it doesn't matter I think oh
okay okay follow the time was over and I
had to go back again but it didn't even
matter
[Applause]
well this is fun fun fun fun game so far
[Music]
Tennessee
it doesn't matter because portals have
made a portal behind the door that
closed on me 12. oh falling cubes coupon
head
momentum playing
a flame fling a fling playing I
understand
perfectly thank you
aha
uh
uh oh dear okay now I have to think with
two portals what are these dots are they
supposed to tell me something
oh no but I suppose one would be here
and one would be there don't know where
we're going but let's test it out oh my
God oh my God
where am I now
ah two I want to set the second level
and now
bigger momentum
can I just
ah wait uh
now we go here
but I can still use that because bigger
momentum and bigger brain oh here's a
here's a
uh okay but where is the cube
here it is oh have a weekend there move
big momentum oh this thing is angled so
I guess I would fall like
hopefully
maybe maybe
oh
is that enough
oh it works oh it was enough so now
can I go over there
yeah put that on here I am a genius how
is she doing I'm doing marvelously great
better than anyone would have ever
thought
probably can't be surprised right now
like what this is not the girl I know
is it supposed to jump her hair again
a little bit behind dude
oh my oh my speed run 80 percent
keep
this is expected of my tangent oh thank
you for believing in me who are you
two types of kfp
all right all right all right hello room
for teeth
how many rooms are there very very long
time maybe that's a line too
feel free to pass out first
I'm not pre-recorded what the [\h__\h]
ah 28 19. wait what did I ask oh the
numbers of
19.
there's only 19.
oh it's written here but that's a lie no
but then I'm almost done with the game
how's that possible
don't lie to me this is enhanced truth
isn't it
that's a lot that's a lie that is a lot
you guys are lying to me too [\h__\h] you go
somewhere else
okay uh how about we start like this we
take this isn't this easier than what we
just did
oh because I said it's going to take a
long time and that's a lie so we go here
we go through here
oh well now mine it might just take long
because it might actually take long
because this looks complicated
um
this is why I'll show you my true side
small brain Kiana
phoenixes are too smart for True of
enhancement
like that word
what is that the weird Ambience sound
why are we hearing that
um uh okay so first of all we put
something there
and then
and then we try to activate this so one
of them will put here
and one of them will put there
hello I want to get rid of you stop
looking at me
oh okay that worked what do we get from
that
what is that
what what actually is that
well I don't like it
makes us feel anxious
oh oh tell me where to go first actually
what is what is there oh God oh God oh
God that's trippy
ah
you want me to put the cube here first
uh all right let's think about it
wasn't ready for that uh
[Music]
come on come back
back okay okay okay
I didn't fit through was that do I need
to lose some weight
sometimes I get stuck in my portals
uh so oh wait
um
the first of all let's bring it down
and
um uh let me put this here and then take
it and then go for it yeah okay does it
have to stay
but where would I get another Cube
it has to stay open because like one is
checked now
uh
[Music]
is that like a collection collect
collectible
I can be a cube oh can I be
puke
can I maybe I can
oh
not quite
ah
I
don't know
I mean fruit
I'm so confused okay
open
ah
as part of a previously mentioned
required test protocol we can no longer
lie to you when the testing is over you
will be missed
[Music]
maybe here for the length the duration
of me playing Portal and after that I'm
gone you'll never see me again
man
go go go next one
next
portal 14 out of 19. uh
-huh
oh
it has a little bit of almost everything
yeah yeah oh yeah that's the thing to
handle high energy gamma leaking portal
technology must be informed that they
may be informed of applicable Regulatory
Compliance issues no further compliance
information is required or will be
provided and you are an excellent test
subject
all I understand from that is I got
praised so I'm happy
uh something there
and uh
I can't okay ah floor
huh
[Music]
okay anyway and that would have been too
easy obviously uh I was saying that oh
oh I didn't think there would be a
stairs oh okay
wait where'd you go up again can you go
up again
I was too slow
um I was saying
yeah
um I was thinking about what to collab
with combo the new member from Whole
Life Indonesia and
um
uh
maybe
I fall maybe I fall
and my idea was poor little because you
know oh Smite I was looking for
one-on-one collab games that I haven't
played yet
uh with anyone and that would be good
collab games oh my God I'm so smart holy
[\h__\h]
[Music]
um and yeah I know Portal 2 has a good
um
reputation and people love the game so I
knew you guys would love that
[Music]
so I thought why the hell not play
Portal 1 first you know never played
before seems like fun here we are oh
okay we don't wanna jump on that
uh
um unless just for a little moment is
that too does that does that work maybe
a bit more
maybe a bit more
uh I don't know here yeah okay oh God
this is so trippy don't you guys find
this trippy too looking at something
straight in front of you but then seeing
it in bird's eye perspective that is so
trippy why not put it next to the door
oh
well I'm in
there there must be a reason why there's
a platform here oh because I could just
try to jump
instead of making portals but why not
make portals if this game is about
portals okay but you guys were thinking
one more step ahead while I was thinking
you were thinking two steps that I was
thinking one step ahead where's this
going
uh
aha now I need them because I don't want
to change the portal
do I
oh now you're thinking of portals oh
you're so funny ah
see the problem is I'm not good with
Platformers
eh okay we're starting from here
[Music]
okay so I'm thinking with portals
you're thinking with portals we are
thinking Turtles oh no [\h__\h] that was
wrong [\h__\h] okay you're going there
oh did I managed to make a loop
I mean I didn't manage to make a loop
but
um
yeah no that works maybe I don't know
and maybe not I don't know maybe uh [\h__\h]
oh it broke
I think I think the ball broke can we
redo this
uh we want one here but I want one there
I think
wait I don't know I don't know where are
we bringing it where do we want to bring
it
[Music]
foreign
single playing cocaine oh is it
different
[Music]
is single player Portal 2 like
very different content
uh uh
does it want me to make one over there
[Music]
yes it is oh okay well we'll play it
multiplayer first we'll play it Co-op
first and then then we can still think
about it
come on
[Music]
[Laughter]
that hurts that hurt
that happened for the first time okay
but I'm really confused this is the
first riddle that's confusing me
uh
well well okay let's remember I'm making
a blue portal here
I'm making a blue portal here
so we can make an orange portal wherever
we want it to come out of okay remember
that remember how about we make it come
out of there okay smart I can do it
after all
I I think
I think it needs to go there we haven't
put anything there before I think we
didn't activate it yet
there we go does this work we just have
to wait a little bit Ah
a complimentary victory has been
activated in the main chamber
yeah you'll need a lift here is your
lift I'm more into Ubers but okay I'll
take a lift
I feel smart once again almost done with
the game wow 19 levels over soon it was
a short time I was just too smart for
the brain for the brakes for the game
they didn't expect it they would have
they would have totally programmed it
more difficult if they knew that I was
gonna play it
already
is committed to the well-being of all
participants cake and grief counseling
will be available at the conclusion of
the test thank you for helping us help
you help us all
right I knew it would be something like
a collectible 11 out of 33.
well that is big that is a big portal
thingy
um
tell me about momentum
is it really not a tutorial when it's
actually telling me uh what to do Loki
ah oh
[Music]
see I don't really understand what
happened
but I think that's
good
stop looking at me
vital testing apparatus destroyed
hahaha
then that solved accidentally I knew
something would happen but but after the
second
I wasn't sure how but but my brain maybe
didn't comprehend it but it's exactly
what I wanted to happen
yeah okay so orange portal here
Blue Portal here [\h__\h] it was two I was
too uh
wait why is it
do I have to do the blue one first
foreign
[Music]
all right
glowy stuff deletes portals
but glowy stuff
this stuff
but it makes no sense like it's uh
but I have no choice because it goes
straight I have to put it somewhere
where it will meet that
huh
also by the way absolutely Flawless
English today where is this
is this where it came from yeah Flawless
English from takanasi kiwawa today oh
yeah wait a second what
what is this this is how I leave okay
and yeah different solution yeah I'm
thinking I'm thinking
um
[Music]
wait see that one doesn't work
but here
this works
this works because it's inside of this
area but anything I built here
no that also works
very loud uh
okay let me try to solve this I'm smart
Okay I I did a lot of riddles myself let
me try to solve the Chicago I don't
think
you just stay here okay portal you gotta
you gotta no don't just did you say
[Music]
just
wait wait wait what
how is this possible no I can do it I
can do it I can do it but I don't want
to get hit by the ball so
[Music]
um
this works
that is [\h__\h] trippy ah
wait what's happening
wait why does it work now
why does it work now
I don't get it why what did I ever do
wrong before
but now it's
that doesn't work
but it goes through the ball goes for
these things so
I just need to
[Music]
goes back
um I just need to
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
it goes there but when I make a new
portal
do I just have to be fast do I just have
to be fast I'm gonna just have to be
fast so the moment it
the moment it goes through
the orange one I run in here
because I have to make it from a
distance right and I make a blue one
here
okay no the moment it goes for no we
don't need this one no we don't need we
only need we don't need this one we need
this one from from that for now and the
moment
it passes through
I want this to be somewhere else
I don't want this to exist right now the
moment it passes through
the
or like right before
right before
no wait but when I walk for it
disappears too
I bring him clothes but wait ah
I think I I don't need to do this I
don't need to do this yeah
yeah no wait no that's okay
we have something going on here
I want to have the ball
here so when it's on its way back to the
orange one when it already boinked and
it's going back here that's when I'll
change the position of the blue one
two I don't know where
um how about
oh God
six dimensional or ten dimensional
all right so it goes through
oh I'm so confused
but but I don't want to fight
um
hey
why have I
wait no
[Music]
oh
I just I I needed to see it happen with
my own eyes to make it happen
[Music]
um
that was too many dimensions for me oh
dear it's only got more difficult right
oh [\h__\h] maybe maybe we just had this one
one
part where we got stuck but we won't get
stuck again okay this is already sus oh
[\h__\h]
I see you
I think I don't see you
let me go through again okay so what do
we have we have this huge room
uh that right now we can't go through
unless we have some moment
dumb which we will get you just wait and
see I'll give you some momentum
just not that much but maybe it's enough
ah no but
can I make another portal while I'm
falling
does that make sense
well what if uh yeah
try it okay it sounds like I have the
right idea uh so I would be making a
blue one or an orange one
and orange one I think
I think
oh dear oh dear oh dear that's happening
too fast how can I how can I find the
right placement so fast it's Gotta
um place it rather low
yeah that was close that was close but I
think it worked haha I'm smart Okay so
uh can I make corals for a no okay
uh
uh interesting room
but maybe not important right now
Maybe
wait what
ah now I see you okay portal here
ah
momentum
well if I fall what does that do for me
oh I'm trying to
um
I know should have been an orange one
[Music]
I'm so
heard
oh my god oh
it's almost unfair because I'm so smart
oh my they want me to keep on recreating
them
so
blue one here orange one here
is that what's happening
oh [\h__\h] no wait I don't need a blue one
there what am I saying do anything
what's happening no I don't it no no
wait I don't need one ah
no I don't need one
or do I need one
[Laughter]
oh
huh
oh wait a second oh wait a second
how do I get it to go here though
oh
sometimes I'm just gonna let it happen
but okay even if I do that what what
what what
what I mean I can't do anything over
there anymore so unless I go there no I
can't go there
so how
about
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] how
about
oh here
what
that's weird why did that happen
angles right angles and angel you're my
angel
you're my angle
well
the lucky look online
oh God I'm so confused
no why
foreign
why don't I just do this
is that on the right height
huh no
oh wait that no no wait why is that
angled oh because it came out angled out
of the blue one
huh
[Music]
it came out angled out of the blue one
so it doesn't just go straight well I'm
still confused removed okay
oh oh
to confuse me
oh my that's too high
no way
they're not just there to confuse me
that was a little bit too high it should
be on the height of this one
so what about this what happens if I do
this
no that I saw that movement before
what
mirror mirror on the wall
who is the most enhanced of them all
right
what
oh boy
[\h__\h]
I'm so close really
am I getting uncloser
oh
[Music]
wait wait wait
oh
[Laughter]
what
what what what
what what
this is
a bit
wow
you take back what you said no
symmetry use symmetry symmetry symmetry
chemistry
symmetry
no way that's not symmetrics it's
symmetric
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man
no uh
what
I don't know what I'm doing I understood
this before
ah oh my God wait uh how do I go back
how did I go back how did I go back wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait I can
do this I can do this I can do this I
can do this you shall
yourself
right now that's not milk
[Music]
I've seem to have forgotten about you
um
how is this not momentum
[Music]
wear my hair
do we want to be here
but how do I get there
let me try momentum
oh
why are we here just to suffer oh my God
my brain worked so well in the beginning
of the stream now everybody's so
disappointed so it's like what what
happened what happened don't touch the
floor yeah yeah right don't touch the
floor they say
oh you're saying this would work if I
wouldn't touch the floor
all right
hey I mean I was I was I was correct
with what I was doing I just kept on
touching the floor and lost my momentum
okay okay okay so in theory I did
everything correctly
um so we activated that are we ready to
go yeah okay okay
um
hey
what what
I don't have to redo it do I I don't
have to redo it let me die
okay uh I see so this disappears
[Music]
um
yes
[Music]
I thought when you die you see like
white light why is it always orange now
okay maybe
don't panic
[Music]
am I just being impatient
I'm feeling impatient I think I need to
I need to look at it slowly slowly
but this is correct I think
this is okay but this one at least
doesn't disappear does it or does it
it is very slow
uh
oh no it also disappears oh [\h__\h] oh it
does disappear
oh God wait that's so confusing where am
I
so now I'm going backwards now I'm going
to
okay okay I think I understand
wait no
ah this is still a puzzle
it's not that confusing it is confusing
over there I need to make a portal there
so when I leave on the right side when I
jump through on the right side
[Music]
I can't make a portal there look at that
Arizona
ah I think against the stream oh okay
I don't know what do you mean what do
you mean what do you mean what do you
mean think against the street
s
you're very close really
pray for my oh she's brain
yes pray for it
um oh oh dear oh dear okay this is not a
difficult part right this is not
supposed to be the difficult part so we
start by making a portal there
yeah is this incorrect
I mean
no
don't get it
I don't understand
I
that that's right okay
um
just stop dying kiwawa you can keep on
experimenting but just stop dying What
if I
do a blue one there
uh no an orange one it's an orange one
because
um yeah yeah I think I
think I need to make an orange one okay
is that correct I think so
next time I'll get out of I'll get
closer to where I just was and then do I
make an orange one or a blue one
I made a blue one no I made an orange
one wait what the [\h__\h] why why are they
next to each other oh [\h__\h] I made an
orange one okay let's just make a blue
one uh here
laughs
let's make a blue one here and then and
then and then can I make one there I'm
gonna blow my blue one there
can make an orange one here oh
hallelujah oh Hallelujah I'm out of that
mess
y
[Music]
you're just gonna have an overview of
what you're doing just just understand
where you placed which color
uh that is very important
so why aren't we sending this one
what are we doing next these are not
moving are they
oh they move when I jump on them okay
do I see where it needs to go
ah here
is this a button ah this is number two
though
but who knows and maybe the game is
lying to me
oh
let's lift it now was that not on the
bottom before
I feel like that was
why does it say number two where's
number one
or is this another one a Wednesday
this is number one
okay
um and that one already was lifted okay
I think I was thinking about this one
all right so we touch button is that
time sensitive yes
I make a portal so I can quickly get to
that side
and activate the button over there
because there's two doors and then
we quickly quickly it doesn't need to be
quickly I think it needs to be quickly
does everything need to be quickly Let's
test it out uh
and then
uh
wait
wait wait
up to a certain point it was correct
um now the ball is just bouncing over
there
keep on bouncing there okay okay we need
to redo this
um the problem was
the problem was
uh
I'm not sure
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh okay
uh
so we push the button we go over there
to save time let's put my orange one
here ah
necessary to put one here eventually
or is that just where it came no no
um
think of portals almost think I was
thinking
[Music]
about portals
yeah yeah okay yeah yeah
okay which means that after I come out
of here I will make doesn't matter which
color I just make one blue one here and
one orange one here
yeah
okay okay
[Music]
I was worried about the placement there
but it went through it went through
oh that was I I figured that one out
nicely grab a room quickly at a good
pacing yeah
okay okay sorry my Japanese keyboard is
acting weird
oh wait these chapters this chapter took
a while maybe 19 chapters is true after
all
but even then we we played for one and a
half hours
um
nah it can't be true in 19 chapters can
be true maybe that's 20.
maybe the LIE is the enhanced truth is
that it's 20. the appropriate chamber
for this testing sequence is currently
unavailable it has been replaced with a
live fire course designed for military
Androids well then I shouldn't be here
apologizes for the inconvenience I'm a
military Android
oh oh those are cute come on deploying
searching for who oh God
is it gonna break no
entertaining
wait wait why that's so scary what the
[\h__\h]
hello
are you still there are you my friend
this gives me near all tomato Vibes holy
[\h__\h] robot's going crazy
hello
am I not supposed to walk into the laser
oh wait um
no no no I'm still here
don't come here
oh my dad
oh we're sneaky that's it's a sneaky
game now
make a game
I told you
what if I oh wait what a fun can I break
it if I let it fall from
um
why did I kill the robot
[Laughter]
[Music]
what is that how you're supposed to do
it because I I don't think I yeah
I think I'm supposed to yeah I'm
supposed to break it that's for sure oh
God I saw it
stop me for a moment once I see it it
sees me too but
The Voice one is looking for me is kind
of cute I almost want to play with it
mmm how do we deal with you oh there's a
cube over there
well
I don't know would it help me to go over
there
Maybe
I can just skip it
oh my god oh
you're scaring me
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
this is making me [\h__\h] nervous
oh it doesn't see me it doesn't see me
let's break it no let's break it um over
here
so it doesn't seem immediately search
mode don't don't look for me don't don't
wait it can't I can't make it here
oh no don't look for me don't don't
search I'm not here I'm not here
only whitefully yeah I thought that was
a shadow
I thought that was just a shadow not a
little wait why is there two lasers now
was there was two lasers
oh my God
oh my God oh my God oh my God
what is this
ctrl's Crouch but what the [\h__\h] is this
is where I'm supposed to go
hey what the [\h__\h]
oh no way am I gonna crush it
oh no that poor robot
I know it's not moving
it moved a moment ago
hello
what is this room I'm not supposed to go
the other side
hello can I help you this is scary this
is scary why is this so scary what the
[\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
why in the schedule
why is it so scary
is there something that's gonna kill me
here
milk uh
no everything's cool I think I'm fine
I guess it's like
um someone else staying experimented on
a trusted friend is insolence
on this they were like counting the days
and asking for help
um
the cake is a lie it is a lie
well thank you for the hint
I already know it because it's a huge
meme
Okay so
hi it doesn't see me because I'm looking
at its back let's just focus okay let's
focus on
hi fixing this
um
uh
oh god oh no
there's something there that I can um
where I can teleport over
portals thank you and portals ah what if
I land right behind it
no
I mean figure out come out of here if I
make a portal quickly
name do I want to land behind it
use the boxes oh it's a shield oh I
didn't think about that does it see me
oh my God but there's another one on the
other side that will see me
which means
maybe think of portals
maybe think with I
I don't I think I understand
I think I understand do I understand I
think I understand
I'm not there
I want to put one here and one over
there
no but without going there because
portals
my brain has apparently slowed down
can I like I don't know put it
ah oh God the laser goes for an
appointment too
okay there we go here
maybe not the best solution
uh
Wait no that's is that that's not the
solution is it
oh
wait wait let me wait a second wait a
second
um [\h__\h] I want I want it back
no wait
[Music]
that's awesome
to think please robot
okay activated
[Music]
am I dead oh my God I didn't it didn't
work though right did it did I make my
portal oh okay
I'm still there
foreign
I'll have to do it again
I have to do it again
my blood
I have another one for the other one oh
wow okay okay
oh God oh God
let's wait for it to sleep because then
it will not immediately be able to shoot
me right
what if I become small
it's like
okay
[Music]
are you dead I think it shut down
successfully but there's a there's
another one there
oh my God
[Music]
he said ouch
what about the other one
what's what do we have here oh you know
I need another one I need another kill
do you have a cube there you are there
you are
um
maybe try to get behind the cube
immediately and then at the end it
sounds like death to me
okay
[Music]
I can hold it while I'm scratching
it
no way
foreign
[Music]
come on
he's twice asleep
oh my God
no no
[Music]
no no no oh yeah he almost jumped in
there oh yeah
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
I'm not here oh my God
why can I does my HP recover
I'm safe here I think a radio
it recovered okay Hallelujah okay okay
uh
I say that I see there is um
you see there's there's a a place
walking for a portal
uh
[Music]
here
you think that will work
[Music]
if that doesn't work then I'll be [\h__\h]
hopefully it works
okay
there's one block but it's not looking
at me
about about here
perhaps oh my God where did it go
Michelle
isn't that brutal it's not even looking
at me and still I'm gonna kill it
that even pop that's necessary
I can lift it what I can just hit it
this thing oh I can touch this one too
but what does that do for me
oh wait if I pick it up for like if I
I'm able to sneak at it from behind when
it didn't see me yet
and I touch it does it start shooting
in any case
this was a very stressful situation for
me
It's Not Over
oh can the radio protect me
there's a lot of Cubes is it because
there's
Western portal I didn't make a portal
here
wait
no no no
why was there a red portal there I
didn't do that
I didn't really
okay
um hello
okay okay
oh my God
I don't feel like I'm gonna die
immediately Portland hasn't been so
forgiving with the other causes of death
so I feel like I'm gonna die like
instantly oh
can I sneak
you guys told me to do this it's better
work
[Music]
who am I
I am your master Chihuahua under control
now do something I'll I'll go and break
him now can I put you through a portal
here how about
I wanted to drop it I didn't want to
fall together
okay
um
oh [\h__\h]
no don't be this
is me I did so well until now didn't I
come on
please be so proud of me I'm trying my
best
oh my God
we spend run speed run the first part of
the game we can have a little bit of fun
with with the second part
right
definitely proud oh you guys are so
sweet
okay okay
oh God oh God oh God oh God
don't shoot me
we killed it
nice I have blood thirsty
last one oh
um
how do we how do we do this with you I
need to put one up there
I feel like I'm
dealing with this in a very complicated
way
at least I can't move I hope they don't
learn how to move later on
this one's there who's there peekaboo
[Music]
huh oh [\h__\h] wait which color did I make
blue okay
anyone there yeah
I won't say they're so cute
I will not be friends with them why
don't we have to find them is it robot
or an Android this is very important
very important
okay oh now we have more than enough
blocks to put on these I wish I could
I thought we were done it's a real one
ah
you don't know
small is better
um
good night
oh there is no X so I'm not exactly sure
where to drop it but I'm just gonna try
here
oh [\h__\h] am I looking at something else
what am I looking at
what is that
[Music]
walk behind it literally walk behind it
oh God oh God okay
like how what what
I can make a portal through this oh
I don't know if I can sneak through like
that though let's try
oh it works
[Music]
ah let's uh
I want to pick it up I want to kill it
let's drop it
uh
[Music]
uh wait what
run into it well what if it looks at me
and shoots me
okay so that was I was just scared of
that it would like fall in a way that
would be able to shoot me okay
and the Enrichment Center once again
reminds you that Android hell this is a
real place where you will be sent as a
different voice
where's the other lady
Android hell
I've sent a lot of a lot of Androids to
end World Health
in a different game
are we done with robot please tell me
we're done with romance
Companion Cube in three two Companion
Cube
team
ah wait did it already have hearts on it
okay this weighted Companion Cube will
accompany you through the test chamber
please take care of it it's cute oh no
it's cool I'm gonna take care of it wait
I need to step on it don't I
wait how do I take it with me
can I have another one I need a second
one can I have another one
he likes that to be stepped on
what a good companion well I can't make
portals here can I hmm
I wanna I wanna take her with me oh
there we go oh I couldn't do it before
oops jump and take okay well this is
easy
that was scary
[\h__\h]
I'm I nearly got shot okay now we just
have to we just take it with us and
everything is good
it's commonly produced by enrichments
Superstition perceiving inanimate
objects as alive and hallucinations
the Enrichment Center reminds you that
the weighted Companion Cube will never
threaten to stab you and in fact cannot
speak
huh
it will never threaten to stab me and it
can in fact not speak speak uh that is a
worrying statement
okay should I go like backwards
so it doesn't shoot me
yes
I guess so or just leave it here but
it's my companion
oh God okay okay
[Music]
don't wanna be without you
I can't live without I don't know how to
sing a song
this is weird
it's weird when one thing I know is we
need to get rid of these evil cameras
I don't want to be watched
it wherever I walk wherever I go this is
my private time with my private cute
Cube okay me and my killed besties
forever
uh
oh this thing wants to be activated huh
oh I can do that I can make that happen
there's like a
[Music]
there are several spots here
that wants to be
uh
made into a portal
in Easter egg in Terraria that's about
uh
that's about
a portal okay okay okay so we have a
thing here again with angles I
understand uh
what is this is this a floor where I can
make a portal
even if it is
I make a blue one I think so I keep the
ball in the room
oh
[\h__\h] where did it go
it should have made a oh I should have
made a red one I should have made it
[\h__\h] no blue [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
come on
and then make this color
I think
oh sorry my crazy eyes yeah yeah the
game is um making me lose my sanity a
little bit only a little bit will mostly
fine oh
could you come back
I'll make a oh my God an orange one
I'm like an orange one
okay yes yes okay now we have a loop a
beautiful Loop
why is it bonking on the ground that's
not good
um
so
now
how do we angle it
maybe I'm supposed to go down to have a
better look at it oh
thinking portals thinking portals
thinking portals
um I can make like I don't know an
orange one here
oh where does it go
ah but I don't want to get rid of my uh
uh
you wanna get rid of my bowl I don't
want to get rid of my ball oh
you have to
we'll have to put my bowl down here what
if I put the ball
oh the ball is still here
yeah
the first room opened
wait
huh
it's not even the room it's just the
part apart wall it's just it separates
the room a little bit
that doesn't feel like an accomplishment
at all but like I suppose
that is necessary because
uh the ball eventually will have to go
through all of these maybe I don't know
um but why why can I not just put this
over there
where did my Cube go there we go
there we go what is what is there oh
you see I told you I told you
yeah it has to go for above with them oh
but can I just stand on it in one case
or do I need to bring another cube is
there was there a cube somewhere
I kind of lost track of what I was doing
it was here
Let Me dance for later
maybe that's what oh
there's a lower
I'm gonna get the fruit
I'm gonna look at it oh is this one not
supposed to be looked at
oh
oh thank you portals
oh no was someone in love with companion
killed
and I stand the question
not in cruelty not in rev the reaper
came today and the angel visited this
great path and took the cube away no
no took him away Kelly the reaper took
the cube away oh look at all those kids
having fun
because I
I'm not sure can't
stop cannot stop for death
hacking
started starved for
oh no
cupad food
the cube has for you you fed the cube
maybe ammo
fund mini bar
password
and I know what it says has someone uh
figured out what this one says what is
this one
stop watching right I'm telling the
cameras to stop watching
no
um two little good
our game I thought the cube would last
forever I was wrong
oh that's disappointing before the cube
will last forever too I thought we were
best friends also this riddle is [\h__\h]
confusing already there's some numbers
here one two three is that where I'm
supposed to put the cube at some point
and it lifts me up and where are we
going oh my God
we need to get the captain
the ball back I completely
lost track of everything oh [\h__\h]
what
I need to get the ball back
I need to get the ball back and then I
need to send it to
maybe not here maybe not here maybe here
and down here
um
use your brain Kiana think
yeah yeah oh oh chat is saying yes okay
okay
uh is it gonna come
or did I make the wrong color no ah [\h__\h]
worked like that
okay okay no need for more puddles don't
over portal okay we open that up and
that means this one moves
so
there's a button there
where's my Cube by the way
I left it in the other room I suppose we
don't want to bring it there yet huh
foreign
ly one it's closer to me
oh
oh I don't know
oh [\h__\h] I know I know
you you go through that
and the land on there perfect
can I land on it too no
I want to I want to I want to land on it
okay uh so we brought it here oh
am I doing this right am I thinking this
through correctly
because I suppose like it didn't we
bring it down here
and now we want to back up
I don't think so
but isn't that what this is for this
lift
you don't know what you think I'm trying
to convey it but I'm really bad with
words
what is that room over there
what is that room
where where is that room
can I even access that right now oh
probably not because doesn't this mean
that this that is where I can leave
we still need the ball
um
I don't know where to
focus on right now
ah
yeah
there's another ball here maybe I don't
need to force that ball to come
here when I have that ball so I could
try to
bring that ball
somehow I mean I mean somehow this bowl
has to leave this room right
yes
I understand I think I understand I
think I understand where did I leave my
Cube
somewhere up there
can you not
I just want to come up here when did I
leave my Cube in the corridor
[Music]
is a lie is this why so many humans have
trust issues is it because they played
portal
understandable know it
a cute
[Music]
let me walk with you
yes don't worry I won't lie to you wait
no I forgot what I was doing over the
cube I want to test something
I want to try to put the cube
um here
no it's not quite
I'll come put this here
cannot seek in the event that the
weighted Companion Cube does speak the
Enrichment Center urges you is it gonna
happen
was gonna talk to me
oh we're gonna build a friendship but
this lady is trying to
trying to manipulate me I think
all right we made the second platform
move
oh I want the the third platform to move
um
why anyway let's stare at over there
really but that's
ah okay what is over there
maybe maybe
um a laser thingy
no
how do we get
that last platform
to activate what did we not look at yet
we did this part does it still create
the lasers
no
thank you
everybody and for the superchatos Danke
Schoen by the way
should we try this now is it time for
this now
what happens if I stand on one
again
but if I stand in the middle won't it
kill me on it
no this is one of those that wants a
laser uh okay so that would mean
um
that would mean
I need to be fast again
do I have to get the laser from here
what what what what color would that be
uh red orange
and it comes out of there but how do I
how do I quickly
oh portals let's let's test it out uh I
said did I say orange
wait there's no more laser here
I'm a laser here
where are the lasers still going on
hello
ah one more in the back oh that's so far
away okay now it doesn't matter because
we have portals but
uh let's look at it unfortunately I
can't dash Can I
foreign
I suppose this one has to be here and I
have to stand here eventually because
I will be able to run over there maybe
and then but then how
do I
no maybe maybe not because it will go
and I will have to go for a minute will
kill me maybe but if the cube is on
there then it will reflect it and it
will go somewhere else
oh too much painting too much thinking
someone's drinking let me just let me
just start by bringing the ball into
this room right Tony Antoinette step by
step you click where the [\h__\h] am I okay
think of it
about it slowly huh
uh wait what color is
ah
let's
um
let's oh yeah
let's make
let's bring it through with an orange
one
I think outside the box
I'm trying to think inside the portal
why are you telling me to think outside
the box
oh my God
what
where did I come from
oh
my God is this working is this what I
want
yeah yeah yeah for now at least the
portal position is correct because I
always get balls through the
for the orange portal
um
and they should be coming through here
there we go
okay it goes It goes through here
um it's rather slow how fast does this
uh oh it closes immediately
oh
ah I just walk on it when it passed by
this part
and then this one is open so okay okay I
understand just took me a moment of
observation
[Music]
what's going on
what's up
what's up where's my Cube
oh I won't like you
should I bring my Cube
remember your companion
my companions wear my cats all along but
maybe I was wrong maybe my companion is
the cube
okay I got it
oh [\h__\h]
and parkouring not so easy with Cube
oh
I left it there okay
okay
all right all right can we really make
that jump
John you think we can do it
kind of doubt it maybe with some
momentum
[Music]
let's go
are we done with this level
probably not oh button
why are you looking at me stop watching
me you want some privacy me and you you
did it the weighted Companion Cube
certainly brought you good luck however
it cannot accompany you for the rest of
the test and unfortunately not be
euthanized no
please escort your companion King to the
Aperture Science emergency intelligence
incinerator but why don't
you mean put it in there
yeah
this one
hey I want to look like a broken heart
no is that a hat on fire
oh no it says ball on fire oh okay
subjects of any moral responsibility for
the Companion Cube use an icing process
no no no no no we don't support that no
no no no no no we don't do that kind of
stuff here and wait how
this how do I open that up anyway
did I just lay it on what if I jump in
oh God look at this it's terrifying
to cannot accompany you to the rest of
the test no I want to bring it down
it will tell you to go on without it
because it would rather die in a fire
than become a burden to you
oh well that is so sweet companion
oh oh no
oh
oh that's what open Assistant cannot
continue do I really okay thank you has
been incinerated do I really have to do
it and then it's even timed really
until I really have to
tell me I don't know
I don't even do it that fast if I can't
it runs
[Music]
your face
foreign
[Music]
what do I care about cake I miss my Cube
how do I get over this relationship
how experiment is nearing its kindness
Center is required to remind you that
you will be paid and then there will be
cake
no there's everything except the cake
because the cake is a lie I will be
baked and then there will be cake oh
that's fun
uh okay well this is looking easy oh
maybe oh wait oh no oh
wait wait
uh
what what
correct
all right it's looking easy again guys
oh dear
you guys need to close up these kind of
things I don't think you want me to be
here do you
am I supposed to be here
it's a radio but it's not on
ah
[Music]
what a nice
long beautiful they don't play this kind
of music on our radios what what channel
is that how do I get that song
85.2 FM I'll try that out when I'm in
the car next time because that's the
only place that people have radios that
right nowadays
Alicia what the [\h__\h] what if I go up
there is this the right top is this the
only path I have right now
what do we have up here
oh there's a door
there am I
am I allowed to see this
no there's I can't open it anyway
okay
maybe it's just decoration here storage
room or something
what a bangle remember how you just
killed don't remind
I have a new waifu and that is radio
radio John you need music in your life
to keep you motivated and happy you know
thank you
come with me
they won't they won't tell me to destroy
you too will they
or some entertainment some bgm because
it's been hella quiet
all right is this where we came from
yeah okay
I need to go uh this way but what what
is down here oh dear
we'll just go over there I don't know
what awaits us over there but
uh
ah
what up
can I make that jump uh maybe if I angle
the jump blower
like here
does that sound realistic to you guys
we can try
no yes yes
that was close was this supposed how was
this how you're supposed to do it my
English is so shitty today because I'm
focusing my brain on the puzzles excuse
me
foreign
all right so we're here now
this is making me think big
is this where I came from I'm so
confused
no free oh
they're so nice helping me out there
so that's a big fall but
um oh God oh God okay okay easy easy
we're number three
uh
now I go to number four how about we
just do this
okay easy so far what's the problem
okay now I'm not sure how to get there
you know momentum I suppose
if I fall
very low like down here
can I
control myself in a way that I fall over
there
what is that what is that part
no
oh
[Laughter]
fall down there
hmm that works right
oh it should work
deploying what do you mean deploying
what's deploying
oh no
wait what what do I do first just throw
on a button
was that open
maybe later
was this open
please don't tell me this opens the
glass door
okay oh oh yes smash him
oh it's not smashing them how
[Music]
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you the cake is a lie no birthday cake
for you
congratulations
[Music]
okay I'm scared to go into that room
I'm too scared of these robots I I I'm
telling you
oh
no I don't know how to deal with them
I don't want to go I don't want to go
oh can I go here first no
[\h__\h]
stop
[Music]
is there is there a ceiling above you
not a feeling I can use
wait okay calm down uh maybe
it's where where can they not see me uh
here
and okay okay okay
open it up again
I wanna go I want to go to the safe zone
is this
[Music]
safe of a control like Jump by going
backwards
yes if you need to go backwards probably
maybe let me try again
I just I just need to uh go over there
oh God okay hide
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
what now
uh
[Music]
this one can't see me
oh hey excuse me for the portal oh [\h__\h]
that [\h__\h]
okay okay okay good now now we're good
there's a ball
ah there's a
the energy ball is coming from that
right
uh okay
where would that where would we want
that to go
thank God nothing can see me right now
you
vital testing apparatus destroyed
uh oh wait do we want it to destroy the
lasers
ah so the lasers are telling me
where to send it to so does this work
would that go no
this one should not go for the orange
one yeah there we go
Ah that's how I'm dealing I prefer this
way I'm very much remember this way of
dealing with them
okay
you need to send one for the blue one
and then we can kill this one
all right
yeah there we go look at it Oh What a
Beautiful Death oh
oh wonderful that feels very satisfying
okay how about we make it quick uh wait
does that make it quick
yes uh is that too low no that should
work
now we have
some silence here to focus
uh oh there's a cube over there ah
there's a cube up here too
um but this is not activated yet there's
a button down here
where's the activation thingy
ah here
huh but that's not opening or so I need
to
I need to activate the button first wait
there's a button here too
can I make the laser touch the button
or can I just touch it from here
oh
there's one turret left I didn't realize
okay let's kill it fast
hey I missed
this
oh God no
how would I miss that that was perfectly
placed
and
there we go
oh yeah there's a there's a platform oh
[\h__\h]
oh is there a reason oh my God is here
uh I want to go back uh [\h__\h]
where where we're gonna go here
okay oh my God okay
moment oh yeah let's remember that
platform I found that one by accident
momentum
momentum don't need it right now
don't seem to need it right now
uh all turrets did now
what was that with the button
we can touch the button
for a portal
but
we need to make the laser
uh
uh go through here
which is the opposite of ah here
okay
I'm about
um we first place a blue portal here and
while
it is making its way from here to here
because the distance is pretty long we
may have enough time
uh to make another portal here which
will be
blue and uh wait oh God wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait almost there
I'm almost there
uh no we don't need the we need we don't
need the red one the orange one after it
went through anymore
so we can just place it here wherever uh
blue orange push button blue orange
blue orange
why is it so high now
how was it so close before huh
taka in The Skittle
where did I place it last time why was
it out of range
why was it out of range why was it out
of range I don't have time to use this
one right now
um
why was it out of range
just place it higher okay
um uh
uh okay okay okay I'm ready I think I'm
ready
I'm ready they're not ready though
blue
wait which one am I placing higher
okay okay
I could have reached it I think
yeah yeah
that looked in a like it was in a
reachable distance
it's on its way
[Music]
I'm so smart oh I figured that one out
fast
ah jump for the portal and click adult
yeah I didn't want to risk um I don't
know when when I'm moving then I
wouldn't have so much control over my
body
oh anyway we are
I don't think we can get the cube can we
oh we can go down here
uh-huh
push the button for what
happened
what did that activate
wait we want probably to go at this
thing
it comes closer
why
let me go through
or maybe huh
oh
what's happening
yeah the angles itself upwards
ah
momentum this momentum
I'm thinking I'm thinking I'm thinking
I'm thinking
activate that again
let me look at it
[Music]
it goes up so
um
[Music]
it's also not very long
ah
yes
now I can't be that easy
where is it
where is that thing from this point of
view
I can't see it I guess eh
let's go in this room to get the cube
should I get back over there
foreign
from here again
Cube
wait oh God this is too big brain for me
hmm
what do you mean I almost have it I have
nothing
got nothing
[Music]
I have nothing
up
here
I want to fall through that thing maybe
that will land me at the cube
but
I need to activate this
so
first
first I I will have to go back for one
of those
is this really how I have to do it
which color which color
wait no wait
uh that's enough time that's enough time
but but I'm not quite sure what the
right order of things is yet
so we need we need to go back here right
and then we need to orientate ourselves
and put
no can I not actually
place the portal on there
because it's moving out slowly
so yeah yeah
and then I placed our orange one there
oh
how about can I redo it
oh wait
uh Orange
was it too late I think it was too late
okay
okay I think it was just a little bit
too late but but the idea of it was
correct
uh okay okay okay
wait do I oh [\h__\h]
I don't know what I'm doing
I'm on my way I'm on the highway to end
toward hell I'm on the highway to Edward
Hill
okay
so uh
activate put orange portal orange orange
orange
oh I really have to wait until
and now put Blue Portal here
[Music]
I need some time somewhere
um
fire while dropping
while dropping ah okay okay
what's up
oh one color
blue blue blue blue blue
blue blue blue blue
[Music]
now it has cute but it's not
it's not my companionship
this is not the right one
how do we bring you do I have to jump on
this okay
oh
oh why is why is there another one over
there
is it imprisoned do we have to save it
am I bringing this the right way where
are we bringing it to
foreign
oh I'm able to lose this one oh
wait how did I enter
what Harry Potter
how did I
come here
someone was here nothing
follow the blue line
huh
what
is this still a riddle am I supposed to
know how to get back lore
there's a lot of blue lines
this is still a riddle press the button
which button that button over there
oh
the other button
huh the other one okay oh
oh because ah this was the thing that
moved uh and angled upwards oh I didn't
realize oh well should I leave the this
one here
I guess I'll
is that enough time [\h__\h] that's probably
not enough time
maybe like this no
uh
I'll press the button
wait no uh I don't need to wait for it
[Music]
wait I've been sad all the time sorry
I'm not sad I'm actually happy that I
solve this riddle oh
God genius
um
just fall over there maybe is that with
the cute though without the cube bye-bye
you're not my companion cube anyway
[Laughter]
that was too much too much energy
but you need to
go slowly and calmly and carefully okay
even if you're excited you have to look
at the situation very calmly
why am I dead for so long okay
okay is it bugged no there it goes
I just want to go um over there
I know wait I would
is this a riddle too
sounded difficult
not that difficult
what if I I can also just go from here
to be honest
walk through here
there we go
yeah not so comfortable way of leaving
this area
oh there's a lot of momentum
for what
oh that's a tall room
[Music]
what is going on here by the way is this
18 this was 18 right
room 18.
not this oh boy a favorite part love
this part
[Music]
what happens if I
do this
oh [\h__\h] oh oh oh
oh
well that's not what I was supposed to
do right
what do I even wanna do
oh God
how do I get back
here
okay that was not it that was not it
or or maybe it was because what else I
can't reach any of the other things
this is the only one I can see
huh
okay
so again
observe observe ah
huh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I understand I understand
uh
oh
okay
a fun one though I'll give you that
all right
um we will place
blue we'll Place blue
foreign
[Laughter]
color but the right idea
really wrong color
I'm gonna Place Orange
oh
okay I'm coming
which color oh blue
not
blue for where we're here
still talking
uh
okay
if that guy did that ever happen to you
guys or just me
is it just me
[Music]
just me okay [\h__\h] what what
well done just stay calm okay
[Music]
safety seminar
okay wow wow that was like a trampoline
park you know this huge like rooms with
huge trampolines
I can't do any tricks so it's not really
something where I can have a lot of fun
I can bounce bounce and Bounds and
that's all I can do while everybody else
is doing like super awesome backflips
and front flips and all kinds of stuff
um
but if you can't do tricks and it's like
the most fun thing ever oh no you will
drop the device in the equipment
recovery Annex no I will not
regulations require both hands to be
empty before anything
um no cake
sad all right last riddle must be
difficult
this will maybe be raised and angled or
something eventually oh
restart by
[Music]
sending this
here
no
that was not correct uh
wasn't that easy we start by
sending it
wait let me test
uh
[Music]
I [\h__\h] I don't understand
it's working is it
[\h__\h]
what's happening give me a hint that is
not a hint
it it's probably very simple
yeah
um simple geometry sure
foreign
guys
wait where is where is on what height is
that thing
[Music]
did I just need him just need a moment
okay
it was so close really
that was on purpose that was of course
on purpose
well that was I was exactly what I I
wanted to happen I knew that was gonna
happen and you guys know that I knew
that that was gonna happen of course
all according to okay
[Music]
when is the next platform gonna come
you're really gonna make me wait so long
I don't even know what to do here
um
when is the next one coming
yep
I don't even name it
what
what does that do
oh
it closes
no it opens it but it just closes really
fast okay oh [\h__\h] no way
no way no way no way no way no way oh
[Laughter]
that's right
you understand me hungo very well my
friend oh I understand I think
how about here
oh I'm so smart
okay okay that didn't take me so long
come on you'll have to give me that what
do we do about this one uh no problem no
problem
wait no
[Laughter]
am I close
almost
oh let me look at it again
I don't know I can't find a better
solution
it's the right solution I just uh
to have a good timing
[Laughter]
oh I mean you just kind of give certain
things a certain amount of tries
um just to eliminate all uh
options and I want to kill the camera
can we do this
in a cool way
I mean that would be really cool
come on
okay I can do it this way too it's not
giving me any style points oh there uh
no it's not there it's not
um
[Laughter]
oh okay
I didn't I don't know what what I was
doing though
um
um what where am I where where uh [\h__\h]
where are we going
well that was a solution
anyway that works works
uh
um
that's not that's not quite it
what
how did I do the first time
[Music]
uh
oh
[Laughter]
uh
um
excuse I'm going closer oh there we go
try it it's the first time the test is
now over wow aperture Technologies
moving safely operational up to 4 000
degrees Calvin oh best to sure that
there is absolutely no chance of the
dangerous equipment malfunction prior to
your Victory am I being made as a fried
chicken
enrichment activity goodbye no no no
what Fried Chicken
the cake turns into Portugues
no no no no no
um oh God it's like a boss game
that was that was a quick reaction from
me don't you think
holy [\h__\h]
oh thank you
[Music]
success I did it in three hours with
your arms at your sides I thought it was
four hours of a game we'll arrive
shortly thank you for your party
Panic solutions to leave the testing
area
submission position or you will miss the
party
here I'll never leave it
what do you want me to do game
money
where are we going
what
assume the party submissions what
assume the party admissions submission
admission
look up
huh
wait what
I I I made a great Panic um
uh
decision but now I don't understand
party submission position momentum
momentum momentum momentum
where are we going
do we want to die now
we don't want to die
we want to go here we want to go there
right
um okay
mmm
oopsie here
and uh
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
what are you doing what am I doing hi
I'm trying to prove can't be that I'm
smart
it sounds different than before
we are very very happy for your success
[Music]
higher maybe higher
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
for your party oh [\h__\h]
assistant
submission position or you will miss the
party wait how about yeah should well
Falling Again
we'd call it which color which color
which color which color uh Orange
[Music]
hi the parties where Kiwa is that
I got an achievement of being a party
girl honestly I really am not I hate
parties all kinds of parties
I vehemently
the client going to any parties you
think that will stop me
I declined I refuse to go to parties
where am I going
I'm here open the door
even no Mario Party is okay
huh
okay cool
where's the bunny
I pressed in
oh maybe I didn't
oh no
honey
are you gonna shoot me again
oh no
what's happening
oh am I the only one
I can hear all the lot of vibes from
some of this
am I getting like a look like at the
behind the scenes now
how this whole uh laboratory works
can I pick this up oh I can
what am I what I do what do I do with it
can I like
how would I go about using it
is there any meaning for me to
why why I can pick it up
there must be a meaning
prop
all right but they do want me to
teleport somewhere I suppose because I
think there's a dead end oh no I'm here
we go
um
hello
where's the cake a party comes with a
cake right at least if it's a birthday
party
thank you
he thinks I'm stupid
must be part of kfp
you guys think I'm stupid too
sometimes you're nice and you say no
that's not I don't think you're stupid I
know you think I'm stupid all of you
think I'm stupid you'll think you're
smarter than me
y'all think you're smarter than me
did you solve that thing at the very end
that I did there in the first try huh
where did we come from
short time memory oh we came from there
should we go that way
we can try
oh God okay
did I want to go here
not sure
I am cool and smart oh you're serious
you're sucking
up to me is that how you say it
open the door
party logo oh
[Music]
it must be somewhere over there
party must be there
ah did I
I was gonna ask you if I was in that
room before I was in there but from the
other side right
okay
am I you
yeah okay go through here and we're in
this room
or did I just make
the circle
nope this is
this is new yeah yeah this equipment
starts and stops automatically that
sticker is not supposed to be there am I
going backwards
I came from there
no
it felt someone new
foreign
okay
that does not mean I'm stupid though
oh wait
there's something up here no there's a
tube though
I want to cook through here
or
when I'm stuck
now I'm stuck
foreign
[Music]
but what about momentum I don't know
oh thank God the fences are
so low quality
error messages let's look at them
vegetable oil teaspoon
cam prepared is this recipes
what are we call is this a cake recipe
oh my God
it's a [\h__\h] cake recipe does someone
like write it all down and tried is it
does it actually like end up as a proper
cake
you never noticed that I'm gonna look at
the details man you're gonna look at the
dates
nice keyboard
I like how one of the things here are
orange good taste
it has fish in it
ew I feel like I heard about that before
Oh that's the room
cool
no that's not the room
wait
went for that herbivore
oh these are monitoring rooms
I don't know
did I come from here
did I
yeah I did
okay uh
I'm lost uh
no I came from I came from here I'm
supposed to go this way okay I got lost
in a lore room that probably is just
lore and you know cute details
hmm
it's so quiet why is the lady not
talking to me anymore is she
disappointed that I didn't want to join
her party
and I decided to make my own
am I supposed to see something new from
here
momentum well I can't oh wait no
where are we going
oh
oh where where are we going
where do we want to go
up there right
so we make one here
and we make one like uh
um there easy
hey
are you still you're still here
I'm good to know
that Well Chad says I'm going the right
way
I'm here we can be friends
I know by now the cake is a lie I've
known all along so in reality I played
you you didn't play me okay
oh
do I want to go in there
I'm gonna kill me oh I become fast too
okay I thought I had to walk okay
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] maybe it was not the
smartest idea to go here
foreign
no
I think
not
wait where does she want me to go
because that's not where I'm going
hey yada
is this why she does not want me to go
no this is what she wants me to go that
evil witch
right
don't go there
no I can't go throw it I can't
where are we going
what is what about this room
it's closed
I have to
she doesn't want me to go there it's
like
reverse psychology
and there's no other way anyway
I'm making a portal there is kind of
useless is it
uh
oh
that's okay I mean that was not gonna
eat the whole cake anyway totally not oh
no no no no no no no not me they can go
ahead and eat some of it without me
feel free
oh
what ah
oh okay that worked anyway
um
but leave leave the big piece for me
please
I'm hungry I need dinner after this and
I'm not sure what I'm gonna eat
oh oh dear lord
oh
let's let's go somewhere but where
what is that
ah who painted that I wonder the staff
or someone else who who managed to
escape wait can I make a portal only
here
no
Bae threat ratman
anything where I can make a portal
what
is this where I came from
no this is new
I think
wait what what
I did come from there
oh
I can't see anything
to work with
except
is this gonna smash me how high does
this the first one go oh no it's not
gonna smash me
um
wait is that
is that where we're going
it's not just where it came from
oh
yeah
that's why I don't see anything
okay I don't see anything
wait what oh never mind I don't have to
see anything I can just uh go through
here is that safe
where can I make my other portal
here
okay
um now
momentum
okay
loading what's loading
yet
yeah we're in the left way
I'm going towards the end of the game
and towards Portal 2 .
all right we have to play with these
things here
obviously
I made a portal oh God this is gonna
crush me yeah
oh mama
that was unfortunate
you didn't notice yet that she was
dealing with a phoenix
[Music]
can you smash me through that
I thought that was gonna work
oh that was gonna work
well maybe I don't even need those
things right I don't even need the
pancake makers I can make pancakes just
fine by myself
hmm
I've been making
a lot of Pancakes these days I'm really
into it
maybe I should make some more variations
I've been making blueberry no banana
blueberry pancakes is there anything
else I should try guys
you're welcome to give me suggestions
always uh Nutella pancakes
when I say banana blueberry pancake so
we're gonna talk about any pancakes I'm
always talking about adding Nutella to
it at the end
strawberry yeah I mean the blueberries
sometimes I replace them with any other
kind of berry anyway you know strawberry
banana
binder done that
cheese no I want them to be sweet I like
my breakfast breakfast to be sweet but
I've noticed that when I'm like at the
hotel for example uh
I am I eat I often also choose the
Savory version
Savory breakfast should I go here
[\h__\h]
because this one goes higher right
but I could have totally stepped on that
one anyway when I was at the bottom then
everything else was not even necessary
was it
on it
on the center alone
Oh I thought okay well
okay
that's not Center is that Center
and it looks about right
yeah what I can just step on it
and why did I walk around it
huh
why did that make it so make it so
complicated apple cinnamon oh well that
sounds good
I thought you know because there was
that side room I thought I had to make
use of it
are we going down
really
oh no I definitely had fun
[Music]
you're like you're like um girlfriend
I remember that time oh sh what
why did I hurt myself I didn't even get
smashed okay where are we going wait
wait wait wait
oh this one this one probably
what's uh
where can I put my portal
nowhere
huh
here
what
chicken oh
yeah
what am I what am I not seeing
hey
look Elsa
oh
[Music]
ah where can I put this one
but that's smashing didn't work last
time does it actually work
does that actually work
oh it works it works it works it works
oh
it works
oh it works yourself
all right okay
all right who put that portal there I
don't remember putting it there
do I go down the ramp now
upright
um I think I think up
got this ah the escaping is actually
taking quite a long time
oh yeah I
oh man what what
did I get to where I wanted to go no
uh oh I need to do it when
that stompy machine
comes over I think that's what I wanted
to do I want to land on that
yeah that was my plan but
was that a bad idea oh no
I don't know I don't know
I know what I want to do
oh
baby that is fine maybe there's one way
to deal it
cat hair in my mouth
okay
is this how you guys did it
this is the piano my original way
open wait don't tell me this is another
place where I went where I've been to
before
or do I need to go even higher
looks like I need to go even higher eh
wait should I not have gone here
but also
did I just not managed to open the door
correctly again no it really doesn't
open
uh
uh here
no not not quite and do I need to land
on that one
probably
oh
I want to go here
is is this is this
is this okay
ah
[Music]
momentum
can we use that what if what if I put
that up pretty high no but more on that
side
and then
no I'm so glad that worked
I just believed
I just believed guys
uh
-huh
aha lady you know
they help you with your experiments
it's time to end it okay it's not funny
anymore no more experiments
[Music]
over here I seen that
I see that
do we want to land on this pipe Maybe
give it a try
oh God yeah
and then and then and then and then
and then she
oh thank God it actually doesn't close
completely I don't know where to go
maybe even higher on those ones
I know I can't do that I can't reach
that
but I can try to
land on this one
baby
yes
okay I mean I'm here
uh I'll make one
foreign
[Music]
but it's okay I made I made it
Redmond thank you for all the tips rats
aren't that bad after all
I I guess that's Casper
Casper's Legacy
thanking me for giving up on killing him
uh
we're totally gonna forget about all the
times I tried to kill him
because all that counts is
I stopped
sorry Casper
foreign
ly now oh where where's the voiceover
you're really creeping me out lady
you're really creeping me out I also
feel like I messed up I don't know how
am I gonna go there
how am I gonna go there I'm gonna land
on the pipe who is Casper oh you're
right oh we
oh my God
we need to make an explanation video of
who is Casper he doesn't really play a
role anymore but
he is an important part of the kfb lore
so
I want to teach everybody who doesn't
know
hello portal yeah I was thinking until
but I don't know
[Music]
that looks so dangerous
wrong color no
yes
yeah
um
a bit more on that side
jump
okay
Casper joined the home no no no no no no
no Casper
Casper
Casper just lives a normal happy
life while eating plastic and chocolate
all the things that I supposedly oh
toxic to rats
Casper enjoys because Casper is not part
of your system
help what do you mean to help you're
almost out rat man
you're almost at the end just like me
I'm really getting hungry
was I supposed to fall down
what was that sound
remember this I'm not good with this
um no
no no no
oh no no
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
hello
hello I know I should have just reacted
fast Maybe
oh no I know oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] which one
comes first
foreign
good night
guys
oh
it's dumb [\h__\h]
no [\h__\h] activating are you still
there
okay okay okay
what is that
over there okay
uh
gosh I'm feeling sick
[Music]
do you agree
do you agree with that
is mean
there's more of them well that one
doesn't work does it this one
snake behind it can I make a portal
yeah I wanna make one here this is all
mean
okay
oh
I'd be still able to surprise it more or
less
or maybe not
Target lost
who's got the power now
um
why don't you're not even gonna
sabotage yourself come on
give me some some light party
EDM lights
uh
you know
really
that's not fun
anymore
no music
I'll I'll take one with me
they're all useless I suppose maybe this
one has a bigger hitbox though because
it's open
I'll take this broken robot with me
where are we going though
you're saying you're coming with me but
I don't even know where we're going I
thought these stairs would continue but
it just ended right there
[Music]
plus we're gonna go up here
all right
all right come with me
you are my friend now
is this not also where I came from
but that's why that's where I came from
that's where I came from
where therefore this is what where I was
where I came from huh I thought this is
where I came from
where it came from
and then I made a portal here yeah yeah
I came from here to here okay okay
oh I see you
I wanna I wanna go here okay okay I'll
go okay
what
what's happening
I'm falling
my sense of direction
oh wait oh oh oh I see oh I'm landing
there I thought okay
um the perspective
confused me here I
I thought that that was like I don't
know
not what it was
but but this should work
no it doesn't
must be a different way
yeah I know it's a ceiling
but I thought no that was a different
room
oh drop
drop
but I just have to
wait okay okay no that was what I was
supposed to do okay okay
um now can we make a jump Cafe what do
you think can a phoenix make that jump
I'll make you chickens proud I need to
make a good example
I told you guys you can fly
and so can I
okay oh oh you're broken too aren't you
are you
hopefully
the light
are you broken tooth I'll take you
like my cats
just following cans but you must
understand
this is the only way to happen this cat
believe me
where are we going
I'm gonna thank you for what no no
no
oh no I want to keep you alive you're
the future
Laura
room this one yeah
but this person is so crazy at this
point it's not giving me any new lore
it's just repeating itself not really
helpful
no hard feelings
you know
hopefully
just wanna make some friends you know
is this where I came from
that's new
no that is where I came from that was
where the turret town was standing
huh
brain power is low please charge me kfp
please give me some energy
why this is over here
what do you mean over here
I need to stand on one of these to see
something
uh all right got you
foreign
which one though
I know from that side
ah yeah
I used up my brain power no more juices
are flowing
chill chill chill
okay okay I got rid of the Blue Portal
uh
[Music]
you want the momentum
where are we going
oh I want to go over here
okay
ah
all right I can still do it after all
these years I still got it in me
it didn't have to be like this
I'm not kidding now turn back or I will
kill you mom come so far I don't know I
think I'm doing that and all the cake is
gone you don't even care it's not about
the cake anymore this is personal
chance is that
here break this one
oh [\h__\h]
here this one
oh this one this one
okay oh that's scary oh that's scary
that one actually goes for the windows
so that is a pretty terrifying
the lady was indeed out to kill me
oh my God
oh my God we're just descending
wait did I come from the store
why did it open like that
yeah it came from that door
over here
how how
break this one can I make them
machine wait can I take it with me
I can't take it with me right
that one goes for the windows what did I
say something stupid can I take them
with me
hello
how are those are we celebrating portals
wait let me make one somewhere else
um
wait what oh yeah angles
[Music]
no it doesn't have to be fair it doesn't
have to be angled oh you can see
oh
no don't look at me
I don't know why I was thinking I needed
the angle I don't know
[Music]
um
uh
[Music]
oh
Nani
[Music]
oh
huh
[Music]
no
no no
no no no no no
no
oh
break it to you what you can do that
oh no I have to get the right portal
again okay but oh let me just get this
ready okay
I'm still gonna use you huh
all right
oh oh did it already happen
it didn't really work look at me
[Laughter]
so it's so funny man uh
the stupid moments such clumsy moments
this is really bringing out the clumsy
chill inside of me I can be pretty
clumsy I can be pretty porn
oh what do we have here
the end is so near
oh
we're going there
really
wait that's just a poncho I really like
ponchos by the way
but I feel like they're really hard to
wear really difficult to pull off
like a winter ponchos like sample
instead of coats you know
oh yeah
uh
this is not good
I never know where I came from
I came from there that's my portal
the office chairs oh
to the pie breaking and I don't know
yeah I I wouldn't I I don't know if I
would have ever gotten that idea about
myself
but good to know that there's other ways
to do it as well I like games that have
several ways of solving the issue
foreign
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
it's a huge maze I I thought I was you
know
ending the game early with three hours
and now we have four hours anyway
I don't wanna
this room is so big I don't want
to hear
it looks dangerous like last suppose so
I'm feeling this is like last boss well
there are these lights huh our Laser's
gonna shoot me again
oh that's me hello
ew ew ew oh no oh I knew it wait what
was that again oh no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no
thank you
you can't put me in these kind of
situations
situation situations
oh okay okay okay okay
you don't play me okay I'll blame myself
uh
[Music]
I'll just enter that room I'll just go
over there we'll eliminate them one by
one hello
[Music]
it's okay it's okay it's okay it's all
good we'll just drop them
think too much about it
just have to grab them
hurt you
please put me down
I'll put you down okay I I have figured
out the situation I know how to deal
with this now don't worry guys
let's go
I'm good at this now
hello are we done I think we oh are we
still missing that one
oh
try that one go oh one more one more
ah can I die
is there fall damage now okay
this is so cruel
Okay so
please put me down
Nero automata has made me very soft
towards Androids and robots
I I did put them down in many ways I I
dropped them and I also killed them how
how nice to have so many
meanings to one word it's philosophical
isn't it
um
foreign
or the whole near series have like an
anniversary today or yesterday
I think it was replicant was it
replicant
I think we killed all of them
what now
oh we probably just gotta go to the top
sounds about right when rap will come
play through ah you know I was really
thinking about it
I wanted to
momentum oh no
that's not a good angle I can't do
anything here I wanted to but I've heard
from several people that it's not the
best
um
it's not the best streaming game
hey
good it doesn't work that one
even if it did
oh it looks like it did
oh [\h__\h] huh oh we're on it okay and now
oh we can easily
put it over there
so
I don't think this I think you're
supposed to do it one by one by one in
one flow
but okay
oh God
what
I messed it up I think
what where I
I
lost my orientation
what am I looking at
I need to make one over there no
it doesn't work
I'm entering upside down
what
that's not where I want that to go I
don't know I'm so confused oh
oh
on purpose
[Laughter]
I like how you can totally like
notice that I didn't help
this because it's so obvious like you
can easily see what I what I did
according to okay and what was just an
accident that I stumbled into
um what do we do about this
hello
oh
that was easy
[Music]
Tiana inside of me is crying
there we go okay okay okay
holy [\h__\h]
ah
turn it down my beloved
I want to fall I don't want to fall for
that let's put it somewhere else
huh
no
orange uh
no I'm scared
what if I leave that blue one there
and put my orange
down here
should I put it on the angled one
what I don't want to regret it but let's
go
not quite
no
no that's not it
um not on the angled one
not in the angled one that's okay
[Applause]
wait what the [\h__\h]
oh I
I
went up there by accident I don't know
how to get up there
um
no I know I totally know
I know I know how to get back up there
[\h__\h]
so cool
what what what what what what what
what's happening what's happening what's
up oh yeah
okay
okay I hope I don't have to do that and
again anymore again okay yes
thank you
um
okay so we want one
uh here
and
why did it go wrong last time
one color right yeah yeah yeah
this should work
yes okay
okay
now it's a piece of cake isn't it
yeah
okay
[Music]
Don't Look Down
finally getting to the end
it's not looking so spooky and dangerous
anymore
interrogation room or what oh no wait
occasionally genetic life form and disc
operation
black muscle
black muscle Personnel over paid
giveaway virgin plus less expensive one
oh wow wow what a PowerPoint
presentation
dollars
live reference oh yeah I thought I heard
that before somewhere
oh wow
this is an insanely huge building if you
think about it oh
is that the end
why
finally well you found me
congratulations was it worth it because
despite your violent Behavior one thing
you've managed to break so far is my
heart
and we'll just call it a day I guess
sorry nice pound isn't going to it
wouldn't work though there's no cable
now I have a surprise for you deploying
surprise in five four cake timer for a
second that wasn't supposed to happen
what do you see that thing that fell out
of me don't tell me it's gonna it's not
the surprise I've never seen it before
oh never mind it's a mystery I'll solve
later by myself because you'll be dead
ah
just gonna I wouldn't bother attack me
my guess is that touching it will just
make your life even worse somehow
I don't want to tell you your business
but if it were me I'd leave that thing
alone
uh-oh do you think I'm trying to trick
you with reverse I mean serious it was
looking at me it's gonna shoot me
where's you taking that thing it's gonna
shoot me
pick it up and just stuff it back into
me now
no no that's exactly what I'm not gonna
do one of us knows what that thing does
just put it in the corner and I'll deal
with it later when it does it's gonna
shoot me oh
swing here that thing is probably some
kind of raw sewage container go ahead
and rub your face all over it
oh oh you notice that I noticed that
thing you should marry bad things that
you love it so much
they're not looking at it you how does
that feel
wait what's up what's up here for
example
I am being serious now that crazy thing
is not part of any test protocol
hmm
yeah how long is it gonna stay open
okay my ball is where's my bowl wait I
could have just walked up up here it's
so dark I know about it uh should I just
put
right there
all right let's destroy your system
here it isn't yours that could work
shortcut
I'm gonna throw it on the ground I tried
throwing it on the ground that was not
enough so we have to destroy the system
oh come on it's not gonna be enough time
but that thing isn't it isn't you
[Music]
it was an accident
seductive
yes I figured out what that
[Music]
the personality
and the deadly neurotoxin to make me
stop studying the enrichment center with
a deadly Naruto oh [\h__\h] comfortable
oh
yeah
oh no oh oh no
oh no
trust me does it go up this thing
uh go up to no all right
you're doing whatever it is you think
you're doing I don't know what I'm doing
six minutes
[Music]
portals
foreign
[Music]
yes it is
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
here we just use the same portal
no uh there was another one of those
lasers
that was aiming at me where did it go uh
this one
what did I ever do to you the difference
between us
pick it up
I can again pick it up uh what is this
thing
oh wait did it fall over there
[Music]
oh
okay
shit's a time stop it stop it
[Music]
okay next one please
try to kill me I think you're doing some
damage
hello come and get me I'm fine
[Music]
as well
okay
[Music]
um
maybe here
did I put that here
[Music]
that's exactly what it is
speaking of curiosity
come on this has to be it
[Music]
so I won't bother excuse me
[Applause]
where's my laser
[Music]
what it was aiming at me through that
portal oh please I have full time I have
no time
oh oh
[Music]
finally I
personally
did it land upstairs
that's it I'm done reasoning with you
starting now there's going to be a lot
less conversation and a lot more killing
did you say something I sincerely hope
you weren't expecting our response
um
guys
[Music]
now
it talks
no [\h__\h] way I'm gonna do this
foreign
[Music]
oh
that caught me
wait how many eyes do we have left are
we starting from the beginning or from
somewhere in between and we have all the
eyes left okay
okay but I should have just put the
[\h__\h] point
I can kind of aim this way all right
oh tell me a [\h__\h] damn while
exclusive
okay from the bottom we go
no
I'm so [\h__\h] blind
the difference between nurses that I can
feel the pain okay now now I know how to
do it they have more than enough time
what's that
you're really killing me with your
cuteness every now and then
making yourself more likable is probably
just manipulating me isn't it
okay portal
I don't like that portal placement here
this one is better I'm fine
two plus two is ten
gouda just kidding
you've managed
what is that angle let me let me put it
uh [\h__\h] wrong one
oh my God that was a close one
how about this angle
yeah that's better that's better
all right
and the ball went
oh up there okay okay okay here all the
way up here
[Music]
I made that jump before
come with me
[Music]
all right all right I I understand okay
I'll order some cake for you
I don't have much experience making cake
myself so please forgive me what am I
doing
I'm confused
directionally challenged as always all
right all right all right okay
but
oh sure
they're actually just cooking here
actually we are just cooking
that might miss
[Music]
okay does this boss have a face too
perhaps
[Music]
are you just talking now
there's just something for me to do oh
yeah oh oh
you it's floating
am I supposed to grab it while I'm
falling
I have your brain scanned and
permanently backed up in case something
terrible happens
don't shoot me don't shoot me don't look
at me like that
they might put too much catnip in your
bed oh no
Kitty You're a good kitty good night now
I did it
finally I'm the one breaking hearts not
the other way around
I feel like it's so powerful
I'm sorry but I'm done with being
heartbroken
[\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
I understand you why I deserved to be in
the Maldives
I don't like these kind of experiments
and Phoenix deserves better than this
I'm just gonna order some cake
and forget about this hopefully heal
from the experiences
wait so
what
do you mean how did my character get
into this [\h__\h] anyway
was I like abducted or
a companion killed all right I'll ditch
right now take my companion cube wait
that was like robotic sounds
when I was moving
am I a robot
oh was it a robot pulling me back wait
what the [\h__\h] no
really
oh
what
what is that oh it's okay
oh it looks so yummy and it's
huh
ah it's a party right all eyes on me
oh that was cake
it wasn't a lie
this was a Triumph
[Music]
what success
I've heard this before
[Music]
foreign
oh I love it
YMCA
am I gonna get DMC are they so strict in
this song
maybe I have to cut it from the archive
[Music]
don't be so real about it come on we had
some good memories too
every piece are you just gonna remember
all the negatives what about all the
positives
[Music]
they were positive
this is just a
a situation of whether or not your glass
half full or half empty person
[Music]
Break Up Song
like I wouldn't be surprised if someone
took this out of context and just used
this you know
as a breakup song to get over a breakup
or to tell someone [\h__\h] you I'm breaking
up with you
[Music]
oh priorities
should I play Black mess
is that what it's telling me
[Music]
I've only heard this before but I don't
know where
you're still alive yeah Portal 2 huh is
that where we're meeting again but I'll
have Kobo with me you're gonna be
jealous and then die from jealousy cause
we're so cute together
thank you for participating in this
Enrichment Center facility
oh activity this cake
[Music]
the fact that the cake is a lie was a
lie too
[Music]
I really thought it was a lie
is there is the truth enhancement
enhanced
wait I never knew that I thought the
ending mama was that that there was no
cake there was actual cake that's the
biggest surprise for me
oh and that music is so good and here is
that the recipe for this actual cake
I wonder the recipe that we saw oh I
just noticed the dial from the phone is
like the little girl
I don't get to eat it well I mean that's
just because people haven't invented a
way yet to you know make people able to
eat certain things in games so oh we're
moving well we're moving
yeah
oh okay give me a mean it's nice when
you think cuddle with my kitty cats
we are allergic to cats
well then [\h__\h] you in that case
I don't
I don't live with all my cats cats are
priorities
above all else oh so I'm gonna drink
some water
[Music]
yum yum yum yum yum
you'll be on the table that's not a you
beat that's a mouse
hopefully
oh boy
[Music]
is it is it
achievements
26 that's pretty
I mean compared to what was that other
game we played a while ago where I had
what four or six percent
[Music]
wait what was that game ah uh Starship
Titanic wait was it no no yeah
Titanic was fun yeah because I had um
yeah
interesting hello uh percentage
[Music]
um
oh did she finish that artwork
oh
oh no oh she finished that thing
holy [\h__\h] it's like a magazine page for
each one of us
I'm talking about Mama Loney Twitter
oh
she was drawing now for a while like uh
oh let me show you
there's one for each ID and Ian member
that um showed their 3D at the concert
but look at that oh I like the cool
um like cool and
um confident look here
oh
and here rocky pie
[Laughter]
wait what does it all say what is
written there
foreign
is that what
is that Mama Lonnie's fault
I don't know there are translated
versions oh
I love I love the the cute faces she
dressed sometimes like like this one
um so cute so therapy oh
holy [\h__\h] the kid getting kicked though
I want every single one of them as a PNG
Thomas
Jose he'll see oh ski I wanna I wanna
print this out
it looks so cool
I want to look at it
slowly slowly sorry I got distracted
because someone in the chat and talked
about it and you know I'm always up for
some new mama learning art wow please
check it out on Twitter I'm gonna
retweet it
yeah
um
now I have uh some bad news for you but
maybe you already expected it because
it's midnight past half past uh half an
hour past midnight
um I'm not gonna Read Super chats
uh first of all it's late second of all
I'm actually feeling pretty
bad right now I have a headache and I
feel sick uh yeah
um very bad really bad
it's been it's been getting worse
throughout the stream so sorry about
that
um
um maybe that's also why my brain juices
were not flowing anymore so smoothly at
the end
um
I learned this kiddle
yeah
um
yeah that was all the momentum gems
Maybe
I don't know it shouldn't be motion
sickness it was not VR I don't know can
you get motion sick from non-vr games
um yeah I'm feeling really uh exhausted
right now from all of this maybe I don't
know it might not be the game it might
just be me
um I had an exhausting not not that
exhausted I had a busy day and
um yeah tomorrow is Duolingo I've been
having a lot of appointments this week
and I also have a lot of appointments
next week but I think tomorrow now I
have something else too besides the
lingo
but yeah
um
Duolingo who's happening tomorrow
uh I I have the stream already up just
private I'll put I'll put it on
unprivate after I'm done here and I
should be able to read super chats I
have to do a lingo tomorrow maybe we'll
do like two hours of Duolingo and then
we'll read the superchatos
yeah
Korean Korean yes yes yes yes yes
um I wanted to finish learning hunger
but I ended up not having any time man
um I I know partially maybe I can learn
some more right before the stream but I
had a lot of things to do the past few
days
oh I didn't work out I went to doctor's
appointments I went to pick up a Wii U
and uh uh then I had vitamins no monkey
all kinds of stuff recording vocals and
all that very busy
um
yeah thank you guys you're so sweet yeah
I got the Wii U now and which is
exciting I guess uh I uh will hopefully
have time to test it out but we're
playing Wind Waker yeah on the weekend
I'm so excited for Wind Waker we're
gonna have a wind waker weekends I'm
gonna play it until we're done on
Saturday Sunday uh the weekends in the
past in the coming weeks uh will be Wind
Waker weekends yeah double uh Wind Waker
days on the weekend until we're
finishing it isn't that a cute name Wind
Waker weekends
oh when Michael was released on wheat
yeah
um and remastered version Wii U
I'm not really feeling
sick
I'm feeling sick and not in a good way
um but I need some food I'm gonna make
pizza
www
well but I have to say portal was fun
really fun I like the riddles very much
uh it's a very fun thing to play around
with the portals
um uh I want to play more games like
this like super liminal and this one
with the the puzzles but also like this
this voice that talks to you and kind of
teases you that seems nice at first but
then you know you realize oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] we want to get out of here of
course yeah I know portal too
I don't know it's already planned
um it will happen uh like uh in the
first week of May I think
with um
and yeah since I liked it a lot I might
want to try the uh solo version as well
Stanley Parable in
um believe me uh we've all we all want
to play it you know I'm English I think
we all want to play it uh
yeah not possible at the moment maybe I
don't know
maybe I don't know I heard there was a
new release coming out so
I don't know I'm not how that works but
maybe for you that how is it releasing a
new I don't understand but I need to
look into it but I would love to plan it
of course yeah this kind of games where
there's just this this
God talking to you
start usually you're sarcastic person
um
very funny Bastion
Bastion
oh wait what part of Russian Bastion
hey why does Google look so weird what
is this
a Bastion is a game like that
I know Ina played badges how is it
uh it has a narrator that's like that
like that really
I didn't have that kind of image from
that it has a
sarcastic uh narrator
it has a good name right now
I like the narrator really
[Music]
I I watched like only a tiny bit of uh
Ina streaming that game I didn't hear a
narrative but I guess so that was not
the right timing for it well don't care
if I'm completing the game yes I am
happy that uh I completed it in one
stream today
um
powered through it and I think
especially the first half I did really
well
affected
there is no game oh yeah I didn't play
that one yet I'm looking forward to that
transistor
I would like transistor
transistor game
oh
action we're playing video games
why does it also have a narrator light
that looks very different
from what I play today
it looks nice Joe
it does look nice
yeah I like the character the main
character
I want to look into it I'm gonna watch a
trailer thank you guys for suggestions
some new suggestions how about tunic I'm
working on it
yeah
yeah that was a fun game too 100 I'm so
excited for one workout it's gonna be so
nostalgic so cute so much fun so much
Adventure
um same company
oh
[Music]
recommend I recommend transistor
okay well we're not here for uh game
recommendations right now although I do
appreciate it but right now my brain
um is dead and my body too
I gotta be playing Portal for the last
time playing Portal 2 yes I will with
kobutan as a co-op collaboration
uh in the first week of May
um
take it easy yes you guys too please
take it easy
[Music]
thank you everybody for watching I'll
leave it at that I guess uh sorry I
I wasn't at my best in the second half I
was feeling but not so good
um but I had a great time I'm glad I
finally experienced this Gem of a game
and it was together with you guys it's
really nice to be able to experience
experience so many legendary well-known
popular that are popular for a reason
games for the first time with you guys
you know also like Minecraft and all the
games that a lot of people uh
usually have already played
I can experience for the first time here
and that makes it very very special
and you guys can look at someone else
experiencing it for the first time even
though it's quite a rare thing
um
yeah tomorrow
vital
Duolingo I'll give the lingo another
chance even though Duolingo really
disappointed me last time
I heard the lingo Japanese is pretty
good but yeah the Korean lessons were
really confusing last time because of
the writing system
maybe now that I know it partially we'll
have an easier time maybe
yeah okay okay green burp love no no no
no no no no no no no no no no love is
going too far
maybe we can't say yet at the moment
still hate
maybe it can change your mind but we're
not loving the green bird at the moment
no no
orange bird love yes that reminds me
please make sure to check out the new
song cover from me and ninety yeah
either go to nanaji's Channel or go to
my community board I posted it there or
go to my Twitter and posted it there too
okay stream orange and Cinderella don't
forget about Cinderella on my channel
hmm
you can switch in between okay okay I'm
about to die right now so thank you very
much I'm just I'm so tired oh my God
thank you very much for watching
I love you guys thank you I love you
sorry for not reading the super chats
it's really late I'm gonna do my best
tomorrow all the way
okay
elevation and in German we sell Peterson
imagination
bye bye
and
don't worry guys
even if everything else is a lie
I am I am real real I'm a real Phoenix
Phoenix real person believe in me
believe in me believe
okay
what wait where is the music the music
the music the music like mute the music
there it is
ah
[Music]
foreign