foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
oh
[Music]
wait
it's just the headset controls yeah yeah
yeah yeah ah sorry game is so
um downloading because not because I
just started doing it five minutes ago
no no I started doing it like 30 minutes
ago but uh I was gonna do it a bit
earlier than that but
somehow suddenly
the wait you don't hit the bgm
uh some like on I guess online services
where is the desktop audio what the [\h__\h]
there we go uh don't take my card
anymore I'm so confused I don't know why
um it says this this credit card
even though it's not a credit cards
debit card cannot be used
please contact the
publisher of your credit card to get
more information
but I can still like go shopping to it
normally
shopping with it normally like in the
supermarket Etc
I don't think the bank locked it but
it's weird
but of course I still have
I still have broke
just get a credit card
shut up
it should work it always worked before
and now suddenly it doesn't work
and has expired no it has not expired
yet
but it's kind of annoying because I
tried to purchase something else the
other day where like something through
Google
uh and it didn't take my card there
either and there was no other option so
kind of weird
I don't know what
I guess I should call them
just use cash yeah and what I did is I
went out to the store to get uh like a
you know one of those scratchy cards
scratchy Nintendo eShop Card
um
foreign
Banks since hmm
maybe like
like maybe like
Maybe
12 13 years
and it's such a shitty Bang
it's such a shitty bank but I never like
you know
got around to changing it but it's a
really shitty like local very local bank
chat on screen missing
you
[Music]
star Ted we have big on
um yes open coming oh we finished
successfully download stuff good job
good job
you should just hear me double
um
I'm here to hear the question oh
thank you for letting me say it
certified arm kind of Moon what's that
mean
s
I I have a arm cannon from blue and a
helmet from Sean Eon and
Sean aeon Ian Sean Ian Sean eh
which one was it
gets me confused
[Music]
this has been happening to me when
purchasing streaming tickets for the
festival except it's because debit card
approaches can be used for domestic
purchasing oh but that wasn't really the
case for mine though
oh well
[Music]
um
maybe it has to do with me being or have
been been being have being been
having been overseas
hmm
it came in time for the croissant I'm
happy that you are happy about the
console
um um so I am home
um
I am happy to be home very happy kiwawa
is home
I've uh man I've been homesick
[Music]
um
foreign
but in a positive way that makes me wake
up at five
to eight A.M
and then
yeah go to sleep at 8 pm which is
fine I took a nap so I'm ready for the
stream because otherwise I would
probably fall asleep in an hour
no but I'm okay
um
[Music]
well I don't know man I have a lot of
tangents
but I don't know is this game does this
game leave any space for tangents guys
do you know
how the babies they're doing
oh man I'm so mad at my bro
yes it does lots of lots of down time
okay okay
um let me just say
told my brother when I came back for two
weeks after the last one month
I told a space like it I told him
because my cats or like at least chunky
wonky had a lot of knots in her fur I
told him what the where the [\h__\h] did you
know brush them they need brushing
um okay I forgave him the first time
because I guess I didn't specifically
tell him to brush them
uh and then he said okay okay sorry
sorry we'll do next time and in those
two weeks I cut out a [\h__\h] ton of knots
out of my cat's Fair ah
laughs
and then
sorry I'm drinking something carbonated
again um
and then now I came back
and
once again
now both of them smoothie and chunky
monkey have knots all over
yeah and I'm like what the [\h__\h] what did
you not brush them again why
and he said yeah I'm sorry
that's the one thing I I just I don't I
don't know I I just can't I I don't know
I don't know I'm sorry I'm like why why
what's
what's enjoy it
um no he didn't seem to forgot for have
forgotten but I don't know he acted like
if it was a really difficult Quest
um cat threatened him
uh I mean the base regular one I don't
think so I really don't think so because
they got so used to him and they really
like him too
um
now I had to cut out so much again
well they still look normal though on
the first look but uh
they're losing hair gradually
love the helmet and Cannon thank you can
buy blue helmet by Sean
anyway
um yeah so my cats are happy though I'm
back and I'm happy to have them back
finally I missed them so much
was so homesick man like
when I lived in Japan before
I wasn't homesick in the like the first
couple years you know where I wasn't in
Hulu yet
but I guess that's maybe because I
didn't have cats and then the recent one
year I got really homesick also because
I couldn't go back to Austria the way I
wanted to
wish you and
yeah now I got really homesick just
because it was too long I mean it total
it was like a little bit more than two
months
oh my God
believe it's some some people come here
and [\h__\h] at me
in the first
10 minutes
for not playing the game yet yeah
chill the [\h__\h] out oh my God you're
making me mad
oh
get out
ah
ah the audacity
um oh I've been playing Fire Emblem
engage a lot
I uh did two
what the what did I call again
prologues
uh uh I did the Sauron one and I did
um what was the other one called
I think I did Veronica
parallels sorry
her looks I think did I do Veronica I
did some lady
where the islands were like separated
and then eventually they moved together
hmm
yeah yeah that's Veronica I guess
yo that one was so easy the islands the
Veronica one was so easy and the
sorry one was so difficult
um
her emblem really good yeah thanks for
the words of a chat
what did you think of Soren I don't know
I don't know what to think of him what
am I supposed to think
Veronica's attitude was like
uh I don't want to be with you guys
uh if anything you should be with me
whatever I guess
oh well I did save don't worry
and then gaming well I guess we're
starting now
oh man I'm like oh
I need to get back into the game
what the [\h__\h]
what's happening
what is this language also I need to
move over the screen
Metroid Prime remastered
oh
a little bit of um history explanation
um in my childhood when I was very young
and had a GameCube
um I remember like
randomly dabbling in the game a tiny bit
but not
in a meaningful way and not in a way
that I know anything about the story or
anything about how to play the game
uh so yeah I was too young and I I think
I just like moved around a bit
but really maybe like always at the same
spot for like five minutes I don't know
so I am a noob I know
[Music]
tonight
yeah we're going in blind you guys are
welcome to help me I heard that it's a
FPS game but it has like lock on
thingies so it's not so bad uh it
shouldn't be so difficult
um
uh are they full screen please full
screen
yeah so also you guys have
a cat only orange
uh armor woman
there's also orange bird woman I am
confused
you missed the beginning oh don't worry
we just got started look we're just
getting started how is she a bird woman
and why did nobody tell me that before
foreign
oh is that her DNA
is that I think that's what or like a
virus or a DNA looks like what is this
oh my God this is so
it feels so old already
uh should I just go straight in is the
audio okay now
is that my DNA
oh
you missed the music
ah
am I the only one in the whole life
who's who's like playing this
oh there's casual and normal it's my
first time guys what do you say
oh right now it's only me day why why
why why
normal
[Applause]
[Music]
casual for story it's kind of
embarrassing
if I choose casual and all of you are
like choose normal and then I go for
casual and you're like she's such a baby
she's not a gamer anymore title revoked
same with Fire Emblem but the Fire
Emblem I actually regret it and want to
make it harder
unidentified distress bacon has been
tracked to a derelict space vessel in
orbit above Talon uh four
bacon hmm
this stressed bacon
distressed bacon
AKA hachamas fans in the first universe
history of human
lash of light from a lone star
the life of a single person should be
lost in space and time but Among the
Stars there is one light that burns
brighter than all others the light of
samosarin as many battles extend beyond
her life
connects themselves into history
here another chapter of that history
will be written
oh
uh I heard this game is pretty short too
so I scheduled it for two times this
week ideally I want to finish it in
those two days
voiceover is new
what was there just like letters before
text
[Music]
oh EU version always had narration oh
well I am European
so wait so humans are dead and Samos is
the only one who survived
well hot body
[Music]
until if I speed run oh
wait what 60 hours no no they didn't say
60 hours what the [\h__\h] is that the Sun
or is that the Earth
yeah humans are still alive I'm a bounty
hunter
[Music]
oh
all right
I think this is
possibly this the area that I remember
in my
in my old good old times
12 yeah right not who the [\h__\h] says 60
hours is that a different Metroid game
I almost killed that plan is that lore I
wanna know more
there are three controls wait a second
press and hold ZL to lock onto Target
where's set L that one the big one okay
oh what if I want a different one
because there isn't isn't there more
and now like it doesn't see that one yet
I have to have it okay like in my vision
oh
well maybe I don't you know
I don't even don't have to choose is
that a goal it doesn't
no okay
hey I don't think I would go for 100
what scan the central pillar to activate
them
use right to switch to the scan vision
scannable objects appear as standard or
crit is am I drifting
is this drifting noise is just gameplay
look I've been thrown into this game and
I know nothing
oh that's just okay
use up or dead r or a to return to the
combat advisor this vision
huh
scanning shooting
[Music]
and locking and shooting and walking and
oh God yeah people say things about
um
using controller for FPS games is
generally rough but
this is how Metroid Prime is supposed to
be played right can I jump oh yeah
thank you Game for just tell telling me
did you tell me that because I just did
it
oh can I jump off though
no sad sad
they added dual stick controls in the
room oh wait how did you do it without
that
damn
uh well actually you know what motion
controls would be really nice motion
mentioned why is there no I want I want
tilt controls motion controls yeah
instead of the
instead of the right stick I would like
to have that
there is oh there is
wow it's me I'm Kenneth just like mine
morph ball
suits
options is it I wonder if it's actually
better
foreign
control scheme using control sticks for
movement and aiming
and motion controls for camera within
the naming similar to Metro Prime
trillic G for we combines classic
control scheme with motion controls for
aiming
which one should I do live controls
based on the original Nintendo game
coverage oh should I do the hybrid one
okay uh
did I activate it yeah okay
it doesn't
it doesn't do it though
how did it just open that
hey
pointer with honey
what was that maybe this one
players calibrate you control it by
placing it on a stable flat surface and
wait a moment okay
[Laughter]
oh no why is that so wonky that is that
feels extreme can I still log on
probably right no you that is that is
like as if I'm drunk
no I can't play like that no
that felt so weird
that felt incredibly weird
um
okay all right uh
I guess I'll just go for the Dual stick
um
what the [\h__\h] the [\h__\h] did I do what is
that I can
I'll go backpack jet pack
oh
that's better than jumping why do I have
jump wait wait it's the same
oh it's the same one shot doors will
open when you approach them
oh
okay
[Music]
my mom by the way was also looking
forward to the Stream
hi Mom what's this
what luck and what is it
oh I guess that's for scanning uh what
huh
what
I thought it was a air lock Repro
repressurization successful repressed
I'm sorry I'm getting confused by the
controls
why is a shooting with uh a H
but scanning I couldn't do away
is that
is that big uh
alien
[Music]
press and holds that L to lock onto
enemies I think I already killed the
thing you want me to kill
yeah I think I already did that
and without locking
scan it okay
what are you
morphology unknown info high levels of
radiation detected
okay
and I'm scared this is a horror game
[Music]
did you see that
did you see what I understood
I'll probably just be spamming
um
z l
so that I I
what's that that's uh-huh door
but I just feel like a
why does this feel like a horror game
should scan that too
subscribe
this is space pirates
that is death caused by Ace Vic Burns to
body chemical type unknown
I'm so scared guys
blah blah
okay I killed it
um the death cause for that one was me
will that be a cold
will that be told in the wait he's gone
I can't scan him anymore
scan like something here
oh I can scan everything somebody said
in the chat cause of death kiwawa
escaped pod launch coordinates
Talon four is that me what
hey just like in my oh just like today
in my new loading screen made by
Olivia's
tail section possesses a mouth like or
advice what the [\h__\h] is that most likely
used for birthing awesome
so
the v-bird
door entrance to deck Alpha umbilical
Hall well there's a lot of weird words
man
I only need to scan red things well
well well it's nice to have some
information
use your charge beam to destroy the
rebel try to just like how do I oh
nice
try to beam oh hi hi
it's terrifying the music is scaring me
can I like Crouch
probably not I guess otherwise the game
would tell me
not yet okay access to deck beta
approved please step into the hologram
oh
press y press one well the game didn't
tell me to do it yet though
can I go back
oh yeah yeah
yeah
yeah good luck oh
and then become normal again
wow where did the little spider thingies
go
press X while in ball
poop jumping jumping jumping
can I do something else oh what's that
oh I can fight with like shock waves
charging no
oh
what if I use them all ah they recharge
oh wait did I oh that's just like
oh I can bounce myself
off of it no no
what a ball that's ball just a ball just
a ball
wait how do I forgot
two parasite Queen specimens have become
volatile on Deck Beto I don't know what
any of this stuff means
infestation has been detected in the
ventilation in systems of Dex gamma
gamma and beta
lots of lore here
oh frigid exterior holds stable and
fully functional
what are these words
oh Talon 4 Ground Zero area secure
crater radiation readings normal
is that good
a new research entry has been downloaded
to your logbook
step in the Hologram okay okay
Advanced English lessons yes class of
[\h__\h]
um but he got that I think I heard it in
German before you have done with the map
of it crap I can't speak anymore press
plus to access the map when you're
finished plus press plus because that's
really difficult to say press plus Price
Plus against resume play
um
oh
oh okay I came from the orange parts
right oh God
all right oh rat this is confusing
cool nap though okay we have like a 3D
map we can look at the 3D map that's
like that's next level guys
because this is a really old game and I
feel like nowadays games don't have 3D
maps at all ever like this you can look
at it from every angle
yo
press Plus
yeah
okay thank you
uh
ball if that was the map what was the
other hologram
this
or elevator you have to stay in here I'm
scared
why
I should have done cash
okay
[Music]
thank you for the rest of the chat if
you go back into controls and scroll
down to camera wait aha
to camera
you can turn on gyro Guru with your
current control screen also yes can
improvise Muslim games oh
okay
we've got gyro Giro
uh what is that
wait what okay where's Camera
ah use R to rotate the camera motion
controls are disabled use both R and
motion control okay we can try that
oh
wait that's a million times better than
what I was trying out before
I mean
not a little I feel like this will still
be difficult though what if I
oh
okay we we can try this I think I like
it I might get used to it can I scan
this
huh
specimen containment bridge on Deck beta
all career report for lockdown no no not
again I thought we were done with that
[\h__\h]
okay uh they said a roll so I'll be
rolling
wow
I was kind of shaky though maybe it kind
of hurts for you guys to watch this like
that
I don't know I don't know do you get
like motion sick from this
nothing in there and one broke out oh no
it's okay I'm using it no problem yeah
fine okay
uh I'm gonna you know read a couple of
lures but if I you know end up ignoring
some of them please don't kill me
because a lot of this stuff just I mean
it's interesting but
okay Overkill
but a lot of it has just done well okay
you read it in this like uh-huh uh-huh
so
use l while holding that L to strafe
around enemies what
what uh this is this what you mean
it was a friend no it wasn't
no way
after mutation the current pace of The
larva becomes rigid
parasite
stage
the void sex in the mouth enlarged after
a mutation
hmm
combat mutation applications are
complete
okay interesting
[Laughter]
pupa
laughs
find myself
why is it telling me that I'm already
firing myself of a
thank you for giving me lots of options
though
now there you go do I have help oh yeah
the 98 it's my health
it's the same thing
I mean there's a chart what oh wait I
not that I said I oh
where's the the friends is this one
stronger oh oh wait I only have a
certain amount but it
does it charge itself back up
okay okay that's [\h__\h]
I have to find more okay well
yeah bye
is that a smart thing to do
it tells me there's something to lock on
there
there's something there too
I'm trying to get some Lord dude give me
a break
and this thing's weak
that thing's just weak
it's a little
camera
no problem Oh should have scanned that
one
there's no time to scan enemies have to
kill them
more Oh you mean these ones
morphology plasmines
uh-huh
parasite larva harmless unless
encountered in large numbers
[Music]
cenotropic life form unstable use
caution
native of Talon 4.
the game will give you hints on how to
defeat enemies if you scan them it's not
required well so far we're fine if I
don't if I like struggled with Anatomy
we can do that
oh oh scanning everything is fun but not
required okay okay okay
we can scan the dead bundle a new
research entry entrepreneur okay so does
that work too
why why so noisy
oh it wants out can I stick my my gun
into it because it seems like the
perfect opening for it
[Music]
okay why is it so scary
I think I'm gonna go
eh
missile pickup
feisty little fella
scared let's go let's go how do I go
but this looks like an elevator why is
it not working
ah
let me check this out
that's it
waste removal in three hours
oh wait there's a huh
can do from here
elevator operation please step in the
door no that's what I was doing
easy easy what's that is that whoa
munition
bless this anyway I started blasting
he's holding on to dear life
okay we're good
how's the health ah okay
give me oh yeah
is that where I came from yeah
hello it's like a museum
it's like a nature History Museum nice
oh
doing good so far thank you
people when I first mentioned that I
want to play made for Prime people were
really surprised but I don't know why
you guys are so surprised about it
it's nostalgic to me you know I'm I'm
from the GameCube
uh gdai generation so can I not scan
this oh
that surprised at all Nostalgia exactly
rules me thanks to the memberships
ventilation covers may become
superheated if airflow is restricted
because it's FPS well
I've played like
some games
in reactive ventilation system
security codes on other turrets are
changed every other lunar cycle
frightlift I'm a Nintendo person that's
so true yes I am
[Music]
plus it's sci-fi yeah but really in this
case
um the fact that oh what is this
the fact that it's a old nostalgic game
for me
from GameCube is just overpowering
everything else
I'll pick up oh
space pirates number one death caused by
a severe leg let's let's let's look look
yeah
and that gamma approved blue stuff into
the Hologram wow
stepping in
School
let's go let's lesserations
um
I knocked my knee against something
under my table what the [\h__\h]
uh
uh for Fest ah thank you I already
talked a little bit about four Fest in
my after four Fest stream after the
first day door lock enable put some
certain metallic sphere to Open Door you
mean my gun
my surprise
[Laughter]
you look great at whole 2017. thank you
uh if you guys are you know weren't able
to watch it live but wanted to watch The
Vault it's finally up now
so you can watch it now
[Music]
the horror and Metroid Prime is me
what
yeah it's not though
it worked for me
space pirate removal of internal organs
who did that wasn't me
definitely not was this energy now flows
through a series of locking mechanisms
on the door's surface
you step into the
stepped into the Hologram wait is that
not what you want oh wait so something
about uh become ball
maybe yes
ah
become as ball next time I stream this I
will not wear the helmet I will just be
a ball okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
laughs
monkey noises yeah sorry this is just
how I play games when I panic get used
to it uh draw in pickups with a
give me
what
wait I just saw my eyes
but now I can't stand anymore
and oh my God I'm pretty
[Music]
that was kind of scary the first time
did they do this in the GameCube version
already
this creature looks like it struggles to
get for the store
[Music]
yeah well this device does not seem to
be functional there must be something
nearby that will turn it on
maybe I become both
well I think that's the perfect shape
though what the hell
oh maybe oh Shockwave how about
Shockwave
no it didn't work I thought I'm genius
or maybe this
don't lock enable please insert my
channel but I they say it in such fancy
words but just say ball
hey but wait I want to go this side
which side should I go
maybe the Sun
oh what is this
Blue Dolphins I thought so
no no no no no no
save for though what you can't save at
any time damn old games where you can
only save
yeah damn that really was a thing back
then GameCube games can only save and
specific points and nowadays you can for
most games save wherever the hell you
want man
good old times
[Music]
okay bye
oh there's a Metro thing
maybe they just like to keep tradition
same
and bye bye bye
well
yeah
oh no oh no oh no oh no do I have to
fight that now
oh no it's too big
spicy funky it's kind of I think it's oh
I am finding this but I think yeah when
when there's like a blue thingy I can't
L and tap l so that's wild
what I don't understand
oh I don't know
uh
[Laughter]
Genetically Enhanced by another means
what the [\h__\h] weak spot has been
detected in this creature's mouth use
your auto targeting to acquire this new
Target okay
wait I can't shoot when it's blue right
what was this about fashion oh my God it
can't show proof what I can
I need help when it's dying I'm fine
chill all is good oh my God you little
[\h__\h]
sorry I'm so [\h__\h] at this I'm so [\h__\h]
I'm so sorry I'm gonna get used to it
hmm
I don't play games like this a lot you
know
I think it would be easier on PC but
immediately
okay where do I go
the way I came from
[\h__\h]
[Music]
do I have to dash because I don't know
how Color dash
okay okay
I'm in the hologram
there's all this okay okay okay then
what was that about with the tapping
[Music]
please heal me please heal me
uh is the time gonna be a problem
can I please why didn't
oh I can go up here maybe
okay oh my God oh my God oh my God
wait
it's like Outlast now
am I going the right way oh my God
okay they don't do much damage we're
good
don't look back don't look back
[Music]
go the right way
it keeps on repeating I'm in an endless
cycle
I can't be a ball
are you okay no
no I'm not okay wait I should have just
got become ball and then do the shock
wave that's AOE pretty sure
now there's no more of these things wait
let me test it
does that work
maybe not
oh Bow go lucky balls oh oh oh
oh my God this is so mean
oh [\h__\h] my health why is it
[Music]
okay bye-bye
hey wait am I gonna feel this
please don't fail
[\h__\h] man
wait I'm gonna die what is this what's
going on
[Music]
this way
Oh No
Maybe not maybe not
that's so stressful
[Music]
it's like a metallic dragon
put nutellas on
grapple grapple uh
oh it's an elf oh
no time to waste
I can't read this [\h__\h] now
look I got any time for this now
[\h__\h]
please let me go
why why
is he died
[Music]
oh my god that hurt my back
why am I losing my armor no I'm
downgrading
vary a suit [\h__\h] Morpher no
no I'm functioning oh but I'm back to 99
health
everything's malfunctioning
is that is that how it's supposed to be
[Laughter]
why is it the [\h__\h] maze here
oh I'm scared
this way
aim don't go
I'm outside
[Music]
oh I lost all the superb yeah
oh what the [\h__\h] is going on
I think we did it we saved yeah
one straight no two strings two strings
am I doing really bad so far
do I need free streams
your ears are bleeding ah I'm sorry
tracking on enemy target has been lost
ground-based reckon required beginning
Landing what
and okay fine
tutorial complete
okay
oh I like this kind of area more
I thought
it would be in that like Spacey area the
whole time
because that's all I ever saw from this
game
oh
gonna be a lot less stressful thank God
was this a stress test
Talon Overworld
Helen
what's a talent
the game is far more chill oh thank God
that was called the plan of this Talent
okay
uh-huh
so glad to see you thank you
uh time to explore new access unlock the
main menu do you want to say it I guess
so
let's do it
wow
my spaceship yo
killed us like a beetle
oh I can't charge now I wanted to see my
pretty face again when I can
wait I can't be a ble but there's
something down there that I want
well maybe that's one of those items or
like well part of my armor that I need
to retrieve but I can only get that one
if I already got the ball so let's
remember that one
see how my my
RPG mindset immediately looked for like
something in the back that you normally
like probably don't go for first if
you're unexperienced but in now you know
no
no Chihuahua goes looking for those tiny
spots you know look up in the sky
why
very classic matchword yeah those are my
exploration instincts yeah
[Music]
I like the music
where's this stuff so blue
blue Mansion sweet
you can swim I can well by default I uh
diet
instead of swimming
what I thought maybe I would get like an
electric shock
oh
what's this this would be a good place
for a movie theater
oh you guys must probably be feeling
like some really nostalgic feels for the
speed Jam aren't you I can imagine
where am I I feel like I'm not going
where the game wants me to go
what the [\h__\h]
not a second time
[Music]
Platformers man
I fell down again no that's okay can I
go here
no I can't
okay let's go back
dangerous mushrooms
need ball
maybe I should go where the game wants
me to go
how do I know where the game wants me to
go
maybe up there
probably up there
okay
wait there's a couple of doors actually
so I guess our Focus now is to retrieve
our powers
oh
what do you tell me again to look at the
sky there's nothing there
what
are you telling me to look at the sky
my instincts tell me to always scream
at first just scream but you know it's
not because I'm scared it's my tactic to
show domination
and make the enemy scared you know
certain animals
before they get in a fight in the animal
world they just make loud noises at each
other to assert dominance and as a verb
I have copied that technique as I found
it very effective
in my private life
just scream at everything
monkey strategy not only monkeys but yes
there's many many animals who use that
no a new creature's entry has been
downloaded to your logbook okay oh wait
wait wait no one more time from the
beginning please can I have from the
beginning sap sack
you believe it thank you
not just a scream it's the war cry yeah
you can't you can't spell takana without
ah yeah yeah
chemical reaction within Sac reduces
violent explosion when agitated because
of its irresistible odor and sweet
nectar
the sap sack was nearly eaten out of
existence the evolution of an explosive
chemical sack saved it now only Brave or
ingenious creatures dare to devour it is
that a description of me what do you
think
can I eat it
um
[Music]
no I don't think that was a description
of me after all
oh it's like a durian ah
hey oh there's another one
okay range
wait is that why you wanted me to look
at the sky because I just saw some boobs
what the [\h__\h] oh what was that
what was that
sorry I need to stop screaming like for
real it's exhausting not only for you
guys but also for me
what is it with you huh
Nani
huh that little [\h__\h]
it does not want to be
[Music]
that seems mean why can't I kill them
no I I shouldn't
he doing now
I didn't think
you know
oh two birds with one shot
[Music]
even though my aim wasn't that good uh
where did I did I come from there
[Music]
wake up the others what do you mean wake
up the others I'm alone at home
with my cats
and they sleep through literally
everything
is it dead it's dead
wow
wow look behind me why they're so scary
why do you say such things
why why why why why why
is why is the grass moving like this
ew ew why is it so Wiggly
it's kind of disgusting
ew
and
[Music]
come on
scan it
ticklish
oh tangle weed plant life with basic
sentience retracts into ground if
frightened tangle weeds are only
dangerous to small organisms they are
covered in tiny Barbers designed to trap
potential
means
scan the door
okay uh Tango with black strength to do
anything more than in the larger life
forms
cute I guess
there is a blast shield on the door
blocking axis analysis indicates that
the Blaster is invulnerable to beam
weapons of explosive weapons may damage
it what about my charge
oh wait I don't have to charge anymore
so I can't do it
um
work again I don't think I have one
[Music]
um I don't have myself
I don't have nothing
whether it's [\h__\h] now uh so why do we go
now maybe hey which way did I come from
uh how do I look at the map again
just why everyone else just dies but you
you you you you on the other hand
Plus
[Music]
I think both doors are unexplored so
if I re-enter the room will all these
things be recharged or can I see it as a
sign that I haven't been here yet
like this
room's reset oh
access to chosen ruins West Grand Theft
please stop in the hologram
[Music]
where am I going
oh it's me
my eyes
will I ever see her without her complete
armor I wonder
whoop
whoop people people people
dessert
incoming Scandal abnormal seismic
activity
disturbance at Rune side
detected should I really be here
that's the in-game hint all telling me
to go there oh it's like a beehive
what
um
what is this
am I in uh the yellow one why does it
look like this
seismic uh
okay
no more birds
for now
wow we're selling a desert
stop seismic people I said seismic and
everybody's like seismic
whoa
but this game really looks pretty for
being so old nice remaster
nice graphics
seismic
um
why though
why
oh
[Music]
no no come back come back
you cannot Escape
original still looks good
I mean this is probably how the original
looked like to me back in the day
you know how things just like in your
memory look so much better than they
actually wear
okay another door and I cannot open I
would like to retrieve something now
enemy coming in three two one
oh really no jump scare
[Music]
the sound of a power up
that was the sound of a power up the
little sound I heard
was that what that looks like
something that belongs to me
yeah
what could that be
how do I get there can I can I yell
I need to
yes okay
uh The Last Resort cannot be reached
from this room oh okay but what is it
let me open okay well okay okay but it
didn't tell me what it is
um
[Music]
did I come from here
no
what the hell
that did a lot of damage at once my God
okay is it recharging that little [\h__\h]
is recharging it
so young
yeah I feel like I need something else
to be ready to enter that I don't feel
like I don't think I'm ready
so
oh my God I did it I did it
but look at my HP man
it's rough
honey
saw that coming
scan the wall
there's a safe around here
wait why you no picky a poo
thank you
oh wait there's something up there's
something here
what is that
we will get there
somehow just follow the path
scan wobbling
you said I don't have to scan everything
which wall
hmm
hey on a mobile organism's entirely
composed of ocular tissue a capable of
launching sustained energy beams when
active the Aeon is sensitive to light
and will close shut if a bright flash
ignites nearby
well we will
on that one
many long years ago many long years have
passed since we chozo first took root in
this land
passage of time has always been a source
of Fascination to us it is the belief
that of many shows or sages that the
truths of the universe hide within the
tumbling currents of times flow even as
we search for answers there however we
find Illumination in other unexpected
places we know not how the ability has
come to us but recently many chozo have
begun to sense things beyond the realm
of ordinary perception strange sights
and inexplicable Sensations flood our
minds filling us with visions we take
this growing ability to be a sign of our
burgeoning harmonization with the
infinite perhaps finally the universe's
secrets are becoming known to us
am I chozo I think I'm chozo right
I think that was good lore
it's kind of lore that I want to say
partially you knew one usually high
concentrations of pores and identify in
three leaves
so guys what was your favorite
performance of um day two
[Music]
day two of the festival
from wait what day is it it's Monday
right so I'm talking about yesterday
oh that's definitely it's difficult
right it didn't feel like okay it felt a
little bit unbalanced to me
day one versus day two already the the
first time when I was told you know
which day I am and who's on day two I
was like why is there so much more like
overseas members on day two right
so basically on day one
all of En members were put into one unit
while on day two they were spread out in
like three units
I already pointed it out when that like
first was told to us but like I mean I
had no influence in that
but I did like my unit so I mean
it's fine I was happy with my unit
but yeah for me like you know
when
um
this first came up
we were like you know able to give
suggestions of we would like to of what
we would like to possibly do in terms of
units ill
um and I think I wrote that I would like
to
um
I would like to be in a unit with energy
or or hold a 20 something
by you know
oh honey did I just activate that
anyway nothing like that ended up
happening
but I'm very happy with my unit because
I mean it would have been interesting to
see like
in Japan ID Etc combinations tool right
but oh well
it was fun to do ah something with mume
and Ina and amen
give me that give me that I don't want
to fall down
why
and I fell down
no save good luck with the Boston hey
what's
Up We're Gonna Save buckle
at least I got a treasure I got a
treasure
what does it say
[Music]
s
what about here
oh I think yeah
only on hatchimal only on hatchimal was
yeah a cool combination really
surprising I didn't expect that one at
all
um
but that was day one day two for me was
uh the Highland I thought caught on
there like overall like there was a
section where they did all these like
meme songs
felt like you know a meme section
5 and some other Mimi songs
or perform coordinate was basically just
sing like a commentating a horse race
look at over there can I not come from
here
yeah and then Corona said by later on
appeared in a unit which also did a meme
song
it was so funny to me if you understand
Japanese it was definitely a million
times funnier
hmm
such a comedian
yeah
oh [\h__\h]
disgusting
why does it not lock on for them
there you go I killed them all
Gamers have a special place in my heart
so true so true what is this
thing why is my boss space astronauts
that's what I am today
on a mission
[Music]
am I back on track now
but okay really stole the show on day
three
day three are you joking there was no
day free
day two though didn't she
free was what he didn't want to stay for
it wait a second oh I can't open that
one either
oh yeah
we told you what they free they first
but man
I actually I wrote
some of my thoughts down of day two I
think oh no day one
what what what what what
you see
yeah yeah yeah
uh uh oh yeah one of my favorites of uh
day one was also Risa once again you
know she just did something incredible
showcasing her singing skills
was really nice like I think last year
and this year everybody says the same
thing
about lisu that she's like underrated
but well
not last year like she should be she
shouldn't be underrated by now anymore
we already know she's amazing I know I'm
not underrating her I am definitely
rating her
how she's supposed to be rated yeah this
is so incredible and then you know
singing was like so pretty too
um sorry
you know like damn she knows which songs
to choose
which songs really fit her voice doesn't
she is this the boss room
and I'm his boy was so funny man I'm
stuck
I'mma went like
off in the beginning at the end
it's so cute and the hearts are my only
combination was like so [\h__\h] crazy
every time
every time they screamed I just bursted
out and laughing like what is going on
oh I'm not supposed to go into the water
right
yeah
okay I don't think I'm I should go into
the water can you guys not fly around so
fast
oh
[Music]
it's such a cute song the last year she
did
and this actually had her original song
isn't that nice
oh nice shot
I hope this movie uh you know next year
if there is a next year [\h__\h] you
yeah
maybe next year I would love to be in a
free portion for once
um because that means you can clip it
on YouTube I wish I wish I was in the
free section
what the [\h__\h] why was I able to capture
them so easily before and now I can't no
no no
[Music]
no no no why why are they so annoying
my hand hurts
oh what am I getting back
oh so that was an easy boss what the
hell
[Music]
they know I'm worth the money hmm
still that that doesn't really mean
anything because all the ones that they
showed in the free section were also
totally worth the money
to switch back to beams missiles can
destroy blast shields on Doors
additional data downloads to inventory
screen press minus to access the
inventory screen
yeah
let's go finally finally oh another
thing what's that energy tank acquired
let's go they cry huh
yeah they crack down on clips from the
free section last year for real
[Music]
um
maximum energy temperature increased by
100 uh energy you mean my health
can black just
he blinks
oh missiles
sauce
oh ball hole and I I can't be a ball did
I come here too early
it's freaking me out that I can see her
[Music]
use them against strong enemies oh guys
oh
oh did they create me a path well thank
you
oh sure
what was I gonna say
I have to walk back
for real
I missed
what was I talking about I'm about to
free section and besides that what was I
gonna say
what they're gonna say
uh
just my thoughts yeah hmm what are my
thoughts
do I even think
ah
myself can destroy house oh The Deco
concert oh yeah well
[Music]
oh that was cool I'm really honored to
be part of it and uh yeah ghost rule
it's a really cool song I like how the
audience went like
[Music]
yeah that was nice
nice audience participation
very happy to be involved in that more
holes for balls but I am not balling yet
warning warning what are you warning me
about
it was a great duet thank you
but it made me realize you know well I
already knew this I guess but standing
next to mume in her default outfit
mine looks so simple and hers is like so
big her hair is so big and flowy her
Cape is so big and cool
where I came from here
and then I stand there with a
Silhouettes are just so
different made me feel a little bit uh
lame
you get another 3D outfit one day I
believe
um
who knows
oh yeah what about this door can I open
this door now
no
foreign
I like it when we were all you know
wearing the idol outfits that was cute
everybody was matching for the whole
concert
and oh yeah now I remember the one on to
say it's like when everybody was on
stage
uh it seemed so funny to me how this I
feel like it wasn't so apparent last
year when it was just myth and id1
but this year it's like
you see
ID 2 and counselors standing next to
Japanese members
and the size difference is isn't it so
funny
some of id2 and like Reina actually only
Lena and then uh Council race so many of
their like body proportions
are
so different
they're so huge they're so big fauna is
big uh crony is big and has these like
really thin stick legs
and then uh
iris is huge too and now Cali's size
also stands out to me how do I get up
there
how do I get there should I just
continue going back
yeah I didn't expect Iris was would be
so big either and fauna too
um
I need a ball as well oh man okay so I
should just go back
okay
oh [\h__\h] you no no no no we're not doing
that again
uh what was I saying
on the other hand
I just love this difference so much
what the [\h__\h]
them
you know looks just so tiny now without
her huge heels doesn't she I love that
in the I love face I love feet yeah she
is just wearing the same shoes as
everybody and now she's suddenly so tiny
uh
so cute I would like some health please
her true height yeah
gosh they all look so tiny next to me
didn't they
in the in the en units
[Music]
they look so tiny
now
[Music]
I look so big
where do I go now
you little [\h__\h] here we go
was there like a door that I couldn't
open before
[Music]
I can't I still know how to get up there
I guess we could try going
where is that
no no no no no no no no no no no
okay thanks for the membership game
thank you those books are scary and they
come out of nowhere
excuse me passageway to Shrine a shrine
oh yeah this is new door let's go please
give me ball I want my ball back
[\h__\h] by the way now I'm fine but so
many times they just feel so much of my
HP
I see therefore [\h__\h] them
[Music]
I can't even properly because you killed
on so fast
we have to like
re-aim every time
listen I want to waste my whistles on
them
oh there's a ball hole again do I have
to
throw the ball later that [\h__\h] sucks
oh but wait my ball is there
no no no no no no no no
these blow-ups seem to be simple light
sources oh okay I thought it was
something more than that
okay
what about these
oh this is also for ball
wait can I just take it no way
[Laughter]
yo
ah easy
just keep on like
running around them
circling them yeah
oh okay I'm gonna tell you guys some
stories now
um so one story I was hoping to tell you
and we
Miss
wanted to go on a trip not really a trip
though
um
we wanted to go do something special
together and we like reserved a day in
our schedules one day where we all had
time it was Africa pretty
[Music]
okay it was after the the 3D showcase
and it was really the only day so but we
wanted to do something together you know
so we had this like locked in our
schedule for a while and we wanted to go
to Disneyland
should I just stay still and wait for it
to
you why why is it so annoying ah
okay I'm gonna wait
double tapi
ah
I practice dashing all right all right
be good
so I have been to Disneyland and Disney
sea in Japan uh many times and every
time I went it was just you know you can
buy tickets in advance sure but you
don't have to like not at all you just
go there and
you're in you just buy the ticket there
and then during the sea times the
seeping times
um Disneyland in Japan locked down
closed for a long time
um oh can I open that
and eventually I don't know when it was
but it was really close for a long time
eventually it opened back up
to something
how do I get up there
oh wait haha I want to go here
[Music]
don't kill my momentum
Pro what boost ball upgrade oh what I
can't deal with this Eva
okay
we go back again
and
so yeah anyway we were all actually
really excited to go to Disneyland and
then and then on the day before
I'll [\h__\h] on the day before
you know we went on the Disney side just
to check you know
and we were gonna reserve some tickets
and then it says
Disneyland Disney sea basically
sold out for the next upcoming
weeks
I was like what the hell what even now
it's a preservation only no tickets
available at the venue
so that was uh kind of disappointing and
then we were like hmm
all right what else can we do
we want to do something really fun right
so hmm
we're doing a funk
and then I suggested one of the things I
suggested but didn't think the girls
would go for
was uh to go to Osaka for Universal
Studio
because it's quite far though
is quite far with the shinkansen right I
don't know two and a half hours three
hours how long was it again
but basically it's Disneyland but the
better
um
I've been there before too many many
years ago
um
um but we had some other ideas too uh
like that would be closer to Tokyo
should I try I don't know
surprisingly the girls were actually
really interested in the idea of going
to usj so then we tried booking the
tickets for that but the usj website
also
seems to not have any tickets available
also booked out on the day before
on the website so again we were like
but we want to do something fun then
next idea was how about checking if
maybe the tickets would be available not
on the actual website but like as a
package like from some kind of travel
agency or something like that because
I thought they probably would have some
what do they just spawn industry they
probably would have some some like
certain amount of tickets uh reserved
for other websites to sell
oh [\h__\h] you guys
I want the I want the HP
them
okay this is a new room oh wait ah the
Vermont for that is new okay
well okay ball
yeah and so we did end up getting
tickets by choosing you know a different
size and I wonder in hindsight maybe
that would have worked with Disney too
but at that point we were all just
already booked the tickets Kelly booked
them for us
and then
uh kind of spontaneously suddenly
we offer
Crow need to join us
and crony accepts spontaneously to go
with us on the next day early in the
morning as early as possible on a
shinkansen to go to Osaka go to usj with
us and then go back on the same day in
the evening
yeah it was myth
and cronini and it was my first time
it's not so happy
for the opportunity yay I mean we
offered like basically whoever wasn't in
Japan at the time we offered it
yeah and crony joined us yeah
yeah I was so excited and I was like
really nervous too some of the members
apparently have already seen crony at
that point like Cali for example but uh
I haven't
so yeah I was really excited
um
yeah now we wanted to go there really
early and I did some research like that
how the [\h__\h] what what when I wait what
do I do
I can't go that far and the water hurts
me doesn't it
it's so dark too don't kill the bugs oh
Something In The Water too
did I kill it
I'm confused they're providing light
okay
I guess so as long as they don't hurt me
um but what
I can't jump that far
oh he's thriving on energy percentage
okay that doesn't help me
[Music]
no no no
I don't know
big fire plus yeah oh thanks for the
memberships
um
what
half on the right
it ends here though
oh bird lore
yay chosen script translated this oopsie
sorry the search is of negative energy
brought by the meteor far exceed our
expectation
we chozo have yet to find a way to rid
ourselves of the great poison all we can
do now is seal it away and wait for the
day when a power to purify the poison
appears however it is already impossible
to collect all the pieces of the great
poison as it has already spread seeping
into the planet and hardening
poison
oh maybe this jump I can make
yep okay
I need something here ah
who the [\h__\h] was that
ah
we good we're good
wasn't there something for me to pick up
in this room though
can I not reach that what was that
a little box yeah
bugs
anyway
um
need ball upgrade for the oh Kai
Marshall
warning
um mysterious
was I saying oh yeah oh yeah so I looked
up you know of course oh
I don't have like the heat thingy right
so I can't go here either
I'm guessing that looks like I need like
my armor upgrade
okay
yeah where do I go
that's kind of annoying
let's go here
maybe I'll get my suit here
yo
okay I did research because I wanted to
go to Nintendo World uh because I happen
to
to usj before but never to Nintendo well
none of us has
so we wanted to go
and I looked up like you know how
difficult it was because I mean at that
point
already exists for a little while
um
but I expected it to still be a little
bit difficult to get in so I was looking
on on Twitter for like people who
recently went
oh
ah yeah and I found out that if you're
not there at like 8 00 am
or
maybe at the latest at 9 00 a.m maybe
you still have a chance maybe
but otherwise your chances of getting in
are practically zero
should I jump
it's almost me what is this
[Music]
sounds really strict well
strict but they have a system that
actually uh same system as usj in
America as well for Nintendo World right
now foreign symbols in this room must be
activated
how do I activate it is this one of them
well that's not how you activate it
apparently
yeah I did it just by scanning it oh
okay
[Music]
no
can't be
anyway because of that I wanted to be in
like a really early train even though I
know
I don't sleep you know it was a long day
the day before and
I know we were all gonna have troubles
waking up so early
what's up
um so we ended up taking a train that I
don't know how late but definitely not
at the time that we originally planned
that's right though you know
yeah we gathered at the station and then
we took the shinkansen and we had some
troubles with the tickets
Etc being the gaijins that we are
um but then you know we also all wanted
this equiben uh like those typical
shinkansen
food lunch boxes right
hmm
so ah we bought some bentos I went for
like an unagi eel Bento
uh I know that you know next to me um
I'm in crony was sitting next to me in
the train so I know what the other uh
what they ate or like chronic crony
didn't eat anything she couldn't eat at
least not for now
uh should I
maybe ball
oh yeah
all set I'ma ate like a big mixed all
kinds of funny things Bento she had like
everything that was a good choice of a
icky Ben I would say but whatever things
you picked up she first showed me and
she was like wow what is this and I'm
like honestly I don't know
because all the things that you have in
your Bento
all right the things I would normally
not need probably and they looked like I
don't know I had no idea what that was
but it's so cute first she would ask me
and I have no idea I'm so sorry I
disappointed her
so then she would ask crony and crony
surprisingly most of the time knew what
the things were damn currently more
knowledgeable about Japanese food than
me what the [\h__\h] is that
that's one of the runes
no no no not that this one
no that which fouls the waters seeks the
Sun
is it the mushrooms
it's a riddle
safe station to the right
wait from here or
this one
okay I thought I would go there later
[Music]
foreign
um I got the fancy one crony wasn't
eating anything for now
and then behind us were the others
uh
give me
yeah and then
um you know since that was literally
like I just met crony
uh throughout the whole train ride we
were like chit-chatting I was trying to
get to know her ask her this and that
yeah
yeah yeah
I made a lot of notes of that day by the
way but right now I cannot look at my
notes
this world is kind of big man
I don't know where to go
I can pull the pickups I guess so oh
I told me that before
[Music]
we're playing a horror FPS platformer
now damn all the things kiwabo loves so
dearly
oh
yeah eventually we finally made it to
Osaka basically me and Ina were like
leading the way most of the time it was
like they were our children me and Ina
were on our phone on Google Maps trying
to guide
getting the right train route oh [\h__\h]
you
[\h__\h] you
so mad
for everyone yeah I activated one yeah
wait but does it count is it the same
room
as the other one oh my God my face
so I had to go down anyway maybe this
was uh
maybe this was
it's a different room
what do I get if I activate them all
oh [\h__\h] you oh [\h__\h] you oh [\h__\h] you oh
[\h__\h] yeah
[Music]
how to
to not die
[Music]
you suck
run at my feet over there
wait I'm scared I'm scared now why
oh there
oh yo two on the floor thank you
I wouldn't have noticed that
um
thank you stop it
oh God I'm so scared I'm gonna die
okay I'm at the beginning of the room
again
how do I
have I get up there
I hear
you're sure oh
this is very dangerous 16 HP is like
nothing
I have 160.
little squares I'll have two HP bars
oh okay then
can I just jump over there as a bone
oh ah wait this won't open unless I have
oh wait a second
one is here
okay I need one more
that looks like this okay
huh
probably not on the floor again
of the room
wait
front hort
ah thank you this room always gets
people overlaying well and I don't feel
that stupid but it was fine it was fine
it was fine
ceiling fan thank you
yeah okay
we're leading the girls
to the
usj Universal Studios Japan
um but while you know while we were
doing while we were on the train and all
that yeah Strong high percentage of this
region okay is that a boss behind that
is that what you mean
um we were trying to figure out more and
we downloaded that app you need for usj
and found out that you know you can't
even register there's like the system
okay let me explain just before we go
into this let me just a little tangent a
little bit okay
I think you guys want to know
um
oh [\h__\h] never mind
we're good
uh
just a little tangent
okay thank you
um
there's something happening here isn't
there
a tangent in a moment
Maybe
thanks for the memberships oh my God
even more judge me let's go
[Music]
ah good morning sunshine
was there something behind me oh yeah uh
let me just quickly write that
disaster struck suddenly we had a vague
dark four budding and it became a truth
a meteor appeared from nowhere casting a
dark shadow of debris over the land with
the violence of its impact its
destructive force spent the Fallen star
burned itself out rapidly and the
incidents should have faded into memory
but the meteor brought with it
corruption a great poison burst forth
into the land a strange energy that
clawed a natural life with ferocity
that strange negative energy emitted
from the meteor expanded to Encompass
Talon 4 in the night as the spider reefs
of web web
oh
should I
I wonder if I can just roll through this
because that's quite a lot
okay I made it
[Music]
oh trash beam just kills them no hold up
oh well I did it hard mode
am I done with this room I thought I
could maybe roll into the snake heads
there but
hmm
I think you're done okay come back later
okay
so basically maybe you guys know this if
you already went to Nintendo World in
America by any chance
but you have to
download the app for usj
and
then you have to scan your ticket
so that the app know which one is yours
so we scanned all of them on one phone
because we wanted to be able to register
as a group
but then you cannot
um enter the
what do you call it Sadie can what's a
Sadie can in English
um
sorting tickets
because first at the start of the day
they give out sorting tickets
but they are gone so fast because the
people come early in the morning right
in the first probably 10 to 30 minutes
all the starting tickets are gone after
the opening of The Venue but you cannot
try to get it before entering the venue
because you scan the ticket on your app
and then it will know when you entered
the venue
so then
once you're in you can enter the Sorting
ticket from you but if you're unlucky if
you're too late and the Sorting ticket
system is already closed then next they
will have a laundry system where
um you can choose a time slot to enter
the lottery which is like a one hour
time slot
and and it makes you think or it made us
think okay we enter this one hour slot
once and if we fail we enter the one for
the next hour how about that
turns out
once you enter that one Lottery and it
gives you the
um the uh uh uh
results which is with a very highly
likely chance uh oh no you didn't make
it
um then you cannot enter any other time
slots anymore it's one
time one time slots that you can enter
with your ticket once per day
after the the Sorting ticket system is
over changes to the lottery eventually
even the lottery system will be over and
everything will be given out
and then you're done you have you came
to usj and you have no chance to get in
there
yeah so you have to be really there at
the beginning of the Park opening
otherwise
you are not getting in there at all nope
nope nope nope I've read that the
chances of getting a place in the
lottery is really low like they probably
only
have a really really really small amount
of tickets they give out in the lottery
um
it's the same for usj for Nintendo World
in America right now so if you're
planning to go just be prepared you
gotta be there at the park opening if
you want to get into Nintendo World I
watched a whole video on it on the
system
um yeah
but it's okay you know we all want to go
into Nintendo World but
I I thought that you know even if we
don't make it I'm personally like okay
with it because there's a lot of other
fun stuff to do there too and originally
we were gonna go to Disneyland anyway so
you know it's just we wanted to go to
some kind of cool theme park so it's
okay
and I think everybody else was okay with
it too because there's lots of other fun
stuff there to do and yeah
um so we entered the park
we tried entering you know the thing but
we saw okay we can only enter the
lottery then we tried that's the first
thing we did we just immediately entered
the lottery we thought that maybe we had
one try per time slot
um so we entered one just a random one
first
um
then we failed that one eventually we
were able to check back later when we
were
standing in the queue what is this
half corruption leads if ever higher
no okay
I need healing I'm down to my other HP
bar yeah bye
goodbye
wait how do I get even higher can we get
much higher
oh
wait here sorry I'm blind
I'm balling
yeah and then you know what we did then
we first of all had to buy you know the
typical cute accessories
we had to
oh
so we went into the shop
the first shop that we saw
and oh there were so many choices so
there was like you know Mario Luigi
stuff and all that and then there was
like Elmo and Cookie Monster stuff stuff
like that and and I I wanted I felt like
the the Mario and Nintendo things where
should I go where kind of
gonna go there no that's why I came home
we're kind of
big and they look a little bit annoying
to wear and I actually I don't know if
you guys know
but I actually really like Elmo
is there a safe point
where
say if you say but where
yeah I really like I didn't I don't
think you guys knew huh down yeah I'm
fine oh am I though my HP is so low I
might not be fine
foreign
[Music]
it's right below
oh wait no
to the left to the left
down
and I have to go all the way back again
oh well okay so I really like Elmo
actually I have to I have to say this
now I really like Elmo Elmo it's also
kind of like red orange
at least the accessories of him were
like a little bit kind of red orange
like Elmo
and turns out
Nina likes the Cookie Monster guys
Anna likes the Cookie Monster
you know what that means
you know
you know it was like I don't know which
one to get I want the Cookie Monster but
I also want I think she was thinking
about getting one of the
uh Nintendo World hats she was thinking
about it but I was like if you're
considering the Cookie Monster because
they were like the same kind of like
katusha
um headband type and the Mario and Luigi
cell phone's hats big hats wow and I was
like hey you know you should I was like
pushing her to get the the cookout
I felt so slow just now did you get the
Cookie Monster thingy
um
gosh I'm confused where do I go
where did I where
ah here oh sorry I lost track
[\h__\h] Platformers
um yeah uh I know Cali got like a Luigi
hat
this and that but you know I think the
only ones who got something matching
were me and India because she did
end up going for the cookie
cookie wear head band and I had the L
you guys to do fan art of that please
thank you
I was so happy
and I had actually I was wearing a uh
twin Tails so please make that accurate
in The Fan Art thank you
yes
[Music]
yeah so cute
I was so I was really happy to be
matching with someone
go artists go artists
go on this
I give you freedom to do Eno's hair but
I feel like it would look cute if she
had a ponytail
in a ponytail oh my God can she please
eventually do that as a hairstyle for
her outfits please please please please
please please
it that would look so good in a long
straight ponytail like oh I wanted her
in like a school uniform
and uh long straight ponytail but that's
just my personal
thing that I want personally
right
oh where do I go
now
ah you guys haven't seen me yet yeah
yeah didn't someone say the charging is
this too far oh no no it came in I don't
understand
why is that one not coming though
oh wait now
why did it take so long to come
excellent taste buds thank you
okay I'm gonna go this way first I guess
oh wait there's more
yeah
so damn
um you know we were still in the very
beginning of the theme park so we were
just like starting to discuss okay where
should we go first what should we do
what
what is this big eyes oh sorry
what are you Stone told praise and
creatures smiling himself vulnerable
only from within so I have to be eaten
oh I can become bald oh I can't shoot me
finally regurgitate don't use their
tusks as a last resort in combat okay
but what about this side though what is
this
ball
uh-huh okay uh-huh
well then shoot me
go
how old oh that does hurt yeah what did
I do that for I thought it would help me
or should I wait it said we've been it's
I can hurt it within I can't go back now
maybe I should have activated my my bump
inside right
I thought it would shoot me somewhere
where I couldn't go without it but nope
oh
oh no oh no eh
look at my HP I'm not ready for a boss
fight dude
[Applause]
that [\h__\h] wasted
[Music]
oh
go
no no no I want to kill this
okay I'm okay I'm okay we're good we're
good
[Music]
hey give me help
what I do in this stage
ah okay
um no wait I have one more bar wow when
did that happen
[Music]
okay I absolutely hate this fight
because I want to aim at the stupid
bees wasps
but I can't
am I even making any progress right now
oh my God I might die
[Music]
oh I didn't die
this is so stupid
that was a stupid fight
don't like it
I was sick
clutch
one more ball modes
why must everything be so difficult to
say in this game
ah ah now I can do the bombs oh wait I
couldn't even do that before then when I
was in that monster
we didn't even have that possibility yet
this one right
camera
okay take that down
what is this
oh I must make this explode probably
probably
structural weakness okay I got you I got
you
hey let's go escape oh what's these
songs
choir
maximum missile carrying capacity
increased by five oh nice soup
all righty danke schoon
ER
back going back
ah can I maybe have some
some more can I break this too
some more HP would be nice but
I guess not
oh that wait
sometimes it's like kind of dark
and I thought I could jump as a ball too
why why not same button
um
I thought I could jump even without the
bomb
I felt like I did that before
wait which where did I came from
oh
come on
wow this game is kind of annoying me
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
but I have to redo the boss
oh that [\h__\h] triggers me really hard
that triggers me really hard now
what if I say no
so annoying
that's so annoying
[Music]
that is so annoying
ah
where the [\h__\h] am I
eh
was it this way
was it this one
I have no idea where I went
up
hold on the Wind
well
I guess
let me continue to tangent then
reminds you of your first time of this
game
why did
[Music]
it
no no no no
oh just just note
[Applause]
[Music]
I didn't want to continue with so little
help already
good
that was
it's a bit [\h__\h] poison water
just because you didn't recycle properly
more
you're killing the Earth
anyway so
yeah so we we um
we you know me Ina matching yeah cute
um and then yeah we um checked out where
to go first and then I was kind of
scared so so basically
um out of all of our group
I inquired cool is good with roller
coasters and who isn't
turns out
crony says she's totally cool with it
she likes um
the big challenging roller coasters same
as Cali
gouda AME
the only chickens
were me
and Ina
which again
made me feel like oh
me and Ina
we're just so much alike yeah matching
headbands matching chickens yeah
so I was really relieved because I
didn't want to be the lame one and I
also didn't want to force myself to go
into the really scary ones
um so we said you know we don't have to
go into everything together right we can
like split into groups
every once in a while maybe
so that the uh even though we
don't we adults because we were leading
the children around before
in this case I guess you know no no
we let the children play in the
challenging big jet roller coasters
and and the the parents me and Inna
we would I'm going somewhere else than
before now huh
don't know where this leads
we would um go take it easy you know
yeah yeah we're gonna let the children
do the dangerous stuff yeah yeah
too old for this [\h__\h] you know
yeah I get it
so I was ah I was quite happy with that
I felt like at least I had Ina
it was nice to have someone because I
don't know
people do it I don't know how people do
it ah but not yet okay when I'm back
and then
um we at least want to do some together
so we thought okay well let's do like
one
together and we were like walking
through the park and just like oh I
guess I was um
I I don't I don't I don't know how the
girls even put up with my [\h__\h] um but
everybody agreed
with my idea of how about we go do the
Minions right first
of
I uh yeah I suggested uh well if you
haven't been to usj before then you
maybe know what the Minion ride is like
it's it's uh it's one of those rides
where you sit in a room in like a
roller coaster
seats but it's not a roller coaster it's
the illusion of a roller coaster and
this is gonna trigger me so hard again
[Music]
but I would like to scan it
wait let me read
device skips indicator
but can defend itself
that doesn't help me at all
[Music]
wait I'm focusing now
okay this actually helps with having
Additionally the motion control
because then I can like
somewhat quickly
switch over
oh whoa whoa did I am thought that fire
where is it
yeah
[Laughter]
oh
[\h__\h] yourself ow
that was so much uh better than last
time at least
okay
wait
okay so minion right you sit in like a
theater kind of thing in a in a roller
coaster scene and it moves along to what
you're seeing but I like these kind of
rides I like them and I don't
think baby-ish because honestly
okay riveting too
I would say
you didn't hug the fire this time a few
times with him
those rides yeah
quite something too I like how they they
actually this one was incredibly
immersive I'm telling you
I really felt like it was so immersive
But first you know of course every
single [\h__\h] ride even this one
um Q time was 90 minutes yeah
Japan
[Music]
um but before we went in
um we actually uh didn't actually not me
just the others they all got like some
Minion uh meat bun
minion nicoman
and I finished eating gudas because she
she's I don't know
so she left like a tiny piece of uh meat
bun
but the way she ate it normally you guys
know what meat buns Japanese
um those typical meat buns look like I
mean I guess they're not Japanese but
you know
um it's like a hand hand size
bun with meat inside and normally when
you bite into it you just eat it like a
sandwich like from front to back but
gouda ate around it for some reason
she ate all the way around it and then
with some at some point she had only a
little bit of the middle left and it was
like the meat was spilling out because
she was eating it weirdly and then she
was like
[Music]
and and you know I was actually you know
I didn't wanna
um get my own at this point because I
actually used up all my cash for the
ticket and I was trying to save money
because I ran out of cash and I didn't
want to borrow too much but then you
know she was kind of like feeling like
leaving it and I was like okay okay how
about I eat the rest so I ate the rest
of her
of her bun
yeah
but it was so messy
how sharks eat meat buns
where am I going where are we going
well it was yummy it was really yummy
and also my goal for the whole day was
eventually finding churros the whole day
I just wanted to eat your rose
um but in the beginning we saw like one
um stand that had churros but it had
like an insanely long waiting line
because it was themed it was like a
themed shirt well it's not just normal
churros I just wanted some normal basic
damn churros
oh wait why am I back here
indirect kiss well perhaps
so we hate those
um those those little meat buns what is
it what this camera where am I supposed
to go I don't I can't move the camera
there we go
why can you not move the camera when
you're in ball mode
hmm I I hate this too like I get greeted
by these [\h__\h] I can't really do
anything because I'm a ball
and now we do this
wow what is this
I think the skin
I can't ah there we go
um basal systems appear to be a
provisional device should operate once
power has been restored what is this
though what is it
foreign
[Music]
wait I'm not gonna just where do I even
go
but wait
okay wait what oh was I supposed to go
here
[Music]
are we good vegetables
now and now
[\h__\h] camera I swear to God
[Music]
Where'd I go
should I just be not ball
maybe just not ball is okay
[Music]
does this go away
or maybe it does for sure okay okay I
did it
I would like to save to be honest but
priorities right now are somewhere else
wait I'm just back here
it's done
honey
was done
I thought that was it so I was chilling
because of that what if I start here
can I
I can't I can't I don't think I can
what now
oh but the water is still drained
oh wait I mean that's so lit up
no pressing y does not
make me jump
that's the second part right
okay
X okay
all right all right all right uh
which way
ah here
foreign
[Music]
I got lost and I fell down
[Laughter]
oh man
hey
Elsie Mamma Mia
I'll make it this time I will I will I
will I will
four times a charm so okay so we ate
something a little bit a small thing and
then we
um started standing in line for the
minions thing 90 [\h__\h] minutes every
[\h__\h] attraction at least 90 minutes
nothing shorter than that unless you
wanted to go on a real kids ride
yeah but it was kind of
oh the waiting part oh it was so funny I
really wanted to tell you about this
um
uh
at some point in the minion
waiting line thingy pretty much around
the end
you know they show you the skit this
video
they're like you know starting up the
lore
the story
for you to enjoy what am I supposed to
do
and then
what was it they're like trying to
banter with the audience like at this
point there was only a few people in the
room because it was already like we were
sectioned off into a group
and they say the minions I don't know
does somebody know has someone had done
the Minion ride before because I'm
pretty sure they have the same yes
minion lore they have they have the same
ride probably in American News Jane
so basically there's this guy I don't
even I haven't watched the Minions movie
there's just that right
um who controls all the minions and he
has actually three daughters
so they're like bantering and then the
the
uh they talk about someone being now
first they say oh stinky and they got
they're gonna like fart and but what
comes out is actually the smell of a
banana like it actually smell it
um in the room and then I don't quite
remember the dialogue anymore but they
said that someone here hasn't showered
for weeks
and then
camera and we laughed so hard because
they literally
oh my God it was so funny
oh stinky
[Music]
that's so hilarious
called out by the minions yeah then we
went on the ride am I just going back
now am I what am I done with this room
what's going on I'm I'm lost
I'm lost
I'm just lost
what is this room
what did I do this for
just police
there's a new door I can access
I don't know which one
new platforms
oh wait that one
okay okay
oh
next to Cali
uh in the ride
um and and I think maybe you know I
wasn't
sitting on the sun I'm not sure
what is this
do I do like a wall jump kind of thing
go safe word save point
oh it's okay no need
uh we're good now oh my God what the
[\h__\h]
spooky
increased by a hundred
oh I have two HP bars now a free I guess
okay
yeah and Kelly you said it was really
funny it was sitting next to me because
no actually
wait maybe it was crony sitting next to
Cali I don't know but whoever said on
the other side next to Cali all of us in
the front oh I think right to my right
side may have been amen
Anna was kind of like chill about it the
Minion ride
but me and Cali and whoever was sitting
next to Cali we were so excited
and screaming but especially me though I
was like
I was having a time of my life but I was
also terrified because I mean there are
some moments
in this ride too that make you feel like
you're dropping
and and and you know
oh where'd it go right now
I can't see [\h__\h] because I said to go
back
why the [\h__\h] did I go back
to safe but well I mean when you guys
say go back right after I've been in
this place then how the [\h__\h] do I know
what you mean
okay
confusion
so yeah I was like clinging onto Cali I
was screaming I was oh I was laughing I
was having the time of my life it was
really really good I felt so immersed
because like the screen was actually
really big
and it felt like there was like so much
going on I felt so immersed into the
Minion ride man oh it's so good
it was really good
where to go next
maybe uh this way now
like that's where I didn't go yeah
maybe where the effects like wind and
water spray I think wind yes oh wait no
not here but water I don't think there
was water
I'm done with the room okay
well well so I mean
I know it's not as like exciting and oh
[\h__\h]
as like the cool roller coasters that do
like 360 and all the ads but I think
it was fun
like that was fun
but the Highlight was the call out about
not showering
but well
it was it was intense it was more
intense than I expected but maybe not as
challenging for the others
what is this
no charge beam
the Highlight was the cute nah I mean I
wouldn't say that
but like oh it was so cool it was pretty
cool okay minion red was pretty cool
am I on the right track guys
what about where did I come from from
that side right so I should try to get
into this little blue room here
is it
yeah is it down there
[\h__\h]
oh yeah yeah okay
[Music]
should be that door right
save doku
h
remember
I'll go save I haven't saved in a while
I will go I will go
Mickey Mouse
yeah yeah
um yes I want to save let me pull up my
usj notes because I wrote some notes
what did I write down I I wrote down so
many notes because I knew I had to tell
you guys this story
um I made a joke uh at the
shop you know where you can buy the
accessories and
um I just want to say
before you guys say oh my God kiwama is
so mean chroni laughed and I said this
joke really carefully because I knew um
I need to test the waters with this one
I'm not sure if that one is gonna come
across the way I wanted to
um I just want to say you know chronium
couldn't enjoy the joke okay and
laughs
so in the shop one of the things they
sell besides the the hats
for like Luigi Mario and the Elmo stuff
and all that was
you will know you will know immediately
what I'm going for when I when I say
this one word
no they don't sell Subway no no no
um
it's gonna sound so mean though maybe
but that was you know
ah
so
yeah like a a full-on hat that covers
your whole head and under your chin a
jaw Jaws hat
so shark right so I I'm like hey me and
Nina are getting to have ones the cookie
monster matching ones so how about you
crony and gouda get matching Jaws happy
now because good as shark but you
yeah
and she laughs
[Laughter]
long and what does that mean look
I don't know I I I I I I I
I I just I
it's not that bad right
isn't it kind of fun and funny why am I
why am why am I I didn't know this would
lead back to this room but
I just want to explore the room that I
haven't been to yet
it's not me if it lands it's not me
right yeah
oh my God okay not even close to being
mean okay okay okay okay
uh where is this
one more thing I want to say about crony
doll
and she has like a big eyes her eyes are
so big
and and her smile is so pretty like when
she smiles
I love her smile so I wish I I said she
should smile more
I told her that she was kind of I guess
uh
embarrassed or flattered oh [\h__\h]
but worth it complimenting chronini
worth it
I went
he did not threaten to kiss her no why
why would I
oh by the way we also were really lucky
because it was a really good weather
so thank God
it was really good weather I I went
without a coat
quite lucky
so yeah we did the Minion ride and then
after the Minion ride
um
we did ah we did it this one's also all
together because it was really close we
went for what is this we went for what's
it called it's with Dinosaurs uh
what's the dinosaur one called
yeah yeah
so Jurassic Park is an actual roller
coaster uh but no no it's not really
actually no I take it back I take it
back but an actual roller coaster in the
sense of it's outside in an actual
moving thing water ride yeah it's a boat
ride but it has like one big drop and
and one small tiny drop but that was
even a big drop it's not that big but
you know you're writing something okay
yes the River Adventure not the the big
one where you it's not a really close
again yeah
and the Minion ride okay
so we had another like 90 minutes wait
on this one
[Music]
and yeah it's kind of man so much
waiting time right after the other one
kind of lame
excuse me I have to spider ball
technology required to access track can
I do that
am I spiderball spiderball do whatever
spider ball can
am I wrong
don't why did you guys don't tell me to
not come here
no missile expansion hmm
we were listening to the story for this
one
I have to go back here again
foreign
yeah okay
okay
fluid patterns analyzed what
main source of toxins detected
oh
why are you telling me this now
yeah lucky I didn't fall into the deep
part uh okay I guess we're going there
next yeah yeah yeah
[\h__\h]
warning
whatever what was I talking about oh
yeah crony cute
funny really cute
um
I feel like
crony for me is way easier to read when
together in real life because now I
realized you know
her expressions
add so much to like what she says and
the tone of her voice
like often when I would just hear her on
Discord
I wasn't sure like was she you know
having a good time like if
you know I was getting worried
but then in real life I it didn't worry
me at all because she may have had like
a sometimes a little bit of a monotone
voice and all that but but then with her
Expressions it really helped me yeah
yeah yeah yeah deadpan it's hard to tell
on Discord only voice only
so now I'm a little bit less worried
because she laughed at all my jokes and
made me feel quite relieved
foreign
that sounds like a good plan yeah good
luck hope you can get a ticket
[Music]
what was I saying oh yeah we went to the
Jurassic Park Ryan and we all
uh a hundred percent underestimated
how wet you get from this ride
because like in the line oh wait I just
noticed something in the line for
Jurassic Park
there would I don't know if they have
the same thing in America but
they have
a
they have vending machines that sell
drinks but also
ponchos yes ponchos
passing by like we don't need ponchos we
don't mind getting a little bit uh
you know
a little bit wet no no problem I mean
we're not like [\h__\h] we're not made
out of sugar what the [\h__\h]
um so we didn't buy any
oh
later on I kind of regret that decision
[Music]
got really wet
um
my hair man I was so
so my best to find my hair on this day
how do I move on
I don't see the path am I blind
supposed to get well yeah I thought so
too you know it's just nice to be a
little bit refreshed but it made me so
wet well
like this
oh wait I hear I didn't see that
ah
yeah but you know once it was finally
our time and the ride arrived and we
were supposed to sit in
the seats were I mean out of plastic but
completely soaked like
the whole
like area when you sit was wet and I was
like how does it even get to that point
when people sit there
how is that possible
how is it wet where people are supposed
to sit
up
yeah no it was one all of it there was
water everywhere so then we were like it
[\h__\h]
again I sat next to Cali
and
you know Cali of course she's like
absolutely enjoying this ah doing it too
so basically most of the ride is just
you sitting calmly looking at dinosaurs
and I was like damn I
I only watched the first Jurassic Park
movie when I was younger I think and
then and nothing ever after
scary
dangerous to switch into a ball there oh
wait I was supposed to go here
uh
[Music]
guys tell me to look out for the Hoops
oh man can I scan anything from here
one is here
well I'm missing too
where
where where where where where
yeah
oh where oh
what the [\h__\h] is that a word was pipe
primary war was dwelling only vulnerable
to heavy Weaponry oh I can shoot this
okay
so what now
okay I have to backtrack because I am
missed two of course I missed them
all day
maybe somewhere in the ball sections
no
should I climb again but look for things
to scan on the way up
um
[\h__\h] them should have just done it the
way I did it before
foreign
ER hate
former hate
I will not let that ruin my mood right
now
even though it's [\h__\h] triggering it
really is very
concerningly triggering
yeah we got wet
like for real like oh my god I've been
on rants like this before maybe long
long ago but I I really underestimated
we got really wet
and I remember good as ass being
drenched
uh yeah my hair was drenched
yeah
um
it it's uh quickly dried off though so
we good we cool
no problemo what the [\h__\h] am I looking
for guys
but when on that one small drop you know
it was really like you knew when it was
coming because eventually you so slowly
went up the mountain and I knew like
okay I was mentally ready for it but ah
[Music]
it was like so
um this is why I don't like um roller
coasters but like when you drop my heart
like it just stops and it feels like
everything is like my body is falling
but my the insides are going upwards and
then I first I scream for a few seconds
but then I just I I can't like I
literally lose my voice and my ability
to scream and I'm just like enduring it
so I even during that short one short
drop I clinked on to Kelly's arm and
like hit myself I I just closed my eyes
and and lowered my head and like yeah
held held on to Kelly with my life
hmm
on the bottom below the wings the Red
Wings
it's not the one I don't have yet you
want them
I thought I already had this one I guess
I didn't
oh oopsie
hold on to death holding on to Sweet
Life but by holding on to death maybe is
not the most effective thing to do
I had that feeling so much yeah me too
but okay this one was short so it was
bearable but it was funny because we got
so wet man man
it was funny
so all is good but that was really salty
because I had hairspray in my bangs
and if it was just normal without
hairspray then getting wet wouldn't have
been so problematic but it really ruined
my hair
for the rest of the day
I was pretty salty about that
go safe now to be safe and where where
is the save point why can I not
why could I not get out of my body I was
pressing y several times
see I don't care about save point I
don't care
I just want to move on famous last words
I'll be fine I'll be fine guys what
oh what am I doing
oh that works that did work
I'm scared doing good I don't know
there aren't any before the bus you have
to go no I'm not going back
I'll be fine
I'll be fine I'll be fine
oh you kind of have to go through this
one fast don't you
because everything grows back
why no skin
did it heal me it did heal me nice
and now I'm really nervous because you
guys tell me to say
I'm so nervous now
I'm full ice cream oh my God it's big
big I'm scared I don't want to [\h__\h] up
it's big
the kite
it's like the big boss from this map am
I ready for this
scanned
fly grab
yeah
let's get it
how the [\h__\h] do I scatter me
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
you guys tell me to scan it because I
know what's gonna happen this is what's
gonna happen
I just wants to kill me I'm just gonna
blast
how do you do that the thing again where
you like smoosh from one side to the
next how do you do
it
how do you do the
face thank you
oh [\h__\h]
I mean there must be more than just
shooting to this because what's with
these things
I couldn't even do [\h__\h] yeah okay while
it's in this face I probably have to do
something
with the solar panels
um
but I don't think I have practice again
and I always wants to attack me
uh grows like a husband radically
accelerated as a result it requires new
constant exposure to some attitude to
remain active this exposure has made
flaggers outer shell thick and durable
it's lower root system is unprotected
and vulnerable however yeah exploit this
flaw when possible concentrated weapon
fire
can dance it for short periods okay but
what do I do when it stays
I shoot the roots where
okay
[Applause]
ow what the [\h__\h]
ing speed
okay I should solar panel next time
[Music]
I'm shooting solar panels
what I'm doing wrong
from behind the song one okay
we're so slow okay
what why is there nothing there why is
it only certain Sumo panel
already never mind it doesn't even have
to be here
you can do it anytime
sorry guys I'm so triggered
[Music]
do we just repeat that again and again
or is there a new
kink
oh
there was something there [\h__\h]
okay
uh-huh
[Applause]
[Music]
okay okay
uh another one
oh
I couldn't stop so fast what the [\h__\h]
your [\h__\h]
I guess I have to do I I thought I could
do it even without stunning it but I
guess I understand that's why you have
to stand and we're just gonna flip it
back I might die
I feel like I'm faster like this but
then again the switching back takes so
much time
yeah
how do I do it
back again
I wish I could Dash
I need to go back faster
please win
oh at least it's focused on me now go go
go go go oh did we did I do that
I think I did it
[Music]
I hate myself
I understood too late I thought he was
just doing the thing
no I'm gonna
die I hate this
please stop please be nice to me
[Music]
I'm sorry guys
I'm sorry guys I couldn't do it
[Music]
can we do it where do I go
la la la
don't give up yet
[Music]
is there a food place
is the third phase
yup of course there is same system but
four no way not four is there four
phases
oh no [\h__\h] way
for this [\h__\h]
is there no way to like get some HP here
[Music]
did I [\h__\h] do it just now did I just
[\h__\h] do it like like excuse me
did I just absolutely slash and smash
them crash them
with full Focus now let's go is there
don't tell me there's another there's no
no more right there's no more
[Music]
oh now I'm gonna die now I'm going to
die now I am going to die
don't don't
know
okay we absolutely have to do it first
but how
how is there possibly enough time
I just have to I think I I think he will
at least although now he's busy we're
doing that
okay okay
hi hi I'm here I'm here please do not
please do not do anything
I did
it
guys where is it oh guys all the way on
the other side
[Music]
why is the all the way on the other side
[Applause]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I'm so triggered I'm so
triggered I'm so triggered
it's ringing cause I was doing so well
this ain't gonna laugh and that was
literally about to finish
[Music]
I'm gonna cry a little bit
what the [\h__\h] no
no
oh tears in my eyes because that was so
mean
hey
what what part of the game am I
what did I do and what did I didn't do
well do I just have to do the big
a big room again
all of you
where is it oh my God now
oh that's so triggering
launch ring around
I should have played on casual why did
you guys tell me to play on normal
I don't mean
wait scan [\h__\h]
monster
all right
I'll [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
no I always knew what triggering meant
I'm just being specially triggered right
now
so that it's worth actually using the
word
oh [\h__\h] hell
it's so tilted yes I'm so tilted
I will get him next time of course I
will
foreign
[Music]
man
oh being such a mean game
points and such an
cient places
don't you agree
did I miss a scam somewhere
I mean there's one up here somewhere but
did I miss anything
yes
did I miss something
down one step
um
[Music]
my hand hurts
uh
no
I I don't remember
triggering [\h__\h] game oh my God I'm so
sorry but this is
up slowly get up
see this is why I should not play FPS
games because they trigger me too much
because I suck at them and then this is
what happens and I now have to take a
fruit candy because it's been triggering
me so hard that I've been screaming so
much
platforming and FPS though
the worst worst possible combination for
me
and horror but not so much horror
anymore only the tutorial was horror
so triggering
if you don't lie to me I'm not doing
well there's no way that this is doing
well and in what world is this doing
well
elsewhere
not this world
I know I'm not doing well
I'm doing yes I'm doing
do you think other players never die no
I think they do but
as a streamer
I get
like judged more
if I don't do well and
then that also triggers the player of
the viewer
when I must have missed it again
I must have missed it again so I need to
do better actually
for the sake of the viewer oh wait it
must be here
yep
okay now I got them all
so if I want to save
I have to go back
to the previous room
that's so stupid
yeah okay I'll go back that's so stupid
though
that Landing yo
was it this wrong
room
wrong room
[Music]
oh sure okay here
thank you this boss killed your three
times
really
see you guys will say stuff like this
but then I think still the general
conception is that I suck
laughs
I hate those mushrooms
okay uh
I will now that I know how the boss
works
will have an easy time
destroying it
thank you guys thank you thank you for
your patience have you guys has anyone
played the remastered version on their
own yet
anyone who's given it a try
yeah I beat it only OG and we
only OG
waiting for physical copy oh
I never buy physical copies these days
I loved it on GameCube when you still
remember everything from the GameCube
days
I could never remember
yeah physical copies I mean they're nice
to have whoopsie
haha
good
it's kind of mean that the boss I mean
you know same point is far away okay but
then at least
wouldn't it be nice
to have oh [\h__\h] you what what
[Music]
wouldn't it be nice to have at least
something that spawns a HP regeneration
somewhere
in exchange for having to save quantity
so far like just a little bit I'm not
asking for
spamming me with it like Zelda games but
okay even Zelda games don't actually I
wouldn't say there's Batman
right
but you know
I wanted to make a joke
oh was there something and I didn't see
it thank you for the pinky
all bosses except this guy does
well well well
uh
wasn't there where are the
oh
so unnecessary
[Music]
okay okay okay
isn't even that good in this game
it's not even that good
because even when I see something it
doesn't aim what I want it to aim at
oh well
let's go
my headphones man
yeah I think it's kind of funky
sometimes
let's go guys
I will you know the problem is I wasted
so much HP in the beginning because I
didn't know
how it works but now I should be fine
it's just one or two now
okay only one now
you see
this part took me like 10 minutes before
okay not 10 minutes but
it took me a long time
you see it
no
okay
two panels
save the bowling lanes for the last
minute
out
I don't know how to do that and what you
mean but uh
foreign
where are we going this time I'll go
here
try to flip the last mirror close to the
last route
uh oh oh okay
[Applause]
so that I don't have to go all the way
around anymore
I thought they just um
I thought it was kind of random where
they I don't know I don't know
brain brain horse
[\h__\h] you
oh okay
hello
[Music]
thank you
chill
[Music]
[Applause]
oh oh
that oh wait it goes up with the the
solar panels also go up with a charge
beams
um and I'm just gonna choose this one I
don't know I can't think like which one
is smart to do at last and therefore
which one I should do now I don't know
I can only hope
it doesn't happen again that was the
smart one to do really okay
now it's final face oh
[\h__\h]
I want to use the charge beam because I
saw it one hitting
oh I think I did I do it okay
I'm here I'm here
please look at me please please do not
do not do not do the thing
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
I don't know how to do it
I mean I I I can probably brute force it
but what I'm trying to do is uh
something else
how do I get it it's uh attention away
from it oh
it's again
um maybe I'll just
for fun we're fun
I have to go all the way around there
but he stopped now he's stuck now he's
done now
okay wait which way with this one this
one
all right
second time is just so easy compared to
the first time
forever don't say it took forever that
was a normal amount of time that it took
and I did well
foreign
[Music]
that thing up there to pick up
rolling
thank you okay okay no nothing
my adventurer
uh inside of me wants to find everything
is that the heat armor
my shoulder pads oh magical girl
transformation
because you see in the festival once the
unit uh songs happened
the moment we appeared
the bows the extra bows were loading in
and I was like thinking it looks like a
magical girl's transformation because
we're like in the middle of
of adding more onto US wasn't that kind
of cute hmm how that was happening right
in front of your eyes
[Music]
yeah where was that one that I saw
may I save because one time the game
offered me to save even though it wasn't
a safe point
thanks for the Super Chat
[Music]
oh
that water
it ain't safe is it
water fine now it's clean now oh
Waters oh there you go thanks for
telling me chat end game
whoa
can I drown though what the [\h__\h]
am I drowned
not that I want but I feel like I'm kind
of stuck it scares me can't really see
well on the water
foreign
does she have endless breaths
what the [\h__\h] is that
yeah
oh
um
why is it such a cute name live form of
raw energy periodically releases
explosive segments pulse bamboos are
energy beings and vulnerable to most
known weapons electrical energy can harm
them however they lack any intelligence
Beyond an instinctive attraction to
other charged energy sources possible
moves produce energy constantly all
excess energy is shed regardless of who
or what may be nearby
um
no
okay I'm just gonna walk by but I'm
wondering does the the thing the attack
that I can do as a ball does that work
because that looks kind of like a
electricity oh I can't hurt them at all
yet okay
um
am I supposed to fall
what
what the [\h__\h]
yeah ow
[Music]
what a warm welcome party hello
everybody thank you thank you for saying
hi
indeed are they just gonna spawn
endlessly again
no no they didn't I thought they would
okay fall damage also not a thing here
incredible
how kind of them
what is this some kind of cult ritual
altar
no it's an elevator maybe but wait
before I take the elevator should I
foreign
[Music]
that connects to the other
rooms where I have been before
I'll go here first Maybe
what
oh wait there's a hole for the ball
fan I like being a ball
s must be one of those snake womens
you know those that always show up in
those big America's Got talents talent
shows
who can like bend over their body in
Ridiculous Ways
how to open
oh Lord
what control that's what you call that I
call it snake woman
samus's birthday and I'm not saying I
know but maybe maybe half bird half
snake
the future is a vague thing ever
changing and always in doubt even if we
chosol could gain the ability to foresee
the future it would be a hollow gift for
we could never hope to control what has
yet to occur the fountain is an example
of this the day may come when its water
dries up and there is nothing we could
do to stop such strategy but we do know
this unlike the uncertain flow of water
the power of our will is strong and
enduring the will of the chosen will
never run dry
I like this kind of lower stuff
these metal gates block entry to the
center of the room
um can you not please
Spirit of free locking mechanism still
Decay The Log is active on this key slot
is open should I um get into it
I can't jump that high
looks like I could fit in theory
oh
what
now
I did something
bump jump
s
what
oh
ah
I know
how do I get to the top
um
come on kiwawa
I'll do it
mid air bump jump
Place let's Jump Place bomb then jump
again
Champlain some
whoa
cute yo
[Music]
yo a lot of good night now yo this is
this for example
that's it it's just voluntary though
right like you don't have to get the
studio the missile expansion
but
recommended
okay I connected the rooms so I guess I
can go back what about should I go here
before I move on
into the other blue rooms that I haven't
seen you
um
keep going energy tank up ahead okay
but somebody said don't jump
energy tank acquired I can't get into
most of them anyway okay
so should I just walk back
always grab missiles when you can okay
I will try
yo yes
very very necessary I want to make sure
I get all of those don't want to miss a
single one so please guys
scream at me if I do miss one
uh
can I go this way
oh yeah oh yeah that's where I came from
can you hear the street I can't hear
them yeah yeah yeah yeah totally
if you try really hard
if you all join in together then yes
okay next we go this way
scary
don't fall
nice kind of a cute puzzle
wait was it right to go this way or
should I was there like a way to go to
the right side too no
gosh the face face is freaking me out
the face is so spooky
what does that do
anything else
oh this room
well why why did I come here for again
is there something I need to pick up
here that I couldn't get before
well back to Ian I'm about to eat okay I
thought you know because there were two
pups maybe I want to check them out
before
um
going on the elevator
and what is this connection for it and
just for later
shortcut for later okay
um
okay
here we go
time to scan
and access to my mug more caves whatever
okay so it's getting hot now
the real game starts no no no no no
don't say that I made me feel like I
made no progress so far
a safe is very close okay
complete after the actual
have one is complete
say that now
whoa that's a tutorial I did some
intricate stuff already
where is someone
bonking
up
[Music]
feels very um
like
Boss music
[Music]
I like it
nice OST
challenging
but with my current progress guys
do you guys think I can make it in two
streams I mean I guess it depends how
long I'm gonna play today
but I was hoping to end the stream in
and out no no no
[Music]
yeah
free minimum this is so for real for
real
I should have started to stream earlier
a little while okay
I only I only am scheduled two for this
week so I guess we got a schedule number
two for next week
that's a lot it's all right
I don't mind it's taking longer I just
expected it to
be shorter
I guess I'm just that bad
maybe there's a different way of doing
it and I don't have to waste my missiles
but whatever I never use them anyway
looks like a lever but I guess it's just
a light
[Music]
I guess better the more I play I guess
so
oh
oh the magma is looking good
getting hot in here
but please do not take up all your
clothes because it's protecting me
oh yeah yeah
yeah
no
but a little bit of a bulky enemy
does it come back
it's getting hot in here but please
don't take off your various suit
I am getting so not hot because I have
my suit on
where's where
Miss
you're too far you can't reach me with
that fire
yeah I like the music
come on does he recharge in the in the
fire
oh that's surprisingly not as painful as
it looks like
oh
man that's a good suit
oh the music is picking up some rhythm
yeah
nice what is this hey
skin
so remix from Super Metroid really
analysis indicates a viable attached
point for the grapple beam ah your
grapple beam was damaged damaged from
the explosion on the research really got
it and cannot currently be used yeah but
for later okay
lay down for later
ouch
I can make this jump
and go
that's it for now
I guess the grapple is just a kind of a
shortcut then
to get over that section easier
okay I see I can roll through that
let me look at this first oh
nothing to look at
scan the bugs okay
[Music]
try clubs hard shelled creature with
powerful jazz
joke
the triclops is a hunter gatherer it
collects small creatures and bits of
food stuff then deposits them
Elsewhere for later consumption the hard
tripartite mandibles it uses to move
Earth and rock are quite strong and
difficult to escape once ensnared
that did not really help me
but it would tell me how to kill them
but I'm guessing
what
it immediately caught me I didn't even
I didn't even notice you little [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you no
that
[\h__\h] that little [\h__\h]
hey
why
damn bump before it gets me
there we go
I got one
yeah I
am a restaurant and I'm I'm a I'm a
Karen
or I'm the one who got too drunk in the
club
but that never happens because I don't
get drunk and I don't go to clubs
like automatically
[Music]
it's not fair
okay okay four
their reach is just too big man
[Music]
you want to speak to my manager my
manager has I think today a very
necessary
um day off
first forcefully because
she has been working too hard
way too hard and she she was working on
the weekend on one or two hours of sleep
throughout the whole weekend
even though already before that
she wasn't running on much sleep
felt so bad for her man
I hope she got some sleep now
[Music]
anyway it was nice seeing so many people
so many kfp uh even like in the you know
during the festival
I saw in the Stream they were showing KF
people
before the concert would start
oh it's so cute to see you guys there
and then also you guys showed me so many
pictures of like meetups and Europe and
in America and in Korea and in Japan
kfp getting together enjoying the the
stream together for the ones who
couldn't actually go and get a ticket
and go to Japan
got it
where's the entrance here
smallest way to see and hear you guys
cheering so thank you so much for that
y'all
was so cute to actually hear you guys
get so excited
what's this warning what does that mean
what is a warning when I stand here
[Music]
ah here's the opening
your fantastic thank you too too much
can't speak anymore
yup
nice so
I can't find a crowd was looking right
on both days
and I I recognize them
how how on Earth out of so many people
they could uh film in the audience
how do they on both days choose some
Carefree that I even recognize
Twitter
one day I know it was meringuezan and
somebody was sitting next to my Danga
also with a Chihuahua happy I don't know
who wants that tell me tell me
and the other day it was Gene lowrid
showing off those Chihuahua
uh like doll armor that was Paul
ah
I got a we got to sit together that's so
sweet that's cute I like that it's fun
to
be there with uh someone you know
with the same Oshi scream and cheer
together
am I supposed to go for here
seems so
honestly now that I got the hang of it I
like this little
thing with throwing bombs at these
little bugs I like it
and it made me feel so proud and so
happy
to have camping be actually represented
because I know you know
in actual numbers I don't think there
were that many
I just don't have you know that much of
a big Japanese audience as Japanese
members do of course
um and that's okay but you know I I felt
so so proud to see them there
represented
and and thank you so much for like
showing your love for me
so proudly openly and
yeah not only during the festival when I
saw you guys were doing like an offline
meeting in Japan and also outside of
Japan you guys are just so tasty hanging
out together doing stuff together
really cute
and in Japan they went to a dark Spa
right
I was watching you guys
went to a darts bar and and it was
filled with kfp and then outside they
also took photos outside of them walking
around
almost all of them wearing orange where
where do I go
where is the exit
foreign
you keep passing it on your left
left
left left
ah here
it's so Invisible Man
can I
fill these holes and then nope
man it looks like I could just
okay I guess not I just it's hard to see
where do what do I do I'm so dark
I can't see
okay
is this what I'm supposed to do be up
here
[Music]
why is this place so confusing to me
crank up the brightness I might have to
places like these
um
uh I guess I just go up
somewhere
[Music]
don't jump
online
I don't think
it that doesn't really look like the
intended way of doing it but uh it works
[Music]
no I can't make that jump
that's too high okay that was not
intended
uh I need to go up here
um but like I can't
I think I need to
make it brighter because I don't see
[\h__\h]
maybe it's my monitor too that's a two
too dark where's the
hell visibility
[Music]
camera
what is that
why there's more oh there's more color
assist
no
maybe there is no brightness option
doesn't look like it thank you Rosaline
thank you
thank you yeah I did so much of fellow
verbs like Louie and and and mermaid
they never had one
why am I here
did I move while I was in the menu
[Music]
this is not the path
what what
[Music]
wait I know it now I know it now
from here
okay I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I didn't
see it from over there I didn't think I
would have to go all the way back
that's it
um I will go back to my tangent
so we did the the the dinosaur one
and we were wet and then after you get
out of the dinosaur a dinosaur ride
what's it called again Jurassic Park
um you pass you kind of forcefully
passed by
oh
some
stand that has turkey legs
huge turkey legs as poof that you can
get oh my God I hate you
[Music]
yeah like actual turkey legs and they
look exactly like those yeah and that's
the first time in my life that I ever
saw like turkey legs like that I think
I was like oh my God these look exactly
like mine I mean I call them chicken
legs just because I can't really relate
to chicken to turkey legs to be honest
because I never ate them before
um but you know it made me really
curious because they look so yummy
they're like they're so big and there
were so many other people eating them it
was like really popular it had a huge
line too
so everybody kind of felt like getting
some
um but some of us were kind of exhausted
and then I think who was that I think
Ahmed offered Maybe
two together with someone else get the
food and we could just sit down
so
we sat down we weighed in while someone
else from the group was getting the food
it's very lean can be dry so yeah um I
I same
yeah impression
um
I don't know I'm not a big fan
it was nice to eat and experience it
once but chicken is better
yeah we never really oh
we never eat turkey
in Austria most of the time we just eat
chicken we don't have Thanksgiving so
that's not an opportunity to eat turkey
for us either
um unless you go out of your way
to get some
um
foreign
a bit hard to eat
um
it would have been nice for some I don't
know barbecue sauce or whatever I don't
know when you eat with turkey legs
normally but no sauce was kinda
would have been nice with some sauce I
think
but you know we were getting worried
about cronini
and so
she actually challenged herself to
eating some turkey legs and she would
like pick At first she was like
um you know trying to get some from me
and I had like I ripped really small
tiny pieces like burp portions
like really tiny like as small as my my
top of my pinky and I would give it to
her and she was doing fine she ate it
just fine yeah no she didn't blend it no
but yes I fed her like a bird mom I was
hand feeding her and got my my fingers
really dirty but I was like she gotta
eat something and then she eventually
like
he ate more of it than I did she did so
well
I was struggling in the end to eat it
more than she does
[Music]
I think she was just really desperate to
have some food she was really hungry
but this is the problem I generally have
with
eating like bone-in stuff chicken as
well fried chicken I don't like eating
bone and stuff that much because
I I don't know it feels so messy to eat
it and I don't know there's like
so many like weird strings and [\h__\h]
um
I never eat it that cleanly I'm so sorry
yeah
I I can never leave it as a clean bone
in the end um I feel so ashamed
so same thing with turkey not only that
but just generally it was really Bland
so Bland so I really didn't eat much of
it I feel kind of bad but at least I had
it once and now I know I'm not getting
it again
yeah
crony and Cali were enjoying it though
that's for sure
yeah so we had that uh oh we all had
those turkey legs and then
um I kind of really you wanted to get
some churros so we were looking for
churros while walking around some more
and looking for another ride
yeah we walked around us Jay for a while
um
let me just read this really quick
[Music]
ly to the monks of grand time however
recommend processing of crystal for that
market once face in operation series
what does that mean
what does any of that mean
um yeah yeah for a while we didn't write
anything we just were like kind of
sightseeing looking at everything
yes I can
how do I get out there
I cannot
ism
[Music]
oh my God thank you thank you
thank you thank you for helping me stay
calm
that was so mean
[Laughter]
ah
um
okay so for a while we we went all
around and um
uh
um oh we were eventually standing in
line for churros
uh there were like we never found normal
tourists we went through all of the usj
and we never found normal churros the
only thing you could get was the I think
the the Anya
churros yes
from that anime spy family and durai
montreals and both of them had I swear
a 90 minute wait
that I did not expect it oh winter now
we were like no way it's gonna take that
long right so
me and Kelly and Uhura
wait this looks exactly like what I also
want to tell you about but we started
standing in line for churros
and holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] the thing is for churros you
don't even see like a sign that tells
you how long the wait line is so we
weren't quite sure
um but
it's uh took literally 90 minutes to get
some [\h__\h] churros and then they were
kind of underwhelming
yeah we went for uh uh the Doraemon
churros but you know the other three
three right yeah they got they just sat
down somewhere because they had some
other food
and oh also guran you know has some
popcorn because they got like some
monster hunter that's also thing they
have there monster hunter is also a big
thing in usj in Japan they they got like
really cute containers for popcorn
so they were snacking on popcorn and I
was snacking on their popcorn too
because I was getting hungry again and
then it was so yummy it was so yummy
um
so so oh my God let me just tell you
um while we were in line somewhere you
know made a reservation and asked who
wants to join
a monster hunter VR
experience not a ride it's not a roller
coaster but it's like a whole experience
that is so cool and I was I wasn't sure
what I was getting myself into but I was
just like yeah sure why not even though
I played Monster Hunter like once or so
and I I really didn't get deep into it
because you know you guys remember maybe
but and and in a really big Monster
Hunter Fans right
so there was a yeah Ina told me there
was a monster hunter ride already since
a long time ago and it wasn't supposed
to go on so long but it was so popular
that they extended it and it was still
going on when we went and she made a
reservation for a time slot for us and
then you know it was getting really
close uh dangerous because we were
endlessly until the last minute in that
[\h__\h] churros cue
then I quickly ate half of it put the
rest of it in my bag wasn't even that
yummy uh and then we gura Ina and me we
went to the Monster Hunter VR experience
while the others went to check out some
other roller coasters
um
maybe you'll hear that story POV from
Cali or so I don't know
um
there are
nothing big
but I'm so glad we went because I have
to say that was the highlight of the usj
that was the absolute highlight it was
so cool even I was so nervous because I
I thought oh well I don't know much
about Monster Hunter maybe it's not
gonna be so nice for me but so we went
in there and then first they explained
the same thing a million times
that was a little bit annoying
they explain the same thing over and
over again you go from one staff to the
next step and they explain the same [\h__\h]
again kind of unnecessary but we put all
our stuff away like literally everything
our bag our head accessories uh
bracelets everything into a locker and
then we get like a little QR code thingy
and then you have to make your character
there's like a section on a on a screen
where you make your character there's
like three different outfits uh and then
four or five different weapons you get
to choose I was like which one is easy
Ina Nina told me I should use the long
sword like a katana or like a normal
long sword I'm not sure I think it was a
katana or so so I chose a long sword I
don't remember the other girl's weapons
they chose different ones though
um
and uh uh yeah then you choose
everything you set up your character
yeah and then you move on to the next
section where they once again explain
everything again and then you stand in
line and then uh get everything
explained again and then you go into a
room
um
uh basically it was you know our group
and another group but eventually we were
like really separated only into our
group that was really cool that we
didn't have to mix with other people but
we went into a room where they started
doing some lore
um
like they were like a monster hunter
cosplayers too I think some cute ladies
dressed in full-on Monster Hunter
cosplay and they were doing like some
feature style acting yeah and they were
trying to get us pumped up and
explaining some things again while being
in role play mode and and telling us you
know the whole build up for the story
that we're about to experience and that
they need our help and they would ask us
are you ready to help us would you
please lend us your hand your help you
Monster Hunters and we would they would
ask us to answer so we had to be like
yes okay like really pumped yeah after
that was done they would lead us to the
next room where they would put a a
really heavy they if they even said how
much it was it was either five or ten I
think it was even 10 kilogram backpack
which was basically a PC on your back
um on the backpack was also like uh I
could see it was like
um basically like a like a a bonk stick
connected but eventually they would put
it in your hand so you had something in
your hand to fight
and then uh like they instead of like
normal VR we are hand controllers they
put something they like wrap it around
your hands both of them
um and then the headset and blue blah
bloop it's basically a valve or a Vibe
no a five I think a five like an older
Vibe maybe but yeah it was so heavy I
felt like
the moment they put it on me I felt
immediately like so exhausted so I was
like oh [\h__\h] and then with the headset
which was also really heavy I was
getting really worried I was worried
about good attilia because she's bad
with like VR stuff right but she was
choosing fine
um yeah So eventually they put
everything on and then uh once again
they explain everything they check if
everything works and then yeah they tell
you to put down the VR goggles and even
still in the waiting area immediately
you enter the Monster Hunter world we
will snow which was snowy and looked
like this actually exactly like this
like graphic wise also it was one-on-one
like the high quality Monster Hunter
Graphics it was really beautiful and the
moment you put on the VR goggles there
was like an NPC standing right there
a lady
um telling us to start walking So
eventually we started walking and it was
so weird because like the floor and the
walls and everything was like uh
adjusted to what you see in the VR I
mean you didn't feel snow but like if it
would go up in the VR world then the the
floor was actually kind of like at an
angle a little bit and if you saw like
you know the room was narrow there were
a lot of really narrow paths like this
uh so you would feel that you know here
there is a wall and here's a wall too
I have to tell you about this now sorry
I have to I have to because I really
wanted to tell you about this it was so
cool cool and cold no it wasn't cold
though
and then
um whenever you were like getting too
close to something uh the VR world was
like programmed to show like a red wall
like you're not supposed to you know go
any further or you just can't uh but if
you still continue to do so the staff
will eventually tap you and you will get
a heart attack from that because you're
so immersed it was so immersive but it
was so weird because
we had to go over like this is really
long uh wooden
um uh Bridge with like at a really high
height you know if you had fear of
heights then oh my God you [\h__\h] and we
were so immersed because
like really scared that we're like gaps
in between the wooden planks and I would
legit even though you don't fall down
even if you step on the gaps I would
legit lift my legs like really carefully
one by one to step on the bridge
properly
it was so funny and you know we were in
our little group with Kura and Nina and
and following each other you know uh it
was so cute and then sometimes you know
I would panic and
we would hear each other through
headsets and microphones
um and yeah told me she was really
freaked out because I was screaming so
much because of the bridge and all that
it was insanely immersive and it felt
like so much actually so much better
than my home VR for some reason
um the goggles were just fitting
actually much better for some reason
even though they were kind of the same
time hmm
yeah so we were walking through and the
whole time you have like some items to
collect and then if you like turn around
your hand uh then you see like a a book
opening up where you can see what you
have collected so far uh and then you
get extra points if you collect a lot of
items but also eventually when you fight
like we would go somewhere and and the
game would continue with the lore and
then suddenly an enemy would pop up and
we would have to fight it and that that
was the fighting was so cool because you
know you had actually two different
moves a normal like
um hitting move that really
um hits accordingly to how you hit IRL
and a charging move oh and actually even
a Perry you even had a Perry
so oh my God it was so cool we were like
we were like in an Emma Murphy tea
together kind of and finding this boss
together and you know depending on how
much damage you do at the end your rank
will be higher
um oh so cool and the Monsters were like
huge it felt like so intense and wow it
was so fun there were like two of three
fights that we did
um and in the end you know uh the the
Lord continues and they're like thank
you so much for saving the day
yeah it was incredible we had so much
fun it was really exhausting because
everything was so heavy but it was also
extremely immersive and it was just the
coolest thing ever like oh my God
ah oh wait no
wait no we had another thing we could
shoot with our uh like you know there's
a grapple yeah we could even grab like
sometimes we would have to go all the
way up like a high mountain without a
grapple and then we go like swoosh to
the top somewhere at the top but with
the grapple you could also shoot if you
I guess you have that in in Monster
Hunter as well yeah yeah it was iceborn
yes yes yes yes yes yes it was iceborn
mm-hmm
yeah we could shoot the oh yeah one
thing I did I would say I want to give
the credit for that one to me
um there was like a part with a monster
that we were fighting where on top of it
there was like an icicle like this at
the very top but I think the other girls
didn't notice but the game was kind of
telling us to shoot the icicle so that
it would fall down on the enemy so we
had to do that otherwise we couldn't
really move on we were just fighting
endlessly and I noticed and I shot and
then it went down yeah
so cool man
I'm so glad we did that together oh
man I really wanted to tell you about
all this so after that it was really
dark and we were trying to find the
others again but uh since it was so dark
and kind of the end of the day already
uh the girls were just like
um good idea wanted to buy some more
stuff so they they oopsie what am I
doing
what's up they uh went to buy some some
more souvenirs summer stuff and uh
I didn't want anything and the shops
were like so [\h__\h] crowded I didn't
want to see that so I was just waiting
outside in the pavement on the pavement
eventually uh Callie and Cole uh
found me on the street and we reunited
and they told me what they did roughly
but you should just listen to them
telling their part
and and then you know what happened then
this is so pretty by the way
you know what happened then
was done with the shopping and so she
comes up to me and she gives me
and a little Elmo like keychain plushie
and tells me that she has a matching one
Cookie Monster one
and that's not where it stops she gives
me a number one she rips off there's
like I guess it was a set and she was
doing a little tsundere thing where she
said oh she just wanted to Cookie
Monster one anyway so she's giving me
the other half
but it was like two like badges one
Cookie Monster one Elmo and she rips off
in the middle the the cardboard and
gives me the album one so now we have
three matching things like a badge and a
little keychain and and the headbands
all elbows Cookie Monster
I was like what's like going on why
that's so sweet and she was just saying
Oh no just just because you know she
just wanted the Cookie Monster once
[Music]
oh that was so happy
very moment you know it was the end of
the day and we were like close to the
exit
um but then we know this
like right next to us
elbow into Cookie Monster I literally
right there doing a little like photo
session and and like grating session at
that very moment right next to us so we
gonna like freak out and we're going
over there and like taking videos and
like looking at them and waving hands at
them and so on
so for me it was a really big Elmo
Cookie Monster Day
that's really really
fun man
yo and then we eventually just you know
left and we were [\h__\h] dead and yeah
we went back to the station where the
shinkansen would leave we tried to get
another like eggy band we eventually
lost everyone and we missed like free
trains that we wanted to take
um
finally we got on the train and got
really late we were all [\h__\h] tired
and then while we were in the train we
had to join some kind of like meeting on
on the phone
just listening though not really saying
anything just listening
um
yeah and uh yeah eventually we got back
and then I said goodbye to cronini I was
like it was really nice meeting you on
this opportunity
um thank you so much for joining us and
you know it was nice
um really lucky that I got to meet
chronium
wait till now I met every every council
member
makes up a little funnel but right I
meant Bales I met uh I met fauna I met
crony
everybody because I kind of meant Iris
like for a short moment
same station nearby thank you oh thank
you I'm kind of done with my tangent I'm
sorry I just really wanted to get this
story out of the way
it hit
I came from
honesty
um
why you know that
I must scan
[Music]
uh of course
reflects beam weapons and can only be
cracked by a concussive blast uh sort of
charge
if I charge it doesn't look like
this
is it just missing or
do I really have to use my missiles for
that
yeah a little waste we're such a tiny
enemy
it's a safe spot yeah
well you can just walk past well yeah
but gotta find a solution
yeah it was really nice we got to hang
out together in a big group it was a lot
of fun
and oh I also
not only with Gouda but with a lot of
the girls I was just every now and then
um
um um what's the word how do I say it
you know my arm arm and arm thing that I
like to do
that one also you know during the queues
out there was a lot of time
to talk about all kinds of things
one thing that I would bring up to crony
was Fire Emblem we talked a lot about
Fire Emblem and Cali joined into it
because she's also really far with Fire
Emblem
thank you
so we had a common
topic to talk about
honestly a man that was so much waiting
time it was kind of lame but I was
surprised how how long I could keep up
the conversation
um
the crony plant yet uh yeah yeah I mean
she did a stream on it right but she's
like she played way further than that
she told me
on it what the [\h__\h]
yeah we kind of talked about
English versus Japanese version and
generally the story and the character
designs and this and that
why are you no open
uh upset
why
last Shield over door is secure
oh so sorry she contr
Ary lines can't open now
what are these babies
oh I strapped one down I think
Nana it's at all
where did I go
look under
oh
something there
I can break that open let's go okay they
need a lot of missiles here
okay open up please
and my Chat is dead
yeah so we were able to talk about that
that was nice
chatting helps the queue go by faster
yeah it was even that bad to be honest
oh God I just had to scan it once and
that worked
read that no I see you guys again
oh wait it was dead on your side too
guys
so it wasn't just me
did you guys talk about all of Fe guns
no because I don't I don't even play
anything besides free helps
although I would have liked to ask her
which route did she play in Free hopes
I'm curious I am curious how did that
get up there yeah
I hit
always black Eagles did I say free hopes
again
free houses when I say free hopes
am I mixing something up
again uh
how do you
how do I find this one again
I just become ball
I'll just roll through I don't know how
to I can't oh yeah right okay you guys
said I'm still gonna learn it
was there something here no okay
[Music]
um
I think that was uh
I think I think that was it oh actually
both me and gooda got really sick from
the Minion ride
we got really motion sick from that I
mean even me I got really motion sick so
what the [\h__\h]
what
they want to play with me
oh they're kind of cute now
all right I can only hit them on the
back I think
why why
all right I I prefer to go up on Higher
Ground thank you
why
I know if they're back but like I can
barely get to their breath
no
I hate when it doesn't like
focus on the one I wanted to focus on
[Music]
why are they so difficult
oh
baby Chico they sell Predator ice shell
protects vulnerable dorsal area grow a
resilient shell of ice on their bags
blah blah blah
turn quickly in order to not allow for
the distribution
Firebirds of ultra cold gas
doesn't help me that is just what I
already knew
around
foreign
ew
[Music]
yeah did you see what I did
what I did you have to have you have to
press both buttons in order to do that
you can't let go of a I had both pressed
like I had a pressed and then also Press
B carefully
with the other side of my thumb yeah
to strafe while having it charged
Next Level gaming guys skill issue if
you can't do it it's that simple
it's getting better
uh let's get up there
what's the secret
um
how how
what
oh
[\h__\h] looks like a guy could melt it but
maybe I need something special for that
can I not go over there yet
I don't I feel like I can't
um
foreign
[Music]
behind me
that's also big jump though
we
show
[Music]
okay
just something I could activate no
here I am once again our turn into
pieces you know
speaking of nostalgic things
you know what I did I finally started
um
the thing that I've been
planning on doing for a long time
let's take it up here
oh I started watching
the one show that I really liked as a
very young teenager or like I would say
probably you could even call me a child
back then
Charmed
and I was
that's the one show that I haven't like
re-watched uh after getting older
because it's not really it hasn't really
been on any like services to stream
ew
so it was just like hard to get
and I was wondering if I re-watched this
now as an adult how cringe is it going
to be and I can tell you
it's pretty cringe but it's also really
Charming
no pun intended and and kind of you know
kind of cute but it's so tacky
my God is it tacky
like I think the story
is still okay
I mean some of the
um enemies and and all that and how they
capture
the their victims
is kind of like cringe fatty but
it's not as bad the thing that really
makes me laugh out loud
is and I wonder how old this show is now
if this was just a given back then or if
it was a thing of budget but the the the
effects
the magic effects were so
out bad
like legit they're so bad
like uh in one of the First episodes
there's like a
dude warlock or whatever whatever they
call it
what yeah bye
uh which like captures witches he looks
for witches and then
he will like uh
nice
then kidnap them then place them on an
altar where they lie down and cannot
move because their arms and their legs
are
tied up on the old car and they go like
I know
you're so stupid tacky
um
but then he would uh come out of the
dark and be like uh
there is no help
I am and then he says like his demonic
name that I don't remember
but he comes out looking like super old
and strange and evil and demonic right
so then he sucks the life out of the
witch with like a laser eye beam and
that's like that kind of [\h__\h] just looks
so bad so then his laser connects to the
eyes of the other girl and then he turns
from from old to younger again
and it's just so stupidly tacky but I
continue watching it because it's
um that part yeah it's tacky as hell but
it's not that bad in terms of like
storing and I will never re-watch it
because it's so nostalgic
is it a 90s show
um
man the magic is so bad
oof
so bad
watching it now is like such a whiplash
a late 99 TV show
um
yeah the CGI my God it's terrible maybe
it gets better in the later season
[Music]
um
don't call me
who says I watched it when it came out
it was very popular when I was a kid on
TV but who says who says I was you know
where am I going
so confused
do you not also like just get lost some
sometimes
no wait Flex okay
right thank you thank you okay
the two people who agree with me thank
you for not flexing at me
[Music]
oops I missed
it
hey why you not open up but hey there's
Laura hidden here maybe that's why
and try to hide it from me
up great oh
so many creatures suffer beneath the
blight upon the land
and we chose are no exception but for
all of our pain we can at least believe
in the promise of the future
we have come to believe that on time may
never come when we can once again open
the door and banish the darkness we've
contained
even so our vigilance will forever
remain we believe that on some Far of
day a savior will come and continue what
we have begun is that me for that savior
we will leave our ancient weapons and
armor the soul who can gather them will
be the entrusted one
the only being who can reverse the evil
that grows here so that's me
I would say
[Music]
oh
everybody dead but I will save you
anyway I started laughing
perfect angle
grotesque but okay
does usj in America have a monster
hunter I kind of doubt it because I
guess most of the things it has like
same Nintendo World and HP Etc right but
Monster Hunter I guess not right and the
Anya spy X family that usj in Japan is
going on probably not
what no there is you Australian in
America
wait but I heard about into the world
somewhere in America
where is Nintendo World down
of course it's not usjs whatever you
know what I mean don't
particular about that shut up you know
what I mean
it don't be like that
hush
never USA oh
you asj in America is just USA wait
USA and USA
platform realignment oh
it's in California but they're planning
to building a park in Orlando too damn
okay so what in Hollywood
[Music]
time
what
I thought the other one doesn't deserve
period Please more
um what
come back please
anyway
there's a path here too that shall be
explored
oh it's just this path
It's Kind again it didn't look scannable
okay
oh okay
I wonder what kind of special stuff the
American
USA
has instead
post ball quiet while mothball mode
press and hold lb to charge the ball
release out you know what it was so
unnecessary that in the beginning of the
game I have everything they teach it to
me once
and now they have to teach it to me
again because I forgot it again
that was kind of so unnecessary they
should have just skipped all of that
they gave me a taste and it's just
okay for me
this is Neil oh I didn't have the bus
okay cool
but still my point stands
um
uh-huh
okay and bow
it
camera I don't see where I should go
great thank you what why is what is why
can I please
I don't like this camera
I guess I should go this way my body
could go up there
why why can I not move
[Music]
d
oh what is this
okay
look at me Tony Hawk let's go
[Applause]
just walk here
don't need to do everything as a ball
no needs to commit to the bits forever
now want my mom to the sub it
thank you for staying a member for such
a long time am I done with this room
wait can I kill them now
[Music]
no
ouch my HP
what
oh
why does it not show the map when I'm a
ball by the way kind of lame
no please go
[Music]
away
what is this room
confusing me
it's just a way for me to hide from this
big monster
oh [\h__\h] I started blasting there
come here come here come here
yeah show me your turtle brain yes
why are you still alive
I learned a quick missile fire a bit
before the final quick myself uh what
what do you mean
just a normal missile what do you mean
you can use it until then
where are we going next
I will go to Safe actually
what where's safe
here
huh
it could be a little thing
ah down here okay
cutscene
Nani
uh-oh am I not allowed to save now
another Nutella Dawn
[Music]
ow
so the Nutella done the infamous
when you mean Ridley it's called Nutella
Don
I named it so
in case you haven't watched the official
program
that I was part of I got some more
official program program requests by the
way
the other day I mean it'll take a while
until you see them but I was I was gonna
turn down one of them because it's a
topic where I was like sorry I honestly
like I don't even know how to make it
into a joke
but I know nothing about this topic I
don't know how to do this sorry I think
I have to turn this one down for the
first time ever I'm turning down the
program and they were like no please
please I think it's fine please please
don't turn it down
well if you really want me to be part of
it man
I guess I'll study this topic
just for this one occasion even though I
have zero interest in the topic itself
you will eventually know what I'm
talking about not not more dinosaurs but
no I don't think they necessarily needed
me
but no hmm I don't know where am I going
what
what ah maybe maybe here
up there
uh
sounds intriguing I don't know
you were the only miss member who
answered the DM possibly
[Music]
more of those pipes huh
let me up please
all the way back
to wear
you don't mean that right what do you
mean backtrack yeah
where's my ship
all the way back
is that my ship
lots of attacking oh no
I don't like that
is this the right way
we're backtracking is a feature not a
bug
it's more fun than it sounds like Zelda
oh
yeah oh no
tell me if I'm on the wrong path guys
please
I'm on the right where was the tank
there was a tank there
honey
are you sure I didn't already get that
one
but where would that be
jump just bomb which one here or on this
one
here
whoa
wait
[Music]
no no I'm never gonna make this one more
right oh
[Music]
here
oh God
oh God my brain uh
what
no I can't I can't
[Music]
it's over it's over
[Laughter]
only one bomb Oh
if I had to go like From Bump to bump
s
laughs
I can't make it I can't make I can't get
out of there I can't get out of it
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's like lift it
I'm jumping I swear it's X right
like bugging
oh oh the bombs saved me
don't save me
pump safely
oh God
ah close
[Music]
oh
oh God
you see a balance there they had just
there
and it healed me all the way back up
Hallelujah
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] what what
oh wait it's already past midnight what
the [\h__\h]
I'm so immersed guys but my throat hurts
man from all the screaming I'm getting
so tilted
uh I don't know how far we should go and
today
you got the energy tank faster than I
did wow
thank you for boosting my ego
I'm scared I'm scared
where am I going
oh
ow I hate these cameras
[Music]
why are you such a little [\h__\h]
you had no jump without bombs so you had
to face the lava every time
[Music]
which way which way do I go I hope it's
this way not in you
me
[Music]
and pink pink
was I here before
I only remember it but I guess I was
bad life decisions
[Music]
can relate
uh
okay
[Music]
thanks to the music
uh wait kill this one first
and then this one was bombs right but
hip
well it has to be without bombs as
possible too no
yeah do I really have to become Ball but
wait wait maybe I want to become ball
because it can possibly push me through
this hole and I want to go there nope
wait as if I'm not
if I'm not a ball
it ignores me when I'm not a mom
you little [\h__\h]
kind of ignores me uh oh I still don't
have the grapple hook I still don't
where how do I where do I go
hello can you tell me where to go
how do I
get back there
oh look at that missiles
oh I do want to go in the hole
well then
please
[Music]
once I am in the lava Panic ensues
cards get out so fast like you know it's
not that easy
I feel like I'm playing a Zelda game
right now
the lava dungeon
partially the music and the style of
enemies just gives me such Zelda vibes
am I just going crazy what do you think
they're pretty similar hmm okay
very Zelda like okay like Zelda but
without NPCs yeah you get all the lore
from scanning not from everything
yep I'm not making that one back
I'm so
I'm so ground
I was paying attention I was trying my
best
the
is the closest one just over there on
the left I wonder
closest ground
[Music]
your little [\h__\h] shits
you [\h__\h]
frog
[Music]
he found my biggest enemies because
these little shits will be the end of me
when they really shouldn't
shut up
oh
[Music]
please turn off that sound
can you link
fall forward
you in this point of view I guess you
probably can right oh my God please
slowly please
can I no
and ball
okay bye-bye
go away
oh I am I'm focusing now
do I even have to go here
do I even go this way
what
um okay thank you that's like in the
middle of [\h__\h] nowhere
oh where I'm going now is just a missile
upgrade oh [\h__\h] that
so not worth it right now
I'm not risking falling down again
more
here I am I have arrived
okay there's more
oh God
it's terrifying oh my God don't change
the angle suddenly like that man oh oh
there it is
am I doing like 100 right now is that
what I'm currently doing because I don't
wanna
so happens to be that if I get these
things I automatically get stronger no
okay good
what is there that you have to collect
to get 100
[Music]
do not go down oh okay really
scanners oh that's part of 100 things
oh hell no
oh no no never ever
hahaha
[Music]
um
even though I have a lot of moments
where I'm getting really tilted I am
having
in the moments where I'm not tilted a
good time with this game just so you
guys know
I'm enjoying it
foreign
it's really chill right now
um
Where'd I go now
[Music]
where do I go
I hit the map
preferably uh
all the way on the other side
it's on the complete opposite
I hate the map keep going straight keep
going forward okay so you mean this way
what
[Laughter]
the [\h__\h] do you want now
blasted his ass
are all different 100 the only one that
really matters is all items kind of for
completion is you already miss them yeah
yeah I mean I didn't want it any it's
not like I wanted 100
like I wanted
you first yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that
wasn't so much though man
oh
yeah
well at least there's like a
like an edge here
but I'm not gonna trust it too much
Samus is always screaming and panic in
this stuff but we just couldn't hear it
because of the helmet so she seems super
cool
yep just I I don't have that filter for
some reason
what what is where am I
what is this place I don't remember this
place
wait do I go on here
in that door there's a safe
mate
is it really though
I haven't been there before
it's not
what
see one guy
I got one guy now because one guy said
is that what you call one guy
this one guy says it
you made up a turn for that
well
it was more than just one guy
it was maybe free guide
no worries I can go back
eh why is it the first time that you
guys say that to me because I feel like
I I do that a lot where I get one guide
I do that a lot
you never mentioned this before
[Laughter]
can someone stop that [\h__\h] alarm now
please
foreign
[Music]
there we go
look one guy was really fast
we've given me information
one guy was just faster than although a
hundred other guys
can you really blame me
just gotta get faster get good
overpowered the one guy faster
oh
what is this where am I
I'm scared
um please no boss fight now please
guys there's no like big boss fight
coming up right away right because I'm
not
ready for it
no just free HP
no boss fight for a while okay okay
okay okay
I don't think I can Farm them
I would if I could well hello
what
Ah that's so dark oh that was stuck
whoa
the PGM is like so
hero ache heroic
[Laughter]
right now
big Zelda vibes
why is Metroid episode zelda-ish what
the hell
so inspiring
underneath
damn
I feel like I'm collecting
uh
not tripods
what's cool
[Laughter]
is there something there
let's see
I know
um
I forgot the name who's that who's that
one artist who always draws my tangents
what's the name
is that one artist
you know yeah she took on the draw me
collecting tripods
[Music]
I love Shiro's like after stream tangent
uh fan art by the way have you guys been
looking at it it's like so funny and so
accurate I love it
yeah that's one reason why you guys
should get Twitter
bad weather man
here huh
honor
I want to be Emma's woman
it's a pun because you know in Japanese
you're either or not or an AM
en you bring good weather you bring bad
weather and then at the same time
I could be i'ma's woman you know
where are we going this way
[Music]
better be this way
high five oh
have fun
is there a half up here
um
here
oh
oh [\h__\h]
why am I losing momentum no what
oh
my [\h__\h] eyes I keep on thinking it's
me
I don't look like that at all huh
terrifying
since when is my monitor so reflective
[\h__\h] do I go down there
why did I come up here
also is this like
Oh I thought I could get rid of the Moss
and then there's a like a lower behind
it maybe
there is
no
ball bomb behind me
oh
I could not see that nice pretty concert
dude
thanks dude
I want to do more please
I won't do more and I want to use the
the idol on the bed a lot
I hope I can well I mean it should
totally be fine to use it for like 3D
anniversaries and birthdays right
because
other members have been using the old
one
I wonder if we'll ever get the old one I
don't think so because otherwise like
wouldn't they have given it to us until
now
[Music]
eh what now
what now
don't it
what
hey
[Applause]
but my ship you guys said you guys said
go back to your ship
you didn't tell me go back to your ship
where do I call them
I was driving by the shiny they didn't
say that no I didn't even get one guys I
think I got 100 guys that go back to
your ship
wait where did I come from where am I
going back to them
oh man
cute little ships
no not this way
moving this way
[Music]
this way find a half pipe again
foreign
yes that way
okay
it didn't show up again this time
don't worry guys
I'm right there
[Music]
oh
you can't get me can't get me can't
possibly be this fast can you
oh look at that skill whoa incredible
can't turn around that fast
yeah Sonic
hey we're impressed by my house plastic
yeah one of the honestly one of the
games I want to play in the future I
told you guys was 10 18 snowboarding
right
I have one of mine playing uh the Tony
Hawk I think it was a GameCube game that
I played back in the day as well
but it has like no story right
sake of playing it again
later
can I go down here
and wrong guys but there's no other way
right
I go here and then don't jump down to
the ship what do I do next
maybe left
what is that
movement upgrade
do I become faster
speed
space jump for the choir
oh well still in the air press again to
perform an extra space jump oh double
jump
double jump
oh
okay
that automatically gets me to
test it out right here
okay are we good now is there like a
boss fight coming up right away or
I don't know should I stop now
back to the snow fields
now we're cooking
now we've got hella movement options
same again yeah I would I would
good time to stop really
okay maybe I will then
all right actually you know originally I
wanted to continue tomorrow but then I
saw fauna has birthday stream tomorrow
at like around I think 11 p.m or so my
time in the schedule so I was like hmm
okay I don't want to like overlap but I
also want to start at the same time
roughly so just gonna take tomorrow off
um
and I'm also going to doctor tomorrow
and possibly also getting a massage
tomorrow because I am in so much pain
you guys don't even understand
yeah
yeah Farmer's birthday is tomorrow what
I wonder what she's gonna do
so many birthdays but in case you didn't
see I pulled up a schedule yesterday you
guys were really hyped because there's a
lot of long streams on there is it this
one yeah Metroid Prime today tomorrow
and then more Metroid Prime
you're going to call in oh she didn't
like ask for
she didn't tell us about any Collins
or ask for any Collins she didn't
so I don't know of anything
uh Magic Prime Wednesday and then on
Thursday members only but now I
[Music]
I actually think we're not gonna do a
watch long not necessarily because I was
like you know not that satisfied not
really because of that book I'm just not
really interested in re-watching it
anymore
uh with you guys I don't know I was like
I don't know kind of like I'm I'm
already I moved on uh I'm sorry
and honestly it's just so [\h__\h] long
it was so hype but watching I was
watching day two with mume together in
Discord and
uh it was just
kind of too long
it's just too long
crazy long like honestly
if back in the day the hello project
concerts that I went to were this long I
would have been really grateful I think
like I could go on forever
I don't know how it felt like for you
guys from a fan point of view but for me
it was just uh endlessly long
oh we could watch The Next Star Wars
movie
yesterday
I don't know whatever time there is now
does it change to EDT
it was long but also hype yeah it was
but
so for me I have
um I have an idea guys
first of all I have two ideas that I
want to pitch to Yago
first of all
um next year please three days
or
um
let's assume we probably don't have I
mean I couldn't imagine that we would do
Holo 27 again which leaves us again with
only one concert per day so how about we
do either three days or two days but
like four concerts if we were able to
squeeze in the whole of 27 then we can
also do two concerts per day now the
problem is that it would overlap with
the Expo right so I actually have four
free pitches
um
I know this would probably be really
difficult to accommodate because I can
understand the feeling of wanting to
have the X-File and the Fest happening
at the same venue at the same time
but I feel like we need more tickets we
need a bigger concert venue I think we
should move on to the next big Revenue
which is the Budokan
dream big yango dream big
we should move on to the Budokan and it
may not have an expo venue but we can
also book the Expo venue for a very
separate day separate dates or on the
same date and well a little bit further
venue but you know it is what it is we
need a bigger concert venue it is what
it is we have to accept it
yeah okay so let's say we have done that
now my my third and my biggest pitch
is
the following wait let me get like a I
need to make this uh give this give us
some visuals does anyone have a
screenshot of like
the festival stage
without anybody on it
for fast online stage let me see
um
[Music]
okay I have one
um
what do you mean this page doesn't exist
okay let's say
[Music]
let's say this
this was the stage right
and uh
big stage right but so many
so many people here right and in the
very back you know it's just what it is
with like
the problem of having a big venue and
humans are
just too small right
so we have um we actually have an
advantage here
we are virtual
YouTubers and in theory you could make
us
as big as you want
so let me cook
my idea
if only I could manage to save
something not as a web P but as a
[\h__\h] PNG I swear to God
give me a moment let me cook
oopsie
I can't
I hear how about
what's this one
oh no I can't show this one
ah
how about this one okay so let's say
you see akidosad they're so small oh the
people in the far seats how could they
ever see but you see what's behind her a
huge screen actually it's a huge
well why not make
prove it and make our models this big
huh
so that actually everybody can see the
full beauty of us in its full potential
huh at least for the soul stages
why not make us this big so everybody
can see
as much as part of pearl
hey why would we do this we are virtual
you can make us as big as you want we're
not little humans
pathetic no make us this big and
everybody will only only carry good
things home from this yes take off the
limiters can we get much bigger so big
yes we can
we go believe me
this is the way to improve our concerts
even further to make us as visible as
possible you could even see us from the
Moon oh yes yes not only streaming
service at home no we will now offer
streaming service you don't even have to
like use a PC no you can literally see
us from the Moon
I think it's like a good idea like why
purposefully because this tiny no one
can [\h__\h] [\h__\h] eat like literally
if you're in the seat where this photo
was taken
I don't know what the [\h__\h] is going on
it's too small
I mean I could then look over here on
this screen but like no I want to see
like
I don't want to be controlled by the
cameras I don't want the camera to tell
me what to look at I want to decide what
to look at so I want to be at least this
size
I mean
everybody
right
[Music]
guys
I am cooking I am cooking I have
successfully cooked now we only need
them to understand and accept it
look
I can walk around the stage
there you go I've used the full width of
the stage
I can still dance like this no problem I
even see I'm even raising my hands and
I'm I'm reaching the top and all is good
I'm using it all but I'm not like
getting cut off
because
what it means I cooked but I didn't
think of course I thought I always think
um
I see I literally see no problem with
this I only see good things about this
who let her what do you mean what do you
mean
William is this not a good idea I think
this is a good idea immersion well
what
what what's wrong with this
what do you mean immersion
I want to see aguda this big
I want to see a shield this big
I want to see a giant gura up on stage
yes I want
then I can see all her pixels I can see
her pores probably even
[Laughter]
I think genius I'm going to pass this
along to staff yeah yeah there's no way
they can turn me down so in fifth fast
if this is happening y'all know who to
credit for this genius idea they may not
credit me because I am only one small
takanasikiwawa but you know even if this
is a small step for the takanasi kiwawa
it is a big step for
whole life ends yes and everybody will
remember that this idea came from yours
truly
from me
you're welcome you're welcome
then you can for real see my giant ass
because then it will really be giant for
once
how it should be
yeah yeah
yeah well it's already 1am I I thought I
maybe could
stop earlier and read some super chats
but it's kind of late man
two stories big yeah
I'm glad we have some kfps to support
this idea maybe we should make um
a petition
I think we would make a petition and who
says that we have to keep the screen
this small like ideally we should you
know get an even bigger screen and then
get this big like this is I think this
is the
ideal size
to make the most out of it and to give
everyone like the the most optimal
experience
hmm
what
are you guys scared of big people
that's kind of
what do you call it sizes
[Music]
sizes from you guys don't you think
shouldn't you wait a little bit less
discriminating ah
don't you see all the potential in this
don't don't you always say like step on
me mommy huh
now with this size we could potentially
step on 20 people at once it's pretty
efficient I would say
um
[Music]
they doubt me now they doubt me now but
you know many Geniuses of the past have
been doubted many revolutionary Geniuses
who changed the world into something no
one could ever have seen as possible
people doubted them people just like me
have been doubted every word we say has
been doubted and then 100 years later
they look back on us and they're like
she was right all along
and we would have made progress so much
faster if only we would have listened
only we would have listened early enough
how foolish of us humans oh no this is
just
how how it's bound to be this is Destiny
just because of the foolishness of
humans no no
no no
[Music]
chef with us
people hated her because she told the
trough
laughs
okay okay guys
all right all right all right
um so I will go now and
[Music]
yeah
I had fun thank you guys
for uh watching me play Metroid Prime
more on the day after tomorrow
um
and then we have Anthony Riza on Friday
one time only because uh well first of
all we already have so much going on
um with such a long RPG I
I don't know if I can't even monetize it
with like I don't know GTA it's fine
because
well at least you know other reasons but
I'm sorry I have to disappoint you
know I asked Can I please monetize it
this time they said no so I'm like oh I
didn't I will only play it once
um
they did give me a coat though that's
why I'm like at least playing it once
gave me a free code and I'll play the
rest um privately I'll enjoy it
privately
sorry sorry and I will continue problem
engage on the weekend because I thought
I bet you know I'd better put it on the
weekend actually because it's such a
long stream I should I should always aim
for the weekend with these games
actually
um
but the Riser anime actually really uh
interested
could be really cute I think they're
making the the story from the first game
into an anime right
hmm
well you don't what played privately
I think I might because you know
recently I've also been playing so much
Fire Emblem Fire Emblem engaged on my
private time too
I've been playing a bit more privately
but ideally you know if I want to play
something privately I really needed to
be
on a handheld but hey now I have the
what's it called
um
steam deck so I can play it privately
because I think I got a code for Steam
yeah that will come in handy yes let's
go finally coming in handy
I said but I do a big QR okay even if
they don't make us big I still think we
should at least aim for either a bigger
venue which will make it difficult with
the combination of the Expo so I
understand or just an additional day
um yeah
doing it Friday Saturday Sunday would be
good and
um maybe even more like twice per day
maybe Friday once in the evening and
then Saturday Sunday twice per day which
would mean five concerts
okay maybe that's a bit much but
hmm
I guess the problem is if it's that much
they're probably gonna like split the
members even more and then if you have
like oh she's spread all across and it
kind of sucks because you then have to
yeah trying to get tickets for
everything and then it's really a low
chance to get even
uh more tickets and yeah
yeah it's difficult man
it's difficult but
I mean
at the same time we want to give more
opportunities to more people to see it
right so
if we can't get more seats we can't
force more seats into the venue
so what can we do we do more all more
concerts but I would say you know what
you can totally do is just because hello
project did this too
you know when they're doing their uh
winter or New Year's concert tour Etc
they repeat the same concert it's not
always different they have like
um I mean some things may be different
but in general like similar set list and
and cast and all that
so you can just do the same concert like
for example uh
uh Friday first one is the same as
you know Saturday first one same as
Sunday first one and then
the evening ones are different but also
the same like you know what I mean
yeah so
people can see the same thing but
they're uh you know depending which day
you know you know more people get to see
you know what I mean
um
but my live emotion no no like it will
be like different like same set list but
performed twice
not just repeated just you know perform
twice so there might select small
differences
but like an MC and so on
well I don't know who's gonna listen to
me nobody's listening to me this will
never reach the people nobody's gonna
listen to what I say nobody gives a [\h__\h]
about what I say why am I even like
talking about I'm just trying to you
know give out the ideas but who the [\h__\h]
cares
it's not like anyone cares ah
it's okay it's okay I'm just uh yeah
have no say in this one day one day I
will
open up my own
YouTuber or Idol agency and I will
become my own younger and then I will
decide everything or can you imagine
no you care but I mean like the people
who would decide these things don't no
way they are listening ever to what I'm
saying here right now
I chose the song you want
nobody else
no but I was I was extremely happy about
that yeah I was so hyped
that they chose the song that I wanted
um
yeah but this is like a way bigger
decision
this this is like next level I don't
have a saying that I don't think so
it's okay
I'm just throwing things out there maybe
someone somewhere gets inspired by what
I say
but generally a tour would be actually
so cool though
like why not
in Japan
for now in Japan a tour in Japan well I
think we're ready to do a tour
concert tour
let's do it
um
go to like I don't know
maybe five different big venues all
throughout Japan
oh
thank you
actually
it was cutting out like crazy I watched
a little bit of the archive like uh
first of all
I already noticed that like she was
being cut off to me so often I could
often not hear what she was saying
and then the other way around was the
same apparently I was laughing so much
and screaming and laughing and it would
cut me off so much stupid Discord man
why why you cut me off so much
could tell you didn't always hear what
she said oh yeah it was so weird so
difficult I don't know why
every time oh cut off when she was like
in the middle of talking what
was really bad on that day
noise suppression yeah
Discord perm's gone
but you didn't have to cut me off
didn't even need your love
now you're just somebody that I used to
know somebody
and I used to know somebody
and I used to know now you're just
somebody that I used to know that's yeah
we I should have maybe nah
I was just gonna say maybe I should make
the members only a chili chatty stream
just Chit Chat because I have so much to
talk about but then oh then that would
be like members only and I mean there's
a lot of things I also want to tell
publicly so that you know non-members
can hear it too and maybe that Clips can
be made out of it Etc so I would kind of
like a waste
um
damn it
maybe maybe if I have time
on first day hold on I don't know I have
a Korean lessons on Thursday hey
they're not gonna be always on for
instance I can like change it up but
yeah but I could I could I'll play but I
feel like I have time
and feel like it maybe I'll squeeze
another stream in somewhere but
generally all of these dreams are kind
of long except the members one
I'm Gonna Be Long Metroid Prime gonna be
long
I don't know
are you back in Australia yes I am
I mean you know Japan was nice well I
just really missed home because of my
cats and just it was so stressful like
uh so much to do in Japan and I just
really missed my bed and my my apartment
and the general routine
um it's just like a lot of social
batteries being used
oh
it was so nice to like I wanted to make
the most out of it and collab as much as
I could but I was really at my absolute
limit mentally
um
I mean a lot of factors not just the
social battery
played into it just a lot of stuff
played into it
um
foreign
[Music]
uh
uh you know enough like I don't know I
think her social batteries were like
totally still
charged but I think she just genuinely
you know lack of sleep and that kind of
stuff was probably
uh taking a toll on her
good on me we were homesick and you know
uh
and uh I mean I think generally
you know food stuff made her feel kind
of like exhausted a lot of the time
every now and then she would feel
like
influenced by that
didn't have much energy because of that
often yeah
so we were all kind of like
looking forward to going home but uh
it's like huh
Unity come again huh
for all of us to be together like that
it was a really precious time
and I cherished it and I I appreciated
it so much
so it was like
torn between wanting to go home but at
the same time not wanting it to end
[Music]
once a year I don't know this was like a
I don't know it depends I asked for
um opportunity to do a myth 3D
anniversary stream
and we said we're gonna we will pay for
our own flights to come back to Japan
if we may but if that ain't gonna happen
then I don't see when we are gonna get
back together
anytime this year
for anniversary you know if they don't
allow it then
I don't know
L.A oh sure
hmm
yeah I guess
um
yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
uh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
anyway uh
I hope I hope they allow it I also want
to go to Japan in June if they allow me
to do my birthday concert please
please please I still haven't heard back
I still haven't heard back man
no what are you guys saying no
don't
we have done stuff before while being
elsewhere in different places
um
do you ever accept your concert or your
giant size thiago's Idol
totally in my control
less than three months now oh my God
yeah it's really not much time
not much time damn
yeah bye this month actually is almost
over
which means
please
I need to hear back also I need to plan
my album I need to I mean I've been
planning and I need to hear back from
from that kind of stuff too
[Music]
um
yeah so lots of stuff
um to be hopeful for and hopefully not
be
rejected I don't like rejection
huh
what's a Sunday
what do you mean winter time what
thank you for playing hinotoli on piano
I posted it in the pre-chat right before
the stream because it was really nice
they clapped
they probably all didn't know what you
were playing but they clapped
I found it already
yeah I thought time already oh I guess
it didn't
for the Europe already changed time to
Summertime
well I guess not
oh
anyway that's on Sunday
oh then I guess Sunday is uh wrong
but I will still start at 3 P.M like
whatever
if it's some Summertime by then then I
will still start at 3 P.M our time
but I guess that would mean
it starts
at nine or eleven EST do we have less or
more time then
in between
because then Japan is closer Japan would
started 10 p.m not 11 pm
in America would it be 9 A.M then not
10.
is your day off on Tuesdays because of
those fingerlinging deals what
okay I'm getting tired man oh
yeah
actually I need to cook but now it's so
late
I already cooked today though I cooked
like pizza rolls
they were really good
I made pizza rolls
from hello
yeah
[Music]
it was they weren't really yummy but I
think next time I make them because in
this recipe there was no meat involved
next time I make them maybe I put in
some pepperoni
some small pepperon or some bacon
well you were surprised there was an
arrested oh no I'm doing good
did you have a dip yeah I had a dip um I
think I'm gonna post a picture
afterwards
the dip was
um it looks like a cocktail sauce but
it's not it's like after putting uh the
the Tomato mixture uh on the dough uh
you keep it a little bit and you add
like sour cream or something like that
to it
so it's not like a yeah yeah it's kind
of like a marinara now it's almost like
but with some like
sour cream in it is that what you call
marinara sauce
it tastes really good
and next time I have to add some
pepperoni yes
mushroom Peppers yeah I added bell
peppers actually because they had
mushrooms in the recipe and I don't like
mushrooms so I just added bell peppers
there was bell pepper and tomato
that's the only stuff in the
in terms of like veggies in there kind
of weird I could have added more but I
guess like it was already spilling a
little bit
um
and I added a little bit of
ketchup just because in the whole
um tomato mixture
just because I felt like it wasn't
enough
like
stuff to spread and it definitely helped
it was very important because even after
I added a bunch of the ketchup it was
still kind of not not so much
liquid I guess
um it was good though I'll post a
picture
um I'm getting tired [\h__\h] I'm so tired I
think I'm just gonna
throw in Las Vegas
my beloved Frozen La Saga thank you
ah thank you
foreign
a.m yeah only because I had a nap
otherwise I would already be tired at
like
way earlier
um
thank you for those membership
oh I'm very tired now it's getting to me
now
hmm
I want to talk more of you guys but you
know have to
um Trickle
trickle effect
make it into a little small
tiny bite-sized pieces
why don't you eat before I ate before
stream I just told you about the pizza
the pizza rolls that I made
but after six hours and 13 minutes of
streaming isn't it uh understandable
that I am hungry again
human Rhythm eat three times per day
right
I had breakfast I had lunch and now I
will have dinner
why would I not be hungry now that's
just human
hmm ah Rowan Hood thank you for the
pinky thank you ah yeah
I know
I'm tired
[Music]
same same body functions
let her cook and then eat yeah no no
cook I only bake lasaga now
I will not cook twice a day
don't get one guide again
[Laughter]
[Music]
press the button no I'm too tired to
press the button
you press the button
no you no you hang up
no you hang up no no you
no
[Music]
um
why the [\h__\h] did he hang up
that moment when the other side really
hangs up and you're like
hey why we were supposed to continue
this endlessly
ah
um
foreign
[Music]
plan like nowadays like you don't what
what generation are you living in
okay I'm gonna go now
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
okay I should go thank you I had fun
guys more mattress Prime coming soon
tired now they're so so tired
[Music]
so I
um
foreign
[Music]
thank you
chronographer was good but back to
normal for now
change every now and then
[Music]
thank you for asking for it