[Music]
so
me
[Music]
so
does everyone hear my beautiful girls
everyone say hello
hello hello
welcome to my to my beautiful christmas
room
wow it's nice
can i sleep on your floor um if you want
to of course it's very close
because behind us there is a uh what's
that what's it called the fireplace
um
have you noticed that the doll on the
very right corner
[Music]
[Laughter]
if you look closely she is writing
something on the floor
something hot and then it stops there
[Music]
yeah rumor has it that
is
although i i don't quite understand
she's she's she oh nothing can
bring her down she ate a tarantula
recently anyway
so today we are uh doing a little
christmas stream we already did the
minecraft stream the other day but i
thought it would be nice to have
everyone together for
a little bit more uh holiday mood
because it's almost over but
not yet um so we have come here today to
read some stories or make make a story
first of all
and then we will do some secret santa
session we have a very special way of
doing it
and you will see that it's very
interesting i'm excited i can't wait
i've been looking forward to the secret
set
yeah and ava has uh i'm gonna have
secretly prepared something as well that
she will showcase at
the end yes thank you i'm very excited
to hear that
at the very very very end we have one or
two
announcements so you better stay until
the end
big announcements yeah
it's indeed a big announcement yeah
definitely worth staying until the end
okay so stay till the end
do it all right stop now does everyone
maybe wanna
talk about their uh this year's
christmas experience maybe something you
want to say and introduce yourself okay
of course everyone knows everyone but
just a hello and hi mori and i slept for
20 hours
that was your christmas did you not have
anything special to eat for christmas
um let's see what did i eat i woke up
and i ordered tacos
[Laughter]
my first holidays um being away from the
reaper family
so that was sad uh but the good news is
um
i stopped swinging my scythe around the
other day uh for good
yeah absolutely
everyone stopped for me everyone stopped
moving for me
yeah i see that i i'm just a bit
surprised they have disappeared
i have probably disappeared sorry i'll
be right back just keep on talking and
yeah it's okay no just just leave it to
me i'll i will entertain the humans
um so yeah uh basically it was my first
time
first time being away from the reaper
family unfortunately
but the good news the good news is um i
i was able to speak with the reaper
family they're all doing fine
you know i'm still thinking lives taking
souls even though i really can't do that
right now so you know but they're still
proud of me they're proud of the youtube
thing
so that's cool yeah and so i got to talk
to them just a little bit before i went
into hibernation forever
um and yeah then i just slept and it was
really nice i
i feel my energy is restored after all
of that swinging my scythe around
um yeah
yeah congratulations on that
i'm having problems right now finding
everyone so i'll just put the discord
images on there for now
all right uh i'll check back later
yeah sure that works
[Music]
where am i i think oh
yes so does anyone else want to talk
about their christmas experience
okay so
yeah how was it for you gura ah
i i miss my family
[Music]
but it's okay i played some minecraft
and i had my my christmas eve dinner was
a
a lettuce and mayonnaise what
oh no
[Music]
and um play a minecraft and i finished
the trident farm and it works
it works really weird what wait don't do
that
i don't have the trident but it's there
if you want to go in afk
right it works
hey how long would that work it's there
and it's just it's there it's right by
um it's by hachiman
area
but you have yet to receive a dragon
from it because the drop rate is
so girl
i want to see that well good job good
now nice christmas whoa
what about inna how did you spend your
cookies
um well after the cookie stream
yesterday
[Music]
yeah it's a regular work day at the
shine
oh they're seeing that i'm uh i i just
made you a bit louder
closer to the microphone
make it okay okay
and then uh afterwards uh i
i had some turkey bunnies
you had turkey yeah i had turkey for
like the first time
like it's the first time my family made
turkey because they usually just make
chicken because
turkeys are too big to finish at once
but
we we made uh we made turkey and then
uh i went to bed for a couple of hours
and then i get to spend the christmas
morning with my favorite
favorite halloweens
[Applause]
why is morning time merry christmas
merry christmas yeah
how was your christmas i was all right
i slept that was nice and then
i had a bag of lettuce
i mean crunchy i get but yeah it's good
the
the flavor
hey eat their own man but listen
actually um
since you you guys don't mention lettuce
uh
okay let me tell a story after alma is
done are you done
oh uh i tried to bake cookies because i
wanted to the smell of cookies this
morning
but i forgot to turn the oven off i put
it on broil
instead and then the top of the cookies
started smoking and it almost caught on
fire now my house is
yay so yeah about the lettuce
i i actually uh it's close enough
but i have a cabbage story oh cabbage is
done
yeah cabbage is great too so i i i
um i was on a train in in in japan
uh in a very uh big town a very specific
city
and um i was riding the stream and
i was just minding my own business
getting into the train and then i sit
down at the moment i sit down i notice
on the other side of the
the the train like like opposite side of
me
i see under the seat
uh a cabbage a whole cabbage
plenty of this cabbage but it wasn't
known there was no there was no one with
that cabbage the cabbage was
uncomfortable
accompanied did you make it your own
i wanted seriously i was about to take
out my phone to get some proof because
who would believe that i get on the
train and there's a cabbage in front of
me
hold on i still don't know are you
adopting
i want to but the moment i take out the
phone someone else comes uh in the train
and sits
in on that seat of the cabbage and sits
like on top of the cabbage pretty much
i'm like [\h__\h] now i can't take a photo
so i was waiting and hoping that the
person would get off
before me and i couldn't take my eyes
off the cabbage the person probably
thought
that i was staring at the person and
probably didn't even notice that they
were like on top of a cabbage right now
but i couldn't stop i would i kept on
staring and staring at that cabbage but
i ended up getting off of the train
before the cabbage and the person did so
maybe they wanted to they wanted to
claim the cabinet
kiada is what i'm thinking they knew
exactly what they were doing maybe they
didn't dominance
maybe they
[Laughter]
but this is died because the trains in
japan are usually like super
clean there's no no garbage or anything
in those trains usually so i was so
surprised to see like a whole
big cabbage there
yeah like an
anyway so yeah my christmas i was
basically i think my viewers know i was
streaming the whole time i had like a
million streams i also released a
christmas story a few uh like
uh two hours before this stream i
released another
uh story time reading blah blah blah uh
yeah
very um for me personally it didn't feel
like christmas
which is weird damn
because i had no decorations no tree no
christmas
dinner nothing but at least i spent it
with my
my viewers right and and everyone seemed
to have a better christmas
because of me apparently they say so
so that makes me happy that makes me
happy
that's good i actually took deadbeats
out to um
to a dinner yeah i was watching okay
yeah
and then we went to a penthouse
but then then ghost ghost strider showed
up and he was wearing a pop hat and was
putting the moves on me my deadbeats
beat him up
and it was fine
yeah but then the room got caught on
fire because you know go strider
um it's his head it's just it's on fire
all the time
it kind of burned down so that's why i
had to go to a motel
and it smells really bad and there's
stains on the floor spooky stains i
don't know where you're coming from
the black light yeah yeah oh you know
what i don't think i want to find out
to be honest i don't want to know so so
that's why i need to sleep on your floor
uh kia if that's okay no problem no
problem
i have a lot of plushies plushies that
you can like hang out with
but they might start they might start
moving in the middle of the night so be
careful
okay i think we got to move on to the
next segment so the actual first segment
which is uh
our mad lib i guess it's called
and wild yeah yeah we have a christmas
map like yeah
uh but while while ahmed we'll be
reading the the original story quickly
to you guys i want to figure out if i
can fix the
you know the moving thing so i hand over
the microphone to you
okay thank you i don't know if you guys
have heard this one before but it's
called twas the night before christmas
actually it has a different name but
that's what everybody calls it and
it's actually written in the 1800s which
means it's
a public domain so we can totally
definitely read it
yeah yeah okay sounds like fun it sounds
fun
was the night before christmas when all
through the house not a creature was
stirring
not even a mouse stockings were hung by
the chimney with care
in hopes that saint nicholas would soon
be there the children were nestled all
snug in their beds
while visions of sugar plums danced in
their heads
and mama in her kerchief and i in my cap
had just settled our brains for a long
winter's nap
when out on the lawn there was such a
clatter i sprang from my bed to see what
was the matter
away to the window i flew like a flash
tore open the shutters and threw up the
sash
the moon on the breast of the new fallen
snow gave a luster of midday to objects
below
when what to my wandering eyes did
appear but a miniature sleigh and eight
tiny reindeer
with a little old driver so lively and
quick i knew
in a moment he must be saint nick
it's longer
yeah i couldn't i couldn't focus on the
story because i turned the thing back on
and gouda turned out to be super super
tiny
i can fix this i can fix this please
make yourself a bit bigger thank you oh
[Laughter]
what are you doing here
[Music]
are you like using your powers against
each other to make each other like
smaller and bigger and then
[Music]
stop moving do you know what this is
fine
please stop oh my god everything
everything looks normal on my side i
don't know it's about normal go down
maybe
maybe yeah maybe you just make yourself
bigger yeah you do that yeah
yeah i think that the controls from the
ancient ones messed things up
means my powers don't work on christmas
maybe maybe a bit bigger
now and there we go
it's still a bit small i'm gonna water
here a little bit
she's standing up right now honestly
i'm on a milk crate
so i guess that's all right uh so
smaller again
i will show them the thing now
there we go so this is the story and i'm
gonna read the completed version right
but we are filling in some things now
yeah and we'll make a funny story
i'm gonna choose not not to look at the
story while i answer
yeah oh okay okay okay maybe the chat
can
so if someone can't think of a word
maybe we can randomly pick from the chat
or or every every sixth word comes from
the chat and not from all so the sixth
member is the it's the chat how about
that
cool yeah someone ran them from [\h__\h]
oh can i sit out since i'm putting it in
you guys do the words yeah yeah yeah
okay okay okay yeah okay if you want to
okay okay
but do you want to read the sentence and
so on and on
we should go first all right we don't
read the sentence we just read off the
words
you just go verb and then okay okay
and then at the end you mix it all
together and that's what makes you go oh
this is a nightmare
really is a mess huh exactly that's
that's when that's why it's mad
the difference between some of those
words so maybe i'm not the best person
i have to google it because i also don't
know
i think it's a verb the first one is a
verb oh
okay who wants to go first
let's just say it let's say
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh it's perfect i look beautiful and i
read the story to you can i hear you
last night
well i don't know what now you're gonna
put where yeah okay
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh there next uh another noun
like plural perhaps uh plural
okay no just no not plural
okay how about skeleton skeleton
skeleton on a motorcycle
nice nice nice oh yeah
i want to change can i change this boy
[Laughter]
but i don't have any in here right now
god damn it i want to deny you
[Laughter]
no i changed my answer
all right uh it turned into fork yeah
much better
perfect i know where's the next one
uh another nap okay
oh another one you know do you want to
go for it
[Music]
how can i make this even better
don't think too much just feel it just
feel it flatting
i think this is plural right this one
should be plural
ah yes plural yes plural ah
this is a lot of thinking for this
earthly sheets
all right and then the next is a person
a famous person
oh okay okay um um rick astley
oh my god
of course that was the first thing that
came to my mind
that's good that's what it's supposed to
be it's supposed to be the first thing
that comes into your mind
okay next word comes by the chat i think
if amy doesn't want to do it
yes yes okay yeah chats
it's a noun or peace people person
animal thing oh i'll choose someone
random from the chat let's see what they
have to say
i've seen a lot of you go uh yeah okay i
think we're going with jungle
okay
would it be one yago miniago or one yago
many yagos
got goose you're good
[Music]
i don't know you decide i mean that
actually makes sense boing boings danced
in their heads
it makes sense
another another person a
[Music]
i know it's supposed to be the first
part it's hard to compete with rick
astley
[Music]
gosh let's see shrek
oh my god now my chat is going to be all
green again i've expected i've infected
yourself it's going to be all green
again
no it's already
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
can they coordinate though and build a
christmas tree in the chat
oh they don't believe it i don't think
they can i have trained my
i have trained my employees to be in
sync but since there's many other
uh fandoms in here right now uh it's
mixing up and i don't think they can do
it
you have no faith it'll be a christmas
miracle
or try to make a tree guys try do your
best
[Laughter]
another noun but like a thing another
noun
[Music]
um
is coming up with such normal things i
like it
that's how you laurel
[Music]
a place a place
oh my god toilet first
next one is
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh person fingernail okay
phoenix phoenix phoenix oh that's a good
one wait that makes sense even then
actually good job guys good job chad
no makes actually sense
good job
[Music]
now like a clone oh
yeah oh no
[Laughter]
uh candy g what
what what a what
okay boy candy g string the things that
you think of
make me worry very much
[Laughter]
i'm worried that you're worried what am
i supposed to say
oh slippers but yeah
[Music]
like object and object
laurel okay let's see
i'm thinking um
bottles of 200 yen red wine
[Music]
that's the one that's the one i wonder
if someone wants to like illustrate this
whole story it's going to be
very interesting here
we don't need to call them they're
already working on it
they started 20 minutes ago
all right now we have uh ina a adjective
we're looking for an adjective a
descriptor right that's what it is an
adjective describes a num
yes oh it's like
it's like
like sexy furry yeah
what'd you say slippery slippery okay
[Music]
slip away
and i guess one more adjective
from me another one okay and that's
perfect the last one can be
by the chat perfect perfect okay so my
adjective is
[Music]
bottom sexy
sexy
no i can't change it i want it to be
thick i want it to be freak i recently
i recently um
remembered how to say that i was i
recently i realized i've been saying
fake
is wrong all along it's been thick fives
not fake ties i've been saying that for
years like my whole life i've been
saying thick ties
bunsen ties that like a business like
stupid guys
thick ties and thick ties and there are
thin ones as well but
[Music]
oh well the last one is by the chat what
does it have to be a man
a person a famous person okay
oh gosh
we're giving them too much power
uh oh now they're oh now it's pretty
mixed uh
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
you got it yes all right uh
uh twas the night before christmas
when all through the fork god
not a creature with stirring not even a
skeleton on a motorcycle
the sheets were hung by the chimney with
care in hopes that rick astley would
soon be there
the jagos were nestled all snug in their
bed what was the boy
boy danced in their heads same sex shrek
in his courtship
oh [\h__\h] she swore she didn't
had just settled our statues for a good
winter's nap
went out on a toilet i wrote such a
clattering
i sprang from my bed i said what was the
matter away to the window i flew like a
phoenix
or opened the shutters and threw on a
candy
the the moon on the breast the new
fallen snow
gave a luster of midday to the bottles
of 200 yen red wine down below
i mean it makes some sense listen
when once my wondering eyes did appear
but a miniature sleigh and a tiny
reindeer
with an old driver so slippery and thick
i knew in a moment
what have we done oh god
oh god
[Music]
i hope emma is not mad
i am
[Music]
hey
[Applause]
thank you for the super fun segment we
are moving on to the next segment which
is our
[Music]
[Applause]
i have it all prepared in my obs but
it's a bit uh scuffed so
i hope i don't accident accidentally
reveal something right away
um but the thing is we all don't
okay to explain a little bit um
we um are doing a secret santa but
uh we are not giving each other real
like physical presence instead we are
doing like
a creative version of it where um
we either drew something or we got
something off of the internet and put
something
together like a collage or whatever and
also we do not know
um who who uh
has who yet we don't know yet it's a
secret
i mean i don't know what you mean my
gift is definitely real
and my person will receive it oh okay
also i am the only one who has seen all
the presents because i i had to lowkey
see it because i had to arrange them but
i don't know who they
uh who gave it to who okay i got it from
uh enma uh so that i don't know who sent
it in
so yeah let's see it should be here
there we go there's a bunch of
presents here on what one person did
extra homework
and made an actual christmas wrapping as
well
wow who did that
i wonder too i saw someone winking there
just
i saw someone winking for whatever
reason
imagination
all righty who wants to open your
present first
this one here okay okay okay so i go
here uh okay it's really scuffed anyway
i'll just
show it
[Music]
reaction the the present giver can re
reveal herself
three one one
uh wait where is it
so i found a trident for you
unfortunately i don't think
i don't think that you it transfers
minecraft world
but i tried my best for you because i'm
the master of catching fish
now you don't have to eat lettuce now
you can eat actual fish
i can have a fish and lettuce salad
thank you
you're welcome i'm always always
thinking about you my dude and what kind
of tasty fish you might like because if
we all saw in the way out collab i am
the fish catching master
thank you i'll put it i put it in front
of gooda
there you go there you go cute
like uh if you took a fork and you tried
to eat with the other side
yeah yeah exactly
you just all sliced them all up on there
nice
[Music]
[Applause]
well then i guess i'll open my present
next oh nice nice
okay let me see present for kelly is
here
okay and
until opening callie's present
uh wait a second wait a second wait a
second
[Music]
wait a second three
[Laughter]
uh
wow can you put it on me right now
hold on hold on oh it's perfect
oh gosh i never want to take it off can
i leave it on forever
yes right i'd like to leave it on
forever
that would be incredible it looks like
it's going up her nose
it does what a gift i'm going to the
healing line
i love it let me take a sip for all of
you to hear hang on
let me hear let me hear
i didn't hear it
sorry this is a really strong one oh so
did the person really
[Music]
i i chose a very uh practical gift
indeed
custom made for kelly
i mean really this is actually all that
i wanted
and i'll use this please please send it
to me later so that i can use it in
future streams thank you i i i
will do a little too i appreciate it
this is beautiful
all right the next one should be inna it
should be opening up a present
let's see i have it here let me put that
up there
[Music]
are you ready to open your present yes
in a present in three two
one
[Laughter]
i think we all know who made that
nice booty nice booty you got that
would the person like to reveal herself
oh yeah
i made i made that for ena i am so
[Music]
[Laughter]
surprised
[Music]
i'm actually crying
yes
but it's here let me move it over here
move it over here move it over here
there we go
okay i'm opening up a present
in three two
oh wait that's the wrong one sorry i
almost opened the wrong one
uh this one this one this one this one
three two one
da da
even has oh bow on it
that's the size yeah it's it's me i made
this one that's a for size comparison i
put a little wealthy almond there
to
only for space travel okay okay
what do you want to use that for what
other uses
[Laughter]
i i was um i was paying attention to
some detail i i put like ammo's design
in there
and uh yeah i mean i like the name web
shopping ears i see the gears and yeah
yeah yeah i think like
you you um from from judging from your
streams i think you would really enjoy
going to space on your
own there you go please please use this
watch shuttle
it won't blow up right
[Music]
i have oh tested it but i mean it will
probably be fine
thank you thank you you're welcome
which means the only one left is me and
the only one who hasn't given someone in
prison yet i don't know who that is
i know i know
let me get rid of those wrappings
the last present must be for me
opening it up opening it up in three
two one
patient does it say patient at
[Music]
ignited passion by them vote did you
write that
yeah oh my god and if farewell if
e for real evil
oh
so it's not only me okay that's good and
ethereal beauty
risen again reason horizon reason i
always wanted
a new life a new chapter a new adventure
to be had
like an ember she closed all the way to
bottom left kiara will girl
any technical difficulties soon shall
pass
now a fixated case a punk healthy sweets
as kiana cuddles closely to cali for the
night here's to being
uh here's the beginning of a brand new
story it stars a phoenix and a reaper
let's call it tacoma
oh my god it looks so good
[Applause]
beautiful yeah pass me the mic
okay oh oh oh you have the mic
you have it uh here we go oh you want to
read that oh should i make it
here yeah you got to make it big
no let me hear you all right here we go
oh
oh yeah i need the reverb to be done a
little bit more hold on
oh oh uh yeah chiara the phoenix
a fiery soul ignited passion bright and
bold and ethereal beauty risen again
from the ash
a new life a new chapter a new adventure
to be had takanashi kiara
like an ember she glows all the way till
the bottom left kiara will go
any technical difficulties soon shall
pass now a fixated gaze up
upon as chiara cuddled closely to
prolong for the night
here's to the beginning of a brand new
story it stars a phoenix and a reaper
let's call it
takamori
sorry i just wanted to give it a little
oh wow
that's such a good poem thank you merry
christmas
i'll hang it i'll hang it up somewhere
on my wall here here somewhere
cute thank you yay
everyone's secret santa has been
[Music]
revealed
that was fun i like everyone's ideas
that's really cute
oh man this is what it's fun you know
how i said in the beginning that it
didn't feel like christmas well now it
does
thank you girls you made it so much
sweeter thank you
thank you guys coming up with the idea
thank
thank you all right i think we before we
go to the announcements that we have
announced that there's announcements
that have been announced not yet but
will be soon announced
um ame will perform something for us
please let me hear i think should we
leave the presents on the screen
oh yeah it's fine
all right yeah the stage is yours you
guys have an option you can have the
uh ceso version or the non-say so
version
original original original
original they're both they're both
original
we know which
that was an obvious choice
okay all done all right
[Music]
oh what fun it is to stream on christmas
oh what fun it is
[Music]
is
[Applause]
can you please can you please upload the
lyrics somewhere
yeah i'll be
i tried not to laugh during your singing
but it was hard to hold it back
that was good that is a clip that is a
clip going up right now
i already got it thank you for that
lovely
rendition of jingle bells amazing
and now i wonder about the about the
cecil version there's a say so virgin
would you like to sing that too
ah no no no it's just the same one
except without the last verse
[Laughter]
amazing lovely that's so sweet that you
prepared that
thank you amen
[Music]
i think now it is time for the
announcements let me ask the chat first
what do you think it is i have actually
um two announcements
what do you guys think it is one is more
like
about everyone and one is about some
some some people
uh-huh oh look at those people
that's going plus we're guessing they're
guessing weddings
interesting very interesting
oh well well shall we reveal i think
i'll first reveal the smaller
one supposedly smaller announcement but
still still a very big one
okay first announcement some people have
been waiting for this
and some people already kind of saw it
coming and i actually i already kind of
like
teased it very much but and callie also
teased it but
ah december 30
uh 30 30 first ice
move 30 of i actually didn't decide but
[Music]
[Applause]
this is actually a song cover from a
song from mick gm
a vocal light sound cover and um
the art and the the video is made by
yoona you know what up you know my my
kfp workers all know you know because
she draws very much for me
so we have been preparing this for quite
a while now and it is finally coming out
next week
[Music]
that's what i was talking about dead
deadbeats as well i mentioned to you
guys
um that uh the the saw there is a song
that i
i have this this month it's not coming
out on my channel it's on diana's
channel
oh yeah it will be on my channel yes yes
yes yes yes
it will be so cute i think many people
wanted something
uh from from takamori for a long time so
there you go now you have it
almost almost almost it's very it's a
very bubbly and cute song
but there's a bunch of wrap parts there
so i thought it would be perfect for
kelly
and now ah the next announcement
is uh regarding
oh everyone god well is everyone ready
yes it's something highly highly
requested
and finally is here presenting to you
from whole life english holidays
[Music]
whole life english origins t-shirt on
sale uh 25th of december so right after
this uh
on booth and on geekjack whole live myth
t-shirt illustrated by
takanashiki
[Music]
this is our big announcement what do you
guys think
um i tried my best to make everyone look
really really cute
it is a big honor to illustrate the
first
ever a whole live merch it really is a
big honor i hope i
i did it some justice and i hope
everyone wants to wear it every day
you can wear it to like conventions
anime conventions 2021
everyone can wear this t-shirt and then
everyone will know oh you're
hold on miss fan oh my god me too who is
your favorite
[Music]
[Laughter]
isn't that fun yeah it's
cool it's really cool
[Music]
and i think a tweet is coming out in a
little moment from the official
live english and probably also the
japanese
account so you can check out the twitter
and you can find the link from there i
suppose
i think it's pre-order first maybe i
don't know maybe it's just
it goes right on sale i'm not sure
[Music]
i want seven t-shirts so that i can wear
one each day
[Music]
wow yeah it's sold hours on the tag
monday
sold out and some people say the cr side
crashed good job guys go down
[Laughter]
great job good guys did it
congratulations so what do you mean it
sold out that yeah
how's that it crashed it crashed it'll
be back it'll be back yeah
it'll be back they probably just haven't
enabled the sales yet yeah they probably
will
probably will start right after the
stream they were just waiting for us to
announce it
it's not exciting i'll first learn
tonight
that's awesome oh my god i can't i can't
wait to see everyone wear it
yeah send pictures and selfies wearing
it you can wear it to bed oh yes
you can wear it on a date go down yeah
big
wear it on a date definitely here's the
hollow miss tag or something on twitter
yeah you have it yeah
well yes this concludes today's stream
uh thank you everyone for watching i
hope you had fun i think we all had a
lot of fun and there was a lot of
going on my screen is very cluttered
with fun images
[Laughter]
[Music]
does anyone else have an announcement by
the way
i have a collab with ha tama later i'm
going to be visiting
the jp minecraft server and
she's going to show me some cool stuff i
think while i'm there yeah
nice nice so nice oh yeah and
then you got me to an idea to the day
after tomorrow normally
the whole attack would be tomorrow but
uh whole talk is this time the day after
tomorrow i mean
at least at least in in my time zone uh
on sunday japanese standard time 10 a.m
it's one day later than usual
and whole talk guest is this time
[Music]
yes yes yes this time i hope she she has
many times already
um told me that she's worried about
whether or not she can
wake up in time and i am very worried
[Laughter]
she's basically foreshadowing what will
happen
so what you do is you tell her you tell
her to be ready
uh 30 minutes you tell her that the show
is 30 minutes before it actually is
that's what you're supposed to do
when you know people that are here
probably too late for that
shion is quite famous for um
oversleeping and then trending on
twitter for oversleeping so that'll be
interesting
i hope you have another activity
prepared yeah
we will be waiting for you on senpai
and also uh let me just announce uh one
more thing uh
i had on my collab on my on my schedule
i had
uh at the end of this week i had a
secret collab written on my schedule
now let me announce who that is uh for
some reason i i kept it secret until now
the collab will be withdrawn
[Applause]
[Music]
yes yes yes i'm doing a collab with
choco sensei on her channel
and she she sometimes does these uh
streams where she
basically um how to say she
not really interviews but what what do
you call that see
she does some tests in the quiz yeah
some quiz test stuff um on her guest
uh one-on-one and this time it will be
me i'm very excited
yeah it's like a intelligent test
not not a physical oh boy physical
examination oh yes that's it so much
going on oh my god anyway
yeah that's all the announcements i
think right
anyone else oh uh i'm doing a live show
yay
yeah i believe it's on the 29th
oh in japan so it's coming up soon
okey-dokey looking forward to that
looking forward to it yeah
and it will be archived it will be
archived so if you can't make it don't
worry
okay come hang out
[Music]
my dear whole life english members
thanks for coming to my room
and uh uh having this fun christmas
party celebration with me
i really had a an amazing time and i'm
looking forward to spending
2021 with you and uh treasure many
blessed moments with you next year as
[Music]
well
i don't know if you said that to me or
to the viewers but i love you too
i responded to inna to everyone
we love everyone we love everyone
and uh in my stream at the end we say
auf
wiedersehen
[Music]
oh no no dmca
foreign
[Music]