[Music]
la
a
[Music]
oh a
n
[Music]
a
why does chat look like
that
why wh
why
K the CSS is not working
so I don't
[Music]
know maybe I'll just make you
smaller like
this I guess I don't know why is it not
working eh
what the hell
okay um sorry I just woke up if I sound
weird
um
I uh this is my last day
today
[Music]
um yeah I don't know if I will be uh
doing it very long today because I don't
think I'm like really properly involved
in many um plot lines at the
moment and the ones that I uh like
thought maybe there could be something
like I've watched a clip uh of like the
whole am
gathan Arc and saw that like it looks
like am is like REM like um planning on
remembering gathan uh
today
um so uh she will not be open to become
my
maiden
um
yeah uh so I'll just like back out of
that uh I'm not going to like try to
push myself into that
um no it's
okay because gavan is very committed to
her so I I don't have a chance she's not
the type to take several wies
so I will stay maiden
lless and and then cie is not getting
online today she said she feels very
sick and has like a a different like
stream that she has to do regardless but
um so that means it's like kind of
difficult like I was going to end up
going to her and work at her place if I
had a maiden and had to put down my
night's duty but that's not happening so
that's also not happening yeah get well
soon
cie and then crony isn't around so I
can't continue any of that and I don't
know if herbs logging in today because
she would be like maybe supporting me in
the claim of nissa's Witch uh
witchness she was on earlier and what
she left again see so that's m going to
be
difficult
uh so I don't want to fight uh
Alone um like so I'm just going to
probably just say cuz apparently I'm
being uh narissa is apparently a ghost
and apparently I'm the cause of it
so uh I don't
I I don't have many people to back me up
so I'm just going to even though the
thing happened with like I cuz it was an
accident like literally and
then uh am like cured my sword from
accidentally activating but we're going
to put that aside
because uh no one's going to listen to
that so I'm just going to say I did it
be because I I've been told she was a
witch but then I have no one to back me
up because no one's like Herb's not
online so I'm just going to say yeah
what whatever yeah sure I did it um but
you can I will I will revive you I will
revive you as uh my what what's an a
fancy Medieval word for
apology
um I don't know help me Penance oh
wonderful atonement atonement Penance
atonement uh
Penance atonement I shall uh resurrect
you with my phoenix feather and then
hopefully she will not uh like be dead
anymore and not be mad at me
anymore that's the plan and then the
thing is be you I don't I don't I think
the finale with that will be tomorrow so
uh I'm help helping beu with not beu uh
Gigi with like building or preparing
stuff for that lead up today I
think
uh yeah they have a way to bring my NSE
I discussed with gigy because apparently
she does the
rituals for
it I I don't know what that really means
but um I like since like herb is not
there I see that as the only way to get
out of
this I no I don't
know I don't know how far m is with her
[Music]
thing I got to check with
M I'm overthinking it I have to
overthink it because I'm not good at
role playing spontaneous ly in this
language and I have um had not so many
chances to integrate myself because of
my absence so I have to overthink it
also because this is a very complicated
situation suddenly I'm on trial but guda
is not playing she I think she like
cancelled her stream right so I don't
know if the the trial is really
happening no
so better to just resolve it outside of
trial because yeah no not I guess no
trial exists but the what is it the gal
Gallows are not uh happening I don't
know
whatever all
right so it might be
short today I have to like clean and
pack and sign po Awards anyway uh so The
Gallows now I like the idea of gallows I
like it uh it's
funny so well let's see uh oh who is
online
huh oops see they haven't been on in a
while have
they let's see
uh I don't know if she's alone right now
if she can speak privately
[Music]
hello hello oh are you not talking
today or are you not in a position
to talk because you're
surrounded oh she's AFK
okay
really oh she just started her
stream but yeah she is streaming
right oh okay she might be AFK like
looking at a different screen
okay
um I kind of want to like wanted to do
more side quests too
but uh it's probably like better to just
focus on the the plot
lines she's a horse today what why is
this elastic cuz I can't play tomorrow
and tomorrow is the
finale but uh there there will be in
other chapters like arcs of this what
who is
that um in the future like not
immediately don't expect anything
[Music]
immediately what do you mean I can't
reschedule tomorrow no it's okay it
doesn't
matter it doesn't matter it's okay damn
this looks amazing
[Music]
there she
is
k
okay I'm so surprised that people went
so hard on building in
general like I didn't expect so many
huge
builds it's
incredible I I would have like loved to
build something if I wasn't like gone
for 3
days was
that like three people there
hello oh W it's me I'm stuck in this
place oh yeah oh oh my god oh don't
don't hurt your horse was there it's
okay I'll die oh no there you go I'm I'm
I'm
alive where are you uh here there we go
hello what a wonderful day uh my Amber
coin mate hello how you
doing uh I am fine thank you how are you
feeling today I'm eat beards look
up same same same well what are your
plans for this lovely
day I think I got to build something oh
another thing no it's just more thing
this time we'll see what you like to
build something as well I heard you
wanted to oh you heard me say
that yeah you were outside here ah it's
okay like I think
today uh since today is uh my last day
uh um I'm going to just try to clean up
my my blood lines you know
a i yeah yeah well good luck then thank
you but if you need if you need anything
while I'm free I can help I can assist a
thank you hello fiery
one wait I have an E I have an echoey
voice in my head my name is Shakira and
I don't trust you anymore get out of
here I have brought you the flowers get
out I don't want your FL brought the
flowers well I'm going to destroy your
bed anyway you're no part of the Kingdom
anymore but
why just betrayed me like that no okay
come come come here come here real quick
I don't trust you I'm
sorry
what oh what happened where did they go
oh m is
moving yeah my phone was
talking hello
hello are you are you currently capable
of
conversations I am hello hello uh are
you hi are you is this a safe place to
have a a a truthful
conversation I believe so
okay wait hold on I'll check if there's
any cameras or microphones hold on
okay what did I want her name to be
yesterday there was one really good one
Vivian right I'm going to suggest
it we are good oh shall we speak in
there inside oh I suppose
so Enemy Lines I guess it is your
territory
at the moment oh yes it is quote my
unquote is so yes yes first of all what
is your name today how may I address you
today oh
shoot
Vivian no I don't like that one can you
can you think of something
else uh how was
Margarita I don't like that one
either how about
Barbara I don't like that one either
what how
about how about
um careful careful careful careful why
must you betray me every day again and
again it's it is
unbelievable what's going on what are
you doing in fun of mar what do you mean
what am I doing I belong here it is what
are you doing in front of I do not
belong here I am I apologize I was I'm
I'm I got lost get out of here you
Heathen I got lost but I cannot leave
what made you think it was okay to step
in here I oh my I was looking for uh
something to putch do you want to buy
something um I was just checking what
you guys have in stock
uh don't open the door until she buy
something do you do you want to buy
something fiery one what do you we have
flowers flowers H
flowers we have
have a chocolate
cake a chocolate cake yes we have many
good things here many many well fishing
chips nothing of
Fun hack
hacks
[Laughter]
hacks uh let's
return scam evad
let's look at the carrier
[Music]
pigeon I do not understand
okay wa
ah
okay where am I
wait I got lost uh is it over
there oh I thought this was blocked I
thought you couldn't fall down
here the water is so beautiful for a
canal
canal oh uh where's gy is she still
there
is the fellow night gigy still around
here perhaps if I knock at her
door she may show herself to me oh she
doesn't seem to be at home
anymore knock knock
knock oh there she
[Music]
is he was in the way yes oh there
is yes T
Shakira oh sorry am I intruding I I I
can come later no you are not
intruding you come Feast your eyes on
the queen Tam
Gander she looks marvelous today as
every day yes as always her quite
beautiful there
good she died from a
misunderstanding that's it yes
well does do you is Tam G alive still
Tam is alive she's on an
expedition she will return once the
Expedition is over and she will come
back to this Kingdom and Rule and take
her rightful place as Queen Our
Queen yes no this is our Queen she's Our
Queen all of our Queen she's the queen
of this entire Kingdom she's married to
to the
kinging then what about Queen
NY what Melody Queen who n
NY
L the p l she is a queen of another land
she is not a queen of Le
bestl Tam gander is the queen of lesto
of these this true this is true yes yes
this is
confusing like have you seen any statues
of this other queen that you talking
about I have seen the the Crone Crown
Throne the throne the throne yes but if
she were a queen wouldn't there be
statues of
her this is the only statue I can see
yes this is the only statue in the lands
and is of our Queen T
Gander therefore she is the queen I'm
the Royal puppy you are the Royal puppy
of Evergreen I assume Evergreen yeah
that is where Queen Mario
rules yes I should go check with her yes
go go with haste run little puppy run
misconception she seems to be a little
confused but she's got the spirit she
has she the heart is within her indeed
good day to you good day wonderful
orange fellow yes uh sorry that I was a
little off yesterday I was going through
a bit but I am much much I am more
chipper today I am uh I am ready to take
on this new day you are more chipper
indeed yes yes I am feeling much better
what has caused
your sadness
yesterday
ah it just seems that haven't you won
the the Arena Battle wouldn't that make
you very very
delighted I was quite joyous that I won
the Arena Battle but there was just an
aching in my heart because of someone
someone who is no longer with us any
longer oh and aching in your heart has
she has she stabbed you in your heart no
she is gone oh
hello there the queen hello fluffy the
queen Tam Gander you must kneel amazing
the queen it is the queen Our Queen
beloved Tam Gander Tam Gander yes yes a
gander at Tam Gander yes Tam Gander you
are gandering upon Tam
Gander what an honor to use some flowers
at the Queen's feet oh no oh yes she
should she deserves flowers I will get
flowers sure appreci flowers she will
she will get a few flowers wow I'm going
to go check my chest oh
yes
well well so what you have not been
stabed in your heart are you okay I I am
fine it was more of a emotional flow oh
to have lost someone I considered so
dearly as you can see yes oh H so yes I
I see I see how it is well I hope those
wounds heal faster thank you while the
time lady Shakira I I appreciate it
perhaps kindness knows no bounds perhaps
when our Queen returns she shall give
you the
the power the strength to move on as you
so desperately need I am just holding on
until the day that the queen returns and
I know I know then that it would have
been all worth fighting
for I certainly agree with that well
so I was uh wondering about what we have
discussed yes uh yesterday indeed oh
regarding
the the princess princess princess have
you noticed come come with me yes oh
oh do you see
this oh my God it is quite terrify oh no
yes it once spewed water but now it
seems to spew blood or I do not know
what this is is quite terrify what has
transpired here I do not know but it
seems there is a corruption plaguing
these lands and it stems from The
Princess indeed yesterday it surely did
not look like this yes it did not
now what has happened to it it is quite
terrifying is she is she the cause of
this I believe that she is I believe
that she is the root of all the
corruption I do not know how to approach
it though I trust in you because of your
loyalty to Queen Tam Gander yes you can
trust
me and it seems that Miss ninoa has some
information regarding her h
is she she's not around she's not
around it seems there are people there's
people on their way
hello
hello we have brought someone with
us
terrifying such a beautiful you have
killed me Shakira and for that you must
pay why hey do not hurt her back ghost
back Jonathan she has killed me and my
child what oh is that you lady narissa
Raven coft yes look so much her voice
does sound familiar yes it is very
familiar you're so
transparent well I have an idea yes
isn't there what is your
idea in lady Shakira's yes memories in
her dungeon is there not a way for you
to be
revived I am unsure I is there a way I
am a phoenix indeed
and if you are truly not a witch I may
be able to give you one of my Phoenix
feathers to revive you and give you
another another turn in life but didn't
you kill her no she did kill me but if
she wants to make this right I will
accept
it the Phoenix Flames have chosen her as
a Target but I personally from my heart
and my soul want to offer her Phoenix
Feather to revive her once again how
great Phenix feathers must be very
valuable yes they are all
right I must however uh go pick one out
of my hair first so oh okay oh she must
she must her plumage fly then yeah I
shall return uh and I will try my best
it takes a little moment because it is
very painful to pick it out of my hair
okay okay you have you have about a
minute and 30 seconds that sacrifice I
it might take uh a few minutes longer I
will I will hurry I will
hurry H where where are chickens it is
Al so delicious where
chick where are chickens
is there anywhere where there are
chickens I need a feather to trade what
ah ah
ah uh well I don't know where this Farm
is damn it how about can I take this
ah can I take well let's just uh ah I
can't take
anything but maybe there's um not in
here I I can't do this so fast
well we'll just have to pretend
okay this is the lottery ticket and it
is completely free it feels like I'm so
slow I have found that a lot of
buildings are completely empty I have
returned
empty back already are you ready to
receive the Phoenix's blessing oh yeah
in about uh 40 seconds uh you can start
doing it now but make it take that long
okay one moment KY can you come here
yes yes my name is Jonathan
sorry jonath Jonathan do you have do you
have a don't don't follow us she wants
to speak to me privately yes privately
uh do you have do you have like a
chicken fed really quickly you me like
she's beautiful she deserves a body see
I may I may have one I just I might I
just need to combine it with my Phoenix
uh po oh yes yes yes yes I do have one
you are in
luck you are in luck you can become like
that as well I thank you I thank you
gratefully maybe but why would you
murder
FEA beted in I never
betrayed let me let me hand you over my
Phoenix Feather so that you may use it
in the right timing when you really need
all right all right
hi um one moment I have made a mistake I
need to still
uh put my Phoenix pow on it this here it
is I very excited to see
this me me as well I'm quite I'm quite
curious yeah well you must accept the
trade
request
wonderful here is the blue and turquoise
colored Phoenix better that will give
you another chance in life this this is
a chicken feather no it is a blue and
turquoise colored Phoenix
Feather oh
I
turquoise is a sparkly and blue and
turquoise colored Phoenix Feather I not
accept this gas lighting look it is
white what no it's blue and turquoise is
going to work I think the eyes of a
ghost cannot properly perceive the
phoenix feather is it because she sees
the world in a monochrome way Poss it
Phoenix
power what is this it takes a few
seconds it takes a few seconds
sometimes you are slowly regaining your
life energy get out of there what is
wrong with
you I think it is not working I was
expecting you know what that is a
phoenix fed does not so easily revive a
person it takes a few seconds have
patience for Life who did this hello
everybody what is going on what is the
conversation topic we are trying
to save the ghost you're trying to save
the ghost you're not quite ready for
Revival it seems oh yes I wanted this as
well I wanted her to be saved so that I
could use her to my advantage shall
return what is it what is it that must
be done to save her why did you say it
like that loser says what where the
ghost go I am not sure she
has loser said what loser said what I
don't know what her plan is
no
Los I said it waiting for the feather to
do it trick yes what what you need to
speak to me
about do you know how to unin visible
her uh she is a ghost currently and um
if she uses my feather at the right
timing when her life and her heart is
ready to return then it will take its
effect however and we can see her
beautiful face yes but one cannot be
impatient because the impatient ones are
not capable of using the Phoenix Powers
oh I see I see so you you are you're
very patient then I I am very
experienced this yes but she is it seems
to be her first time so she is uh a
little bit too excited about regaining
her life energy oh I see you must calm
her down ah well she ran away so you
must run after her m
but our conversation was not finished
yet either oh yes what were we
discussing um oh your plans are about uh
perhaps returning to ambercoin
officially I am an ambercoin yeah but
they don't but they don't know it yet
but when are you going to let them
know once my master plan is fulfilled
I'm receiving a call
oh hello
hello oh
oh who are these
people oh because I am a member of the
Scarlet wand she needs my help wink wink
I will go help her sure I will go help
you help help whoever may be in need of
help I had Shand in my eye it is a very
long and
arduous trials and tribulations but I
believe in thee I will come with you on
your quest and so nice where are the it
together
H well why don't you get my body and
then we can go and do yes you know I
will seek your body I will find it seek
my body bring it back I will find your
body call me once you have found my body
yes yes I will yes I shall can ride
horses while
you of course oh you do that my don't
worry about it call me once you have
found my body thank you yes I will call
you once I found your body so what's to
what um conclusion have you
come sorry I was just so taken aback by
her horse riding skills we need to take
her body back and then you got to give
her a blessing so she can merge the soul
and body together in a ritual that
Jonathan J will perform yes you you must
give her your blessing and and heart and
and then we will go to your your temple
and she will get the last hit on the
Statue and then her body and soul will
combine and she'll be one again yeah I
suppose that is indeed how it's done I
just forgot about it so yes the long the
long ritual yes the long ritual yeah it
is necessary for the
impatient uh Souls out there yes all
right I shall assist you in regaining
her body mhm
we I will find her body it must be in
the sewer system somewhere oh I will
find it in the sewer system find it yes
we will find it has has somebody dropped
her body in the sewers it seems as if
someone has brought her body down there
to rot in the C but we will find it it
is no matter that's why the smell such a
bad smell in this the bad smell is
because
yes the waters very disrespectful I
cannot believe this and then you may
come along with us because it is your
temple and you know the ways and then we
will watch her as she fights against the
final statue and okay her body will
become one oh yes oh yes yes that sounds
like a
plan shall we shall we
proceed oh but did you want to tell me
something Mario yeah I have something to
do first excuse me excuse us Shakira I I
I need a moment oh you open the
[Music]
door okay that got more complicated than
I
thought
uh we still need to save the
princess yeah I don't think that will
happen today oopsie oh no what is
this I think that will happen maybe
tomorrow wait um I seem to be stuck
I seem to be stuck in my own guils
castle
hello
help help
help I shall teleport
indeed what do we have this stone for
this holy Stone
do they
know they don't seem
to but yet some something seems to
always bring them back together some
kind of bond that seems to be connecting
them and their heart
are just meant to be together as
one some kind of special magic it must
[Music]
be yeah this also seems very cursed this
is also one of the princess's
doings
pathetic oh the princess oh there she is
she's standing right by her monument
that has been
corrupted oh she gone
again
H maybe it was just in my head the
corruption is starting to spread in my
head oh tell me let me know okay hey if
we have an open position I would be more
than happy to take you in no I meant
like open as in like in the stock market
oh in the stock Mark oh my well at this
time we are not public but okay that's
okay well let me know all right fiery
one greetings it seems like another
store has opened in town another store
has opened are you would you like to
purchase I am selling berries the
juiciest of berri and the highest
quality of meat we also have a
lottery if you care for a ticket the
ticket is free completely free oh what a
deal I would love to take a lottery
ticket from you if I may have one if you
have some in stock it is first come
first serve first 20 members are the
winners but I cannot tell you where you
are in the queue oh I have a good
feeling with this so I think I will give
it a try all right I'm sending you your
lottery
ticket handing it under the table under
the table we have to it's on the down
low you
see
what what on the what what under the T I
cannot see no no not it's a fig it's
it's quite literal and it's quite
figurative and I see how it is oh oh
what wonderful let me I think I can see
it now oh it came through under the
table
oh 100 coin for
free if you win if you're one of the
first 20
people the gods are on my side today for
sure wait is this going to be
tomorrow no it's today it isn't an hour
and 12
minutes wonderful I shall shall I be
here in this vicinity when that happens
that that would be most uh convenient
for me oh I'm so sorry wait no do not
I'm so sorry wait wait the green one
come back my math was incorrect I meant
to say 2 hours about 2 hours but it is
truly an hour and now 11 minutes oh
goodness I will send her I will send her
ad mail and then she will okay she will
understand oopsie doopsy well you're so
generous for doing this for free Lottery
yes I also have free things everything
here is
free we have the juices to berries and
the highest quality of meat can I
interest you in either or both Perhaps
Perhaps some more juicy steaks would
suffice some sorry I'm so sorry what did
you say some juicy steaks will suffice
juicy steaks all righty how many do you
want M perhaps about
20 20 or 10 okie dokie 10 I do not want
wish to be greedy in this uh charity
okay you want 10 open your mouth please
ah must I eat them all at once 3 4 5 6 7
8 9
10 I appreciate your
donation donation no this is
business okay do you accept
donations what do I look like a charity
case here currently what it ins
but an insult to think I would need
donations there's no one around us right
now I just want to help you support the
there is there is a behind you
hello I made opinion that you will buy
my items that I don't need anymore you
this this is a some game of telephone
that went wrong I I'm not doing that
what oh you w well if I ask nicely will
you cuz I have a very very uh wonderful
wooden axe and a wooden pickaxe has been
well loved like could use a new home and
your home looks like a good home for
them
right sure what what sure I'll take that
what's that what was that just now
wooden wooden tools at this day and age
I don't have much money so I I would
expect some money for my well- loved
items oh I'm so sorry but there is a
recycling fee it is one coin per
item
reasonable never mind that doesn't sound
good can I interest you in the juiciest
of berries or the highest quality of
meats meat they're free they're free yes
this sounds
scary it is not what's in it what's in
it berries and meat I can confirm her
foods are very delicious and I I have
had my tummy full of it the ju berries I
have a lot of things though a moreu is
always looking for food maybe she'd be
interested she already took some oh
really yes you can trust me it is
completely free nothing weird is going
to happen absolutely nothing weird is
going to happen she's just of good heart
believe her I know I'm not going to feel
sleepy right no you will not no I don't
know something's funny about your voice
voice there is nothing funny about my
voice give my I don't know I'm getting a
weird feeling down would you like to
know the secret the reason why it is
free okay why the reason is because we
are in competition with the
funart and the fart prices are just
simply not fair so we have lower prices
to encourage people to come to this
establishment they have they have ruined
the economy in our lands and she is
merely trying to fix them again I'm here
to balance everything out and the juice
is
free the berries and the meat you can
make it into juice I could do it for you
oh I'll I'll accept the juice the juice
wait do you want the meat to become
juice or the berries to become juice I
like berry juice berry juice
okay all righty I chewed them and made
it into juice would you like some okay
I'm not too sure of how hygienic that is
but I'm very clean I accepted the wrong
Quest here I'll I'll throw in an extra
that's enough room room really really
really that's okay I can hold on to them
or you know
what I will take one of your wooden
tools oh really to encourage encourage
you to come back and see me again okay
to take more berries or perhaps get a
taste of the juiciest of
meats you take take this just one just
one gu what
[Music]
okay pleasure doing business
a thank you oh you're behind there now
too what look so scary yes aren't you
both wearing the same hats aren't you
both working for the same guilt you
should be able to trust her no I I
received this hat from Jonathan oh
Jonathan G yeah it's only kind to wear a
present that you get right would be
happy indeed indeed cute but it seems
like is is a proof of someone's uh
realness I changed the conversation
topic too early oh God I'm so
embarrassed I'm so
embarrassed what's wrong before you go
can I interest you in a lottery ticket
it is completely free first 20 people
who take the
ticket win you said it's free it is
completely
free it is tell you where you are in the
queue but first 20 people take the
ticket well win oh I don't worry about
it this Lottery there's no scam involved
there is no risk at all you say it like
that that's very scary no it is true I
have bought a ticket as well and
received it
safely no I've seen what kind of things
um Mo has been up but you're not
spending any money you're not spending
any money there's nothing that you are
losing than you for the
[Music]
juice well higher chance for me to win I
suppose exactly I appreciate you helping
the business by encouraging more people
to take
oh oh I'm on a phone call excuse me Good
Luck your endeavors I shall support it
when you need me thank you dearest
Shakira ofes seems that we have obtained
narissa Raven cft's body it seems that
your feather has done enough that her
body has returned but we must combine
her body and soul so we are going to
make way to the temple would you like to
meet us my feather has worked after all
even after all the doub your fether has
worked yes yes it did work I have told
her soul and she has still adopted me
well then we shall retrieve her soul we
will combine the souls shall we meet at
the temple using our warp Stone oh that
is a great idea I shall be there
immediately yes I will see you there
[Music]
farewell
Fair see told you Soul told you Soul
Phoenix Feather always
works Phoenix Feather always works look
uh this one Mountain
Road uh
no
uh
here I have a rifle wonderful you have
already regained your
body yes it is delightful to see
converting the chicken feather into a
phoenix Fe has proven to be quite very
very effective but only halfway now we
must speedrun a dungeon let us go let us
go oh could have taken the quest oh it's
fine toon toon toon
toon maybe maybe we should join the
party call oh uh
yes gathan please join the party call
yes I will join the the telepathic link
yes the telepathic link indeed here we
are into let us go the Shakira dungeon
once again yes
yes be careful found a shortcut of Sword
yes this way be careful it's quite
dangerous you do not want to fall I'm
sorry I have built it this way my family
just had a lot of fun with it yes no
problem quite meticulously planned it is
wonderful thank you a lot of work went
to it over
Generations Generations I can I can tell
I can see o have your families in the
past built similar things I do not
remember remember yes oh you do not
remember your
family no we do not
any oh that is really sad yes it is very
very sad oh
goodness I have fallen I am disgraced
how how do oh my God I fall again
please get the
checkpoint I have fallen
too no we can't all be falling this we
must we must speed run
it the fate of the kingdom it rest upon
it oh while while you were gone Shakira
yes nura ravencraft has apprised me of
some very interesting information oh
oops what might that be yes it seems as
she has come to the same conclusion as
us
that the king fall off the edge May oh
yes the king may be a stain oh yes no no
the king yeah he creates the stains I
think he is the stain King and he has
corrupted our princess our dear princess
mhm oh no not again yes I do not know
what we should do but seen such things
in the
past that is to us to stop ter fate it
is a very terrible
fate a terrible fate indeed I felt like
I saw her today close to her Temple
already a little while ago and then she
disappeared quickly almost as if some
kind of dark magic was possessing her
she was flickering in and out yes she
was doing
that weird what is she what is she up to
what is the the evil evil possession in
her doing to
her yes what indeed it is quite a
strange corrupting our
lands oh our
lands yes have you not seen the
Cerulean uh that is a biggest tell the
Cerulean the Cerulean plot ceran it has
begun there did you see the forest the
corrupted Forest the corrupted Forest
indeed I have witnessed the corrupted
Forest it is something I I've only seen
in my nightmares
before wait the corrupted Forest
where oh did you not see it next to the
Statue of the
queen I did actually it is a new
addition right yes it's like the
corruption is spreading into the
kingdom it is very very terrifying I've
noticed it is crying blood yes it is
crying very very dangerous tears it is
quite horrifying we must we must get
your body with great haste yes we need
your power something terrible terrible
happens I will get this for you my
queen po Queen Tim Gander our powers
must be combined we are doing this for
you
Queen
yeah
forward oh I
I um I'm sorry uh that was the wrong
button that I have pushed correct button
I believe oh yes we must die before we
can progress yes the gimmick of this
such is the life of a phoenix I will
take this L bear thee
well right me too for me it is just
another day in my
life another day another Revival
rebirth Loop endless loop
I'm tired of it sometimes I wish to just
die no no we need you yes you are all
that holds us together death is not
allowed you will rise
again I shall I shall at this very
moment I am at the
end are you ready at the end of this
part at least where are
you we went up the ladder yes M all
right I shall follow I can smell your
scent I'm slowly
dying I also
dying that might be a malfunction in the
castle that my family has built I
apologize your family built a lot of
traps in your
Castle yes it's quite inconsiderate they
were possibly quite
sadistic I would say
so very very sadistic but I would say I
have not inherited those jeans from
them that is good to know yes if
anything I am I am more on the
masochistic side I believe yes oh thank
you for not building a torture chamber
for us to go through for me I'm glad
here
oh for me it is more like a fun chamber
but oh no that that felt good it's did
it that felt amazing it feel good now it
is just almost like a
massage I have opened the pathway we are
almost there to the end thank you you
are quite fast gathan you are indeed we
are working together
yes a little pain is necessary if it is
for the
kingdom yes no pain no gain as they say
in my family yes yes I have received the
next checkpoint m thank you
Fest Raven ah I will fall I will go to
the checkpoint no by orange it okay we
have made
it it seems we are drawn to the orange
juices the orange lava I will go to the
top side one and I will I will get it
yes you will speedrun the
Maze yes I will speedrun the Maze
above oh there's already one light
activated
you grow are so fast at this it's as if
you have visited my family's Castle
several times in the past yes yes
multiple times I am
quite there I say familiar the yes
familiar with your family sadistic ways
oh it's almost as if it has been treated
as a kind of tourist attraction these
days almost I mean it is quite a nice
place to hang out I must it is a nice
place but it's it is not just a
playground for people as you know it is
also there to ser greater causes such as
Revival of souls or combination of souls
with bodies yes yes I'm going to attempt
Revelation Revelation I wasn't too early
it was too
early
no I jumped from the wrong wrong
spot be careful my dears it's very very
dangerous in here do not underestimate
the Phoenix
Flames they can cause great
harm I'm Not
Afraid yes we must do this we must
conquer our
fears I'm not afraid of fire I should
just go this way
[Music]
what yo what yo what is
okay ah
my thing that I've been using to get
over that isn't working it's no longer
working I don't know why I'm pretty sure
that's not watch this
Revelation what no there's another
hole help I am not sure how to assist
you when you are so far from my hands my
goodness how does one go about this area
again I I have
forgotten ah ah no bro what's going
on you fall down to um I just wanted to
make sure you're okay it seems like you
were
not yeah yes I'm fine now it is it is
all right it is all right I I quite
enjoyed the
uh the Onan yeah well as long as you are
in this uh yes the building you can
revive forever endlessly as their
Phoenix powers are imminent thank
goodness otherwise I fear that we would
have long been dead already Revelation
why did my Revelation not work what why
did my Revelation not work ah ow there's
great pain I think perhaps your
Revelation is connected with your heart
and as your heart is broken your
Revelation grows weaker no no no that is
not true it is not
true it is okay it is okay to accept the
truth no it's not true do not believe it
Gan believe that my double jump the
heart has great effect to our
powers I can confirm I will grow
stronger I just need to I just need some
time to grow stronger have you yet to
activate the next checkpoint no I fell
because my Revelation had failed
me you must you must try to also help um
no as I said I am masochistic I also
enjoy uh seeing myself suffer so I want
to make this as long as
possible I see I see I see watch this it
will work now
Revelation I have done it I have done it
I love this suffering no don't make it
faster make it slower look at
you my soul will be revived I can feel
it I can feel it as well why are we
still in the same place oh we are going
going to the next area oh yeah I forgot
about this part ah yeah I am
falling what a masochistic place it
seems my body is out of balance because
I have given away a
feather now I cannot fly properly
anymore I need to get used to this
imbalance true
yes thank you for getting the checkpoint
yes great you're quite welcome I see it
I see the statue we are getting
closer soon your body will soon become
one with its Soul oh my mother my mother
is close I can feel her anger oh no your
mother she wants to ah curse us with the
Flames but I will I will tell her to do
the opposite and
gracefully give us the blessing here we
go oh no I am going we got this with
great taste oh wonderful
thank you mother she is
mothering mother is mothering oh oh oh I
got it
oh is it this
way you are orange and you are so
talented in these challenges perhaps you
have some genius for the queen it's
worth it I oh yes get the next
checkpoint the queen I've gotten it I
received it please meet me at the
checkpoint on my way
yes Maiden you are incredible mother or
sir Jonathan
mother once again I meet you we must let
her get the last hit pleas the only way
please mother have mercy on us please do
not be angry we only want to borrow your
powers for Revival want
revive to join the soul and body of ah I
am on fire it hurts but
it doesn't hurt as badly as yesterday it
is okay o you become stronger I I am
stronger now I presume we must uh after
all prove ourselves uh worthy of the
Revival
yes she wants to be bonked so we shall
help her with
that all right I am on it but I shall
give you the last hit of course yes yes
thank you fair Maiden
mother I am sorry sorry Mom
me sorry oh okay all right I will leave
the rest to you yes it has become a
little bit
dangerous get the last hit is the only
way on you go on you go we have
completed it feel again you feel it do
you feel it yes I
feel so
alive H the this magic has worked Han
huz huz oh you are to touch
again you are finally whole huzzah thank
you for saving me yes it is no problem
what a glor day yes all right now we
must find princess beu and help her
Perhaps Perhaps there's a a way to save
her after all I will too I will warp to
Leal Castle me too all right we must
find princess beu
is she is she
around is she around her Monument
perhaps join our party
call she's not even in our party
oh hello Jonathan we have revived her
hello fluffy one it is good to see you
no longer AO a pleasure to see you today
I'm sorry I'm not I'm not in the party
we have just revived m The Raven craft
how do we make a
shield a shield from the seems you may
need some iron and and some uh I will
make one for you guys it's no problem
yes let me see if I have any I have iron
I have iron too you have some iron I I'm
here now oh at this my shield welcome my
cat gathan you are quite the kind Knight
Jonathan it's Jonathan Jonathan with a
jeans is Jonathan I will go get it I
will go get it I felt sad that you had
died cuz you kissed
me
cute
run so did you did you get your body
back did S I have retrieved my body and
her soul I'm no longer
dead let's
go yes I alive again but now we must
search for princess beu cuz we are quite
worried about
her my daughter what did oh here you go
I will trade
you take this Shield yes would you take
care of my daughter in my house problem
fluffy one oh thank you I will return in
the party call but I have to leave for
now no it is everything oh your
inventory is full you have too many
things in your pocket yes I have gar I
will I will trade you of a shield okay
thank you
garage yes yes for
you is huzzah Bow Bow it okay yes is
there any way to make it extra strong
Shield there we go this is the only
Shield okay I feel like I'm up to
Shakira
I am awaiting our next action
that
is it is looking for the
princess gathan we are in a to the
gardens is destroying
it oh what what is going on to the
gardens to the
gardens the gardens we must stop her
which Gardens the gardens right by the
build area you guys passed it see
look I do not think I do not
st stop
it and starvation will come upon us stop
it no what is she doing you remember me
what is
happen prin oh no she's out of control
oh nice moood thanks um I must I know
that it is a very treacherous thing but
I must be away talk about this
Revelation I didn't think it's going to
work I shall better not use my
Revelation on these fields I I don't
want to use my too fiery to the
princess I can't believe the person who
wasn't planting stuff was the princess
herself please don't you remember your
mom princess princess stop we will all
die do you want us all to die when we
have no food station will come
if we don't stop her no no that is our
last rations
rations I don't know to say the word
stop stop no no I
replant perhaps I shall replant in
something I she's Unstoppable stop her
she is Unstoppable I don't know how to
stop
her stop
stop stop
Revelation
princess princess maybe she just need a
hug come here H oh
no made the land starve no no no no no
no no no no no no no we cannot let this
happen replant
replant don't just replant the seeds
make sure you replant the actual carrots
and potatoes too yeah oh oh yes I
shall the unthinkable has happened who
would have known that we would get into
this kind of trouble you what happened
to my lovely daughter I don't
know destroying the
kingdom I can't believe
it it has it seems like we have uh
become the farmers
I didn't think I would be a farmer it is
my new occupation but for the Lance I
shall do it all for the queen yes for
the queen I'm going to start with
potatoes
now maybe in this area potato
potato as as as an avid farmer myself
it's quite nice when the area is
completely filled with one thing for a
while uh is that sarcasm my sense or no
no no oh I'm just explaining what I'm
doing so if you see me tearing stuff up
you don't get
confused is this not the way of a
farmer am I doing it
wrong I don't know but I'm quite
distressed how could your daughter do
such a thing Queen Mario I don't know I
just don't know what maybe you erased
her wrongly no that's not how it
works m
[Music]
no I I'll make this back area beats back
here can be the beat
area
well I don't I I hope she will not
return and undo all of our hard work
once again
hopefully that would be cruel of
her well that seems to be what she's
aiming
for CR
destroying well it looks marvelously
green once again is possessed by
something I I just don't understand what
like Nisha do you remember about the
corruption that you mentioned about the
king yes I do believe that this might be
his doing I think maybe since you've
been trying to usurp his throne as the
rightful Queen trying to also marry the
other rightful Queen Tam gander um that
he has seen you and the princess as a
threat and is hence here to try and take
you
down via your
daughter cuz seeing her corruption will
make the citizens of lie Estel doubt you
as she is around cusing chos you're so
right I need to do something about it
yes I need to send my Pon as soon as
possible yes do not wait make haste I do
now
what has my cat
[Music]
done meow what has my cat
done poor little
kitty all right I think we've done a
good job replanting the gardens perhaps
we will not starve only for one or two
days until this has grown back there
this whole area back here oh it will be
fine we can regrain
everything it will be beautiful again
Bountiful indeed over over time m
everything will be all right cuz even
after a harvest has been destroyed you
can always plant new
seeds
beautiful thank you well
said what are you planting at the
moment beets beets more beets since this
whole upper area is
beets for the most
part all right success we shall leave
the garden for now yes
yes perhaps we
shall uh get like somehow make it
inaccessible for her wait is it over
here as well no
no wait how many Gardens do we have are
these all empty what yeah we have come
so
late we really have huh here go go off I
will fix it give me give me your seeds
yes the seeds and do you also want the
grown potatoes uh yes I don't have I I
have room for just one more thing so
maybe for now I I think I need beet
seeds beet seeds you shall have thank
you I have many I shall fix the gardens
to the best of my ability okay I wish
you luck thank you for the people of
liestal for the people of liestal
well well
well why could we not stop her
sooner well Marissa has regained her
body and her soul for the
lesbians she seems to be of sound mind
again if she was ever a witch maybe will
not be proven anytime
[Music]
soon but perhaps in chapter 2
for now I shall
be of help with my Phoenix
powers and give her the benefit of the
[Music]
D whose lands are these the ceruleans
how are we allowing this to grow on the
Cerulean lands
anyway maybe we must get rid and cleanse
the corruption
here anyway let me try to
call uh oh wait are they in a party call
no let me try to call gigy uh
gathan gathan with
[Music]
a g
with oh yes the damage on the farming
lands has been greater than expected it
but greater than expected yes but Nissa
is currently on it um what are you
currently doing I am playing a a mini
game currently a mini game how
delightful on these sad trying times yes
where is
it um at the Amber Hall Guild Amber Hall
Guild
M maybe I shall join yes you should come
join if I find it let me try to find it
we would be delighted to have you
okay
Amber that's my isn't it like in the
middle of the garden like some
Gardens uh west of
me uh that
way is it that way
yeah mini games to cheer us all up again
and put us in nicer Weller
Spirits this is the
Amber
Gardens but isn't she speaking of the
game that is next to
it this one I know of this game I do not
know of the other
[Music]
one she
misspoke she meant the Scarlet Guild oh
where the arena
[Music]
is she has misspoken I see well the
arena was
uh wait wait arena is Jade oh God
uh Scarlet W Hall oh God
uh wait I am
hungry let me eat the fruit that I have
gathered from the remains of the field
from the
crops
M beetroots M potatoes raw raw potatoes
raw beetroots
[Music]
M I am confused it seems you have
misspoken and now I'm uh severely
confused it is the Scarlet one Guild the
red ones I very sorry is that um what
shape is it it's the very pointy hat um
yeah but red Jonathan I am
ready um yes I am
ready what does it look like it's the
red Guild um it is a building by the
arena I believe I believe that is near
the arena the arena okay I shall find it
do not disappear
[Music]
there wait I just pass it over there
over there ah this one ah so confusing I
need like V visor uh can we put up like
some signs like this way is that way is
that every normal town has such signs
signage
wait it is taking me longer than
expected is it here it must be here
oh oh okay we have to we can't let her
win uh n this
is what is this oh it is a game we are
playing a game such a colorful
game yes you should play as well what is
happening I'm not sure I understand the
system it seems to be a pattern
recognition
game is too strong it seems we're
playing a pattern recognition game p
what are you whispering to yourself
about what what is going what is going
on may I ask I was I was trying to focus
and talking to myself to Hype psych
psych myself up oh I
am oops cck one
mysterious very mysterious okay okay
okay it reminds me of of a food what
called hot dogs what are you whispering
to yourself I see I see ketchup I see
mustard and I see the the
green onion like
things that is all I can think of as I
am hungry relish
yes a shame is a
shame what is what is wrong
what I hate
you I hate you oh goodness goodness I
wasn't talking to you I was talking to
myself because I'm so disappointed in my
prep oh I see I see well well you should
you click on this person you speak to
this person and then you press you let
him know that you would like to join the
game oh pardon I should read the rules G
yes me I have opened a new establishment
called Nana 11 and we offer the juiciest
of of berries and the highest quality of
of of meat and we also have a lottery
it's free to enter I would love to enter
your lottery would you like to enter the
lottery first 20 people who enter
win oh what have I won am I won of the
first you don't you don't know if you've
won yet oh I highly recommend her
Services all right you I will give you a
ticket hold on I'm pulling it out of my
pocket they are very profitable have to
go to
the I am looking forward to it
here is your
ticket I also got a
ticket now you all have
tickets yay in only 31 minutes won't the
lottery be pulled it will in 31 minutes
wonderful
huz generous be sure be sure to meet me
at the N 11 where I will announce the
winners I be there with great haste in
30 minutes will you be here playing this
game in the meantime no I think that
it's rigged
oh yes be aware this game is rigged oh I
want to give it a try sometimes you
don't have the color that you think you
have and sometimes you don't scroll
enough or sometimes you scroll too much
and it is not your it is not your fault
it is the fault of the game but yeah
will keep theid want and sometimes they
I know we're not perfect none of us are
perfect it's okay it is okay but just
but just be aware that sometimes also it
says that the blocks are in one spot but
and then they move them somewhere else
so it tricks you making you think you
just have really bad
memory I see what oh there is treachery
a what in this Guild in this Guild Hall
you treer co honest mistakes human eror
I mean human
yes we aren't robots here well you
should try one more time I will not be
entering I will be allowing um Miss
Shakira to enter so I would like to see
you guys I will stay quiet I promise you
one more time no you should play as well
you should play as well I would like to
see you one more time you do not want to
play against lady Shakira oh I would
love to play Lady Shakira Shakira
Shakira well I am a beginner in this
game I I I I I'm not sure yet of how to
play it but is everyone ready anybody
you shall go I'm ready ready to be
distracted and to be rigged no I'm not
rigged to experience other other world
other rigging what yes yes yes how
terrible maybe you should submit a
complaint are these not your gu
leaders no I will put a note and let
them know that it's out of order it
needs to be fixed yes yes yeah maybe we
should do one more try so we can like
really test if it's out of order or
what's the problem you know backing
Check Yes okay okay whoever the first
one has to start the game it was me oh
oopsy begin okay
begin so may the best memory
okay like
so oh
easy so you have been playing this for
30 minutes green one
yes yes I have been and you would say
that your memory is quite this is fun
good this is delightful uh no no the
plague may be on our L but this is
delightful it's
fine but I saw that you had gotten the
high
score oh yeah but then you beat me I did
not beat you did not look at the other
colors oh yes oh yes I did not te your
high
score I like I remember this one maybe
you are yes maybe you do have SL this oh
thank you for Fletching me like that I
forgot the other colors already a book I
would like to donate to your library
difficult I shall say that this is
rigged then I shall agree what did you
put in your cake
today cake oh a strawberry it is only
red when I am failing course princess
yeah the princess do you think she will
take now it is rigged I don't know she's
speaking weird to be honest I talking
her and she did like this thing and like
once it
worked weird it has been a little
strange forgotten you do not sense that
something is no I have not forgotten
rigged I definitely know something's
different but I don't know what and no
one's told like told me what's wrong and
everyone's confused as I am apparently
yes it is quite very confusing may you
have to share with me May at the library
in a bit yes in the library in a bit in
the fart Library I assume yeah yeah The
Great Library yes yes yes the greatest
library of them
all it was rigged it was rigged it
was present where it was
not what a terrible do you think that it
is the green one rigging it she seems to
be beating everyone no because you beat
me
why are you coning against me Jonathan
what have I done you I am not I am not I
was just a thought a thought in my head
again again again again again again
again go again again it is certainly
rigged because I have
failed yes only then it is R you can
play this time Jonathan I'll watch if I
were to win it would not be rig again
again again again again did you enter Mr
Chira let's play two games on once two
game what other game shall we be playing
the quiet
game the what oh the quiet game game a
very hard game what does the loser what
does the loser have to
do the loser there need to be a
punishment does there need to be a
punishment wait why but why why does
there need to be aish in this game
playing in this round and then you are
not even you are going to enforce a
punishment when you're not even play I
thought I have to be quite as as well
okay I won't be quiet okay ready ready
ready ready are you signed up I I have
signed up yes ready ready I shall
participate in the quiet
game we are going to participate in the
quiet am I not allowed to speak I guess
we not allowed to speak it seems that
okay nanu does not want us speaking for
some reason you hear me then I will not
speak do you hear her
n do you hear them I think we are
failing at the quiet game oh we feeling
it's a quiet game going to okay okay
it's not a one two 3 2 1 2 3 3 2 1 2
three do you hear
them some voice in my head is
obstructing me
Unforgettable what what is that song hey
What's six I mean Jonathan what's 6 *
12 what is what 6 * 12 well beautiful
pattern
in the land of lesto we are not taught
algebra Jonathan tell me what happened
where what's with the princess oh what
no you cannot just ask that in the
middle of the fields oh I have why game
is a fun game
no I do not have to answer that oh okay
sorry my bad I don't know I didn't I
didn't know I was stepping on a mine
there sorry uh Jonathan how did the how
did the Revival of narissa the ghost
go it went fine it wait what are
youc it was successful it was successful
it was fine with the power of my family
we have revived her Jonathan I'm sorry
did I I didn't mean to step on any toes
I was seriously asking I was just
curious It's just okay I understand you
had good intentions it it just so fine
it's nothing the Revival went well it
went perfectly well it was fantastic and
wonderful that's good that's good I
didn't I didn't like that sadness in
your voice so I I maybe we should change
the topic uh shall shall we how shall we
change the topic um how has your your
little statue gone for Tam Gander oh
it's going wonderfully the the statue of
the queen is going much better oh not
bad not bad true game it has gone
decently for me the game has been fixed
oh it is no longer rigged it is no
longer rigged no longer rigged this was
and this was the game that determined
who had the absolute best memory
interestingly I wasn't even playing it
seems a little bit unfair we say it is
not rigged when when the when the green
one is not participating I sense a
pattern oh my goodness there may be a
pattern indeed a pattern wait we must
test it one more time
acent it yes not you should play again
and see if the green one is the problem
oh no I have played enough you have
played you do not want to play any
longer I have played enough what about
the voices in my head are growing tired
oh I see well they have very little
stamina it seems let's what seems so
they're quite
weak quite weak minded Shakira there is
another game at the Cerulean cup Guild
you patch chickens in a basket you may
have more fun playing that yes sound fun
oh chickens I see chickens in the basket
oh it seems the game has begun
however oh this one I will watch we are
playing again there there's not been a
single one that I've watched I've had to
participate in them all ah nanu nanu
[Music]
yes her name is nanu today Jonathan yes
okay such a simple name today did did
everyone join
Jonathan did you join I'm getting a call
sha yes I did join okay I'm
starting what are you up to I'm playing
a mini game currently in the in the red
guilds
Chambers uh I think we're about to end
this one but there's another game that
we might start right away the the the
other mini game with the chickens in the
Big Blue building red red green
red there BL
we are not sure if it is riged so maybe
you're you can help us determine
it oh God the voices are not helping
ladies they're sabotaging me
too I see you later uh goodbye cat
Alabama Alaska Arizona Aransas I cannot
focus anymore how was that
corrected
green green red two yellow two yellow to
the side salt I shall not listen to the
voices no they're influencing
me to
remember I will never forget you cannot
distract me it will still BL spinach
okay okay okay okay oops I pressed the
wrong one
I cetch up I cetch
uped I shall do my best they're also
trying their
best you forgot the red one there
you over there you forgot it red one you
forgot the blue one you doing great
ladies
actually
top a red there's another red oh no the
you it helping there is yellow there is
a
red
everything falling apart you are going
to
lose you
cannot it is rigged it is rigged it is
rigged once again rigged it is because
of the green one I believe it's the
green one the green one it's the green
one that is rigging it how come she
always wins it is not realistic the
green one always wins it is rigged it is
because she is paying the last time
Jonathan joined it is because she is
paying them she's paying them off she's
paying this D off hold on hold on let me
step in here I think it's an honest
mistake I think she's doing something
unintentionally she doesn't know what
and she's just as confused as we are and
just as scared as we are confused she is
very confused and scared it's kind of
strange to be honest I wonder what's
going on oh may I should not play this
game again should we go to the chicken
game we shall
go to the chicken game instead everyone
should go to the chicken game The ceran
Guild continue
there though ow oh your head attempted
horse murder matching horses matching
horses wait hold on hold on Whose horses
are matching I will I will I will I will
I as Horses do your own oh you must be a
wealthy
lady she has
almost I too will match I too will match
I will also match how come you so
many wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait do you have this polka dot this one
does not have the this is an impostor
there are no polka dot oh goodness good
the wrong horse again wrong horse oh you
thought that me still Inc no help help
now oh there we go
there we go finally matching
cowes yes yes
okay this
way I follow we follow her I could be
lying I do not know where it is you
could be I'm trying to learn how to
trust
people trust one day I will know the map
and then nothing HS stop trust is a
difficult Al coin
Guild isn't it here to the
left here to the left
ladies is a little sick ladies please
please do not make him self conscious I
think you have gone the wrong
way I found it I found you have infl his
ego please calm down seems we have gone
in a circle oh no this is
correct here it is oh it seems someone
is
already hello oh how fun
are you catching the chickens yeah I'm
catching the chickens she's capturing
chickens very good very good thank you
for helping
out it is cute how wonderful does this
distract you yeah
okay now you can see it's fine can this
game be played from both sides couldn't
I
see is okay can you catch me catch me in
the basket
yeah I want to be caught I don't know if
you want that I think these are for
dinner dinner it is over you know you
know Shakira I think you should open a
restaurant okay everybody click ready
join the game oh we can play together I
think
so oh it says another player already
enjoying the game is it only two people
can two people okay two people I leave
my brought to someone else go for
it
uh I have joined the game did you join
as well you should start now oh wait
wait who joined I have joined I don't
know who else has joined you how many
how many people can join two it's okay
you do and then I'll we'll do the
next it seems she's a little bit
preoccupied with her store another
player is already playing it seems only
one player can play here
Raven fast hello can I you you must
start here completely
free who am I playing
against oh NAU wait how do Ive oh oh go
go go oh maybe it's not worth to go for
certain chickens maybe some of them have
to be dropped you no I my eyes are very
focused on the chickens oh the most
important Target wonderful yes the
wonderful mov the bucket from right to
left in amazing come to me little
[Music]
chickens Mario is trying to distract her
but she's not succeeding it is
impossible to get them all but I will
try my best to take you all under my
wing Shakira is focused come here come
here into my safe warm fluffy wings
I wonder know what she's going to do
with the
chickens they will work for me and some
will die for
me and die for you in honor terrifying
in
honor fuers what fck how has it gone yes
[\h__\h] oh that was really good well was
I up against do that you my first time
Le and it's okay you can exchange it
this way but you you like
a leader board
yippe Yi
huz I want to play again
five I see is it perhaps only one person
at the time after all what the hell no
I've already played oh
talk
oh can we meet by oh I see with this
go
no kitty cat go catch the
chickens it's difficult sorry they
are going wherever they want to go we
hope to um to to drive them out of
the there you go there you go they're
falling in my head as
well it is full of chickens
M they're flapp in their
wings they're excited to come to
you yeah they want to be
adopted can't wait to eat them adopt the
chicken today fortunately it's
not cute we have the perfect emote for
that oh you have done it what a
wonderful high score not
bad oh I before no I sent you five in
the disc scord that is your mind one
more one more
attempt you're welcome I want to top the
high score of the chicken game hello
hello is it
happening what no I just sold tickets
over
over this m when is the lottery being uh
announced in 11 minutes okay in Nana 11
minutes yeah marvelous wait not quite
because that would be 18
[Laughter]
oh it was 11 a joke H what is
that something
fun chickens let's go come into my arms
here sparkly one right away how I love
to see it
sparkly this is looking like a good one
oh oh the sparkly is worth it right how
many how many does it count for oh no
I've abandoned it but for the sparkly
one not my best not my best R I must say
h let's stay on this
side
and one of these games and then I will
return to not o what a
run amazing and there I will anounce
I've missed a sparkly one I hope I'll
win
ah
ah more chickens oops more
chickens come on you got to do
more you're doing
good no what how is this worse than my
first try
impossible why are you abandoning me
abandoning me Jens why for what
reason yeah
hm sparking ones do not give extra
points they
don't why are they sparkly no the
sparkly uh I think they give you like a
buff a temporary buff they got you get a
little little little faster
oh oh no glowing chickens score free
points and give you a brief speed boost
so they do give extra points okay they
give you extra points then
M okay do you want to play again yeah
sure I can try again okay go go go go oh
I need to talk to the quest uh
good let's go oh I need to
start let see how she will
do cats are pretty good at catching
birds after all you think so
M it's in your
jeans in my pants in my jeans in your
pants
I thought you were going to say panther
but yeah it's also in your pants and in
your
jeans it's also in your
skirt yeah it's in your I skirts oh
true as if I am playing through
you almost as if I can control
you no you have missed so many lot of
them no you are in a bad luck streak I
can recover I can
recover H it is not looking very good
for you in this
turn the sparkly chicken that's no you
have missed it once
again that was
unfortunate I want to play I want to
play go give it a try I want to
try let's see all the luck that you are
sharing with people it will come back to
you
game game how does this work let me see
let me see Catch the birds let me see
Catch the birds good
luck sparkly ones are very very
good they make you a little bit
faster and give you extra score oh you
are doing great so
far you have a natural Talent it seems
have you caught chickens before in your
life many a time I oh I missed it I also
been chased by chicken
oh it seems you are destined for
this I'm not going for
it I'm locking I'm locking oh I'm
locking are you locking in you're doing
good I'm lacking I'm lacking I'm lacking
new
SC yeah new best score oh
wo w 100 100 yay what a Challenge 100 H
H 100
chicken so good hoay I saw it happening
o the leader board is growing
bigger you at the top of it please be
sure to come by Nana 11 where I will be
announcing the winners and giving out
the prize money to those who win okay
just one more time and then I shall
comeb over is it going to start now it
will start in about 6 minutes I will
miss it you w't miss it oh you won't
miss it you
w I will miss it I will miss it and
you Okie doie I will now return to my
market to make sure that every you want
to come with me let's go I want ah I
play one more time then I shall come
okay I need to get good I keep on
forgetting I have to talk to him all
right get all the chicken save them from
their
downfall oh that's pretty good that's a
pretty good start some must be
sacrificed for the greater good but I'm
sure they're just going to chicken
Heaven which is a beautiful place oh no
oh oh that was not good why did I not
catch this one also it is so looking so
bright it is hard to see the sparkly
ones oh I have a sparkly one why is it
so bright suddenly the sun has come out
to sabotage me I didn't think the sun
would be my
enemy oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh you must make your choices wisely
sometimes
[Music]
but I feel wiser than
ever oh perhaps this can get me on the
leaderboard at the top of it
w let's [\h__\h]
go even with the sun sabotaging me I've
been
sabotaged yippee let us see my name at
the top of the leaderboard wow 106 it is
barely
visible all right now onto the
lottery sabotage May yeah maybe it
wasn't a sabotage maybe it was a
blessing in
disguise am I going the right way I
think
so
right why has she left the game why has
she left the game out of Despair over
the crops
oh she's
done for the
night has she closed her chapter for the
day wait where am I
going where am I to
go it it's supposed to be where the
arena is ah there it is h ah it seems I
cannot find the right way to pass oh
there it
is move
Mar here I
Amed in 3 minutes I have arrived gather
around I'm ready to be a winner
11 have you seen my high score being
announced in the I did I went oh wo she
beat
it I have sabot wh to
me sabotaged by the Sun and still got
106 yes let me let me look in the saving
chickens is my
priority yes
yes everybody gather gather around the
na 11 I have a feeling every day will
everybody will be a winner
today could it be well you have a
feeling
it just feels like a like we all need a
win today something this time I really
need a win I think we all need a
win yeah after all the corruption that
has befallen our lands uhoh very true
very true I'm just trying to make this
land a better place and I respect that
even even for our differences I respect
that I hope this [\h__\h] 11 can it bring us
all closer together and perhaps
introduce a
piece to this
land it is a great responsibility to
carry huz but I am
strong I'm here oh hello hello I'm here
for the watery H good luck
Mak oh oh mo mo of the co hello the
lottery will be announced within the
next
minute I'm so excited
here
my
lottery lot we love Lottery very nice
wait I saw a ghost I swear I just saw
somebody come
by a ghost a ghost oh you know what it
may have been may have been my memories
of what fuwa the wa sounded like be a
little
confused I'm so
excited I'm so
excited oh the time is here but we are
missing some people it appears
thatal where is Jonathan G wait did
Jonathan G get one yes Jonathan G got
one perhaps we could call Jonathan of
the G with our I shall call Jonathan of
the G magical for them to be here then
huh no you even if they are absent from
actually never mind I want you all to
keep me company I'm not going to tell
you the
truth the truth the truth being that you
really don't have to be here right now
you'll still get your prize money but
but I just wanted everybody together
because I'm lonely hello oh I am here
for the lottery oh excellent is
everybody here except the single person
who refused a ticket yeah you refused a
ticket a free ticket
yes the wall refused a free ticket she
was very suspicious and paranoid seeing
what happened to her
sister sister sister sister wait a
minute I'm so sorry I'm so sorry I you
two just look very similar I got I I
assumed I should have assumed they look
very different from one another they
look nothing alike yeah yeah one is pink
one is blue that's not true they look so
much they look as a like as you look
pregnant
what what term are you in wait are you
are you perhaps not pregnant that would
assume male pregnancy am I even able I
apologize able to get pregnant I
shouldn't have assum your business
partner you have to stop stop insulting
your guest am I even able to be male
pregnant try not try not to stop
stop am I backwards
backwards what do you think oh maybe you
are and I and I am just revealing it to
you I have a hunch you have a hunch
G am I I say
nothing am
I is anyone a doctor do we have a
doctor Cecilia are you sure you're not a
doctor too huh is there a doctor I I did
take I did take a a first aid course
once yeah is that good enough we is that
good enough we still here I
suppose okay okay oh yes what about the
lottery at all I guess but Lottery let
me see is more important Lottery if you
are in fact pregnant you would really
need the prize money wouldn't you given
that given that your wife seems to be
out of the picture now yeah you would be
raising it alone the child H I suppose I
would could be what child what happened
to her oh how sad oh she is not of this
world any
longer are you sure about that yes she
is no longer with us
H when you say that want s is no longer
she's no longer with us but she's not
dead is she she dead the the version I
knew is no longer here with us what are
you talking about maybe she can come
back stillar the Pearl if you believe so
I would not put all my eggs in one
basket do not give up
immediately I do not know you as
somebody who gives up so easily on their
their
love I see well don't give up you know
we
got small
difficulty make I think you deserve it
too
honesty deserve a second chance
I am
pregnant we the ly money money money
alert money alert money alert has
arrived the money has arrived oopsie
wait oh shoot hold
on all
right oh she's snuck in wait what you
that's fine that's fine you can hang out
she really wants Mone
patient because you're so patient all
righty all righty everybody I will now
be announcing the winners but please be
please help have even more patience as I
have to go through an ENC count yes yes
okie
dokie the first winner of the lottery
is you whose name I did not
get the GRE you who is
Green
Oh
Cecilia Oh you go by the green one oh it
is go I can go by the green one I like
the green one but there's another green
one so get confusing oh well heard the
other well just whoever is present is
the green one and whoever is not present
is the other I win but yes you win I win
you you win 100 coin Oh wrong thing
congratulations W congratulations on
your 100 coin what is going why
is oh yes that's what I want this is
what I want I thought I was trying to
make me call somebody I will accept the
TR
request you get 100
coins H winnings Sor to be
had 100 coins for you a lucky
winner
winner the next winner is the Lady of
the oranges yipp
huzzah yipp huzzah indeed you win 100
coins what a
surprise I had a
feeling 100 coins for you
I think today we're all
winners yes next the next winner I love
this N1
Mart next winner is
[Music]
Mario
yeah Mario congratulations so many
win you get 100
coins not sure why you need it since you
were the queen but I'm just happy you my
lottery at all sometimes you must donate
to the Royal
Team all the time sometimes it is
required that you donate a portion of
your they need it the most don't they
powerful they need all the money more
than we more than we starving
people huzzah huz winner is Jonathan G
thank
goodness
great great
[Music]
day got to keep your chin up Jonathan
yes I willk you for giving me A New
Perspective
nanu wonderful glorious 100
coin
huzzah huzzah the next
winner is or I believe would have
been Nissa oh of the ravening
Cross she has already departed for today
she is not here right now we did confirm
that she can pick up her earnings
tomorrow which she will do well it is
dark outside she may be sleeping this on
the marrow the ghost
one but that's okay we have now the
final winner of today M of the
co and because you bought five
tickets you
get there was the option to do that you
could buyy
what I did not know of
this could I have bought 20 tickets and
get everything no you could not have
five was the
maximum I see oh wonderful well
congratulations everybody you have all
won the
lottery well it's okay if she's addicted
as long as this the only Lottery she's
going to because then she will not lose
any money here it's a beautiful
beautiful day today we all winners
so sad by the way
[Music]
everyone look everybody has one it was
not a scam oh everybody won this is a
without spending anything family run by
a family of one that is me destroy
F destroy fomar destroy
F no please to destroy
oh no M has gotten the most
winnings per perhaps M would like to
share the
winnings for you oh thank
you you're wel Jonathan of the G yes may
I speak to you on the side for one brief
moment of
course good job good job I am just like
you deeply concerned about
what will come of your baby If
there really is a baby it
seems then you might be big trouble you
not think that she is I think you're
pregnant well in case that you are
pregnant and then in in the case that
you are you were to be raising the child
alone if your beloved wife is not coming
back to you I shall just uh of course
platonically offer my assistance to you
in raising
your child of course if you may be in
need of any assistance yes I will keep
that in mind thank you for your kind and
generous offer Shakira you are so kind
and wonderful yes since we also support
the same Queen oh yes I yes of course I
need to help you when am of child if I
am random suddenly male pregnant I will
turn to you I feel as if I I will need
someone to to lean on but keep your chin
up because I have a good feeling about
your wife
good luck with your
preg thank you thank you I do have
something unfortunate to mention oh yes
that I think we should all keep in mind
and mentally prepare
for the chances of a male surviving male
pregnancy is extremely
slimness what what should I do how you
know this are you a doctor
no but I read I read books
kind
liary your Kindle I see I see what is
the Kindle well anything that is written
on paper must be true yes there's no
wrong things written on paper that is
true that is true the library that you
that you that you that of course is
there anything we can do to help her him
through the male pregnancy
there is very little maybe some healing
items maybe potions anything you can try
but I we can do our best to help but I
think it's very important that we just
prepare in case Jonathan G I see does
not make it g just now that we became
friends no I don't believe it I think we
could still make it if I am to die Miss
sh
yes you would see to it that my child is
raised with their head on right oh but I
could also just uh bring you to the
temple and revive you oh that is true
it's fine revive me it's fine we have
done it today we can do it again we have
done it we can do it again that's true
simple well that's easy then oh okay
okay thank you for your
concern the resurrection Temple and
there may be there may be many things to
be negative about like the corruption
that is spreading but this is not
something we have to be suing about
don't worry we should be of the
land the princess jewelry beu that has
been acting very strange as of late oh
yeah I'm going to kill her what you're
not going to kill my princess not right
now not right now you got to fight me
first kill her I'm sorry kill wasn't the
best word kill wasn't the best word I do
apologize maybe if she were to be killed
uh and then revived by the Phoenix fire
she could be cleansed
automatically I'm going to make sure
that she is a good girl and doesn't do
anything bad
yes protect her all cost I'm sorry we
will not let you k you kill her for no
reason we need we need a good reason's a
good Reas word I'm sorry Reon she's
killing all of us by killing our crops
and we are resulting in Salvation do you
want us to die one princess where's the
proof is she bringing up a the proof is
in the
pudding what do you mean where's the
proof narissa has rebuilt all the crops
for us we literally have seen it with
her own eyes when she was destroying
them I asked for a tri the gardens let
us check the gardens well rebuil by
Nissa who's
offine no there there is a rebuilt them
already it is it will not become a proof
oh well seems
The Fluffy one is convenient planting I
don't see any proof that the princess
has done anything well it's because Thea
has rebuilt it I have helped
her huh I'm oh hello thank you for your
kindness fluffy one and replanting the
gardens yes the gardens it Wasa you are
tending to the gardens you are so
wonderful she was just taking it I see
it was narissa oh thank you narissa
Raven crft tending to the
gardens M but but how can okay so she's
been destroying the crops what if it's
just a simple prank why would you kill
her for that what what's that does not
sound like a good prank to me I because
there is empy in your heart fluffy but
it seems that the princess is corrupt
okay I I'll be honest with you guys I
mean the princess the princess is my
daughter and I've never seen her acting
that weird this morning M like I I don't
know there was something extremely wrong
with her today and I couldn't stop her
even her mother say so that's a good
point yeah I've also noticed her being
very strange but I feel like murder is
very ex extreme can we maybe have a
trial can we have a
trial it seems that wish to ever kill
the princess I got to get my carrots oh
okay very well she does not want to be
involved in this murder is quite
treacherous for a fair such as she um I
will I will ask
well I would like to ask maybe we could
have a set a court date for tomorrow
court date would you guys be okay with
that Justice rules it would be what but
Justice I don't know if somebody can
have a fair trial go for justice with a
corrupted evil
mind I have seen the evils that have
happened upon well we can we can we can
talk to her and see if she's responsive
and then we can have a have a trial I'm
sorry but she seems out of control it
okay can I can I be honest with
you it seems like something is
corrupting her from inside and Nisa
Raven coft the the she told me that
there is something about the king that
is going extremely wrong like a
corruption from from the kingdom itself
really so yeah and and yeah Shakira was
with me when she was talking about it
and like apparently the king is
corrupting the lies and the the lies um
transform into the uh stains that we see
outside the kingdom and so I'm being
called sorry one second I'm calling
you who's goinging oh we are at the
gardens we are currently at the gardens
Naru oh I
see also if you needed any more proof
talk about the pl that you started
wanting to kill the
princess
eh you said kill you
said what you true it's true s we have
to explain her about what n told us
before okay then yeah also the princess
has uh that's true the princess has used
the community notice boards to uh write
a cursed corrupted message to us what do
you want to do with the queen tell true
I have seen it I've witnessed
it it was in a cursed language that it
was really hard to decipher it was and
if you notice it is the same the same
font that plagues her her
lands the the notices on her her Forest
the forest it's like at the Blue uh
there like one must be blind if one were
not to notice that it is a garden or
purposefully ignoring it
it's like on on the side of of the giant
circular
building I
see
well she's corrected too in front of
them but remember what Miss ninoo said
is that there is a
golden oh yes
hello
what okay never mind well nanam is
confused okay are you sure she also
seems to be confused okay oh yes she's
very I see she has made
way okay so tell us about this
corruption well first of all all these
lands were cleared by her destroyed by
her I saw her literally doing it and
then Nissa has rebuilt it and she has
then spoken to us in her cursed language
telling us that we must all die also if
we go to her St statue it is now
bleeding with deadly blood and then
right next to it in her Gardens or what
it is it has also been cursed and
corrupted she might just have a tummy
AEG think it is a tummy ache I do not so
it might be a t a tummy egg it seems
more an aching of the Soul hello
hell I do not want to say this in front
of her but it seems that she is she has
a few screws loose I do not know she
changing her mind talking to but I do
want to trust cuz she's part of the
Scarlet
wand and she gave us money earlier with
the with the with a lottery you know she
is full of kindness but I do not know if
she is in the right of mind maybe I am
not pregnant maybe she's just making
things up yeah I don't think you can can
I can I put my hand on your tummy yes go
ahead okay I know of a technique to find
out whether you are pregnant or not oh
what technique well I have suggested it
to nursa before but she did not want to
try it however if if you um pee on red
sand if it turns green you are pregnant
if it stays red you are
not oh what how do you know about this
what is this how do okay well there's
some red sand at
the I don't remember I have red sand in
my in my backpack oh you have red s
maybe we could try that only if you want
to hello welcome back I suppose we will
have to will you give me when I do it of
they're trying to figure out if she's
actually if he's actually pregnant oh
here's the Red Sand quite a bit of red
sand yeah in case you want to um confirm
it 42 times oh yes if you unsure be safe
I will be back if you may give me some
privacy yes wait I don't know if we
should give him PIV privacy what if he
lies you mean yeah what if he's going to
collect somebody else's sample
I don't think anyone else is
pregnant no I mean what if he's trying
to hide the
pregnancy the pregnancy I don't think
she has a motive for it but we can check
but but what is but I want to respect
her wishes for
privacy I don't oh okay I'll stay
further
away it seems as
if privacy has been invaded
already shh I'm trying to listen what is
happening what is happening are you
pregnant are you pregnant
oh are you
[Music]
no are you
pregnant oh are you pregnant I I'm not
I've not built it yet I'm I'm building
an ouse
oh will be necessary to pee on the
Redstone it will be necessary I do not
know how large to build this though I
think 3x3 is fine a 3X3 out house maybe
perhaps like this unless you're visiting
the ouse with other people I think this
size should be yeah appro looks pretty
nice mhm it will be it will just be a
very crude ouse currently
because yes I am on my
lands cool oh thank you it it will be a
very humble out
house um is there to be a door for your
privacy do do not do not watch me please
there will be a
door you can't tell me not to watch why
would you want to watch me I like to
watch everything can you add a window
yeah we are very observant no no wait
but it's going to get so stinky if you
don't add a
window that is true that is just how
medieval oses are yeah just it's it's
going to be terrible they tend to be
stinky you need some ventilation a lot
of things are stinky in Medieval ages by
default axe go seems I have lost my axe
I will
out but it's isn't this shared is it
there is is being aired out where where
where I don't see oh I see oh at the top
oh there's a hole upstairs okay at the
very top at the tippy
top
sufficient safe
[Music]
okay that's perfect you still have
privacy oh yes no there's the door
wonderful ventilation wonderful
ventilation is that the is that the
first out housee in the whole Kingdom
perhaps I suppose this is the first out
housee in the entire then everybody must
use it can you give us all access to it
yes but not right now I am currently
using it all right good luck with the um
peeing why are you sticking your head
inside
who is trying someone is attempting to
stick their head inside of my door what
color is the Hat sorry
sorry oh yes one second
coin one one second one second before I
you are making me nervous let me too
nervous to pee is it let let me maybe
you should drink some more fluids are
you are you are you part of no no we
none of us are seruan huh
you should drink more fluid make sure to
hydrate hydrate Lots if you want to pee
times I am now going to be peeing on the
the the the sand yes okay okay let us
know if it turns
green if you need something let us know
oh I heard
water oh that that must have been yeah
it seems that it is red it is red still
it is red still can you try again show
us show us show us try again show you
where is it get out of get out try again
try again make
sure okay I will be peeing once more oh
I hear the juice is Flowing you're
really good at doing that on command huh
no it it was it was red you must Hy you
must have hydrated well previously yes I
I was very very hydrated maybe All Good
Things Are
we have found out that you are not
pregnant yes the is that I am not
pregnant well I would agree with that
you want your s back I toally apologize
for my assumption earlier you keep it in
case your uh your wife one day gets
pregnant I see I see thank you I do it
was because not because of your stomach
but because of your glowing complexion I
do apologize for for the mistake you may
because of that uh big juicy looking hat
oh thank you my very very juicy hat that
surely looks like you're hiding a baby
in there but it is empty I
think SC what it say SC Ward member I
have a question yes you will marry me
will you marry me wait who asked that
who
when that's so
romantic will you marry
me who did that was that always there
now to crony
when what I thought she hated
her well that is very
titty marriage of Queens I supported for
the Les
bins where did they
go the out house tried to kill me ouch
political political marriage yeah makes
sense that is uh honestly the smartest
thing those two could have done maybe
the smartest thing Mario could have done
maybe not um Tim Tander for her she was
not really in need of this political
marriage I think but at least and she
doesn't have to bother anymore with all
the
complications of
big
Queens I do not know where they
went but at the same
time I think I could leave I could take
my
leave I think I have done my part
today ous stuck ending exactly
did you not also want to marry the queen
um the no I just wanted to serve
her and protect her I do not uh have
such Ambitions in my life to um Ascend
on the Royal uh Throne no but deep in my
heart I think I sense some love and
feelings towards the one but they are
not requited and it seems rather
complicated therefore I've offered to
just assist her in case she were to be
pregnant but it turns out she hasn't
been pregnant
so which is in one way a relief for me
of
course but
um I I I I
shall continue to observe the
progression of her relationship ship
with her wife
and from the sidelines I
shall make my decisions not too hastily
not too
pushy and she might never even
know about my I will see you what did
what does this really want for me
where'd she
go oh dear oh hello we just celebrating
friendship oh wonderful
yes wonderful well mayhaps you should
give perhaps I shall you have gosh she
gives such good
advice thank you goodbye for now
farewell for
[Music]
now is there any flowers I can
pick is there any flowers I can pick
maybe outside
I just would like to how do you say it
in the medieval way to uh like give
someone a flower and then offer some
like um what was it again like in the in
the fights where they go on the horse
and they have the lances and then they
they poke each other to death
um but that's the other way around is it
no I gave her a flower him
well I am am I the woman in this case I
don't
know it doesn't matter it does not
matter yeah jousting but give favor does
it make sense to court her by asking for
a favor or am I giving her a
favor just in the most innocent
[Music]
way the favor of a fair Maiden more like
the favor of a fair
night is she still here is he he still
here knock knock
knock knock knock
[Music]
yes hello hello I would like to inquire
where might you currently be I am next
to the statue of Queen Tam Gander oh
wonderful that is my favorite place to
be yes it is my favorite place as well I
will find you yes I will be
[Music]
waiting hello dear Jonathan withu I have
something to give to you oh yes what is
it well I'm about to depart uh for for
the day and we might not see each other
for a long time but um I I just had a a
really joyful time with you um and we
seem to be of the same mind so I I
enjoyed your company as well I just
Shakira I was just um I wish you the
best of luck with regaining your
happiness and all that I just I just oh
a a flower thank you of the highest
order I will place it here with the
queen for she would also enjoy your
loyalty how glorious and
beautiful yes for the queen of course
that was meant for the queen oh but I
know that you had given it to me but I
thought I would share your loving flower
because it's a beauty that should be
shared with everyone oh yeah no no it
was uh I just F because I don't have the
rights to build on this land so I just
oh gave it to you to yes yes yes for the
for the queen I I enjoyed spending time
with you today too and I know that
yesterday was a little rough with you
being accused of so many things but I
have seen through it that you are pure
and kind of Soul thank you it means more
than anything to me to hear that from
you yes yes thank you for joining me
today I will miss you dearly but I know
we will meet
again I know it too in our quest for the
queen yes forever we will be together in
our quest for the queen yes she's the
one that brings us together and I thank
her for it Gander thank you thank you
miss queen Tam Gander T tender we love
you and thank you thank you
Shakira to have found an ally in you it
means that oh yes the queen yes yes I
love you dear Queen for have I love you
yes farewell farewell I will miss you
it is
fine I would rather see her smile from
afar on the
side of her wife that she thinks does
not love her anymore but I know she does
she will return to her
side then I shall continue to dedicate
myself and my life as a knight
to the clean
and the queen only such is my destiny
such is my
job Kiki's book in The Scarlet
Library what isn't that such a thing as
a diary I don't think I have the right
to read
it but I may or may not have seen
Snippets of it in a uh vlog
long is a problem wait you mean
something new or something from
yesterday is it a new
one a new one from
today now
yesterday I have kind of already seen it
oh what a nice bed so pink and cute
oh is this my Chambers
perhaps I wonder oh
well it's okay I shall take my
leave I am a knight and I remain a
knight I'm honored to be Maiden
lless because the true
Maiden was Tim tender we met along the
way
made in L by
[Music]
choice
ah yes okay so so so so out of the Roll
play back into normal that's very Maiden
lless Behavior I know well I am Maiden
[Music]
M but it is the right thing it is the
right thing to do for for I have sworn
my duties to the
queendom yes yes yes
yes so I'm going to read super chats
during this time I do want to say that
even if I couldn't participate too much
this was a really really cool Pro
project I hope it
continues uh sooner rather than later
but there will be a break after tomorrow
but I'm not participating tomorrow so as
you know and I'll be not streaming
tomorrow uh I hope you all had fun with
it it's so cool like I know there were
so many fun moments even like so
uncountable many where I was not even
part of and they have been very very
exciting to observe and follow
I keep on seeing people that are like
super overwhelmed by everything that's
happening and I'm and are like whoa whoa
whoa whoa I it seems I need to catch up
with this Ian REO thing yes you must yes
you must I'm so happy that it's um it
turned out so great I honestly did not
expect that uh everybody would be so
active in it m i I didn't think so
but I'm I'm great this is a great
turnout
yeah uh chasing Cali with the
music yeah the dungeons were great I
hope that we get some cool dungeons in
Chapter 2 as
well
yeah yeah many many opportunities to
interact but I actually oh I realized
like if this happens again it will like
all most of the activity will be like
around this time right and if I'm in
Europe at the time I honestly don't
think that I want to or can force myself
to be up at 3:00 a.m. to whatever 5 6
a.m. yeah that's like roughly the time
frame if I were to be in
Europe no I am old I'm I I cannot dude
this is my this is my four no almost
fifth year of streaming I I'm no it
doesn't matter if somebody else does it
that doesn't mean that I have to do it
I'm not going to do that
sorry yeah I'm sure that um I I know
that will not be good for my body and
also yeah I'm I don't I have other
things to do in
life yeah but who knows maybe like it
will happen when I'm in Japan again for
some reason
like coincidentally and then then it
would be good then I wouldn't
mind
H
yeah speaking of
sleep man these one and a half months
that I was in Japan my sleep was so bad
so
uncomfortable every day every
night so uncom
able
man I hope amorn can be more who knows
if it will even like still be these
guilds maybe there will be a new Guild
or like to like switch it mix things up
who knows or like the guilt will be
rearranged or I don't know because I
feel like you know
ambercoin kind a rough
start h
who knows who knows maybe the whole
Kingdom will be destroyed after the
finale maybe the finale will destroy the
kingdom although that would be a
waste oh you guys will see perhaps while
I am
absent I'm excited to read it on on the
new on the newspaper
[Music]
yeah there Isa SP
oh oh thank you GD I appreciate it EDF
EDF EDF EDF okay and which spring our
rest in pie thank
you gathan and Shakira when only in my
delusions only only in my dreams
the orange one and the orange one will
only find each other in the depths of my
dreams it's a is this a almost a love
triangle now
because outside of this my love belongs
to
so through all the dimensions especially
now that we have regained memories in a
way it's a love triangle
but just that both of my loves are
unrequited and the ones that I love have
found love in each
other
no no how
painful pain Peru pain
per third wheel in all Dimensions yeah
I'm used to being a third wheel
[Music]
we'll get you the chair K what
chair wait what
chair you should read G if it's the one
from yesterday I I've kind of
like swooped my eyes over it don't tell
her about the
chair it
ignore chair
comments
okay
huh
[Music]
what spicy well it is the end for me
anyway I cannot make use of any
chairs I only heard of a chair called
the
throne and gathan G would not sit on the
throne because it belongs to the
queen no I really refuse to know the
truth about the
chair I really don't
know I the only chair I will fake of yes
is the is the queen's chair the
prone sker Skipper that information I
will read to chats yes yes
yes wait are we staying here no we are
going to
here yippee I'm still hungry let me get
some more fruit cuz I I ordered fruit to
snack
[Music]
on you know ever since I like came here
I met this one tiny spider
and like I was like well I don't want
you to be here but I keep on meeting the
spider it's the same spider I see it all
the time and then recently it has been
pranking
me when I go to idle meeting both today
and yesterday it showed up each time
like on the toilet roll dispenser like
when
I like this time this time it was under
the the Li
kind of like I I reach for the paper and
then suddenly it appears and I'm like
ah and then it falls
down and yesterday it was just on top of
the paper but today it was more sneaky
it was under the lid thingy not the
toilet lid the the toilet paper lid
thingy what the trickster yeah sound
doesn't sound like a prank what do you
mean murder attempt or
what terrifying and and one time I met
it in my bed like it's following me why
is it what is it trying to tell
me it's really tiny it's kind of
cute yeah it surprises me I'm my most
vulnerable
exactly maybe it just wants a hug yeah
but why why when I'm
vulnerable they kill mosquitoes like a
champ well the thing is there's still
like tiny ass flies coming out of the
sewage like when I came here I had to
vacuum them all up cuz they were all
like around the window especially there
were so many and now one and a half
months has passed and they like I can I
I vacuumed the floor a few times but I I
didn't vacuum the window sill since but
I can tell there's so many tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny like
0.00001
mm size mini sewage flies drain flies on
the window again and dead ones they're
all
[Music]
dead so I would hope that the spider
would eat it
but it seems it would rather eat
[Music]
me cuz it keeps on going after
me ew well yeah that's what I thought
but it's
[Music]
okay this is okay this is but a
scratch I look more
delicious this is mixed of cut fruits
and it has papaya and I realize I do not
like papaya
[Music]
um so by the way my new assistant
manager who will at one point become
more of my main manager it
seems as I've told you
[Music]
I've kind of discusted with
her she's now to be named PMA she has no
choice she has done too many porn
things in a short amount of time even
yesterday like we were taking this like
video we were filming after my stream
which was interesting but it was
fun and then like once we left like one
location where like I was I was doing a
thing and while I was doing the thing
she had like her laptop out doing some
work and then she packed her things back
together when we left and it seems like
she like forgot to close her
backpack and then we walked quite a
while with that she was usually like
behind me so I didn't see it and then a
different like Foreigner had to notify
her was like I thought I thought that
forigner was going to come up to us and
be like hey are you
[Laughter]
Ki was like feeling a little bit nervous
about it in that moment but no he tapped
pma's shoulders and was like hey your
backpack is open and we were like oh oh
indeed well thank god this is
[Music]
Japan but um while she was okay with
being PMA for now it seems like she
wants to like one day I said one day you
can Poss
possibly graduate from this name PMA and
upgrade yourself to a
more name likee name so so she is a PMA
temporarily and I said minimum one day
one one
[Music]
year I know pomma is
cute but like the thing is her her PA
moments are thankfully I guess uh only
like things that are not really it to
work like just like you know having her
bag open or getting lost on the street
stuff like
that although well she's still getting
used to all kinds of work things but I
wouldn't call it pawn so far she just
like very Pawn in terms of
life so
yeah look forward to the result of what
we oh right I have to send the files oh
my God see I forgot but we don't have
much time so I I must send it as fast as
possible um perhaps I shall attempt to
connect with a cable my phone instead of
trying to get it through the
Wi-Fi
WiFi like uploading is it just me when
you try like put uh upload videos or
whatever on your like drive or so
through your
phone it's just way
slower than it needs to be like it's
just not doing
[Music]
anything
okay so instead of trying to upload it
over
Wi-Fi let me
connect connector what the hell is this
why would
I why would I sign in with M M M
[Music]
Microsoft I just want to see my data and
give it to cow
carrot where is
it ah there it is internal storage
[Music]
sh DCI I m I haven't done this no while
camera Microsoft wants to slice I don't
know what the [\h__\h] they want from me
Microsoft they always want something
don't
they it's so weird seeing my picture on
yeah what happened with the chatter box
again what happened this time I guess
because I changed the
scene uh okay now if I make a drive to
Tom I'll just do this because otherwise
I'll
forget I will
forget let's make a
drive new folder cow carrot now there's
a folder called cow carrot on my
drive
okay the files are taking a while to
load but I have the window open so now I
know what I'm doing right what's what's
what was the
date yesterday was the 6th of
September so all the videos that I took
at the 6th of
September thanks for streaming today
you're my favorite po v n e r and
Michael it's been a lot of fun really
me really I think there's probably a lot
of more entertaining povs but thank you
so much for choosing mine I appreciate
it thank
you yeah I have a PC set up here in
Japan that works really nicely
[Music]
indeed I'm cheating on my
own I'm cheating on my own PC other povs
don't have Ki 100% of the time that is
true if that is what you desire then you
shall be on my
POV well I've at least left my mark on
the chicken game the chicken collection
[Music]
game somehow this is really not well
organized why is is not properly
organized it is supposed to be sorted by
name but it's it does not look like it
is well I shall give it more time maybe
there still loading why am I still
talking like this it is
infectious infectuous it
[Music]
is okay yeah the switch the recollection
never
ends only there was a lava POV for
finale well I would recommend watching I
don't know gigy
cuz she's really good at role playing
and she's fun and she's
orange she's
orange have you have you noticed she's
orange okay I think H it was EDF EDF EDF
EDF EDF EDF EDF EDF EDF there it is EDF
EDF I shall read the super chats from
the EDF stream
PE PE
H there it
[Music]
is this reminds me of another thing how
are my permissions doing for the MMO
RPGs that I wanted to
play
still no progress has been made also no
progress on the the the new game from
the Ori creators by the way I don't know
why they're
not let me inquire
perhaps oh thank you for the ROM chat
what r r
rat is that how I say your
name yeah no rest for the wicked it's in
Early Access yeah but I asked if I can
just uh be in the Early Access I don't
mind
[Music]
well well
well TR for Rachel what oh your name
reach so Rogue ra all right
[Music]
perfect okay I shall read Jacob 47 n my
and N Hulan dun edf5 fencer oh dun thank
you for the r Super Chat I wonder you
have a kfp bucket as your icon did you
just change your name or is that has
that always been your name thank you for
the redp chat kpf
kpf no it's
kfp Cruz D candy stamps
sty chunky chunk thanks for the pinky
EDF EDF EDF but I cannot get wa decoy
and another ones in game because of
region difference oh no yeah it's region
Limited
was it uh like na only
[Music]
or sorry another pineapple has been
devoured well yeah I heard something
about
the ah CA has the Japanese members M I
heard about the the the region locked
that's
unfortunate oh well oh well thank you
the it's the fult that counts junky
chunk Hulu than Mal content than Hulu oh
thank you for the
pinky you are no longer k aimo really I
don't know I don't think uh we can use
EDF as like a
proof what Tam Gander accepted the
marriage prop puz what Tam gander is
[Music]
online
it on Twitter
oh what how
peaceful now I now I am to serve two
[Music]
queens well but the thing is there's
usually like a queen
consort and like a king or a king
concert and the
Queen so I would
say yeah
lesbians I've told you since the
beginning what they really meant is save
the lesbians not
liestal yeah my cat is now my queen that
is
confusing I guess yeah now this is less
complicated for me
m less complications I appreciate it
[Music]
more peaceful I like
this these cats are your Queens oh my
God I can't wait to see them
again a I can't believe it's finally
time this felt so long why does well
this trip really is long this is like
one of my longest Tri P trips I think
since I left
honestly since I left um like living
there like one half months man although
like in between I was in New
York but still I don't think I've been
like away for a full like over maybe a
month I've done before
maybe yeah but this is just so
[Music]
long how long you still staying in Japan
I'm basically one foot out of the
door
basically my house oh myth house oh true
no yeah myth house was longer I would
say I think I was there for like 2
months but maybe I went home for a few
days in between I don't know I don't
remember it's too long
ago anyway thank you Honolulu I don't I
don't think you can say that I have good
AIM now just because of this game
because somehow aiming was easy in this
game but thank you n h now the 55 danan
PSY danan and spanking thanks for the r
Super Chat I want those small fry
figures thanks for the stream well
before we get these small fry figures
where the hell is my
neroid it is time for my neroid to come
first come
on honestly I saw that picture with like
some orange haired anime chick replacing
me I was like what the hell this looks
like me
[Music]
thank you for sping
time H from love
life M
[Music]
momar oh yeah the froggy ra plushies and
everything is coming in yippee it turns
out she does not have eyebrows even
though I remember I checked I ended up
checking I asked like several times like
hey can you show me can you lift her uh
like bangs for me so I can see if she
has eyebrows and then um they never like
in the production they never replied to
me about that they always missed my
question I think and so it was just
never resolved and now she has no
eyebrows which really bothers me but
it's okay she still looks
cute depending on the angle if you look
at her from above she looks like she's
crying and if you look at her from like
just from straight or below she looks
cute normal doesn't she look like she's
crying when you look at her from above
that's so cute she's so cute I wor my
hoodie today thank you so
[Music]
green yeah she's cute I already saw some
people putting her next to other
plushies like the dino
gooa very baby so
baby so cute make sure to give her fly
every once in a while feed her she's
crying because she's in
captivity my baby need yelled froggy
when I put it on
AW a wait You the froggy you're the Frog
now give her the uppies yes give her
gummy worms yes give her everything she
[Music]
desires still waiting on her she will
bless you eventually
[Music]
Roy oh yeah wait what was that ah can
you guys stream Kima today a little bit
huh can you do that for
me I just saw like some statistics from
the music department and I figured oh
okay well it has good good numbers you
know but uh could could
[Music]
appreciate a little bit
[Laughter]
[Music]
more stream it stream
Cima the MV or the
audio perhaps the
audio thank
[Music]
you
y taking the crown now you're calling me
King you going to hear all
sing now even YouTube music uh counts I
think like if you just listen to the the
audio one on YouTube I don't know if the
m music video really counts for it I
don't
know but yeah we're getting closer I can
sense a new song coming closer and
closer so let's focus a little bit more
on
onima before our new child arrives and
is
born yeah it's SP time thank you py D
and zly D wrong
one this
one there it
goes and next up is a which spraying are
part six Orange Is the New Pink
don't I have the thumbnail like here and
[Music]
somewhere
yeah this part no that's not part six is
it part
seven part
[Music]
six cute game seems like it has really
good ratings I'm happy for them
[Music]
I think I read that oh maybe I
did oh that looks familiar the the
somehow the poly Super Chat looks
[Music]
familiar bat Gat setup oh yeah that
looks
familiar Mikey oh yeah I read this one
[Music]
M finale
what oh do I need to go one back part
five what no one ahead so what about the
K to 1
1.54
uh oh it seems I have read it because
the link appears to be
darker the to dama too also the dark the
Luigi's Mansion also we finished that
[Music]
game have we finished Lo this
Mansion no we just haven't played it in
a while I thought we maybe
did
oops Yeah I I I felt like oh something
something feels incomplete but how come
we haven't played it in a while we just
didn't have time
leave it for
Halloween I don't think I will I want to
finish it within this month because at
the end of the month there's a new Zelda
game
coming or the first Zelda game
ha spring finale okay so I'm skipping a
couple again and yeah okay I see
it
yeah H dun Jacob Jacob 47 dun or should
I put up the thumbnail
there it
is
[Music]
yes wow I miss
her uh Rat
lunch G p d d thanks for the pies JK
monkey thanks for the red super chat
before I forget my annual tith to the
Church of vaa for this being probably
the month of my introduction to this
world called
Earth what oh you were born in this
month
huh thanks for all the fun so far wow
and here's to another great year with
you also can you say happy birthday in
Korean for reasons
the reason is I like w Korean and know
this isn't actually the day of my birth
just the month well uh it seems we have
already passed the whole month so this
seems appropriate uh even if you sent
your Super Chat early so
s JK monkey OPP
[Music]
Mony thank you for appreciating Korean
waa
[Music]
Kim I hope your birthday was
delightful what did you eat H what did
you what did you
eat what did you
[Music]
eat is there a French waa oh
yeah very i i i displayed my French
skills my French reading skills a lot in
Ian
Reco whenever I read um the soran cups
dialogue probably a
banana oh wait and Cake steak and shrimp
and cake
but hopefully not all in one thing
hopefully
separately but even then I don't know
about the shrimp I do not support the
[Music]
shrimp oh happy birthday Davis mango
cake oh my God
yummy that sounds good happy
[Music]
birthday jaob 47 D J SW than Studio Rob
thanks for the pinky 10 into it the end
of spring witch turns to Summer the
summer of the witch
what wait no we have finished it what do
you mean we have finished it it was
indeed the summer of the witch I it was
a nice little game to spend my summer
with thank you Studio Rob Daisy thanks
for the red super chat here's an extra
late birthday super oh your birthday or
my birthday my birthday I guess by this
point it's closer to being an
anniversary oh yeah okay my birthday
at this point I guess the actual
anniversary super will be on
Christmas all Jing aside thanks for all
the great streams and music and merge
that kills my wallet you are
welcome I'm
sorry I'm sorry but yeah it is closer to
my anniversary now but Daisy was already
late it is not just because I am
late I'm not that far behind I'm
catching
up you must not doubt me
kfp I am the you are the only ones I
have left my
chickens thank you so much Daisy how you
doing thank you so much for still being
around much love much much pets and
ruffle
feathers
and
Choo Anthony webb thanks for the pinky
it's always nice to catch you streaming
live kiaha wanted to let you know you're
still my Kam Koshi good to know I need
this confirmation every once in a while
thank you I appreciate it yipp huzzah
Alex Dan spider Dan L Moonlight thanks
for the red chat thank
you J oh we have a bunch of flush chats
it seems Slavic fellow d reer d Fri D J
SW D Doom say Dan D RS D J SW Dan silent
Nerf D just another
kfp good thanks for the red super chant
boss that isn't truly fair to judge me
by my subscription I wasn't comfortable
using my real name in February of 2021
during your trip home so I tried to
convert to a brand account but it didn't
work and I lost my subscription time wa
this this I didn't really like seriously
judged you by your status did I I don't
think I did it's more a joke right
it's more of a joke I
think oh you tried to convert to a brand
account why did you do
that but that's mean
YouTube why do you take it away from
grafted in give it back give the
subscription time
back it is
mean but don't
worry don't worry I am bad with math I
cannot really figure out how long you
guys have been here just by your icons
it is hard to tell for
me oh cow carrot is here oh no I feel
pressure let me see is it oh oh no I
have uh changed the folder therefore I
must load it again it
seems so
annoying so
annoying why does it not just load all
at once and stays like that
[Music]
come on come on I'm trying to create an
entertaining
program what is this oh I think it has
loaded has it oh oh the yes oh all the
videos are in one
place
Perfection perfection
[Music]
Perfection cow carrot take note
generally you may
um uh
cut pma's voice but if there's something
funny she says or so or something
important to our conversation then you
may uh pitch her voice
up or can people pitch it down then no
[Music]
then I don't know cut it out probably
the best way to
go okay I am at this very moment
uploading my videos my evidence it
is 43
videos Good Luck a lot of them are very
short yeah maybe add some
if she says something important but I
think generally I was just talking to
myself and she was just following
me okay this will take a
while uh but it's currently uploading so
it's only a matter of
time as they
say where was I here H
Kim you Chong
[Music]
one M eight thanks for the r chat hey
Tel today is my birthday so thanks for
streaming well it was still today a few
minutes ago if you didn't know Umbrella
Academy Season 4 came out today too is
it good did anybody watch it oh an NES
World Championship definitely counts as
red draw stay safe in the Heat and good
luck with work thank you well I I
completely like gave up all my help and
particip ipating uh that like soon after
that it was okay not yet I did not enjoy
it I haven't watched it yet okay well
the people ring proes to is great are
you really saying that a lot of people
were like oh I have strong
opinions yeah I did not have time for
Bingo I'm so sad but I'm still reaping
the benefits of it because ol Ollie want
something and she already sent me like
the Deets of like invitation
[Music]
because she won like uh a trip to an
amusement water park or so I
think she already dm'd me about
[Music]
it well I'm leaving Japan and I don't
think she is in Japan now so you know uh
that's uh not happening anytime soon but
it will happen so I will reap the
benefits of the competition of the
challenge one way or
another yes
yes yes yes yeah and every participant
got like the ah I wish I could have like
at least slightly participated because
apparently every everybody
who participated it was there was a
participation reward I think you didn't
necessarily have to clear everything uh
but everybody got like these like things
that I already use all the time like
these like cooling sheets sticky sheets
with like herbs and stuff um that I put
on my legs and my
shoulders would have been nice to get
some more of
those and also like uh like
hot uh herb full uh eye sheets I don't
I've used those before I don't really
like those that much but the the leg
thing is you
know those I
appreciate no it's it's not quite like
Salon pass but it's
similar I tried salom Pass and salom
Pass feels like way more
intense but I I like the one that I
always use it it it's quite nice on the
shoulders
[Music]
no it doesn't help against irings it's
just supposed to make you feel relaxed
when you're trying to sleep or something
but I don't know it just bothers me when
I have something on top of my
[Music]
eyes mhm
yeah I don't like eye masks oh but I
don't mind having like a a little Tower
a tower towel on top of my eyes when
I am at a massage
place um they don't usually they don't
even do that like in Europe or so when I
get a
massage like when it's tummy upwards and
I have to like be blinded by the lights
of the ceiling or so
and then my eyes get like all Twitchy
right I'm I'm closing them but they get
Twitchy and my eyes want to look around
in Japan they always put a towel a tiny
towel a lightweight tiny towel on top of
your eyes so that your eyes don't get
blinded and also I guess just because
it's like less
awkward when you look up you're facing
up and then yeah I wish that was the
norm for every massage place all over
the World they do that in haircut places
with a warm towel seems to be a a barber
thing yeah cuz they don't do that in the
the lady
salons I mean or maybe the really
expensive ones I don't know I think
maybe they did that ah I know I remember
they did do that okay same thing as with
the massages like so in salons in Japan
when they wash my hair after like dying
it or
whatever when I I'm like in the sink
thing then they would put a little towel
on top of my
eyes which I appreciate but in Austria
when I'm at at the sink leaning back
they don't give a [\h__\h] about that they
don't put a towel on my
eyes it's bright it's weird my eyes are
Twitchy do you guys get that too like
you you want to close your eyes because
you're in a situation like that where
having your eyes open is more awkward
but then when your eyes are closed
they're like looking
around and they're twitching and they
you feel like one eye is more closed or
like heavily closed than the other you
know what I mean so I trying to like
open one to like readjust
it and I don't bother with any of that
if I have just had a towel on top of my
eyes what you don't
relate why do some of you guys not
relate you're supposed to
relate how is this not relatable to
you the lady is looking me straight in
the eyes
when while washing my hair what that's
creepy as
[\h__\h] no I'm not even talking about
massages I'm talking about just being at
the hair salon as well when they wash
your
hair in the
[Music]
sink I don't have hair you do you do
but I know what you mean you don't have
the same we're you and me we are not the
same you don't have the same kind of
hair I don't go to salons okay okay well
okay then don't relate to me fine I gave
you two ways to relate to me massage
places or hair salons and you choose to
not relate to me with any of them fine
then fine with me
but I do think the eye closing thing can
be
relatable in any any bright place where
you're trying to close your
[Music]
eyes huh
whatever whatever and don't you close
your eyes
[Music]
sometimes yeah hey dentist yeah for
example
dentist I mean that's also like like I
feel weird like do I keep my eyes open
or do I close
them but they certainly even in Japan
don't put a towel on your eyes at the
dentist it's just
awkward and then when I do close my eyes
again they're doing this thing where
like one is more heavily closed than the
other and then I have to like readjust
it and and then I wonder like if I open
one eye to readjust the heaviness of the
the closing of my eye will the dentist
fake that I'm taking a peek I don't want
to be peeking I just want to close my
open my eyes once and then close them
again until they're like nicely closed
but then still my eyes are like moving
around and I'm wondering if the dentist
can tell that my eyes are moving
around it's just
weird
overthinking overthinking
[Music]
[Laughter]
anyway um where was I ah thank you
mate happy birthday by the way oh my God
I tangent it away from
that very far oopsie thank you thank you
so much for your patience I now wish you
a happy birthday happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday m h
yo Happy Birthday
to
you thank you so much for your patience
always and for always supporting me and
all the cool info you're giving me also
often serves as
tangents I appreciate it yeah Umbrella
Academy new season I got to download it
and watch it on my iPad my iPad by the
way still has The Moldy cover
I bought one a new one a while ago I
think I told you and it was the wrong
size and since ever since I have been
telling myself to buy a new one maybe in
a in a store in person but I have yet to
get to it whenever I found an uh Apple
Store I did not remember the size of my
iPad after all and then I just said oh
maybe another day
so yeah it's just like this moldy iPad
cover but it's okay it's not like it's
get is that fuzzy it's just
[Music]
colorful I was hoping to buy it in Japan
because it might be cheaper in
Japan yeah it's better than no cover
because I would probably destroy it if
there's no cover also the cover uh helps
to lift it up when I want to watch
something don't worry it is not fuzzy it
is just
colorful it's not fuzzy nor
fluffy it is just
[Music]
colorful don't worry about
it don't concern yourself with
it it's mold
[Music]
C no don't worry I will find a new cover
eventually
[Music]
it is just a little bit dirty or
speaking of dirty or speaking of what I
don't know how I how I come to this
thought but let me
quickly check
[Music]
something on my
phone how you doing guys
H how are you
[Music]
about to pass out okay don't worry my
stream is going to be over soon I want
to finish all
my polar awards today but I still
have a bunch quite a bit to sign but I
got I'm going to finish it today
and then I'm going to go get a massage
but then I'm I'm just worried because I
sleep One Night in this bed and then my
body is like stiff and broken again
what's the point maybe I should just
stay up and not
sleep then my body shall not be ruined
oh wallpaper oh God what reminding me
now is not really there's no point to
that remind me after my stream
have we tried flipping the mattress over
no I think it's flipped the right
[Music]
way I wish I could sleep at the M
massage place because I can sleep so
comfortably on my tummy
there so
[Music]
comfortably let me
in let me in please let me upgrade my
flag please
please why are you blocking me from it
since
yesterday it just doesn't seem
possible it's just not possible it just
won't let
me it just won't let
me I want to sleep comfortably on the
plane please let me give you
money let me give you money
[Music]
I am just worried that if I try to do it
like in person at the airport it would
probably be more
expensive than if I do the the
thing on the
app or it might already be all full you
know man it probably will
be I don't really like spending all this
money
on on that but I'm so exhausted and my
body hurts I just I just want to just
not think about it and throw the money
out of the window the airplane window
and sleep in business
class yeah I'm sure it's usually more
expensive at the checking counter
100% sure well I'll try it maybe not on
the phone but on the website once after
this on the
[Music]
PC yeah well the good thing is again for
this trip I didn't pay for the flight so
I would only be paying for the upgrade
which to me seems excusable also I'll be
getting the miles from the upgrade and
the and the flight so that's how it be
bu man would do
[Music]
it no the upgrade is not as much as the
flight if if I do it the way I would
usually do
it how much was it like I think like
maybe 300 bucks or
so or something like that or 400 I don't
remember it's a while
ago I think that was like the minimum
bid Airline 's favorite
Phoenix ah I am a frequent traveler now
which I could have been way earlier if I
just like joined one of these programs
earlier
[Music]
on frequent travel that is so true I
have been a frequent traveler for the
longest time but now
officially and my next status is sanitor
isn't that insane sanitor status is kind
of ins saying I'm not that far from it I
feel like I might reach sen Senator St
status next year but like a different
kind of
Senator not the not the American kind of
Senator but it's like the highest I
think almost or pretty much
like the
highest in the miles
program vote for me kfp I will be the
[Music]
Senator yes I am the
Senate soon by next year vote vawa so I
can become the senator next
year Ambassador and Senator it's hard to
say I don't like that word senator they
call it
senator in
German next step
Senator Senator sounds cool
right okay let's let's
[Music]
continue naan of the pinky
congratulations ahead of time for
finishing yet another game W I must
retire for the evening for my IRL job in
the morning but I look forward to the
next game you aim to
finish which is Luigi I would say Luigi
is still to be finished I saw in the
store they have a Luigi campaign going
on and if you if you uh watch Japan eat
he also covered like this like Luigi
Ramen uh or actually curry curry ra
something like that and he said it
wasn't really like that good I think and
it wasn't spicy even though it said it
would be spicy but it looks cute because
it's all green it's like packaging all
green and they have a bunch of other
Luigi things and if you buy the Luigi
Ramen then you get like a Luigi
sticker this and that yeah
[Music]
yeah so muchi
everywhere everywhere is this is this
Luigi I'm happy that he's getting some
appreciation he deserves it I think I
think the game is selling well
right sasuga I'm glad that he does not
befall the same fate as War Mario
and Luigi no
Waluigi woo
IGI had to think about it for a
moment
yeah or even Donkey Kong for that matter
but I do not really care about Donkey
Kong only my Oshi cares about Donkey
Kong anyway thank you naan Richard G D
Richard G D Richard g k Dy D Richard
thank
you car thanks for the r of chat thank
you for this amazing series wah great
game great play through I'm probably
going to get this myself as well as
other witch spring games me too I want
to I need to get the one for the phone
thank you for the red super
chat Marcus G Dan oh the ker and which
spring bro
Kim uh you
shano one probably come once again Mary
P Dan The Gamer cre Dan Cru Dan space
water rash Channel thanks for the r
Super Chat and happy birthday
belated but it is your birth year as it
is every year so I shall still wish you
a happy birth year
congratulations Sky d red D peekaboo d
space waterful d and Chris
D that was the final
wberry I'm so sad we moved on from that
let's do Minecraft uh panachi Arc the ID
cup if you think about it we've had so
many Minecraft projects uh this
summer early this summer we had my the
morning that I organized the one block
was it yeah one block not Sky Block but
it was kind of in the sky so I'm
confused one block with myth we had ID
cop do we have we have a Yen Rec and
there was probably something else in
between I'm not
sure M yeah after so much time no
Minecraft I'm
glad I'm glad oh yeah hard yeah right
right right the hardcore P one right
there's so there was so much Minecraft
this summer
oh
wonderful no I don't think it's getting
too much it used to be so much more like
just every day it was like everybody's
everyday
[Music]
game yeah the hardcore hardcore server
was really great this one
[Music]
too one block myth was kind of like a
warmup for this Ian
[Music]
REO yeah it's our DNA
true check 47
D it's really just a few super chats
here uh this is the the the Pachi
Minecraft One
py D fancy
d d Cruz D thanks for the pinky it's my
birthday tal I just wanted to say thank
you for making the past almost four
years such a blessed I'm happy to be
part of kfp you also have inspired to
work really hard uh and can say I'm
doing great can I have marmalade in my
shoe love you forever K thank you of
course you can happy birthday to you
happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday and your pants too happy
birthday Edan to
you
congratulations let's go have fun
washing it
out washing it out of your
shoes and Rainer anothera birthday thank
you for the red super chat Rainer today
my birthday and I wanted to send love to
my hardworking and creative tento your
dedication never goes unnoticed and your
streams brighten up my days thank you
for all you do here's to another year of
success just much love oh thank you so
much
aw I appreciate it Happy Birthday do you
want the jam as well are you
[Music]
here you are I think from the European
lands so there's a high chance you're
not here oh you are
here you want the
marmalade happy birthday to you happy
birthday in your shoes
happy birthday in your pants too happy
birthday to
you yeah what a coincidence that your
birthday is on the day where I played
with
[Music]
Rea congratulations mwah mwah mwah mwah
mwah mwah
mwah thank you so much both of you hope
you had a nice birthday
party even if the party was at home
watching my streams that's a great party
that's the best
[Music]
party uh wah wa birthday already a while
ago but anniversary coming soon oh my
God oh my God it's this month well it's
next week I was thinking um I might be
able to
do a
stream uh not
to uh
far
from
uh I can do a stream on the 13th I
think but then but then I must go for a
few days but you will be you will be
blessed with other things such as a
video and another video and another
video several
videos that will be pered as a stream as
[Music]
well but yes the 13th may be a real live
stream yes one of those videos that may
be perceived as a stream that I'm
talking about is the myth anniversary
yes
indeed counts as one of my streams
because I am part of it
[Music]
why do I talk like this I don't know it
is
delightful so are you okay with
celebrating my I don't know what when
would my actual when would my actual
anniversary be was isn't it actually
13th isn't it truly actually
[Music]
14th 12 well then that's not bad then I
am not missing it after
[Laughter]
[Music]
all 12 and na okay okay well that's not
bad I don't know what to do though
because as you know well you
know guess I could do a a call in or
something but it's a short notice so I
don't know what to do maybe I'll do a k
okay just wing it hell yeah hell
yeah what do you mean no stream for 5
days which days are you talking
about also like eh of course there will
be there will be the myth anniversary
stream on my absence so I am not really
absent what no that is not true I have
not claimed that I will not be around
until the 13th I have just said that I
could stream on the 13th which does not
mean rep that I am not around before
that I am very much capable of streaming
on the previous days as well I could
stream on the 12th if I wanted to and if
I wanted to I could also stream on the
11th for the 10th which I will I will
[Music]
indeed I am just saying because I will
be absent on the 14th and the 15th that
the latest stream you will receive will
be on the 14th but in in a way I will
also be streaming on those other days
because if you must see it so I I will
be giving you content and therefore I am
not really
absent so I'm not really
gone I am
around and
there's there is Wawa to be had Wawa on
demand is to be had and
received mhm
mhm yes
[Music]
quite will there be a hashtag possibly
so Shing as Wawa well that is funny that
you say so because we have a a viewer
Among Us with that name with that very
[Music]
name sh sh walk
kiaha
kiaha yeah of course he is present why
is he why did he lift the
knife why is he what is that knife in
your
hand what are your
plans put down s
[Music]
Beef anyway I still need to think about
how to go about things
it would be fun to have a little
collaboration stream with friends
wouldn't it be and perhaps a little K
because all the other things I have
prepared are going to be at a later
date but uh I am capable of streaming on
my anniversary and that is
wonderful isn't
it okay
spectacular I shall return to my super
chats uh which are finished no wait GD
thanks for the pinky a little photo
massage H how fitting it is as if you
see the future as I'm going to massage
today once
again once again and this time I have I
have chosen the previous
massuse to do it to me again her
magic I want to experience it again oh
there's another pavoni Minecraft stream
following right after check 47 D Jim
Tracy D M D zip d h d and Edison
D wow perhaps I am almost caught up at
this point almost one might say even if
it doesn't look very close to it but it
is I may read the super chats of the
rebroadcasts of the
K let me see how are my uploads going oh
one video has uploaded are you certain
Let me refresh this page you are kidding
me aren't you es It also says zero bytes
are you [\h__\h] kidding me are you
[\h__\h] kidding
me you [\h__\h]
donkey what the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
what
why what should I do
where do i s my
data must we make it so
[Music]
complicated let's
do how much can I upload 300 giga
uh on Giga file maximum how much is this
in
total 20.8
okay well then Giga file it
is seems more reliable I guess I could
have zipped it yeah how about you diip
it
huh no you did nothing wrong I apologize
it was just such a great opening
[Music]
it was just such a great
opening got
them guess I'll die
no guess I'll
die well guess I'll
die ja
forr D manid D D D J Monkey D perfect
night D Mr empty block D B Jones D Benji
gaming d
Kaz
denin I know this may be confusing
because I have not put up the thumbnail
but this was the wildor K rebroadcast
super chats and now because these are
also of small numbers I shall read the
AV super chats Che
47 crusty thank you thank you guys for
getting the aat
earbuds okay everything the two streams
beyond that are ooh scaring me I shall
read the Super Chat from the first
enigmatic recollection stream how about
[Music]
that cuz these are not so
overwhelming who would have F I would
get to this point Che 47
NE just Studio Rob f with the pinky T
enjoyed Ian REO and the games but mostly
I was impressed with the number of times
you and inaan had the exact same pose
really did
we truly myth and body is the Buddhist
term many body one mind thank you did we
in the official
program I'm stuck no I'm coming
back yeah that stream was fun the
official 3D program
H
the confusion
with well you know I think I don't need
to explain myself right
somehow
somehow colors are perceived differently
in that room that we were in in the
little box that we were put in the the
colors just look way more similar to me
I do not see pink or blue so clearly and
I can't tell them apart so
clearly H also the length of their
hair has been maybe concealed in a
way
H it seems as as as as
if the suit that I have also been
wearing these past days
covers the whole [\h__\h]
head I always get like such deep ass
like um like like like things on my
forehead like from wearing the cap it's
so deep it it hurts so much I get like
really strong headaches from it and then
I wear the bigger one and I still like
get headaches I'm like what the [\h__\h] why
is my head so weirdly shaped I don't
understand hm
yeah but it has to be a relatively tight
one because like when I swing my head
around it's not supposed to fall
off egg head yes I have an egg
head but yeah I'm I'm I'm glad I'm
getting a break from wearing the suit
for a while
[Music]
now I don't want to wear it anymore for
a
while uh
it's get it gets so hot too and they
don't turn on the air conditioning like
as strong as you might want it because
they always say oh the camera equipment
the camera
equipment ah but they don't understand
how hot it is for us dancing in the
suits
H yeah it's so hot oh my God
bro imagine being covered from head to
toe dancing your ass off
man you know how expensive this gear is
son yeah but I feel like they could
still turn it down like a few a
few I remember like in New
York we it was cold as [\h__\h] and the
cameras were
fine it was cold as [\h__\h]
actually so that's telling me you could
make it colder
[Music]
still it's you against a 66k camera okay
well I get that but it was way colder in
New
[Music]
York on the
stage risk of cameras is overheating
them
right well but I don't think they have
like the the typical air conditioning in
that room anyway it's like not the the
machines that you see it's like
somewhere in the ceilings or something
so maybe it maybe it's just not capable
of cooling it down that well to begin
[Music]
with I complained about the heat well
that was
outside Al honestly I I only felt that
like on the last day that I spent there
I felt it was hot outside the other days
was
fine the CSS yeah I don't know man it's
broken
today it's okay I accept it for what it
is I do not judge I do not
discriminate I did not forget about the
super chats no no thank
you step sings Cruz G
[Music]
key D Garden Park D lunch boook d n and
cotton D for the pinky I love that even
mid MMO questing W still finds time to
Grace us with a tangent you know I know
you guys like my tangent so I tried to
put some in there in the beginning
but every time I do that I think uh
there's a high chance of of getting
interrupted which is a happy thing at
the same time interrupted by people
running by
so it's better to just use those
tangents another time another time g d
d it is done day one has been
demolished mm
[Music]
I am sick and tired of it now I do not
wish to read
more my eyes and my mind are
[Music]
tired I should reach uh uh I should sign
polar wordss even if I don't want to I
need to spend the next hours signing
cuah my leech H that's a word I should
have used
when do we see you
again I do not know I cannot say it
because that might spoiling my
arrival it must be a
[Music]
surprise get ice for your hand if you
need it no no no it's
okay uh that was
like that was that was a lot I tried I
think on that that occasion try to like
sign everything in one day or two days
yeah probably two
days did you get to meet matara no I was
trying to like find
time
but yeah time is not there crony is
like I don't know where
traveling so that's the issue that's
what happens
[Music]
she's in
Spain s with pain once again in
Europe and not asking me to meet up just
kidding it's okay she's she's not alone
right otherwise I would keep her
[Music]
company well I hope she has fun I hope
she comes back with Tales of her
[Music]
adventures now I want to go to the idol
meeting I hope I will not be attacked by
the spider again but I think I will it
would be so funny if she's why is the
[\h__\h] spider always in the same place
now it be funny if it's still
there I will greet it from you guys I
will give it a hello from
you do you want to say something to my
[Music]
spider he loves me is this like Casper
all over
again Casper was a little bit more
aggressive and like bothering
me oh
[Music]
tell he's going doing a good job good
job I what obviously not he's not eating
all the dead flies at
all nice legs okay I'll tell him
that Leo are you still like writing
Minecraft uh or drawing Minecraft comics
because I
would imagine this would be
extremely difficult for you this time
with so many story lines
and your tablet broke okay it's probably
better that way this would be
overwhelming what
huzzah
now
[Music]
h
h welcome welcome
welcome I appreciate you all of you
huzzah
indeed let's break some freaking glasses
huz but I was also about to
go seems like me and gathan with a
ghe are
also like kind of connected I was saying
we might just be in a love triangle do
you guys think she noticed did you guys
notice what I was trying to do with with
the
flower but it's okay it's okay I'm
committed to the
queen it's okay I'm fine you did
yeah yeah it's
okay I I I do not wish to take her and
then for Amelia Watson to return and
regain her memories and then be like you
know I do not wish to create
chaos when there's still a chance for
gan's heart to
be
mended yes
yes I I have not been wooed if anything
I am the one trying to woo but nobody
has wooed
me I don't know if there's even a
fraction of love in her heart for me if
there's any space for me in her heart in
his heart sorry his heart I am maid
andless I have I have remained maid
andless yes this was my last day for
this
chapter this was my last day therefore I
had small hopes but one cannot rush or
Force any love let that be a lesson to
all of
[Music]
you
gathan gathan with a
ghee at least you tried
lamentable but fate shant be swayed is
it fate though is it fate am I fed to be
forever alone it's the Amber coin Deb
for real we are bound by orange we are
bound by love for the queen we are bound
by similar morals
[Music]
and similar spirits and souls I think
but she has yet to
notice the reality of it which is fine I
wish her nothing but
[Music]
[Laughter]
happiness you could be a side chake no G
ofan the gee would not do something like
that g of the G is the most honorable
honorable of them all not taking a
single side chick or even considering it
not even looking back
like in that Meme picture the painting
of the
memes yes no harm route no
no only eyes for his Pearl it's like a
horse with the things on the side to his
eyes he can only look
[Music]
straight the tapestry of a distracted
male a classic
blinders yes
blinders gathan has
blinders around his
eyes or only only uh figuratively
speaking though because there's no need
for actual real
blinders gan's heart comes with
blinders that's yeah that is exactly
what makes Gan so amazing
yeah I agree you have good taste to
follow for sir right I
know well
maybe maybe gathan
will look at the flower again
and
realize what the true intended cause was
[Music]
but at that time I will not be there to
be
confronted I will not be
available it's like Romeo and
Juliet kind
of well at least I have proved the non
pregancy I knew it would
work the red powder
flower okay well I'm I'm glad you guys
came over uh but yeah as I said I was
leaving I have to do some work AKA
signing Polaroids signing many many
Polaroids but you guys can do me a favor
and listen to
Kima if you want we are on a quest of
raising the numbers so that I may
please well there's not it's not really
about pleasing the music department but
it's more about it's more about reaching
a
goal K
stream press for in German we say in
yippee I will be gone for a short amount
of time and then I shall return next
week for my
anniversary it will be my anniversary
week yippee four press four
four four
years four years will have
passed so continue to press four I guess
yeah four is the
number we'll go into the year five oh my
God oh my God right did I do the math
correctly it's confusing
sometimes four years will be complete
and we're end entering year five right
mhm
crazy
crazy I'm excited next week oh my God I
can't believe why is it only next week
enj in
byebye kfp thank you huz
[Music]
h
h my mic on oh sorry I'm just like I
just noticed that the the files I have
to put them in one by one so I'm doing
that right
now wait when I'm done I'll I'll end the
stream when I'm done putting each file
in one by one I can't copy paste the
whole thing
apparently
[Music]
about cuz it also just uploaded one of
them funn
but I noticed oh okay it won't let me
put them in all at once I'm just going
to I'm just one by
one and this one and this one and this
one and this one and this
one
[Music]
that
um
okay I think that should be
it 96 96 96 96 96 96 9 69
69 69 69 69 69 69 69 69
6 just checking the
date
43 I suppose
[Music]
96 I need to go to idle
meeting
whoa
[Music]
okay it is ready it seems to be
ready that was fast now I just put it in
and then it immediately uploaded every
single one of them
okay I'll go say hi to the
spider byebye
[Music]