[Music]
w
uh
[Music]
[Applause]
uh oh my
God sorry sorry sorry sorry I'm I'm a
big
Bo I am so big Bo big Bo big Bo thank
you thank
[Music]
you we are white team white team white
team let's go
[Music]
it's okay
waor
sorry sorry I I'm a I'm a Qui okay okay
be
[Laughter]
[Music]
quiet yeah you don't have the slim mode
on so you're Green in the background in
the
back it's okay you have wide shoulders
today I was born like this I'm
sorry it's you look beautiful okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
fore
[Music]
okay kobby MK I will fly and I will fly
high
[Music]
for escort the
princess
[Music]
[Laughter]
hi
green
[Music]
nice okay
okay
[Music]
Four Seasons relay race
hi
[Music]
[Applause]
Kyla has no last name in this
[Music]
h
h y
[Music]
[Laughter]
the
[Music]
this
[Laughter]
we're goingon to check out the
[Music]
venue okay
okay go to the top go to the top
everybody
[Music]
okay I never played only up but I'm
playing H
up
left
okay right
click weak and strong yeah
[Music]
yeah right is strong
okay you can
try
okay great
[Music]
start it's
parkour nice nice I
got
[Music]
Trent how do you use this thing and you
got to press the Press right click with
one of the Trident the right one is f
longer distance the left one is shorter
distance yes so you choose depending on
the distance you want to
cover I understand understand
yeah sorry
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry oh my
God somebody has been
[Music]
Kor acent
AC no
accident
I want to get rid of the
clouds you want to get rid of them yeah
cuz it confuses me there's too many
clouds real ones there are too many
clouds it's in my
options this one not
real
oh it's
real clouds off okay
nice found I see now it's a clear
[Music]
sky hello
hello
oh
[Music]
no
okay
[Music]
okay in the
actual contest I would die if I fall
down and I respawn at the
[Laughter]
bed prac
this gotta find all the
shortcuts
okay let's go
next check out next
[Music]
one oh right click the debug item
board hi to get rid of the Trident yeah
right click
again
[Music]
pressure pressure
PR okay go back for the stairs again
okay okay so dark it's so dark
than someone didn't pay the electricity
[Music]
bills I'm not participating in this one
but I'll be
watching relay
race M are you in this one I don't
remember I think so
am in the princess one and in this one I
think let me
check you this
one got to go to the other side St over
there so
[Music]
tall yeah so
short oh okay they'll be a gate here on
the actual contest
day
yes no Gates
today
okay one person races for half uh round
half only half half
[Music]
round okay
okay okay
four rounds and eight people so M maybe
you can like talk with your partners
which side you want to race which one's
easier for you okay okay okay okay okay
okay
okay okay okay
oh
sorry I'm translating for you too
KY there de when you touch
it we
[Music]
start
this is
intense
okay big
jump
pretty easy so
far easy
easy just deep snow can't help
it and
touch oh I'm off the
[Music]
Rhythm time first time try I can't get
it m try
harder
I do the
prce I hate going
up this is
cool
I like this obstacle
course what's
happening
on
[Music]
fore is being
[Laughter]
[Music]
punched
I want to go one more round let's go oh
okay run
[Music]
run oh dear okay
okay I messed
[Music]
up
yeah this is
genius genius genius
genius I'm like a
horse that was pretty good from the
beginning no no no no no no
no no
[Music]
you got to get the
bread what
you
[Music]
for okay thank God I'm not in this race
because I can't get the
bread I this wol throwing
yeah Dodge the dod Dodge the
bubbles it is no
run it is fun to
watch okay so the thing is if if you
don't get the bread that's fine but uh
in reality it will be like you're going
to be really hungry at this point so if
you don't get the bread you're going to
be starving and really
slow okay
okay right click the bread too
okay that's why I couldn't get
we to get one
right nice nice nice
oh you got another
one how how many do we need to take I
think you'll just have time to get one
if you want to be fast
[Music]
okay
you might want to eat it before entering
the
snow yes yes otherwise
yeah
really oh try to jump when you're in the
snow
M like only
jumping only they say it's
faster jumping and
running no no no no no no it's okay I
freeze to
death if no uh no you run jum before
before you hop into the so it's like
when the ice block you jump in the
momentum so you can go
um yeah go further try again let's go I
see oh that's they only meant that jump
okay cuz it looks like the others were
jumping before you drop to the snow
block you jump first as far as
possible
momentum yeah yeah like that like
that I see easy I see I
seey
it's
[Music]
icy
okay princess
play
[Music]
princess that wants to be the
princess
[Music]
Prin
for oh
[Music]
we're doing we're doing the the knights
and the princess grinding are she
practicing are you
grinding I'm still in the ice the I is
stuck
forever
I I practicing okay okay let move
on
grinding very important very important I
a
grinding we got to grind too after
everything's uh explained then we can
grind okay okay okay
okay
y
[Music]
okay
okay we're going to split into the teams
that are actually going to do this and
the remaining ones that are not really
participating ah
okay M go to real team
[Music]
hi hi hey
[Applause]
for
[Music]
which one is this H the the one is
orange the orange one is for you
yeah the princess
is so
handsome
[Music]
hi hi uh princess I'm a
princess my
princess princess
I I am your princess protect
me
open
my princess
yes
okay how do I get
up nice nice nice
nice nice
nice okay okay aile
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay okay okay
okay
okay okay stop please stop
pleas stop please okay
[Music]
everyone
stop okay and next next
position
[Music]
nice beautiful beautiful beautiful
beautiful nice
okay okay
okay
they did it too
nice they have to build something
[Music]
okay
I'm
[Music]
one more one
more it's red again
[Music]
okay
okay new new one
[Laughter]
orange ah if they first go for orange
for red maybe it
isan
sorry why is it always red just take
[Music]
Pake
please cutting use cutting board oh no
hey princess hey
[Music]
princess
[Laughter]
[Music]
for
wait this is a
bunny yeah
finally let's go okay go we cook
oh so K is
[Music]
hungry baked
potato I
Bato
yeah
okay okay I'm cooking bakato yeah
okay
yes beef beef beef beef be beef Ste
okay cooked
mton
[Music]
for okay
okay
[Music]
is K with me
yeah we have to make a h hamburger yeah
I'm I I'm trying to I have the steak
already oh you have the steak already
yeah the hamburger steak or the other
steak hamburger I only have the steak oh
yeah oh okay okay actually I
misunderstood that cuz I don't
understand gra uh we have to only make
two specific things and they are the M
hamburger steak and the cooked mutton
right now I'm uh explaining the
hamburger steak okay how how's the
hamburger steak
um okay we're done with the hamburger
steak wow wow wow the second one cooked
m
it's
[Music]
pretty okay but one more one more one
more
M Steak M Steak
okay K cooking
cooking steak Yeah M Steak
okay
yeah smell good oh oh what is this cut
potato oh
cute oh oh nice
nice Yum Yum Yum
[Music]
Yum let's
go let go oh oh this one
[Music]
okay
yeah M okay so you guys girls guys
Knights are going to te tell me um what
the missing block is cuz I see uh I see
free blocks and the uh the there's a
fourth one that I can't see the color of
and I need to know that one so we find
the pattern by communicating I guess oh
okay and I find the missing color for
you
guys uh top left red H top right white
orange orange the bottom bottom left is
yellow
mhm okay new one top
left yellow
top right M
pink and the uh bottom
[Laughter]
left
oh yeah yeah I'm fighting I'm fighting
and I can heal I
[Music]
think
okay okay you fight I buff and
[Music]
heal
okay let's go okay protect the
princess push please okay
okay go go go go where are the monsters
w
[Music]
w y nice nice next next oh dear oh
dear oh dear oh
no destroy them destroy them nice nice
[Music]
nice
yeah next
[Music]
next wait wait wait wait wait wait up up
up
up gold
horn legendary gold
horn she
[Music]
is it their second round already or is
are they still in the
first yeah where where fighting
where they're still on the they're on
the second no
okay yeah they're the real
team
it's fun new
game fun
fun okay okay
y let's join them again
okay
oh I need
to I need
to
[Music]
toally right click
to
exit
okay
[Music]
okay which one
uh good job good job good
job
[Music]
then I have to change it back
okay hi yeah we got H
it's sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
can you girls go back to four because K
Senai had the Discord thingy set to the
fourth
Channel I was making sure Kyla
still are you alive Kyla are you alive
she's alive let's
go
[Music]
commun
let
prce okay next is last maybe
hunting hunting
[Music]
this next one doesn't really need
practice cuz you just find whoever the
prompt is
for
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
for
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay it's not H hunting it's the other
one
[Music]
for
but I'm not sure what we're do we'll
[Music]
see on
[Applause]
her
[Music]
hi okay top person attacks bottom person
runs basically H and we all have to play
this game it
seems we
hunt sorry this is the other game
apparently the one where that we're all
participating this is the horse horse
riding or something like
that I see I guess we just kill each
other I I was
excited oh okay get the most
kills oh free hearts free punches
[Music]
[Laughter]
maybe R wants to be the
[Music]
horse
okay okay okay I will wait KY also press
red okay and then press on guess
maybe yeah M my rid KY I guess right
click on
yeah they
[Applause]
go good
horse oh uh the
[Music]
writer M do you have a book I did
right click the book I
think oh there's something about needing
to become U like some roll I think
there's red white
yellow by yellow and then white and red
nothing oh yeah press red red red mhm
okay
okay okay
nice kill kill
destroy no mercy M no
mercy
what's happening I want to see
closer I got one hit one
[Music]
[Applause]
hit couldn't die
[Music]
kill oh yellow team has four
kills oh my God yellow team
[Music]
red te red te let's
go go go go more kill one more
kill we have to we have to
[Music]
win
close very
close
it's okay it's okay horse we get them
next
time come here I give you
carrots
oh my God everybody will be doing this
game at the same time like all the teams
all
members
oh 21 teams 21 team yes
wow yeah that would be a big
fight
okay you can get like bigger points if
you kill the like leader of the red
yellow or white team so that will
probably end up being Mi Senai mikai
subu Senai representing each team so if
the others kill meai they get more te
more points at the end
[Music]
[Laughter]
okaye
[Music]
spe oh they're going to be a
team
nice okay check it out member hunting
but there seems to be something
[Music]
unfinished but it's okay no practice
necessary probably only
[Music]
knowledge
[Laughter]
[Music]
friendly
[Laughter]
nipp
what a special special
[Music]
bird
oh okay free free Hunters per team
basically okay
mhm
[Music]
okay okay so let's say there's three
hunters from Red Team the other white
and yellow teams will all be present and
only the threee red hunters will be
hunting
okay
oh okay yeah that'll be a prompt like
find the people who are like animal
characters yeah like Fox girls or
whatever
[Music]
oh
okay so when you're hunting you choose a
person you're right click them then you
put a lead on them you lead them over
here you press right click on the board
and it will judge whether or not you
found the right
person
they will be imprisoned
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice
no
animal is Angel not animal
[Music]
angel
oh okay then the hunted people are can
like run around and try to escape as
much as they
can okay
understand
[Music]
yes
okay
interesting
foree
[Laughter]
[Music]
foree
thank
you for
[Music]
explaining any questions otherwise she
she'll be going but we can continue
practicing
fine
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
okay okay some people will be
leaving do you want to practice uh after
this like and I'll still be streaming
though I want to practice a little bit
before I go back to sleep y okay yay
[Music]
okay
mm what do you want to practice Kyla
what do you want to practice um I want
to practice the race oh okay I think
Kyla wants to practice that too
right okay then you go practice race I
go practice my Holo up close by okay
okay okay let's go
should we go should we go in uh like
English speaking channel to like not
bother them are they leaving uh some of
them I think
[Music]
yeah w
byebye her favorite food is uh raw raw
horse Sashimi yeah yeah what's you what
do you call yeah basashi what's it in
English like like horse tartar horse
tartar I guess yeah like raw raw horse
yeah basically horse Sushi
[Music]
Sashi
e
disgusting
e yes good good good M I
[Laughter]
agree Maybe
prce practice yes practice otherwise my
stream is too short can't have a one
hour
stream I have to go
longer
[Music]
11 I
see I think they stay up
late I
assumed normal Japanese member
lifestyle
[Music]
she wants to talk about it uh maybe
maybe you guys are still changing
positions because um you can like test
out who's better at being the princess
and who's better at being the knights oh
I see so it's not final right
now
[Music]
okay
sorry I will be I think
[Music]
we
okay before we go relay race first we'll
do the uh princess one
because they want to figure out some
[Music]
things
for
spe
yes water only
[Laughter]
water
[Music]
whenever you
want
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
foree
[Applause]
[Laughter]
sor
[Music]
that was my
bre I hold on for thank you yes it's to
heavy she poisoned it oh yes thank
you
does she have a license for
this this is
my
okay let's go him princess
princess
okay Kyla what are you what is Kyla
doing I'm practicing it's fine okay
we'll do the the princess one cuz the
team is still
here she will Master the relay
race before the night is through H yeah
I'm still wondering I think I can get
like
[Music]
for
okay
okay they might test out
[Music]
different
okay uh so they're testing out if
princess should be
or because thinks she can be more useful
as a
KN
[Music]
okay
you okay good luck Good Luck Good
Luck okay
okay
[Music]
M you understand
right
[Music]
pink okay
okay
[Music]
using
F5
[Music]
M it
might it might be easier if you press
F5 for this game
[Music]
only stop
stop okay Mo move okay okay pleas
[Music]
okay
okay now you buildt whatever is the
prompt what on Earth okay what's
the everyone get the
[Music]
same need you build it
together got it oh I forgot what these
look like in
[Music]
Japan
I was a ambulan or so or a police
car that's
difficult
TV cooking
[Music]
time
Grill mum will be Grill Master
[Music]
Okay lamb Grill
lamb yes bye okay lamb lamb lamb
[Music]
bye
okay so they'll be like splitting roles
and you can be Grill Master cuz it's
pretty easy to understand I
think let them
[Music]
cook
so difficult so
complicated
okay why I didn't sign up for
[Music]
this is real master master okay okay
easy
[Music]
okay M they'll be numbering them so it's
easier to say than like top left bottom
right Etc so the the top left will be
one the top right will be two and then
bottom row will be from left to right
three and four I think is that easier
for them or is it for
me
okay yes yes to make it easier it might
be easier if they just say right left
and up and down honestly but for me
really they can do it in Japanese I know
those I think numbers will confuse me
do you also know up and
down
okay okay
[Music]
okay
yes yes hi hi hi hi hi I can like
explain everything to you after we're
done with this cuz we're trying to make
their team work I just I just woke up
[Music]
morning nice nice moment
so she is so oh my God
colors wow but you know Kido I don't wow
you know K not yellow
so
[Music]
okay yeah M just fight but if you really
need like healing or Resurrection then
SC out okay I will
scream
yes I me you're still
fine just one enemy left
nice I just wanted her to heal
me fight fight
fight potato fries potato fries give me
potato
fire stand the
fire I did
it what
I thank
you last
[Music]
one
this a real
enemy I don't know what that is I can't
see very well nice
nice
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay no
problem
[Music]
thank you
okay seems like this is the final lineup
M no ni
[Music]
good
okay
[Music]
if you you want practice so please
chatting
me okay
okay
[Music]
ohe bye bye
by
little English speak English
no English
good
good PR so if you want to practice
please okay okay I okay
okay no need for me to be
here
no so
good
[Laughter]
English yeah yes so thank
you let's play together
[Music]
Minecraft thank you see
byee bye bye bye
bye and you know what this means it'll
be only English speaking members left so
now we can speak English y English
English
englisha do you know what games you're a
part of
um yes give me one second you're in the
relay race and in the Hol member hunting
the Hol the hunting is not really
something you need to practice much and
also the thing is we can't even practice
yet cuz it's not quite finished um but I
can explain it to you anyway and then
the Four Seasons relay race uh you can
already practice and Mum and Kyla are in
it too so they want to prce it as well
he came and picked me up cuz I was lost
oh oh okay good good wait so let's go to
the race we're doing that one already
but I think there's something wrong with
the Piston you know oh really with what
the bread one yeah there's something
wrong because the the the pressure plate
is not sticking with the
Piston did someone break it
uhoh bouncing on it a lot it's not like
this before I'll be right back because I
have to feed my animal oh okay no
problem and then I'll probably practice
for like 20 to 30 minutes before I have
to take her out and then maybe take a
snap okay okay a by the way do you know
oh do you know that uh they're going to
split so that like there's you only run
half of the race but you can decide
maybe which half you're better at and
which you
prefer okay there's like a Finishing
Line at the half of it where you pass it
on the button but button you pass it to
the next person but and they'll do the
next half so yeah the slime block is
missing this is not like it was before
yeah yeah yeah there was a sign block
when I got here on this one and then
when I jumped on it it disappeared yeah
well that is um actually I think they
said if anything is broken or so
reported to us so I can tell
them I I wasy I burst the SL n you
didn't let me go away this so loud uh I
I shall
report
to
yeah maybe just take a screenshot of the
slime block oh
yeah yeah just snippy
Snappy oh but if I Tab out oh wait check
screenshots what was the screenshot
button f11 it's been too long F2 F2 F F2
F2
okay uh app
day Minecraft screen
shots
mhm
and Japanese
writing slime block
right okay I have told
them okay
so
narissa follow me I explained to you H
member hunting where was it ah there
thank you Kyla you're so good at this
you're going to kill me you're going to
get good too yeah I'll practice okay so
over here just practice 12 hours a day
and you'll be fine 12 hours a day that's
realistic totally
realistic yeah so you're also part of
this game basically um there will be cat
hair in my
mouth
uh I have a cat
ha I hate when that happens yeah okay so
there will be free Hunters if I
understood correctly threee Hunters at a
time um but uh the other members who are
participating in the game from the other
teams they will be scattered all over
this Arena and they can like you know go
up and try to like hide somewhere or run
away from the hunters so let's say
you're hunting you and they give a
prompt each round for example find the
Live member who uh is an animal
character so uh do I even count as an
animal as a phoenix I wonder I guess I
do so you could hunt me and I run away
from you ah but you will be getting a
lead so I think with right click you'll
be able to put on a lead on any member
you find and you right click them and
then they can't escape anymore once you
leash them and then you bring them over
here to the cage and you have to right
click the um this like yeah this board
and it will test it will tell you
whether or not you were correct if it
was wrong I guess the member will be
released and if you are right they will
be stuck in the cage until this prompt
round is over I think mhm so it's caught
or be caught basically yeah yeah is it I
don't know it it's basically you have to
find the member according to the prompt
but that requires some knowledge about
whole life because there might be some
difficult questions that you don't know
unless you maybe talked to the member
before so you got to maybe guess
sometimes but generally it shouldn't be
too difficult just got to find the right
member and bring him over
no that's basically it I'm in this game
too so we'll be doing it
together sounds good yeah so you'll
you'll be saving me when I get yeah well
I was saying like I might have an
advantage a little bit cuz I I did holot
talk with a lot of
senpai so one would assume that I have
some knowledge here and there if I don't
forget
it nice hello
hello hello it's all birds in yeah oh
yeah right oh my God English speaking
verbs let's
goor Kyla too kind of not really though
our penguin almost pretend imaginary
penguin not
really okay so um I think do you need
any other explanation there ISO no I get
it then go practice the relay race I
guess however long you want because I'm
the only one left streaming it seems or
it's Kyla streaming no no I'm not I'm I
I will I will be going like in 15
minutes I think I I I got to have
another stream of this yeah oh okay I'll
be practicing H up but if we can
chitchat yeah yeah I'm not that
far it's
okay which part do I want to do when we
were practicing this off stream for a
bit I felt like I was so good at this oh
it's F the slime block fixed this is too
easy but now suddenly suddenly fixing I
I
struggle okay I have to hold space
bar okay
um I'll practice hold up
[Music]
two one two one two okay this way and
this
way oh my gosh easy oh it's so so easy
yeah you say that now it's no it's so
easy I go down it's so easy did you did
you partake partake in the uh sports
festival last year not last year I
wasn't I thought I'd have a Time
conflict I can't remember if I ended up
having it or not okay okay cuz this year
I was like even if I have a Time
conflict whatever nice cuz it's always a
relay race but this one's really like
fresh I think the all the other games
are like completely something new and
then this relay race they made kind of
they freshened it up but it's basically
the same concept why am I I feel like at
least from two years ago it's pretty
mhm fresh fresh yeah okay it's right
click okay okay let's get good at Hollow
up no no that's that's my left oh
what's the fastest way through the ice I
need to study it the snow or the or the
ice you go in that like the snow and the
ice
both well test it out can you jump in
this kind of but it's not good enough
it's not good
enough you know what I actually had a
whole life related dream last night yeah
and it was a bad dream oh no oh no
so bad I I dreamed that I was doing a
hand cam stream I
guess and
then I realized that the the cuts of the
camera like it it showed more than it
should and it revealed that I wasn't
wearing pants I was just wearing
panties so um they saw and like I
noticed and I was like oh oh trying to
like hide nothing happened hopefully no
one noticed but eventually I I kind of
ended the Stream but I I kind of put my
PC on standby what the hell and um then
I laid down on my bed to take a nap and
then when I woke up I realized the
stream was still going and the moment I
I touched my mouse and the PC turns on
again from having a black screen uh the
camera the headcam camera was also on
again but this time I was completely
naked and the C camera captured that
tool a little bit and everybody saw and
I was like it I'm ruined
forever like I cannot recover from this
my all my viewers saw me
naked is like the the new like having a
dream about being in front of your class
naked I guess m you left my
room oh what no I didn't mean wait but I
you're in I'm
do you want me to come back yes I think
I need to restart Nissa you can join my
room too
okay what the hell that was I've had a
dream that was kind of similar except it
was like Twitter space but the space had
like a video option and I didn't realize
that it was on and that it was on and it
was showing my
feet and I was so embarrassed cuz I was
like oh goodness my nail polish is
chipping that's awkward
oh my God the game is super laggy right
now for me what the hell your your nail
polish was
chipping yeah it was like it was like
well not not chipping you know how like
you know your nails grow out and so it
kind of looks gross if you leave your
nail polish on yeah so it was kind of
like something like that cuz I used to
leave my nail polish on and not bother
taking it off then like my toes would
grow out so like I trim my toenails but
it'd be like half covered in na polish I
I used to do that whenever I used a
little bit of nail polish but I haven't
used I was so embarrassed I was like oh
no I'm going to be known as the as the
member who doesn't take off her toenail
po oh that was terrifying certainly my
feet your feet yeah want to show your
feet I felt so betrayed
M
understandable I wouldn't want to show
my feet my toies either don't look at my
deformed
feet deformed oh no you have normal feet
they're not they're not deformed but
they're
flat which is like bad for you yeah you
you I think you told me when we were
shopping yeah I was like my flat feet
want to
look I don't think I said that
but oh n joined the
room yay she's just staring
[Music]
Kyla you can join my room too if you
want Oh but now everybody left it I
don't know if my room is like it might
be you yeah I'm going to leave too it's
fine okay oh there it's back it's back
it's back wait you guys don't see it are
you winning Kyla I'm always winning even
I'm losing you will win you really are
you to me you're the definition of
winning thank you like Kyla lost just
doesn't make sense like that's it's not
grammatically correct oh yeah that's put
a lot of pressure on Kyla no it don't
yeah don't do that oh wow
amazing why ises this I'm
sorry toally for
that nice we have BBS many BBS T and
from here I don't know where to go cuz
like these are all so far away is the
fastest way to do this
one oh that's it okay maybe up the tree
I
guess oh okay and then
somewhat blossoms are so
pretty they are they're in nice addition
about the the hollow up you
know actually there's
um
hack not really a hack you can you can
just
are you pressing pressing the
shift no yeah so actually you can just
um pass through it like you can go as
far as you want and then you just press
shift and then it makes sure that you'll
not fall down when you land so you press
shift on the sky oh when you're flying
on the sky you mean I don't get fall
damage shift no like um it let you stay
on the
platform so so you'll not fall down even
though you kind of past the
platform okay I'll have to see
it how when and how my my problem is not
going too far it's more like going not
far enough yeah so that's why you you
you go like a little bit higher yeah and
then shift I guess mhm yeah yeah yeah oh
really
okay damn Kyla knows the tricks even
though she's not competing in this
one I I I practiced before right and I
kind of get it a little bit
[Music]
mhm oh good okay yeah I I imagine the
other's going to be doing this really
fast but it's I haven't even gone up
that far I need to figure out where to
go this is a
lie oh oh
This Is A Lie
tiny oh by the way it's November girls
it's no more October no don't tell me
it's no Merry
Christmas Merry Christmas
everybody oh God there's so much extra
stuff that's not even do you guys feel
like this year went faster than last
year yes
yeah it's faster every year I don't like
it yeah uh I mean that happens as you
get older you know ear become faster and
faster and I think for me it's just
being busy with work makes every day so
fast
yeah okay I was like out of commission
for half the year so it makes me
extra
mad H so was the actual match then when
I fall down this far I would die and I
would respawn at my checkpoint but now I
have to restart from the beginning oh no
how to die how to
die I want to die many
ways I just fall down fall down make you
it it's it's but I don't get fall damage
it's I no wait no yes endless not not
November yeah nonstop nonstop not my
faite I don't want to say it wrong
no it's starting It's Beginning I'm so
excited yay finally every year I look
forward to nonstop not
November but she said that there's not
going to be an N this year right
what what there's not an
end oh no wait there's not a start or
there's not an
end I think there's no start at all it's
so over it's so over
no it's all
over why we love non-stop not did she
not save
enough throughout the year save enough
nuts she doesn't have enough nuts for
her stash
why doesn't this work I'm so bad it
does actually oh my God I chose to sign
up for this because it reminds me um of
the the in the previous Sports Fest uh
the the flying elyra one oh yeah that
one yeah I thought oh this is perfect
for me just got to get good
but I'm so sorry I'm getting a little
tilted
higher go
fast it's hard to see these sefr blocks
man yeah any shaders no not right now I
wonder if it would help H I think I
think I would prefer if these blocks
were like pure
white rather than see
through but
alas they not oh I did it I did it I
went I went to the in the morning I
wanted to get a
quasa like for real I wanted to get a
quasa so I went to the Super Market but
it was close so I couldn't get a Quant
why was it close first November I think
is some kind of holiday I have you told
the story was it you who was like saying
that stuff where you live is just like
closed at the most inconvenient times
like on Sunday is everything closed oh
uh that is true but I wouldn't even say
it's inconvenient cuz I'm just used to
it is how things are here I guess so but
you can't get a fresh qu yeah qu why no
qu how can I survive without qu on a
Sunday how dare they yeah wait it's Sund
freedom from you it's not Sunday it's
just I know but how like on Sundays how
dare they take that freedom from you
right America would never do that just
kid the land of Freedom the land of quo
Freedom mhm oh really oh
n e they're so hard to
[Music]
see can I resign from this I can I let
someone else do this Kyla do you want to
do this
what do you want to do Hol uh only
Hollow up you you can do it I believe in
you that's
F the pressure will destroy me cuz like
only other ones are like except for
princess the princess ones are a little
bit less cuz it's just four people but
most of the most of the things most of
the challenges are like like seven eight
participants like a lot of participants
this is only like yeah one per
team right well two yeah but like a and
b right
so that's like if I up then it it
it it matters a lot while in the others
there's so many participants so maybe we
can like balance each other out so this
is like so much
pressure you can do
it you can do it my skirt is stuck in my
chair
I love you need another
help I do you need another help kiaha no
it's okay okay I'm fine I still remember
the wait let's the last
time last time I over help not ending so
good so I'm trying another one oh do you
want to start over go I'm just messing
with you we can start over the Kyla
crotch story but I already told it Kyla
I saw that one you saw it three what
were you thinking Kyla when you asked if
you can help me with my crotch problem I
just want to help and it's going well
not
thank is that a Spider-Man theme sorry
guys my live 2D room keeps on falling
apart it's okay they keep on
disappearing and reappearing
I can see both of you and that's all
that matters I'm just kidding
[Music]
a iot
to I'm feeling so hot I want to take off
my
clothes in
November what yeah I'm wearing too many
clothes I've gotten to the halfway point
nice I am hello okay we start again from
here she's halfway
there she's Living on a
[Music]
Prayer take her hand she'll make it she
swears oh is that really the lyrics no
oh I fell I would have believed you I'm
cheating I'm cheating I'm
cheating stop cheating I'm
cheating I've gone too far with the
cheating I actually have to go soon
though because my animal is making the
the noise of sh makes when she wants to
go out that's fine cute animal I think I
shall narissa you
in yay I was Aiming High Enough but I
guess I wasn't okay I go oh bye bye
M make sure make sure to hit the the
princess and kns knights's uh up for
practice I shall they said they're ready
for practice when you want want when I
want oh yeah I mean you'll have to
figure time zones
out okay okay I
will I will bye bye bye bye bye thank
you for translating k no problem Mo it's
my
job have fun practicing thank
you byebye bye
bye oh sleep here byebye byebye byebye
and now that was only uh K NAA and
me yay come closer to me or I come to
you wait what part of the relay do you
want to
do I'm doing the same with
you so do you want to do the first half
or the second
half oh about
[Music]
that I'm actually okay with
anything yeah I feel like I'm now that I
figured out how to do the bread jump
jump I feel like I'm pretty uh decent at
the the first part as where it fixed not
yet right yeah it's it's working it's
fixed oh it's fixed yeah I
did oh
okay um fast the only thing I can't
figure out is how to skip this like I
can't seem to jump far enough here oh
you I need to like get the right
momentum about this
one wee
nice is there a goal or is it just get
as high as you
can okay wait I'm on my
way
sheesh okay get the right momentum
so uh I've never been so high before
left or right or middle up go maybe up
I'll go up I Can this seems
manageable m
y okay not not there's another
checkpoint which doesn't matter to me
now cuz I'll if I don't make it stop
halfway if you stop halfway the speed
going to like
decrease
okay I love the pro no I'm not pro now
wait this is going lere
[Music]
though
okay and FY I would go here and touch I
think that's pretty good enough yeah
okay K what are you streaming after
this I'm playing as a
warm swm warm yeah warm warm worm warm
warm warm what what kind of
warm a yellow worm
what what was the game
called imoi imoi imoi yo I'm so
high I haven't even upload the waiting
room yet oh really when's it
starting should be now but oh well it's
okay no waiting room and should be
starting now okay yeah it's okay it's
okay it's
Kyla we will
behave good luck with the worm yeah
thank you the hell is this
go
okay Mama m m m and another checkpoint
wooo okay in
[Music]
touch
go yeah okay I've never used the short
one yet I always used the long distance
Trident I think I don't need the short
one there I
guess
okay then
[Music]
there going to go high
oh and there's another checkpoint oh my
God you are so high up oh you see me I'm
looking at your stream ah I had it open
cuz I woke up because uh I think I
mentioned my sister's visiting with her
kids who got me very
sick um she got you sick or the kids got
you sick her little her little uh her
little kids oh no you do sound a little
bit raspy yeah another checkpoint so I
woke up and I'm watching you and then I
was like I wonder if it's okay to join I
is it okay or are they going to be like
wow look at this weirdo showing up when
we're almost done no no it doesn't
matter there's some people who didn't
show up at all but there's one more um
kind of practice but also like pre party
in the night before yeah Japanese time
night before so they said it's like uh
zasai like celebration but I think most
people will be practicing I
guess I don't know if it's worth going
to the checkpoint but
Raa go back here here come here wasn't
worth it the way how to do
this you you offer all of your mouse to
like up just go up
like like you never look down okay you
just don't need to look down yeah
go yeah okay okay wait wait that that
that's that's too fast okay but you're
doing it it's okay
okay
gosh ah it I want to get my respawn
reset point I want to no I don't want to
start from the beginning but got get
maybe maybe you need to have the wi jump
and
we see you make it right
okay see you make it you need the wi you
just need to remember the wi me too I'll
also go
[Music]
we too far yeah
yay
meow the wi really helps we saw I saw
clips of your Koka with your sisters oh
yeah cuz like when you were actually
streaming it it was like 2: a.m. I think
probably yeah um I need to stream your
sisters seem funny yeah they're pretty
funny that's with where I get it
from hey are they your older sisters
right
yeah I'm the youngest don't I have
younger sister
energy um I don't know I think it
depends I would have to maybe get to
know your sisters a bit more to judge
because even if you're like you seem you
know relatively
mature but compared who knows how mature
your sisters really
[Laughter]
are they might be older
but yeah so age doesn't necessarily mean
just being older doesn't mean that
you're more mature than the others mhm
so this
nah I'm I'm a I'm a middle child M I
have a no wait I am the youngest but
like oh I forgot what am I saying I'm
the youngest but I have some half
siblings that I don't really uh
know so in theory I'm I'm uh older than
them but I don't really count them cuz
from my side of the family I'm the
youngest why did I think I do I give
middle
energy you give honest
only child energy wow okay oh that's
rude I think that's an insult no no
that's I think that's an insult no you
don't give it in the bad way cuz I know
what you mean I'm independent but aren't
only kids not independent because they
get spoiled cuz they're the only child
not so not always no some some only
children are still uh not paying
attention to and their very I guess it
depends really on the family picture but
damn see I could imagine that you were
your parents first kid and they had you
and they're like we don't need to have
another we already had
Perfection okay here she goes again
kissing my butt I love you I love
you KLA do you have any
siblings oh yeah how many is it
secret it's a secret but I'm the
youngest child yeah a baby
cute
baby we are babies together except I
have a younger brother
but I I do hear the the kids in your
background sometimes Nissa I'll I'll
leave soon no no it doesn't matter no
it's fine they're not like that loud and
not that often so yeah no they woke me
up at
screaming I heard it first I thought it
was a cat but then I realized oh it's a
baby that's a baby oh I see bub I would
bring we call one of the babies Bubba
which is hilarious have you witnessed
the
birth no sad that's sad I'm not I don't
want
to understand
of that is honestly I don't know why I
asked it it would be funny if you said
you you you witnessed it because that's
seems like something you wouldn't want
to witness really you already know I've
witnessed my own birth
but because uh my mom recorded it so I
have watch it yeah I have a whole it's
it's in like my my baby video
compilation how did it feel watching
that um I I don't know I took like Child
Care growing up so I I had to watch
videos of women giving birth
so is weird exciting content very
exciting content
educational good for the future good to
know what to
expect yeah
yeah nice nice I mean I can make it I'm
just really slow I wonder how fast the
others will be but if you think about it
it's safer to go somewhat slow because
if you go too fast and you fall down you
keep on falling down and so maybe it's
good to be somewhat
slow I got to peek into other um Trident
players streams and see how good they
are
yeah no oh okay the other Trident going
to hit you too right if you're like
standing in the same position Oh you
mean oh we're all going to oh we're all
going to be up here at the same time
yeah right so you need to like be in the
different platform well I feel like you
know we'll all fall down at different
times and then at at some point we're
going to be like in the beginning it's
going to be maybe close but then I feel
like later we would be okay cool quite
separate
[Music]
maybe like one is like really high and
then falls
down I'll be chilling slowly going up
slowly but surely do we have to eat the
bread in the bread race we don't right
yes they said that at uh at that point
if you don't eat the bread the setting
will be that you're like pretty like
starving and if you're starving you get
really slow in the game so can't eat the
bread right now right yeah right now it
doesn't make a difference but in the
actual race you will be needing it
definitely good to know and you should
eat it before going into the snow they
said okay otherwise you won't make
it hey at the top you have to fight with
the other contestant for real well I'll
never reach
it don't
say yeah we're counting on you kiaba uh
don't count on me please of course we
are you'll do great you'll do great I
regret my decisions I want to um retire
from this I want to put the pressure on
someone else please Kyla please save me
Kyla no
I you need to get some help but not from
me I
think KY already has enough to do
well I can take your place in in in a
different
segment aren't you supposed to be
warming right now anyway
warm become
warm
yeah are you
okay the
time start in 15 minutes it's fine
okay well the race okay I understand the
race I feel like I know what to do
you're a pro right now right yeah I'm
I'm a pro I'm a pro if we if we competed
I would definitely not be Kyla but you
know it probably be
[Laughter]
close okay I'm getting faster at least
oh this is really
far
okay so
far see you're doing so great let's go
no no I'm not you're amazing k i St it
okay let's practice going to the pink
bed but like it's like we need go kind
of lower how do I throw the Trident here
that may be too
low okay
touch
okay
um
well the end is
near okay
that was a b Sky yeah Kyla you're you're
the pro at Minecraft how do I throw
things without going into my inventory Q
Pro but yeah
q that one now Mommy
milk milk that's the first time I heard
that I'm so sorry should I go grab a
baby yeah bring it here okay I'll be
right back she brings a baby let me see
if I can bring a baby yeah a baby or
more than one the more than one
baby oh was it a mistake to come
here cuz I can't make it over there I
can't make it here no way o got to go
here here this is like a a bait
section how do I go back okay we throw
things using the key button right but I
have like I change it because I have
um a very bad experience about the Q
Buton okay great Q while
fighting did you see oh are you watching
my stream yeah I'm I'm watching I wish I
could just die so I can go up there I
got to practice the top
part I need a die
command Dam
damn you should go try going straight up
to test your height
oh oh that pretty high is the baby
here a
baby oh he immediately got cranky what's
baby
name here I'll bring you back to your
mama Holo babies that was
short this is the real Holo
baby I have a pacifier I should have
given the baby the pacifier oh
what's that who that who's that Kyla no
he wanted to eat his Halloween candy in
peace apparently a you're cute how old
baby did I already ask oh I don't know I
don't know how old he is oh A he's
just baby AED you know baby AE yeah
understandable I think he's like two but
I don't know he doesn't talk yet and I
feel like when I worked in child care
like the 2-year-olds
talked so I'm not
yeah I I think I remember some like L
lore about babies that they talk at that
age yeah L baby lore might be near to
but he's still very baby bubble he he
changes his own diaper he changes his
own diaper is what you're saying no
I that would make my he
Chang I thought that's what were you
were saying no no get yourself a baby
who changes his own
diaper all of the kids were dinosaurs
and we took them all trick-or-treating
what oh wait I got so confused at what
you're saying oh right it was Halloween
yesterday they were
dinosaurs mhm you cute what were you
just normal um I dressed up um I didn't
have a costume but a really really long
time ago uh you can buy like the there
there's this place called loock Haven
who makes like Harry Potter um they they
like made the the sweaters for like the
movies for like the school uniforms so a
long long time ago I purchased one and
ordered it offline and then uh my sister
was like I'm going as a Slytherin and my
husband has a Ravenclaw coat so why
don't you wear that and then you could
be warm but it was still
freezing half frozen over so you were
Ravenclaw yeah I was a raven class
student o but what would you have liked
to be um it's a good question I don't
have an answer I saw all the Advent
costumes that they were so cute my God
you got so many good ones they keep on
popping up in my Twitter timeline and
they look so awesome I'm so happy
talented jailbirds I wish you could like
legit put them on and and have them be
like live to D already mhm me too okay
let
okay oh go go go two one
go was this the was this the bait
section
no was
it go
here oh yeah this will become harder
with other people in here won't it yeah
there will going to be like a lot of
people oh no um it's really
so oh two
people ah here comes the bait here comes
the
bait first pink
bed
here
no this I want to I want to go to
my
checkpoint faster re a faster I'm trying
made it
FASA what if I you got to be
faster got to be
faster you got to be faster Rea no
pressure I don't think anyone can be as
fast as you
Kyla no you need to be faster we're
going to win this I
know let's go
Rea no
[Music]
but did this reset my checkpoints
no I love Kyla
Senai I want to test I want to practice
the
top no I don't take damage in this mode
like even if we punch each other you
don't take
damage it's like set to be always
healthy okay I think I need to go if you
want helping me drink
Kyla byebye
byebye good luck being a worm yeah I'll
be enjoying my life as a worm thank you
for having me thank you thank
you how do you go to cre love you even
if you're a
worm
yeah will she will will you still love
me if I'm a warm yes let's go
good luck have fun thank you keep
transations thank you
byebye can I go to creative
mode can you just switch to creative
mode I don't think
so it was it was
possible oh it was possible during the
meeting we had
but F3 plus F4 I don't believe it that
sounds
scary yeah no permission
okay I'll ask if they can like make it
possible that I lose HP when I start the
Trident
game
[Music]
Su sorry
up
uh
[Music]
check
HP
[Music]
okay nice
Tak hold
up you said you get one of the babies is
there more than one there's four there's
four babies how many babies did she make
um well she has one cherub that is
currently in her body at the moment oh
damn um so she'll have five
what all in all mhm American families
wow yeah wait so there's four babies all
from her mhm which one is it the
short-haired sister or the long-haired
sister the long the eldest sister oh
damn she's busy yeah she is very busy is
is the oldest one the 2-year-old or how
does it work does she have twins no no
no no the oldest one's
like I think they're all like a year or
two years apart I think they're all
really close in age so I think the
eldest is eight and the youngest is like
almost two or two who Okay okay so the
one you brought was the youngest yeah
the other
ones the one you placed as an offering
to me okay yeah who immediately screamed
upon seeing the vtubers oh my God he we
should look like ctoons to them like oh
funny cartoons no they they watch too
much I don't even know what they watch I
go down the and they're watching like
these weird cartoons that I don't
understand yeah we're more interesting
we're we're more interesting than the
Teletubbies come on but I'm not really
kid-friendly
so well it's okay as long as they don't
understand like the two-year-old maybe
doesn't understand these evil words yet
that we're using so I
mean I still get yelled at for using
them though it from your family or from
from your viewers my my my sister she's
like or uh oh so I I a common phrase I
like to say is oh my God right yeah and
yesterday I said it in front of one of
the babies and he he he
turned he said don't say that that's a
bad word what oh my God I guess okay for
religious people it's not nice to use it
all the time I was like I didn't know I
said a bad word can you please tell me
what word I said so I don't say it
again and so he's like I can't say it
it's
can't even say it we we ended up um me
and Anisa she's like will you whisper it
into my ear you won't get in trouble
it's okay and um so he whispered it and
then she was like
narissa can't say
that yeah I think I've heard about that
like religious people don't like their
to have people put the sh not take's
name in
v yeah but like what if it's in a
positive way like oh oh my God I love
you so much no it's bad it's bad no
matter the context okay well yeah I
don't I don't get it but you know that's
like too hard to control I can't I can't
even stop saying really bad words so
yeah right like I can't stop saying the
f word nonstop like
you any of my language be honest have
you accidentally said in front of the
babble Babble children you said it
before yeah no I I've said
because I I you know I'm not used to
them being here right so I used to work
in child and because you know I'd have
to prep myself every day for going to
like work and stuff and it was like for
set hours I I I was really really good
at like controlling like my my sailor's
tongue um but like with my sister's kids
I'm like not I'm not used to them they
just kind of randomly come over and we
have like a few like maybe a week of
notice and then they're like here you
know suddenly
so then I'm like I I don't expect it and
then like it's really stressful because
I'm not used to like you know being
woken up at 600 a.m. from screaming
children yeah oh dear hey how long are
they
staying hopefully not much
longer yeah I don't think I could live
like that yeah know I it's it's a bit
difficult but it's nice to see them you
know I love my niece and nephews so
there was a time when I was still like
visiting one of my younger half sibling
now I have two but I only met one of
them and he was a baby young small
brother and um I was like sleeping over
there and I I remember yeah there was
like lots of baby crying but baby was
cute pretty cute and so yeah it was it
was not too bad I
think but it's it's still it's still a
lot when but you know what I don't like
I don't like the baby
smell oh I love baby smell will grab her
babies whenever they're here and take
them and really I hate the baby smell oh
my
God it's wow that's so surprising it's
like how I hate a hospital
smell okay I see I mean that's okay you
don't have to like baby smell there's no
requirement to like baby
smell I'll have to like it maybe at some
point who
knows I I mean I think when if you ever
decide to have your own little baby you
know like it won't matter because you
know your brain will trick you into
thinking you like it m I guess so oh my
god I've come so far is this the top
look at you what are these other blocks
I have no idea the yellow the red block
do I have to is this the last thing you
have to do reach the maybe the the
emerald block over there damn I should
read the
rules oh I wasn't make
it you did is this what I have to reach
what is this
then so there I don't see where what
that we would fight up here let me I got
to read the
rules let's see let's see uh English
version of the
rules I thought it was only going up
that's
it okay uh use the mod Trident to jump
up the platforms reach as high as you
can within the given time don't forget
to touch the beds on the way too
uh participants will receive two more
Trident that would launch to blah blah
one Trident F across another Trident F
across hold left shift button midair to
trigger slowmo it didn't feel much like
a slowmo to
me I was I was doing it without the
shift all this
time uh touching a checkpoint Nets EXT
you get extra points for touching
checkpoint
too oh two rounds in total first round
red versus red versus yellow and then
again per reaching 10 platforms one
point per reaching the checkpoint Five
Points reaching the top 10 points oh
that's kind of low like in general the
the points you can get from this are
kind of low but it says nothing about
fighting oh wait there's
more participants register for the sign
get starting starts the team that
reached higher within the given time
wins okay so it is a reach as high as
you can with in the time not a fight at
the end who said that I there's no
fighting M confirmed okay there were
like a few people in my chat who were
like I am going to fight at the end
Death Match I'll fight you for fun no no
love
forever
dou I got one guide okay yeah well
that's good I didn't want to fight up
there so reaching the top reaching
checkpoint reaching each checkpoint
gives Five Points in total if you touch
all the checkpoints it will give you
more points than just reaching the top
quickly if you ignore imagine ignoring
all the checkpoints cuz you think oh I
got to go up faster it will give you
less points than if you touched them so
got to touch
[Music]
them are you doing anything else today I
have to record one song actually
urgently um I just realized that today
this when I woke up and read the message
the reminder message that uh today is
deadline I'm like
H wait what have fun yeah so I'll be I I
actually yeah that's why I can't stream
that long anyway but you know this whole
time I have this feeling that maybe it's
because I don't have a bgm on and now
that now we're so few people um more and
more fewer fewer but it feels like we're
just like not even life right now I feel
like we're just having this like normal
conversation just chilling just hanging
this feels so real chat does it feel so
real to you too like you're peeking into
our private
conversation it's such a quiet quiet
time but I like it it's so comfy yeah
just me and you stop don't say it like
that oh my
God I just am sick I'm so
sick what do you think you have just a
cold it's just a it's seasonal I'm
pretty sure I would like to hope it's
not Verona you know but I don't think it
is I haven't I I guess I I hear some
people still get it but in my like
acquaintances and friend Circle I
haven't heard of anyone getting it these
days well they they were the the
children were traveling a lot
internationally
so they there's a possibility they could
have brought in something back
but how does this shift
work do you press it before jumping
I'm not sure I don't even know how
anything Works actually I don't need
shift disable the toggle
oh uh wait sneak
toggle versus no
shift
shift versus no shift it's the same huh
I don't get it mid maybe uh
mid is it just a
landing oh I think it's a landing cuz
now I without shift I landed with a
Steppy
sound wait no I also I'm good stops your
[Music]
momentum
versus I don't know I don't really see a
difference there was a time I went two
years without getting sick then my
cousin broke my streak ah man you know
in Japanese they
say
Baka idiots don't get sick so if you
don't get sick it means you're a sussy
baka my
God mean like as if it's not something
to be proud of to not get
sick why why makes no sense just showing
off if you don't get sick I used to you
think you're better than us you don't
get
sick I'm teasing you used to I used to
never get sick but ever since I joined
Holo I get to go outside less so my
my illuminum Illuminati system what
what's it called
your immune system immune
system
system my immune system is like really
so when I do go out I get sick so
often since I joined whole
life it's really
bad really bad you don't even know Nissa
do you know well maybe I guess you know
cuz you were probably watching at the
time cuz you love me this time more like
December last
year I
got so sick like I haven't
gotten so sick like maybe maybe two only
maximum two times in my life um what did
I have I had I had everything it was so
funny I went to the doctor and he said
yeah you got everything like everything
what did I have the bronchitis
thetis
laryngitis dude and a third thing as
just uh was it just called sinus
infection like everything you get in the
winter and it was so bad because like oh
my God I was I was dying I think I also
went like too late to the
doctor so I got my my medicine too late
and it was a big fum Arc I kept on
spinning out fum for so long during my
streams too I always had a spit
Cub no that's so disgusting but oh yeah
that was it was like so bad that when I
was um I had so many coughing fits that
would make me throw up and it was so
painful I was crying because when you
throw up you know how your eyes get
really teary and and and I was just so
also so so defeated
man no and I couldn't sleep and but but
my cats were always with me part no not
really I think smoothie got sick of me
being so loud and then chunky wonky
still stayed by my side chunky wonky
good
yeah was so bad and I still tried to
stream cuz I I noticed that like uh like
a lot of members were either also like
sick or they were taking the time off
because of holidays so I felt like kind
of this pressure that I have to stream
because nobody else is streaming like I
I have to I have to so I still streamed
like I had one stream where I was just
like typing on the keyboard which was
actually kind of
funny that was funny right
guys no and I that's that's why I hate
like I love living alone but when I get
sick I hate it because like no one is
there to like help me make some soup or
something right that's the worst part
worst part but now I live with my family
yeah so you're not alone yeah that's
good oh wait I got a reply
[Music]
already the
checkpoint yeah they're saying I'm using
this the I guess I'm going down again
I'm using the wrong mode but I tried
entering
normally and I don't no so it says here
right click to
enter uh wait can I unbug wait let's
unbug
maybe uh wait
but okay so now I'm not in debug mode so
I choose which one first this is game
start and this is
entry I
entered and then game
start
oh do I get my Trident too
oh three a two a
one uhhuh wait I also got a bit what do
I do with this bed do I put it here oh
oh no it's just to press the new bed I
don't know we'll see okay let's go let's
go oh it says there is slow motion
now oh it but does that make me it does
that doesn't that make me
slower I guess I just do it when I'm
like really concerned mhm wait the try
itself also has it
oh it also has a like a cool down you
you have two you have two yeah but the
one is
shorter Kyla please do this for
me I don't feel like I can do it anymore
not with these
cooldowns oh wait no this one's this
one's definitely
faster oh my God it improved yeah they
made some changes since yesterday today
actually how do you know you were
watching some stream weren't
you I have not practiced uh until today
so this is the first time what so if I'm
if I'm on the cool down from the long
one maybe I go short with this one how
short oh okay we got to test how short
the short one really
is H well that's a shitty position maybe
go with long
okay but slow motion I don't feel like I
need the slow
motion too good for
it maybe at the top when it gets like
really iffy
yeah okay otherwise why you something
you don't need no are you still
practicing the relay race no I'll leave
I feel like I've got the hang of it so
I'll practice more on my own later okay
okay but for now I just felt like
keeping you a a little okay do I wait I
haven't touched the checkpoint yet M
okay I
should okay what were we talking about
before I saw this answer I don't
remember my brain isn't all
there she just here from
me wait time oh there's act oh okay okay
there's oh running time
so this n oh and it keeps on counting my
meters
oh okay well let's say that this is a
real match and I fell down cuz I'm the
nervous little
which is really realistic cuz I
will
crumble and fall apart when this is
happening I'll be like oh my God I can't
handle this I'm so
sorry so this is just
realistic let's go here and then use the
long
one yeah like this okay can I go up with
the short yeah okay 42 M 100 seconds
left okay so the real challenge is
reaching the top within the time limit
oh my
God okay
cool let's
restart checkpoint did I I didn't touch
it again well it doesn't matter because
I want to restart
um red and
start yeah points for touching s is
there we
saw
K ah we were talking about getting sick
and being alone
so I'm sick and alone no you're not
alone you're not alone don't lie to
meally alone everyone's watching the
kids they don't care about me being
sick yeah okay I can see
that them not caring about you and um
well actually I I don't know if I've
talked about it yet but the reason my
sister is here is actually cuz she's on
bed rest right now oh from biring from
being about to birth yeah yeah basically
so um everyone's kind of trying to help
her out me included which is why I got
sick but um yeah so really no one gives
a that I am sick how's she doing is
she doing well uh no no not really um
but it it should be fine we're trying
not to get to stressed out yeah you
would think after so many births is just
another
one yeah well it's it's more of like uh
uncontrollable stuff that you can't help
that sometimes just happens with
pregnancy you know I you know she's had
a lot of babies though so she was
singing while she's breeding the bubble
in her yeah yeah and like pretty deep
into it
too but I mean singing is like
not like difficult right when you PR I
mean it depends it depends cuz she kept
saying she's like I can't breathe
properly because I have a cherub up in
my lungs because you know moves all your
organs out of the way so all your organs
get kind of like crushed into each other
so can't breathe as well when she's
pregnant oh
damn damn that sounds
rough yeah babies
man so so
motivating let's get some there let's
get our
own you want to adopt
cuz no I I thought this works
wait I'm confused you are you saying you
want to have a baby with me cannot get
prante with
Nissa I mean maybe if we use bone marrow
or something I don't know what what's
that bone Mar
bone I don't
know what did you say you'll be carrying
though right not me I mean I guess I
become oh my God this is so funny I
actually had a dream where I you said as
a stream idea where uh for nine months I
I followed through pregnancy but it
wasn't even a real pregnancy it was like
a virtual so I like commissioned like
that sounds like me that sounds like
something I would come up with yeah I
know that's probably why I had the dream
because I watch you so often
I'm oh yeah let's go play on for nine
months for stream idea and then and then
um we we raise a baby and then it just
disappears because there's no baby it's
imaginary
oh that sounds good
man sounds really good maybe there's an
actual video game where you learn to or
you try to the challenge is to raise a
baby it's
okay just being dramatic cuz I fell down
I love your dramatics I love your your
whatever everything I love your
everything
too but like I'm not the
simulator uh no thank you Mom simulator
is a thing is it multiplayer I need my
dad you're the
dad man life sucks yeah this is really
hard why did you sign up for this
because I thought that it can't be that
difficult and I thought it's like the
the elyra like it's a replacement for
the elyra um thing and I participated in
the na before because I'm the Phoenix
and I feel like you know I should show
off my flying skills but I regret
everything
now uh I feel like well I just need to
know how good the others really are cuz
that will make me feel maybe more
confident or more less
confident yeah I'm sure I'm sure there's
going to be some I mean it's like
anything you know there's probably going
to be some people who are good at it but
I feel like most people probably be
pretty similar to you and be having hard
time and be really worried the good
thing is I guess that people weren't
even able to practice this until like I
don't know this week most people only
started like in the white team at least
started practicing this today this day
so overall it's not like there could be
a big difference in like skills unless
that's all you do for the next four days
yeah which no one is going to do yeah
and I I really couldn't because I have
like sponsorships and stuff like I need
to record songs I need to uh learn coros
I have like so much to do right now that
I can't like grind this really hard
that's my issue yeah no I feel you I'm
I'm still new and I've got like so much
to do
yeah man oh okay all
right at least the games you chose I
mean relay race is always like
pretty oh cuz I knew I didn't want
to let down the team by picking
something too hard
ah this is how it works you don't die
you just press the bed okay yeah don't
want to let down the team but really
race is a big team so the good thing is
the others can always make up for the
failures of
others and we've got Kyla on our team
yeah
yeah really race is fun I signed up for
it too but I didn't get
chosen I was glad why did I sign up for
this why did I sign up
oh I still don't need the slow motion
though I don't need it where do we
go can I make it with the short
one e close but yes
okay Kyla was getting three to four
bread as a strat in the relay race I
don't I would wonder if there's really
enough time to take and eat so much but
can you with one jump can you take so
many or can you only take one per jump
I think it gives you multiple I feel
like every time I do it I've gotten like
three two or three okay well then that's
good that's good all right let's go to
the green
bed nice okay all right okay not bad not
bad um where do we go from
here maybe long long one up here cuz
that scares me you just need to channel
froggy waah and to just jump I am froggy
waa
jumpy
so true if you could make yourself like
an animal Persona like I made frogy waa
for myself what would it be that's a
good question I mean I'm already a bird
yeah so but need another one backup oh
did I get baited no I can do it maybe a
fox I really like foxes
foxy foxes but you know that that seems
like such a like nice one and frog for
me was kind kind of like a joke one you
know I love frogs what do you mean what
do you mean that was a joke
[Music]
yeah come on I can do it with a short
one
yeah yeah being being being frog is
Serious Business
yes let me look up funny looking
animals funny for Faun for example I
would say it's being an elephant right
now or like meme animal is being an
elephant now
mhm else like you could be a giraffe
because you're so tall you could be a
giraffe let's go giraffe narissa
giraffa
giraffa wait here how can you even go
further with without the long one like
heck I guess this jump I should have
done with the short
one oh well
giraffa
Kisa
k e this one too needs the long one
can't tell me you can do this with the
short
one shall we
test let's say I'm on cool down oh it
does work okay do not underestimate
the the short range one so it's like
short like at that point I think it was
like a switch a rule between one jump
long one jump short one jump long one
jump short otherwise you have to
wait so close yeah
is this one also possible with
short
no okay then okay
long after the bed which color yellow
after yellow
bed now this has to be long
too can't tell me that works so
short no
[Music]
well honestly I think that's like it's
realistic that a lot of the participants
won't reach the top because of being
nervous and falling down by by TR being
by trying to be too fast and all that so
oh I can continue here
actually there's just no time all
right so I don't want to put too much
pressure on
myself yeah don't stress about it just
have fun at the end of the day that's
the most important part having a good
time okay that has to be a long
jump ah you're starting uh solo B skate
today right yeah yeah yeah I am oh my
God you're being evil right yeah I'm
going to be doing the durge and I
actually already started a a dark urge
run where I'm being a good guy so I was
thinking for stream I'll I'll try to
make all the curs decisions that I but
but the issue is I don't want to play
the game without
carlac I saw you like discussing that
like making posts about but what do you
guys think why do you ask them if you
want to if you already made up your mind
I haven't I'm going I'm going to have to
sacrifice her which means I haven't
picked my well she won't die but I mean
yeah but what the f i'mna I'm going to
try TR to okay remember pink bed go
higher than you think pink bed go higher
than you think yeah he I'm excited
you're starting pretty early in the day
too with your Bal skate streams right
I'm just going to play it all day I've
been when starting today uh 2:00 p.m.
CSC my time so it's in uh it's it's
currently about to be 11: a.m. so how
many hours until
start
like three three hours yeah three hours
is I'll ra you but I don't think you
know I I wanton stream that long but
finally I can raid
you yeah a ton of people that were
asking they're like when are you guys
going to continue your run yeah the
thing is like uh we that we we were
going to but then everybody was like
busy and gone and this and that and we
were waiting and now we're not talking
about it anymore no one is bring it up
yeah and it's it's been kind of a long
time too and since we're planning on the
the next one being the last one I feel
like it' even be kind of awkward to just
randomly bring it back for one yeah do
people know that we're ending we we're
planning to end it uh with the next one
yeah at least I know I talked about it
and I was like okay yeah we're just
gonna we're gonna make the last one
finish off act one and then no we didn't
talk about it again yeah I never
mentioned it but you know it's just like
as you can see even now even scheduling
the last one eventually you will run
into bumps where people just are too
busy and so it's difficult to have such
a long running collab with four people
with two people it's still manageable I
think totally yeah but four people and
then the problem is like we made a team
that consists of like kind of four
different time zones yeah and three of
them are very far apart mhm so it it was
never really realistic that we would
play Until the End
yeah yeah I hope you will still beat the
game at some point kiaha yeah um higher
than you think yeah I I was already
going pretty high let's go this High
okay
finally yeah B is G and I was playing
solo too but I have so many long running
games going on I don't know if I'll go
back to it on stream yeah you should
finish it off stream
M yes just one of those games to enjoy
in my
privacy no for real it's it's so fun on
your own especially cuz then you don't
have to worry but I I'll probably play
through it faster and not do everything
but um yeah I have to wait was this a
short jump perhaps maybe it was cuz this
is a long one this could be a short
one let's let's
try okay whoa and then this is a long
one
again oh I even made it up here okay I
remember that the the double platforms
here you can make it to top but then I
would have to wait for the long one
again cuz this is
short okay at least from my judgment
yeah I should get going I have to I have
to eat and stuff before
before I have to stream it a bit cuz I'm
going to be streaming the rest of the
day that's
understandable I love you thank you for
letting me in I love you too good luck
I'll be watching you all right I'll I'll
have a lookout for um PR co-op
games all right I love
you l
l and so finally kiaha was
alone I mean she's still kind of there
there she
goes I'm alone guys this is it I'm too
lazy to turn on bgm so it's really quiet
this whole time today is bring your own
bgm to work day not a h that doesn't
work with a short one okay we learn we
learn I don't know how much longer I
should be um streaming today cuz as I
said I have a recording to
do that's really urgent oh wait I said
no no ah was ah cuz when I'm
on right click on the Trident and then
switch to the bed while still on right
click I automatically go here o if that
happens to me during the Home
bun that'll be
up
damn
yeaha
I tomorrow I think I have lots of time
to practice this cuz I have the
sponsored stream early in the morning
then I'll obviously go back to
bed I'd rather wait here for the long
one then risk the short one even if I
have to wait for the cool down and
actually same thing here but it must be
possible I guess let's
try have I tried this before oh yeah
okay this one works but you got to try
to land on this or this one otherwise
it's
over so excited for the sponsor yeah for
people who don't know cuz it wasn't
written on the
schedule um my sponsorship tomorrow will
be Star Ocean never played Star Ocean
game before oh this one let's try
getting to the second
one yeah nice nice
nice uh yeah but it's just a um really
weird time for me to stream so I'm
hoping you guys can show up even if it's
really weird it's like I never stream at
that time it's so weird even for EST
it's really weird 2: a.m. EST I think
but PSD could show up so I'm counting on
you
guys oh okay I see from the big platform
here short is possible let's remember
that this one could be short
too but I don't want to risk it cuz I
haven't touched a bed in a
while we'll be there thank you thank
you yeah it's like mainly pixel Graphics
but uh it looks really HD
nonetheless okay short short short short
double short oh oh or do a long one and
try to land on this one again huh I
don't know
actually I don't know what's the best
thing to do
you'll be there no matter what thank you
but after that I'll after early streams
I always sleep again cuz I never managed
to get enough sleep before them so I'll
sleep and then I'll probably do
Minecraft practice off
stream yeah and do other things like
probably practicing sleep talking Coro
sleep
talking sleep talking yay okay cool cool
I'm I'm I am more like accurate in my
jumps for sure oh I made
it damn at the end there's like no
checkpoint for a
while not hold it or or did they remove
the
beds after I was done time
wise
confidence is this like I still wonder
what these are for maybe it's like a Cod
S at the end for showing who was
first if you want to be number one and
get the medal for it you have to stand
there and then number two number
three
h i know the beds aren't
[Music]
there yeah extra points I don't know
about that finally here to watch the
prep for waa sweep ah thank you welcome
oh you you're so late I'm ending soon
probably I guess I'll go one more
time
um but we used to have a big
family
uh White team not all of one team but a
bunch of them it was my first time
talking to ladin and I kept on roasting
her in
Japanese I didn't even know how I was
able to she gave me the best
openings just can't help
it
oh oh she wanted to be the princess um
in the princess game and then I was like
I don't think
princesses usually smoke so you can't be
the
princess she was everybody laughed and
she was trying to make excuses oh oh
today I didn't smoke today I didn't
smoke what was my other roast uh the one
time the one time when she was trying to
leave and I said eh Don't you want to
support your your senis cuz this whole
time she's like being so oh senis my
senis Are Holy I love my senis and then
you're not going to stay to watch us
practice and I was kind of making
references to um how in Japanese work
culture often you got to stay drinking
with your boss and like you got to stay
until all your superiors are uh there at
work and then there's often like
afterwards drinking sessions right and
then and like even if you don't want to
go you're kind of forced to go unless
you're like really high up in the
ranks and and then you um every night
you go drinking even though you you
really can't do it like from a physical
yeah point of
view but your boss makes you go drinking
so we were making references to
that and then people were like hey is
this a isaka what's going
on can I do this with a short jump any
of these maybe this one or just no this
one yeah should be work yeah
yeah power
harassment yeah sadly that's what it's
that's that's what it's called like I
never experienced it myself but I hear a
lot about it
[Music]
so she just gives me so many openings
man but I think like she en like enjoys
this like like having any kind of
dynamic with any Senpai really at the
moment and she seems to be
ah
oh oh a didn't touch the one bed
she seems to be the type to be like
totally open
for any kind of um banter so I like it
yeah and I want to cuz I'm like so
strictly uh not against but like I
wouldn't I would never smoke anything or
drink alcohol so I feel like we're the
complete
opposites so I want to like tease her
with
that yeah straight edge
wa okay
tou important keep on forgetting
it
go didn't
work
okay I hope there won't be lag uh in the
home BN Home bun
because if you guys were watching for a
while I don't know if you saw but I had
some lag in the beginning of the
practice if that happens I'm going to be
so
like I would I would charge the
Trident but the jump happens literally
two or 3 seconds
later oh yeah I'm so stupid that was
obvious that it's not going to
work server
lag I think I remember like in the
previous years
year that the lag was improved a lot
wasn't
it the general
lag
aiming highest is always preferable that
is
certainly
it unless the platform is pretty much
Straight Ahead then I want to be careful
with where I'm
aiming I guess you could do this one
here short if you have the time to jump
up on the top
block and then here is a bit interesting
because there's a middle platform
that you want to reach first and
then it didn't work I charged it too too
too
little okay so this
block up
here then like
here and then
here oh no oh it's already ending oh I
didn't even know we had a time limit
right now I didn't realize I turned it
on
I guess you could jump normally but like
if you're like in the groove I feel like
I don't want
to I don't want to switch
around he yeah once you touch this bed I
wonder if you have to go back here or if
you could could do a long jump all the
way over
there no not
really but okay ah can do a jump to the
m to the over there
though let's see
short fine
short
what nah no
way no
way okay it's possible and the good
thing is it's right after the checkpoint
so even if I fail that that one it's
okay does my stream really say that it
started ages ago you're not the first
time person I writing that
comment weird funny bug yeah let's Flex
those hours takanashi Kiwa the
endurance endurance
streamer it's totally true I've been
practicing for 14 hours 3 hours for me
oh that's fake that's the
bug
oh H
okay
I
sure I might actually want to go to the
vet
tomorrow cuz I think I got time because
I've been really worried about chunky
wonky and I've been trying to find time
to go to the
vet she's been throwing up a lot and
that's not
normal it's
not I guess it's
long
m this is the point where I think I said
I want to wait for the cool down because
I don't see how I can do it with the
short
[Music]
one this
one Let's test
it I don't
know I don't know about
that any changes in the food no
and it doesn't look like hair balls like
it's always the food that I
see
yeah okay you guys agree you must have
pets let's bring her tomorrow my I'm
so my baby my baby she's so fluffy right
now now her her winter fur is crazy it
makes her poof up so much it's so cute
smovie is
like she gets more fluffy too I guess
but it's not as noticeable as with
chunky wony it's like she gets one more
layer a whole
new extra layer it's crazy
poofy oh waa okay okay sheesh
sheesh
you pink
high
[Music]
nice yeah this one's going to be long
this one's got to be long first person
po jump King true that's what that is I
never played only up like everybody
played it that was flavor of the month
game number one at the time was I too
busy to play it where was I what was I
doing was I in Japan at the time maybe
that's why I didn't play it but I also
just didn't feel like interested in it
just boring looking to
me yeah I just didn't care yeah that
that's that that seems
legit s game was a bit different s game
I cared for I only play flavor of the
month games if I really find them
interesting for me personally
can we do this one short please because
I otherwise I have to wait for the cool
down all the time who did you see I was
already falling down I stepped too far
no
boundaries and this
one sh Wait this
one's
shape wait wait
okay got to practice that
one let's go
long no that there was two of these
thingies where there's like like a
cross-shaped platform right on top of it
this was not the one that I wanted to
skip oh
God okay
nice all eyes will be on me when I play
this game man at least from the
white Team all eyes will be on me cuz
there will be only three people up here
doing this can you imagine how nervous
I'll be I'll be so
[Music]
nervous
might carry white on this game don't say
that I I don't I don't I don't think
I'll be good at it but I'll practice
more
tomorrow for
sure now I have to go record a
song uhuh actually if you think about
time zone then the deadline is already
over but we we'll hope that I will be
forgiven cuz it's already past midnight
in Japan let's hope I will be forgiven
thanks for streaming a little longer
you're welcome you're
welcome like literally cannot end the
stream after an hour it's impossible
like the button is grayed out for me the
ending stream button it's great out for
me my my my account has a special um
block on it yeah programmed by my
Harvard
student
um I I'm not allowed to end my
streams uh under 3 hours yeah it's kind
of up but I accept it cuz it's
kind of how I how I roll you know yeah
parental
lock only sponsor streams are now yeah
yeah but even for the sponsor stream
tomorrow I think I want to go a little
bit longer cuz like what can I how much
can you do in a jrpg game in 1 hour I'm
going to play at least one and a half if
not two if I'm not too
tired
Al I I I'm glad if I can make the
sponsors Happy by providing them more
than they asked
for oh yeah I have to PR like actually
there's nothing to prepare for no I'm
just playing a game so nothing to
prepare just downloading the game yeah
nice yeah can barely get the intro in
yeah will you have to play it from start
or will they give um they didn't say
really but I think it's expected to
start from the beginning
so I'll be doing that I want to know the
beginning I want to play the beginning
with you
guys I wouldn't have time to go like
much further anyway I think you're
playing it on release date yeah I guess
depends on the time zone but maybe I am
you I saw vam I also um played it today
it was also
sponsorship isn't the opening cinematic
Alone 2 hours in most
champ no it's not that
bad may I ask what your channel is about
you seem pretty
cool huh I play games I sing I make
music I I mostly I play games though
mostly jrpg and like funny oneoff
games um a little bit of uh RTS games
recently and this and that really this
and
that so subscribe oh you already
subscribed by the fact that you're in
the chat and
[Music]
I talk
about I do a lot of hand cam creative
variety streams that those are those I'm
really proud
of very proud
this yeah I'm I'm I've been in
subscriber only mode for
months no yeah no cuz everybody else was
doing it I thought I guess I'll do it
too I mean at these in these trying
times you have to get everybody to
subscribe as much as you
can yeah talk about cats yeah so true I
do talk about my cats a lot so cat
lovers
welcome
oh wait I've think I've been giving they
must have went staff must have been
watching my stream cuz like they gave me
another um memo about using shift
entering slow motion I know but I didn't
really feel like using
it thanks though thank
[Music]
you so nice of them hi
[Laughter]
staff okay what go fast yeah no time for
a slow motion what the hell but you saw
I don't really feel like I needed most
of the time I landed my jumps it's more
like I'm taking my time in between each
jump to like focus on getting the right
height and
Direction you know you
know okay so it feels really awkward to
end my stream early I don't even I'm not
going to read super chats
now but I'm I still feel awkward um I'm
going to go now I will go now uh kfp I
know we suffer the
most it hurts I know but I shall
vanish have fun with the VA for people
who came in late there were a lot of
people in the
beginning and then there was only
English speaking people and then there
was only
[Music]
me it
hurts
thank you good luck with the recording
thank you thanks for hanging out yeah
you're welcome I I had like such a chill
time it felt like
so so realistic
today such a real hangout just
chilling head empty just chilling soon
it will be only silence yeah I'm the
last woman standing and now I will be
not
standing h no bgm you enjoyed it
really I'll be sitting well I was
actually I was the last woman sitting I
guess cuz I've been sitting this whole
time yeah
yeah I like my own bgm sometimes I I
would think so that yeah if you watch
the streamer like every day wouldn't you
want sometimes to play your own bgm or
no no bgm at all why wouldn't you like
it if they don't always choose your
bgm I can
imagine what chill especially bulying
Ren yeah I love
it absolutely love it all right then
and thank you guys for watching support
team white Let's go Team white Let's go
Team white Let's go Team white Let's go
Team
white hey
yeah bye-bye guys see you
[Music]
tomorrow