[Music]
hello
hello oh man
who who am
I where am I
where
is where is where is this really darn
tuden place oh good gosh I don't I don't
know where oh what what who who's
this
ah definitely cannot
see this but I can see this beautiful
beautiful cute
blockheaded
woman I feel like I feel like I may also
hear voices in my head Chad am I
cooking who who who the heck is this
cannot see this name either who is who
is this person that looks like they are
perhaps the final of
fantasies I I I don't
know I don't I don't know who I I am I
don't know who I was and I don't know
what I meant to
do who else is here she looks awfully
awfully aw awfully familiar but I I
can't place
why she's she Square very very
Square they're so cannot see this I
wow very blocky and then there's this
like what is
she Australian I can't I can't tell I
can't
differentiate what the what the heck
what what what is this Square
Room kind of reminds me of a very faint
memory of
nothing who's
this she also looks well I don't I don't
think she is but I if she said anything
like that one
like a lower version of Australia I I
don't I don't know man those shcks
what's
this do do I know how to
read hold up the voice is in my
head Chad am I
cooking I'm that's that's the voice in
my head I like to talk to
myself every now and then I I have this
sort
of guardian angel who tells me not to do
things and and I like to call him
chat chat how do you read this with
languages
this e e n oh crap that's em motion
breaking e
n
enigmatic re
collection but what's oh she's moving
she's who who's this this who's who's
this whoa what is she what is she doing
to me actually what is what is what is
happening what is
happening chat who this who's
this
mysterious green lady
wow oh I thought we're communicating
they like a mating ritual I don't
know who
this she's got
legs she's a
block a block around
town and and this is awfully
red and she looks awfully if I can
remember right
[Music]
BR uh sorry I was I was talking to other
chat other chat being called they're
like they're like the evil version of
chat I think they're called
[Music]
staff oh man I I sure wish I knew what
was going
on apparently apparently only very few
people have this problem that I do and I
ain't talking about the Amnesia I think
it's this broken broken setting in my
mind in the back of my mind
called a privacy setting that refuses to
save for some
reason gosh I wonder I wonder what's
happening man if only I could hear the
voices of this moving statue the fantasy
of finals because they're going to quiz
you on what's about to
happen wow you see that
yeah I don't I don't know who I am I
don't know where I am I don't know
what's going on it's pretty it's pretty
on point honestly Chad am I cooking Chad
tell me what's going on don't tell me
the accident was my fault the last thing
I recall the last thing I recall is
perhaps there was a truck that showed up
that's right I think I I don't know if a
false memory but but I distinctly
remember something
called New York is that
right something happened perhaps a
[Music]
truck oh how how difficultto for all
this to happen right in this mysterious
event so enigmatic oh I can't recollect
anything I can't I can't recollect
anything and I can't I can't see
anything I oh crap I I can't see
anything
uh hold up Chad I'm I'm cooking oh where
am I where where am I what what's going
on oh oh man
man what is this I'm getting
instructions I'm
getting uh blah blah blah blah blah blah
[Music]
blah
okay what is this magic
word wow I fly recall there is like a
recollection of something called a
rehearsal
wow it's Pitch Black in here I can't see
anything I wonder I wonder what be
[Music]
happening wow at least chat be
cooking that's right I don't know oh sh
I don't know what my name
is I but I bet I look freaking pretty
right I I hope so I hope so no you're oh
uh oh no I uh who am I where am I what's
going on it's so Pitch Black in here I
think I think I can't see anything
anymore what what what's happening I'm
so scared maybe if
I maybe if I
H if I do that will I be able
to oh
oh oh
[Music]
uh it's really awful freaking time
H oh okay hello okay it looks like looks
like I guess that's it all right where
am I where where are
we oh you guys can talk
scared what's happening oh my God my
hands what happened to my hands they're
so blocky where's woory already why is
it why is it
so who who am
I everybody's so
cute
ow ow what happened yo voice in my head
how's how's the on your balance why my
head I think I hit my head what happened
I I hit my head too how's the how's the
audio balance voices in my head wow oh
man I wish I knew what you said but I
think I understand theft of it cool
thanks for letting me know voice in my
head you guys are great are you sure I'm
very it was trauma
damage you look
familiar hell are you guys also heroes
from another world Heroes why would I be
a hero did anyone see the lights I
wonder if you can Hur people here did
you see the light I already tried
nothing's
hurting
completely what's going on who are you
why is your belly button exposed
feel you my bones you're decent
you're each did you see a I don't oh oh
crap oh crap
wow
enigmatic so mysterious
wo wow I think I think I'm remembering
something this
this world look kind of familiar oh yeah
this called The
Abyss wow it feels like
home oh I wish I could remember things
for example oh
[Music]
okay
woo oh guess we're
back I trying to
I was turning around I think my brain
just di for a few
[Music]
seconds a
human yes I think so wow
the what about you what are
you I'll be
[Music]
honest yeah why are you short huh
than you anyway sassy child what is
she is something comping about you the
last 24 hours as well I think it's I
don't remember are we beginning I think
I don't know but we can do whatever you
want baby I can't stay as a blank
forever yeah talking I'm not talking to
are those real people all right that was
the quickest enemy
H what's what's your name actually this
is just the inside of
[Music]
my oh you know your name I don't even
know what my name is yeah random
[Music]
people oh okay what if they like Li
I don't
think yeah but what if they did you
don't know anyone like what if I lied
about being your lover what if I just
want your money you
know
you no no I would never lie to you
beautiful I don't trust you no you trust
me look at
me I
look exactly I don't trust you no no you
can trust or maybe I can't trust you you
Twinkle
Toes you can twink
I called you tickle toes
rity no it's okay we'll make up I'll
make it up to
you I will bite you you'll bite me
you'll bite me that's a little that's
I'll fite you that's a lot for a first
meeting isn't
it oh what's up who are you who are you
yeah who are
you I'm told my name is trying to get
you people told you your name have I
seen you somewhere before I don't know
you familiar you kind of Give Me Your
Money a fatherly VI how would you get
that
impression supposed to be a cute girl
right you could be well you could be
whatever you
want mother fig
I I don't know why but I'm still been
and
enhanced maybe the walls will slowly
start closing in on us to make a very
fast decision everyone's just
socializing
huh know who I
amander remember you
[Music]
slightly I feel that your name is Gander
your belly button looks awfully
familiar sett okay I'll try thank you I
I thank you too for this I feel like I'm
interrupting something like very
intimate right now actually who are
you is that what your name
is last name again oh I don't know what
I am the last thing I remember was like
maybe a big
[Music]
truck oh echo of Forgotten
memories Who I Am the world I lived
in and more than
anything the people I hold most dear
face with Oblivion I
feel
empty press sneaky
relieved press
sneaky
perhaps
distraught press sneak
key I do not know
so much I don't know and yet press
sneaky and so much I don't know and yet
that bright light he calls to me so much
I don't know so much I don't
know hey I'm walking here hello let's go
towards the light let's go what if I
fall in the wait which which light
actually there's a lot of
lights just jump off
baby
I yeah don't fall there's a it's called
oh wait it looks so cool well you can
technically
fall oh this looks
dangerous I can't do this this place
must be like if oh oh oh I guess I can't
go there lady oh thank you thank you
madam go to the
light
light I'm at the
light are we got to sh up do we sh up
like I feel very powerful with this
light they have them I I don't like
that me the Ali take me take
me wake me up this what it feels to be
dad so many voices we go go up can we
can we go go up should we go towards the
light I I don't think anything oh what's
that that looks like an egg this
is what is
that it's like a broken egg what
is but what came first the chicken or
the egg don't turn around it's not a
which one's around this way this way
which w
instructions un clear privacy settings
also not
[Music]
availablee bright it's so bright and not
very
warm oh is this like a
hospital liil Castle
oh oh you there what are you doing press
n key you have the look of Outsiders
about you press n
key exclamation mark could it be quick
send word to his majesty your majesty
better be cute though the heroes have
arrived at the sanctuary multiple
Heroes right
away your majesty better be like
adorable the Royal audience chain
Timber welcome Heroes this is the
kingdom of liestal and I am its king you
look kind of short the guards who
brought you here have informed me that
you remember not but your own names do I
remember my
name hey voic is in my head what's my
name a side effect of travel between
worlds no
doubt what is what is my
name this must all come as a surprise to
you but hearken well it was I who
summoned you here you see an
unprecedented Calamity now threatens our
world it has sewn your Earth with
corruption and driven us from our HS and
it is called the ugly this blighted land
now gives rise to creatures of Shadows
known as
stains the kingdom of Li and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us
livance but should the cam be left
unchecked just only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire
world oh getting kind of kind of short
faced with a prospect I scoured the
ancient text for a way to combat the
Calamity and therein I found one the
ritual of hero summoning you who hails
from another world have been summoned
here by me to become the saviors of
lival uhhuh only you have the power to
save our world and so I ask Will you
what what I thought it was a leprechaun
your
majesty what is it a great host of
stains has broken through a defensive
line no we are rushing to mount a
defense but the situation is dire your
majesty I must get you somewhere
safe yeah what's up who are The
Strangers what's say you Heroes will you
accept this
Destiny to save this world will you use
this great power within you to save us
the power of sneaking let's
go oh shoot my power is a wooden sword
and 10 pieces of
bread oh what's up
Heroes hello hello beautiful maidens it
is so good to see you I would you like a
piece of bread may have oh thank you
I'll take all your bread I I like cars
what oh would you like some bread too
you give me bread I don't I don't feel
like I'm gain bread I I'm attempting to
are you hand me you lie to
me I'm sure I'm sure you g me tons of
bread I appreciate it bre
Fair Alik you must be
FR my name I think based on the voices
in my head who I call Chad I believe I
am Shori of the
Nolla of the N
I am Jonathan
g g g g
g that sounds pretty GG and great with a
G That's
mighty he
think are
ween with the way oh thank you I am also
taken with your short and not as
impressive baguette every together we
can be very good
friends I don't
Bel who are these
people facial
hair uh facial hair kind of cute that
facial hair is that just a helmet I
can't tell
you they won't even talk to me who are
you
I can't I can't rip out their facial
hair
want let give away
bread whatever this place is I think
they hate donations I'm going follow you
everywhere
now more like according to the voices in
my head I believe you're called I am
going to
this guy supposed to be talking
actually man sure
wish what this purple lady I I cannot
understand the language of this world
you're sove
[Music]
the
kingdom is
my I assume that's what they said you're
talking to yourself I cannot tell I
believe everyone's crazy so I'm just
going
to oh peace and quiet and indestructible
grass you're my
enemy are you sure hey do you know the
language of this world if anyone's
talking outside the heroes I canot
understand get him to change his the you
who has the power of privacy
please tell me if these NPCs are
talking uh uh I don't think they are oh
good good to know I thought I was going
deaf I think they're just staring at us
yeah okay they disgust me with their
facial hair oh but hey voices in my head
if you got facial hair I bet you look
good like I said I was oh you have
voices in your head too oh yeah yeah do
you yeah I have voes in my head to they
keep commenting about me being stupid
sticky keys oh no I'm sure your sticky
keys are like stickily
wonderful I don't keys on I I would
stick with you anytime you know oh wow
thank you wait oh they're talking they
are no I see
nothing guess I'm explain to you our
kingdom faces
[Music]
un I I assume they're talking I adopted
her she's a cat tell me tell me with
your great power of the ability to know
all what are they saying understand what
what are they saying I do not have the
great power of privacy statement
unfortunately too late to save this
world but I I bet they're having like a
really great conversation right now
speaking another language oh man Dy to
defend our King it's your duty I sure
wish I knew what they were saying but I
don't know this world's language
defeat the stains I'll defeat you all
right is that a
St get laundry fight for the
king oh
that's you with my stain wood take them
down I take on the bus I think that's a
stain King actually that did
not no way it's impossible
actually I need that's why doesn't he
why doesn't I don't think my magical
wooden sword of is working I believe I
better
perh someone
died this one this one uhoh okay think
this is going to destroy us
all oh no my serious short girl is gone
wait he's going to kill the king he's
going for the king well the king
probably sucks anyway we good take many
hits from so many of
us we do not have the proper
equipment oh crap King why don't you run
away like a normal person not taking any
oh crap they just see some Super Mag
beam oh what
why why do I not hear oh there there you
go oh no the M there's no
way be a solution to this everyone is
dying this is e time I I need
GF there you
go I don't have enough bread for
this this kingdom is poorly equipped
with materials
oh why like poor guys are helping
us
oh I feel like there's something we're
missing
though St oh uhoh uhoh it's big dumpies
doing
something it's it's staying the ground
with a big gigantic stainy butt
oh also if people are yelling I think
they're dead
now H
uh oh that's another Mega
beam oh oh the dream
ascending Hold Your Weapon shout
Revelation oh okay oh
okay oh okay what time time to get
revealed let's go
ra
vation wo
re revealed wow I think it's solely
unveiling I'm
[Music]
regaining I'm I'm regaining some
memories in the meantime it sure would
be nice if this memory of mine fixes its
setting so I could see text in my
eyes wow
[Music]
at least I have the voices in my head
woo
[Music]
Revelation I feel like I have just a
little smidge of a
memory I think I tried to to watch
something on this device known as the T
[Music]
all right we got the tally in five some
some amount of minutes it's a very long
Revelation you see it's a it's a very
long
Revelation so um and the snippet of
memory that I have I believe that I try
to watch
something that I probably should not
mention for we are in in this wonderful
wonderful world where nothing should be
mentioned but I believe it's star a
ninja but he wasn't really a ninja he he
was some random blonde dude and the
first five to 10 minutes of this memory
is he has a wife and a child and there's
like it starts playing as an AMV for
some reason despite him talking in this
mysterious language known as nongo AKA
Japanese
they he start he pulls out a guitar and
starts singing in complete English and
then the AMV of his happy sugar life
place where he has a good time that is
like you know shopping with his wife and
he has his random kid and all is well
all as well but then on the news there's
something mentioned like
uh uh something mentioned that there's
random comporting occurring in the world
not sure why don't know why but this
dude and his family live in the middle
of nowhere probably this uh unknown land
called Kansas for all I know
so he he's just having a good time to
his AMV and then one night one night he
has a feeling he has a
feeling and he walks outside the living
room and he sees red light and then
silhouettes of
robots I I don't know this part was a
confusing bit in my memory my Memoria of
one movie ninja but replace the W with
maybe like a k or something at least I
think that's the the memories name so so
they show up for some reason this random
blonde dude has really good fighting
skills makes me wonder what his past was
in the same waya I wonder what my past
is huh
oh is it is it back yet uh and then oh
unfortunately
unfortunately this see see this was
already spoiled in this trailer that
I've long forgotten but I've just
remember just now it already spoiled
that like oh this is a a man out for
Revenge because they destroyed his
family they destroyed his wife and his
child so already going in you you don't
have that element of surprise like you
kind of knew what was going to happen
which is unfortunate I really think that
they should not have done that they
should not have told you that his his
Familia perishes because if you're going
to have this really cool AMV to some
this thing called American
Music he should have the the the
surprise you know the
surprise yeah but yeah I I did not get
to finish that memory because I'm pretty
sure I I got hit by a truck while
thinking of that so that is something I
just remember just
now did they kind of have an
AMV me thanks
[Music]
anyway wow I sure I sure wish there was
something in this Darkness maybe if I
conjure up a memory really hard I'll
remember something right chat we're
going to go cook let's see let's see
what hm
I believe if I think really hard I might
remember oh crap that's for later uh we
might remember
something but you know I just can't
remember anything I can't remember who I
am something about shry of the
nelas let's see let's
see let me let me think about all the
things that I can possibly think of I
can't even
remember what I am
am I even goth what if it's just a
lie oh I do remember
something that's right I'm sorry to
remember this very faint faint thing
that
happened I believe it was in a section
called a game platform that's right I
believe it runs on this ancient
technology
called maybe cream replace the C and the
r with s and t because this is a very
very specific thing that's right it was
powered by the Magic Magical wonders of
cream that's oh yeah I I'd be cooking
I'm I'm definitely cooking all right so
from what I remember oh let's let's do
let's do
this oh why am I so small oh oh actually
it's not the size that matters it's the
heart oh
crap maybe maybe not in this section
okay yeah it's definitely the heart uh
from what I
remember there's apparently there's
apparently a a trophy holder for a
person who owns the most I guess games
games and achievements and their
accounts worth the most on this unknown
memory website game platform called
cream but replace the CNR with
st so I believe there account is worth
$500,000 and they have a lot of games
and possibly achievements to sell for
that I actually I have this thing in my
head called a tangent list if I remember
correctly if only I remembered anything
right only remembered oh yeah uh gamer
spent over 500,000 to gain the highest
account level on this mysterious website
wow but but I feel as if someone that's
a lot actually what games do you have
like 10 million versions
of inoar or
something wow also is that is that even
your is that is that your money or maybe
it's like mommy's Mommy's little credit
card I don't know I'm not sure if only I
could if only chat talk to me right
right oh there's also this uh okay this
is like a completely false memory you
know before a freaking truck took away
my memories uh there's apparently a
vending machine that freezes your drinks
into an instant slushy I I don't think
it's real I don't think it's real it's
probably like as real as me there's
supposed to be a video that that shows
the evidence that it does indeed turn
into slushy but I don't think it's that
efficient I think it's a very random on
whether it works or not I don't I don't
think it'd be working well
[Music]
it exist well I can't I can't tell I
don't think I've ever seen this curious
machine and gadget called a a vending
machine let's
see oh right and then in this snippet of
my memory cave oh hold up I believe uh
oh
okay wow let's let's go back into
[Music]
my oh okay it's this one
okay wow that was what a what a loop I
was in for Wow amazing amazing cool cool
yo oh
crap
vomos wow where oh crap where oh hey
this place looks cool it's SP than that
crap H cool oh no this place looks like
crap take me
back take me back to that wonderful
place the place this place does not look
as cool
go this place has people in
it find the most corner so I can stay
there I find it absolutely adorable that
the voices are too loud I already have
like a ton of voices in my
head I believe they keep calling me
Shori Shori of the Nolla or maybe it's
Shori Nolla or Noel the Shori I don't
know I keep my eyes on the yellow one
yellow one oh you wear the belly button
girl Bell button girl yeah I see your
belly button you yeah I guess belly
button
girl you're M well I think I think my
name is
[Music]
sh sh is that what my name
is the last thing I remember is that I
got hit by a truck you got hit by a
truck I believe so maybe I was the cat
trying to cross the street
fuzzy I they are pretty
fuzzy yeah I'm glad that it looks like
you have all your limbs oh that's good
it looks like you almost have all of
your clothes I think your shirt might be
a little short though I just lost my
memory I didn't lose my clothes well I I
feel like you need to go to the shopping
mall yeah maybe I don't know if there
are malls in this world whatever this
world is but but we can go shopping for
clothes oh guess we're going
shopping what a weird girl can't believe
oh oh echo of Forgotten
memories for the second time Who I Am
the world I live
in and and more than
anything the people I hold most
[Music]
dear wow face with Oblivion I feel and
see
[Music]
relieved perhaps the Str press sneaky
press
sneaky multiple sneakies i f that felt a
lot
shorter wow I feel like I've been here
before but I can't remember
why Wow I sure would love going going
towards the light I made it oh for the
light again oh I feel like I jumped of
you guys before I feel like funny huh Vu
yeah feel like I've been in this thing
before cow a cow wow it remind me of
something small and rock hard does that
mean am I
hard do I make you hard
baby bro what what who are you fantasy
of the finals Who Who Are You yeah who
are you voes in my head told me to call
you be
I
I to disting it but it's disting
I'm yeah I don't know what AO is have no
idea where they got that from AO I'm
I've never heard they tell you to call
me anything yeah who are
you
don't are you sure I don't see a ring on
it I see a ring I see a
block yeah me too maybe you find to
happening over there well I don't know
it's a first meeting I'm not ready I
don't know who she
is I don't know who she is I bet she'll
kiss anyone I'm looking for some I'm
looking for some food do you have
any that might
be because I find you very I have food
later I'll oh green lady is running away
from me I think she's scared I'll follow
her my name is Jonathan G
she's still she's still ignoring me she
hates me she hates me no wait let me
turn you
up you would you turn me you want to
turn me down that's what it is rejection
rejection at first
sight I don't know to be fair I also
cannot hear that many people there's way
too many
voices my
ears am thank you green green woman what
is your name beautiful
F because you're so
fun exactly wow I'm I'm sure hold up let
me take you here FAA it's a little loud
over there I need some privacy hello
some
[Laughter]
privacy wow nosy one
huh oh boy I feel like I've never been
here before
wow liil Castle what are you doing here
you have the look of an outsider stupid
Outsider we hate Outsiders I don't feel
like they were this mean back in the
memory I had oh you're good to go the
Heroes Have Arrived stupid looking
Outsider can't believe your Heroes tell
the king I bet that King's an ugly ugly
creature bald not that there's anything
wrong with bald people but I'm just
saying he been stressing
wow side effect of travel between worlds
press sneaky wonderful ooh W ooh BL
there's this thing called doing the
laundry if they did the laundry maybe
they wouldn't have so many
stains
woo we have the power to save the world
so I ask Skipper
Skipper oh who is this
dude wasn't your name in my memory
called veredes
apparently you're unimportant enough to
remember
actually oh okay very long movement
right there skiper
skiper wow
there
um I think I think maybe I skip too much
no no no just really really long drawn
out talk yeah okay cool no Skipper
Skipper oh
someone maybe one of us yeah just
someone oh yeah let yeah this place
looks familiar
I you
do actually amongst one of us away
actually what if I not conform with
what's expected of
me yeah actually why do I have to save
the world I don't have any
memories yeah I'm I'm going to go be on
my own maybe pick up some
flowers
yeah let's let's go see what's around oh
oh wow despite my urge to wander free
like a a wonderful cute cat I think I
have this thing called obligation and
Duty because I feel my will it is being
sapped out of me by this entity called
invisible
wall are you also trying to escape
fantasy of the
finals there is nothing out
there oh I I've been here all
along I I'm leaving leave Estel I'm not
meant to be a hero you see oh I've
already tried trust me I've tried this
is the far as we can go oh my God I'm
pretty sure I'm pretty sure we're in
prison or's something there's they just
took our will from us that's not fair I
know they give us bread and a sword and
expect us to fight no wonder they're
dying from the
stains what about this way
huh oh of course so close yet so far
obligation and Duty why did you do this
to me come now I don't know who I was
before but I'm pretty sure she also ID G
AF
[Music]
wow Li is still kind of looking empty
honestly I think so too you think so I
think so too
rubius Captain
Celesta I'm I'm go wander over here
actually what is that what is that me
correctly call me Shakira just call me
don't lie eation all what is this feel
like everyone's kind of
like of crazy actually they're just
talking amongst themselves I'm pretty
sure maybe they're just like you and me
chat H you're
cute WS how about this way what if I go
this way oh it's probably the the same
obligation preventing me from
[Music]
leaving that sounds like we need your
help
hero the dialog
well I sure wish I knew what he
said please save my
family no's
translating help us I mean I don't know
who I am you are
my who are you mother you look awfully
out of water to be honest the daughter
you're not the first person to say that
do you have any idea
why why because they're unoriginal and
stole my joke it was my
first please listen please
listen I think you hit your head pretty
hard Oh no I got run over by TR that's
the last thing I
remember you get run over by like a boat
or anything oh there
stains
will oh I wonder why let's
goping I'm going to do this Wonder thing
called watch the
show I feel like I feel like nothing
happened in the dream I had so I'm just
going to watch the show you got bread
Gamers let's go who do you think's going
to win my money is on that stain King
whatever that stain's made out of it is
one stubborn stain let's
see oh oh someone just laser beamed
something I'm pretty sure that was him
actually oh looks like Australia's
joined here what's up
[Music]
Australia Australia that thing's doing
things that has
a that has
a oh
fantastic some oh laser I beam oh it
missed doesn't have that long of a
laser it's kind of like a nice picnic
actually it's like a circus show
honestly it's pretty neat it's pretty
neat that stain is not getting removed
oh hey what's up what's up who are you
again are you also are you also being uh
um back up in case they fall no I'm just
I'm just watching I I don't care about
this Kingdom you need you need you need
like a like at least an excuse you know
in case they ask you oh oh no I'm having
uh I'm having cramps oh no I can't move
we are we are back up in case you fail
so we can be like the second we like the
the the r on the B I am feeling me
you're
procrastinating I'm not a procrastinator
never my life I cannot remember ever are
dying on the battlefield well maybe they
should get good three people have died
while we've been Dilly daddy think that
sounds like a skill issue how is that
our problem May
better how's that our problem stop
freaking dying oh Revelation let's go
left click re oh this one get get re
revealed let's go
I just tickled them to death tickle
tickle the stained host has
been routed that
routed
[Music]
woo yeah awkward awkward eye contact
let's
go wow I feel like they judged me for
not helping I helped the first time in
my dream okay it's not my fault I jump
of this scenario again let's go yeah
that's right I didn't help what are you
going to do about it kick me out I'm
apparently a hero I think you need me
I'm pretty sure they need
me wow I I think they're supposed to say
something but maybe I just I don't
understand her language I don't
understand the language of privacy
settings despite having changed my
language of privacy
settings well so you guys uh you guys
come here
often what's the dude's to the left you
have like an onion on your
Shield who's that second are you are you
a girl or dude you don't have facial
hair I mean you could also be like a
pretty boy for all I know I don't
know wow third person what are you like
a thief maybe you're like a what what's
a person an oil baren or maybe you're
just a wnab be fourth person what are
you supposed to be
huh facial hair
I got nothing for you
oh oh I love pressing this oh cool
finally
wow longest longest eye contact of my
life Wow Royal audence chamber let me
say a quick thank you to hear to the the
voices of my head first I heard the news
though we called upon you suddenly you
roasted yeah heck yeah I did I Rose all
right you have my deepest gratitude
what interests me most however is the
strange power you manifested during the
battle the power of procrastination
which we were able to defeat the
stains that power May well be the key to
saving our world from
Annihilation woo let's
go you know what else will save you
sneaking wa where's the king
actually yeah I you know the King was
actually the Throne all along
so am I supposed to move
now oh here here Heroes I ask of you
once more will you lend us your strength
yeah I guess I
will oh on behalf of all libon I thank
you let's
go man this is such a beautiful King I
would I would sit on it I would
definitely sit on
this oh what what's going on
uh okay
okay things things
happen beautiful things
happen maybe if I oh okay cool where
where am I did it put me in the
dungeon I'm going to keep pressing this
button in my
mind I can't
move maybe something's supposed to
[Music]
appear wow is this I have a f oh oh I'm
moving I'm finally moving I went I went
out the door for some reason I don't
know why I don't even know where I am
the room of Truth stop on the platform
and receive the will of the
ancestor sure random person in my head
why
not what's my
will I think something just broke Begins
the Journey to Find Who I Am press sneak
key okay
oh crap it's the cramps I'm part of the
the Scarlet Ward D the
[Music]
cloak yeah
wo wow well what I think I just I think
I
just wow I feel so beautiful wow
I feel great I feel
like I feel like I
have the optional
accessories I still can't press that
darn wow look at me I must now seek to
defend the soul of Jade whoever that is
I have the bookmark of
memories because I am the enigmatic
recollect woo
got an axe got a Ste summoning Egg and I
have I have Scarlet people here you're
here too
yeah what's up for someone who looks
blue why are you in Red Master I I don't
know honestly oh what's there's a radio
you think we can jam the
tunes maybe oh what's what's this maybe
like a takeout box green after all oh
hey what's up beautiful lady hey hello
oh what do you have you got like an
apple I have an apple golden apple is
that wor on you got this giant weapon
and I just got
a and you feather I have a feather I'm
going to tickle you guys tickle tickle
wa dangerous of all I know no one ever
suspect I think I just used it oh crap I
just used it
sry well that's going to take a while to
recharge tell me what
click on him how yeah right right click
on him yeah we don't understand the
language without the power of privacy
settings oh ah good morrow welcome to
the humble Guild Hall of the Scarlet
wand I Am The Guild Master
[Music]
rubius um I think that's all he has to
say oh no he more thank you for joining
the battle to save Leal so soon after
your summoning at that you will
henceforth be working with us to mount
resistance against the stain and save
this world oh what's up oh my go are you
also Scarlet one people you also got a
fork I got a feather feather cool
feather man I know I like your Trident
that's sick thank you I like
your I like your wooden yeah it's not as
great as it no I have something cool too
I have this this cool thing what do your
thing do oh cool this is this is
like welcome you have a
what oh hey what's what do you
have I have a cloak I have um red a
cloak you have a what got a cloak a
cloak I've got one more thing hold on
guys oh you got a giant like uh
Christmas looking or you guys I got a
feather I'm going to tickle everyone's
death no
oh that was this better goes in your
nose and you're not going to like it
this guy right here Rubi is
rubious ignore
him all I'm it's night time I want I
want to
rest longest boss battle of my
life Scarlet keeper I I wish I could
talk to you but I don't know you're oh
oh he talks what so cleaning up the mess
after a stain attack stop by some other
time dropping off now
actually I keep reading what's over here
maybe like a hotel Li
lion it's kind of cute this table's too
short for you
[Music]
guys oh I guess there's something
here I should probably stick around up
there
okay uh
[Music]
hey is there like a hotel here it's
night time and I like some rest um I
think oh wait are you two able to join a
party I I I kind of doubt it let's try
it can you attempt to invite us to your
party yeah can it be I need to look at
the are we not cool enough to join your
party okay you may forming parties right
click on who you want to invite
and then just press the blue one okay
I'm going to invite you I can't press
anything
actually okay well we can always be un
partied yeah I guess I guess I could
solo let me let me solo it you
know yeah how do you kind of sad but how
do I accept the party T
accept I I can't press accept accept uh
let me see uh oh wait you you click oh
hey I'm in the party where I'm in the
party wait wait wait wait I'm to I I
didn't I I didn't do anything I just
pressed random buttons please please
invite me again wait is it is it the max
limit five I feel good about this Guild
something about
it is it is it the max
five does anyone know where the social
menu is why is people in the
party because she's been we B and I were
in the party from the beginning but how
do I
it says click um on the right it says
when the person if you click on the
person you formed a party with again of
the oh I have to find in order to kick
[Laughter]
her ride my horse I feel an attachment
to you perhaps I shall name you oh oh is
my is my horse tired do you guys want
to you like my horse yeah where's the
quest
board how do I unsummon horse I don't
know we have a map oh shoot is it this
way I I do not know how to un horse oh
oh horse has gone away okay to the quest
board it's speak to the quest m i see
where is the quest board this looks so
cute maybe it's inside oh wait wait
what's this question mark
[Music]
the question mark this this thing I
think it's supposed to be a question
mark because it looks questionable the
quest oh wait
no oh I I probably should you speak to
him uh right click how did you speak to
the right click oh okay yeah yeah I
think you have to just Spam it they're
forbidden from entering a San
[Music]
go into
town our new leader oh okay I think town
[Music]
is oh well it's
daytime it's daytime I I don't know what
happened I looked away I blanked out
there
why why did everyone disappear
actually was everything just in my
head am I am I
crazy or am I Shori of the
nelas hello
anyone where did where did everyone
[Music]
go hello
oh man intrusive thoughts oh Fountain
I'm going to go
there my horse can
help go oh you're different you're
different you're not my horse guess I'll
ride you anyway though ooh Fountain ooh
ooh kind of
nice I how it there you go
Yoo wow this place is really
pretty I I may have lost everyone but I
have gained this new power of
Adventure
Majestic all the
space beautiful beautiful grass
what this at this oh hey what's up
everyone SW is way bigger than mine
hello hey I don't think I was supposed
to be
here honestly I don't I don't think I
was supposed to find you guys
oops wow I I guess I just saw raided
into the wrong
[Music]
area what's here Horse
Center oh oh oh crap enter probably a
little too fast oh it it turned me away
it rejected me just like a mother
duckling or something
is this a quest board like a quest
board sure what team is we're not so
different after
all hey are you what team are you guys
perhaps we
are oh hello there we are part of the
amorn must go back to our and speak to
the I don't know I just sa ride one
yeah wait where do you check the where
do you took the I didn't steal it it
just wait don't burn my horse my horse
never did anything to
you creature no no horse this
isure it's a wonderful Pure Heart of
stallion hey what's up girls complete
the where is
the that wonderful cute girl named Boo
Boo is still part of our
party and it's quite unfortunate for the
fantasy final
girl perhaps you should have studied for
your finals a lot
better up blond
woman you touching my horse I guess you
can I would let you ride my horse too
but I think it can only
[Music]
sit how do I get off horse
actually oh there you go horse is gone
[Music]
I press right click I'm hoping it works
no we have to complete the quest find
the the sney I I still don't know what
that I just think I just killed
everyone's memor can go to
the what's this one of
one okay I can't write
on thees
the we going on a quest do
us I shall join you of course as we
areil join
us for tell me that I have no purpose
[Music]
materals it's the only one available on
the board materials needed at the Smithy
I'm The Apprentice at the Smithy and my
master says we're running low on raw
materials if you can help us please stop
by this inv you to the I'm too sure to
reach
anything everyone what she click on I
think is there a way we can fix our
group chat because it would be a lot
less chaotic if we the
only I think it's party call right I
don't I think apart from just turning
everyone else down probably
not is it a is it a radio and then party
call or is that something can you oh
there she is okay okay okay okay okay
okay stand still do not move I shall
free you oh you're the quest
Master oh no he's actually useless okay
try talking to the Guild Master where's
the Guild
Master and
now pretty pretty green lady where's the
Guild
[Music]
master master yeah I never talked to the
Guild Master I wandered off like a Lost
Child I spent time with my horse please
show me the guil
master thank you you're so
wonderful accept the inv I I have to
talk to the Guild Master I skipped them
I shall be back away we
go I don't know but we can figure that
out together I'm pretty sure it's to the
left I think it's this way this way oh
crap she's going the wrong way I got I
think it I I think it's this
way
yeah pass this bridge the red
area I don't know it must who looks like
a Guild Master they all look short and
bald follow the red
banner oh my horse be
lagging I follow you my wonderful
Majestic green lady
[Music]
my wonderful Majestic Oreo oh I thank
you I'm edible
too
o yeah you can you can dunk me in milk
or you can split me apart you can do
whatever you
want is this the Guild Master the moon
as a
demonstration wait I I think I think
we're
nearby okay so where's where's Guild
Master um
[Music]
rubius this guy rubius no wonder I
didn't talk to
him oh crap I keep riding my
horse please talk to
me he he refuses so talk to me actually
no I think I have the same issue as the
final fantasy looking girl had oh no
yeah I think she specifically hates
gothom
he should hate me too then he just must
not be able to see inside yeah but
you're pretty you're pretty he believes
in the goodness of your heart oh wait
wait thank you oh
shs it's
okay maybe he just hates pretty
girls
m but you're you're beautiful you you
look at you you look so like homely with
your piece of bread and your
Apple yeah H good H good it's like the
opposite of a home you know hopefully
it's good like like a
hobbit Hobbits are good too they they do
things I don't know what they do they
probably party and get drunk all day we
must know what they do I I already
forgot most of their names like there's
like what Frodo there's like uh his best
friend don't tell me his name it's not
Peter Sam Sam has his
name I already forgot the blonde dude
the cute elf boy don't tell me his name
I don't know his name lus legis I was I
was close
lattos I I was pretty close it started
with an L manage to
join oh that's good too bad like I don't
know what the quest
is um oh okay you could you could follow
along with us okay I'll just we we can
explain to you and hopefully they will
fix it for you
I will relay my thoughts to this voice
in my head called push shift a bunch
does it work oh oh yeah yeah you're so
you're such a genius you're beautiful
I'm so in love with you right
now hold on let me let me relay
this okay I have relayed it to this uh
entity in my head head called staff I
must do it again good I I I did see
completed and now I can never see that
that word again all right let's go my
pretty lady go back wait which way was
it it's this way it's this
way uh this way the other other way this
this way
yeah no no no no this way this way
pretty lady I mean same thing same thing
same thing it's okay oh I'll just follow
you I'll just follow you I'll follow you
to the ends of the world okay I think
it's this way yeah I think they Le to
the same place it's probably a
circle the most unimaginative shape
ever
don't I'm I'm still here don't
worry I'm not going to do like an orus
on
you orus and
pranie oh where is everyone did they
die maybe it's just us left on this
Earth I bet they you're having SL party
on this guy and also spam shift
okay oh crap I keep riding my
horse uh sneak key this is a quest board
I understand your main duty you must be
tired hello I died once maybe I think I
think I I did the quest dangerous out
there um well you shouldn't try to like
get stuck in high places let me just say
that oh I see I see do you think this
has Wi-Fi how do you accept the quest
properly to him and then click on this
and click on the thing oh click to order
thank you so much you have my gratitude
Forever Green lady and black and white
oreo lady thank you so
much thank you beautiful orange woman
anytime anytime I shall honor my my
promises oh okay not now what okay do
you have the side quest yeah something
about a Smithy yeah we can go to the
blacksmith oh okay oh you're so
wonderful you're showing me around I'm
not used to Fantasy settings I'm pretty
sure whatever I came from it was like a
really hot place with a lot of topics
Grim dark setting oh I see yeah there
something like Halloween world for all I
know that sounds nice yeah lot of C Andy
a lot of work for the
dentist yeah are there a lot of dentists
in your world um there might but might
be only one I I don't remember I don't
think your licens either yeah it might
be me that's a scary idea too oh it's
you it might be me yeah to know we have
a dentist in our party oh I'm not good
though I'm not a good dentist well
better than me oh wait is it here did I
go too far oh uh I don't know they all
look the same honestly oh someone
died oh hey it's boo boo oh hey what
it's you boo boo what' you call me what'
you say I called you Boo
Honey yeah hey what what wait what
weapon do you have you have like rock
candy wow delicious you have I have a
feather I can tickle you show me your
Revelation okay it takes a while though
oh you gave her a 10
so cool instant TP oh nice I cast
instant TP I think my fe's failing to
tickle people right now I can't tickle
you dead forever oh oh how did I how did
I do that oh oh crap I think I just went
off I
can't oh I could trade with you and I
can invite you to
parties no not don't invite her again
we've been through
okay sorry you're not fun at
parties oh
no I'm a my people need me okay have
fun what a what a nice boo boo girl we
got lost we're at the black wait this
looks like an anvil place oh yes now
that we together we can hang up the
phone
call goodbye my fellow I buy again they
need materials actually they need
material wait do we bring the materials
I don't know what materials they need we
talk to The
Apprentice oh they gave us money to my
master 10 Oak LS make you stone tools
okay okay thank you I don't know you're
still on the phone with me okay I don't
know I didn't know how you called
me what am I supposed to make I don't I
I I guess
you all right are you ready to cut down
trees it says M needed
H let's just dou a
check what if I 10 oak logs right oak
logs oh maybe we just find like a random
tree hey we have a lot of trees here you
have a lot of trees here
fa want to make
ay you're right you're right they they
don't want to do things the normal
practical way accept the party though
outside town oh we are yeah I I think we
have to be farther
out is this in what about this this tree
this tree is certainly still in town
right okay I guess we got to wand out
where's the
exit there's a maybe that giant gate
yeah it's a awfully big gate for tiny
people do you think it has a tiny door
inside it I really like
have a have a tiny door yeah here
otherwise you're going to have to go
like climb up the walls or something
yeah you know what's weird this place is
so big but like there's not a lot of Li
lion what do they call it again well
maybe they all got murdered by the
stains right oh Sho that's what happens
when you don't do laundry your stains
kill
you I wouldn't know couldn't be me oh
yeah I trust you I trust you tree lady
what's this oh another location I guess
so oh why
[Music]
not oh heck there's stains here oh just
here for a tree we chop down these trees
they seem yeah I think
so they you think I can chop this down I
want to steal like a land oh
cow I'll let you live oh I let you have
that Chi I'll take this one oh it works
hey oh are you okay down down the states
are after your
laundry oh man these are really harsh
stains I need a better
detergent eat my detergent
sword actually you're not really doing a
lot of damage I could probably just
finish this
yes yeah go away it's not a lot of
damage there you
go oh hey trees grow back wow what a
very good
world I think they're hurting me I I
can't tell hey what is what does this do
does this work yet can I have your
memories I hope it worked I have no idea
col hey I got
coins that's
nice cool
okay are you okay ow is that you no no
no it's this this thing is this guy yeah
they give you money oh that's like a
bull here you go get your wood I'll kill
things sounds okay I I'll take
them I mean I can't really hit them
honestly oh crap get away from her she's
chopping down
nature
hello okay oh oh they're still chasing
you down trees
the here how about how about I gather
you wood another I grow at me okay okay
okay
good talk okay good good job hold on can
I give you some logs too oh I have 12
I'm okay found you oh you already have
we found you yeah it's been so
long we were we were on an adventure scy
W finally we've been
reunited yeah and it feels so
good it does here eat my memories at
least I'm hoping it's get tickled get
tickled oh oh 20 coins there you go are
you getting tickled you are not getting
tickled here feel my
fluff that's right I'm the tickle Master
here your feet get tickled your nose get
tickled I would like to farm I would
like to farm coins right oh that took
forever to die holy holy quack um 128
that's cute bunny I got
171 wo cing up you got some heavy
Pockets oh there's so many
stains I'm just going to collect wood in
case they ask me
again this one has hor you feel familiar
I think you're my sister why am I not
using this 10
of
11 all what do you guys think we
need I have uh like 15 I think 15 that's
like 25% 50% more three get I think
we're good do we each need 10 I think so
I don't know oh my goodness yeah you
only need 10 you only need
10 wa each person though or we all
together uh I was I think we should all
get 10 just in
case oh no sh I have some Spar if you
want mayh have my humble
opinion summoning egg oh we should
probably run I think they're after us
I'm have a horse I may have run the
joyous crew I think there's a lot more
at
night my woohoo can I use
this oh
crap Scarlet one is hurting me I was
wondering ring ring we're good okay wait
does everybody have all their logs yeah
I got my log Castle Gates it's not safe
out here come on I'm GRE have logs yeah
we have logs
okay let's return all
right well that looks cool how how do we
return
actually how does one summon the
[Music]
gate okay thank gosh please please
please say yes 1 we're back
together yay we did it hooray let us go
back to the
blacksmith yes we can have horses if we
use a summoning seed egg that is
true you have a pretty horse pretty BR I
must do it
myself she has toes I do not remember
what a blacksmith
is okay the shop was not very noticeable
where is the shopkeeper give me my money
thank you so much my M over there if you
bring
the Cobblestone next
too many people are speaking to him at
[Music]
wow wooden pickaxe if the Smitty and
speak to
different am I am I using all of our
Cobblestone okay we got to go I not
think so my money has not decreased I a
table this is a table I have your wood
how much money do you have three a
wooden
[Music]
pickaxe make sure
a wooden pickaxe
okay wow I I don't know how to make one
I've never made one before but for some
reason I just have this inherent
knowledge that I can make whatever I
want if I just put in the heart of it
wow what am I my hands are moving on its
own my hands did not
work the pickaxe did not work why did
the pickaxe not work he needs sticks oh
um yeah he need did I did I do it
wrong am I am I
stupid
money hey how do you make a a
pickaxe it is not letting me got to make
the silly items maybe maybe this one
right I'm pretty sure it's the other one
though Timber SMI it oh okay one okay he
gives me a new I've created the wooden
pickaxe I have also from now on when you
find new materials stop here and talk to
my master the more different materials
CRA takes forever to talk to see my
master okay I talk to your master then
speak to the black okay could you bring
us 10 Cobblestone next you can probably
find some lying around all right I
purchased the wooden
pickaxe wow I I sure crafted this wow
great 10
Cobblestone wow yeah I don't feel like a
hero I feel more like
a what's it called like an intern I do
want you pick
your to the child in the gens I
believe I will just I'll speedrun
it this say
maybe or did they have like a different
different mind to go back are you ready
to go back yeah we ready how much how
much do you need
let me oh it's not
opening yeah
uhoh well I guess I'll wing it
oh I don't know how much material they
need oh here it this yeah this is
different
10 oh for what oh once you got it you
can't get it back I feel like I'm I'm
stealing all of the resources for the
team
yes uh you should just steal it I'm
getting
Cobblestone me too I have collected 10
Cobblestone I'm going to get enough for
both of you I already got 10 just wait I
have 10 also yeah I was thinking what if
we take all the Cobblestone so no one
else can do it yeah we should prevent
the other teams from yeah okay let's
just do the outside so they won't know
yeah byebye yeah let's let's Rush Oh is
she on the phone
oh yeah they called me they they need
this one soon you probably need like
Cobble for that I want to touch the co
just in
case hey do I've got I've got 31 so
let's head back oh hi okay you think it
response oh it response darn it thank
you I got hit by a orse how do I throw
them an orse uh yeah I think you have to
trade you have to left and right click
at the same time wait I have to trade
you're done you can't throw things
normally plus n oh my God okay I'm sorry
I can't share with you after all maybe
here I I have some let's see hit trade
oh never mind you're trading with
someone else I'm sorry who are you
trading with I'm stuck in trade with
Nissa hold on oh no wow I see how it is
no one wants to traed me I see right
click right
cck no that doesn't do anything why do
they eat my memories I feel kind of bad
eventually what do you mean I think I
killed me into a
trade are you guys still trading oh
sorry leave maybe it'll
cancel at this point you might as well
just collect Cobblestone I will secure
the last hits for you so you can get all
the golds make sure you get your yeah
you might as well just collect
Cobblestone if you couldn't trade yeah
was I was for a very long
time
unfortunate nothing's clingy
I'm
going I got stained meat I bet that
tastes
like there's this thing I remember
something something
novel whatever it is I bet they taste
like
[Music]
that oh crap I only have bread they've
only given me carbs there's so protein
in this
world except like stained meat I
guess but I prefer my stained
meat my master more different materials
you I talk to you no now it's completed
you bet my master will make you some
cool stuff pick uhhuh completed yeah I
already got the stuff I don't want to
talk to him though arriv right as we
were losing
hope uhhuh okay I wonder what would suit
you better you bring Cobblestone next I
guess I guess that's the end of it
actually you must use your Oak planks
did you buy did you buy
Quest is done that's it to Apprentice
again if you B one you quest speak to
the quest Master okay talk to The
Apprentice again in in the I see that in
the corner of my vision for some reason
oh crap the quest master's like so
far what is my my quest master all the
darn didly to in place
there why weren't you like near the gate
like a normal
person this way
place looks nice oh oh oh uh oh okay wow
Deja Vu I feel
like I feel like I've been here
before Guild
Master oh wait Quest Master who's Quest
Master not the Guild Master there's a
difference oh chat you're slaying me
right now aren't you man sure wish I
knew what the people in my head were
saying
[Music]
at the big board ah I see thank you
thank you voices in my head oh thank you
so much you're bring life to my desolate
little mind my mind which is so empty
I'm very desolate did I tell you that
it's very
desolate at least I have my horse my
horse babysit you babysit me please yay
y are you still on your first Quest yeah
I am I am
how do I already did um C and then you
click on accept speak shop keeper your
cursor talk to the blacksmith again this
shop
keeper am I just like entering someone's
Random
House okay okay good good to
know oh you you have this wonderful
looking place
and I can't even
enter I I you know I don't think this is
a real town I think this is some
convoluted plot to keep me without
memories because I'm too dangerous with
them whoever the king is I don't trust
them I don't trust them this place is
too too
suspicious I feel like it's that if I
recall correctly this one thing called a
a movie about someone whose entire life
was a
lie oh you're a
shopkeeper bid I'm talking to you you
were wrong this isn't where you're
supposed to be wait I'm just okay what
oh hi what's up
three oh I think it's that house three
is that this is a shopkeeper
right yeah I don't think they
count darn I I don't think they count as
a shopkeeper it's a bar I well they're
keeping up with a shop you
know yeah voice in my head oh let me
just talk to the blacksmith again he's a
shopkeeper all right so talk to the pr
right this time good job are you a
shopkeeper oh I can upgrade my weapon
how come I can't UPG should it won't let
me upgrade have you talked to talk to
the blacksmith first all right let's go
to shopkeeper apprentice apprentice
apprentice hello wait you about the cop
what's a good shopkeeper map real okay
wait what
shop shop okay good good to know would
have been nice to see like a giant shop
sign who it
Chef this is the same place I was at are
you a
shopkeeper shopkeeper do you
shopkeep hello speak to me speak to me
good sir speak to me what about you are
you a
shopkeeper you oh wait wait what my
shopkeeper has changed shopkeeper is now
in this
[Music]
location oh you're a shopkeeper hello
Shi hey waa what's
this I'm next to a
shopkeeper oh where did you find the
shopkeeper he's like near some tavern
probably getting drunk there's a Tavern
yeah yeah okay so go for go from this
blacksmith and then just go across okay
it's across the street from the
blacksmith yeah yeah thank you no
problem you're
cute you're
cute thank you
bye-bye oh that was cool is that the
radio can I private call anyone and
theyes oh hey what's up is she okay I
think she's disconnected to the
shopkeeper make sure you got a coin ski
a skipper skipp a skipper skip a skipper
Skipper holy crap that's a lot to skip
dialogue just Quest completed thank gosh
speak to the child in the
gardens why talk to me I'll show you
what I've got in stock I want to I want
to
for maybe we can buy stuff from them and
then we can sell it with an up price you
know I think we should just steal his
stuff and then sell it to them so we get
money yeah yeah and your
heart I like his top Pat should be
mine okay now we got to find a random
child the
guers this way the children are
attending to them why are the children
working at all right you guys ready to
find a lost
child yes okay the child should be
around is Nissa back hold on I think so
ring
her phone callone
[Music]
oh what what stuff does he have clo s
berries oh that's flame hey wait a
minute I recognize these song titles
nonfiction oh okay okay we were about to
head there we're looking for children
Nissa children that have the tent to the
gardens
yeah the children they grave the corn
they yearn for it all right are we ready
for
child finding we're going to meet
narissa in the garden okay uh the garden
should be across there Quest
yeah
Hesed
theity I I went ahead without
them wait this map updates way too
much I don't know I stay with you
guys for garden
um oh they're small people they can only
handle so much oh this is kind of
nice this is not theard are I don't
think this is a Gard this just a this is
It's The Garden of
betrayal I think this is the the the the
oh wait it's marked on our map it's in
the bottom right corner I think it's
like here
maybe if I if I go this
way oh man Maps I I'm more used to
GPS this is good to say let's
go GPS update please satellite where are
you oh this looks this is a
[Music]
garden
yeah looks kind of like a garden
ow child where are you I think I ran the
child over I'm sure they're I'm sure
they're fine it builds character is in
it my keep an eye tiny scare away the
birds and stuff if you don't like
gardening you can also try
building there's an empty lot
just can build whatever you like
arrows you and your guild mates could
work together to make a voice if you
place to stay stop by any time if you
want to do some building or
gardening tell you a secret did you
know trying to communicate with the
child it is so far not working AR I
think he does not understand my ability
to tangent sounds would terrible way to
advertise TOS TR I believe he hates
talking to me he hates golf
girls maybe you could go check it out
and tell me what it's like Anyway is not
working
[Music]
I'm aware that I am talking in my head
that is because I'm trying to talk to
the child it is not
working we oh finally he's finally
talking to me oh thank
gosh goodness talk to the pit door it's
okay FAA read it for you let's
run to the
P the pit door man I'm a stop his pits
and make him regret being a door man
ladyo
platonically this
way hey is he is he in this
Garden I'll go
here pit door man he's across from here
okay lucky lady lucky lady I've got a
game for you oh says your new face don't
tell me you want those Heroes who save
the town aren't you you want to get rich
I know it could make you a fortune wait
don't I promise it ain't nothing Shady
look about how I tell she something
useful see I used to run with the Jade
show for I join the Amber
coin I was just wondering to myself I
wonder if the music in my head is
starting to get
annoying I I think it's pretty
chill just point yourself at your main
right click on I think he will talk to
me after he's done talking to the other
it's cool okay that's good I'm glad that
the music I have provided in my head is
amazing didn't you thank me for that is
good to know uh I know you it is so warm
in my head easier if only it was a
little cooler coins I'm saying give us
give us the money then what's the
point up down how you doing
I don't care ju just stop
talking bro quite simply I don't care
shorten it yeah bro this could have been
sent an email shut up yeah
literally let's him up and take his
wallet okay oh does he have one is that
your power take his bow tie in hit him
hit him excuse me wait we're committing
cries against
another pa pa it's a misunderstanding I
think I still what are you doing
here
tell we have drama I still haven't talk
to P door I am not activating
him and Amber coin it's okay you guys
can go ahead without me I'll just keep
oh wait that's a social
menu there you go
finally I got
it all right who's
Jade right is that where it is that's
very yeah yeah yeah it
is
oh it's that D from the beginning the
one who looked at me
funny oh keep going my gosh wait she's
from that one movie she's from that one
movie where they sing and make dinner
there you
go I assume they are in the
Coliseum perhaps over
hither where my horse cannot
[Music]
o fact we are traveling too fast
Gladiators is this going fight to the
they actually TR blood in the
Coliseum where is this guy though don't
you die if you do that well yeah but you
know they're dying anyway to Coliseum oh
I guess so I guess so yeah it was is for
a jolly good
show you know where going
dud maybe they below is he under the
Coliseum oh cuz they're the like they're
the fighty
ones FY ones they're The Feisty ones
they're feral we don't know about Jake
Jade M I think this is
him oh that's a sword member we need a
Guild Master you don't want to get in
between them oh they all look the same
learned about
adventuring
we
has I have not familiarized myself with
that's a pretty Moon same it's actually
a nice screenshot
find oh oh you calling me not work in my
head in my head I was like what is this
sound
hey you just got a you know oh here
that's a sword member why can't I talk
to you but not him yes in the city near
the
planes right it's horrible
okay he's got the biggest
hat Mumble Mumble what's the mission
after this I still have to talk to him
though um exit the Town Gate head to the
Plaines and speak to a Hostess of the
Jade sword h I I'll keep spamming here
I'll see you guys out whenever you
go
okay who has hardest mission ever trying
to
socialize really is please socialize
with me guil bastter please I begging
you regain your powers of
Revelation I'm not I from one of our SCS
regarding a
possible to the PLS to speak to host go
over here there you go on the Jade sword
oh
he he's still not socializing can you
read an Italian
accent have you skipped everything
again then read wherever what you're
seeing right now okay uh so you oh oh
fin go with Valor I finally talked to
him oh thank gosh I'm here today to
thank the Guild Master bravery he really
hates flirting with
me were you trying to flirt I was just
trying to socialize man I told him like
how you how you doing goodlooking you
know you just stared at me Le a little
little softer next time oh maybe like
how you doing ugly
person that come here off in you bald
looking
guard all right I'm going to follow you
other green
woman
okay the flatter green woman
apparently oh there you go let's go wait
something has this head did a planes why
is it morning
here a while to leave oh I guess
[Music]
so by way are you still talking uh I'm
green where is he I can't hear you for
some reason oh there you are
I'm just following her I don't know
where she's leading she could be leading
me to my death for all I know and I I
shall happily accept
it uh is this is this where I meant to
be he looks like a hus oh crap I'll send
me
back
arrived M please 1 2 3 4 5
strange voice fastest of the great sword
souls of STS open the
way okay we have to kill we have to kill
10 stains I okay that's pretty easy
easiest thing in the
world you're sleeping you're
[Music]
defenseless actually how much damage do
you need
I so
sadly all right I killed I killed one I
killed
two oh look at you so
powerful oh there you
are you were just minding your own
business probably wondering what to eat
for dinner or who's close to stain oh
you're dead now
sorry you are not a stain you are a
banet
hello I mean
what wow this is the slowest fed attack
ever oh
okay that was the slowest tickling ever
okay that's how much have I killed I
wonder if it's
combined cleaning up the stains
hey
Revelation I assume we still need a kill
it doesn't show the thing though what
does this even do when they die in
scares me every time oh it's
lagging it's uh it it it be uh slow in
my
head this one just sounds so sad I know
I don't think I can even hit it anymore
I'm not sure we're the heroes after all
I think we might be the
villains I'm going skip that that's
[Music]
big how about you defensive speak thing
I can hurt you
apparently uh-oh normally counts each
man I have no idea how many I've killed
but definitely not
enough it does I have no active side
quest maybe that's a side quest what
about a main quest wait scarl one never
mind how many how many have I killed
wait for the Center Bar okay I need more
stains
who has dirty
clothes remove it so I can like destroy
it
no
you you must be eliminated you must be
executed
[Music]
okay you get wet get moist P
treat that that would make it an issue
no wellow I think I need one more and
then I
believe I must
uh attend to the
council in my
head for a meeting after so we should we
should try to get this done a mop re I
kill 10 St yet I don't think I killed
investigate the underworld dungeon then
speak to the Jade swword Guild
Master I can't even anything anymore hey
uh bird bird girl because bird girl we
must attend to a meeting in our heads
yes I know so I'm aware I am man you and
I have great minds huh we think alike
well we can just go but I I really want
to keep
playing yeah I know I really want to
enter I I would rather have him fixed my
language I cannot proceed okay thank you
for telling me observation that is
that's good to
know quite a quite a shame that I do not
know the language of the privacy setting
we're done despite having tried to fix
the privacy setting okay the privacy
setting was not enough you guys we can't
wait to play again or I me fight
together again are you leaving my life
we must we must away yes we have
adventur got the fireball
it is me the Phoenix of the fires and
the oranges hello lady of water I will I
will see you I can put out
your try it then mop put out my uh
you're on cool
down beautiful other green
woman good luck my beautiful beautiful
lady Lady of the woods you yes you
wouldn't I must retire
my yes I must have a a meeting with the
council people who call me stupid I will
see you whenever in this wonderful
wonderful world thank you for showing me
around you're gorgeous by the way very
well you're
beautiful get in there back I'm back to
where I was there's a diamond how about
you go get that diamond there you go
this this is where I belong di quiet and
if I think at least I I wish it was
quiet I sa by then because I am oh good
God something's killing
me oh oh oh crap oh crap oh crap where
am I
wow oh wow where where am I actually
okay I don't know where I am but hey
thanks for thank you for being a
wonderful voice in my head wow I hope
that we get to see more adventures in
this world of libus sto where your libus
be stalled and your stalls be lius I
will see you oh U meet and greet and
panel for those who are able to attend
in the upcoming time so uh who is going
to be alive I actually don't know
because considering
things uh let's see who is also in my
world how
about I don't know how long she's going
to play but she's
beautiful all right I'll see you guys
tomorrow in my head of course in my head