[Music]
[Applause]
me
intoxicating DJ keep play
[Music]
danc so emotion
feel it rush through me
[Music]
me
feel it
R feel it me
[Music]
he
oh
honey night is fall
[Music]
feel it R
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
dancing sorry so emotion
feel it R through me
[Music]
me
he
[Music]
Kitty
key chunkers was sitting on my chair and
that is a legitimate reason for me being
[Music]
late right
definitely
is whatever you say
waa she she was taking
Refuge because I was vacuum cleaning and
I was cleaning overall I cleaned the
kitchen I cleaned I'm I've been doing
the
laundry I have to clean more though I
have to clean more because I'm gone for
the next few days and someone's coming
to take care of my
cats
so I need to try make things look decent
keep them
tidy make them
tidy cat hairs indeed
yeah
um okay disclaimer I'm so super stressed
out uh I need to do so many things still
there's many things on my to-do
list and uh
yeah uh
sorry I actually also have to record a
few
vocals um see I I I knew I knew that I
would have this problem that's why so
yesterday or last night they yeah no
this morning I think or last night they
sent um you know some deadlines like hey
uh here's the data please record this
until this Sunday and I'm
like yeah okay so the only day I have is
today
Des because uh
I won't be there so I have to do it
today um but that's okay I actually kind
of knew that this stuff would happen
that with me traveling around so much uh
in the next weeks uh it it will be
difficult I knew this like one month
ahead of time so I was like I wrote to
Gemma I was like Gemma can I like record
some things in advance even if they
haven't asked for it yet and even if
they haven't sent any data yet can I do
it anyway and she was like yeah I guess
so should be fine so I recorded a few
things in advance in the past uh two
weeks or so um but there's still some
things left over chunky wonky
hi so that's one thing I have to do um I
also have to do a bunch of other things
so as as much as I want to stream like
until
midnight I will not be able
to yeah at least you're crapping ahead
I've been trying my best to do that
yeah oh I have a few tangents for you at
least and we we're not so far behind on
super chats as far as I know and the
only real problem is I still haven't
gotten to the Polaroids but uh you guys
probably have forgotten about those have
you just like me um I just really don't
have the time for it I'm so sorry I'm
I'm so sorry ah I'll try to do them next
week next week I maybe I can squeeze
some time I even next week is kind of
yumy but I'll I'll do my best worst case
I'll try I think oh I have photoshop on
my iPad now I should be able to do it on
my iPad when I'm traveling too I
think should should
work I think I even found my iPad pen
that I thought didn't exist I thought I
didn't buy it I thought I didn't have
one now I don't know how where it is
again but I think it
[Music]
exists yeah on the plane signing
autographs like the star yeah see that's
the thing I don't really want to do it
on the plane because I feel like the
seats behind you like diagonally can
kind of
look
uh that reminds me my
[Music]
iPad okay this will be so disgusting
thing to you
guys my iPad cover is still kind of
moldy and I was I bought a replacement
on Amazon and then it arrived and then
it turns out it was too small but for
once for once I
actually um this was this was the first
time because I had like two things that
I wanted to send back because I I didn't
it was wrong so uh I I finally learned
and did it experienced how to send
things back for Amazon normally I would
just accept it and just like I don't
know what I would do with it but
normally I just accept it so this is an
improvement how to get moldy well this
is one of the stories that I think I
talked about on Twitter before where uh
something [\h__\h] drinks recently that
don't have B proper bottle caps they
just spill in my backpack and then yeah
my iPad got affected by it the the cover
mostly and I have this like magnetic
cover thing that covers both back and
front and you can take the front off and
then you make a little stand out of it
you know what I
mean yeah and I wiped it I wiped it I
wiped it um but there's a stain and it
it's it's not like it's growing mold but
it's like uh it's like the the orange
stain has turned into a green
stain so anyway I want to I I want to
replace it but the replacement was the
wrong one and then I forgot about
getting a new one anyway anyway anyway
anyway it's not like there's like white
fuzzy stuff on it but you
[Music]
know and then I wanted to to make sure
that this time I buy the right one so I
was looking for my measurer so I can
measure the iPad um
but I couldn't find the measure
on thanks for Super Chat we
won so I don't know I have girl you live
like that well yeah n it's rough it's
[\h__\h] rough
man there's so many things I want to do
and I can't keep up with things
man your iPad's expiring yeah YY wonky
is sitting on the floor in the door
frame like
Cleopatra chunky wony cute um is going
see much
there
you H what she's cuz she's a ruler
a ruler of what come on she ain't be
ruling nothing but I like the joke I
like the
joke I do like the joke I'll give that
to
[Laughter]
you so yeah anyway I can't go too long
today I'm
sorry at least it will be longer than
yday today okay that's for
sure I'm actually looking forward to
relaxing a little bit with this game
getting my mind off of the stress a
little
bit and I have tangents yay a
few wait where's my phone the phone has
the tangents BRB
[Music]
just carrying jonkers around the house
she carrying her around now she's with
me but she wants to go away
no no
oh I love carrying them because that's
the only form of like holding them that
they accept for a certain amount of time
and I get like a full handful of of
fuzzy fluffiness in my arms and around
my shoulder and my neck it's even better
when I'm
naked then I can feel it everywhere
oh you're right I took a I I recorded a
voice P yesterday and that's also a
thing I need to re-record like the very
beginning just
one two two seconds or so because it got
kind of cut off apparently I can't
forget about
that let me write it down I have like a
to-do list right now
re-record beginning of voice pack
okay when's the Cat
Wedding I want to do
it okay okay okay
okay this music is so
relaxing it's
so w
Corina bgm
go okay uh where did I usually have you
guys it's been a little while maybe up
here and I was like I don't know we'll
[Music]
see okay whoa wait there's three people
on my roof
now she's
new the girl at the top the the fake
Witch she's
new oh I wonder how many more they're
going to Al the robot behind me is also
new new automata robot but maybe there's
still space next to him maybe there's
going to be someone there
too more will appear how many it's going
to get real crowded up on my
roof
cute okay it's been a while it's been a
while let's check in on
Anna I'm so
cute let me know if it's like too quiet
or too loud uh what are we doing check
go to Anna house
okay teleporter toy I think the way to
get to Anna's house was
[Music]
here music too low I thought
so turn it up a little
bit can I not can I not
Dash surely there was a button to dash I
can't find right
now
h p pump it
up pump the gem pump pump pump it up
pump up the gem pump it up
pump pump pump it up pump it up get
your on the Dance Floor
pump up the
gy P pump up the gam what's up Anna are
you pumping it
up
yah sad story
incoming I had a pulp came and uh it was
kind of dramatic yeah I remember that
[Music]
why I W to I W to it's so cozy here
didn't we offer that to her before now
she's actually asking for it let's
go nicey
[Music]
wait wait wait
wait okay okay I called her she's so
good at escaping
there's no space for a bigger bed in our
[Music]
home no bed
wony won weet turning the commander
Insignia I forgot to return the
Commander in in
Insignia to Olia I promise to return it
to her if she taught
me I thought I thought it said word play
Sword Play I should go to laak Village
and return
it that will surely go
well uh lak Village uh
uh this way right I could go this way
yeah disguise time it's disguise time
not that guys it's this gu
time
[Music]
uhia ah probably over
there
Olia huh
oh look how angry those mannequins
[Music]
are you don't have the same Authority
liia as the pope that's why they don't
polish
[Music]
it not her
again she doesn't recognize
sorry my hat is so
[Music]
big I'm right here I'm literally right
here
[Music]
right I was on their side usually
recently I mean EV
[Music]
F her attitude
oh [\h__\h] fight cat
[Music]
fight what yellow card red card
thought she was going to be like yellow
card last
[Music]
warning how
how does that
[Music]
[Laughter]
work we want to you want to murder her
or
what you going to live
much longer
[Music]
otherwise she's collecting president's
cards American president's collectible
cards or
what look who's behind
[Music]
me
okay he not dumb not dumb like Kate
[Music]
daughter perception greater than
one
yeah I'm glad that at least some people
are not so standard
dumb to not recognize me at least
there's
some
[Music]
for a little bit more realistic oh
chunky H is is looking cute on the floor
I didn't know she's still in the room
she looks kind of
dead she looks she looks pretty dead
she's like lying sideways like
where belly is kind of
exposed Kate and Livia seems like
something big is going to happen between
Livia and Kate afraid to ask me a favor
I need to go after Kate when I see the
name Kate now I have to think of Kit cat
K Gemma sent me a
picture of uh her
loot like previously she got me the
quasa and now she got me the ice
cream she showed me the Kit Kat ice
cream
loot cuz uh there was an ice cream place
that has a uh Baskin Robins has a Kit
Kat collaboration and I really wanted to
get it but I won't be in Japan uh until
it's over so I was like JMA
please
than m
thank you
JMA can't wait to eat
it it's probably going to be really mid
I'm just kidding I don't know it could
be just really a normal
[Music]
basic but I
mean they get it they know that limited
time Edition things you know they're
really
really uh tempting man where do we go it
said lak mine entrance where at the lak
mine
entrance
o we we're here is where
do it doesn't show on my map either does
it what about
here here ah found him
[Music]
bro I'm right behind
her
oo dark
magic they look cool though I like
[Music]
okay oh she heard voices in her
oh I guess that works
[Music]
genius another group of people joins us
I'm not even there wait where am I my
bird is there
fight fight
fight oh there I am there I
am nice well prepared
[Music]
it's his daughter
right
[Music]
probably love
no
way I didn't expect
that but give me that SW it looks nice
how to turn
table
Yahoo if only I had put on the that
accessory that's good against this magic
I I think I didn't put it
on it's okay though they'll they'll be
really
weak oh I can control
her uh
only normal attack I
guess okay uh it's been a while let's
get out some pets right uh oh I this
one's
new
[Music]
summon oh
summon
oh
salmon all right it's been almost 3 week
wow I don't remember
[\h__\h] we have the five fork lightning
five for f for fly fl five orb flame
threee orb flam M how let
just
ah ah yeah yeah yeah yeah now we see
like where it goes okay um yeah we can
do like this one for example
[Music]
woo Flav FL flavor
FL ah she doesn't get like a second
followup attack mhm mhm I see I see how
it
is okay my pets to the ground workor
maybe I
can oh
oh oh okay strong
strong fly maybe I can do like
a double swing maybe is
enough kill him yeah and I get the turn
bonus let's do another double
swing okay that was surprisingly not
enough did I have a crit or
what it's okay we win
anyway I didn't get even get to see the
the robot fight
I want to see the robot
fight
what oh
not just her everybody
chuny she jumped up my
table and went behind my
monitor what a reply
she getting desperate now
I would like to see thate
[Music]
how did you know Chad how did you know
I'm just petting her though she's an arm
arm reach arm length reach
so Happ
[Music]
how you like that placement of the mouse
huh doesn't bother
[Music]
you
for Fore
[Music]
I am
so
[Music]
um hurry to Rew Kate dealt with all
those evil demons on her own I wouldn't
want to get on her bad side I was able
to return to Commander's Insignia to
leave you this time what the [\h__\h] why oh
my God just hand it over I heard he is
about to be promoted I need to hurry my
M my m one training possible but I'll
just like save it up a little bit uh lak
Village
[Music]
again
um maybe here
[Music]
meow
meow I'm in front of the microphone
[Music]
I I'm here to give you the stupid
Insignia you wanted
[Music]
to no we missed it
no she demoted
[Music]
basically liia
oh who is he again
[Music]
that's the reason why I kept them saying
Justice and and felt scared
of saying something by
[Music]
accident see this is my
defense I only was saying Justice all
the time because of this character
[Music]
she advocating for me
oh let's go change the perception of
witches I appreciate
[Music]
it
for I'm very old
[Music]
actually fore
sorry nobody can take you serious like
this you suck so much I hate you
[Music]
H you just called out
mhm you take me
serious when I pronounce things wrong my
my voice is not as high pitched as hers
come on
not this not this
bad you think I talk like this come on
[\h__\h] you it wasn't this
bad it was it was more like this I think
if
anything perhaps
K uh I'm whole life English
Tak maybe even maybe even a little bit a
little bit less Maybe want something
like
that
[Music]
K but she's
like I'm more like more currently I'm
more like
k
k I used to be
K and she's like
[Music]
suspicious justice justice has
disappeared somewhere in the laak forest
it seems that the the policing ones are
being policed Now by me I must find them
those that are trying to find Advent are
now being the ones oh how the turntables
what is that not what it
said is that not what it said for
justice uh did he go down here yeah okay
but isn't this where Anna's house
is no okay I okay
[Music]
honestly
don't
justice justice kind of joined and
immediately started playing games it
doesn't really seem like they're here to
get Advent does
it so far they're just like singing and
playing games I don't really think
they're doing their
job they're literally right in the same
company as
Advent and they're not even like you're
right there you found
them and they're not doing
anything take him bring him to jail what
are you doing no wonder Advent escaped
[Music]
exactly the said she doesn't want to
catch well it's not about what she wants
to is it it's her [\h__\h]
job you can't just you can't just arrive
at the destination and then be like nah
I'm
good I'm just going to scribble in my
[Music]
[Laughter]
notebook it's so funny like their lore
is go find and catch
Advent and now they're together and it's
like what what are you
doing why must cats be so lazy well I
would think that domesticated cats and a
panther are kind of different I would
think a panther would be less lazy but I
guess that's not the case with this Pink
[Music]
Panther yeah maybe maybe once the collab
band is lifted maybe then they'll get to
do their job
[Music]
f look why are you defending her
slacking
off they need a plan though all other
plans weren't good enough do you really
the plan when you're already
there right in front of them next to
them o Justice showing off here is a
Justice doing his
[Music]
job way he just fell down was
funny bro
[Music]
yeah yeah so
tomado time
[Music]
she's your fan girl
now
exactly nice
[Music]
argument get wrecked by this tiny
5-year-old girl
[Music]
face he's like my emoji
we're liking
him exactly
[Music]
oh smer smer child Times
Free L
Fs in lak
Forest
nah nah we can't take you
[Music]
we can't take these
kids they're too
small
[Music]
danger okay uh the path to aart Temple
is Northwest of laak Forest there's a
lot I'd like to tell Anna but she might
know I'm here to keep an eye on the pulp
but she'll prefer it if I have happy
news to share too so I should secretly
go meet imard
first makes perfect
sense oh this
way meat Shield yeah oh we're going up
here
we have been
found who's
David is that one of the
[Music]
kids time for what
for
[Music]
no
for E I want toe
[Music]
she had to touch the grass to find her
family not be lonely
[Music]
anymore it's good to touch grass
we'll get it
back I'm going to get you your daughter
back don't
[Music]
worry
whoa are we proving our strength
[Music]
yeah don't underestimate
me okay say
[Music]
it Dave the diver has a collab of Nik
wait are the characters from Nik going
to Dave the diver or the other way
around
Dave's
ass jiggling in
N wait he's shooting his Harpoon and his
ass can you
[Music]
imagine they added Dave the dier mini
game what
[Music]
Focus guys stop thinking of D's ass
please
[Music]
please the characters are getting skins
the N
characters can't imagine Dave characters
in in N outfits either either way it's
[\h__\h] weird
[Music]
EV way it's
weird but I really enjoyed Dave the
diver man maybe maybe at some point I'll
play a
DLC maybe when I take another
Break
N it would be too short I think
[Music]
maybe a
Focus it's fine it's gonna be
fine no problem
the spring of
[Music]
witches this spelling
Stone okay
[Music]
M we have to learn how to dispel the
walls yeah where is
the There She Goes
uhoh that doesn't sound like a nice
friendly
voice even though he says he comes with
good news let's go back is she
gone
no oh but that good news I feel like
it's not going to be good news so to say
but I feel like
maybe it will be something about her
daughter but there will be a
catch
right something like that for
sure I want to see what's
there can't see
[Music]
nothing all might is that you m it
sounded a bit more evil than that but I
can I can see where you're coming
from okay was there a
running button cuz I can't find it maybe
[Music]
not ah the
Lions oh yeah true I forgot about that
thanks for reminding me pberry
[Music]
oh only Mount ah yeah right true
the name
[Music]
yeah I just had an
idea I just had an
idea what
if Age of
Empires with
me
Elizabeth and
[Music]
CeCe against each other everybody
playing their own
Nations now playing the
[Music]
Italians but wait me and
CeCe what would we play the same
thing what what would I
[Music]
play I don't think probably none of them
ever played
aoe2 okay I can play the hungarians yeah
that makes sense thinking
and then CeCe would play the totons
probably right or she could also play
the French maybe if she wants
to okay we got some choices
yeah
oh I'm such a genius sometimes man but
it will be quite the learning Arc for
them first if we were to do that and I
don't know you can't guarantee that they
like the game because it's quite a lot
to take
in uh so who knows who knows just a
random
idea you can't call this God figure
slave
bro he doesn't even
[Music]
care random but excellent right very
random I was just like in my brain
thinking of Austra versus
Turkey and then
somehow it went
there they can't imagine the smell
[Music]
now oh dark fur lions are okay to attack
okay
that's asan that's racist
[Music]
oh he's
racist wait this is is this considered
dark or light fur I don't know they're
looking like they want to fight
[Music]
me oh good night
good
[Music]
night
okay
okay that one seems light ah
wait are you angry are you
friend oh okay yeah
friendly friendly I want to rub their
belly
pleas I wonder if they'll per for
me oh oh there we go okay
yeah wait a
second who he's there for
real wa oh we're already we're already
full
heart he's so ch
Lions cannot Pur ouch they can't
Pur maybe I should introduce them to
smoothie and junkers and they can teach
them how to
[Music]
Pur don't let your dreams be dreams pet
those cats yeah and then they'll bite
off my whole head let's go
[Music]
oh
yeah oh I should have summoned oh right
this is fine this is fine
although okay they died from the fire
magic the
fire do damage let's go let's go
[Music]
I'm very strong this yeah there was no
need to be worried about
me anything else here floofy Flo FL
floof
cute more enemies would have been
appreciated but
okay regenerate my head like anuy if
only I had like vampire in me
oh look at that one
brilliant interesting let's start with
these
[Music]
ones I know I know I can mount him I
just want to walk
around that one is
op yeah I thought I thought it would be
a pet yeah yeah I thought as much
[Music]
okay I
thought I thought that would do the
[Music]
trick that big guy is one of the best
physical pets in the
game isn't my voice kind of quiet
[Music]
today against this battle
music I think so I lowered it a little
[Music]
bit y Yum Yum Yum
uh
whoa grilled lion yum yum yum
[Music]
finally using up those dried
pies
[Music]
K you have to go oh bye-bye when goes
one another one
arrives I want I want such a like big
cat paw like from a lion or a panther or
a tiger I want that to slap the [\h__\h] out
of
me there's something or just let me hug
it please don't have to slap me but I
don't know like
imagining squeezing and petting a big
paws compared to the small Paws I
usually go
for M it sounds too good too good
[Music]
they just look
so okay I wonder if I'm strong enough
for this one hey yo look he's been like
kind of
eating these dark Alliance
this one hasn't been taken over by the
dark magic oh if anything he looks way
more uh affected by it than the
others H harder it will be for him to
survive to be
captured oh you think so
[Music]
is that his tongue sticking out it's
kind of derpy
[Music]
okay okay we get it we get it we get it
we get
it no you're not seeing what I'm seeing
maybe your screen is too
dark oh wait you can see my
mouse here this part exactly where maybe
maybe we can we can get closer
ah here this one H this one this one
that looks like it it looks separate
from the rest of the
fur and a little bit
lighter or maybe it's a
tooth maybe actually yeah that might be
a tooth the others have also teeth like
that but I'd like to think that it's uh
his tongue because that kind of feels
very Derpy I like
it okay let's not kill
him um
[Music]
good
bro this is a little bit dangerous
okay how does this work again we go on
to the individual
ones ah there it is first try come on
please it
failed can I try a second time in the
same
fight
hopefully come on please
pleas you know you want it
yo y a lion that was tainted with dark
magic while fighting dark Lions before
managing to overcome it and regaining
its own
willpower we we have basically freed him
by capturing him we we're saving him
okay we're doing him a
favor oh we have arrived
oh Justice no justice doing his job in
chasing people unlike other
[Music]
justices
perhaps h
all
right bring it
on ah they're so weak
2,400 start battle without tools because
I don't need
them you are too weak
M nah-uh nah-uh you're going down
immediately ooh both of them no this one
costs four this one costs
three I want to see him in
action and then
maybe can summon these two together big
lion
power they' all lose to beu in a fight
what why beu because the they're like
both small and squeaky voice is that why
you're making that comparison
[Music]
he still Bonkers with your build what
how do you know what what what what
what small small
recovery small is
okay people is the strongest L wise
he
really what part of the lore says that
just because she's a a
[Music]
rock oh just because of that
I think
it'sa well we'll have to see them fight
it out before I can make any proper
judgment okay it's his turn
next let me pull up a Magic Shield cuz
my HP is kind of low
[Music]
thank you Magic
Shield waa it's his explosion wa
4554 nice damage oh he's
dead yay all weak compared to myth which
is weak compared to promise
hey hey but yeah promise are
Gods it's two
op
nah push him off the
cliff yeah let's do
it damn no mercy
[Music]
whoa whoa whoa whoa wait what what did
he just jump off
himself did he push us all
down [\h__\h]
idiot bro
[Music]
dude how did you survive
that you were already
[Music]
damaged looks like
it
fore
[Music]
cute
fore for
[Music]
she's just crashing on
him crash crash crash crash crash
nothing compares to a handsome
Knight on the road
just
Justice is hot I can't deny it now
not now my type
but come
on collapsed
Justice the blond-haired Warrior
overexerted himself and fell off the
cliff with me how romantic luckily he
was knocked out and now he's nice and
quiet still I should help find a way out
for
him Mama Mia what a tragedy tragedy
trag oh how ironic that Justice is right
in front of the
[Music]
prison but is once again failing failing
in his quest of imprison in me just like
do you do you see the
parallels are you starting to see the
[Music]
parallels n let's fight let's fight
oh
oh oh oh that one
stays but I I kind of do want to fight
so
but I them I should
actually
oh is it like one of these enchant
[Music]
ring increase magic 3% plus
5 okay increase agility 5% plus
7 magic resistance and then there was is
this one yeah dark magic
destruction purify small amounts of dark
magic it's an additional skill I don't
know should I put this
on maybe instead
of that one
maybe do I have better
armor
[Music]
no
no I better shoes
got some better
shoes
okay wait I'm almost
dead oh didn't know my HP was so [\h__\h]
low br
[Music]
all right I'll take one of these why
not here we freaking
go attack how does this not get all of
them God damn
it
ta How do you like this
what imagine there's an option where we
wouldn't have had to find any of
these oh are these the walls that they
were talking
about a powerful barrier stands before
you okay now we need to find something
to break
these uh
barriers I that's a sick ride
man that's a sick
ride
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
damn
oh oh cute
mm I'll need a dispelling stone to
remove imard Temple's barrier wall I
should be able to find it in the imard
temple mural
yay oh I see a glitch in The
Matrix you have no tools
so wait so
I where do I get
them oh oh there's oh there's so many of
them
okay
H my
[Music]
intuition find the stone in the mural
oh I'm sure once you know the full story
of this game this mural probably makes a
lot of
[Music]
sense let's look at this oh it's the
pope and there's
that could be uh me or probably the
daughter of
Anna I can't go all the way up I want to
go up there though
or I want to pick the stone that's at
the
[Music]
top it's in his [\h__\h]
head
huh does it even matter where what I
choose
for a prophecy Magic Stone used to
dispel the barrier wall okay I collect
like all of them right okay this is
funny
looking what what does this mean there's
like an upside down person it's like a
reflection or maybe this is like water
no but it's like horizontally flipped
anyway it's probably here
[Music]
yeah oh this is like same but he's going
away he's leaving with it and now maybe
it's inside of
him
sasuka mm someone stole Evil dark magic
or something I don't
know where's the beginning of this
anyway is this enough now
or is there
more use this spell Stone use oh yeah oh
yeah oh this looks like once I
completely uh dispel it I'm this will
come out of the wall and I'll have to
fight it
he's growing
arms yeah yeah well I I'm not surprised
6,000 okay okay that's better than some
other enemies we've had
recently
mhm how did you know how did I
know so I have some sad news
guys I was quite sad upon hearing this
but uh my
favorite story
lady told me that
she has quit her job I mean she's still
going to be working for a while
longer but she
quit
and I'm so sad to hear that
but I've been getting along with the
other store people
too even the stupid sussy
Baker seems like he's not sulking
anymore he's kind of acting normal again
should I go straight or
down now she doesn't have a new job yet
but uh she's
looking
oh this one looks stronger
so yeah well she told me this like uh a
few days ago and I forgot to tell you
guys
W 7,200 that's not much of an
improvement oops I I accidentally used
the tool
no
[Music]
no but today when I went today to get my
quas um you know you know we talk a
little bit
and I asked her when when's your exact
date of your last day and then I
realized I won't be there and so I was
like a I guess I got to say goodbye on a
different
day and then she was like well
well well do you do you you know have
some you
know social Med
video or
so or Conta
of you know so we have
exchanged
contacts we actually did
it and it came from her so it didn't
feel as
cringe
yay wa and the story lady together
forever United
did never to be aart
again
yeah yeah how do I do it I didn't do
anything it just happened
naturally I just built this lowkey chill
Vibe with her
[Music]
this kind of
weak
yeah
so waa got the Riz waa isn't even trying
but I got the
Riz um
[Music]
a he's shielded a no
problem just got to blast his
ass okay he was kind of stronger cuz he
had this
[Music]
Shield goal completed barrier wall
y so it was only two I should continue
on to the spring where I'm h
resides in there but I want to see
what's below then or is that where I
came from I
wonder oh and down here wait down here
too
oh Soul
incinerator
what what's that
[Music]
friendship
brid I think you can use RZ for the
purpose of friendship
[Music]
too for
for
not do you want to stay here a little
longer I guess I'll leave if the game
is offering me
this seems like something for
later you need the sword behind one of
the barriers for that one uh I still
want to see what's down here is that
where it came
from ah not
[Music]
that is where I came
from
okay now we can
proceed oh kute it what is
that kind of reminds me of um midna
midna was that her
name just with no
body from a Twilight Prin says
yeah where did you leave your
body what happened to
[Music]
it I want to play Twilight Princess I
want to play it I want to play I want to
play I want to play
[Music]
now I didn't check if the Wii U works
but
um did I dream this or did Twilight
Princess get uh a port on the
switch I feel like it will though even
if it doesn't have one now
[Music]
right I observed it and found the way
before I stepped on it I used my brain
first before
proceeding and these are easy though and
maybe there's several rolls Solutions
too maybe if we're lucky we'll get on
the switch Yeah I guess it seems too
late to bring out a port at this
[Music]
point so perhaps no more port for
switch I mean there's
several paths I would say a damn it I
think I [\h__\h] up no but I had it I I
had it I
actually think I can do
yeah this is what I wanted to
do yeah I think I bought it on the Wii U
I think so but I mean if there's already
a new Z game coming out this year in
September then I suppose I'll just wait
for that there's no rush I don't have
time time to play Twilight Princess
anyway until
then but maybe after that there will be
a draw in Zella games for a while I
don't think they'll release another one
next year a new one certainly not a new
one but next year could be a year for a
port so I feel like I'm just going to
play the yeah echo of wisdom this year
and I'll be so [\h__\h] hyped for that
man I'm so [\h__\h] hyped I'm so excited
I can't believe it's coming out so soon
too like when they were announcing a new
Zelda game I thought oh surely it'll be
2025 or so no it's [\h__\h] ready to go
pretty
much
damn oh yeah they'll have a live action
movie maybe maybe
2025 did they say it would be
2025 I don't think they gave a date did
they they just said it's in the works
but it could be
[Music]
2025 I forgot about out
he
mad let
us oh damn the
roast oh oh oh o ooh strong
[Music]
looking the head looks like a [\h__\h]
tum more two two more two
two yeah tum more or like a f cyst that
he has on his
head two two more
and oh oh 7,22
6000s okay okay okay I'll take
something this will be fun a little bit
of fun oopsie a little bit of
fun oh I can get all of
them will they hit me hard
I am a little bit
scared I didn't go into it with full
HP oh he put up a
shield I can put up a shield
too wait so what helps against the
Shield can I break it somehow or is
there like a special way special way to
break
it yeah the do on it I I don't mind them
running low I don't they're so you know
small I'm just trying to get rid of them
all one by
one you think it's like my own oh could
[Music]
be oh well
okay just got to brute force
it maybe we can kill him with together
with uh
brillian come on
yeah okay one down one
[Music]
down the arrow for
you okay not dead that's okay cuz I got
another
turn uh actually can we finish ah a
triple
swing I don't know if that will work on
a demon king kind of I I'm hoping it
will
ah I did it did it did got the turn
bonus okay and we got the crit we got
the
crit Dan I'm going all in on the magic
storm hit him
pberry who why why is his attack doing
more than my critical
special magic blast what the
[\h__\h] oh oh cuz now The Shield is down
maybe that's why the shield was still up
when I attacked was it ah okay okay okay
okay then I shall
forgive just a small
attack that's fine I'm chilling
I'm leaving it to my
pets I think I'm starting to
see the thing that someone said
previously about the pets being stronger
than yourself at some
point maybe it's
true it might be true
end game you can have four Pats at the
same time
wow that will be
nice oh nothing here you could have put
a chest here what the
hell oh
I want P me
too I want pie
too cherry pie would be really sick
[Music]
ah
hi she's so excited oh my
God
okay why is he Rising me
Master why are you raising her I thought
you only lik me
[Music]
weird name I know
[Laughter]
[Music]
speee
oh she still thinks it it might
be oh she still didn't give up on that
[Music]
NE is stuck just kidding
scary foree
[Music]
doing me a
concern these
words I don't want to put on the tin
foil hat again
but what if what if what if I am
Anna
uh
um magic
maybe magic plus 25 what do you think
guys or HP
yeah Through Time
Travel agility or HP do we need HP that
much I feel like my attacks
are I guess they're strong enough my HP
yeah okay okay okay I can I can see how
that might help
you I'm might absolute defense uh am's
blessing creates a binding of absolute
defense around pberry while the barrier
is unleashed the enemies receive uh
undefendable fixed damage every time
they attempt to attack pyber nice
[Music]
bro I don't even need
you if you don't want to be with me [\h__\h]
you
your boss says so so you better do what
your boss
says so what it also works like a pet or
what I am the chosen
one that's right
[Music]
oh that's the same voice that talk to
Anna I
think
oh he's got some sick armor he looks
like he could be from Dragon
Quest oh
Savage pberry let's go
yes praise me more more
[Music]
please this little girl will [\h__\h] you up
4,000 n weak ass
moo after I kill you I'll take your
armor and I'll size it down and I'll be
wearing it will look better on me for
sure okay I already got uh one pet out I
guess but where is that one H oh wait it
might not count actually it doesn't
count it does not count will it attack
oh yeah it
will
[Music]
o it or am I blind
no it's not
there
okay here we got I'm heart's absolute
defense but um it will be available
after one turn
[Music]
okay
oh that's a good ratio
ah he gave me a little helmet
cute H that's what he does he doesn't
attack you didn't kill him brao
yeah uh
[Music]
H yeah now the bird is available and I
can heal
myself and we could try this
thing wait is that the only attack I'm
allowed to do no okay I can do something
else
too had to go to work before I saw the
options that
they but what is your choice you're
still not telling
[Music]
me should be able to take down a few of
them if I do this
again
yeah there we go did he buff me me
[Music]
again of course it's okay I would
probably try to end up asking you anyway
if you were like in pre- chat or
whatever at the time when I'm signing
them who
Bonk okay I should have paid attention
how much damage that did back to him was
it
200 I just saw the number 200 so
probably
probably oh I cannot use aru's Arrow
while having the I'm heart blessing
[Music]
on Yay good good stop good
Stu
foree n
[Laughter]
H are you sure you didn't blackmail
her
no I'm sure she had no choice
[Music]
see she doesn't want to do
it see I told you there's a c mhm and it
was about her
daughter
[Laughter]
for it's
okay I can deal with
[Music]
this
fore
foree
[Music]
for what bro
are they going to take
[Music]
her you didn't actually kill her did you
is she dying
fore of course you do
no
no Mommy
[Music]
crying
fore
fore fore
I did not step back though am I going to
be okay
[Music]
spee spe
damn she's got an attitude
suddenly
for don't fall for
it don't fall for
it let's go
she seems kind of evil right now not
going to lie
how the [\h__\h] did she do
that
bro oh
he's like shaking like crazy but he's
talking so
calmly everybody's shaking like crazy
all right bye
suckers oh not
good yeah they should have recorded it
while sitting on a washing
machine into the void they
[Music]
go for
Fore
foree
fore
[Music]
foree
foree fore
[Music]
fore speee
M well your eyes certainly looked Dead
all this
[Music]
time
for Fore
[Music]
speee
foree
speech foreign
for
[Music]
for yeah her she's she's at her best
when she cries with her voice voice
[Music]
acting
damn like that gets me the way she
screams cry is she did she grow
up are we doing a Time skip now I don't
know she's
she's not yet
right what did we
but that headband is
cute touch grass yeah touch some grass
it helps for
depression that voice sounds more grown
up yeah maybe she did grow
[Music]
up she sounds older and they're hiding
her looks
she sounds different but the art is
still
young okay there she is again she was
just sucking
no the DLC art also has a grown-up
version Oh Joe sitting on top
cute fluffy
bird on
tmy fluffy bird in tmy should
be not on dummy
go in
tummy
cute cute her pajamas
cute
[Music]
bro what
what giant bird I'm suddenly sense it's
maybe it's a prank to get me
out maybe this is
all
fake am I right or am I
oh that's not a bird that's a dragon I
must be on the wrong path
the [\h__\h] or Griffin or a Chima or I
don't
know
really he has been
eaten oh
really no bird went in tummy just like I
said but not my
tummy damn I jinxed
it [\h__\h] we got to open up his stomach
quickly quickly
3,400 ow stop poking
me okay no problemo no problemo oh ah
now I can summon him I guess he was like
forced to be on the battlefield
previously I know
[Music]
I wonder if I can capture this thing
probably
not summon more food yeah I
will next time I do some
[Music]
leveling oh that sounded like we turned
it into crispy
chicken ah there he is look at that fat
[\h__\h]
[Music]
sorry for jinxing you I shouldn't have
jinxed
you I'm
[Music]
sorry C foree
no she's still thepress W press
[Music]
what do you mean delivery attempted
today at 1 hour ago
just check my Amazon
[Music]
package [\h__\h] you I need a
dance I swear to God
[Music]
punch him some
more ni just didn't ring my bell I would
have heard
it I would have heard
[Music]
it
braah oh uh okay new chapter a sanctuary
awaiting
reunion okay
[Music]
yeah no they didn't
try but I don't
know it says they will try again but
that usually just doesn't it's not true
usually that just means they uh are
going to have me pick it
up idiots
idiots let me check I have N9
DMS wa
[Music]
uh
what whatever blah blah blah blah blah
blah can I go grab some
chocolate I want some
chocolate that's
[Music]
not like you can stop
me it's what I wanted to be
yeah [\h__\h] it I'm fine I don't need a
diet I'm beautiful the way I
am uh I already have so much on my hands
of Anna but black Joe is adamant about
going to illusion Temple I don't know
why but I trust him to get to the
illusion illusion plane I need to go
through back hill Golem cave where I
first learned teleportation
thanks for reminding me I still don't
know which one that is somewhere in The
Beginner's map I
[Music]
suppose yeah I need this chocolate the
scene was so
[Music]
emotional I think we should
level train
I have three
[Music]
sessions what should I
do maybe an one
[Music]
overall always good to have this
one now stressed out chocolate helps
with
stress scientifically
[Music]
proven it's Kinder
country it's true it's true everybody
who says otherwise will be banned
[Music]
I cannot
decide what do I need
[Music]
be something I've done before please
okay yooo
o stage
two how bad can it be
[Music]
woohoo come on perfect bonus
y I did it it was basically the
same I don't think it was any more
difficult more skills
[Music]
got a passion
Justin okay now then we wanted to make
some
food I got so many books
now these ones are
good can only make one
let's just again ah
mhm nothing new that I can make I
[Music]
think okay we can make
M more of these
um I guess I I I prefer items although
some I really need both both like some
items that can heal both at the same
time and some items that just heal
[Music]
HP you're welcome I did see my message
but I think it might have been a lot
later I don't know how long you guys had
to deal with that free
chat I told her am I think your chat
your free chat I think it's like
over I'm going to stream alen ring
tonight I saw
yeah I'm so
bad they nerfed the
DLC right away after it released just
like with the base game huh
[Music]
seems like they didn't learn from when
they released a base game they
overestimated the players
again I guess I'll make more of these
[Music]
M A how's this going
where would we get lava eyes I
wonder are we able to get those yet
probably not
[Music]
right
okay
uh I think I'm ready to
go maybe I'll change my outfit I want to
be I want I'll be base outfit again
maybe for a
while and let's
[Music]
go oh they didn't Nerf they just buffed
the skiy pieces it's like telling those
players oh Noob you should get that
those things
[Music]
okay yeah I don't really know what's up
with that I'm not planning on playing it
either where are we
going wait that's not no what what what
am I doing what am I
doing
sorry I remembered it's on my current
[Music]
map it's right there
wait wait which way which
way which
way which cave is this
[Music]
one yes back hill Golem cave
woohoo y
[Music]
where do we go to
exactly I don't remember the
path up and then could it be
[Music]
there let's
see was it where are we going
keep going
up is it behind these big boards
okay we we never fought them before oh
really I think they'll be pretty
[Music]
weak cat punch too
strong m
okay they looked really threatening
before so I never gave it a try but oh
oh we can jump up
there mhm show me
how he G keep keeping me
oh I I think I support
that yeah make him stronger Bring It
[Music]
On just go my
God you guys need to learn how to do
that you need to learn how to carry
me is this a
[Music]
k maybe not quite looks like a goat
Dragon wait there's a stupid Derpy Bird
that's a stupid Derpy black
Joel but he's
[Music]
white cat
stop talking look at the
birds look at the
[Music]
bir his eyes are turning this is
literally you guys looks like a
chicken hey hey it's not ugly don't call
my chickens
[Music]
ugly one of
us he's just missing the red
[Music]
P what the
hell they don't recognize me I'm I'm I'm
Wawa I know I look different but I'm
Wawa kfp come
[Music]
on bro kfp why so
[Applause]
[Music]
aggressive guess I'll uh guess you'll
die guess I'll kill you
[Music]
tonight's didn't assorted yeah good cuz
I I don't know what to do
otherwise okay nice new area wee maybe
we'll find more of those birds oh
[Music]
B are there more of
him was the
same oh he rebirthed he rebirthed he's a
phoenix Phoenix Golem
does he remember me I wonder
[Music]
do you guys want to hear the Korean
voice a little bit I'm curious I'll
change it why did that why did that
reset everything
o it looked like it reset things I don't
know did it
though
[Music]
oops
okay I know what
suddenly
Korean let's check out how different she
will
sound he sounds
[Music]
similar okay not that way you want me to
go up there but I wanted to fight the
Derpy Birds
I can't learn Korean with this means
there oh they speak so
fast
[Music]
cute cute
[\h__\h] Derpy
bird
no
uh guys you didn't see that right don't
worry the kfp is fine the kfp um uh is
totally fine it the dragon immediately
spit out the kfp behind the scenes
[Music]
so fast oh my God west of elusion plane
the entrance to illusion Temple has been
destroyed it's a bit far but I'll have
to turn back and go around I should
follow black Joe's instructions and
enter the cave on the west side of the
elusion plane so now we go that way okay
now you let me
go they only have 50
HP
what
[Music]
Z bro
h
e ugly bird meat hey stop roasting the
cute
birds bro look at them there's so many
of
them they're so
cute Combo level up Egle
let's try uh see how many die from this
so we can actually wait first hit we'll
do a normal swing then I get a second
turn free free to two free
two really
[Music]
come on give me your friend what's wrong
with you
I like the Korean voice it's
cute it's a little bit less squeaky than
the Japanese one I
feel yeah it is a Korean game it to be a
Korean
game ugly look at him look at
him
funny oh what the [\h__\h] is
that oh o oh a white rhino with a huge
horn that looks
pretty
wow pretty
Rhino
[Music]
big I understand to
uh-huh
uh
N I just want small
heal not too small this is
okay I have a lot of HP I guess now so
small heal the the heels that used to be
big heels are now medium heels more or
less um um uh yo uh let me summon a pet
he's got 4,800 oh okay that's not that's
not
bad I still have current summon cost
free
okay oh only the lion talks
[Music]
you already missed
the it's okay I can say it for you
speaking of voice acting so yesterday I
recorded a voice pack right uh I have
like a lot of voice packs upcoming
actually I didn't want to sign up for so
many I already signed up for like three
or so for this summer and then I made
one for my birthday uh I think I think
it was for the birthday no for the
anniversary I think
actually and then
uh
then like staffan was like oh are you
sure you don't want to participate in
this one because today is the deadline
for you know participation you know so
just let me know and I'm like e well I
wasn't really planning to but you're
asking me directly so I guess I guess I
guess I'll do it all right then now I
have another one on my
plate and then for the for the one that
I recorded yesterday I
was having so much fun because the
script was actually really good you know
usually they had scripts
um written by Japanese
staff unless you want to write it
yourself but usually it's written by
Japanese STA and then you
uh get it translated to
English and you record
that but now for this one for some new
projects they hired English script
writers so it's I mean I think the
translations were always fine but this
way they're already written in English
and they're like considering slang and
this and that so I noticed the script
was like so much more natural and fun
and there was like banther and stuff I
had a lot of fun recording it and I went
like full in character and I think it's
like probably probably my best voice
pack performance ever there's several
coming up but this one this one I think
I have absolutely
exceeded my own skills so far my own
performances so far I think you guys
will like
it can't wait to hear it yeah there'll
be a lot of them like I think like end
of
summer most of them September or so as
well where you will be bombarded with
voice
bags sorry in
advance but there's some cute ones and
some interesting
ones
[Music]
yeah you save up for
them thank
you oh it did hit the other one
wow feite ducky oh ducky makura in the
feite outfit oh wow okay that actually
sounds like it could sell
well oh that would have been good if I
would have released it as merch right
when I did the outfit
reveal but I don't know I'm still kind
of against the idea of doing daki
makula
sorry and booby mouse pad
although nah it's just I don't know I
would cringe at myself if I released
that kind of
merchandise
[Music]
uh can't do it I just can't I just
can't D you're already cringe hey hey
how dare
you a a butt mouse
pad I don't
no I mean for the
upcoming both birthday and anniversary I
already have it pretty much set in stone
so those are not going to
change but there's been some
good uh
fanmade actually I I say it as if it's
plural I feel like there was only one no
maybe there were more but no you know
Akida made a really good one in the past
um I mean dakim makura a really good
one yeah Duma made a booby mouse pad
right of Ki so you know at least fans
are making it so I don't have to if you
really want one you can buy one from
fans and I don't have to make
one and feel embarrassed releasing such
merchandise
the say so mouse pad sold the most
interesting I didn't even see the the
different version I only saw like one
version of it I
[Music]
think I need more of this bore meat it's
like the right amount for
me oh this one's also actually
fine yeah ah
oh this hits all of them let's go nice
positioning SAA also released a very
classic ducky yeah but if you're going
to make it wait CL classy if you're
going to make it classy I mean for soda
sfai I wouldn't ever expect her to do a
spicy one but if I were to make one
what's the point of me doing a classy
one if anything it should be
[Music]
spicy now as I said for this year I'm
pretty um set in what I'm releasing
so don't get your hopes up for
anything actually I just I should just
summon another pet I'm too lazy
sometimes to summon another
one they should just be there from the
get-go they should have me set which
ones I want to be there before I start
the
fight which ones I want to have there I
can't
talk night merch well that will have to
be next year and that's kind of late
late and random probably I mean frogy
waa merge would happen pretty late but I
don't know if I would really do that for
fite oh what is he doing what is he
doing charging I think it's
charging release your charge
rifle release it now before it's too
late and the fight is already over
how about chicken
D well you guys are too small on round
to make a dakimakura out of you that
would have to be like like a small
pillow and I mean we already have a
plushy of you guys
now
[Music]
for I understand some words let's go
chin
beanbag be yeah bean bag is
cute that's kind of squishy I like the
idea of that oh my Korean Bros are
coming out of the Shadows
don't think too much about it black Joe
with your tiny small brain it's not good
for you you're going to explode what I
already have this don't
die I already made that I
think wait uh I can handle these Free
Birds angle
[Music]
okay these are kind of weird I don't
know if I want to fight these now what's
their
HP oh 14,000 a Golem formed from the
white rocks of Illusion
plane am I even supposed to fight these
now 14,000 I think I can handle
but maybe better to kill them
later good morning Good
Morgan
on they look very strong but we we
fought a lot of strong looking enemies
and oh there Derpy bird
Queen
cute ugly Bird's Captain the leader of
the FL ugly birds AKA chickens it moves
much faster than its large size would
have you expect that's not really large
to be
[Music]
honest 15 damage what the hell what's
why are they so weak they could have
made them stronger or put these enemies
into the beginning into the very
beginning what's the point
man what's the point
why were they Gat keeping me from these
cutie
[Music]
ponies to punish low agility BL oh oh
it's not much of a punishment like it
would be funny if they had really low HP
but like really high
damage then you would be punished if you
are not able to clean them up really
fast but they don't they do eight damage
eight guas light gate keep girl
boss let's go
[Music]
oh but yeah I like the idea of being bag
chicken if I still remember that next
year if I ever ask you for oh what
should I do for
merchandise then you guys shall remind
[Music]
me 800 oh I can probably capture this
one huh
you stupid
[\h__\h]
PA in
Korean two Mill oh okay okay all right I
think we okay if I get 2 million Subs I
promise you I will make either a spicy
dakim makura or a spicy uh Mouse booby
mouse pad or butt mouse
pad all right
deal
[Laughter]
deal you better be ready for
it I why did I come here there's not
even any path it's a dead end
2 mlion said laboratory cake what if
what if is like instead of a you know
what if it's like exactly built and
shaped like a booby or butt mouse pad
but it's a
cake is it cake or not yes it is yes it
is
why
not
oh oh wow water water who oh what the
[\h__\h] is that the one that ate the
chicken no that one looks even bigger
damn who are
you which taryan lost
you bro I watched both episodes so far I
watched the second one last
night it's been really good so
far I like
that
uh I like that I like I like it I like
it I don't know there's not really much
to say I'm just because it's still fresh
in my brain no spoilers okay but I'm
really wondering what was the point of
the twins um that whole Arc what what
was the
point in the end I was
like okay they made egun an actual
sympathetic character you mean um egun
wait there's Aon and egun and Damon and
Egan is the one that's currently King
right
H to highlight how the Civil War is
tearing apart the realm yeah but like I
feel like you could have highlighted
that differently I I I want to I don't
want to talk about it too clearly but I
feel like it didn't have to go that far
I feel like that could have been an
interesting conflict if you
know maybe you know he like like also
what was the point of maybe we'll find
out in the third episode okay quick
spoiler just just don't listen if you
don't want to hear it for don't listen
for 2 minutes or so please I have to let
this out but um you know how like the
girl she was going to the ship and then
she sees the twin coming in and uh she's
like hey yo please wait a minute and you
think that she wants to like alert them
ahead of time that something's wrong but
then you never see her anymore until the
end of the episode and I thought she
would like show up when both of the
twins are in the room maybe I thought
she would like comes
in or I thought that maybe she'll at
least play a role in differentiating
them cuz they fight so much and then
everybody's like uh wait I need to
protect the the queen but who is the
right twin that's on our side and I
thought oh that this is interesting cuz
I literally also don't know
anymore yeah she surely tell that one
guard but I thought she would also like
play a bigger role in like
differentiating them and and like I I
would think she would like really be the
the one who makes it clear and then the
queen will be even more thankful to her
so I don't know um but she didn't show
up anymore which is kind of
weird and then I thought I thought like
at the point where one is dead I thought
it would be it would have been
interesting if the one that
remains she uh uh she re neighbor would
be like okay but are you the real one
and he'll have to prove himself but it's
not like one is dead one is dead so how
can the remaining one really ever be
truly
trusted uh cuz you could ask if they're
both Al life you could ask both of the
questions and you can probably figure it
out but if there's only one alive
there's no one not his other twin
wouldn't be there to disprove him so he
could continue to infiltrate and and uh
act as his other twin brother you know
but then he just suddenly yeah he just
commits to do I'm like what wait what
about this whole Arc I had in my head
now where you could have made it really
interesting in deceiving them even
further and infiltrating them even
further that's not where I thought this
was
going you thinking the same right
bro well obviously the one that was you
know slicing himself up in the end was
the good one the real one um but let's
say that it was the other way around
then he could have totally just stayed
alive and infiltrated and because it
wasn't exactly that I understand that
but then why didn't the book do it
differently this wasn't even this wasn't
as interesting as it could have been in
my opinion you know what I
mean you know what I
mean caning is a huge to he couldn't
live him himself yeah but as I'm as I'm
saying they should have just written it
differently that the remaining one was
the evil
twin aren't you surprised isn't a genius
no it's
not it was
like kind of antil climatic you could
[Music]
have if that's how it was in the book
okay good for following the books
but
yeah the book didn't really get deep
enough into any of these characters to
facilate this kind of Storytelling it
was just a recount of historical events
so just sir so and so killed himself
there
a so they actually probably made a
bigger deal out of it than it was in the
books well that's that's unfortunate
that uh you you you you kind of start
making a big deal of out of it but then
you ended so in such a lame
way there was more potential there I
want to say
H but yeah so far so good I'm liking it
and
[Music]
um yeah I'm very interested in what was
her name Helena the mother of one of the
again
twins both of them but one of them is no
more and yeah uh she's interesting also
because I watched a little bit of um a
recap of the first episode like a 4H
hour recap I didn't get to watch all of
it but the do the the dude he was
talking about like he knows everything
right so he mentioned that Helena has
the ability to look into the future or
something like that so I think it would
be interesting yeah egon's wife and
sister mhm
mhm so much [\h__\h]
incest I think it will be interesting if
they work more and more into her story
and uh use it more yeah her dreams about
the future
I hope they will show that in the show
more so far they've been focusing a bit
on her with you know the events that
have transpired but I I would like them
to show off her powers a little
bit maybe people would take care more
seriously
now yeah it's my birthday this week
happy birthday you remember me I hope
you're not the same person there was
someone I think I ended up muting that
person there was someone who uh wrote to
me on Twitter like hey it's my birthday
can you wish me a happy birthday but I
think it said like tomorrow and I
ignored it because I was like well you
wrote it in caps you're kind of like
spamming and but then the next day they
wrote that again and the next day they
wrote that again and the next day but
they kept on writing like my birthday is
today at that point like several days in
a row they wrote my birthday is today
Tak would mean the world to me if you
wish me a happy birthday generally I'm
open and willing to wish people happy
birthday even if they're you know just
like uh sending a small message in the
chat or so when I see it I'm happy to
wish you happy birthday you know uh but
this person seemed to have birthday
every day and was very dramatic about it
and then at some point I checked their
profile and I'm
like and I see that they've been
spamming several whole life members for
like two three weeks now saying every
day to several whole life members today
is my birthday it would mean the world
to me if you wish me happy birthday
please please
please so obviously I'm going to ignore
you if that's if you're going to spam
and spam and spam when was your actual
birthday huh when is your real
birthday I don't believe it
[Music]
anymore yeah didn't I I think I just
ended up muting that person cuz I
haven't been seeing those messages
anymore happy birthday Chad happy
birthday sounds like bot Behavior I
don't think it was bot Behavior it was
not a bot no no no just you know
probably a
Zoomer Zoomer is like a real
Zoomer oh
[Music]
oh second on dog pet rock
years okay not anger the big
dragon seems like it's not even noticing
us to be honest
the
Dragon drag on these
Stones
police hello witness
[Music]
me foree
oh that was longer than I
thought yes an army of ugly chicken
[Music]
birds that sounds good yeah he seems
kind of
Tangled Fire
[Music]
magic f magic girl think about your
magic that you had since day
one get
your
what what do you
[Music]
mean how did
he how did he accept that now when we
didn't even know what we were going to
do
huh secret what do you mean he didn't
whisper anything into his ears I didn't
hear anything I didn't read
anything let not question it then
[Music]
oh
okay that's the point of whispering so
the other party can't hear but I heard
him talk
I heard him talk though apparently is a
path Northeast of the darkstone cave
Northeast
[Music]
humu uhuh upgraded version of those
small
stones these
are
uh lost Pebbles from bi boo that have
lost their
path and need to be enlightened
again we need to help
them we need to help them corrupted yeah
they're
corrupted can we fix them can we help
them can we save them
p
p she saying P not ego
maybe damn they're kind of strong
[Music]
H heal police
uh what what was it uh nuke the nuke
field was it Northeast or
Southeast what was the direction they
said oh wait it's on the map
ha SM SM dark magic Stone
oh what the hell are
you you want me to fight you it's kind
of wait it might not even be that
direction is it up
here oh
yeah you know cuz I'm feeling I'll
probably come back here eventually like
with other places I often come back so I
couldn't I could leave some enemies be
oh that's a lot of
them N I want to try I'll I'll I'll take
them
down who whoa whoa
whoa yeah maybe Shield Stone would have
been
better h
that's okay I can take
this
uh although we need a Magic
Shield
[Music]
okay
nice
oh okay yeah I definitely had to tank
that one
out and now I cannot get black Joe to
heal me
[Music]
so okay one thing I'll try is at least
take one down before I heal my
myself
mhm 10
[Music]
HP hey o
e strategic crit
time
[Music]
wait yeah yeah yeah yeah don't worry I
think I can probably almost end it in
this round if not actually ended yeah
like this
maybe no almost he'll die from the burn
damage or that one
okay yeah yeah no need for that barrier
no need for
that but yeah that was a little bit of a
challenge 10 HP is
close indeed
[Music]
okay let's go that
way I'll ignore the big ones for
now
oh oh there's several of those birds
[Music]
that's like r in
koreanum it sounds like the Japanese
word chumuk same word
[Music]
actually is he Whispering something
again
bro fore
[Music]
my regular Joe where's my regular
Joe I don't even have a regular
Joe but this one special
[Music]
nuke field ala black Jo is Friends of
the nukes I'm surprised he wasn't eaten
by them I'll have to defeat the unwanted
guests on top of nuk field if I want
their help okay who are we talking
about what do you mean oh
oh dark magic evil
nuke fore foree
fore
oh this ctie again
I think she is
let's
go yeah I do have a feeling that she's
mle oh 16,
7,200 oh Shield
[Music]
Stone
am yeah B
uh let's actually
no I'll go with this one
[Music]
again the pop isn't that bad are you
sure about that
[Music]
I can probably just go for this one
might be very
effective thank you for standing in one
straight line I appreciate
that oh oh what whoa whoa whoa whoaa
what what the
[\h__\h] interesting
attack a he's getting another one
bro stop
okay um
definitely definitely need a
[Music]
heal I think we can go for the
pie and
then we put on the absolute defense is I
can still do something something else
right if I do
that
yeah
[Music]
and the same
power I I'll I'll give it a
try oh good good good
good three years of
kfp oh 800 damage back to them let's go
this is AOE so it should hit both
anyway y I killed a
witch that is possibly the daughter of
Anna yay I feel so good about
that is it worth doing like maybe how
about the overload strike I we have full
HP pretty much we can do it I want to
oh that was
good 800 damage you're welcome 44 months
man thank you those numbers sound and
look crazy to
me holy [\h__\h] 8 this is pretty
op that is so op wow
damn next attack is a crit but we're
pretty much
done
yeah oh thank you guys wow wow wow wow
wow damn yeah that's so
strong oh no he's dead
oh what what did you say do you think
there will be next
time
[Music]
you you're in your
40s okay we've done our job
here we've done it and now have the
ability to
fly but only in to one specific
destination I
suppose oh
wa
wow
wow nice
[Music]
oh it looks like the other Temple that
we've been
to
what that's the Pop's
Castle so he's in there
okay of course there's always something
nice in the
temples well what's wrong with it I feel
like I've seen several like
these
[Music]
M that's what I said
what thank you
coin
heyo is she growing up is she like
having growing pains right now and she
just suddenly plop becomes
adult imagine
[Music]
sus
Behavior okay weird
random a oh
[Music]
C
okay she had a a speedy nap now we're
ready to go in let's go
oh wow we're up so
high o is that the path to the castle
what the [\h__\h] is that
bridge boing boing wavy Bridge oh
no oh
no dangerous
brii okay I'm going
in enemies are getting stronger I feel
like we should be like
getting stronger as well
but it's okay to fall behind a little
bit because we were too strong
anyway yeah this looks like one of those
okay but a very a very big and and crazy
version of one of those warm
tropical houses of tropical plants you
know that you can go in when it's cold
outside even and it's hot as [\h__\h] in
there what do you call them
again a
green yeah yeah I like it
do you guys like the Korean version the
Korean voice acting more or the Japanese
one exploring illusion Temple as
expected of a God who controls life the
temple is overflowing with love energy
in the past illusion even raised the
dead why why did Black Joel bring me am
I
dead
Japanese well maybe uh you guys
understand at least like a few words in
Japanese so you feel like
more uh a little bit like you're
understanding
it yeah I I think so maybe when she
grows up I'm I want to hear the Japanese
voice again but oh
hello I got to agree her Japanese young
voice it's a bit too squeaky for my
taste her crying is really good
well that's a nice voice and so echoey
wow that's
Crown thank you for the pink Super
Chat Studio Rob
[Music]
we can do it
18,600 with no other
enemies only him I think we have a
chance does that mean I think it means
uh pieber is here or has
arrived I have learned that Korean
before yeah
mhm yeah I turned down the uh battle
bgms and stuff because it was too loud
couldn't hear myself
[Music]
okay
bro can I win
this surely I can
[Music]
right okay this might be kind of week
but I'll go for it anyway because soon
oh we already have a im Hearts okay
maybe it's just kind of made to use this
you have to pretty
much yeah you got to put up that barrier
then then we're good we'll be
fine k k
exp oo AR Arrow oh [\h__\h] right I can't
stack it
okay
um 7,000 I could put on the Magic Shield
and a r i can do this one first
anyway W 2,200
yeah I think I'll be
fine I think I'll be
[Music]
fine yeah my pets do maybe the last hits
he's charging some something
strong y charge rifle come
on Lightning
[Music]
ball y
oh he's so
cool oh I think I prefer his career
version a
lot uh Jo no
Jo finally true form and true power of
Jo what the [\h__\h] don't tell me this is
your true
form now is the time you choose to show
me this
bro
what that's why he was able to
communicate with
them
who now we can't we can't make fun of
him anymore
am I I guess I
[Music]
am he has his own charge rifle
oh sick he was hiding this power all
along maybe he only was able to re uh uh
unleash it here because it's his
Temple or
so weak ass
bastard oh oh oh
witch male
witch foree
he must have been really sweaty under
that helmet because look at how shiny
the top of his hair is it's like
jelly young di he means Me Maybe
[Music]
I thought we were
witches
foree
spee for
oh
true true yeah
murder okay I don't understand all of
this but cool
stuff okay but can we talk about Joe
what the [\h__\h] was up with that I need
explanations
[Music]
are you guys saying it's my mama like yo
mama what happened with you
[Music]
but why was he hiding that
anyway what's the
[Music]
reason
for signed an
NDA for
[Music]
no for hiding things
Joey okay okay if you say
so that better be the full truth and
nothing but the
truth but like the fact that we already
learned
that witches are are like so to say
descendants from Gods was it well didn't
we know that since the
beginning that that's what witches were
in this
game except the
truth yeah they are so but now they're
saying am ATI which is a God right
uh but they're putting it like as if not
all the witches are are
that so it's kind of confusing right now
pberry didn't know okay so we had that
Knowledge from maybe from the
intro but she didn't
know but then are other witches in this
game not
DS maybe we'll find out a bit more to
clear up the misunderstandings
don't worry it will open itself for
you it will just fall apart like
that it's my
presents
okay wait I'm almost dead can something
somebody heal me please
bubble
[Music]
uh I will be transported by a freaking
like baby
basket which is used normally to get rid
of the children you can't take care of
in Medieval
ages and in load of the Rings
Universe bruh
what okay maybe we
need the
animal how does this
work oh
no what okay I don't know
what I'm I'm I'm opening it right oh
wait I did did it accidentally
what n that's on
purpose yeah oh
yeah
baz hey lay down pberry come on it's
comfy it looks so
comfy
who what a weird
Transportation Choice
oh
[Music]
down fore
Nathan thank
[Music]
you foree
weird stuff going
on big
reveals this is a really nice location
by the way really like what they built
here wow wow wow
maybe after this blessing I grow up
because I'm strong
enough or so
me me no
mommy M she was in the with me on the
tree
right but it's me maybe it's me
actually looks like me
Lu
what you gave yourself that name girl
remember okay we've heard that
explanation a million times
sorry
Mommy
oh what why is she
so
why why since she get it like she
immediately thought of Anna as her
mother and now there's someone who looks
exactly like her and she's being a big
big dummy
don't you wonder why you see her in your
dreams she even has a name for us
[Music]
for
for he's being real sweet
now for
[Music]
for
fore
foree
[Music]
foreign fore
oh she's got a good crying voice too
[Music]
fore
foreign
foreign spee
[Music]
a I think I oh I told
you I
changed wew we grew we grew up let's go
adult R 18 from now on this stream will
be
[Music]
y I think I might do something crazy
like
agility
wow elusions blessing allows pberry to
overcome death wanting combat upon
reaching zero HP P will be revived like
automatically or do I have to activate
that
bro
what
[Music]
oh spee
different
[Music]
though wow she's
cute
wow cute yeah maybe a little bit more
mature not like crazy mature
wait this is now this is what I'm
wearing I got the same hat and the coat
I I was already wearing the adult
coat cute I like how her the back of her
hat is like dangling around when she
moves m dangle dangle
dangle she's definitely taller even in
the chibi model there right she looks
taller they stretched out the model
[Music]
tarians almost at least
I'm
Jesus that game
FY or a god
Theory that's all it is a theory a god
Theory
[Music]
Oh wait we're
gone I was focusing on the
dialogues no that was not my OBS that
was YouTube that was fully on YouTube
you little
[\h__\h] welcome back welcome back what did
we miss just I don't know where where
did you leave me huh just talking about
I we need more blessings because then we
get stronger we can gather
more of the
scattered Temple Lord dispersed magic
BL the
more Yeah the more we get stronger the
more we can collect the dispersed
magic y
[Music]
look at her oo oo mouth
so Anna was never our mommy huh
okay then what the hell was
[Music]
she second mommy yeah she also kind of
wanted to see us as a
[Music]
daughter we'll see about that
easy exactly
[Music]
cute no that's not where I was getting
at I think she was saying from now on
to yosu
oh we did two chapters today and
honestly I was thinking this is the
perfect point to stop we grew up we
finished another chapter ooh we're
getting a nice
preview the way she's strting
should we be
scared Amen to the Pope
[Laughter]
fore
for foree
he will make her
work against
me in some
way snowfield
o adult
human adult human pyber
[Music]
I mean I feel like we've kind of done
that before more or
less be fine should I dress up as a
knight
[Music]
instead need some warm
cloes
winter Fire
magic once again I suggest Fire magic
[Music]
she's so cute M Mia I can't stop looking
at her cuteness I really like the
character design
ah you mean her the the that one
witch ah now I know who they're talking
about how would we even find
[Music]
her how do you assume that she is
there I need to go for the snowfield to
get dur to Durk Temple but I hear the
cold D is magical and freezes everything
oh well I have to go for the snowfield
no matter what so I ought to just try
exactly that's the
spirit okay so let's get ready to end
this let's
train
[Music]
cute she's still
running cute
well thank you oh yeah Austria win
woohoo thank you for the red super
[Music]
chat now in the level up I already went
all on
agility
[Music]
so maybe
this and
this training time ah this also changed
ah another new
illustration it's it's somehow it's
always this one even when I'm giving it
other options all right
perfect I got this [\h__\h]
[Music]
down perfect bonus
45% nice one and then I think I would
just probably sleep oh
H H
haido don't know if we need that but
let's
go ah did you see your sleeping mask
just
now it has like black Joe's eyes on
it cute yeah I switched the audio to
Korean did you just come in here now or
how did you not notice
oh an outfit she can finally wear oh
let's check it out
oh this
art
W cute [\h__\h] so
cute I got several outfits that she can
finally wear
now this one so this one I cannot oh it
doesn't fit anymore doesn't fit oh
doesn't fit okay this
fits ooh yeah she's definitely stretched
out a little
bit cute and then this one
[Music]
oh yeah that looks good that looks good
cute her hair is so long in this
one wow but I think for a while I still
want to wear the basic one and then you
know we'll switch around
[Music]
again nice lots of progress today even
though we only played for 4
hours we got really far in my
opinion very
productive and I'm glad we got so far in
such a short time because I have to no
than but I'm actually ending at a
reasonable
time which means food might not be such
a big
problem thank
you yeah Super Chat
reading nah it's not about me wanting to
go to sleep sooner I do want to go to
sleep sooner but I also still have to do
some things yeah have to pack my things
as well
I don't know where my things are
anyway yeah I have to fix my sleep
schedule a little bit got to wake up
early
mhm thank you for understanding I
appreciated very
much yeah I am time crunching travelino
yes I'm
traveling um but I have some short
little videos I think
and and then there's a rebroadcast on
Sunday I still need to figure out how
I'm going to do
that but one way or another I'm sure
there will be a rebroadcast of the K on
Sunday so look forward to
that and I'll do my best with my things
while I'm
gone yeah thank you so much for watching
today Wawa grew up finally Wawa is
adult not just adult but I'm a God now
you all know it now you all
know looking forward to playing this
again next
time but I don't know when I have
time we'll see we'll
see maybe
[Music]
might have to take another little break
like one or two weeks I don't know if I
can play it next week honestly we'll see
about
it
yeah okay then thank you very
much yeah the summer is back
really really
packed next week we're getting Fallout
though right what did I say that I don't
think so because I wanted to do a longer
stream on Tuesday but then I realized we
are having a match on Tuesday against
turkey so there is no Fallout next week
I didn't say that thank you thank
you thanks for playing W spring stream
again o me oh thank you good night
you're you're not
like one of the people who worked on
this
right Masa
Masa
death developer
[Music]
son yeah I don't know could be could not
be
football trumps Fallout
yeah H honestly right now by Miles I
really want to watch more
football and I'm kind of worried that if
we win this one
I uh don't know if I can watch the next
ones so I will be very [\h__\h] sad but
we'll see the next the upcoming one I
can watch for sure so we're going to
watch
it turn I'm coming for
you you should be very very scared
because I have been the luck charm of
all luck
charms every time I watch A Match
Austria wins
so it is so over for you turkey you're
going to get
[\h__\h] and in German we
say Al in
[Music]
wa out I'll miss you guys I'll miss you
guys a little
bit see you bye-bye
[Music]
n