[Music]
I'm On Top Of The
World boat bo bo
bo no
please no
please hello pretty Madame I can
got it
[Music]
genius okay
guys what's
up as you can see Callie Ena and I are
having a first outside of the studio
filming in
Japan
go oh my goodness outside in the Wild
For The First Time in Forever it's hot
yeah I was going to ask you guys like
how's how's the trip so far you know any
things that you're doing Etc but then I
remembered it's it's so sweaty so hard I
can't even go outside and do anything
yeah well Japan you know it's it's
always fun to be here and always fun to
reunite especially with you c yeah yeah
well I'm sure there are a lot of things
you guys wanted to do in Japan but today
I wanted us to do something related to
Japanese summer activities so what do
you guys think of when uh you think
about like what people do in Japan by
chance
that's
well I don't know maybe
camping barbecue glamping going to the
beach but I I know like you know there's
also some things that uh are typical in
Japan like horor in summer is very much
of oh yeah like un like unlike the West
you know sometimes here they release a
lot of like scary movies and stuff
during the summer cuz supposed to like
the The Chill from the horr as opposed
to like I guess cool down or something I
don't know about that I make that
connection yeah oh yeah and like
Japanese haunted houses what is it
called it's like pretty uh popular in
the summer as well yeah obakki I think
I've heard of that have you been to any
of those like uh like an obakki or like
Escape game right I've never done Escape
NE neither obakki or Escape g i me I've
been to like haunted houses when I was a
kid but right apparently there is a
haunted house themed real Escape Game in
Asaka and I was told that we should go
in and try and escape from there
together and who told you that what why
can't we just you know go to the beach
or you know go camping cuz I really
don't like horror stuff as you may know
a come on I mean well look at me you
like me right I'm horror incarnate so I
mean you got to be fine with I see you
like that you're very dorky so I don't
see
you whatever you say well you know what
fine you know we'll put a pin in that
I'll get you for that later after we
escape from that haunted house though
there is a big reward waiting for us so
let's just challenge that and then solve
the mystery and then do even more fun
things later how about that Kar can make
a deal with you okay but wait well
promise can you make me one promise
girls all right you girls are obviously
way more okay with horror stuff so can
you please take the lead and protect me
sure thing Ena of the void and Reaper
yeah sure we will right Ena yeah we
definitely will then it will be okay you
got it thank so it'll be fine I mean you
know we'll be there I'll be there to
reap the ghost for you you'll no ghosts
are going to hurt you all right don't
worry ghosts are friend uhuh well then I
guess we'll go guess I'll die let's go
to the haunted
[Music]
house okay here we are oh oh this
doesn't look scary at all oh wait wait
wait wait never mind it looks scary is
is what we're going to do no say no oh
yes
actually get ready okay I I'm mean you
know first time experience for sure
we'll be fun and you guys said you will
lead me so we got you it was fun escape
from The Haunted
[Music]
Manor nice oh thank you well before we
go in let me read the story behind this
haunted house if you don't
mind rumors of a haunted mansion plague
a certain Town everyone who enters will
never be seen again the town experienced
missing person incidents frequently
making this claim seem more plausible
you a detective have been assigned to
this case your job was to verify the
theory that the suspect occupies this
house you've come while they aren't home
in hopes to find evidence in this
so-called Haunted Mansion you and your
team desperately search the dim lit
house for Clues just then a door Creeks
open and you sense someone entering are
you ready not
yet you find yourself whispering in
reply to the horse voice The Voice coded
in Amusement replies I'm coming for you
and thus Begins the horror game of hide
and seek What secrets lay hidden in this
house
why hide and seek Can You Escape before
terrible things happen conquer your
fears solve the Mysteries inside the
house and get out alive will you
succeed o I don't know about that hide
and seek are you guys going to hide and
seek no oh really I think you know
they're they're saying people who enter
never leave again so I think it's a bad
idea for us to enter no we definitely
should go but what if we can't stream
anymore no I mean I'm sure they have
internet Hey listen the only way that
you're dying Kiara is if I allow it to
be so I won't allow it to that is true
no it it really doesn't depend on you
I'm
Phoenix hey let me feel like I have some
control here okay jeez uh but yeah you
guys can go like I want to continue
streaming we've been whole alive so I'm
going to go get some ice cream okay so
no you don't no you don't no you get
back here I want cookies and cream get
back here both of you we're going in
we're going in okay let's go MRI Kiara
and Ena will s the mystery let's
go on go come on come let's go all right
here we go oh no
[Music]
no this is
exciting watch out for the step oh no
time for cooking
ooh kitchen time okay that's not scary
yet yeah I'm here to illuminate the way
that's not scary That's a classic
kitchen ooh they got a nice rice cooker
too
let's go it's so cute ready for some
Gohan anything suspicious in the fridge
no or what is it called microwave I'm a
bit of a dummy okay start game start
there's something interesting in there
oh yeah there is something it looks like
a picture or a piece of something inter
maybe let's arrange it on the table okay
yeah that's that's what I do oh there's
another one there's a smart person over
also there's a cupboard that's open here
I'm going to open it a little bit
what the they did that on purpose those
SS those sobs check it why is I found
another piece though W well there like
what they're doing jump scaring
me yeah yeah yeah give that dra can we
speedrun this can we speedrun it let's
go maybe we
can all the maybe the last one there's a
jump scare in the last one probably
careful no why not I've played enough
horror games to know how this goes
anything in the sink under the sink how
about nothing how about snoops is that a
rat trap down there oh yeah definitely
for catching small
Critters try get inside it I don't know
if you can open you can't open the
bottom part but maybe the top part let's
give it a prank oh there's one in there
oh nice you got to reach your hand in
there going the dirty
trash snoops oh oh you ranged it already
nicely where would this go don't know
yet I'm but I guess it's a side piece
Let's see we can't touch the random one
thing of water in there oh there's a
coat chairs did we check the coat I
don't think we
did the
coat oh yeah somebody's yka surely it's
in the coat H let's see into the pocket
Maybe please don't be like bugs or
something weird NOP nothing in
there oh is that door open I don't want
I don't want to somebody else I'm brave
as I'm brave as heck let's do
it
jimu is there body is there a friendly
person just a lot
of what okay there over there though all
right so who's brave enough to go grab
it get go get it
girlsa of the Void go grab the piece
okay did you guys open the rice cooker
yet to clean that no I haven't actually
clean your showers every time definitely
get that hair out of the drain you know
you're going to ruin someone's day if
you don't I'll I'll open the Ros clo all
right do it for you
must okay no nothing I mean it was a
good try yeah it made sense to me to me
too well let's see let's see the pieces
we have so far is it on oh I got it oh
it's on I think that was all it's done
those are all the pieces it's a
plant
oh what we not a mixer wait wait wait
what where did I come from it's a mixer
it means that we got it it means that
we're smart oh the ghost like maybe said
something to us oh stop looking for me
the ghost is like go towards the pl Sil
this is the key at the bottom of the
fler wait any plants we get out of the
mixer is there a key in there no we
we're not supposed to touch it right
there must be like a tree some plant hey
how about the no the paintings here we
can't touch those there should be a
flower
pot flower pot flower flower I don't hey
wait a minute oh you found something
there's a little guy back here what
remember that rat
trap remember that heos trap right here
it's right
behind you want me to grab it yeah oh
I'm brave I'm brave as heck yeah I'm
super
Brave there it is okay so it should be
inside like pull the pl all right I'll
hold this and then you grab the plant
okay run it oh oh okay nice one
speedrun all right see if you can a key
out of
there it's wrapped real nice nice we got
the key I so I think I know where that
goes okay right over here oh
ah check it I'm an expert lock open
opener sorry it's just hard with the
gloves it's just is a little difficult
Sor hold on a second let me just okay
there we
go did did it now let's put this over
the side yeah got to leave this in here
so open
[Music]
sesame time to get out of here oh
there's a doll oh hello pretty
Madame um very beautiful um hello this
is a bedroom oh oh there's some hiding
places here by the way just make note of
them in somebody
[Music]
said did I scare you take this this one
down here hey you don't get to claim a
spot out of nowhere come on and yo if
you hide under the table someone's
definitely going to find you that's the
oldest freak in the
book no is this what is this no
should we say it yes one two
Mo what the is this
game no please
no please
Santa stop it
yo stop
it it's gone
okay I
think is it
gone I think it's
gone it's gone
are we
[Music]
okay
now no
K now what the what the is happening
what
no no no bye girls I'm going to die I
guess okay
okay I'm more
dead what do I do with
that I knew he was coming for me okay
what what am I locked
in what do I have to solve a riddle okay
well it says um uh
2751 oh okay I'm not going to reals let
me there's a dead person it says
2751 yo yo what
theen where did she go they freaking
they they stole her they took her they
they kidnapped her they killed her yo
what the did they leave anything behind
I'm
okay there's something there what is
that the red red red dot okay do do we
look at the
face
hello okay
okay I don't know what to do I don't
know what to do with
this
girls help me oh no they took a prisoner
oh no I'm here dead person no no no
you're alive we just have to save the
phone is ringing the phone's ring answer
answer that the ancient ones are calling
Ena the ancient ones are calling answer
their call
[Music]
moyy I got
it it was a prank Cod the lock code
2751 and is it wrong hold on no it
should be 2751 and
then oh shoot I'm coming I'm
coming no hang on hang on to me 2751
isn't working
it weird Moon thing here it looks like a
digital clock or something like that
there sun in the moon and I have a red
around 27 51 doesn't work so let's keep
looking around for Clues did you uh did
you did anybody say anything on the
phone youa no it was just a did a call
then oh it's a prank call those sobs I
wonder prank calling us when our friend
is
missing C cie there's another book here
too does it mean anything that there's a
sun on the oh yeah there's a sun on the
digital clock thing it's got a sun and a
moon in the corner okay yeah me I have
that too right the sun is in the top
left corner the moon's in the bottom
right
yeah I guess I'll be stuck here forever
guess I'll die don't worry gu we're
going to save you really we promise
doesn't feel like you're going to save
me so so far just just wait a minute
we're we're cooking we're cooking we're
figuring it out oh I think I got
it will Ena save me really how are you
so
smart did Ena get
it oh got it genius T side let me out
let me
[Applause]
out oh it's so cool in here see person
inside oh yeah I want to see a dead body
de person I love dead bodies it's my
natural favorite thing in the world we
go you see quite often right hello
oh but I still have this thing here look
o is there a secret I just want here
this is the thing that was inside maybe
we needed it maybe it's a key to
something is there a place we can slot
it in see anything
interesting uh a headless animal I mean
I don't know if I call that I opened all
these
you no that's very scary didn't it open
on its own just now no he likes to do
that his favorite thing to do yeah no I
tried opening all these
andig it's not this one can you open the
one with the
shape oh please uh dear GH please dear
ghost please open the one with the with
the shape
inside there may not be a shape
inside open
it's probably the last one that one why
is this doing
that okay okay okay stop stop stop stop
okay so we need the square have we
checked all the hiding
spots not here the back ah wait why is
that here did we miss something all the
way back in here I found the square I
don't know why it's
here what if it opens to new rooms I
guess I only have one choice here Brink
it in there
Kiara I'm wait
please be nice please be nice please be
nice
okay nice Kiana with the keing K that's
why they call it K all right 20 minutes
pass minut are we slow maybe we're a bit
slow that door doesn't have a lock yeah
that was the bathroom we haven't gone
this way have
we follow me girls I have this women's
intuition oh yeah it might just be over
there I trust
youa a totally different door
wow oh no oh no what something
scary there's um well should we go in uh
yeah there's not much space Oh there's
oh there's another a school girl up
there lot of corpses everywhere
please live you go all right I'll walk
but this guy's waiting for
you oh wait there's a note on the hand
oh shall we read it yeah all right
anyone can anybody read hiana or maybe
it's English wait speak English speak
English five out of five if I have that
and that if you hand it to me that and
that if I only had them if I only had
them no more no more I don't have the
kill anymore gra what
five so there must be four more five
others four four others sorry I can't do
math okay I have to kill those who get
in my way if I see you that will be the
end hide hide if you are found while
hiding I won't have to kill you hey
there's another one oh you found it dang
they sure killed a lot of people I'm
jealous all right hold on a second uh
here's three out of five four
notes I have four notes so we need one
more maybe it's in there maybe the final
not is in here we need to go find it the
corpses seem to be
holding
hey what it
do oh no we already found the five out
of five I think it's two out of five you
got it oh
no she encountered
something just move
take than give it a grab all
right wait is that
they were looking through the window
[Music]
ey we're want to run out of time we're
going to die we are going to die but we
should try and find we should at least
try and go down without a fight um but
now that we kind of have the sentence
should we go back together can we maybe
bye-bye
yes oh boy oh no
[Music]
[Applause]
oh it's Hing it's Hing it's
[Music]
he was so happy to see me and his voice
you have a big smile for you he was so
happy he was always
smiling big smile okay I got the key we
can get you did it yeah we did it
that's herea one minute
left the bravest of us all the bravest
of all no you conquered your fears okay
bye by oh he's so happy to have his
toys oh I guess this is the front door
guys oh yeah so we're free now we made
it we made it we made made it yay we're
heroes we're all heroes
[Music]
yay so ladies
what do we uh what do we think about
that experience we definitely protected
TI for sure you liy to me did you think
about us your humble bodyguards from the
dark um you were not uh as much of a
distraction I guess as I thought you
were going to be to the the the Oni I
mean I feel like the Oni stayed away
from me because he knew I was the Grim
Reaper I didn't see once not a single
time that makes I ran across the only on
they were pretty chose me I was like
and they like those are freaking yeah I
I kept on getting
haunted like that one time with you yeah
I kind
of so the oi kind of bursted through
from like a secret room and then K
screamed and ran away I was just
standing there CU it was scary why did
you not scream I just don't wasn't that
SC I was very scar to me I've seen much
scarier things in my life I love that
the ghost was just like oh yes Ena of
the Void excuse me have a good day past
you well I think I have to apologize to
you because I guess in a way I like I
ran away I did you to die I guess no but
I thought he would follow me and he
would run after both of us I kind of
missed my chance
of
like and then like on the way back I was
kind of going you know slowly to hide
and they were see you're were lucky the
Grim Reaper was hiding too or I may have
had to come out and get you guys ni that
would that would have sucked know the
Ancients one and O you know ghosts were
kind of kind of chill connected yeah and
chill with you very lucky but of course
they want to go after the Phoenix Right
may be jealous of your longetivity yeah
he wants also to revive but nuh-uh
you're not getting that Phoenix
Feather so Celly you said there's a
reward after escaping the haunted house
I really want it so I hope it's nothing
scary what is it what is it the reward
is you'll have to
see wait a minute we're going to go get
the reward now okay okay you know hold
on hold on oh okay but I myself am
actually very hungry I was worried about
my stomach growling into the mic I think
we're okay though done that before let's
go eat o
f all right swim me the river swi the
river swim in the river or small
I ha small I sorry the puns continue
even in Japanese
classic our reward for escaping the
haunted house is
this oh that's a
reward
[Music]
right do you know I don't
know I've seen these a lot
though I've seen these boats kind of
floating by when I whenever I've had
like dinner like by the Riverside I've
seen people din on these boats yeah pink
well pink isn't always a super girly
color can be a bad color
too W shut it wao is that for
us apparently we have the best course
meal they have available so
good well is that like a full bar back
there
you know I'm excited about that but I'm
already going to feel kind of drunk on a
boat so maybe I shouldn't drink too
[Music]
much
setan Lely
[Music]
ocean so have you guys ever done uh is
it yak
yak is she right oh yeah both yeah first
time for me too I've always seen people
do it though so I really wanted to try
it myself so chill I love being on the
water shall we cheers hi
compai let's go yay oh this one this
kind of looks like a
taco sh yeah he's got the little the
little flaps should we should like edit
in the little face on yeah good idea
all right Taco it's time for you to go
oh the taco oh me too me too Taco it's
your time taco probably likes it they're
like should have been me this is what I
for probably in the chat right now
should have been me it should have been
me
me so that's roast beef
right vague roast beef with mashed
potatoes and broccoli all right let's
give it a taste
M nice oh oh very soft yeah that's vum
that is
clearly it's not tough at all which is
how you can tell oh is it time for us to
eat a squid wait what's this is it squid
time what is the rule what is that me
and Ena are getting squidy what is that
what is that is that squid the whole
thing all of that isqu sure it looks
like a full squid body yeah yeah it's
squid with r there's like a piey there's
like eggs in it all wow that tastes so
good cuz it's like it's not fishy at
all Ena Ena does this scare you no does
this scare you it's kaga cucumber oh it
doesn't look like cucumber it looks more
like d it's because they don't have the
skin on anymore but in order is like
really really like spiky cucumber is
that what well not anymore that's for
sure they're trying to trick you into
eating cucum from the
Cucumbers oh
pop nice
pop and just like that it's time for
some sparkling Sparkle
sple cheers staff song gave me the most
thank you
cheers W fancy
fancy rainbow fridge Rainbow Bridge you
can't really see it turn rainbow right
now but that is the Rainbow Bridge one
of my favorite spots in toky
actually oh it's anchored at OA Seaside
Park for a little bit oh wait can we go
on to the deck to look around maybe yeah
yeah what's going on out
there
cute how
romantic beautiful up to the top kind of
makes you want to hold hands with
someone
oh how romantic doy doie hey what does
he say again I'm on top of the world uh
I'll never let go wait that's at the end
oh ena's haing me right now guys what
what does he say I I'm on top of the
world I'm on top of the world uh I don't
I'm not sure I'm on top of the
world
I I have received a memo from
stafas let's see
summer night on the deck of yakun is a
pretty romantic
situation so let's play the game here
who is the most romantic contest oh boy
definitely not me definitely not me okay
so each of you pick your favorite view
from up here the deck and number one
think of the best romantic situation
possible it could be with your friend uh
your OSI hono member fans or even your
pet number two come up with sweet and
romantic lines number three make
everyone go
a oh I'll definitely be able to do that
all right so they'll probably be more
like
oh find your favorite spot let's
go H those two buildings look nice with
the clouds yeah in between them oh yeah
yeah very artistic but I feel like we
don't have much time for they'll be
disappearing there's of course the
bridge which is Ion IC I think the
bridge Freedom ladyes also over there I
go with the beach beach beach I'm going
to get those clouds maybe between the I
actually have my
characters waya is with us on the boat
welcome hi win I will think of something
with these two
[Music]
GAA stop leaving your hoodie in the
washer without drying it it stinks I'm
sorry Bubba slobbered all over it it's
not my
fault if you hate me so much I'm just
going to jump into the sea and swim away
wait no I can't live without
you just kidding it's a joke I love you
Amy I love you
[Music]
not Canon by the
[Laughter]
way not
canon I went for the comedy angle
yeah voice I like how she doesn't say
gura she says G I already prepared my
story okay let's
[Music]
see Revival sound SFA
K revives on a beach alone after she
died in a big battle in a different
dimension oh where am I now oh my God
what is this world what is this country
H A I don't know any of these people I
don't think I even speak their language
all I can do is speak bird language I'm
a phoenix after all
maybe if I start my mating dance maybe I
can bring some birds over here and they
speak my common knowledge all right
let's give it a
[Music]
try oh
hello attach him
please who are
you I'm Tak Shana you understand my
language oh yeah yes yes I do of course
I am a very sophisticated peou after all
uh okay what what's your name I am way
pavoni from Whole Life
Indonesia H life
interesting well so you're a bird here
among all these humans how are you able
to communicate with them you know uh
I've studied the languages of course
well you know it just happens when you
live here oh I see you are
very beautiful bird so colorful and blue
can you revive
too no I mean I I don't think I can I've
never
tried okay I shall protect you then
because you are the one bird here that I
found who speaks my language may I
protect you beautiful be lady uh I I I
don't think there's really such an
imminent danger here like you know it's
pretty peaceful oh uh
sure okay I'll protect you with my
shield and my sword and in case you die
I shall revive you with my Phoenix
feathers to pay you back for your big
help okay that sounds unnecessary but
sure t t t t yay thank you
yo and then they lived happily ever
after in the Glorious world of
Earth in Japan yipp
yipp
pun what a romantic story that's my
favorite one best romance since the
Titanic
[Music]
but
Ena oh past Ena is that you of course
actually I'm future Ena no present I
forget but I'm another you what I'm not
alone no no no Ena me and you are the
same person but so it's not really being
with another person but you got all your
friends with you now what look behind
you
[Music]
ana ana come eat dinner with us we're
going to have fun the D machine Park oh
I'm not alone anymore right past future
Ena oh where where' she go but it's okay
it's I got my friends
now
okay watch watch watch watch p p p i I
will go ahead and say that my Am story
was not very romantic so in between the
two of you guys I mean mine I feel like
it's not really romance as in like a
traditional romance it's like a
friendship love you know yeah romance
like you know like a romance is
different from romance romance and while
was you like a was definitely romantic
and the most traditional sense there was
a romantic dance yes there was a mating
dance away I feel like that that gives
gets plus points so I guess that means
the winner is Kiara Kiara's story
PUD K is the most romantic you guys'
stories are really cute too thanks
somebody else take care of the romance
I'm not really when it comes to
Ras I really like this man The View here
is amazing beautiful
it's starting to get darker too you know
the clouds kind of being overcast over
the bridge has its own Beauty especially
with all the ships dotting The Horizon
oh so
poetic pretty s L's
Master dotting The Horizon my heart a
beautiful view yeah isn't it nice but
you know it's kind of romantic because
we have to like hold on to each other
because my hands are short because it's
so shaky on this bow
my romantic W my heart is wavering
because the waves are intense get it is
my heart beating from the of being on
the boat or is it from being or or being
with you that I think it's just the love
isn't the air doie doie doie doie shaky
boat is shaky it's actually not that
shaky boat but we definely no was just
human
[Music]
hey you still missing give us a kiss two
friendship
to come on come on on the cheek on the
cheek on the Teek on the
cheek let's go
youa I'll take it I'll take it I'll take
it that was the most romantic story out
of all of those that should have won
honestly bo
bo bo bo bo bo
whoa I'm
surfing okay and now Kima dance
especially
Kim
Kim call press press four twerk twerk
twerk twerk twerk twerk butt There She
Goes Again with the butt
[Music]
can you imagine 4 years ago be sitting
here
eating 4 years ago it was like
Unthinkable still that we would all meet
up like I mean and me and Cali at the
time I still lived in Japan so I was
meeting with you a few times but yeah it
was like I I was like when will I get to
meet the other girls when we going to
get to meet Ena and so um it was so
impossible back then too because of the
world situation yeah there were a lot of
restrictions it was impossible to and
now we've been hanging out way more
doing fun things like this at the escape
room making memories in Japan I like how
like we're like from all over the world
whole life English is like from all over
the world yeah but our like hot spots to
meet is
Japan thanks to this job mhm
okay girls yes recently we have gained
another generation Justice now 14 cois
Among Us Among Us so okay with those 14
k h is there anything you keep in mind
as a senpai in
Holan kind of subconsciously but I like
to always say hi
and ask if they need any help and stuff
and like I always feel like once we get
a new generation I'm like let's do big
collabs let's do big collabs yeah you
really talk to everyone yeah well I mean
I don't know I feel like we didn't
really get to experience that too much
right like cuz we the first ens I feel
like we were kind of pretty lost and it
was difficult to like talk to we didn't
even have a shared server where we could
talk to the Japanese members we had to
DM them and even that was kind of scary
in the beginning scary bunch of Lost
kids in a shopping mall was so I think
we try to give a very open Vibe open
feeling when new Koh High come in just
you know talk openly like we're already
friends you know true exactly cuz I mean
technically I don't know I feel like it
would be weird for us to not feel
connected as a big Branch we got to look
out for each other you know yeah you
know so far everyone has been always so
happy to help like each other and stuff
so right I want the new gens to be able
to have the the dream come true
scenarios success that we found right as
the first generation oh yeah I hope that
we can help them get there if we can
right ho is a place where dreams come
true
yeah to our K do your best they're doing
great though they are doing amazing but
I think it's uh one thing I think that's
very important is like I know you might
want
to like overwork yourself in some
situations but always pace yourself and
take breaks when you can because if you
want to do this for the long term you
don't want to burn out true that's a
good point I say well
not wink won do as I say not as I
do yeah you're you're a I want to say a
bad example but like you're an outli i
man work is my hobby that's not how
everybody is yeah I love the feeling of
all of us chasing dreams side by side I
talked about this before how about like
if I wasn't H alive I would have never
met you guys cuz are like paths are very
different different we come from
completely different different areas so
100% you know it's very interesting very
sure is I'm glad it
happened we're getting corny here now oh
boy how how am I going to do this
without cringing myself out what do you
like the most about each member that is
in here in this
boat oh my God they're looking at me
though can't lie you're good the sappy
stuff I think you it no it's only when I
stare off into space while streaming
that I start to ramble you guys are
looking at me right I look I look at
this beautiful pitch black scener right
beautiful oh no I see my
face never mind all right I'll stare
into this oolong CH yeah stare into the
Blass let's
see let's start with uh with
kiaha
yaaa if she wants to do something she's
going to do it I think that's cool I
think it's important to stand up for
your dreams doing things the way that
you want to do them and I think if Kiara
has a vision she's like I'm going to do
it this way and I'm going to do it the
way that I want in like an admirable way
you know like it makes me respect you a
lot you always chase your dreams and you
never stop working your hardest to to to
get those dreams you know I'm terrible
at this I can't can't choose the right
words but I respect that a lot about you
thank you I need to be more
assertive I don't know how to be
assertive sometimes I feel like a
chicken not that kind of
chicken I wouldn't know that feeling I
don't know what you're talking
about you wouldn't understand you
wouldn't get
it for Ena ena's so chill I wish I could
be
chill man sometimes I I'm like I wish
that I could just be laid back and plop
down on my floor and speak to the the
creatures of the
Void I don't know if that's a good thing
I think so to a normal person they would
call me a little
pooo maybe a little bit but you're also
so easy to talk to maybe that has
something to do with the fact that
you're like a very chill person you know
feel like I can talk to you about
whatever and I think I think that's cool
anyway
blush blush I'm going to start turning
red
here don't look at me don't look at me
please somebody else go take the
mic
okay for Ena I think like out of myth
you have like obviously the most
relaxing and soothing Aura and I think
like with so many Gremlins and so on
Among Us that is very important true to
um have like a balance within the group
so you feel this like this role of a
very yashi K person and you don't only
yashi your viewers but us as well I
think your presence is always very
delightful and she feels the void
mhm thank you for feeling the the
void so yeah I think I think I that's
that's why people just love being around
you a yeah thank you there you know
there's people that when you're around
them you maybe get anxious or or nervous
or so but I don't I don't think I could
be nervous or anxious around right I
don't get that Vibe at all anxious
anxiety no way ah for C oh my God I
don't even know what there's many things
I could say like about how how
hardworking you are or whatever feel
like I don't do anything and I think
I've told you these kind of things many
times before that you work too hard to
and and also that I've noticed that the
more members join the more you are like
the most active when it comes to
creating this camaraderie and making
everybody feel welcome immediately
including them in any project you know
and and just have them feel at home and
safe and like at ease you know they're
so cute I can't help and you also like
always when when we come to Japan you
always make sure that there's something
fun planned activities for everybody to
bond and stuff like when we went
painting that was fun core memory for me
that was really nice I I like the
results we had with that and I think
that did indeed make us Bond I think so
too it was fun getting to do something
actually like fun and relaxing together
we don't always get that opportunity cuz
we're Idols you know we're singing
dancing training practicing you know but
as we said before like whole life
English is scattered all over so I think
it's important that when we get together
that we make use of the time we have
together do something fun together so
yeah I'm glad you think that I do want
to try to do that more often it sounds
corny and very obvious but it's fun to
have fun together I know that that's
that sounds really lame in the same vein
of like people die when they're killed
it's fun to have fun with everyone to go
I'm glad you think that thanks last but
not least seg into the I guess from
like I'm never the type of like actually
like invite people to do stuff right I'm
always the you know waiting for to be
invited or something I really appreciate
it when Celly just was like yeah let's
do this and that together like these big
projects and stuff and knowing how much
workload she has too like the passion
and dedication she has to her job and
like to be nice to everyone I feel like
it's just really it's a really difficult
thing to do to balance everything I do
that I think you've done so well and
you're doing such a great job thanks I
really admire that about you like how
you're able to balance so many things
Kelly's like very
FL or maybe a little bit she getting red
yeah you're doing great things and I
feel like it'll go to even like Greater
Heights going on so always cheering you
on I apprciate and waa like one of the
things I really admire about waa is like
the grit she has like to get stuff done
and like try new things and get things
to work try you know when stuff doesn't
work out you don't give up you you know
always try to find ways to get it to
work and stuff never gives up I think
that's like something a lot of people
are missing of using to have like the
grid to actually like even if you fail
you try again again again it's like a pH
you know is the last person I'd ever
expect to give up on anything that she
wants to
do yeah I I but I know I know how you
must feel like oh maybe that's not true
cuz you have your own self-doubts but
for us on the outside though that's what
we see when we I me I know like yeah
like whenever stuff fails like for me
too like I feel down and stuff but then
like even when I see K feel down like I
know she just Rises back up she's like
okay go next you know all the times I've
been like ah forget it this isn't
possible I'm over it I can't accept it I
can't it has to it has to work well
thank you admire that
thank out of nowhere gosh I'm over here
like I'm literally over here like
putting my fingers together like
like I'm chill oh my gosh let's work
super hard and get Holo to be even more
Global how about it yeah let's go let's
[Laughter]
[Music]
go
go think it's going to be
quiet worlding for
cheerfully meting to
Heart hey hey hey hey hey he hey hey
hey from a dream swep up into a stream I
make a wish and wait for my how will we
conect in this front we're turning
through SE no one's
ever colors bursting like
stars
and energy that cared
Uso each new debut brings mirle to life
sure got to take that chance we're
running no stop straight to the top
that's
right we're ready to change the game a
shimmering showcas creating a new place
where we can shine day by day sparkling
St through
inter get ready to cross the
W stage
gooss the SE endlessly follow me and we
the
[Music]
P Break okay breaking through we know
we'll fig out a way to clear each
towering Char sharing all our we any
challenge
smile face Smiles everybody will L our
hearts as we search
across no matter where we are no matter
how we can be start let's
[Applause]
go together everybody I want to T wish
waving out story share the futes that we
can see making them
reality take my hand and reach for the
screen
all we
need our hearts and soul all fulf in the
world
[Music]
we we're ready to seize the day tring
the pathways discovering highways to
everywhere step by step gather stories
that we can share get ready to Le away
with this generation a shining sensation
of dream UNF let's Friends making a
moment of History
joyfully
follow our Legend grows and
continues beautiful we'll car on
Starting Now setting Hearts In Motion
connecting on
the
world oh
yeah that
was nice
one that was fun oh we burned nine
calories oh yeah nine only nine they
don't consider that we've been
dancing that was fun that was a
good it felt like we were getting the TR
traditional tourist
experience and that's crazy for me cuz
I've lived here for quite a while
honestly I never I've been to Tokyo so
many times but I've never like did this
so it's a new experience that I didn't
know was missing out on thank you staan
for planning this for us and putting us
on a nice boat and into a nice Haunter
house thank
you really like you know like we always
do a lot of like reminiscing of old
times but like doing that well we're
doing fun activities is like
refreshing is that fireworks going on I
hear fireworks but I don't see them I
wish they'd pop off behind the uh Sky
Tree cuz that would be very romantic so
the sky tree is the fire maybe the
fireworks is the Sky Tree we saw along
the way W this would have been a good
place for the romance thing I wish I
could have done my little amam hot skit
right here it's kind hard to see stuff
cuz it's kind of true enough yeah well
well well today we had this beautiful
fun uh together and I really cherish and
appreciate it but what's uh what's
coming up for us uh we have a free d
lives right here anniversary
3D when is it could it be
tomorrow yeah nice is it tomorrow it
seems to be
tomorrow well we're currently in the
past right in the past you guys are in
the
future it's going to be great we worked
super super hard on it so I hope
everyone really looks forward to it
practicing plenty even now so
sore hope you guys look forward to it
thank you for cheering us on for the
last 4 years yes four is a great number
it's a long number in theut yeah thank
you everybody for watching hope you had
a good time we will continue our journey
forward into the future um for a
thousand years for a thousand years
let's party tomorrow let's party let's
celebrate
ourselves all the hard work put in we
don't always get to do that back to the
fans for training
us see you tomorrow tomorrow say
tomorrow together
yeah
one byebye byee see you peace
[Music]