oh if you forget to let us in the
burger one more time i'm going to fire
you
[Music]
um hello oh heavenly kick in the key and
welcome to kfp to you
you don't look like a normal customer to
me oh are you one of the new employees
starting today
great we are lacking some stuff today
unlike chicken nuggets
then we better get you started right
away all right
[Music]
the screen please
wonderful welcome to kfb 101
how to become one with the bucket
today's topic is going to be australia
wink
in the beginning i did not want to make
it too clear where i was from and
avoided talking about it
but one still early day during a drawing
stream i accidentally revealed it
but once i'm back in austria if i
if i um
yeah whatever
it had to happen eventually australian
yes
i am australian
i i am from australia mate
after that i just kind of rolled with it
saying i was from australia to at least
not directly say where i was from
but i thought besides the fact that my
english isn't perfect anyway it would be
clear enough that i was joking since i
also winked every time when i mentioned
the word
australia australia
australia australia australia us
australia wink wink australia australia
australia australia
australians
australians australia australia
australia australia those australia
australia australia australia australia
australia
[Music]
sometimes though the joke didn't quite
land so well though
uh yes of course i'm from australia by
the way totally ignore it i mean that's
a that's the flag of australia don't
mind it
that's the flag of australia yeah
and in australia we eat raccoons
a country that's famous for its snow i
think of australia there's not a single
poisonous spider that exists in
australia yes australia has no wildfires
yes yes yes australia has neighboring
countries yes i'm from australia i know
english very well i'm from australia our
first language is german that's why i'm
not from australia but from australia
yes australia has no ocean people are
asking me to speak in an australian
accent you want to put some shrimps on
the barbie barbie we got a ciggy we're
going to go down to the arvo later and
you want to get mru if we look at it
from an australian point of view this
point of view specifically uh mozart
from australia oh lived in right that
house we made an australian citizen
right here it's my first time in
australia
trying to clear the confusion i added
fake australia to the mix which was
actually the real australia
japan japan fake australia wait which
one wait which one do you mean
whoever lives in that house that was
liara not kiara liara is from fake
australia i want to go to the fake
australia and go diving like i want to
visit the fake
no no link the fake australia you're a
fake australian i knew i knew i don't
know
it didn't quite clear it as much as it
made it a bit more confusing
from australia by the way originally my
australia
isn't it from eu oh my god do people
maybe really think i'm from australia i
whenever when i'm in japan i miss
austrian food and when i'm in austria i
miss uh japanese food i don't know i
don't feel like saying australia today i
feel like i'm confusing so many people
this is the story of a friend of a
friend
my friend likes whole life and is very
aware of what i'm doing and the friend
of the friend also kind of likes whole
life so my friend
says oh okay
austrian right and he says uh
no no no she's australian like dead
serious
should i stop with my let's try the
other thing some people miss
misunderstand
and what you just saw was the point
where i thought i should stop playing
around with it maybe even though it was
a great beam and fun to joke about it uh
i don't live in germany and i don't live
in japan where do i live australia
no no i don't
um
i do not live in australia it was a joke
okay
it was a joke that i've been saying for
a year please
i need to correct myself spread the
information
i am not actually living in australia
i live in austria next to germany it's
in the middle of europe and we don't
have an ocean we don't have a beach
we just have this
[Applause]
so many people really thought that i'm
from australia so i need to stop it i've
been misunderstood completely i thought
that made it really obvious like every
time i said australia i winked yo every
time i said i'm from australia is that
that kind of suspicious guys does that
does that not tell you anything that i
always wink when i say australia out of
all the things
so
what do we learn from that kfp
that i am just too good of an actress
bloody hell mate you're looking gorgeous
that my english is too good for my own
good our english is superior to young
and austria is not well known enough
that's not german it's austria it's not
the same thing that's just two little
people watch my full streams
the newbies i'm confusing the newbie
whatever it is the days of australia
wink are kind of over
and remember
there are
no kangaroos in australia
and in german we say au veda
[Music]
fun fact in australia we only have the
grades one two five and in germany they
have the grades one two six where's the
rest of them where's three four
uh