foreign
[Music]
thank you
this is
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hello sorry
I'm waiting time with froggy Wawa is
always always very long
how you doing doing
[Music]
wow wow wow the loading screen of the
game already has so much music going on
but you don't hear it yet now you hear
it can all get off
ah how's it going how you doing baby
frog
I'm doing very well thank you oh ah I
wanted to show you
um there I have wait let me fix the chat
first
there have been some improvements
again every day wow wow wow you you can
really honestly see how my staff
my stuff yeah has been so behind this
project
every time I stream there's some
improvement at all
[Music]
so uh one thing I've noticed and I think
you guys noticed too is the mouth shape
was a bit weird but like sometimes and
especially in certain
um expressions and it bother me too we
were trying to figure out why so now we
found out and because it's so noisy
and uh it should look better now get all
so for example
uh uh um I think the most noticeable is
like when I have a sad face ah
I don't know I don't know if you noticed
but the mouth is like
oh opens
um better now
and same with angry
uh uh like before I don't know how to
describe it but it was like
I don't know I don't know you know what
I mean
oh
yeah I feel like my mouth opens more
um
yeah yeah it didn't even bother you well
now it's better though
I think
[Music]
wow
that's pretty much it though look I
thought it was um important because it
um bothered me too so let's go here with
a big face big face get all holy [\h__\h]
why is the loving skin so noisy
what's going on
is this 16 to nine get off
as always I'm wondering no this is not
this this might be
so noisy
[Music]
ah
oh
[Music]
has anyone of you guys ever played this
game before
any bunny
logo
we are you know in a weird web P format
what'd you say no
answers the answers
no no Heavens heavens
I haven't no yes it's great
no no okay most people haven't yeah but
um the ones that have uh seems to really
recommend it oh now I wonder
I wonder if it's better to play in with
a controller if it if that's even
possible it should be right yeah yeah
I just my language kid all thank you
[Music]
controller okay I wonder if it reacts to
my controller
wait a second
well it is like a platformer so
controller would be better I agree you
know
and also the game was probably like five
hours if we do well
um here's my glass right here it's
probably five hours so it might get
pretty late for me so I might not even
read super chats today again sorry but
it shouldn't be too bad in championship
piling up cannot
[Music]
because I don't want to split it up but
I'm also I'm also gonna force myself to
finish it if it's if it doesn't uh
motivate me to finish it
all right let's see please react to me
no no okay on it
oh oh another okay okay I'll get them
oh [\h__\h] now on how to how to use this uh
B
back there you go there we go continue
I've never played it before though
is this music
coming from
[Laughter]
[Music]
a lot of what was playing in the
background was a video a gameplay video
that's why it was like doing so many
noises
okay now it sounds way calmer
again
well well I'm still new to this
streaming World style and things like
this happen why does it say continue
now she's looking at the gameplay but oh
[Music]
dog hello everyone Peppa
I'm looking down so much today I feel
like
I changed some settings
I'm not there
changed change some settings yesterday
because I was experimentating
uh maybe maybe it's just
no
not necessarily oh well it should be
fine
[Music]
hello Peppa so this game um on First
Site uh if you just look at like the the
cover or so you may not really think
this is a game about frogs but in the
end the whole life the whole world
everything is about frogs you just don't
just don't
you just don't think about it right away
but if you think about it more and if
you look around more if you open your
eyes then you will see unlimited frog
Nation everywhere understand
frogs say everywhere frogs are part of
your life of everybody's lives your life
my life your life you're yours and yours
and yours and yours and yours and yours
and yours
behind you there might be a frog just
right now yeah behind you look behind
you
and on the side right next to you on the
right side there might be a frog
and if you don't see it then you have
not opened your eyes wide enough to
clearly see frogs
these are from here behind you there is
that see it works it works
especially has a front behind them right
now at this very moment so everything I
say is the truth and everybody else who
doesn't have a frog behind them right
now they're just yeah they're just not
not enlightened yet which means we have
to play more frog games to you know be
enlightened cattle
mega zombies
um
foreign
[Laughter]
I will say
so hello hello Peppa wait wait I'm in
the wrong window hello Pepper
[Music]
hand tracking kind of pissing me off
today all right thank you for coming to
my talk professional friends engineering
101 we're gonna learn how to make
friends
it's quite helpful you might be
wondering what is a professional friend
now I think of it I guess I have a lot
of professional friends get off
not alive
who brought me to this Dark Void
yeah let's get you out you should be in
a beautiful beautiful beautiful pretty
sparkling pond with other
with other frogs kettle
when will we get the complimentary lunch
good question complimentary lines yes
I will I will make sure you get some
fried flies fried or fries
I will answer all these questions in due
time but first let me show you this
[Music]
oh
what is that meow
says meow
um
it's a coin also no it's cash money
I get your friend I get you
but how did I get this money well my
friend being a friend of course oh
friend keep money
my friends don't give me money Carol
do I have
fake friends around my friends right
fake because they don't give me money
do I need to get new friends who give me
money
the real friends the super Chatters I
met along the way
um
[Laughter]
let me show you hey you there
cute I'm very sad no one you said
it's all right buddy I'm here for you
I am less sad now and also a compelled
to give you money Carol oh is that easy
what it's like a
he's a master of friendship but a master
of my money making oh thank you thank
you friends get off thank you I have
learned that you guys are my real
friends
hello thank you super channels
thank you all again for coming to my
talk
you too can become a professional friend
today oh you guys are my professional
friends or yeah and I am your
professional friend too
and remember helping people is its own
reward
nah everyone what is the money that
comes for
let's be real that's what you just
taught me froggy
oh is this a train or a bus
looks like a train bus
Here Comes Nico wait there's a frog in a
logo I never noticed that that shadow
where the speech bubble comes out of
that's a that's a frog
I didn't realize all right let's see
it's a 3D platformer but with 2D
characters
it's really cute that's that's me
for today moving uh-huh gonna jump yes
oh hey neighbor yeah but the thing is
beside the frogs and this cute girl
everyone else is like a like a
somebody's persona
they all look like somebody's first show
now
but okay I'm here for the frogs hey
neighbor you just moved in right I got a
feeling you don't plan on staying too
long I gotta say this place is pretty
cozy oh
who knows maybe I will grow on you
oh I should probably go there's his
friends
see ya oh let's go one is up here if
there's milk can I drink how do you wait
oh there you go
milk drink wow
oh
can I knock it over ow
that was uh okay I see I'm getting to
learn the oh wow
controls whoa
but whoa
okay this one does not bounce
oh the camera I can look at everything
everywhere kettle
y
um
hello I'm Peppa and the executive
manager at tadpole Incorporated oh
I'll be handling your job application
before we can start we need to make our
way to hairball City
you're both sitting oh it's because of
all the furries here
can you talk to the dispatch about
getting us here oh yeah Paper Mario yeah
yeah it's like similar to like like you
know how it works with 3D x2d um
all right let's visit the furries
hello wait are you you're not the right
one are you
hey hello frog
hi frog went on to that Tower over there
to have lunch
is that one just high for up because
he's on a high building and you're just
low frog because you're low on the
ground
but he left his lunch bucket here can
you bring it to him to carry the bucket
just bump into it okay
uh oh oh I'm carrying it okay what's new
can I look inside oh
oh interesting look I can like this is
so cool I like the mix of those 2D
Infinity Graphics that's kind of like a
cute gimmick Kettle oh you need a coin
to open it there's a there's a pretzel
inside
you see that thing over there that's a
pretzel brittle
um
throw it off but where did it go
oh I lost it
uh can I have it back oh yeah okay okay
so if I press that again I let it go and
it disappears forever all right all
right
[Music]
this is kind of you know the train
coming out of the water and all that
gives me
Spirited Away Vibes Skittle
I didn't see what you put your name
why is it showing me inputs for keyboard
when I'm playing with the controller
it's so confusing I always have these
issues when I use a controller on a on
um
steam game
why what is space
I guess it's just jumping yeah okay I
already know how to do that that's
that's just X I guess
what the hell
whoa
whoa I want to get oh oh I can just
climb up if I just stay
can I
no wait how do you
I just can't I can hold on to it but I
can't I don't know what I can do I can
do a wall jump and then
there you go can I get the money now
you found me yeah Mario can't do that he
will sink but this girl this chick or
boy
they like think they don't think yeah
they don't think they hold on to that
you saw you you can't get but right yes
is that my lunch thanks for bringing it
to me so cute so cute thank you
apparently you can even like meet like a
thousand frogs different frogs in this
game and there's an achievement for it
but I guess we're not aiming for that
Ella
the soda cannons Will Blast you off
wherever they point to Aha be careful
blast frog okay very simple where was
that other frog that was supposed to
meet though
one with the glasses
okay we're back here
fine with me that's really good I missed
the important frog
a thousand Frog's Dream wedding
no no no no no
candle huh
what is that
it's just again telling me I know okay I
don't have to do that space and then e e
is my Square I think
this
well oh
why is that on the Frog
I feel like I missed him
there's one up there
okay
I'm a lady I should have I should have
hidden my face you know you know when
I'm outside get home
I hope you know I don't actually I don't
I don't sneeze into my hand I sneeze
into my you know I'm gonna turn my hair
into my elbow the inside of my elbow
because if you sneeze into your hand you
know you will touch things and you touch
people and then it's disgusting yeah
every time I see people either sneeze
without like sneezing into something
or or while sneezing
uh into their hand it always makes me
like
like that
okay I thought maybe I missed something
up there but what wait wait can I drown
and I'll go I'll go back maybe I miss
them and get off you could just wash
your hands yeah but a lot of people
don't do that okay
now okay okay
do you want to oh I said giraffe hello
hmm
[Music]
the dab yeah dab sneeze dab while you
sneeze and you're cool and and you
protect others from your germs
do you want to call the Hairball City it
will cost one coin to clean up the sand
on the real sand
that's water I think I'm pretty sure
it's water but okay
all right no no I want to
um
wait no no
ah there we go
[Music]
yeah but when I stream you know in my in
my little room
I just sneezed sneeze it all out
yeah the only thing I can get sick is
myself okay no a few weeks ago I had to
move out for reasons I was able to move
into my own place yesterday in this
economy unbelievable I know oh yeah it's
really expensive nowadays and in Europe
especially
like uh lots of lots of increase in
inflation and [\h__\h]
someone I was there also able to find a
job listing in this area is for
something called a professional friends
I was a bit depressed desperate so I
applied they want me to go for a trial
period can we all be professional
friends isn't that like amazing what a
job
you should do something for people and
then give you money what a nice job that
would help like so many people who don't
have a job
okay I really really hope this works out
it has to work out let's go
go
right next to you talk talk to frog
voicemail you have one new messages new
message
hello are you there
why why
won't you pick up uh please come home
we're worried about you it'll all be
okay just go home all right
press one to save message press to
delete all let's save it I mean I don't
know
I don't I don't I don't even think my
voice message thingy has that option
listen up kid
oh dear you have some more wisdom to
share Peppa
as you know you've applied for the job
of professional friend a professional
friend is someone who is a friend to
everybody and who occasionally gets paid
occasionally it has to be every time hey
[Music]
the first time we talked
you didn't make that kind of impression
occasionally will eventually turn into
another one
hmm
however before we can hire you we've got
to successfully complete your trial
period scary stuff right for now I think
we'll just have to call you uh junior
intern French
how does that sound we're closing in on
hairball city which is also
takanasikara's apartment uh the first
step in your trial period you'll do
great I can smell it get all
okay I am already in takanasikiara's
apartment
hello City
well I don't see so many hairballs
[Music]
hello oh sorry for bumping into you yeah
I just got here I mean I got here an
hour ago I'm worried if I go to the main
island someone might try to talk to me
well I even look you hear and still
someone tried to talk to you so it
really doesn't make a difference I think
because I talk to you okay here I guess
we need five coins to get to the next
Island
and we keep on switching to other
Islands
what is this
I need six coins here and two letters
and ten
ten Chihuahua Banger songs oh ten I only
have like five now here we are hero City
there's a lot to do in this place and we
need a handful of coins if we want to
make it to our next destination rabbit
that's a good place to start is up here
that guy looks like he could use a
friend rivet okay wow that's pretty far
I'm pretty up high but let's go and I
got one of these tapes
this game is crabs too and this one is a
cheering crab cute whoa
ice cream no that's sand cream
that's probably sad just with some yeah
chocolate chips nice frog a patient frog
if someone is trapping around the fort
too long you can all walk away from the
conversation just hold any direction for
long enough
oh
I just did that interesting
here I don't think I can swim that far
probably but maybe we'll get there with
like a Canon Kaboom Canon Canon
Canon
Brittany
do you see that big Dolly winter bin on
the horizon that's where turbine town is
those birds have the best snacks I tell
you Birds
I don't know if I want to go to the bird
town
hey yeah I see in your eyes
Oh I thought his nose the fury passion
of a true big volley champion who big
volley is a sport I myself designed
it's quite simple make sure the ball
doesn't hit the send don't get your
hopes up though no one has ever managed
to pass the ball back to me more than
four times
oh is that a challenge Rock hello I
can't talk to you
yeah apparently this game also has like
frog American knives by the way I saw it
when I when I bought the game
they have frog merchandise and I'm like
considering getting it
say
wow who the hell did I manage to send it
back to you wow I didn't even aim
okay
did this count
no I don't think so did it
okay one
no probably not let's go
oh freak
oh
I think it always automatically goes
back to him and he never moves
[Music]
focus focus
get up
this time this is the one
[Music]
you know
one
[Music]
two
three
one more one
oh thank God finally
yeah
hello you seem really shooked
you're amazing at this here's a gift
make sure to invest into your big volley
future
wow
money big money I want to invest in Big
Money future not Big Valley future
Frank Frank
press this button if you want to check
on all your stuff there's always more Oh
see now it gives me a controller
problems
I don't appreciate the stuff you've
already got oh thank you
no no frog what's this frog wearing
this frog probably can so
it's okay
that is so adorable has a swimming hoop
thingy is
[Music]
stop interrogating me
I mean you could swim here too is this
salty water too
butterflies
I am collecting butterflies now
oh one more
there's really a lot of frogs in this
game
if they look look [\h__\h] [\h__\h] traveling
frog if they if they advertise it
you know with more frogs instead of the
personas
maybe maybe it would be in the top 10
games of this year
I mean I mean you know what browser
better than everything
hey you're the kid who just moved here
right
um
[Music]
going on in England I hope it's not too
much of a bother oh this neighborhood
get on
is that so oh
look
there's a another butter could I fly
like a butterfly
oh tunnel
let's see stuff
what
it's dark and the sound is like
different in here that's cool
I found the number two let's go kiddo
and an element of course it would be
better than Elden ring
now because Elden ring also doesn't
advertise its game with frogs
beginners amateurs
I need to get better at the jumping
seven eight how many are there nine
oh
ten
eleven how can you order hello I'll talk
to you
what are you covering for
oh
oh can I like plant it no I find that
outfit oh
what is this
what is is this like a secret game
I understand I feel like there should be
a reason why I'm able to pick it up but
let's see what what it is oh oh there's
a tape over there all right let's try to
get it
foreign
how do we get back
wish
oh skill oh Apple where's your Apple up
there
um a transparent Apple
what is the meaning of these
oh there's more Apple here and and
yummy maybe I can Grill them
oh oh apple apple or apple I have a
butterfly I have an apple oh
Apple will fly
I want to please them get up there
right now
there we go are they important examples
I'm like a nice view to the to the Frog
statue over there and having some sweets
oh my God I envy you guys
ah frog life is just best live I mean I
don't envy you because I I'm living that
frog life obviously more butterflies
but I'll just collect everything I see
oh and then one and two and three and
four we played that in school too
we were showing off our platforming
skills back then already
[Laughter]
take a photo
Vlog frog cook
Hey kid don't mind me I'm just the
camera guy okay
hello there sorry kid I'm so basically
just take a selfie with you you weren't
going to ask for a selfie don't you know
who I am I am and uh bless me from
blessing is blessed bites I'm a food
blogger mainly focusing on bugs I came
here to try hairballs to these famous
butterflies oh
hey don't you happen to have Freddy
butterflies do you ah they're for you
all right I'm gonna have 30. oh
but I'll get some more
here uh 19.
yeah 20 and let me get one more I should
have gotten that one first
what
it's been supposed to be perfectly for
an optimal shade enjoyment I should sit
down and check my virtual pets
if I stand on the bench long enough I'll
sit
why is it
why is it on the side it's cut off
the Tamagotchi
I'm doing a look at it properly
it's normal
I pressed something but it doesn't can I
can I move it can I I don't know
glitch
maybe only on this bench maybe there's
other benches
last week my dad took me aside and said
Son someday he'll take over our sandwich
shop I don't want to be rolling
meatballs for the rest of my life so you
know what I said forget about it
oh because I'm sitting and came back
again oh should I restart the game
does it have all the safe let's see
um continue it says is that a saving
mechanism
oh
that one is hard to get
[Applause]
is it the resolution oh I mean it's 16
to nine though
maybe maybe restarting would help
foreign
I came here just for the butterflies to
be honest
what is this place
nice nice rooftop garden you got there
get all
right there we go we got 30. amazing
when can you come see me for a little
something no wait I want to see
something
Graphics
um uh
um I don't know what I mean I don't want
to make a smaller
hmm
[Music]
now I reset the position on my monitor
yourself
can't go higher and I can but
um also I like it to be this size so I
have to chat next to it
foreign
can be mean to you right
hey talking love you has been a lot of
fun bro
I think I think I want to try going down
for a little bit
you can have this if you want
me I like your bearing also goodbye I
just kicked him off the roof he's dead
now
another dead body
but yours truly
I did that I'm I'm proud of myself yes
what if there's fall damage from me
though
oh so badly butter for us
oh
Let's test it
at least that distance didn't do any
damage oh give me money do I smell bugs
give it
that was terrifying
do you need the Snickers or something
like oh my God
holy [\h__\h] kettle
cool
they're Lord oh
my that was delicious thanks sweetie you
accept my credit card uh I might have
some coins somewhere here you go
[Music]
[\h__\h] I feel like you know I could expose
you online for that behavior but let's
let's let's let's continue
these grades are quite sticky from all
the summer they've been carrying oh kind
of like what does that mean stick on to
them I can stick onto anything though
me love snack oh snack yes especially
snack yum bar with one sea snack um
that was a joke I'm just green
oh no oh no oh no no I'm supposed to be
having my job interview in this building
but it doesn't have a door oh no no no
no no the building has no door
well let's make a door
is this is a quest I guess not
a building with no door that's
interesting wow I guess we're done here
whoa what so many I can I can get those
what
oh some of the bushes or all of them
if I wrestle through them
no not all of them I think
that one was sparkling I think oh this
one's yeah Sparkle Sparkle
okay so the ones that sparkle give me uh
apples
okay
oh it's white is this the door perhaps
it's an interesting way to place a door
and entrance Door
okay you do you ah wait wrong direction
wrong direction I thought there was only
one direction
[Music]
yeah
what something wrong with that
can I still collect them oh
hello that's a frog hey you found me
seeing you gave me an idea for a riddle
want to hear it how do you spell your
neighbor just two letters
are you write two letters
I mean you know like actual letters that
you like send proposed for mail oh
um I don't know
[Music]
oh my God
I need to give myself some air it's
getting hot in here
look at all okay look at her
stop you oh yeah
what a cutie but Duty you are
[Music]
sorry this is like oh distracting me
what a nice frog hello
I joined this whole kind of soda in a
single day and then after that I made
the last most awesome there but no one
was around to hear it so you probably
won't believe me that's so bad but at
least I enjoyed it and that counts for
something
yeah good for you I don't like verbs I
don't really like it when people around
me burp and you know
I think this is where ship stock looks
like they mostly deliver more soda lots
of fizzy folk around here oh you like
the soda
more apples
I wonder if they come in handy as well
I like I like soda even though like I
have a bit troubles drinking the bubbly
soda
too fast at least
especially like the more bubbly the more
yeah difficult
so like Coca-Cola often the like fresh
one served in the restaurant also
they're like especially bubbly
especially sparkly I can't drink it too
fast because my nose won't be like yeah
you guys have the same
yeah yeah yeah yeah it goes to my nose
yeah
I go like
foreign
drinks at all oh
my dog yeah
[Music]
that's why I don't drink soda oh I've
been like that at first but then overall
oh
you like flat soda
I will get canceled for this but yeah I
don't mind drinking Cola after it stood
or after it like got a bit flatter if
it's like completely flat then I think
like for Coca-Cola for example
yeah I used to drink it completely flat
but nowadays I don't enjoy it that much
anymore you know
cancel life no no
no no I was just you know trying to
share some stories about Kiara too
because you know you guys seem to miss
her a little bit or even though you
shouldn't get off
you can use it
no she cannot
no
yeah I don't want to waste it right it
was just a little bit flat and no
problem
um
I want to talk to you
I lost my blouse at all but how am I to
fish now I know how about I tell you to
my life
do I look like a tasty
something for fishtail you can jump in
and grab the fishes what do you say just
bump it to me into tight enough
keep hope no
okay how what oh oh [\h__\h]
yeah yummy unless that will be my lunch
thank you you want fish though oh
specific fish
hmm
how do I make big jump
oh that's not that's not an either Maybe
I try to push you
go over there
wait there's a there's a solar can but
it goes the other direction anyway
how about here
what is that oh
that's one of the things I said it's
overlapping again this is normal it's my
favorite fish thank you for catching
this looks looks like our flying Visions
are these the flying fishes
okay okay okay okay but you want more
right okay okay
I'll go get it for you
what is that
do you need that fish
let's get it
yes you wanted this one too okay okay
not straight might I help oh
it should be fine it's a common fish
don't worry
Pixar I think is not gonna
not gonna come and get you
here's the long boy
what's the picture of Disney oh [\h__\h]
that looks like a like a little leopard
fish a little creepy do I really want to
keep this one yeah take it take it it
was basically okay so my first instinct
was right
what okay where could be the last one I
see one jumping oh
[Music]
yeah
I'm doing a good job here oh this is a b
no
is this a bee
is this a b
is this a butterfly
so Chic it'll be great addition to pawn
yeah I like this one
is
this a muscle car
okay I did everything you want wait no
there's one monster like behind there
ah oh right here
[Music]
oh cute it's like a goldfish right
I just got in my ocean yeah it should be
better off in the pond yeah wow
is just one more coin if you can't find
what to do comes out of me no I think
I'll be fine I'll see you um also
someone over there
or butterflies I wonder if the lady who
eats all the butterflies would
appreciate a second lunch
so far I'm enjoying this game kiddo it's
fun also by the way apparently it's some
company
um replied to me when I put out the the
Frog schedule and they were like hey we
have a frog game too in case you want to
play it and I didn't see that but
apparently Jenna saw that tweet somehow
and got me primps for it too
so I could play that on oh let's do that
I could play on on
um
Sunday uh instead of frog bath
I already bought frog buff so maybe one
day I'll play that
um
in an off collab if someone ever comes
visit me we can play frog bath because
it's local only and I was gonna try with
parsec but I don't know it was it was
gonna be a little bit too annoying I
think so I just and then I was like okay
let's do kind of okay because I kind of
want to show off myself a bit more and
sing some fractions but there's actually
really not that many frog songs
surprisingly
so now I don't know what I'm thinking
now is playing that game um but that
game is like kind of simplistic so my
next idea is playing the game for one
hour
um while for the whole hour singing
okay
look it's challenged you know
[Laughter]
I feel like that would you know
um
get two flies with one fly catcher
but I'm still thinking about it you know
if I actually feel like not streaming at
all then I might not even stream at all
because I already noticed that I'm a bit
I'm a bit um
exhausted already you know
I can't talk to you huh
what's the gaming on purpose
um I think frog frog copter frog copter
it looked like a game to me where I
could try to sing along to because there
doesn't seem to be dialogue
I saw a movie Once where the
protagonists lived in the lighthouse on
an island attached from the rookers of
the city
oh so I thought hey that sounds perfect
for me does that movie exist can you
think of any guys
turns out it's pretty lonely it's the
first person I've talked to all year but
don't worry about me I've got about a
thousand hours of sitcoms on VHS
honestly yeah I wouldn't mind living
like this
the lighthouse oh it's called The
Lighthouse
I see kiddo all right let's try to get
back oh wait is there maybe I oh
so much that there's some people over
there kennel
beautiful
hello there are you also sitting on a
bench
carrot the roof often skyscraper looks
cozy bro if the building had an elevator
I'd go check it out hey I know what
you're thinking I'm not lazy I just did
a lot of stuff today already no reason
to Tire yourself out right
exactly I mean you're a kitty cat I
think so just do with kitty cat style
take it easy relax
[Music]
we have six already wow
oppressive hello information frog frog
of Destruction that's my title sometimes
you just want to wreck stuff don't ya I
heard that some blocks break if you hit
them in the right spot oh like these how
will I hit them
how how to hit can I ground pound
what
I don't I don't know
also I want to get to the top of the
lighthouse there's someone up there
[Music]
let me try onto the cracks oh that
cracks
good eye Skittle ah
oh my help
how do I hit it though
have fun I don't know how to do a
headphone I okay never mind
well I've gave me nothing unless you
reward me for that no oh yeah that was
the Frog no okay I just wanted to let me
know all right then
let me try to get on top of this
lighthouse
um
I don't know how
maybe a cannon but I mean that that ramp
over there is suspect
um
oh it's quite high oh
whoa whoa Maiden yay hello
oh you look like a an adventurer Dustin
what are you doing up here I'm looking
for places only I can reach
I thought I found it yet you're here too
I suppose it makes you my rival we'll
play if I only mean again just for you
[Music]
is that what that means did I already
explore like most of them or all of that
hmm
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay it's okay I'll go for the
water
[Music]
um
a new rabbit I wonder if I'll meet him
on the other Island as well
because that that was the most difficult
point to reach here perhaps I'm gonna
take a quick look around oh
no okay I thought she still like had
more for me
what about that red apple that one over
there hmm
oh wait there's still something over
there too
more apples
I wanna go up let me go for a hair
there's a crack in the building oh oh
would that open it up oh wow okay I'll
take a look
little
[Music]
Gabby's ah there are three kinds of
points I need them for all four flowers
is way too hard
I was wondering about that
like how do you how do I do
oh I just jump into it what the hell
foreign
[Music]
it's just like
ah
I see
reset please
ah
it's a game
[\h__\h] let me do that
oh
what should I know
yeah easy okay
nice cute game like it
I did it for you give me money
I already did it maybe I get the reward
from the Frog
baby
huh
what
one more I need to do another set
over here
behind me what
what
oh there oh
okay see I get we get some some kind of
fall damage
I jumped through it it didn't do
anything all right well these are like
kind of not properly aligned oh well it
works now
hey
froggy wow to the rescue oh
Apple
and pineapple or apple pie
Apple pen apple pie apple pie
yeah that song should not be about
adding a pen to an Apple it should be
adding
Apple to a pie
apple pie
why would you make
Apple pen when you could make apple pie
handed out anymore
I have a pie I have an apple
oh apple pie I have a
I have a apple pie
it's yeah yeah
Japanese meme song
can I take the remaining money to the
other Island I wonder or does it get
like deleted
because that would already be helpful
for the next Island
wouldn't it
like I'm doing apparently a
completionist full percentage gaming
right now that was one more thing I
wanted to do I had to crack the crack
the crack where was the crack Kettle oh
did you see a crack on this building
ah I see it
um
how do I do this
I'll come
I don't have to though
we can already go there's never below
I do not see
where well
or maybe here
below the crap what
foreign
make door make door now
huh
maybe this crack is just decorative
sorry about that I think it's just
decorative
maybe maybe not what about the Apple
Zone did no one want my Apples because
foreign
I thought that's the way to open the
door wait there's a cassette tape up
there oh
how'd you get up there
how do I get up there
oh wow that was so close
don't know what the cassette tapes do oh
I got them
how many of you tackles don't know what
a cassette tape is
I remember like trying to put in the
tape back into cassette tapes back in
the day also my other I never got over
to that Island the Frog Franco Island
how do I get there there must be a
cannon
I want to know
oh are the tapes changing the background
music that I'm hearing
no way
so I really want to know
is there like a secret here
I want to get to that Island
oh
what is that
[Music]
um
swim can I realize I'm just assuming I
can
silly kennel
oh
I'm so used to other games that don't
let me swim forever
there's so much stuff here to collect
is these
The Tackle ink website did mention there
being a frog King he's supposed to run
the company I guess he's a big deal
is that him
can I go in
I need a key
how do I get the key
by maybe clearing every Mission uh on
this map Maybe
hello friend oh don't be nervous
okay
hahaha
cookies
[Music]
I'm curious I could already leave but
I'm curious
in terms of quests
I don't see anything else well maybe him
but was that really a question
maybe I can like
I'll move something aside and papa
there's a door haha
I'm head cutting them but they don't
wait there's a door behind this thing
no oh
Apple
[Music]
can't break the boxes
thanks for the pinky get off
yeah I said there's no entrance
[Music]
maybe it's behind the poster
it must be behind
[Music]
the park I know
all right maybe
maybe it's time to go
oh you're welcome
I want to say I don't care but I really
care about it uh it's bad snack machine
okay
machine
I love snacks oh
that's about it
back yum
maybe if I do it often enough
something will happen
hmm
you Rebel
God damn it
[Music]
secret secret headphones for free stuff
yeah don't try it at home or in real
life
what do I do with all these apples
Kiana frog Palace
yeah
yeah let's think about it next week
well six out of six two out of two
letters
wait there's what about the
and two more taste in this world ah
[Music]
ah
um
yeah I already got two letters I'm cutie
pepper
[Music]
Peppa Peppa Peppa Peppa oh my there are
no coins left or anywhere oh oh
so I did do all the quests
possible quests
all right
I've missed I've missed something but he
doesn't tell me
[Music]
but okay at least at least with an old
quests even though we didn't have to
mama mama
[Music]
let's go next we want to finish this
game event today after all oh [\h__\h]
why do I do this all the time
because yeah
bye
yeah we all need to complete even though
I'm like really really really
tempted to do it
water
is a frog
why
[Music]
ah
ah is that my mommy how have you been
quite kick on and now you can always
call me right no matter what time ever
since you ran away it's been pretty
boring here and you're all settled I
could come and visit if you like for
sure
love you bye we're almost in German it's
a town built from shipping containers
surrounding a big wind turbine ready to
show me what you made of time to be the
best friend you can be yeah
go get him tiger I'm I'm a Frog
no tiger no see not good cow but good
rivet
everybody in town
looks like a lot of containers oh
so many containers
I still have 142 apples
oh I guess I'll return to other Islands
okay so here it is two keys
six coins
will granny tell me that the winter one
isn't oh well I'm sinking I'm sinking
isn't spinning the birdie to be precise
okay the last what's up okay I'm sinking
[Music]
oh
my channel okay I thought it was a bug
seems like I just wanted to show me
what's up here
on oof
I've been dragging in your mail for
these fellows all day and there's still
no ending silently let me help you
go to apples stay the same oh and these
things make me fly
nice
welcome to turbine town named after our
Majestic wind turbine wow it's [\h__\h]
huge the town itself is built out of
shipping containers how did we get them
here
sorry I I saw it it's the after effect
of eating takanashi Kiana
we kept ordering a ton of snacks online
after a while the shipping company just
dumped them on the island container and
all it's very real
school oh a cupboard let me look at you
you have to attack this body you can
never feed me or you can get the squawk
out of my face
[Music]
[Laughter]
what did I turn on
how do you like these AC units
they create a heck of a gun why the hell
are they built like outside like this
frog you see frog dog on the container
on the right side
oh my God but is there so many friends
it makes me happy
[Music]
some turned on and off depending on what
color ah
oh no
big thinking time a little bubble it
[Music]
so maybe something like this was also
hmm
on the other Island
can I use this key on the other Island I
wonder
do I have to use it here
hello another bird wow you look like I
don't know
how to describe that look
you're ascending
a little while ago I got to go on a tour
of the tadpole Inc head office it was
impressive and all but when I asked for
the bathroom was they told me they just
peed in the pond oh gross I ended up
dropping my business on the Play-Doh
[Music]
wait you dropped you probably dropped
two businesses right you dropped your
business with the tadpole link and
another business
like a respectable bird you think
they're better dropping it in the air
and hitting people's heads with that
making them stinky for life
no
full
think of how embarrassing that is for
the person who gets hit
by your stinkiness
Ewa
hello you have a quest for me don't pass
for the White story again
it's funny because Tony
you know are these guys but also means
bird in Japanese so it might be a pun
because there's all the birds here
and then there's the Tony engines that's
probably why they put those here
bad luck
wait she didn't
um
I wonder if that's really true because
I saw white Tony Gates before
in Japan when I was traveling and I was
wondering why it's white
I didn't get a good explanation
but
they never said that it's bad luck
ILY
never been told that is bad luck
hmm
I'll go this side first oh oh no it's
her again you want more butterfly flies
on that
why am I just dump your ass this is
actually the best place to find
delicious green red butterflies thanks
I still have enough Butterflies from the
other color and you don't want those
why am I collecting these apples anyway
the rat out of red paint
[Music]
ing oh
I missed it oh
apple apple
um
[Music]
nice
oh there's I wanna there's a there oh
okay they're kind of repeating these
quests and NPCs huh okay well fine with
me this one was fun
and this way I might be able to finish
the game relatively uh on time if the
games are the same then I know what to
do
oh number one is what oh Burger okay
that was not the hmm
not the red thing let me
good
no he didn't want the ducky either God
damn it
ah I could change this
oh we're smoothing
I didn't realize it was moving
huh
but it stays like this
between the red lines huh
but there's no like splashing inside the
red ah it moves still they move now they
don't stay in the same location I think
because I feel like it moved that fish
come back please
how'd I make you come back I'm not sure
what this does
let me try to that one oh
foreign
over there but also what's how's it
looking here ah
it's a bit annoying now because I have
to rely on the
on the Wind thingies
foreign
shrimp sandiest of shrimp you go into
the Container little guy
okay
they move slow oh just slowly
and the button is Pink
oh and they don't move ah ah when
they're blue oh guys just realize that
now
okay
let's try to get that one on the left
side I guess
let me try I guess I have to like follow
it
okay okay don't go here
[Music]
good aim wait it's a it's a what were
they called again
um
it always mixes up in my head because of
foreign
[Music]
I have to like
jump on it a bit earlier when it goes
back that way
I'm in trouble I am coming from no no no
no and I know what I'm doing
there's a close one here
oh yes what is this
albino corydoras
cute
okay just that one ah wait for me
[Music]
I'm on there can I go from oh wait from
here oh
[Music]
piranha dangerous
it will eat me if we don't put it and
close it
in the container
our second coin here we can't I'll
finish with you so much yeah yeah you're
welcome
what is here
well in the wild is that frog doing what
the frog
no he eats shrimp
is this what Herring happen is what is
this a joke
is this joke you think he's funny
where do I oh
let me do this I can do this yay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
mm-hmm
what are we doing tomorrow by the way I
think a member stream and then we are
wrong right
oh I got that's right I can swim
let's go back
oh that's where I have to go originally
hello there sir
Kelly the engineer my boss told me the
winter spinning but for what I can tell
there's nothing wrong with it the
problem is that there isn't any wind
and we must post to fix that I'm an
engine you're not good what you wanna
help out are you God I don't think
there's much to do if you will see maybe
go ask a runtown
maybe if all the birds gather around the
wind turbine and flap their wings of all
they got maybe then they'll create some
wind
genius solution
[Music]
no big waves means another day of just
sitting blah blah blah sorry
what is in here secrets
yes
got it got it
I'm getting better at finding secrets
how many butterflies do I have a 15 I
need very
well I eventually I'll probably have
more than enough
let's try to get into that one then
since we got one key okay
let me get this one
okay let's see what is in here oh oh it
just opens a path
I can get to the top of the winter bun
what if I wouldn't find the key is this
not necessary
oh
that's you again
it's you my rival you found me once
again my Journey to Find Uncharted
ground is not over yet you get your
reward
oh thank you
[Music]
he's wondering if we can get much higher
can you get much higher I don't think so
buddy it looks tough
oh skills
yeah
okay I got hurt a bit but that's okay
now
see this luck no cause
there's no luck
now look at all
[Music]
good night you sleepy sleep oh
good night
oh I had nightmare kettle
both today and yesterday
um but this time it was the first time
in a while that I had a nightmare about
being
chased oh I see what I need to do I need
to stop it when they're all in the
middle
well that's about right
I got two keys here and the other one I
didn't find the key uh
[Music]
yeah yeah
chasing dream again yeah
come on weird
but different kind of chasing kind of
different different than usual
ah I'm okay though
it's just dreams
okay uh we almost have
[Music]
where's the lady we want to see that
terrifying scene again how she eats the
butterflies I feel sorry for that maybe
I shouldn't be helping her
I should be consuming them
would do them a favor I think
that's because turbine town is much
younger than hairballs doesn't mean we
don't have culture we have lots of
culture like eating snacks and screaming
at each other
that is
quite still
deep riveting culture oh okay here's the
same again same game again
where
okay what your ten weren't you younger
before
all right let's see
uh-huh
can I move them no
[Music]
that's redo
what how did I do that
let's start with this one because that
one's difficult
look at the signs y'all see the signs
oh
ah
but can I move the pot still because I
feel like um in the other world I was
able to move a couple of them
this one
okay that way the word
I think before I place it somewhere so
that it filled up all of these except
that one
but I forgot how I did that
oh no this is what happened then I had
these two
um
thank you
oh
thank you Chad actually helped me with
that okay there's more
let's see maybe I can get this one on my
own
I'm assuming here maybe and maybe here
no hey
haha
froggy while I sneeze whip hand
special sneeze
[Music]
maybe maybe here
yeah yeah yeah now we're talking and
then over here
[Applause]
smart froggy Wawa
all right one
but there's only one ah
[Music]
yeah how about
here
yeah that's what I bought
[Music]
fun indeed
is that they you know repeat all the
games
that's fine though
give money
makes it easier
oh hello
oh what's in there
also we need to find the next spot where
we can open something with the key
unless there is no more and I can bring
it to
maybe that's why I didn't find the key
in the other world
they want me to come back
because there was no key to find in the
other world only here and yeah
I'm supposed to come back maybe
Maybe
is that how it is
not finding the key I was
I was falling apart you know
it was like I have to find the king I
can't but I can't waste too much time on
this I'm gonna go crazy
foreign
okay
on the other Island you're gonna play
the same game with me all right all
right all right all right
but then eventually
become friends I feel like
oh the ball game is here too oh dude
that looks more difficult though
when riding the guns to get some extra
height
okay
oh
let's start
what go
go
oh
where is it where is it going
where's it going oh it's so slow
hey
oh
yeah okay actually this might be a
little bit easier because it's so slow
[Music]
okay okay
oh oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I say was just too too easy
go let's go get up well I touched it but
not not the ball not the Ball die yo
I'm still in the game I'm still in the
game
Dutch
come on kiddo come on kiddo
holy [\h__\h]
one more one more
[Music]
thought I could forward
four times the charm
or the fourth time like last time
hi
you know those those big Halls where the
whole ground is like trampolines
I wonder if you could
play this game in a hall like that put
up a net like this I think you would get
like a similar feeling but the ball
wouldn't be so slow I guess
at Italian was really bad just now
[Music]
so I was just coming down kiddle
say I pretend the twitch bit
yeah this seems safer because if you
fall down you fall into the water water
oh
this is kind of makes me mold
the timing is tough sometimes
ah
said that she's broken
can I leave this game out
like last time we had
um like one or two coins more than we
needed
see okay [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] this it's really hard to like see
where it's going you know
special perception oh yeah that's maybe
what you call it oh
I think that means one oh
one
[Music]
I want you to go through all of them
without going for the red one
two
three oh yeah
freeze son four
years
[Music]
oh
hello Almighty Dragon wind dragon all
did I just solve the mystery are you
gonna bring Winnie to this place again
can I what are you oh
what are you doing here I am bring
Dragon gown sorry I don't get a lot of
visitors nowadays
I guess people don't need wind dragons
as much as they used to
it's good to have company
would you like to see what I can do yes
yes oh by the pleasant Breezy uh yeah
that's exactly what we needed huh the
wind's back come see you for your run
yay
nice
pretty busy now even a wind dragon needs
to do his taxes gross
y'all [\h__\h] taxes like real but you gotta
do what you gotta do look at these frogs
are these alien frogs holy [\h__\h]
this is Facebook
no alien frogs schedule I don't think I
should bother them they look like they
came in peace
did they eat some green frogs though
because they have some green juice
coming out of their
Alvin the canopies
wow
oh
these lettuce I'm so excited to realize
that I have to leave and soon but where
to go I guess there are plenty of
options sleeping in the forest under a
pile of sticks sounds more cozy than
whatever this is
huh
this is I guess
oh one
like Nico's thoughts
I see little secret
oh yeah butterflies yeah yeah I was just
you know going wherever the wind takes
me and wherever the frogs take me
saute
what is that on top of
on top of the train what is that
looking mighty sassy to me
it might just be nothing oh it's just
inspecting the train
[Laughter]
what will you tell me about the train I
wonder what's over there
where looks like a forest surrounding a
mountain
are you telling me to go there or is
this the next Island
free of the six cards but we'll get the
fourth now
and actually no we got five uh fourth
and fifth because we did several things
okay I did that
um
Super Mario Sunshine Vibes oh now that
you say it
I think I can see what you're saying
yeah Super Mario Sunshine meets Paper
Mario ghetto
mini Phoenix oh you made it get on nice
Skittle
hey I'm supposed to talk to you right
here's some change buddy thank you he
didn't have to sign over his head that
tells me
I can finish the quest oh
tape and apparently we can already go
but let's get the coins for the
for the
um butterflies
no I didn't take a look but did it add
the coins I already had from the other
Islands
like if you do enough if that was the
case then you could do like all the
quests of the first and all the quests
of the second and possibly don't even
skip doing any quests in the third
island or so because you already got so
many from before
where was that lady
wasn't she in a container yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I wrapped with one okay okay
so it does carry over
Super Mario Paper sunshine Mario
Paper Mario would be a great stream and
he never played it before I think no
where's your plan not
something like Paper Mario
how did I not go in here the first time
Carol
she played the new one yeah she never
finished it yeah yeah cause I'm the only
one in whole life English that finishes
games hahaha
okay not the only one but I do finish
the most games that's for sure
which contain now it's container
ah there's one more tape over there I'm
getting it
[Music]
over there I want to get that one too
but wait wait wait wait don't forget
about it uh where is the lady
he's the lady
at all
what are suitcases they're so cute
[Music]
see I like the fact that this is a
platformer without like any battling
like it's peaceful
and yeah
I think this is the first time I play a
platformer game that has no
battling
Pokemon best completion player
I got what it takes I went from this
side yes yes
collect the fun
Rocky Wallace stealing Kiowa
whoa whoa yes
I get oh
I get that because she
because I killed her
huh
we're just gonna ignore that
oh
follow me oh my God
you'll have one extra one in the next
world again
and two keys can I go back to Otherworld
please
no
had to do that sorry
Salmon Creek Forest what how do I go to
the other one though
oh well we can always go there maybe at
the end
Creek Forest oh and basketball
did could I ever reach this I don't
think she finished the game did she
she's not she's not much of her full
game finisher either
I'm just flexing where's my and one of
your message your message okay oh Dad oh
no we haven't talked and that's my fault
things go pretty crazy huh we're looking
for you it's pretty hard but you look
good anyway
okay okay
you run
a safe
not to brag or anything yeah
did you pack your hiking boots we're
going to Salmon Creek Voice next a
beautiful voice surrounding a mountain
I've got to say you've really impressed
me so far
you know what I just realized we didn't
find any special
oh maybe maybe the alien frogs were the
special ones you know how we found that
one with the the like oh yeah oh yeah
face in the first world
but hmm I guess maybe the alien frogs
were that here
foreign
let's go
get rotated choke what's that mean you
had a handsome frog
have an intern get lost ones when we
found him he had a beer and everything
well can you imagine
oh
I am curious
show me a picture please
be really handsome frog
chat frog yeah
wow oh
wait maybe that was Diaries made me know
some
transparent apples
will become non-transparent oh
oh yum yum yum once I have
a certain amount of apples
therefore once again pushing me to go
back to a world where I have been to
before already in Cairo
maybe
also these apples now
once again have a different color but
they are like a mixed color
and we have a new one can I eat them I
want to eat them I'm hungry frog
nice okay I'm actually not that hungry I
had a little little fly sandwich before
I started the streams I'm all good
all right shall we start with this game
where's where's the girl to tell me to
start
never mind I'm doing this first
[Music]
fly with Jess
yum yum yum
[Music]
you wanna hear a story about frogs
so back when I went to frog School
there was like um
you know maybe a few mean kids I guess
and you know there's some some kind of
trend was going on
it was like
I don't know it was like um when you are
from the town it's too long people would
make fun of you
and then there was one child
in the school and the one frog child in
the Frog school who had like a really
long tongue like insanely long and it
got bullied all the all the time man
it was really hard to look at I'm kind
of sad you know
oh
that's not gonna work
yeah so since it was bothering them so
much they actually went so far to get
tongue surgery and had their tongue cut
short in half you know
what is it was
you know normally normally
frogs wouldn't do that but in this case
you know
the Frog child felt like you know it had
no other option because they kept on
bullying the frog jump
yeah they had tongue surgery
my my my tongue is by default not the
longest so I didn't have those kind of
issues you know
I felt sorry for the other frog
um because they were still young and
they went through so much
a lot of frogs when they become adult
frogs they they do this stuff you know
on their own accord because they want a
shorter tongue or a longer tongue or
whatever
yeah I know you must be thinking
wouldn't it be the opposite why are they
making fun of long tongues wouldn't
wouldn't it be like
the longer the tongue the better well no
not really I don't know why
you know children they don't have good
reasoning
they just make fun of something they
don't have and then later on in life you
realize oh that's what I wanted and then
later on like adult frogs often get
tongue and lengthening surgery yeah
I'm happy with my tongue
so I'm not traveled by it or anything
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
oh look it's a keyhole I could use the
key I already have maybe we'll find
another one
probably well let's look inside
a weird story what this is the big
fan this is just Halloween
some really embarrassing deep emotion
with you
not my personal experience but still you
know
anything you
talk to someone who just opened up to
you
there's a massive jumpers and you know
why
[Music]
oh yeah
Justin
okay since we found one here I'm
thinking we missed one in the other
world
I need to I need to find him we have to
go back and find him at some point
I wonder what this is all about though
so many apples
[Music]
I'm so excited to realize that I have to
oh wait that was the first one hang on
my friend Nico is looking for a job
they're all basically good at everything
go hire them or else
why the first letter seemed to be from
Nicole but the second one not
second one wait it said Sarah wasn't
that his mom I'm confused
come here come here
okay we need to talk to people where is
even
the first one I was supposed to talk to
oh dear there's a leaf perfectly placed
between your legs
anyway wait let me talk to you I'm out
here on this rock the fear dear we're on
the streets kind of freak me out trees
freak you out you are deer shouldn't you
be like huh I don't know between
them I don't know you do you know
you don't like them
No One's Gonna force you
I wonder who's up there
hello oh
it's a Discord wait that looks like
Discord this
featured in the game
but why do we have so many Discord
windows open
oh you must be really popular I have
lots of lots of service huh
ish hi
that's it that's it but nice workspace
outside with a Mountain View and trees
and fresh air actually that must be the
works the best workspace ever
hell yeah good for you man
sorry
if I swim too or just jumping from rock
to rock rock on little one says Diamond
dough wait
[Music]
wait
I'm just I don't know hanging
what's hanging with you huh
sorry you don't have to answer
bounce bounce
Apple Apple
it's just the new this beach oh
perhaps yeah that makes sense that's why
we see all them naked
reindeers
and tears
dearest what's the difference between a
reindeer and a deer
[Music]
oh
I got you I got you
[Music]
thank you
the weather funny
[Music]
you're just kidding right
one comes out when it's raining one
doesn't like the rain
I think you're lying to me
wow oh we have to really like do a lot
of platforming here on this world bam
foreign
always follow the apples and the
mixtapes
should make a mixtape for like if I if I
ever if I ever
meet like a whole member again and I'm
thinking of oh what to give them remind
me I could make them a mixtape
don't know for who
was definitely an option at all
someone who would appreciate it
why would you think I have trouble
I'm like doing really good I'm just like
not not
having myself
be restricted by your stupid quests
I'm still fighting like everything I
need to
but I wonder where the rest of that
Quest was
uh you know that one we started with the
plants well I haven't seen anything but
we'll find it we'll find it
getting a bit confused though hello
I'm gonna trade five percents for one
coin oh
is that the only use they have
I wonder
because if they have another use then I
want to be sure that I want to use them
for this if there's no better use
Reyna will appreciate EDM mixes really
she likes EDM that much
really no if anything I would make Dana
like a sexy romantic jazz
mixtape
[Laughter]
[Music]
so does anyone know
if there's other ways of using it
it is fine to do this oh thank you
music sounded really familiar I heard it
in a different game before
[Music]
music gives me a good feeling at all
Mario Party
I wonder also what the hell is this
oh I read that this voice is full of
sunflower seeds can you help me find any
of them
how come I haven't found any what
Brazilian Rhythm Osama Samba
Supermarket um
probably
happened to start rolling what this
thing
yeah
wait what jump
break
oh my God okay I see them wow
[Music]
wait is that what the door and that
first world was for as well
and how do I jump there you go
[Music]
yeah
one oh God
it's fun though
let's try to have a system okay
oh God oh God let's try to get you know
oh that's that's the lady with the bugs
look at each side of the
Mountain for rolly
this music is really nice still isn't it
I like the soundtrack of this game very
much
a lot of this would be good background
music for streams
also guys oh my God I don't know if you
saw it on Twitter some of you guys
really look at everything I do on
Twitter even tweets that I like
I know you do that
um but
uh oh wait what is The Game's name again
the entropy Center I think you know a
game that's really a lot like portal
really inspired by portal
on Twitter they said like oh we heard
you're interested in our game
let us know with uh in DM we can give
you a key and all that
oh there's something there
yeah very nice I mean I would have
totally bought it but that also reminded
me that it's coming out really soon and
I think November the 3rd or so
I didn't realize
it was so soon hey this this question
is a big overview of the island kind of
helpful actually
yeah so I hope you guys everyone that
enjoyed me playing
um uh portal one and two hope you guys
will come to see me play the entropy
Center
because last [\h__\h]
because I think yeah it will feel a lot
like a portal it was very inspired by it
probably won't be doing two parts
because they told me the game is like
eight to ten hours if you played
casually
I asked them because uh there's no
official record yet
okay
let's get that one
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
laughs
no
bounce bounce
bounce higher can we get much higher
what happened
what's this who will have the sea thing
right now she's recovering okay
don't you follow her Twitter
privileged information yeah
yeah they probably underestimate how
good I am at games so maybe it will be
longer than eight to ten hours
one until you guys were able to help me
a lot because you played it but entry
Center I want to play it like right away
when it releases and I don't think you
guys will be able to help me that much I
mean at least not from experience but
maybe from
um
just like being smart kiddo I'm counting
on you guys get all
right where's the last one
[Music]
there's a note over there too foreign
observation we're gonna use our brains
together
[Music]
like where you found the last seed
and the last one I found
how would I remember that now
I'm just gonna go this way
[Music]
somewhere
the one I fell from oh okay
oh here's more of that game
controlling
no no no
oh
[Music]
yes oh yeah I remember falling down here
come on
come on it's so hard to control in the
air
like Riley on the air you can barely
control
okay okay this is it this is it
now
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] one day I should you know try
to get into one of these balls like in
in I think I've seen something like this
before
on vacation at a beach they offer these
things to roll around in the water I
think
try that one day
foreign
let me try it falling down from above
somehow
ah
[Music]
why is this one so painful
let's go around
so far so good
getting close to it now
no no no no no don't go back
should be there yep yep okay chill chill
chill chill
oh oh
yeah why don't you just teleport me back
to you why do I have to come back you're
lucky that I'm close to you
hi uh wait how do i q
I'm just gonna push it on the keyboard
because I don't know what controller
button it is hello
that was uh pretty challenging
oh the name of our invention hamster
ball yeah that's um yeah not really far
off
I should get everybody I should get two
cards for that not just one
data
all right but as I said that actually
gave us a good overview of the island
Kettle most of this one
keep on getting more difficult
yeah oh I I think I did it right
on the first try but the question is do
I put it here or here I would say here
[Music]
still didn't figure out the Tamagotchi
thing though but oh well I'm I'm
assuming it's not like an important
feature of the game
uh highlights bag give up do you know
what sound the deer make
um
does this matter
yeah no that was accident
I would say Eden
million I was between that one and a
t-hole I guess now that I know I can
make an MD here
's traditions
a nice pond
[Music]
foreign
Center will be helping me fill in the
time until Pokemon a little bit as well
because it will take like two to three
streams at least
oh
damn it how do I talk to him
how do I talk to you
oh what's this
gaming machine so
dive into me to find it interesting
that's cute a cute way to get a coin
oh we have to get
uh uh yeah okay okay oh wow wow wow
a new game one one one one one one
look at this cup over there it's Inu
versus Kappa
yeah
why
coupons don't seem very involved in here
I know
one bounce boots oh oh there's two here
one here
wow yeah
[Music]
do I go to the doctor
Uncle Tom
[Laughter]
cute okay so they do add a few more
games here and there that's nice
wait there's more aliens over there
they're eating they're eating food
[Music]
that is the future guys they will take
over if we don't do something
and trust me they might be eating frogs
now but once all the frogs are gone they
might start eating the chickens
because apparently they taste similar I
don't know much about that though
so we're all in danger
although you guys are tadpoles now
but your your chicken friends might be
in danger look at
it oh well let's see maybe this is the
beginning of the game
cross
maybe get two crosses that's it
[Music]
how would that work
ah it goes It goes um uh like in a
straight line from my experience so I
know how to do it
as long as it can go yeah yeah yeah and
then the other one I wonder if it will
be interrupted but let's try
ah [\h__\h] I thought it might go down here
um is there another one that I'm missing
like a single piece now
[Music]
all right I'm close enough
let's try first this one
but then this one will be interrupted
again
do I have to stop it before it gets to
that point I have to be like really
Speedy no way
this one's a thinker kettle
and of course isn't there's a
there's an order but maybe I have to
look at it from a different point of
view
hmm maybe he ah uh yeah okay
I got it
I got it and I'm here
[Music]
where's the quest person anyway
also do I have enough of these bugs
but just now she let me know that she's
ready to receive my offerings there you
go
oh look
oh God
oh
spineless
[Music]
thank you
no you should take a photo of me
oh well okay so that's that how many
coins do I have five
five I already have five
oh [\h__\h]
oh why am I still collecting them don't
need them
all right
um
this this world is like a little bit
hard to find the
people it's so big and like
hmm
oh no
[Music]
not my favorite world I mean I'm I'm
getting around on my finds where I need
to go eventually
but
wet
horror game the tree
I tried to talk to him it wasn't very
easy
oh wait
this is Super Mario Sunshine he can do
that on the water on the wet surface
oh wait now you want to talk to me huh
ah it's just from here
hang on there my little friend I've been
having this itch all day
oh I think there's something stuck in my
needles could you help me get it out
just dive into me as hard as you can
oh
that's it
oh turn that to me okay
that must be it and even if it's not
I'll just leave you there it's suffering
no that's one you're welcome
yeah okay I'll keep it thank you now is
this like you know a secret
like with this with this thing can I
read something special no
am I already able to go to the next
place I don't remember if the game
already told me kennel
[Music]
I mean 18 months of Kiara but I I think
it's fine that you'll continue
taking that with you even now okay
though why not
foreign
I'm new here my my first time nice to
meet you kiddo oh another one
well let's see so um
shouldn't be too difficult
nice to meet you get all
well I don't sound like her at all
that's actually kind of insulting stem I
don't want to hear any of that
so peaceful right now I should go on a
hike I kind of wanted to go on a hike
like in Fall I mean I guess it's still
fall so autumn
it's not too late it's not too cold yet
oh come I wanna go hiking but I don't
know what food
like my my one friend who seems like she
would be up for that she's always busy
she's a she's as busy as a bee
and with that I don't mean even though
amen would definitely go hiking with me
I'm a bee
that's why I wanted to go
hello
oh we have yet to find that one person
who wants to be in a spot that's really
hard to reach
we'll get to him
sure Emma will enjoy hiking
okay we have two crosses again
easy
clap I have like a good feeling for this
that was
wait wait I didn't jump
I have a good feeling for these now and
uncle
Google
I want to jump here
yeah I probably accidentally jumped on
the top one
is the Girl doll
S
I already did like four or five of these
where is she
[Music]
what is that oh
flower flower
go skiing it's not skiing time yet what
are you talking about skiing is
unfortunately one of those sports that
ah
you can't do all the time hiking you can
actually do no matter what the season is
so I guess hiking is kind of superior
[Music]
where are we going
is he here perhaps wow Sakura
[Music]
flower
oh no numbers okay well what's up here
nothing's here
there's something spawn here
when I do something specifically
no NPC here
as music though oh yeah it's hard so I
just walk this path and something
appears
no
for later am I gonna get married
time for me
I want to find the girl I did so many of
her puzzles but
where is she probably the last one is
where she is
are you out
there
[Music]
hello I did this one
running straight is difficult here
are we invited
the official guests
oh no who else invites
oh would I invite besides you guys hmm
Mama Tony of course
although Mama Tony does not really
believe much in marriages
but I'm sure she would come anyway
oh yeah I don't I don't know right I
thought I thought I forgot something but
no I don't even know who I'm marrying
maybe we can try to get on top of that
tree house
there must be someone there
oh no
oh no it's like I thought that was like
some kind of secret here didn't see you
so well Apple Apple
hello
oh there's so many
McDonald's
foreign
have you guys seen that new Super Mario
rabbits game
looks a little bit interesting
I wonder if I should play it
um
I like rabbits
yeah I think I ran out like should work
there's more than one person who's
playing it right now
paying attention to me I guess no you
just wanna
and some of your own games oh oh I see
now now how that works you jump through
them like yeah you give them a headbot
and then they dissolve into apples well
then let me go to that one place
oh hello
finally I meet someone what the [\h__\h] is
that
taking off classes from a real master
becoming a master and craft is still
rebellious
let's paint a little Rebel
that looks like whiskers what do you
what do you mean paint a rebel where
where anyway where
I'm making a cat I guess
oh [\h__\h]
yeah yeah
I don't change
you liked it hits really yeah
[Music]
that doesn't feel dessert
but okay you know seven coins holy [\h__\h]
let's get up here
this is what's here
oh
hey
oh technique
am I well I'm stuck in a tree
oh
platform ah it leads you to a soda can
okay didn't necessarily want to go there
but okay
let's see
how okay I actually wanted to go back
here once because now I figured out oh
nice many many apples I still don't know
what they're good for also how do I
another dip in the water
[Music]
very cute game
oh more
is this Paper Mario yeah with um furries
yes
Paper Mario with fairies
uh
I'm like I'm Not Gonna Leave This Island
until I find that stupid sogucky brat
is she
[Music]
okay let me try to just walk around the
mountain as
the game wants me to go like according
to a path it feels like there is one
this way
I already went to the top I saw like
five different spots
where I did the puzzle
I saw this one we saw it we saw it
almost 300 apples
yeah we were here
oh wait was I up there
seems to be another one oh
you're here
ah finally oh is she here
I see another game but
what do these do another cross okay
foreign
[Music]
wow
this
I don't know how you would do that
and honestly where's that girl let me
see
is there any like
anything that stands out to you guys
need to start checking your train
okay
did you guys see her and I just missed
her
somewhere
there's a family close to the train
station oh girl again
I did also do one of the riddles near
the train station but I didn't see her
maybe I'm just blind
so there's a frog family
and
ah there
ow but this time she's not even standing
next to those fields and pepper I didn't
I didn't leave until now
love is in there although it seems like
it needs a little push today
that's what that up there is about go
see if you can help that little bear oh
that's probably why they didn't tell me
yet that I can oh wait no it needs one
more coin
so that means there's still like a
couple more quests
I feel like I already did ah
the trampoline one no no that was in the
previous world where is the ball game in
this world
hi I was just visiting my parents since
I live around here can you keep a secret
I have a huge crush on Melissa the panda
bear oh I'm gonna ask her out but it
needs to be a surprise could you help me
out could you carry her to that Plateau
over there find it by following the
flower pills yeah I was already there
before
candy tree okay
at least with these main quests they
show you where it is
yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo
yo yo yo
yo yo yo yo
here we go
yo yo
yo Yoda yo
Yoda yo
yo yo
[Music]
yo I'm speaking the language of the Gods
if you don't understand it then you're
not sophisticated enough
okay finally we're back here
get the last coin and we're not going in
with an extra coin next time I guess
unfortunately
[Music]
hi is this a setup
it's a setup it's a setup it's a setup
it's a setup it's a setup do it peace
yo you know Candy tree I need to tell
you something
I like you a lot like like like
you know so I want to go out some time
just the two of us let me thank you
oh yeah thanks for having me out kid I
owe you one one coin that is yeah
Grinnell
that took me 10 coins man I wonder
if there was any other quests that I
missed
because now we have pictari exactly as
many as it takes
time
I've got the Whiteboard
what
oh yeah the Whiteboard will tell me that
uh why not I got everything right
ask Peppa
okay
oh wait there's a note one I saw before
and I wanted to get to it eventually
Alyssa phone numbers text them yes
surrounding
great deal it's supposed to thank you
for fixing the train tracks thanks to
you more people can use a train the
islands you visit now have more to do oh
go to the other Islands by stepping
inside the train
oh for free Hello fish
so we're not going to any new islands
we're just going back to the old ones
that makes sense that's fine I've
already
seen a lot
let's see let's see
ah wait I want to look at the Whiteboard
nine out of 13.
it's free keys
okay I'll try to get around a little bit
more
maybe if I climb up here okay the Fisher
is there is there the Fisher the
fisherman how did I miss him
[Music]
hello
of course you are here Kayla
I will help you get off
where are they oh
oh can't go further than that
oh [\h__\h] should I get something
no of course not
I went down
okay that's one fish trout
into the pot you go why why why was that
pawn not good enough
okay one is here
[Applause]
than the other one we had oh that's milk
no idea
it is not pawn and did he say a pond
no he said pond
goes into the pond
okay do I have to land on the stones so
that I can get further because then it
doesn't count yet
uh-huh
yeah this one feels a bit easier
come on come on
you know his his analyzations of the
frogs kind of
uh remind me of the Hut The Owl and
Animal Crossing telling me all about it
all and wait there's a key in there I
was wondering like was that an apple but
no there's a key
okay let me get the key in a second yeah
there were no frog villagers were they
an animal crossing I don't remember
I don't remember frog seeing frog
villagers
I might be wrong though
okay I totally got it wrong I'm kind of
stuck
of course there I just completely forgot
about it hello where the fish
hello
oh
wait is that on the other pond
wait
that's cheap
all the way over there
okay
I'm gonna go get you
a drink
oh this is a pack I got all that all of
them
[Music]
yes 11 coins okay so we got one extra at
least
and now add the key the key the key
don't forget the key
on there
water
in the water
seems a lot of wine
though
okay what's next
maybe we can find one more
it must be like one of those ball
volleyball missions too or was that
basically the hamster ball this time
I was here too
ah right here
ah how'd I missed this
let's play I oh
yeah and let's use the violent Sports
skills it's possible sport football what
hit the ball back to me five times don't
let it touch the ground so don't worry
about the ball getting stuck in the tree
or something this is some quality gear
you know get out there and try not to
get a splinter okay
ah
these obstacles okay let's do it
oh no it didn't count
trying to stay a little bit further
behind
[Music]
me
haha
oh it wasn't so hard
even six times oh okay
oh not so bad that was easier
you're shocked shocked yeah yeah I was
all up in those tree snacks come back if
you want to hone your sport final skills
also take this coin-shaped beef I just
found this now
[Music]
I don't feel like now I'm like
I got like to all the important parts
pretty much
uh was I up there
I think so yeah that was the The Gamer
the the computer guy
but there's one more key that I could
find
um
[Music]
in the first map the key helped me
but I don't think it made it it was
necessary like he helped me to get no in
the second world help me to get up to
the wind turbine
um
am I speed running this or am I
normal speed
I wonder I feel like I'm pretty fast
right now
this place is peaceful
um
you bathing here naked ah
you wore magic Wizards why are you not
wearing matching swimsuits now after
censor this YouTube's gonna ban me
yeah bye
yeah bye ghetto
YouTube
the leaves the leaves are not enough
the leaves can fall off anytime if
there's like a little bit too strong of
a wind
it's not safe for YouTube
all right I think
I think let's try to go to the next
place oh [\h__\h] why am I doing that
it could uh 12 out of 10.
that's a good start
all the public pool maybe that's the
last World
[Music]
oh wait oh we're getting closer and
closer to the Frog aren't we
you have one new messages new message
hi honey how are you doing hope you're
doing good I really miss you dear honey
guess what I got a really good doctor
and he says you're totally normal he
said he knows just how to fix you let me
know what you are and I'll come to pick
you up just pick up please
[Music]
yeah I mean I kind of already felt at
the beginning but this game seems to be
about
a child having depression and the
parents
not depression necessarily but like some
kind of mental
problem and the family is not taking it
seriously maybe and that's why they ran
away because their family is not not
really like yeah
accepting it and helping out
yeah yeah
do you smell the chlorine that means
we're getting close to the public pool
can us frogs don't go there often ponds
are more hours
time to get off go get them tiger now
uh-huh
[Music]
cool
cool oh almost six coins here okay
we got a tip that something terribly
happened at this pool it looks like
there is already a detective on this
case oh it's a fun
attacks or free frogs maybe either
uh Frozen chickens aren't that different
after all
foreign
key only interesting
I want to go over there can I go there
first thing I do is try to get
only completely other freaking side of
this place
[Music]
no no
[Laughter]
man what
um
[Music]
try talking to him
nobody immediately
kicks me back
oh okay got him I got him hassle hop
down to there
okay okay Hasselhoff
number
whoa that's a fake frog
nice
you're fake
don't trust him brothers and sisters
whoa It's like a cloud frog because
visit the Frog howdy bear I'm fancy the
frog one two three one two three one
child come to a half with me
no no you're fake I don't like it
also I see a tape above the the speech
bubble
listen again I'm not getting paid enough
to keep you busy all day let's be like a
yeah like a clown in a child's party
although I've never seen that before
I've only seen that in Americans sitcoms
yeah TV shows
that's the only place where I've ever
seen something like that
but is it common in America do parents
really get their kids clowns for their
parties
or is that really only a TV show thing
I remember a few parts where we had
those whoa
[Music]
my cheeks just puffed when I did you see
that when I was like gulping if you
looked closely you can look at it in the
archive I was drinking water and then my
cheeks were like
[Music]
most of the TV shows
come online 20 years ago
yeah I wonder if kids would even
nowadays be impressed by having or like
happy by having a clown in their
birthday party nowadays they probably
want other things clowns are not not the
cool thing anymore to have
kids at Fortnight now it's more like
Elsa Disney characters oh
[Music]
um
for their birthdays
yeah my actions are well reflected as
froggy Wawa
if it was Paul got the ecstatic yeah
yeah yeah me too I used to play soccer
it was pretty bawling
oh you're so funny
[Music]
oh it's like a puzzle
and here will be the king
oh wait wait that's fine too oh wait the
water looks actually pretty good
it's a public pool
I haven't been on a long time like in a
public pool where like in summer when
people go for fun
like this
I mean like you know the outside ones
I'm more for like teenagers and so on
it's been a while people say the
steaming hot tubs in the bath house are
the most relaxing thing in the world yo
you say nothing beats lukewarm pool one
oh yeah please no no cold pool water
it's so hard to get in I bought like a
swimsuit that covers
um like it kind of it looks like kind of
like a more or less professional
swimsuit it doesn't cover the legs but
it goes all the way up to the neck
and it yeah covers like everything
except the arms and the legs like yeah
pretty good coverage it's like a sports
yeah because I was hoping that with that
it will be easier to get into the cold
water I thought well the more fabric
the warmer I'll feel right right
it wasn't quite the kill
what's up what's going on
serious there's a key over there
look at this
see there are little legs cute you can't
fool me I'm one of you guys
you're on this case too we'll be
prepared it's a bit gruesome see this
poor kid's pool floaty got murdered
[Music]
please like this make you fake how did
the world come to this that was not the
time to get distracted however
go check out the crab scene and see what
you can uncover come back to me when
you've got a good look all right all
right
leave it to me
hello everybody oh
woman
Hawks
well hi there I'm taking a bit of a
break
you'll handle this whole jumping bins
okay oh is this like a reference to the
previous game that ah
I looked it's the same developer or
publisher I'm just not sure probably
developer
Ah that's the cute reference oh
in a
soyuz oh
oh there's like a really strong wind ah
in the water but
if you just jump on top then you'll
reach it eventually oh wait why did I do
ah okay okay I thought I had to jump on
top so I panicked but nope
the cookies now so many keys what to do
what to do whoa
what to do with all the keys oh hello
Dirk
oh he's a hamster
uh wait was having time
wasn't that like a co-op game
am I mixing something up
if yes then that's one of the few
better Club games that I have not played
yet oh yeah it does
I want to play that with someone oh
didn't we talk about this recently that
I uh
this this will already make me nervous
this this would be the highest I could
go
I remember like going in these kind of
places with school and then
at least one time I did climb up
but not not this time maybe in like to
this height and then I was like nope and
then
didn't make it oh hello we're facing
over there okay good then I went up here
let's go
wait I don't know where where I went
anyway
sorry that's just milk
Premier is the most for me you're a
chicken no you're tackle
[Music]
there was something here
did I get it oh yeah funky
oh you're standing on there well they
indeed really do not belong into a pool
so I agree with that
uh oh there's a there's a there's a
Kamehameha
comment comment
s
even though
frog did I get up no oh I did
squid oh I got the squid not the shark
goodbye turtle
is the shark so bad maybe it was never a
shark I think it was yes
[Music]
you're thinking I need help I don't need
your help wrong
you think Sam just a little stupid human
but no in reality
there's a frog behind all of this
hmm is there one in the second pool
well there's there's a Crocodile down
there though
[Music]
oh cute
thank you okay now let's try to get that
mix it up
that was a nice save
and apples
oh what apples
oh there they are oh they fell down
pretty slowly
oh ah this makes me want to go back in
time to Summer
and then swim frunk on the bottom of the
water walking some water why
how do I dive
how do I get okay oh I have to like jump
from really high and then I'll get
really low oh never mind I thought this
was good enough
you really want a hot apartment again
you know
no
oh by the way guys I told you guys
yesterday that I booked a hotel for
Kiana's mama and me right
Michelle
um
actually
there's a bit more to that than that
I wanna to book something nice you know
[Music]
um but
I booked something that looked nice in
theory
and
like it looked really good and it had
insanely good
um like
not reviews but like you know on
booking.com
it's like the the rating
if it's like over 9.0 it's exceptionally
good right
hello
oh wait five percent oh yes yes please
[Music]
over 9.0 would be like really
exceptional actually and I I so far I
never had problems with that when I went
to a hotel that over 9.0 right was
usually really good
what's on Candy but
I booked something that had over 9.0
and also really good reviews on
booking.com
so
the focus also looked really good now
book it and then on the next day
I get an email was telling me
like from the hotel seemed like rather
like
um an automated one Ah that's how you
get over there wait
let's go oh
you can't stop me
Frank Hoven or whatever your name was
can we stop here thank you oh
oh oh I can't move the camera it's only
sideways
yeah so I got an email it says in caps
lock
we now first it was normal and then we
would like to remind you and then caps
lock that we are not a hotel but a bed
and breakfast and I'm like what does
that mean
what's that supposed to mean oh
and you know that made me feel sassy
oh my god oh what is this this is
supposed to be like Mario
yeah I think so
um so I look into it and you know I was
wondering like what do you mean you did
it I didn't even book breakfast anyway
so when I looked into it I found
actually some like only bad reviews on
Google
see when did I do that
they were saying that this was like not
at all like in the photos it was much
smaller it doesn't even have a reception
the hotel is like
like in like an apartment building so
it's more like an Airbnb it seems
then
yeah like an actual Hotel it feels like
a scam they didn't say it's like a scam
in the reviews but definitely it seems
like that was what they were getting to
um yeah and then like stuff like they
had to pay like so much more money for
arriving after
a certain time in the evening
so having to pay for late check-in guys
this is ridiculous I worked in a hotel
and that's like not what hotel's
daughter if anything yes we're paying
for for early check-in is a thing from
the fully chicken
oh oh
so that really started worrying me so I
actually kind of wanted to cancel
because it did more and more sound like
a scam like on booking.com it didn't
seem like that at all and I don't
understand how they got so many positive
reviews though and it looked through
them to see if they seem fake but I
don't know they didn't necessarily seem
fake but I don't know what to look for
in these cases you know
um
yeah it was like pretty Bamboozled and I
wanted to cancel but it was
non-refundable perfect right like
normally when I book something in
booking.com it's like always refundable
I rarely ever seen a Booking.com right
that's refund that is non-refundable
um
it's comfortable review maybe about
reviews I don't know I did see a couple
negative ones after digging really
deeply I need to bump into sorry
yeah it feels like such a scam
I'm gonna talk to my mom about it and it
was like well it'll be fine because
we're gonna be sightseeing and as long
as we can sleep in it it's like whatever
right
I mean that's fine but I still feel like
the price was
it's not it's not like
yeah before if all those reviews are
really true and it's really that shitty
and so disappointing that the money is
not worth it I paid quite a bit
another thing that was weird but that
was like totally
like I knew from this diet that that was
[\h__\h] the rate
was
over 90 percent off
going from like
around 5 000 per room per per
um
the total of nights that I had like
three nights or so
90 off
to like 500
I mean I
like there's no [\h__\h] way even for
expensive hotels
that this is how much they go I mean
there are hotels
cost this much really rarely like even
even really luxurious ones are for a
standard room
not a thousand per night it is like a
sweet Junior sweet or something okay a
thousand per night can happen and like
something really luxurious five star but
this was obviously obviously that was
not the original rate I knew that like
by the way they're moving I knew that so
I was like they're probably just trying
to make it look more like delicious like
oh what a cat what a deal I knew that
before booking but I mean it did look
like judging by the photos it did look
like it's the price is appropriate but
now now I don't think so anymore
so I'm kind of angry
[Music]
I thought okay that might not be the
original price really but they
at least there's some kind of discount
probably right
yeah it doesn't sound sketchy right I
know
where is the lady this time
why is she not here
also I'm actually happy that I don't
have to do her Quest maybe because the
things here seem to be hard to catch
really hard
sketchy right I was gonna call
booking.com and talk to them about it
but the thing is you know I I know how
this kind of stuff works normally
um if it's a non-refundable rate it's
not bookings Choice it's still the
hotel's choice
booking can like call the hotel and be
like yo yo this customer wants to refund
us but the whole hotel is very much
allowed to say no thank you because it's
their rules booking.com can try to
communicate but
[Music]
um Small's advertising I don't know man
like the it seems like the the photos
are
they they definitely send on the reviews
it's misleading and then smaller than it
really is and there's no reception or
anything
but it could still I don't know I didn't
go there so it could still be
real photos I don't know
I don't know man
I'm not sure if I want to fight it
crime happened here okay
let's put let's play another one of
these
no if I cancel I've lose like the full
amount
unless you get to we get them to somehow
okay happy dog sounds bad
let's get them to like you know
um again don't come to be really
really persuasive I would not go there
please find it from y'all yeah like my
mom is like totally fine with it you
know but like I'm the one who's paying
and and like I I feel like I'm being
scammed a little bit you know so I'm not
so happy with it
if it was cheaper
then I wouldn't mind so much
like if the price fits the bad reviews
you know
and I wouldn't be so
worried I I don't mind staying in a
shitty hotel
for a few nights but the price just does
not seem too much
I have to start the process with my bank
um
I don't know if I really want to go for
the trouble of all that though you know
what I mean I've never done something
like that before ever
so I'm unsure like how to get a ballot
um
I'm not trying to ruin my vacation
that's all I'm doing but like in the end
it would be fine as long as we can sleep
there is fine
it's just kind of messed up you know
this is why you do this with credit card
oh is that a problem that I didn't use a
credit card because I used like a debit
card
no problem does that not work then
[Music]
you can just call up your bank
will I do that
how cool now will we
no okay no not now maybe tomorrow then
it's like late in the night anyway now
they wouldn't I mean I think there's a
24 7 first service but never mind
you can still charge back
into charge bag with credit cards yeah
but it's not a credit card
's gonna make it easier
[Music]
wait I'm supposed to go there
okay
perhaps ask tomorrow
thank you
we're supposed to thank them
oh no wait wait the victim I thought oh
[\h__\h]
we already saw yesterday and that's good
with pointing fingers
and I don't mean those societies I
wanted to say the society is the culprit
every time ghetto
I don't know I want I want a credit card
what
[Music]
not being refundable and that's okay but
they told you that it was not a hotel
afterwards in the email yeah
but proud because
indeed has a lot of things nowadays that
are not actual hotels like they put
apartments and stuff in booking a
comments it's supposedly fine like
there's no rule against it
yeah and
it does not exactly like you look at the
page of that thing of that you know
place and it looks it seems everything
seems like a hotel but this I guess
there's like a little tag that says
something like
um bed and breakfast yeah but bed and
breakfast to me sounds like just a hotel
like you get a bed and breakfast in the
hotel too but I guess that's really all
you get here a belt and a breakfast I
didn't even book The Breakfast though so
all I got is a bed
um
[Music]
I don't know I don't know if I could
really say they lied
it does I don't I don't think there's
anything that's like really 100
black and white this is a lot
where's the LIE
it is just like getting your hopes up
and okay but it feels more like my fault
for
not looking into the reviews
foreign
[Music]
I don't think they lied I think you
didn't read it well hey
well I guess that's what I'm saying I
guess yes but when you say it directly
to me it feels mean
best lines are half true
yeah see that's what I ended up like not
not going for it because my mom said
it's fine and I I'm not sure if this
would really work out but I might try
anyway
I need a personal assistant yeah
would be nice
I don't want to bother with it
got more opinions I have
a bunch of opinions right here I'll just
counter them and explain the situation
they'll be able to give him an uncertain
time when you say damn do you mean my
bank or booking
or the hotel
Hotel I promise it's gonna be like haha
your phone [\h__\h] you we're not giving you
your money back
um
I was gonna call booking originally
just gonna call both then I like where
you're going with this but we know for a
fact that this kid's pool floaty got
murdered
[Music]
let's continue guys
oh yeah I don't know if that's grounds
for like as I said even even if booking
agrees with me the final decision is on
the hotel
hmm
when I heard that booking account can be
very very pressuring and annoying to
Hotel owners
with like demanding refunds for their
customers because like I've had this too
like I I had to talk with booking.com
staff a couple times before but our
hotel always was like no we had a really
harsh and strict stance like I wouldn't
even get into a conversation with them
but I heard from other Hotel owners that
they're they get like really pressured
by booking.com like our customers and
this and that you have to refund it for
them do it do it do it
um
the hotel is like oh they're so [\h__\h]
annoying I guess I'll do it
they're really really like like to apply
pressure
if that's true then in this case it
would help me because now I'm on the
other side I'm the consumer
um
now I almost actually helped me
uh second what is the murder weapon oh
wait am I actually does it actually
matter what I say here
um
scissors probably correct oh is there
any evidence that tells us who or who
committed this crime
foreign
[Music]
there's a couple bunnies over there
it's bunny child the owner pulls on
himself and away all right
wait it's crying
bone tears you see a dog bone tears
well maybe not
in
I
guys I didn't even try oh wait there
were scissors I saw them wait never mind
so I didn't know the answer it's like my
my car my conscious told me the right
answer even though I did not 100
consciously know it
did not see the footsteps
mother said I have to use it why so that
you would stop using your floating
as that
great work working we need more people
like you on your outside I got a little
something for you oh thank you
well sometimes you don't really have to
use your brain just guess just a mystery
solve a looking for truth well well not
at all
that worked out really well for us
Victor
finally
all right let's see what do we have we
already have eight coins two
that's already enough to go to the next
world no like go I don't know where
we're going though
because I bought one
is there no other quests here though
and what about these flower quests you
are here but where are the flowers
oh yeah
actually on the water yeah I like it too
10 of those
what
Sammy Sammy
Sammy Sammy Sammy
Sammy Sammy maybe now if we go back to
the earlier the first island they said
then there's more more
ask me
[Music]
that's me
he said there's more Mission so maybe
there's something with the apples now
and they want like 500 apples and then
everybody who collected properly they're
so happy that they did it
[Music]
thing
cool Ryan I know very cute
speak for a small part I'm guessing a
small one is the baby
weird where is where are the quest
people
the one who wanted the the bugs and the
one with the plants were all they are
cassette tape at least I saw that
they're all chilling I guess I'll see
so tired
oh cute
because because these two yeah I
remember them yep
her name is the best oh
wait what here
this one's just hanging they're not
doing anything this time lunch break
yeah
okay yeah because I I mean I might be
blind but I really don't see anything up
I don't see it
[Music]
here I filled up some food
house stinks
I'm not allowed to help you ah there you
go clean clean how do I clean it
I know how to clean it
poop
I clicked something
[Music]
as because I sat down
oh oh
I wanna play Tamagotchi
uh it's okay we don't need it it seems
right
we don't necessarily need that I think
you don't know
I love Taco
cute Taco is on the pole
[Music]
incredible
okay eight out of five I guess let's go
coconut I also got oh wait six oh I did
delete everything I'm just missing two
cassette tapes they shouldn't be so hard
to find
oh well let's go I got everything a key
the one key and all the other quests
around around ikuka
it was way smaller than
the
oh two letters
oh whatever I don't care about the
letters
[Music]
world
I thought we're just going back now oh
wow from the water like this this is
this is
Spirited Away
on fan
whoa
ah before I left I got into a big fight
with my mom I couldn't take it anymore I
got real heated and I said some things
must have been heartbreaking for her I
just had to get out of there and now I'm
here trying to become a professional
friend it's kind of ironic you'd have to
be crazy to hire me I guess I'm being
evaluated by a progress of time someone
else maybe I could be happy someday
hmm
at least you have some someone to hold
on to
happy for you oh
hey hey what's up is that my mom you
sound a bit off are you okay
I don't know I'm here for you I always
will be
stay strong okay and call me when you
need a pep talk just remember you're the
best love you bye
that's just a friend okay I'm very
excited about the next next stop the
bath house is a place for relaxation
taking hot steamy bombs
one time I sat in the bathroom so long I
got all wrinkly sorry for the mental
image
wrinkly frog I don't get wrinkly
almost forgot it's time to give you a
new title
Junior trainee friend
almost there remember you can do this
[Music]
wait it's only been three and a half
hours
this game is supposed to be five hours
still quite a bunch more
but we're more than halfway from nine
coins three keys okay
snow
I was browsing the weapon noticed that
someone hasn't been mining their work
life balance as someone currently locked
up in that Tower
oh yeah oh yeah
they these don't seem like they're made
out of snow why they have faces
they're very bouncy it's like they're
white plastic balls
not buying it
oh
nice atmosphere though
whoa
oh Golden Frog
they come and go too of course we do
Lucky frog
no chocolate oh chocolate frog no no no
real frog
20 20.
oh did I build a snowman oh beautiful
smells nice too
wow oh this is this looks oh copy
[Music]
looks really nice they got the the Mikan
and the milk gentleman
oh boy
cute Hello I'm joining you I could sit
in the steamy tub all day
this is perfect when it's like open air
and ice cold outside and you're in the
hot
even Bob yeah yeah that's what I
experienced with with Cowie we talked by
the way like a couple members are in
Japan at the same time
um going to be in Japan at the same time
and Kelly was like Let's do let's do
Onsen
and I was like
um Cali
one-on-one with you was fine still even
though that took me a lot of courage to
do
but
with a group of us I don't think I Wanna
Know
I want to make me want to do something
else but you guys can do it but then
Cali actually agreed with me she thought
a little bit about it and was like
actually you know what you're right I
don't feel comfortable with that either
yeah yeah
I thought I was being weird but no yeah
you know we're not really
yeah
don't look
I mean if we could like rent a whole
Onsen for ourselves
and then go in with swimsuits that would
be ideal actually that could be an idea
yeah
mmm that could work but I don't know how
expensive it is I mean we might really
be quite a bunch of people
um
and there are some Onsen
that are okay with swimsuits
let me actually before I forget that let
me let me let me let me pitch that
because I mean I like the idea of an
Onsen but I don't like the idea of being
naked
and chill man
um
[Music]
I pitched it yeah maybe maybe but even
if we can't do this then I'm sure we
will find something else to do as a
group yeah I'll definitely be meeting
Cali but I think I'll also get the
chance to meet some some other
Ian members that I haven't met before
wow
is it so dark outside you're not going
to tell me that I have actually been in
the shop all day yes I understand why
though wow nice
[Music]
I was working with some shrinking Tech
to make a smaller version of my
invention the hamster ball mini once
again I strong down my SoundCloud says
can you help me find them it's a great
opportunity okay where is it
there's really many what
am I supposed to
like I can't use it huh am I just
supposed to run around and find them
without the ball
[Music]
right right
ah
what they say it's a great opportunity
to try out this thing but I don't know
how to wait I was supposed to bump into
it right ah sorry
I forgot
small bouncy things
where are they though oh this will be
difficult
yeah oh wait there's one here
[Music]
at least this one's easier to control
but it will take a while to get through
the whole island
kidding me
for the red super chat kennel
hello
[Music]
I'm stuck in this ball oh wait ah
it's Island uh thank God
oh
[Music]
can I get the key while I'm in here
I can't
see
okay
that was fun I wonder if I can get in
here though anyway afterwards
[Music]
not to kill attention again what do you
mean again she's dead she'll she won't
come back right what
yeah how would you do that
once you're dead you can't possibly
revive
no no no that would be crazy like what
never heard of such a thing
oh
[Music]
something up there I wonder
I don't think so
what about here
why is the wall that's closer to the
mouth okay okay there's wall here oh
thank you
[Music]
well thank god there's an invisible
barrier ah here like brings you back up
I guess
okay hmm nothing much in this area
oh
[Music]
just stay still stay still yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah that's it that's it good
job
some sunflower scenes for me oh
going uphill is quite the fight row row
will fight the power what do you think
here
turtle
traveling turtle or finally someone's
body suitcases so far never found
someone by the suitcases
[Music]
what okay
oh
this one's not working
was there a button
sandwiches
and what do you mean
let me find you guys have to get used to
me I'm here to stay
I will not leave so easily
you're underestimating me
oh
what do I not know
I know everything I'm all knowing froggy
Wawa
oh
hello
oh what's going on in here
[Music]
three more
one more in here maybe get on
no
no no no Google
I need to talk to her later though
[Music]
lacking critical information cannot
how do I get the wrist where's the rest
three more
[Music]
can I make that one
that won't work I want to go higher can
we not get much higher
I think I found everything here
[Music]
I guess I'll go down
oh
oh that one I missed okay
I tried jumping on the blue photos maybe
I didn't do it properly
two more what
[Music]
more
last one last one's always hard to find
it's
okay I'm trying to go up one more time
let's hope we find something
no
okay
where was that thing
over here
Super Monkey Ball now
yeah it doesn't even seem like buttons
no
I don't think I ever played that game
you know
and there must be one more up here
or a button to change the wind there
turn it on
camera
look at everything though
foreign
oh there's also Keyhole here
yeah no I don't know man
did you get the one that was near the
key yeah
we traced my steps
nothing near the key
or maybe here
[Music]
let's try inside here one more time
although I already found like two in
here I feel like
girl where's the last one help me
hmm
o
maybe in the coffee bottle
I think I went in the other one before
[Music]
no
I think I saw it
I'm gonna miss it before
didn't I go inside
four
then
oh well okay
[Music]
I did it
Yay good job
[Music]
now let's try to get up there again
because there was oh wait can I actually
go down first
how do I go down there for to the key
when I'm big
oh here here here
I barely fit
squeeze
[Music]
okay
still gonna try to get up
I don't know if that's the normal path
but oh no now the air here is gone
what is the normal way
to do this oh next time
no
what
no ah
hacking gamer frog
hello okay we're on this level now oh
happy Bana
[Music]
and this one
I wanted to talk to you took it out
what's up
where's my Louise I hope he's not cold
what is that a person
or an item
I'll probably she said I hope he's not
cold so okay
[Music]
with no key I guess you won't be able to
get him in here at all I and popping
around this bathroom so what do you need
I'm pretty busy
wanna help me uh I guess you could check
on my husband so far
looking after the kids
check if everything's okay do you have a
blue
blue basketball they're rare I think
my beloved handsome frog
hang in there
okay I think I got all I needed in here
all right let's try to get there okay no
okay no
how do I pop you guys know poppy that
that artist
it's like someone on YouTube
she used to make pretty creepy videos
nowadays not anymore turns out that um
she was kind of like more or less forced
to make them had like a really bad
creepy management and all that I was
like yeah a lot of stuff going on behind
the scenes there
um
still makes like stuff music and so on
but like completely different
um like image and like you know not not
like the old puppy
[Music]
she reminded me of like a modern
version of Maggie bun with more budgets
way more budget because it was all so
professional
[Music]
cute
oh the ball game is here oh one of the
ball goes down
volley it's an all new sport by me it's
quite simple make sure they're long
Molly
her ball doesn't hit the wood let me see
you make it doesn't hit the wood like
the sidebars oh God
oh God
oh
hey
that didn't go as far back as I expected
it oh now it does
[Music]
her too oh God
is that long it's quite a long volley
[Music]
yeah the the good old
first generation of Japan culture
YouTubers and so on
[Music]
I'm Becky Krill too yeah yeah Becky
cruel
what was that
do these names say anything to you guys
long enough why are you this good I'm
this good
never heard of them
absolutely not
I guess we you know we were we were
brought up in different kinds different
corners of the internet wow so many of
you guys say no
oh
that's back when this when stars were a
thing when you're delay mean what does
that mean Stars Oh you mean the rating
system
five stars yeah yeah
back then it was not okay don't forget
to leave the video a thumbs up but then
it was don't forget to give the video
five stars
you know the the oh where is she
did she die
did she get poisoned by the bugs
foreign
[Music]
does she nowadays only show up if I
actually already have the number that
she desires I wonder
ladies
and this channel has an LCD screen so
it's hard to play it in the dark oh you
know what else is hard this challenge to
go from The Mark Stone Lantern to the
mic bathtub and why are we starting this
game so far away from the starting point
do not set foot in any snow
but
wait what
okay but we're not stopping from here
right okay you're weird
classical
let me try getting up there again
because I'm mad oh
when I get on top of the boxes thank you
no
I see I see how it is
where was it
where was this thing I was trying to
reach out here ah
foreign
[Music]
but I don't care
spooky
I think
oh
this reminds me of tunic
go like for this tunnel that's dark and
you don't know what's the weird leads
and then suddenly this big Skeleton
shows up in the Darkness
couple Island
but there's a there's a little Axolotl
on top
what does that mean you wanna play
gotcha
gotchi
oh it goes away
it's for later
[Music]
got to Facebook
later okay
[Music]
mm-hmm
oh hello wait I can buy
clothes from you
yes
oh it's a twitch reference I was like
one of those emotes I didn't even know
Queen oh wait that looks like a secret
I have to crush it no oh no
no
oh it's just I in order to get up here
maybe
oh it's a frog statue ah on the cassette
up here oh hi hi hi hi completionist
froggy Wawa
is added again
oh well cold cold
[Music]
well all these places are so peaceful uh
but this really reminds me a little bit
of my whole kind of piano some kind of
trip oh look they're opened Kiana's
Hokkaido trip of can we
um
like that one evening
we walked through the snow to like a
like a cafe that they have like a the
really hot food bath
it was dark but they had like a couple
lamps and we walked with the snowy
yeah it was a really really nice
atmosphere and not evening and we ate
the they ate those um grilled apples
and drank like some kind of punch or
something or hot wine I think yeah yeah
and I just drank something
non-alcoholic it's very graffiti in the
snow has a fleeting Beauty to it as in
Stone Mountain disappear some of your
eyes and of course still super her belly
isn't cool
oh you want to do it again
but how do I actually get a different
one and this one oh
God damn it beautiful really I don't
know what the hell I'm doing even now
looks like [\h__\h]
no effort necessary they could have
improved this game if they
um like wanted you to recreate something
they should have put like some some
guide on the on the ground where you put
in the color and then you'll try to
recreate that with your jumps like place
it as accurately as possible and this
way it's like you do whatever and
they're like oh and then
[Music]
are the subjective you're still but this
is like this accidental nothingness
no it feels like it's my memories
because I watched Kiana's streams and
then you know is listening to her it
felt like I went through it because
she's so good at telling the tales of
what she's done and you know with the
photos that she shows it's like I was
there
I mean right
I know you know I know you know
bam okay where where next go oh hello
[Music]
I wonder if this counts as you know
the Whiteboard says so and so many coins
you can get here
I wonder if this counts as one of those
or if this is besides like extra
separately
what the [\h__\h] is that light
they follow you eight other five I can
already go
five out of nine hmm one of the three
hmm
you're talking about the puppy you're
chat message seems to arrive extremely
delayed
let's try to finish the main thing here
oh ah they're not touching the Snowman
I don't know if I want to do that one
it's like a lot of effort
go over here though
elmy lives in the past I I let me catch
you
fireflies
would not believe your eyes the 10
million five lies without the skies I
fell asleep
hello
[Music]
they use Elizabeth
the fourth I told you to take a left kid
we're supposed to be chilling by a pool
with some other cameo character I I
thought you look like you're some kind
of Cameo yeah yeah
now I'm freezing my Hilltop
thumb
what is this referencing to
it must be another one of their games no
okay mom is so cute I know thank thank
you it's supposed to be shy guy Oh I
thought they would only reference their
own games
hello
all the family is here ah she's cute she
has a little ribbon Skippy is gone he
told me that he wanted to see what
happened if you go for all the white
Tony games do you think a monster took
him oh that's still though the one
that's on top of the skull now
Maybe
and she's kind of lost I mean probably
oh poppy said you she probably thinks
everything's gone wrong I'm perfectly
qualified to look after kids you know
just having a rat all the time they're
sippy and maybe Zippy and Flippy and
Skippy what
[Music]
what I messed up I miss something where
could he be you look smart can you help
me look for him I think I found him
foreign
but do I just go back there
and now I'll get the option to talk to
him or so maybe
oh my God
for real nothing at all
right all right uh I forgot
double kill
oh the game is actually telling me to go
that way
I totally knew it didn't need your help
one guy must be until the trailer huh
there's one guy
huh I already forgot
what brings you to my Realm you can use
oh oh your skull is talking oh this kid
yours
figured someone come to pick him up
[Music]
thank you long enough don't worry he's
all right we were just playing a board
game
guys let me tell you
thank you it's time to go home
I guess he knows the way do you know the
way
now we go back to the parents
[Music]
it's for White story again so then when
I first went through
very unlucky did you not hear little
kids he's white Tony gazing don't bring
you anything good
seems I've heard
whistle
[Music]
um
I want to learn how to make apple pie or
apple strudel even though apple strudel
was invented I think in Austria
I never made one but I don't think it's
so difficult
but with with hot hot steaming hot
vanilla uh cream cream sauce and and
then ice cold vanilla ice cream is the
best combination like together apple
strudel not only like usually if you get
it in a restaurant in Austria I think
usually it's served with a hot vanilla
sauce
but if I have the choice I usually also
add
um some vanilla ice cream to it
that gives it just the perfect balance
yeah and then that is no problem that
the the rest of it is so hot
you will not burn your tongue
your precious tongue because you eat the
hot apple strudel with the hot vanilla
sauce and then combine it with the ice
onion
[Music]
so good
how long is it to make apple pie you can
do with your eyes closed oh really
I wanna try both yeah
money yes meow meow coins we really
haven't run all the time now to get my
list yeah the that's a little family
cute we have nine coins
what's up here
was I here before
any Secret
I think if the game lets me leave this
island already I'm gonna do it for the
sake of keeping keeping the streamers
short as possible
what
I activated your sweet tooth
ah that reminds me I got one of the
snack boxes today and I thought it would
be like according to the website
follow me on Japan snack but uh yeah
Japan's Xbox but no somehow they messed
up the order
I got a special mix snack box
which was kind of disappointing because
I was hoping I could stream the Japan
snag box like next week or so
um
yeah no special snack box had like like
two snacks from Poland
uh one snack that I had before in a
snack box
I think it was maybe an American snack
you know
those
um how did I scribe them
they were I didn't like them hit number
one and they were like little Rings
donut rings and they were hard though
really
yeah hard ones kind of reminded me I
don't know it was very sugary too and
they had like um
pastel colors
Lifesavers what's it called life savers
um
yeah it was like mini Donuts but flat
ones and hard and they had pastel colors
and I didn't really like them I was not
impressed with them but I said oh like I
can imagine this being like
something that parents would give their
kids just made them shut up about snacks
maybe it was that maybe it was life
service I don't know
why that mm-hmm
yeah so they had that and and a nesty
ice tea that I do like but why is that
in there and
I don't remember the rest nothing too
special though
nothing that I would make a whole stream
about so I'm just gonna snack on it
privately oh
I need a theme you know the fact that
it's mixed makes makes it a bit more
difficult for me to make it into a
stream I was thinking maybe members but
even then
I know the snacks were not so special
actually there were less snacks than
usual but they were much bigger than
usual
so that's also a problem that there's
like really small variety
I think I'll go
let's go
Michael
wait
Apple so we're going back now was this
the last World
[Music]
um
how do we end this wait no wait tackle
headquarter okay okay go get
um
prefer small snacks easier to say for
later
I don't understand your logic small
Stacks would you would just eat fast if
you have a big snack then you have more
for later you just close it down
close it twist it close it
then eat more later
anyway here comes the feels oh really
okay
let me
uh
[Music]
what is wrong with you
where are you you have to come home
right now we're looking for you and we
will find you oh
you just be a normal kid
[Music]
now she's not nice anymore she was kind
of okay in the previous messages
well next time is table headquarters and
I went there and you might too
when we arrived I'll go on the head to
my office feel free to look around the
headquarters as you please
and when you're ready come find me
I have one final task for you
can't wait see you there one final task
only one task
oh
I'm really speeding for this game I
think
unless it's a really difficult long task
oh it looks pretty big
oh
[Laughter]
hey
oh it's just frog welcome to Taco where
the last company in the Friendship is
wait I know you
yeah because
um I'm quite famous in the Frog World
um
all right
my keys aren't working
nice job whatever wait I know you have
prevention you in the company group chat
you couldn't stop bragging about you
anyway have a great time and
headquarters make yourself at home
he's Starstruck
I haven't found one of these in a while
oh yeah I texted them
wait it's the same
oh this also again gave the other
Islands more to do oh
maybe that was just really
if you really want to play this game as
long as possible but it's actually not
necessary to really for the sake of the
story to go back holy [\h__\h]
no [\h__\h] way
huh
where is that person anyway
[Music]
you [\h__\h] let me know
stop frogging with me
oh my God where is she or he I don't
remember
looks really exhausting to play
it's time are you ready
it's Upon Us hit the ball back a few
five times get out don't let me crash
don't let crash into the ground
foreign
this will take a while probably
I need the coins oh no
no you mean the coins from the other
Islands the extra ones
oh my God oh my God
[Applause]
oh God oh God oh God where will it go
just gonna squish me don't squish the
Frog
[Music]
go ball go big ball big volleyball giant
volleyball giant ball
come come at me bro no I feel like it's
not going so far no never mind oh oh oh
yeah
yeah actually it's not so hard to hit it
because it has a huge surface
going kind of this way
oh oh
oh
Godzilla
[Music]
Nico's got arms
arms no no
[Music]
yeah I can keep this one going on and on
and on and on
because it's like Bowser fighting Boss
music
like I like some achievement if I do it
like 10 times or so I wonder
[Music]
oh no
no no no
[Music]
no no no no
she don't go down
[Music]
there
oh wait let me take the
can
find 10 times
okay back to the real world
give me my money
I know I know
cute Molly
pension
[Music]
okay you cannot make it any bigger than
this yeah I think it's fine this way it
was fun though I'll give you that
is
I didn't make music when you activate
though okay
a music pure party oh
okay okay okay
crabs I like you guys
I like crabs
band
bye
crab weeks in quinoa as as crab no
fishing well we're gonna fish anyway
oh it's
oh oh here everything is mixed here is
it
I can find any of them
perhaps
yeah that's cute
honey
[Laughter]
wait where where are we fishing here I
don't see anything jumping
this way
ah I saw something
oh
yeah sorry about that
and crab soon
with these hands I can I can do
sit
huh
ah wait
wait
I can become crab
me
I am crab and grab honey you just have
to uh edit my green into orange or red
or so and then I'll be very crab like oh
crap crap grab grab grab
I love crabs
okay okay focus focus kfb oh yeah kfp
it's still kfp no problem there
nothing wrong here
could be close here no
spy
oh maybe not
but here
[Music]
we're suck it all
no no Kiana also liked crabs not to eat
but just to
look at them we're very similar in that
regard
a neon tetra
I think that was one of the fish I can
have maybe for my fish tank I feel like
for Kiana is fishing
that was my accident
fell off came up
this yeah
yeah yeah yeah okay somewhere here
better be safe I'll wait for it kiddo oh
it worked
I don't know what was that jump I don't
know
fashion fish
it will help me pull a pond oh
really do they have that kind of
function they look pretty
foreign
did I go too far
it continues here
[Applause]
no way
no
out of bounds for bgm music
BTM okay
okay
don't talk to me now
a blue face whoa
the blueberry of the sea what there's
blue shrimps
do they taste like special
what
or is that the crab fish yeah you say
it's one of the [\h__\h] but no I didn't
they were called crab fish not not
shrimp
but it does did indeed kind of look like
those yeah yeah oh
did that work
crayfish Not crab fish yeah
one more one more one more
big is tastier yeah this one's name is
to be just a small one right
not the shrimp yeah yeah crab fish wet
crate crayfish might be gone then stupid
shrimp
sorry I didn't mean that I don't mean
I don't mean those
yes but I am curious because I've never
heard of blue shrimp before are they
like really hard to catch
wow what makes them blue anyway watching
too much Gouda
so we're good as shrimps eventually turn
blue
oh is is that the color they turned when
gouda doesn't stream for a while they
turn blue huh because they're blue about
it
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
you can do it
I Believe In You Nico I believe in you
your mom may not believe in you
no no bounces off they bounce off oh
wait I got it I got it
whoa where's that fish something about
go go go Rami
whoa
that's a pretty fish
a little
oh
I see your tape
honey gurami wow
fancy
and we see application frog
where do we go
[Music]
this is
oh
we're on that island again
a blessed blessed be the fruit
[Music]
I'm gonna call that far but okay maybe
there's something here that I missed
there's a secret or so
no
this place is [\h__\h] huge
don't go that way
this way
thank you
[Music]
just frogging around a little bit oh oh
where does it start is she there
uh yeah I see her okay whoa
hello
where they sell the flower bulbs good
thing no one noticed me sticking up wait
we're playing the game again
why do I have one of these
oh
ah now you have to like connect them
okay I see what we're doing
oh
can please redo I know what to do I have
to put that one first of all in the
middle
only free
wait maybe it's not this no this it has
to be this spot oh I know that this one
would go here
yeah
why does this one not fill up properly
maybe I can make wait is that not the
only connection I can make can I get
more of those
no
maybe I have an idea
under comments tonight we don't connect
it there maybe we connect it here
and what about the single one
maybe here
[Music]
foreign
I'm trying in my head before placing it
um
if I put it here I think maybe
let's try here
one
[Music]
who's that what about here
no no not this one
it's not what I wanted
that's possible you can put it on the
top of the same one
I'm thinking maybe no
uh wait what was my idea
I know this doesn't work
I was looking at this combination too
but hmm
three three
uh if I use it like this
[Music]
uh maybe
but then I mean I would put this here
and that would be fine
ah then I'm missing that one
damn these are like it's really
difficult and then the first one in the
first roll that was like ah it's so easy
no problem for me
but now
here
oh
oh okay
okay
[Music]
all right
oh we have a single one
we have connectors too no in this case I
don't think we have connectors
oh okay but we have two crosses oh dear
oh dear oh dear how about for example
one here
I put them on
[Music]
I mean
it could actually work
Maybe
[\h__\h] it pretty close I mean
ah
or Cena
[Music]
something like that
I feel like
um
start with this one if I place it here
it will only fill up these two I think
[Music]
right
and then like ah
I think I would feel this oh
genius
and I started with the right side
because then it goes down here then it's
not interrupted oh
never mind
same problem here oh
okay okay but I think the placement of
the crosses is in theory correct
just have to do something about that
daughter maybe it's not correct maybe
it's not correct
and I don't know I'm onto something
no no no no no no no no oh
okay that would fill up all of these but
I'm still missing one
[Music]
yeah got closer than before
a little bit closer than before
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
how about yeah oh oh what if I start
Ed
[Music]
one of these I could fill with the
square
nah but this is not
not enough unless I start maybe with one
on this I don't know man
no no no no
[Music]
ah one first block but
I need it here now
why would I want to block
stop the cross
ah we're here
so if I put the cross like here for
example we'll go all the way this way
and then this cross won't go down there
so in order to stop it just has to go
oh not the one
[Music]
uh-huh
[\h__\h]
here
no maybe not
oh
wait that didn't block anything though
[Music]
um
so yeah what if I press here no
oh [\h__\h] that was by accident
I was correct with the one the first one
I forgot where to put it
[Music]
there
wait what if I
now go for the one
let's say uh yeah let's say I put it
here
then the left cross could go there and
yeah yeah yeah
yeah
start with the left cross after putting
this one there
foreign
[Music]
quite challenging this one is a lot
smaller
[Music]
oh wait what where's the cross
there's like a space for it they pick it
up oh I did
and we have a cross and uh
oh and a pot to connect oh okay okay
that's why it's like smaller the pot
makes it a bit more of a thinker What if
I
put it here oh
what if I put it here
and um
I know what I'm thinking
um
what I know
[Music]
ah
does that work if I put this in the
middle
oh yeah and then yeah
let's go
oh
look at all
one more maybe I think the last one is
next one
oh this one's big
enough
and with a connector
[Music]
let's just put it here for now because I
don't know man
um nah it probably has to go here
because otherwise I don't know how I
would reach those two over there
probably girls here
probably so oof
let's start Mimi you know we need to get
an image you know
let's start it's gonna like interrupt
each other again probably
over there when I want to place one here
let's see what we will be missing
so let's say we put this one here
and then we put
example this one here and I would only
be missing
one more
here
but I don't know if overall this is the
way to go anyway
mm-hmm
visualize it
visualize it I guess I really need to
use that one to block something or maybe
again this one first actually hmm
[Music]
oh wait I didn't even use this one yet
I wonder if I'm correct though by
putting this one here at least
yeah okay
then let's wiggle this I wonder if this
one was roughly correct
I put it here it gets like a good corner
is this one good too
feels good
no
Wonder left you guys are looking up to
the solutions aren't you
oh [\h__\h] I forgot but it's fine I think
it's fun
didn't necessarily mess up anything with
you
ah
[Music]
yeah now if I place the cross here
goes there so we want to block it with a
single one
if I block here it should be fine
[Music]
wow
it looked like really difficult in the
beginning but it was actually fine it
felt you know because it's so big it
would be
very difficult to get right oh
knock on the onions break and look
oh
frogs
wait a minute I plan to give my brother
guns or all these white flowers on his
wedding oh that's a good way of using
them she's still single but I'm thinking
this will really put a flame under his
butt he can't possibly oh [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
flame on his butt I would like to make a
joke about that about Kiara somehow but
I'm not sure how
yeah
oh buddy
are you on the top floor oh yeah
[Music]
with this new technology I can finally
experience the feeling of a294400 tiny
LED lights flashing rapidly in front of
my eyes wow
hello
are you gyrus no Nico Alpha 0.45 they
told me I would be the star of my own
game oh but you like the testing model
that they tested out things of
like just a stigma is that what game
developers do in the beginning
oh Phoenix
turns out they only use me for
prototyping do you think you fancy all
of your colors and all
to me you're just a tacky jerk oh Buzz
office wow what an ass all these are
here again yeah that was why they came
from the store
looks like it takes a lot of work when
they write mine would spend their time
making video games
media games yeah
oh oh that's another one of these games
um let's try
oh I wonder if these coins count for the
coins you can get
because they're behind the keys
I wonder
[Music]
oh wind machine
hello hello
[Music]
you happy
your
this one how do you
hmm
chill music what
ah
[Music]
she do be platforming whoa whoa
oh
breakfast baby
oh my God what's up you smile oh
like a crunk puppet hello I'm Rebel frog
I'm here to An Answer gaming experience
would you like me to assist you by
moving a colored Puck perhaps you would
like me to move a spinning top what does
that mean
because every company needs a game
development Branch yeah you do
I've been able to make this game right
okay is that all that was to this
um building
oh
Mike
too good
brush brush
brush
what's this again
no bro I was thinking of broom yeah but
it's a mop
maybe I was combining broom and no I
don't know I don't know man
yeah
you want the apples my secret technique
is quite simple first make sure you have
10 apples so I can press down and make
sure to hold it
don't let go jump until you're
thoroughly squished then release and you
think you can do that what
you little [\h__\h] you never told me about
that
oh but it takes 10 apples
oh my God
wait you see the poster it says I want
to leave it's a it's a crow being
abducted by a alien
and frog
oh wait I haven't seen you in a long
time
why was she not in the other levels was
that a bug
anyone who played the game did you meet
her in the other levels that where I
didn't see her
I honestly Wonder
ful performance oh
yeah I'm not only a food concert I'm
also a high-tech businessman but I'm not
here to do business I found actually
hosts a variety of bugs she shows up now
since you got the nose
oh
oh okay
put her her thing was already there
that's weird
melange of 30 specimens
oh but even though I have more than
enough from other Islands they have to
be like collected from this island okay
Well it can't be any of them
all right
I'll be back and in Japanese that was
actually a pun
I also um announced this stream in
Japanese with a pun I don't know if you
guys noticed
but I wrote in Japanese if this game
doesn't actually have frogs I'll go home
so
going home means Kyle and frog means
kind of so there were kind of two times
someone needs to do the dishes
oh my God are you a coffee addicted
what animal called a little more
hey hey
no yes
I like the tail was so fluffy and long
[Music]
it's dedicated to accounting that means
we make up random numbers and send them
to the tax bro I'm just kidding that
would be fraud and you're not a fraud
frog right not no frog frog
what the frog is the capital gains tax
no idea man
I
I think you're high on coffee very thing
so
going slow I don't know not need to get
back to work okay
[Music]
I don't think they're okay oh there's a
cassette tape there rivet gold all the
posters are so fun I actually want them
I want those posters
um
[\h__\h]
oh well done you can do it in this game
but not in Super Mario games
although yeah I don't know was I
I think in in 2D I would have been able
to do it okay but in 3D
I'm not good at little jumps I think
that was that was the problem
what did I just say there an Apple
probably just an apple
yeah just an apple
did I look at this place
no no I did not are you also selling me
a coin
lazy lazy
I don't think wall jumping was a problem
and just generally I was sure and I
played I thought r d stood for rice and
dumplings oh I'm just starving wait what
was Art where's r d stand for
nothing work related
[Music]
um
guys surely know
researching a cost of implementing
stabilizers in our standard equipment
all people need friends too
at research and development oh
boom
huh
and some frog was there
[Music]
and let me look at you closely
it's got sushi on his head with the soy
sauce and I think he's wearing a mask no
no he's a he has something in his mouth
for this guy
what is that I don't eat sushi much so I
don't know why I don't know it doesn't
look familiar to me
oh what the hell are you
[\h__\h] property oh
your kid that was always going on about
nice to meet you wanna be friends no
no
I refuse
magical
oh do you look here not that it matters
this guy my assistant needs an immediate
vacation just look at how miserable he
is talk to me if you're up for the job
oh
[Music]
dear what did I do
I killed another frog
with my assistant's job to listen to
what I have to say you know what my
schedule is like my Roy's deepest famous
questions is this like a quiz anyway
blah blah corporate Synergy blah blah
yearly random Revenue
someone just asked me where do I see
yourself
where do you see yourself in five years
and I was like frogs don't even live
that long probably long story short I
spiral a little bit and now I ruin the
motorcycle and likes free skateboard
skate frog
what am I supposed to do with those I'm
a Frog
all right yeah good point good point
you're a frog Mama frog we're both wrong
you and me we're from
same kind of worries
no offense do you ever wonder like
what's up with the ocean yeah totally
like from Amazon really like the ocean I
think
we prefer you know lakes and ponds so at
the ocean
so big and so deep whatever lives in
deepest parts it's even with the cute or
extremely terrifying I think it's
terrifying
someone needs to figure out this big
stuff can you keep a secret last week I
met someone who I was totally into
her name is froggiana she's freaking hot
like in terms of frog hotness
look like she was into me too
[Music]
nah
don't listen to him guys
very handsome [\h__\h] for smile turns out I
was looking at something called
embarrassed
laughs
it's just back battling because he heard
me turning him down
I think I'd be mad but the first step in
finding love is finding loving yourself
you know
that's a good thanks assistant number
23. she who's some money for you
kill 10 coins that was relatively easy
hmm
what do you mean not much resemblance
that's so rude
[Laughter]
oh is it all the frogs I talked to
yeah
you're looking at the 10 time employee
of the month oh
[Music]
oh autographs are 10 bucks a piece they
look like you want to become employee of
the month so hi
I just wanted to use a small fry maybe
once I'll retire you'll have a chance
24 out of 70. oh no that's my the total
coins I got
and what happens if it's full I got the
last one the last picture
I know how these things connect to each
other but
okay that's two years old yeah but the
truth is in frog ears that's not really
a baby anymore that's also the reason
why I'm not uh not a tadpole but a frog
yeah
I was looking for a bathroom but I got
lost can you bring me back to Sarah
shell yeah don't jump more than two
times please
huh
sir shell was
um
[Music]
Michelle was
um
the most recent one
how do we get in here without jumping
do I just talk to the giraffe
where's the giraffe
wouldn't I be able to see the giraffe
because it's really tall
two times two times he says
that's why I get to jump twice
maybe I can do it without jumping
what's up with that sticking
oh did that count I wonder so we're
going
oh oh the bath house was it the bath
house
uh I don't remember where the hell that
dude was
um
[\h__\h] which button is it
I wanna mess it up what if I mess it up
I think it's this one
a bath house
is he in that in darling wasn't he like
in in that the first
bath house
well you have to explain to me how I
lost my friend
why is he not on top of me anymore
how come
foreign
Island
maybe he was here yeah
oh I just saw a bath up there that's
probably where he is and I can just do
like a big jump okay I'm just assuming
that's where he is
holy hack frog cook who's the green
what's wrong with your fans no lies I'll
fix it for you
because
oh can I stay like this you're not
supposed to be no I am I am I am
my my eyes are kind of low though and it
makes it look like I have ears up there
where are you supposed to be very
peculiar otherwise no no
no one wanted to be frog
the superior race man
[Music]
yeah looking for a bathroom yeah yeah
okay we'll get you again yeah
is there
I don't actually know let's see what was
that okay
maybe this won't even help this thing
here
I don't know where that leads me
God damn it it does count as a jump
let's just put him back
again
this felt very Super Mario like
[Music]
did that count as a job as a jump
ER I did not press jump
so I would hope it doesn't count
okay I think I know where I want to go
up there I can probably do it with one
jump with the ultra jump
but I have to do it right
okay that might have may have counted as
one jump okay okay we only got to the
first level
foreign
okay what's the real path to take I
wonder oh
interesting
[\h__\h]
oh oh
what's going on here oh
are you kidding me
how difficult is it to finish this game
because even though I'm enjoying a rally
I have a feeling that I will get very
many sign now but if I if I have to go
back to the other worlds and do a bunch
of other quests and don't feel like it
yeah it was meant to be five hours long
and we're about to get to the five hours
yeah so I mean it's fair it's fair
do I just have to get the 15 coins
pop to the pepper
maybe maybe only that
[Music]
I can do that
it's not very boring bling it's not
boing booing at all
[Applause]
I thought it was goodbye
foreign
two out of five
froggy Wawa also has no boing boing
oh that reminds me the other day when I
had the recording with
some
en members
you know in the waiting time well not
Ian movies but like English speaking
members in the waiting time
um
I don't know how we got to the topic
what is this stuff
I don't know how we got to the topic but
um I introduced them to this Japanese
meme song you know
um some of you might know it and I might
have sang it before I mentioned it
before
[Music]
um
it talks about all the cups
old sizes
and they were fascinated by it
that's the one time where I felt like oh
finally I'm the one teaching the memes
finally I feel like I know something and
they they're entertained by it
wait was this not here before
it's a different one
yeah that was you before I guess rebuilt
itself
[Music]
did I go here before
[Applause]
on it ah this place
what about here
oh yeah I was here before too I'm
getting confused
what have I what am I missing one more
bun oh yeah yeah
okay let's get the one more bug
oh ah this guy also I don't I don't know
I don't want to do a stupid mission
okay I got that
[Music]
somewhere down here I think not so hard
to find
[Music]
it
wait
wasn't she on the ground level
uh
[Music]
I feel like I remember her being on the
ground level
cute
[Music]
go frog go
oh yeah I could go to the previous
levels to give her the bugs there yeah
that's true
ah here it is
just do it
it's an absolutely terrifying oh God
she even eats them like seven ones at
once she should enjoy them one by one
huh
It Blend so beautiful and very tasty
thank you
15 coins they said right
I hope that leads to the end
let's go to the other islands and I
think I can get two more coins because I
remember at least two missing ladies
okay I should be
easy
[Music]
yeah yeah okay let's go
thank you why is this rainbow I Love
Trains
your baby loves strings
cute Rock
ah
okay so I don't remember a lady here a
butt oh
I'm guessing this means everywhere what
these question marks are is where we
have new quests but there's not one at
the bath house
all right let's go to the public pool
first
I mean we could also maybe find a
different Mission since it's really just
two that we need we'll probably find
something oh this was the one with the
the cicadas they're kind of hard to get
do I even have pretty I don't think so
16.
you guys
[Music]
because they're a bit hard to see in
there but they're always on surfaces
walls
I guess when you aim for that they might
not be so difficult to get
[Music]
there you go yeah that's fine once you
aim for them
okay here's a couple here's so many
[Music]
almost have them
hey
one more here oh it's on that side no
wrong side
oh
the flower game is here now
I was like did I miss it last time no
it's new isn't that oh I wonder how
difficult it is
26. we can try this one
after I get those bugs
huh
or apples
we've really sunken into a very cozy
mood haven't we guys
I hope it's not too boring for you guys
it's just I don't know all these games
I'm playing they're so cozy I I like
them
but they're just very very cozy
so not much like woohoo
what excitement okay
thank you for the Super Chat Channel
comfy it is I know but I know like
normally people desire more exciting
exciting stuff
wait wait wait where's the lady again up
isn't she up there
somewhere here I remember she had like
everything set up
oh isn't she here okay no
I make everything special
just me being here
I'm going crazy I thought she was here
ah I see her
can we play soccer now
is that a game
crickets
oh God
yeah is this what you call oh yeah boy
there's definitely a gap but the Gap is
the terrifying one normally is it kind
of the other way around
do I have a gap moment
oh no I don't think you can play
I think this one I broke before
pretty sure yeah okay let's play The
Flower game
[Music]
okay let's see
we have I should be easy
yeah okay I see it I see it
[Music]
foreign
I will stop it
uh here
and then one replace here oh [\h__\h] no way
Maybe
sneeze jaw yeah I'm sneezing a lot today
ah
no need to stop
um but if I put a cross here
then I would need two single ones one
here and one here
[Music]
what I want to do is definitely place
across here so it goes over here and
over here ah and then we'll go down here
and down here but we don't want that so
we place I think here
watch and learn
um
yeah
yay
Santa
genius okay we have a cross or two
no only one and uh a single and a square
okay
cross probably goes here
or maybe not maybe a cross goes here
I don't know let's try
that that's obviously not it but I want
to put it there now to look at it
[Music]
maybe we might have to
foreign
I don't know
if I put the cross here it goes up there
and there
I probably has to go
[Music]
quick
maybe the cross goes
here goes up and down nothing right
um
no
cross left
wow
here
I see
visualize it
[Music]
'll help
me
where is she
ah yeah
this is the last time I'm helping you I
think I hope
is this it
is
[Music]
oh let's go I want to go back
I'm gonna finish this
is the anyone who knows how to play the
game
is that all I need those 15 coins and
then I'll I'll get I'll reach the end or
is there more to it
are they gonna be like well wait there's
more
maybe a bus fight oh
that's all yeah
another game finished on Frankie Lama's
game finishing list so far I have 100
finishing uh rate
pretty impressed as I would say
and when do we go where was it again up
here yeah yeah yeah yeah I see you
foreign
I know what I'm just gonna use my apples
why am I why am I suffering why do I
make myself suffer oh wait there's
actually
this one what why is that there
[Music]
perfect
konnichiwa frog
wait wait
wait
I'll see hey hey
who's fixing oh fix frog
generous
these frogs are just like us at kfp
because we also have you know all kinds
of France and tadpoles or different
kinds of jobs right
is that your office
you have a rooftop office so cool what
was that clip did you see that
I'll do it again whoa
okay sorry I I may have um
lost all your documents you may be fired
now
sorry about that great you're here it's
time for your final class can you guess
what it is it's a job interview we can't
be hiring someone without the classic
cardboard staple that's a formal
interview people like to stress the
meaning of formal music
[Music]
question one the first what is my name
Peppa
no right answers in a job interview but
this is a good one question two the one
after the first what is your name Nico
the one that would kill me if I had a
big glowing eye probably the case of
experience do you have of being a
professional friend
as many as you need me to
[Music]
this position
bunny we're helping others of course of
course
[Music]
what's 41 Square
huh
[Music]
but I don't think that surely the game
did not expect you to get this one right
right it would just be like ah this was
just you know you didn't have to get
this one right I think oh I have no idea
he doesn't even know
keep that in mind how many questions
have I asked
five
we're at class six alternative but
before we started I asked it's time for
your final test can you guess what it is
question seven oh [\h__\h] he keeps on
saying
[Music]
much more stressful than social direct
is the future where do you see yourself
in five years
um don't want to think about that right
but hopefully swimming in cash I don't
know Moon president
IAL
[Music]
we're getting close to the end what is
the name of the forest we visited
Salmon Creek
I know that one
the penultimate you think you'll get the
job Yeah
final one one more question fans do
enjoy being a professional friend
do
you can't improve unless you're enjoying
yourself those were all the questions I
have I've got to process this whether
you got a job or not I can't say we'll
send you an email tomorrow tomorrow
it's been a busy trial period you must
be tired thank you for your time I'll be
sending you home now goodbye
yeah
yeah oh
[Music]
Homes at home Dad
I won't tell her where you are
he's more chilling mom huh I just wanted
to see you I'm sorry how things went I
should have protected you there's not
nothing about this it's your fault you
look great enough
[Music]
it might be best if you'll keep living
here in this [\h__\h] Subway because this
is where you
where it's okay to have your child
continue living it yeah
how can you not like I don't know get
your child hotel or something at least
or friends place if there's anything you
need I'm just a phone call away oh it
looks like my step is coming up see you
around I love you
[Music]
how did you manage to find me
um maybe you have like a GPS tracker on
you
doesn't matter I'm glad I got to see him
again
totally screwed that job interview
kiddle don't even wear those questions
there aren't any other channel listings
in this area what if I have to move on
again you know I guess I can start
packing when I get home it sucks I don't
want to move kid on this place is
actually kind of nice first time in a
while I felt like I belonged somewhere I
cannot maybe some things are too good to
be true
hmm
[Music]
no
home
huh
[Music]
million
[Applause]
[Music]
wow
hello
[Music]
pepper told you to go home wanted to
survives you
[Music]
but wouldn't the more tainted ending
have been for my family to accept me and
then I can go to my actual home
no
the crew a little bit of where you could
become a play of the month
yay hello so many of you yo look at you
this is Hot Shot yeah I've heard you're
a professional friend that sounds like
the perfect job for you
thank you
and I want to talk to you
can oh on the train kid is up there hell
no I'm having some cake too
I can talk to this game machine blippi
you wanted that was a long mom for
someone who is a 300 pound arcade card
thank you so much for playing my game
your game oh yeah I guess I played a few
times yeah I don't want to talk to the
furries I only want to talk to frogs
can you have you heard about the
employee of the month you should check
it out
it's the last spot me
oh that would be sweet
[Music]
is this my home oh
it is I just went in there and thought
maybe I can find something someone
the end
I'm 6 out of 75. that's not so bad
oh wow
[Music]
[Applause]
I didn't expect this ending
the the meaning of the ending is not so
wholesome yeah I found a new family but
this also kind of feels like it's all
just my imagination
I'm feeling
down
making up with my family my mom
understanding what the character is
going through
would be more wholesome kind of get all
um
and then understanding that this whole
game was just
a way of the character coping and going
for their emotion schedule
but oil oil or oil oil
why are we back here now automatically
to look at that
it's empty though
why did you bring me here
why don't you bring me here game I'm
confused this is just where I start
after ending the game
this should be me
wait it can be me also interesting how
it waits
is this a bug or
those of the frogs
are they stuck in the wall
oh my God they're stuck in the wall we
have to let them get out
they may be smiling but that's because
they're stuck
like you
like forever living person into a pit
and then poor
uh like we have buried them alive pour
some um
the stuff that you make the floor above
on top of it
it's terrifying absolutely terrifying
they they could be still alive we have
to open it up save them
anyway
see
it's one of my favorite frogs
concrete yeah that's a little lemon
concrete cement yeah
wow
[Music]
I like the oh wait he's playing the
accurate music now
I like the the the platforming I like
the mini games I like the characters the
Brows were absolutely adorable I like
that there were so many of them hmm
foreign
[Music]
was fun to play a platforming game for
once that doesn't have like you know
serious fighting and all that
boom boom boom boom
instead we had a wholesale mobile game
and it's about you know some
problems that this character is going
through
ah
and no enemies just friends
and we learned that the real friends in
your life are the ones that give you
money
[Music]
yeah so I'm not gonna read some chess
because it's really late and I have to
cook I really have to I have to make
some food for myself I think tomorrow we
have an early member stream and then
later we have another stream
the VR Rock was beautiful
yo it sounds amazing with trumpet
oh
I love trumpet kid all
[Music]
and I think I'm just gonna make some
spaghetti because one of the recipes I
got for this week just for the sake of
Simplicity I got myself a
Bolognese spaghetti bolognese
ingredients
and I already know how to make it so I
don't even have to look at the recipe
spaghetti
[Music]
um
when the ending let me
let me get on top
of the big frog tool
ready
I wanna die
let me hear me
no space for me
come here
I'll be here
thank you for watching me play here Here
Comes Nicole this one is this this is
Nicole over there
yay
thank you for the recommendation yeah
and tomorrow maybe I'll leave a just
play something slight Aspire
um and then later we'll play VR Rock if
uh I'll get it to work properly
hopefully she'll be fine I mean
VR I'll figure it out
[Music]
I put up the reservation for the members
now and then on the VR wrong reservation
I pulled up after I wake up
okay thank you thank you
[Music]
two times
two two thumb stream tomorrow you know
okay good night everybody
[Music]
ah Ruby Daddy yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
on
oh
[Music]
thank you Carlos
thank you
[Music]