[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
okay
do you hear the slight mario music in
the background
so let me move the microphone a
[Music]
well um
welcome to the membership thank you for
joining everyone
er we have come here together
to see this majestic phoenix play
super mario 64 again to experience the
suffering and the pain
all together and laugh at her together
i honestly hoped
to never see
[Music]
the day again where i play this game
because it's just too much
suffering but do i have a choice
yes but whatever
therefore i have chosen
once again my own suffering you must
understand i am a phoenix
i am uh used to dying i'm used to to
pain i'm used to suffering
so this is just what i do this is my
genre my favorite game genre i said is
rpgs but in some way it's just
my favorite game genre is suffering
it's a pain uh
yeah so
today
so it's been a while it's been a while
uh
i i must uh confess i probably
already unlearned everything i learned
before
but today i'm
playing with a pro controller which is
something
you guys kept recommending me
so that might help out a little bit i
hope
so so now
i'm trying to a pro gamer hell yeah
i'm trying to procrastinate so i don't
have to play but
i did this to myself
i guess we gotta go do i have to
make the game oh wait do you still hear
it now
is it uh is it too loud or
too too quiet
it's good
[Music]
too quiet good
i believe in the ones who say it's good
yeah yeah
what i already have 27 stars how did
that happen
oh okay you guys know i am i currently
don't have a hat yeah uh
[Music]
one second
i got a dress accordingly
um i gotta
[\h__\h] that
guy
uh what my brain is not working actually
i just took a nap
i just took a nap i don't know how to do
things
you did not see that yeah what was i
going to do oh
here i am again unfortunately
i've lost my hats
goodbye saraba boshi saraba
that's the only place where you can lose
your hat right
well today's quest is to get my hats
back
hopefully soon
because i must say i feel a bit naked
without hats
let's see how it feels to play the game
with the pro controller
uh offering last time
i fell down a hole and
fell down that river and was absolutely
devastated is that when i quit the
stream yeah
[Music]
oh yeah i take more damage without the
head yeah i gotta take it back
oh where's the desert again how did i
get to the desert again
no where do i get my hat back wait where
is it is it in here
wait why does that keep surprising me
oh my god i'm crying
hidden door thing right the hidden wall
thing
oh my god can you imagine me playing
playing a horror game my hat must be
here
stand tall on the four pillars what
stand tall i have to fly again oh
uh i feel like actually maybe i
already feel like the controls are
much easier
and the camera is so much so much easier
to switch what
what it changes so much
well it probably still doesn't ah change
my skill
all righty um i'm borrowing this pro
controller right now but i might as well
ah
get it myself if it helps this much
okay whatever we'll just heal ourselves
but wait no this gives me so much damage
so if the second one hits me i'll
actually die
so better be careful uh you go here here
then down down
the suffering without my hats
all the damage what do i have to do in
this mission anyway go on the
pillars but for what
oh my head hurts actually legit my head
hurts
yes i need my hats wait wait
no
concentration okay we just started out
i'm still like a bit uh
blue as you have noticed
i'm not
that much
that's our those were some pretty quick
depths let's go back go back
go away spikey thing
okay okay
concentration guys
okay this is my least favorite place
forever and ever
[Music]
get in the water where's that bastard
who stole my hat
where's that bastard huh
do i need that actually
what do i do once i'm on the pillars
question chat what do i do
and just let's just see hello
[\h__\h]
is that what i do i just hit him
come come
[\h__\h] come here
[Music]
i don't understand like they need to
give me better descriptions of what i do
well i got my hat back
does the birds target me when i'm over
here
maybe not but other things will target
me you're safe nowhere
ah please don't hit me when's that
[Music]
don't worry this time i got it
i got my hats back wow okay so what do i
do
probably not for long this is probably
not where i go
what do i do okay okay chad please tell
me what's
ground pound yeah for real about this
camera
turn around
ground pounds under you're for real
right you're not trying to make a joke
right right okay how do i do that
wait i forgot that is a joke oh
oh oh
we'll do it
stand on the pills you don't oh what i
just have to stand on them
well well well how do we get on the
other two
look closer huh
one second please
unbelievable this is unbelievable
no respect have you no respect my friend
well we are not friends unbelievable
honestly wow
how do i get to the other one do i need
to like uh
fly up there i guess i probably do have
to okay
let's try it from here come on
we'll get the hats back late i should ah
but you die so quickly without
it you will pay for this can i
burn this
don't say don't say evil words kiara
don't
calm down well the only way to get to
the other two is by
flying to them right
can i shouldn't this be possible with
and papa no i'm not
i'm not aiming for the sun
[Music]
no my papa i know you want it but it's
not happening
how high does that have to be will i die
i feel like i'm going to die aim for the
sun
no why is it flying right there
can you [\h__\h] off for one second
let's go
i can read those two really easily but
we have to do the difficult ones first
what do i get tonight maybe flying after
yahoo
[Applause]
[Music]
will we do any progress today
okay that was obviously a glitch okay
you cannot count that you cannot count
that
okay
we're not counting that at kfp
i'm gonna wait here on the mat
nice
[Music]
where are we going where are we going ah
no hat is dangerous i'm living the
dangerous life
safe wow come on come on
come on come on come on come on baby
is here yes smart
bird very smart bird atomic
okay okay okay i probably need
the wings huh
[Music]
wow
where am i okay
okay find the target
find the target where is the target
this desert and flying
will forever be the death of me
how about we get our hat back and then
ditch the desert
forever why is it disconnecting
hello i'm back probably
yeah yeah it keeps on doing that um
but only for like really short moments
so don't don't
don't pay any attention to that
we go
number one give me back my hat number
two
give me back my head [\h__\h]
for me like i'm so mad
i'm aggressive today okay i will not
accept
theft
[Music]
oh wait that's me
thank you for the super chat but it's
not even my oh my god i'm
like dead i'm like that ah wait where
did i meet where did i meet
[Music]
don't die
don't die is this only so hard for me
am i the only one suffering in mario 64.
what some there's like so many like
professional mario 64 players they gotta
teach me
but this this must have been the right
strategy right
okay okay okay i wonder how close i was
to the time limit though from the
from the hat
okay where do we go
maybe let's try to not aim too high
let's oh smite smash my spot nice safe
concentrate concentrate concentrate
concentrate hello
wait is did that just land on the ah
i know oh okay thank you
what do i do now
[Music]
this is suffering okay
[Laughter]
yeah these are about the same noises
that phoenixes make when they give birth
[Laughter]
okay we can do this we can do this i i i
definitely saw progress
i am seeing progress
let's go let's go let's go
first here
where's my hat by the way
[Music]
you don't have it anymore do you no
oh he has it didn't i kick it off from
you
okay okay okay
round of professional flying simulator
with
takamasi
[Music]
it was real it was really not bad last
time so
not bad
while we're at it smash that
mf real hard in his stupid
face
where am i
okay
[Music]
how do i do this how how
how do i do this tell me
tell me i need to know
ground pounds ah
i should but i forgot how to do that in
the first place
we're at the beginning again
[Music]
ah oh you got it oh
okay let's go is there no easier isn't
there
like wings up here too how do i get
to that one
anyway i don't care i don't care
i'm going and why is everyone always
standing in my way
yes
i just hurt my own ear of that imagine
oh my god
chandler oh my god
chandler bingham
where's your head well i asked myself
that too every goddamn day when i play
super mario 64.
ah here right
must be here yes
i'm recently re-watching friends that's
that's why i every time i
i hear myself saying oh my god
i gotta think of that
here i am again ah but without damage
hello
okay you guys said ground pound when i'm
like around there
that's why you change the camera
[Music]
my hands are sweating
i believe in myself a little bit
but i'm flying so fast how can i do robo
but do i have to press the jump up
button
even though i'm in the air where the
hell are we going okay chill
chill chill chill
okay oh
almost okay we're safe here though
that's all good
[Music]
just leave me alone
no
is
[Music]
but whatever
yeah because i kind of need the cannon
anyway right i need the cannon
i got my hat
oh if you steal my heart one more time
you steal my hat one more time i'm gonna
code you out of the game
gonna coat that stupid bird out of the
game i don't know how that works but
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
quick
what quick [\h__\h]
[Music]
what
what's up bird's name
what's that bird's name he's on my list
he's the only name on my list forever
faster
okay two two
two ah quiet come on
where is it where is it i don't [\h__\h]
say it
oh no murray what are you doing mario
mario mario
[Laughter]
but what now i just can't reach that is
there no easier way to reach it
oh
i think i've seen that before wait
shell shell shell shell
you need to use a green shell you tell
me that now
you tell me that now are you for real
you tell me that now
huh
[Music]
where is the shell only two only two
steps yeah i know i know
what
ah what's on the grey platform
in yellow box great platform and yep
yellow box
ah okay
after dying a billion times
i have found out how to do it
is you how i get up there are you the
one
let's see no ah
[Music]
maybe not uh when i get up there
it's up there right triple jumped up
really
hop on the shiny shell and ride wherever
you want to go shred those enemies oh
you
know i'll be shredding those mother
okay this should make it so much easier
right
okay let's go
okay does that count they're standing
did that count
as standing on it
[Music]
does that does that count no yes i'm
done
boy i'm done you want me to do it again
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no okay don't kill me now where is it
where is it where is it where is it
where is it where
[Music]
go there yes this is safe this is a safe
zone almost
oh my god where's the star
[Music]
camera
top top of the pyramid
do i have to fly up there or get the
shell or
[Music]
she lacks critical information
that means i need to shell again
fly or climb it flying
is my strong suit
us yes yes
why is it always like that
okay you know what i go here again
my pleasure it where's the show
there's a shell
only one shell
[Music]
huh
okay um
in that case yeah maybe
um maybe the god damn it
in that case oh my god wait where is the
was it always like without the top
was it always like that it's a little
colder
i feel like no get the hat back oh hell
yeah
i'm not gonna die now the last thing i
will do now is
die
[Music]
okay get that nice crystal clear water
and then we shall teleport
okay but with the hat
i suppose
okay now don't mess up
how high should we aim and don't save
for the sun
oh no no no no no
[Music]
this is okay this this is fine because
um
i thought i have to fly again but that's
not true i have to just use the shell
again
and maybe if we're fast we can
then use the shell to get up on on
the on the pyramid where's her hat
well since mario doesn't have his stupid
goddamn head
i'm i'm one of them simple
what i'm just i'm just doing the same
thing
because it's cute
[Music]
sympathetic
ah sympathizing hell yeah
oh god okay
[Music]
okay
okay okay how did i do it the first time
no i mean we can do that i guess we can
do that
but i can obviously not do it when i
wanna do it
okay i'm showing you the coolest tricks
here
the uh
[Music]
the plan is my friends one
two three and then go straight up the
pyramid
if it uh
if it's um if it's ready because we had
to do two rounds apparently we weren't
properly
on each of the pillars
next
probably that counted should it be fine
should be fine
where did it go where the [\h__\h] did that
chill go
huh
just kill myself
get your hat back what does that even
help me anymore in this situation it
doesn't help me
how to how to play the same level
uh for an hour in super mario 64.
this is how you do
i would say this is quite the challenge
you know
mario wow
[Music]
why why did it break why did it break
why did it break
come on mario we are friends you and me
right i mean we've had some rough times
but you can't do this to me
i gotta make some progress in this game
okay
okay nice good job last one come on and
then we go straight up the pyramid you
know what
you know how to do it right okay
no no no no
mario it's not that hard mario
it's it it is not that hard
okay
is there like there's probably like
communities right
for mario super mario 64 speedrunners
they'd be looking at my stream and
they'll be laughing at me they'd be like
this [\h__\h] eh
just as someone wrote in a chat she's
getting better
just as someone wrote in the chat she's
getting
better i want to prove that to people
too
okay that that was done had some style i
must say
you go back one hour same level
who can do that huh
who can actually do that
that requires quite the skill mario by
the way you only have to go
straight
i will not give up
give me my hat kyle said [\h__\h]
get out of there mario we don't have
time for your [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
he's gone come back come back oh you're
scared huh
[Music]
get your hand back where is your hat is
it in the air
what he has it again okay i'll just
forever live without my hat
who cares
[Music]
it was on the pillar oh
i guess um
don't look at the ghost don't waste it
again on the other side okay don't look
at it
[Music]
kiara there's a ghost i don't want to
see it
[Music]
so i guess when i play super mario 64
it just comes with an extra challenge
because i'm just such a pro player
it just comes with the challenge of me
playing without a hat
it just makes it that's why i'm failing
so much okay
yeah yeah almost
you almost had it mario
wow wow nice camera
okay we can do this
we can do it concentrate
if only the camera wouldn't change
because i'm not
changing it oh this is going well
come on come on yes and go
up no no no no
no no
[Music]
i will kill someone today
tell me why
tell me
you know i wanted to be like a calm
skilled wholesome kind of player
i wanted to be respected by the people
and yet this game keeps making a fool
out of me
oh okay here we go
again why
[Music]
it's okay i can do it i can do it i can
do it i can do it
[Music]
you know what i hate the controller is
the controller is like
pumping like a heartbeat it's making me
quite anxious okay now here yes smooth
smooth [\h__\h] you can't
ah no no no no no no no
can i not get up there with the shell
can i not is it not possible
[Music]
excuse me
uh what you need to fly you can just
jump there
you can but you need to jump
you can walk up the sides of the pillows
without the shell no but there's
quicksand about
around one of them or the answer has
only two of them
just keep jumping forward if with the
shell or without the shell
can i do it without the shell
super chat sneezing super jacked
never give up yeah isn't this
basically your theme song
never gonna give you up i'm never gonna
let you
down never gonna run around
to search you
[Music]
i don't know the lyrics to be honest
okay so question to the chat
once the star is there
should i try to get up there with the
shell and keep on jumping jumping
jumping
quick answer quick answer please
no what do i do what do i do then
do i just i just i just wait until it
runs out and then we find a different
way
but don't tell me it's flying because
i'm just too [\h__\h] stupid to fly
we have seen that okay there it is
where do we go okay wait here
nice
okay what do we do use the cannon use
the stairs where stairs inside
i guess we can go inside
to your right there's no stairs
you think i can outside you think i can
go up there
jump up i'm scared
you think i can just jump up there i'm
gonna slip and then slide down there
i swear to you it will happen
back flip back
[Music]
the thing is it actually does a lot of
damage now so
okay let's do that come
calm
we will not [\h__\h] up this time
you know i just made a unpred a
coincidental pun in japanese i said
i would say i will get the star for sure
but
tony nuku means go and get it but tony
nico
also means bird meat
[Laughter]
ugh
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
aah
ah
uh
i'm a
[Music]
mario get your
ass up from that
two two
[Music]
one why are they moving the [\h__\h] are you
doing
i don't have time anymore just
okay
[Music]
what is this camera
all the screaming killed my voice
i wanted this
[Music]
what is this camera why does it keep
moving just oh my god
oh my god
oh my oh my god like you wanna
wha what is your problem
[Music]
oh oh what did i what did i do to make
the camera [\h__\h] around
so much
[Music]
right position
almost yes
where are we
mamma mia
[Music]
um
i am single-handedly
going to kill you mario
i will kill you and your family
will kill you and luigi and peach
and daisy and toad every single one of
them
i will kill them i will burn
your stupid castle to the ground i will
transform
my papa put a little piece of tape
on my belt that says not allowed to
transform
but you think that can't stop me
you think that stupid piece of tape can
stop me from transforming into a phoenix
and burn
everything you own everything you've
worked so hard on
so far to burn into the [\h__\h] ground
you think it can stop me
[Music]
people keep underestimating me and my
power
[Music]
name
oh he's going smooth because he's scared
all right don't [\h__\h] around hey we did
it which one did i not get properly
mario mario mario mario
mario mario
mario
what's his last name i need to call him
by his last name
he doesn't have a last name does he
ridiculous
no don't look at that side mario mario
okay
mario mario your little
bastard
how dare you insult a phoenix like that
it's ridiculous it's ridiculous
because of you people think i'm bad at
games
i can't believe it's been an hour
it's been an hour
i'm never gonna play this game ever ever
again after the stream i'm never gonna
play super mario 64 ever again
well who knows but
[Music]
um okay mario
don't do anything stupid
oh my god
no no
i cannot take this any longer
how to play the same level over and over
again for one hour
how this is hell
i have to change the title after the
stream
is
oh yeah and the title it says italian
friend
we are not friends
my papa said it's amazing that i'm
playing the same level for one hour
i don't know if he's trying to
compliment me
[Music]
one stop shouting
mario
[Music]
let's go
counted 22 it feels like much more to be
honest it feels like much more than 22.
much more than that
oh this is the lucky try i tell you this
is it
this is it
[Music]
everyone excuse me
for mario's stupidity
mario fans all over the world probably
hate me now because i
keep on insulting mario brothers what
choice do i have huh
i loved you mario i loved you like a
friend sometimes
some nights i even loved you like more
than a friend
and you just throw all those memories
away like that
huh
one
i need i need someone to make uh
to make a thumbnail for the stream um
so i can switch it out it must be the
desert my angry face
here
and mario
and then it should just say pain and big
letters
or maybe i'm doing it myself but
if you if you are feeling motivated
just make sure that you see the
suffering in the thumbnail
and you you feel the pain and the anger
and the flames burning in my head
actually let me get permission from my
papa to
unleash much for powers papa
papa
foreign
he said he said no
[Music]
well i'm a good daughter and i have to
listen to my papa
[Music]
do
i will not forgive not forget
kfp will not forget
the anger and the suffering you have put
me through mario
how you have invented oh my god
how you have embarrassed me in front of
thousands of people
is unforgivable
i will forgive you if you make me
lasagna
if you make me a good italian lasagna
okay here we go again
it's that easy
[Music]
no
this is actually a world record i think
i think even five-year-olds would manage
to clear this level earlier than me
i'm pretty sure about that this is
actually world record material
[Music]
my nose is itchy
sorry my nose was itchy
[Music]
yes go go go go go
go go go
i mean to some extent
i understand that bad gameplay
can be really entertaining to some
extent okay
thank you for the super chat i
understand it can be entertaining but
i think we've reached the point where
not only me
is only suffering but also you guys are
like [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
right
no what
it's still fun how is this still fun
you've been watching the same thing for
an hour
i wanted i wanted to show my skills and
then like reach 300k during the stream
but i guess it's
not happening it's just not happening
by the way please subscribe
so i can show you my skills in the
future maybe not today
maybe not today but in the future i will
show i will show you my skills you know
i'm
quite the professional player of
games of all the games to be quite frank
um
professional player of all the games
obviously not this one
thank you for the membership and the
super chat
[Music]
don't [\h__\h] around don't
okay
go down chill mario
a shut up
okay so up until this part we're doing
quite well i would say
um other than the times when the shell
just says goodbye
and decides to decide to leave me while
i'm surfing
we've got this part down okay we've got
this part down now
this is the part that comes now is
actually the easy part
but at this point i'm always like so
[\h__\h] nervous that i'm like i can't
[\h__\h] up now and that makes me [\h__\h] up
cannon no it's all right we'll just it
should be
easier to just walk up there
look it's that easy it's that easy
[Music]
yes
i just
thank you for the super chat fooling my
suffering
this is this is a skill no i must i must
i've come to the realization that this
is a skill and this is a world record i
want to see someone take
more time than me even though they're
trying
five-year-olds can do this
five-year-olds can do this kiara how old
are you you're eternal
and you're you're failing at the easy
part
you know okay here we go again
us we can do that
i have to say though one problem is the
thank you for the super chat one problem
is the camera
still
no no no mario not
[Music]
fly you guys saw me flying you know this
is not gonna work i can't just fly up
there
oh my god this is the worst stream
ever from my side
i did not expect so much pain and
suffering today
i was like hey i was checking
our calendar no oh my god mario
i was checking out cal and i was like
hey no one is streaming
this is my time to shine it's my time to
shine
so i decided spontaneously to stream a
second time today
you know just wanted to show you how how
motivated i am
and this is what i get
well here we go again stupid
pyramid which i deeply
deeply respect
just it's not that hard kiara
um can that flame stop no no
no no no no no no no no no no this is
not
can i just ask my manager to do this for
me
can i ask my manager i wonder if my
manager is good at mario 64.
manager probably just need someone who
still has some sanity left in their head
i'll probably just need someone who's
not already
at the end of their patience
[Music]
i didn't hear it hello and then activate
which one okay there we go okay this is
this is okay
this is okay bam bam bam we can we could
even
get back my hat now but no i'm not gonna
risk it
this is okay this is fine
no i did not ask for this
wait actually come here now
no i don't want it
i don't want it i don't want it
nice camera this will help me thank you
for this angle
thank you can i even i
[Music]
mamma mia
oh
yeah you don't need to go around the
whole pyramid just bump into the first
sign and go back to make it
first sign
what and go back to make it easier than
going around what
what sign
use the damn cap you mean the flying cap
i don't want to use it
but again we can try and you see how i
will fail with it
i will use the flying cap
flake
mario just get up there
mario oh my god the anxiety
is real
i don't see [\h__\h] ah mario why are you so
wobbly
okay okay okay okay okay get up there
okay now they
but you guys have seen many times how
how i fly especially when i start from
here
it doesn't go well like i can't even get
the the how do you say altitude
try starting from the pillar
i've tried it like in the stream before
too use the cannon
but you guys gotta tell me what is the
right height for that
you can't [\h__\h] around with me this time
like i'm i'm done
i'm done just like don't tell me like
aim for the sun funny funny
please just help me help me
this one time oh my god
now leave me alone leave me alone leave
me alone leave me alone let me know
quick
we got our hat back which means i'm a
bit happy
but i'll i will not
change my face facial expression
and wait you want me to cannonball
myself up there but do you want me to do
it with the hats
do you want me to do it with the hat
yes it's not it's not gonna go well my
friends this it's not gonna go well
um
okay how do i do how high
here like it's so hard for me to
find like where i am and then get a good
angle
higher don't tell me aim for the sun
don't
there
[Music]
sky it's good it's going almost almost
we can't do this i can do this
we can do this
[Music]
ugh
hmm
i'm not crying you are crying
stop crying guys
[Music]
wait where's my hat by the way
what did you just steal it when i looked
away for a second
you piece of [\h__\h] i will kill you
and how do i oh
[Music]
wait i need to i need a shower
when did he get my head
mama
no i will not give up now i will not
give up
[Music]
save the game
save the game why
why oh
there's no need to save it like that
when you're flying around your shuttle
tells you where you are
but like the problem for me is more like
sometimes i just completely have no
orientation i just don't know
where i am at all
well i hope that count it
mario you know i don't have the patience
for this right now
oh
guys after seeing me play this the same
level
for one and a half hour now
do you honestly still want me to
continue my playthrough of this game
like after today
yes are you guys insane are you guys
insane
who wants to see this
[Music]
my nose is itchy my nose is itching
ah i almost oh no what why is it wha
why is this why does it keep on
happening
[Music]
not there why why why why why why
why why why why why well yeah 11 000
people
but many of them have not watched this
for one and a half hour
only some of you have watched this for
one and a half hour
and have experienced how i gave birth
to a phoenix
i mean not not really but like
you know the sounds of giving birth
as a phoenix you have experience that
like some of you have
[Music]
i mentioned i've been through through
most oh my gosh
chill i've been through most of the
stages of
grief and pain now so i'm actually like
so disappointed and frustrated that i
lost
all my thoughts i just don't care
anymore
i i'm at the point where i'm like okay
well another try here we go
this is my neighborhood now apparently
this is where i live
this is where i will spend the rest of
my life
which one did not count
this one okay
[Music]
oops
oh my god the explosion
don't no i don't want you hurricane no
oh yeah
oh no no what no
i don't care i don't care i don't care i
don't care i don't care i don't cry i
don't care i don't care i don't care i
don't care
oh yeah the cannon oh i forgot i was
gonna do that i forgot about that
it's been a while it's been a while
since the last
try that worked
okay mario i'm sorry for the things i
said
i'm sorry i i apologize
so please just let's let's
end it okay
that's not what i meant
that's that's not that
is not what i meant
oh my god
oh my god i almost jumped into the
[Music]
quicksand
i hate my life
let's go mario i know i know that was
fun i know it was fun to
kill me when i said let's make it end
here
i know but let's just not joke around
anymore okay
mario it's not funny anymore
smooth smooth
okay smooth wait
we're going somewhere else
i don't want to go to the cannon don't
mind me
don't mind i just want to go straight to
the cannon but
obviously there would be something in
the way that i did not consider
this was funny until about 40 minutes
ago
it was funny until about four minutes
ago it's not funny anymore
not for me at least not for me
i need a win i need to win
i need a win
i'll also take 300k oh my god
oh my god oh
my god 10 bluebeam
who wants to watch this
what was i saying oh yeah i need to win
i need to win
i need a good gameplay
[Music]
that better count it mario
oh my god the heartbeat in the pro
controller
i don't know if it's uh sexually
arousing me or giving me anxiety
i did not cut which one did not count
huh
well great but um just run up
hey not there
wait wait wait wait why why why why why
why why
i was on all of them
the first one
what do i do restart again
take a break
take a break take a kitkat
[Music]
can i get there with this i mean what do
i have to lose let's go
but the question is how do i get out of
there once i'm up
oh well but not once
thank you for the super dead
because like from here
there is only quicksand
can't yeah but like long jump you think
i can do such a thing
yeah flying cup yeah i get it but like i
can't get down from here like
there's no no no more ground here
there's no normal ground guys
how do you want me to go there
jump on the side thank you what is the
budget
step on the shy guy you think i can do
that
[Music]
what oh
well that was hella lucky oh [\h__\h] that
life
okay chill chill chill chill chill chill
chill chill
chill chill no i don't have time for
this
oh god don't steal my hat don't steal my
hat don't steal my hat don't steal my
hat don't steal my hat
[\h__\h]
[Music]
okay now's the time finally we have
reached this point again
we can do it you i just did i just did
the
the ground pound too early
but we can do it i mean i
honestly i don't i've failed so many
times i don't believe that this is
even possible like this this level is
like rigged or something
okay it's just impossible like i don't
know
[Music]
my star wars my star wars mystery
where's my star where's my star where's
mister
boss fight what what you guys did not
tell me about this
what do you mean boss fight
what what do you mean boss fight
what what do you mean boss fights
i don't see [\h__\h] i don't see [\h__\h] what
what
what do i have to do
what do i do
[Music]
i think after one uh one and a half
hours
i deserve to get my star without
fighting you
kick the kick how do i kick again i only
know how to
how to punch the eyes okay that works
okay oh my god
no mother no
no
[Music]
shut up shut up shut up
punch oh my god
did that work
[Music]
hey
is that working
probably it has to be open right
it's working it's working
no don't die don't die don't die yeah
don't die don't fall off the bladder oh
my god camera please no
camera is so toxic
[Music]
am i finally free from the suffering
take the star of power we sleep darkness
we're struck
well yeah this part is first try
oh my god you guys did not tell me
oh my god
[Music]
this was like almost two hours
ah thank you for the service at
almost two hours
okay let's say one and a half hour one
and a half hour
for one star
korea my game
thank you for this video wow what an
accomplishment
wow this is such an accomplishment that
i deserve
super chats for that i mean honestly it
feels like i just saved the [\h__\h]
world from from like
an apocalypse
i have to say i'm really trying to act
happy
but in reality i'm not really happy it
i'm not even like i'm trying to be like
oh yeah
we did it but i'm like honestly in
reality i'm like
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h] ah
[Music]
we did it i mean thank you guys for the
tips
thank you for believing in me thank you
for going through this with me together
[Music]
thank you for believing in me thank you
for not giving up
game clear yeah i would say the game is
cleared now there's no more
no more stars to get oh my god
wow speed run speed i speed round mario
i speed run to no okay let's be real
this was a world record
of how how much time you can possibly
take
for one goddamn level that is not even
that hard
oh i should watch i should go on youtube
now
and watch a video of a speed run of this
level
and then just kill myself
[Music]
thank you for the super chat
i shall
i shall bless you
bless all of you who have suffered with
me
because i don't know if i want to do
this anymore today
i shall bless all of you with a song
i kind of forgot how to put on the echo
ahead
of me
let me sing the song for you
which describes
my feelings thank you for the
memberships and the super chats
do you hear the echo
can you mute mario ah i felt like that
would have been a nice bgm but okay
acapella let me give you an acapella
come
oh he just said 9.90 to me why one
second
oh man
okay wait one more second
one more second okay i hope you don't
hear this
just imagine the music
strangers to love
you know the rules and so do i
full commitments what i'm thinking of
you wouldn't get this from any article
i just wanna tell you how i'm feeling
gotta make you understand give you
up never gonna let you down never gonna
run around
and to search you never gonna make you
cry
never gonna say goodbye never gonna tell
a lie
and hurt you
[Music]
i've known each other for so
your heart's been aching but you're too
shy to say it
inside we both know what's been going on
we know the game and we're gonna play it
and if you ask me how i'm feeling
tell me you're too blind to see
keep you up never gonna let you down
never gonna run around and desert
never gonna make you cry never gonna say
goodbye never gonna tell a lie
and hurt you never gonna give you
up never gonna let you down never gonna
run around and desert you
never gonna make you cry never gonna say
goodbye never gonna tell a lie
and hurt you
[Music]
never gonna give
never gonna give them we're gonna give
[Music]
aching but you're too shy to say it
inside we both know what's been going on
we know the game and we're gonna play it
i just wanna tell you how i'm feeling
gotta make you understand never gonna
give
[Music]
never gonna make you cry never gonna say
goodbye never gonna tell a lie and
one more time never gonna give you up
never gonna let you down never gonna run
around
and to search you never gonna give
you up now i gotta oh [\h__\h]
never gonna make you cry never gonna say
goodbye never gonna tell a lie yet
okay i just painted myself out there
[Laughter]
thank you thank you gracias
thank you thank you thank you so much
i think
i think we have reached a limit
hope you enjoyed that i hope uh singer
sing it and singing it
in karaoke didn't stream uh didn't kill
a whole stream
well
i will oops i will move on to
a super chat reading i guess
and i i just want to forget about what
happened today
and never think about it again but one
thing yes i did save
one thing that i can proudly say
has is
proudly and single-handedly
retrieved her hats
for the million times but this time i
don't end the stream without my hats
last time we ended it without my hats
wait
oh my god
i actually i really wanted to make some
progress i didn't think we we would only
do one level but i guess that's how it
is
that's how it'd be sometimes um
well i mean
it's all right sometimes things just
don't go the way you want them to go
i shall play for you
the song of my people
you hear that
actually this is a good beat for rick
rolling
oh wait i still have to echo right
never gonna give you up never gonna let
you
down never gonna run around and dessert
never gonna make you cry never gonna say
goodbye never gonna tell a lion
hurt you wow yeah but you didn't hear a
sound
you can't oh god damn it why can't you
hear it
no music is hurt eh
how is that possible now
too low oh god damn it
anyway and my friends if you want to
leave you may leave but
i'm doing my super chat reading and
usually we also have some fun small talk
in between so
you can also stay if you want many
people have spoken
er from the legends of kiara
talking about funny things during her
super chat rating so if you want to stay
i would
gladly welcome you to stay
so yeah i should maybe turn off my echo
echo echo
yay stay stay oh yeah i gotta i'm gonna
i gotta do a uh
a check you gotta do a check for the
super chat
it always takes a little bit of time so
bear with me please
i'm gonna try to be quick
send the superchats over to my manager
if you want a super chat now would be a
good time
now or never
i really i really just cannot believe it
by the way we're doing uh the one from
last stream as well of course
[Music]
scrolling scrolling scrolling
what what the hell was all that
suffering though i cannot believe it
that it took me so long it's actually so
embarrassing
[Music]
i i just i don't know do i really want
to play this game ever again
again
i don't know if i can take any more of
this
still a way to complete everything
italian i think the small difference
but then it's a completely different
language
okay i handed it over
yo momento espanol what
they say you need ten thousand hours to
become an expert at something so you're
basically already there now
right it feels like it
popular is portuguese
what why are you laughing wait what did
why are you laughing did i say something
what
what okay
go back to english chat go back to
english
or japanese
don't go to brazil i've been to brazil
[Music]
dark souls oh no no matter what you do
for me it will always be
i'll ask the son are you sure about that
please come to brazil again oh no you
want my drink
dark souls i mean simply
like um i generally like to play games
that have like really
cute graphics and dark souls um
i just simply because of the art style
i already want to turn it down and
reject it
not because it's a difficult game which
is probably also a good reason not to
play it for me
will you play atelier yeah as soon as i
get permission to play it
what about a little which know better uh
i i checked it out
uh i i installed it
i checked it out but uh i'm not sure if
if i should stream it
against an impact people keep on asking
about getting an impact
i want to play ganjan impact so much
believe me
but currently we do not have the rights
to play it
yeah i would love to will you try this
scare
if sorry if i said it wrong i never i
never know how to say that this guy
is scared i want to
i never played uh this scale game before
uh isn't there like
a new one for the switch to scale five
but there's like so many i wouldn't know
which one to play
[Music]
this game
when are you five collabs in about 12
hours
from now
xenoblade yeah i'll play xenoblade after
my fire emblem free houses
flavor
[Music]
i'm gonna keep on asking
i keep on asking what i said many times
yeah all this fear oh
i actually uh already uh cleared autumn
sphere before
i played it privately i really really
liked all in spirit it was really
awesome but
i i don't see much
it i don't think it's like really
exciting to see someone play a game
again
that they already cleared before
ah what do you guys think about that
speed round and with audience fear i was
actually
good at the game
that's a visual novel right uh
other visual novels for streams
like first of all i'm not a big visual
novel
fan to begin with the only visual novel
that i would consider playing
on stream is steins gate
due to obvious reasons okay for some
people it's not obvious because many
people don't seem to realize
my papa is the character designer of
steins gate
and blackrock shooter many people don't
realize it many people don't look it up
my papa who is also often in the chat as
a moderator
h-u-k-e check him out
yeah he's legendary so if anything i
would uh
if any if i would play any visual novel
it would be steins gate
i watched the danganronpa anime though
it was pretty good i watched the first
season
but i never played the uh steins gate
game so
i'm not i'm not sure like has anyone
here in the chat played
the steins gates visual novel
anyone
yes oh what so many
would you say it's suitable for a stream
though like um
because there's like a lot of text right
really i can't really imagine visual
novels like
no not really yeah not really
if you react to it i don't think it's a
string game yeah
you can narrate narrating
i mean of course i would do that but
way too long ah
not too different from movie watch
amongst oh is it like just like
can you even make decisions is it just
basically like telling you a story
chat will often spoil oh i mean my chat
is uh
genuinely good at like they
they might backseat but i do appreciate
the backseating but spoiling is not
really much of a problem i would say
in the live chat at least ah just a chat
to vote on decisions here
i mean if if at some point we like run
out of a game
and want to try something really
different at for once
then maybe
what 30 about 30-40 hours of
linear story time
for streaming that doesn't sound so good
style ocean well i don't think we have
um
permission for star ocean actually i i
made like a small list of games that i
i requested permission for
so i do have some things planned but
really um
sometimes you know sometimes you get
permission click sometimes you like it
takes
months so for now
it's good that i'm like taking a lot of
time with my rpgs
because who knows how much time it will
take until i get permission
near automata yeah i don't think we have
permission for near
um but that can always change in the
future
actually i think we requested it anyway
yeah guys i got i got it on the radar i
got it on the radar don't worry
there's one okay once again a thing that
i have told you many many times persona
we cannot play e because the company
will ban the string uh it's complicated
but
the company behind personal five
is not yeah they don't
want their games to be streamed at all
at all
also personal five four three two one no
difference
full guys season two y'all maybe in
between maybe in between i
i could have some fall guys
fun i only played it once i bought that
game i gotta play it more often i only
played it once even privately i didn't
even play it
play against an impact are you kidding
me i just played it i just said
two minutes ago we don't have the rights
ori and the blind forest see this is
something that um
is not my preferred genre because i
would probably suck at it
i played that kind of genre before and i
was really bad at it
but ori uh i know has a really emotional
really deep story and
my favorite um real life youtuber
real life youtube's favorite game is ori
and has been um like
uh complimenting it so much
and ori uh the developers
come from a place that i feel very
connected to
so i kind of want to play the game just
simply for that reason
from where the developers are from and
from because uh the story seems to be
very emotional and sweet
and beautiful and the game graphics are
really beautiful too
and so ori might
and we also even have permission for the
game so ori really could be something
that i would want to play soon but i'm
gonna be really bad at it
i'm gonna be really bad at it
are we done
smash brothers with the girls wait isn't
it maximum four players why are there so
many
games which are maximum four players
wasn't smash broad as maximum for it
but i mean like in one battle
eight
what since when what for instead what
what what what what
still eight in one battle
why is it that in my mind i only see uh
i i mean i played it before and it's
always like four
four was a previous smash
oh oh cuz i played it on the gamecube
okay good we're done
checking is done so i shall proceed with
the
super chat reading
super chat
and so here we go
someone is trying to make me say i love
someone by their username
guys i mean it's funny but like also
it's not funny but okay
uh i love v gamer 311 thank you shane
the gamer 311
is promoted to something that i cannot
read thank you shin beginner for 11 dan
kitchen
alberto de kfp jennifer zankischen
murphy 11 daniel h
can you sing happy birthday in the
language of your choice
there is not so many choices
english or german because in japanese in
japanese they actually just sing happy
pasto
happy birthday like kind of like in a
japanese
way
[Music]
happy birthday picky cake thank you
thank you so much
thank you for the soup chat thank you
captain pepper jackson how about that
production actually let me let me get
on my uh cough drop
because i already failed for all the
screaming today
i really screamed my soul and my heart
out there
so i gotta i'm gonna do another on it
gotta get a cough job
is
drink some water everyone
actually like since two days ago
something uh how do you say it again a
mouth occur ulcer
has been building itself up again in my
mouth
i hate it it's kind of annoying
when i eat
and when i speak it's uh mama mama it's
acceptable
i just had one recently
why did i keep on getting them cankers
or what
hey i said mouth mouth oh
what
what what are you saying
yeah probably i don't know can chris
sort well i got a google i've never
heard of that before
why did i never hear of that before is
that a different thing than what i said
oh disgusting
yeah i don't know this can have many
causes but so i don't really know
probably stress whatever
now actually i have a medicine for it in
my house but
it's not in reachable distance right now
now i'm going to buy one again
[Music]
let's continue reading
i know i don't have mouth herpes i don't
have
herpes you can get
what is it canker source just like for
example even if you like
bite yourself in the mouth or something
there's many reasons that's not herpes
anyway where are we uh
warm salt water
but maybe i'll try that
and thank you new members
new membership
captain pepper jackson
[Music]
kitchen kitchen
what are you snacking i'm just licking
a cough drop with honey
your name here dankeshen melty cloud and
kashan
not only are your streams the best but
you also make the best collabs
thank you you are such a great minecraft
teacher to cali and i could not stop
laughing at your antics at the end of
this
oh yeah so many people enjoyed the
collaboration between me and kelly
yesterday
thank you guys and yeah i'm trying my
best at collaborations i'm trying
i mean i guess when not yesterday i
wasn't even really trying
yesterday i didn't even try it's just
like especially with cali i feel
like it just it just comes out of me so
easily
and so naturally yesterday um
i was just like you know leaving
all the the administration
thanks to kelly and like the moderation
but like it started off with her
starting the stream and like us getting
actually her it was only her you didn't
see it but she was just getting followed
by
all kinds of enemies because she had the
game on like a few minutes before the
stream
so it had to turn night right at the
moment when we started stream i knew it
was coming i knew it i was like
[\h__\h] she gotta start the stream when
it's day time
and then it just started out so
chaotically
i knew that would come
i i saw it coming but i didn't even die
but then you heard the creeper exploding
like
while she was still in her loading
screen
so we didn't even have like a proper
beginning greeting or moderation or
anything just we just went right into it
and died
the same happened to kura oh
okay then i have to say my start in
minecraft
has been better than gooda and calis i
didn't die like
in the first second
i did not die in the first second i
might have died in the
probably i died on the first night but
still
anyway thank you so much thank you jv
dankeshen
wish i could stay to watch the stream uh
that was for the uh
fire emblem stream but i have been awake
for about 22 hours wow
so i'll check the archive later oh and
if you ever find yourself in a lose-lose
situation press the lr
plus and minus buttons in order to do a
soft reset
back to the main menu
for fire emblem lr
plus minus soft reset
to the whoa
that's interesting i don't
you mean if i'm like in a battle but it
will lead me back to
which main menu the one before the
battle started
i very ah to reload the save point okay
okay okay okay
thank you i will try to keep that in
mind
but the good thing is i always have
people in the chat who keep on helping
me which i really appreciate
so we're always kind of fun thank you
thank you for your generous support
thank you i really really
appreciate it
remember that if you want to build
relationships don't give people actual
good advice just tell them what they
want to hear yeah that seems really
accurate
[Music]
i really want to watch it in real time
and
i put up with the archive until my work
settles down
[Music]
keeps on recommending me i shall believe
your mom i shall believe your mother
if she says so i will believe it
your name here glory of combat
since i can't stick around for the
entire stream so you have any
information and when the collaboration
yeah
well i don't know like if this helps you
but from now it's uh
11 hours 40 minutes from now on from
this
point right now since we have all kinds
of different time zones i'll just say it
like that
but i think gura did not reserve the
slot yet
i think
she probably didn't but she should soon
because i think
she's online right now i think she was
sleeping or something
[Music]
thank you do you play read visual novels
i don't know if i i feel like i answered
that in the
stream already but no i don't really do
do that
thank you captain pepper jackson alex
jensen thank you
yeah people keep on hinting to me that
if you like idle god make sure you get
at least a c plus support and speak to
her during february on one spot why but
superman
people keep on keep on hinting to me but
i have to speak to her every month blah
blah blah
don't worry i already got it i mean i
i'll probably just have a
special cutscene or something i get it
dylan
yeah oh happy birthday
happy birthday your name here thank you
merson thank you um
[Music]
riding is too expensive of a hobby also
kiara you should travel the world i've
been like
to like 30 countries it's the best me
question
yeah but like in inside of europe
traveling is
not so expensive and
i mean i've lived for a long time you
guys know i'm eternal
so also like
i did a lot of traveling with like night
buses for example as well
and some some travels were work related
as well
and sometimes i just really tried hard
to save money
but traveling yeah i mean it depends
sometimes it's expensive but if you if
you do it smart and
if you pla plan wisely then it's not
that expensive night pass yeah
yeah yeah yeah
kiara has that senior discount
i wish i had a senior discount
night bus yeah trains are like really
expensive
somehow it's either bus or airplane
why are trains so expensive like i
actually really enjoy riding
trains but why is was it that trains are
so expensive not that
dangerous
who would want to ride a train if it
takes like 10 hours
and costs you like what's 200
when you can just ride fly with the
plane
be there in two hours and it costs you
like half or even less
europa league
i don't know about you guys in america
but probably in america it's a bit
different
i i want to trade long distance trains
are
more are cheaper in america than
if you take a plane is that it in
america
or it doesn't end up being cheaper if
you get like a nice
cheap air fly airplane
you guys trains good one eh
oh okay see also in america trains cost
more than flying that's ridiculous why
trains don't exist
that's funny
thank you for
thank you so much for that red super
chat with absolutely no text
thank you i know you just wanted a kiss
[Music]
of luck side note really glad you chose
black eagles they are my favorite and i
love every member
i have to say today little guard said
something
that made me doubt her good heart
she said she wants to eliminate the gods
and
while i to get to to point with her
to get good points of her i i agreed
with her in that moment
in today's stream i should be back i
should be back
[Music]
hello
sorry about that happens sometimes
no need to worry so what i was saying
some people
have been hinting at me that edelgard is
maybe not the best person maybe doesn't
have the best personality
they keep on hinting that to me and
today i feel like i felt that when she
said
she wants to eliminate the gods i
thought wow that's suspicious
yeah but apple i already joined black
eagles i don't think i can
undo that so i'll just go with it
i'll just go with it every character has
a vlog okay
well we'll see i'll continue and see
what her reasons are maybe the gods
really suck in this game
maybe they deserve elimination but i
hope she doesn't want to kill his office
by the way for everyone who didn't
realize yet there's a danke
and the shooting emote now so
and you can like to spam it together
with me
so that i get some energy to get through
the super chats
thank you guys
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
there was nothing wrong with your uh
with
the thumbnails you made for me but you
made them quite a while ago
so when i was looking for i i really
spontaneously decided to stream
super mario 64 today and
the thumbnail that came up right in my
mind was the one i used today
which i also found easier it's not that
there was anything wrong
is this that yeah i didn't it's so long
ago i wouldn't have known where to find
it or i didn't even remember it sorry
so yeah cannot always use everyone's
thumbnails but i really appreciate when
people are making them for me thank you
so much
[Music]
15 dexterity plus twenty percent
ergonomics plus zero percent suffering
prevention
yep it's weird
my i felt like so much more
in control today
but the suffering was like five times
stronger than previously i don't
understand
why thank you awesomeness
thank you thank you thank you i'm glad
you enjoyed our pictures thank you
well thank you for watching the archive
m.c dan kashin for controlling kiara
pro gameplay totally that was proven
today
of course thank you and rectangle
internet repair fun thank you
i'm still waiting for my new internet
for the contract
i mean we made the contract but i'm
waiting for them to come to
my house and install that stupid
internet
still have to wait until the 26th
[Music]
yeah and it was originally supposed to
be
at the 5th of october
and then they it kind of like there were
some issues so i had to
make the contract all over again because
i just moved guys
in case you didn't get that
so i did that contract all over again
and i chose the the 12th october i think
which would be
tomorrow and the day after tomorrow
and then you know it shows you like the
available dates
so it turns to 12. but then
one day later they they call and they're
like no we don't have it available
we will come on the 26th i'm like boy i
need it for work
i need a shirt for work and that is why
i tried at home to stream with my pocket
wi-fi my
my um portable wi-fi but that was
uh with that i couldn't really stream
properly so that's why i'm streaming
with my manager's
internet which is super good
it's like really speedy but somehow it
cuts off sometimes you wonder why that
happens
is that legal where's company well i
mean um
i guess it's just it just really takes
so much
time i guess
i don't know should look for different
no no
if i do that now it will just take even
more weeks
anyway just gotta keep on waiting and
waiting and waiting
it's just so annoying because like
i just wanna get this [\h__\h] over with
is there a date set for the collab with
subaru uh between us
yes but i will not announce it yet
but it's next week mentor aliyu
[Music]
i'll probably just announce it like two
days before or something
eric stoltman carefully employed number
a lot for his refrigerator
don't feel bad about your struggles with
mario 64. lots of people
lots of folks struggle with the game
really really so much as i do
i doubt it your humor and time is why
we're here after all thanks for being so
awesome thank you
thank you for staying with me
thank you
well actually i got my manager to speak
to that internet service
uh i just read the super chat that just
came in so i'm replying to that but
yeah because i i knew that i would
probably start crying on the phone
so i let my manager do it but
yeah even
even then
[Music]
would you ever do a language teaching
stream yes for my members only i'm doing
german teaching streams
sometime soon okay jsr dancing
hi best burp i missed some streams
because of the time zone difference but
wanted to show support
thank you so much thank you i know that
because of the time zone many people
don't get to watch my streams
today especially the fire on blime
stream was like so
so empty but i was like what is going on
where is everyone
but oh well
hopefully you all watch it in the
archive instead
thank you shin rikota elmar dankeshen
kero you may be bad at this game
what i'm not bad at this game
but you're entertaining when you play it
and that's all that really matters
thank you oh people making up excuses
like it was 3
a.m or 2 a.m or whatever
guys i stay up until 5am every every
[\h__\h] night that's not an excuse for
me but okay
of course like if you had something
there's a reason to wake up early okay
okay do your thing and then get back
home and then watch the archive promise
me
please
okay thank you
oh yeah we just read that just continue
to do your best and try to have fun it's
a better story if the hero struggles
before triumphing
i don't want to struggle that much that
was just too much today
thank you joey bear 94 dan kashan it's
my birthday today
oh everyone has a birthday happy
birthday
congratulations thank you
[Music]
i hope this cheers you up for mario help
thank you
so much thank you i really appreciate
your support thank you mwah
cerulean wings duncan sleepy nectar and
manchester
mario player for streams hell yeah i
would rant someone to play the game for
me
secretly next to me
one day maybe i'll do that
thank you guys keep on spamming the
dunkishins
[Music]
michael rivera destroyer supersonic 1995
foreign
[Music]
if you want the truth this level is why
i personally hate dessert desert levels
oh yeah i mean i i originally never had
desert
levels uh in my memory as such a painful
experience but today was proven wrong
ricotta jkh monkey duncan
disappointment is immeasurable her
friendship with mario ruins
viewers having the time of life having
fun watching
did you really did you really
i can't blame it mario mother your wife
one whole live idol oh thank you love
every stream you do
and can't wait for more pro gamer
gameplay of this quality
[Music]
cerulean wings
yes
so much pain so much pain
thank you so much
[Music]
florence thank you thank you thank you
ian williamson
nate zero five six zero thank you first
ever super chat for anyone we believe in
you
yeah you may tease you but watching you
persevere
okay and overcome is the main highlight
you will get the star just don't give up
thank you
thank you please don't use such
difficult words when you
sent me a super chat please use
simple ingredients i said it right
wow really
thank you spencer millard big wild beast
and dynamic vector
[Music]
m
i was actually thinking of singing this
in my next karaoke you know it showed up
in a super chat are you reading my
[Music]
is
i was just planning what i could sing
next time
[Music]
is
which accent is that
[Music]
yes i am british
foreign
scared a scared owl thank you
i love watching you play oh thank you
but it's because of you and not because
of the game thank you
if i wanted to see a perfect play for i
would watch a speed one video
you know very entertaining and bring me
so much joy also shopping for them
thank you looking for the top thank you
thanks for satisfying my inner ass
i don't want to satisfy your inner s
yo
thank you [\h__\h]
it's a red super jet so i feel obligated
to give you a kiss but
now that you told me your s i feel like
there's some
sexual tension between us
[Music]
please send me a super jab to ruin this
sexual sexual energy
say something weird say poop
say poop
memory of twilight
many of us are here not for the gameplay
but for
you the gameplay is secondary if you're
stuck on a level for ages we won't get
tired of it are you sure about that
you make it fun by doing your kiana
things the kfp pandas for love you guys
thank you
thank you so much thank you thank you
sure
[Music]
can we see your feet no
actually yeah wait
now that goes out yes you can
[Music]
hahaha
and if you don't want to see this any
anymore the only way to undo it
is to send me soup
[Music]
huh
ah foot pedals well i guess this person
asks me to keep on showing them so i'm
just gonna go with it
eric sanchez
one second please let me mute myself for
a moment
i'm back
let me drink some water
where was i have i missed some super
chats who are telling me what to do
show armpits show elbows oh damn now
there's
two what do i do maybe i can show both
at once
i mean i can show you the armpits for a
while yeah
new request show armpits
okay i shall i shall continue wait
wait uh okay there's a tie request but
let's stay here for a while
wait someone else also said ties god i
mean let me read a few here and then
we'll move on
and michael kenny duncan
[Music]
that is a really sweet request but uh
let's move on to the
uh
wait i'm too big
i hope you're happy with this
wait wait this is so confusing
go up a bit yeah no this is the focus on
the knees
and we won't get done if we keep on
doing this guys
you first the first first kfp employees
thank you nicolas james
[Music]
super chat has turned into horny chat it
seems so
my super chat is like going a bit crazy
right now i don't see what's the most
recent one
in the in the chat window
uh directly
[Music]
thank you so much just because i
finished one level
in in one and a half hours wow
well deserved right well deserved
okay here's something good
enjoy
[Music]
oh thank you for joining the man vision
a good choice i must say a good choice
very good choice
welcome plant thank you
like for the chat obviously like the
chat goes so fast
that i mean i can pick up comments every
now and then but what is difficult is
like remembering people's names and so
on obviously like
it doesn't really give me like a moment
like oh this person was here before
like i don't have the time for that but
for the super chats
i i do like realize that like i say oh
this person was here before oh this
person was here before
that's really nice
yeah it's nice like i can remember some
of your names
because you keep on sending like even
like small amounts you know
it doesn't matter like at least i can
remember your names like for this for
the chat
it just goes like i can't read the names
in the in the chat but for the superhero
account
so thank you for everyone who keeps on
supporting me of course
you don't have to but i just want to let
you know that
i acknowledge that many of you are
repetitive addicted super chatters
[Music]
there's certain people who always like
donate
in the very beginning
yes i remember i remember
i will not forget you do you have a tail
no i don't
do you want to switch to a different
area
maybe a close-up of my face
and look at me
oh i'm shaking so much hope you can
focus
ascot zero two four two down
[Music]
hello
thank you for joining membership yes i
jesus thank you for the super chats
resolution
[Music]
minutes 100 free deaths too many to
count stars
one amount of us are proud of you all of
us
ah thank you
oh those are my own feathers those are
not earrings i repeat those are not
earrings you can look they come behind
from my ears
yes
[Music]
is
i knew this because i watched your debut
stream thank you
thank you for like listening so
carefully and you know
watching so carefully thank you
and where was i tackle pacman freedom as
foreign
[Music]
first try don't forget we watch you
watch for you more than we watch for the
game so it's okay to be stuck like this
for an hour no it's not okay
so thank you for watching thank you shin
s17
b32 dan kitchen good work yeah wow i
just came from mario odyssey and by
comparison
the controls for mario 64 are terrible
he actually
actually did well to power for that mess
through shared determination well thank
you
how sweet of you guys even though i was
so
horrible you guys keep on you know what
you call that in japanese
i tell you what you call that in
japanese
when you say something that you don't
really mean
it's like something nice but you don't
mean
thank you
very common thing in japan
we actually mean it oh come on
oh come on
oh funny
you can't tell me that those are not
when you tell me you
like especially if you tell me that my
gameplay isn't even that bad or
something like that
alex thank you so much
[Music]
i'll get back to normal my friends back
to normal
joe fernandez was the last one
scrolling scrolling swelling scrolling
scrolling squalling
scrolling swallowings falling
sip because this bird is
thirsty
always thirsty but you guys i mean
it's okay for me as a joke when you guys
call me bottom left and all that
but you must understand deep in your
heart you must understand
in reality i'm the purest and
shyest idol ever
and that is the truth
so
for real
for real ah you don't believe me
why why why what
i think japanese audience they don't
really they usually don't
call me like bottom left or whatever
no matter how i look at it you are pure
slowly
yeah for most japanese viewers they
think i'm pure
your paid actor no
no no no no no
why did i teach you that no it's not an
ocean
[Music]
uh
i started this myself
okay here we go
nina
[Music]
huh
alchemist yeah it reminded me a lot of
inna now
[Music]
thank you so much like lucia suffering
right
our best picture thank you
kyler sundance no matter what you do for
me it will always be i already read that
thank you
for texting the accelerated
one visual novel i want to play someday
is the the
kentucky fried chicken colonel sanders
visual novel although i read a review
that it's not
actually that good it's just like
yeah it's actually not that good
but eventually maybe one day i'll do it
just for the just for the jokes just for
the memes
yeah it's free but i still need rights
have you ever thought of playing any of
the ys games on stream they're a really
cool series of action and rpgs that i
think you'd be really interested what
what why ask what thank you
for your attention
do you need licensing permission for
indie games yes but they're much easier
to get
because they reply much faster thank you
and
foreign sure although i'm not so good
but better i'm better at arc nights than
at
pretty much all of the other games i
played on this channel
billy joe channel
[Music]
is
don't drink okay okay i wasn't gonna
drink the salt water yeah
i was not gonna drink it
[Music]
moist fish
my mouth doesn't move anymore let's just
say
[Music]
oh
feel like my tongue has like a
my tongue it has like a
what kinnikutsu
but i'm almost done like for real
[Music]
m
oh
[Music]
i mean super chat ratings always give me
like the last
hit
i wonder if i ever get used to it
it's
[Music]
uh in ten and a half hours from
now yes
[Music]
i'll do some preparation on minecraft
and then sleep sleep and then wake up
for the collab
thank you for listening to the superjet
reading today
and thank you for watching the stream
generally for
way too long while i was struggling
struggling like an idiot
thank you everyone
yeah i hope everyone enjoyed it i'll see
you tomorrow
and thank you hashtag
[Music]
oh well love you guys
and in german we say
[Music]
that
in
bye bye
[Music]
so
you