hello
everyone
Cheerios oh is that your British
greeting I don't know is it is it
British you got to say and more like
cheer that well actually that's Goodbye
Oh goodbye then
goodbye Kara's British lesson hosted by
Aura who is confirmed a Brit um y so as
you can see small W's driving the bus
can you
drive okay NE can I so
these are the topics we're going to be
discussing we're going to talk about
American versus British English language
Food Shops and icons and um I found this
tweet of yours so would you please read
this tweet in a British accent of course
of of course um there's British people
sitting and talking next to me and
listening to them is like music in my
ears they sound like G
Ram you you remind me of like um there's
like people from
they go like oh I've got my comboy
norvest um why to me it's a f they sound
like gentle Gordon Ramsay how do you
make Gordon Ramsey gentle do you just
like swear like you're an idiot
sandwich oh no they leave those out
Gordon Ramsey also like in his private
life doesn't even swear I suppose so he
just TI Tok though he reacts to people
cooking oh yeah I saw I saw for you
actually I wouldn't say you sound like a
gentle Gordon Ramsey I feel like I only
get that feeling with like you know men
talking in British
accent I don't know what to compare you
with I guess is there an angry British
woman there might be uh I don't know
British women do do they exist where am
I who am I let's let's get started so
American versus British English so let
this is a bit of a test let's get
started all right so what are these in
American English pants okay good job but
what about British English
pantsers yes that is correct pants in
the UK means underwear pretty much um
yeah underwear is we also call pants and
pants are trousers and and yeah so these
are trousers so you need to say trousers
okay trous trousers trousers yes very
good very good you're learning you're
10% British already so we're Banning
pants we're allowing thring yes is that
what the what the girls always mean when
they say ban pants did they just mean
they they say to the American language
and they say let's adopt the British
language a lot of streamers are American
right so when they talk about pants they
they're talking about trousers so when I
when I hear someone say like oh I forgot
to put on my pants like I'm thinking you
forgot to put on your underwear what the
hell but that's us talking about
trousers so yeah all right so next one
what are these shoes okay other than
shoes uh sneakers that is right in
American they call them sneakers but
what do we call them in the UK coners oh
well that is a branch been through
Jerusalem man uh this begin with a tea
tie tie up
shoes with a tea it does have a tea yeah
trainers trainers yes right yes I didn't
look at the chat I swear I didn't look
at the chat promise you promise no
cheating no cheating it'll
be let's go sh said Tippy tppy runny
LS okay okay you're doing very well what
about this orber or je or you got it
right yeah that's the British oh because
uh probably because in German we say
that too because it's an eggplant in
American right eggplant yeah I never
understood why it was called eggplant
but it starts off like egg shape wait
yeah that's actually interesting that I
went for aene first H we call it aene
too you know there was a lot of there's
a lot of British words that the
Americans Chang but like also stuff like
Center the word Center and F like in UK
we spell it fatra like yeah but the
Americans like fixed it yeah I don't
know I don't know why it makes no sense
that's the only time I feel like uh we
should have changed the spelling but
yeah those would be nice if you guys
like match it the words already so
similar just match it up what the hell I
just feel like no one says Cent it's
center it's fancy though kind of fancy
it is fancy maybe it's the Brits trying
to stay fan hly like theater I'm more
familiar with that but I feel like when
I look at Sentra that's that just looks
like a typo to me it does I guess I
guess like we just kept more of like the
maybe it was a typo and then they were
too embarrassed to admit it but you know
a lot of a lot of our words have the u
in it like color and favor I I used to
always write the words of you but then I
think recently ever since I worked so
much a whole life I stopped at you to
like color a lot but every once in a
while I add the you again I'm on your
side Aura I mean what would you be
without the you you would just be a ara
ARA
girl I have an amazing AR an I don't
care about that next you care about
Britain don't care about the just
kidding I didn't want to give you an
showcase but okay bring it on no no no
no no I can't do it now I'm too shy it's
a I do like a I do like a one cuz like
my voice it sounds like this but I can
do like a deep voice too all right it's
very spicy two one oh
no oh my God you sounded like
crony wow that that was um horny very
horny should we ride horny with you oh
you all right next one choco block choco
block choca block yeah ch something like
a place is crowded like if you're in
like a traffic jam you said all the
traffic was choco Block it's not choco
ball no like your schedule is full like
you can say I cannot go see the Lord the
Rings musical mate that that day cuz my
schedule is chocola block oh damn mate
you must be so got
it that was
good that was good
yay this can't be ours yeah this
basically means when you don't want to
do something when you're really lazy
when you can't be bothered I can't be
asked to go to the shop so I'll get
delivery instead I feel like that is
very common I've heard that a lot yeah
can't be asked but you can't say asked
you got say asked mhm I understand yeah
let me sense I can't be ask to go to the
shops try to try not to um stress the r
too much ask oh I can't be asked yeah
there you go wa read the read the whole
thing again I can't be asked to go to
the shop so I'll get delivery instead
like a like a calm quiet Gordon Ramsey
ASMR Now read it in a Gordon Ramsey way
he's so he's Scottish but his accent is
definitely not Scottish so oh he's like
I can't I can't be asked to go to the
shops so I'll get delivery
instead your Gordon
ramino all Gord you have to do the hand
as well like he puts puts his fingers to
his Temple and then he brings them back
and forth and like you know I can't I
can't do anything so I'll just wave so
just wave but he next one food we're
going to talk about food now you spoke a
little bit about British food anyway
earlier but do you have a favorite and a
least favorite I like uh I like British
breakfast honestly except for I I would
like to eat it without uh any mushrooms
or the the the black sausage oh yeah
black pudding no I hate them too I
always take them off yeah my the rest I
love yeah I mean I take I take off the
tomatoes but like um you can have them
then it's both for you what about things
you don't like like you ever try like no
cuz see like mostly the things that I
wouldn't like I I I have a feeling for
it and I don't even try it true yeah
yeah you just look at it you're like nah
I would eat that yeah so I I don't think
I would like hats fair enough or here's
some food yum although this has got the
stuff we wouldn't eat the
mushrooms yum yeah the right side is Yum
so I love a Gooding there's absolutely
no sauce There where's all the the
ketchup sauce yes I love ketchup I put
it on every I mean normally the beans
are like swimming in that kind of
ketchup sauce tomato sauce oh actually
you have a good point these beans would
be looking very
dry I do look a Ted Tad naked but yeah
it's missing the toast as well actually
though yeah unless it's like buried
under something but there's a lot of
bacon
in our in our imagination we added on to
that yeah yeah yeah you know it's good I
mean some people call it a fry up some
people call it a fo English and then
this Oh I thought you were going to
bring fish and chips but you're just
bringing basically girl this is
basically the same thing as on the left
side yeah but this is just that thing
this is just that you got is that all
you got this but this is this is very
special it's very simple same thing
it's it's a closeup of the beans but on
the on the toast true this is this is as
my manager said peak British Cuisine
right here this is called beans on toast
because it literally beans on toast hey
K I could have literally showed you a a
toast sandwich but no I for the
representing the UK very well right now
I'm sure you have more like food options
well do you know do you know what toast
sandwich is I know what an idiot
sandwich is and that one's right next to
me ho [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] sorry the Sass came
out of me sorry it was just such a great
opening it was such a great opening
a s I couldn't control it I walked into
it it's fine but toast sandwich is when
you toast one slice of bread and put it
between two unsliced to um no un
untoasted slices of bread so it's just
just bread between what ew what is that
stupid that's stupid it's it's dry
probably but yeah nothing else isn't it
just bread it is just bread is that a
British invention
yeah
un ironically pretty good I mean bread
eating plain bread every once in a while
especially if it's fresh what you going
to say French I was like no yeah buten
but the thing is like I wouldn't really
say that for toast bread maybe for baget
yeah or
quas today I wanted to eat
quas so I went out to get
AAS and I went to the shop to buy a crle
and then I came home with the
crle and then I ate the crle
crle so
cute okay but this is this is food you
may know but here's food you may oh wait
no have hang on this's this beiz piz yum
wait yum so there's lots of weird food
in the UK lots of things with weird
names too o interesting interesting
bring it on but here's one so do you
know this oh
oh well Scotch
eggs yes oh my God it came out of my
train I know it yes it's my I love this
so much so you're too excited you like
them yeah I love Scotch eggs is that the
mint meat yeah it's like meat with um
Coke like C and breadcrumbs and then a
boiled egg in the middle next
one ew disgusting what do you mean it's
British
the fish the fish heads sticking out ew
so so not appetizing what do you mean I
guess it's something like a fish pie
well yeah this is called stargazy pie so
it's called that way because the fish
are gazing up at the stars
e what's inside like mashed fish oh what
do you think's inside
beans all right we're going to talk
about shops next do you have any shops
that you like in the UK or restaurants
or anything like that ah ah um there's
this uh shop that's kind of expensive
that has toys hars what it toys and then
know herods herods the one with all
kinds of stuff like yeah that's a fancy
toy shop pens and uh H am I mixing up
things H hes and herods those two things
they're fancy shops they're fancy places
so this one is called Gregs eggs eggs
eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs
eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs so this is
Gregs this is a bakery but it's give a
little bit expensive
recently oh I probably eggs saw there go
eggs
eggs but yeah this is Greg it's very
popular for the sausage rolls have you
ever had a sausage roll uh you mean cold
cuts like um it's on the top shelf on
the right in this picture oh that
something oh oh oh I think we have stuff
like that the one 10 thing that thing
there I didn't have it in the UK but I
feel like I probably had similar stuff
here in Austria I feel like um to be
British you have to have a Greg sausage
ra it's like the L all right next we
have poundland and you know what's eggs
to poundland here's the thing wa they've
put up their prices nothing's a pound
anymore oh wait that's where it comes
from oh it was totally like my oh okay I
didn't even connect that okay no no they
used to be the 99 P store and pound land
and pound stretcher and they would all
just be like a pound everything in there
is a pound you go in there and you're
like oh how much is this and they go
pound I guess it should be pounds land
so several pounds yeah so they keep
increasing the price of things oh bless
you thank you everything in there is not
a pound anymore but they also have this
oh bless you P
Monopoly look how much it is look how
much it is it's
15 I mean for Monopoly I mean but it's
poundland it should be a pound all right
we're going to talk about British icons
this is like celebrities do you know
British celebrities SP girls Spice Girls
that's a big one yeah the One Direction
boys oh yeah yeah the one that the
they're big too anyone else Gordon ramse
mhm Beatles oh yeah The Beetles of
course yeah dualipa oh yeah I love
dualipa I like I like a
dance okay show me show me show me so so
here's some I uh I can't remember what
order I did this in but uh who is she a
pig what's that do you know her name
she's a British icon she's a natural
treasure Peppa Peppa Pig her voice is
her voice is like this hello my name's
Peppa Pig and this is my little brother
George I don't know what to think about
her she she's living a best life she's
she doese she's Immortal oh if you
Google her you should Google her height
her height yeah you should Google her
height p height why what why is he so
big what I guess if a if a grown ass Pig
stands on two legs I guess it would be
pretty tall there's a there's a meme
that um she was 7'
[Music]
one