[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
questions
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
again
I am so sorry for the wait uh
close yourself
I am so I I'm so sorry for the weight
hello
um
I already want to apologize for how bad
the stream will be
um
[Music]
garbage bag
you know I usually
oh what the hell where did that come
from ew ew I usually have uh gloves made
out of fabric
um but
uh because we're we're baking today and
I have to I have to touch the
um the dough
um I thought that if I don't show if I
do it with my bare hands and then I just
don't show you then it would just be too
boring because like what part would I be
able to show you almost nothing so I
hope these work I bought new gloves this
time they fit somewhat
I mean they're still a little bit big
but I I hope they work
we
wow wow
um
yeah they only had a size on Prime so
oh my God I had to check I thought I
thought I thought that the angle that we
used last time would work
um but at last minute I realized nope
this angle does not work so I had to set
up the webcam uh again
um and you have no idea how sharing my
setup is
I um
I I am now using a couch table that is
partial like right next to the table
with this by the way is a balcony table
I don't have any other [\h__\h] table to
work with that is decent and big
um so this is the this is a balcony
table and the sides of the balcony table
are like uh uh this thick and the thing
that I'm mounting the webcam on uh can
only go this fake uh so I realized oh my
[\h__\h] God I need something else to
mail it on that's stable and I was
looking around I couldn't find barely
anything so I brought up with a couch
table
uh and in my space I'm like right next
to me I am trapped by a a loading cable
on my left side so I can't go to the
left side it's like it's floating in the
air because it's so short and on my
right side I'm trapped by the couch
table uh contractions
foreign
[Music]
also I will probably be mostly tilted
today as you can already see
because I I
can't position things properly I don't
know
okay
um because this is a really scuffed
setup and
um because it's my first time baking
cookies
um I don't know how many cookies we'll
be able to make but for now
um the first thing I want to make is
this stuff here
I already have a finished dough
thankfully so we don't have to make the
dough this should be fairly easy
um these are some of my favorite
Christmas cookies
[Music]
it's just basically I I rolled a dough
out a little bit and then uh I make it
into small Moon shapes and then I put it
on the uh into the oven that's pretty
much it and once I put it outside I just
cover it with
um
sugar and like a normal sugar and
powdered sugar mixed with vanilla sugar
is what I have read on the back side
thankfully there's a there's a
description on how to do it on the back
side
um oh my God thank you for the super
chats already and thank you guys for
being so patient uh I will [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] up I will [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] up so
badly and the other thing I want to do
is something called linta algen uh
l-i-n-z-e-r uh algen and Lindsay Elgin
it's um also an Austrian uh cookie
Christmas cookie I think you know both
of these cookies probably have
variations all over the world but here
they are called linta algen and they are
like a like a sandwich cookie with two
layers and in between there is a jam uh
as far as I've read supposed to be a
specific type of gem but I've eaten it
with all kinds of gems so I'm gonna put
in uh apricot jam I think because that's
the best Jam I have right now oh yeah
finger cracking let's go
um yeah and that one we will do after
these if I still
if I didn't already [\h__\h] up too badly
and if I feel like
uh I'm still in in the position or so to
make more cookies I want to make more I
even I actually prepared even more than
that but I highly doubt that I can make
more than these two types of cookies
today
um
you guys know how [\h__\h] nervous these
kind of streams made me always
where's my phone but ah here's my okay
that's my phone um my mom said if I have
any problems she will be watching the
street hi Mom and she can give me
advices but I should be able to make
some [\h__\h] vanilla Cafe that's by the
way what you call them these Corner
foreign
[Music]
word for a specific type of croissant
which is not really a croissant it looks
like a croissant but it's not a Kristoff
um but yeah I'm so excited to eat it
these are like my favorite tap they're
so good they're really crumbly so
um they're gonna fall apart after taking
them out of the oven probably I mean not
like immediately but they they are very
crumbly
um but we have a finished dough so it
wouldn't be really my fault would it I'm
already preheating the oven by the way
it's uh at 190 uh degrees or so
oh
I'm not on setups that I'm not used to I
really don't like it oh no oh no no no
no don't like it
um out of the things that I have
prepared for other cookies that I won't
even be using I have like
I have a chocolate to cover [\h__\h] I have
I have this [\h__\h] uh I have like pens
that you can like draw with
I have sugar coating that you have to
warm up
okay and then uh I have more I have this
and I have
I have this yes
what oh
God I'm so scared I'm so scared
I'm so scared okay we should just get
started this is a tiny ass thingy
normally I guess you would just do this
on the kitchen counter without anything
but I figured if I would do it on here
directly then it would have like you
know these lines so that's another
reason why I was like oh I'm [\h__\h]
um cat hair yeah
um I do have a bigger one I guess but
should I put like it didn't say anything
about
putting
um
putting uh
uh uh
what's the word again male male uh
on the ground here
putting a floor oh yeah on the ground it
didn't say anything about that should I
it says
it doesn't say but wasn't that normally
what you do flower pudding like put it
like here
I don't know let's get started uh let's
just get it over with okay
um God oh God
um
whoa
[Music]
it smells it doesn't smell like what
it's gonna be
uh uh oh God
oh God
oh
[Music]
oh my God a few cat hairs will not uh
be bad right a few cat hairs you know
what let me I want to bring the
[Music]
which let me bring the other uh
one is
a little tiny bit bigger
and a bit more stable
okay
[Music]
it's the same color oh no almost at
least for the camera it's not really in
real life but okay
um if you see what I'm doing here oh my
God
the camera is not very stable I'm so
scared
um okay how do I how it said to first
start off by slightly
um massaging it
um now I wonder how it will react to my
gloves oh God
be a good baby okay be a good dog
massage
where
uh uh can I touch you is it okay to
touch you oh my oh it's kind of wet oh
[Music]
see that
um what can I like just take a part of
you oh nice texture I'm just gonna take
this apart okay okay now we have this
part and um How do I
yeah
okay gently oh it works it's really
moist but it works
with these gloves okay it's good that we
chose these gloves
okay
uh oh and it doesn't stick to my gloves
either that's perfect
okay okay okay that's enough right
that's that's not too much it said not
too much okay and then oh God I already
forgot it's the simplest description but
I already forgot and nine two uh little
rolls of 9 to 12 millimeter
and then uh five centimeter long pieces
okay okay five percent I have a I have
this thing look isn't that cute I bought
that in Japan I think in Daiso come on
got cat hairs on my gloves no
no
no no
no no no
well anyway this is fun because you can
like pull it out there uh
like this and then you push the the nose
to rail it back in isn't that awesome
it's amazing
[Music]
things like that are only sold in Japan
or maybe maybe in other countries Asian
countries as well but they don't sell
cute [\h__\h] like this here in my country
why am I not moving on
okay I don't know what that was uh okay
so uh I already forgot what was it
9 to 12 millimeter and five centimeter
nine to twelve will have what that's not
even a centimeter
so it's that's really thin that's really
thin mine too light
[Music]
so like like my
like my my small finger
for example five centimeter length they
said how much is five centimeters
also like I think
like this
okay
um uh nine nine one it
Too Fake way too thick oh roll it up
baby roll it out let's make some vanilla
cake well why do I keep on stop moving
doesn't matter you guys are looking only
at my hands anyway right
blush okay okay okay okay okay
whoa
I never washed
there's this there's this uh German
um Bakery song for children that
um I used to sing when I was younger
it goes something like in the dinosaurs
[Music]
I don't know the lyrics
yeah oh is that oh my God it's
overflowing that was already too long
is that is that is that a good
[Music]
um
probably okay and then five centimeters
like like here
look here maybe
oh
like here
this one is uh
[Music]
oh yeah a little bit too thin I think
a little bit too thin
oh God cats hairs
but
oh God oh God no one I won't look I mean
I probably have been eating a lot of cat
hairs in my whole life already anyway
um
okay and now we make the shape this is
really not so difficult
but they look so tiny shouldn't I guess
do they become bigger after putting it
into the oven I wonder at least a little
bit right
probably
probably a little bit does anyone know
where they do right okay so if it's like
this
but it did say to make the ends a little
bit thinner
[Music]
I think
no
I mean that's that's fine right it looks
like a shrimp
okay I have a on the couch table next to
me I have the baking thingy already
um sorry I keep on stopping
and so I'll place it on there
let's see how many we can get on here I
think a lot
okay
I'll let this on here
and oh my God I'm baking cookie
cookies
fun this is actually I guess easier than
my cooking streams somehow because at
least I can like keep the camera at the
same place but most of the time
and it's basically easier like the
shaping these cookies is fairly easy to
compare to
the other stuff that I do
okay two cookies
two already
uh no this shape is a little bit weird
thinner on one side
um
how do I let me squeeze you
so that you go become a little bit
thicker on the other side does that work
does that work I don't know oh well
you're fine you're fine
yes okay guys open the show
let me let me do this WOW bowl and now
the ball becomes a sausage
[Music]
[\h__\h] no these must be a specific certain
shape
yeah
Tiana's balls no no no no
different ball
[Music]
yeah perfect oh yeah this one is
beautiful
gorgeous gorgeous gorgeous oh dear oh
gorgeous
oh I mean okay now it's almost connected
open yourself up a little bit more
beautiful yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
so far so good I I think you can't
really make anything wrong do anything
wrong with these
except putting them into the oven for
too long
it said something like 10 minutes by the
way so we will be able to do taste
testing
um
is Gordon Ramsay here sorry Gordon
Ramsay I don't need your advice today
I'm good at this
I'm so far I'm rocking it yeah yeah yeah
yeah
there it is
oh sure
okay next batch next batch
oyster and
I do want to say what Gordon Ramsay says
but
I'm like occupied
I'm very busy here
I I don't have as much time as you
Gordon Ramsay you're probably just lying
around in bed all day watching Netflix
okay
let's do this part
nice nice first
he's very good today is he is he
complimenting me
oh
yeah he better
you better be complimenting me
[Music]
stops it keeps
see me vibing is the camera moving maybe
oh my God why do you do that
[Music]
oh my God is it moving
oh God oh God camera
lithium fix this oh God oh God I know
what's happening oh God
oh god oh
um
[Music]
okay you good you good
you good you got camera okay okay okay
gotcha got him
[Music]
don't stop at that stupid face come on
let's focus on the dough please
hello
hello here hello no apparently not
okay um focus Kiara let's get this done
mm-hmm
[Music]
okay five
so let's use our ruler here is this
really
it comes in handy
camera
[Music]
what
oh
is it focused it's focused
it's focused
still stay like that
nice nice
autofocus
stop rolling the worst app that you cut
it it is that like serious advice why
why not shut up it's fine it's fine
that's beautiful
look at my little baby
there we go
[Music]
here we go
down
[Music]
so fun we have one two three four five
six
and I'm not even through with uh half of
the uh uh dough wait that's not enough
stay together okay
[Music]
thank you
are you guys making Christmas cookies
too
this season
or are you being uh lazy and you buy
them from the supermarket huh
that's usually what I do
[Music]
did the same ones yesterday what same
ones are you from Austria
[Music]
yo we didn't say anything about putting
butter or so on the on the uh on the
thing before you put it into the oven I
hope that's okay
wait that's not nice
caramel brownies mmm
and lazy can you send me some uh
no
no maybe I think you're gonna ask a
different Austrian to make them for you
and send them to you I would love to do
it but uh
um I would probably accidentally poison
you
totally accidentally
ask someone else this one is too small I
think oh well
[Music]
yeah
okay bacon
honestly for these kind of streams
[Music]
I'm I'm actually really glad that even
though these are nerve-wracking
the good thing about them is I I force
myself to do like cooking and baking
like learn new things learn new recipes
so
yeah
I probably wouldn't be cooking veggies
baking cookies
if if uh I wasn't
um a streamer yeah
cooking
Alicia this one is too thick
in general
close enough
[Music]
okay that should be good that should be
good
now shape them into a nice Moon
if you guys can't find this cookie dough
in your Supermarket yeah you probably
can't but there are probably a lot of
recipes out there how to make this
cookie dough yourself and I really
recommend you to try these because these
are so good
these are my favorite Christmas cookies
for a reason
oh God by the way I haven't eaten
breakfast yet today so this will be my
breakfast I am
oh I can't wait to eat these
no oh yeah that one is oh God no uh go
back into Bowl
reject moon shape return to ball
they are addicting yeah cookies for
breakfast yeah
I guess I could even eat the cookie
dough huh because like people love to
snack on cookie dough right
a bit more
[Music]
maybe that's too much damn it
okay
eh does it have eggs in it yes I think
it does
pretty sure
oh God I'm so hungry oh God oh God
um
cute
not as cute as my Champions though
yes okay this part now
should we take the whole thing probably
can't fit it all on my
workspace
okay
[Music]
I am so hungry
yeah
once it's with the connection man what's
what's going on
oh
wow why does it do that sometimes
did you see that
the camera when I touch it it does like
it switches the the aspect
don't worry it's not a different angle
it's just a different aspect
roll that dough roll that dough
and finally next week I'm planning to do
a gingerbread uh house making stream as
well so more cooking more baking
and I
I ordered
um the set to make it
already however
um
I will have to make the dough myself
I've been because I haven't seen the
dough being sold anywhere
um so what I also bought was one of
these mixers that go like for making the
dough which will be useful in the future
as well so something that I wanted
anyway
yeah I'll be I'll be making the dough
myself
okay let's do this one two three four
five
hmm
that's kind of too long
hmm that's kind of too thin
my little worm
[Music]
make it chicken chip no these are
supposed to be a specific shape we're
not we're not uh
doing anything
weird with these I do have
I went to like buy stuff for this stream
yesterday
um I went into several stores trying to
find cookie cutters
[Music]
um
I just wanted simple cookie cutters like
style shape heart shape
uh round shape
just just really simple ones and where
no matter what I went to I couldn't find
um normal shaped cookie cutters they
were all either sold out or they just
didn't sell it to begin with
so the ones that I found
I'm
and I will show you in a moment
later once we're done with these ones
but
they are shapes like alpaca shape and
shark shape
and dog shape and all that like who the
[\h__\h] this Dad I love alpacas but
no
foreign
[Music]
I then asked uh last minute I asked oh
that cat hair in the camera oh
[Music]
oh no where is it
it messes up the focus
um
thanks
I can't grab it it's like honestly I
wrapped a lot of uh
um tape around the the webcam to like
make it stay
um so I think the cat air is stuck in
the tape
um
[Music]
please Focus here
oh
yeah yeah yeah that's good that's good
that's good I think
nice also I think the camera has been
moving again has it
has it but for now it's still fun
it's episode
it's fine unless it does a complete 180.
well this one is really thick hmm
but better too thick than too thin when
it comes to cookies so that they don't
crumble
cat hair shaped cookie
wash your hands no they're not on my
hands at the moment they're already in
the cookie dough don't worry
what is done is done
so yeah anyway uh I'm preparing for the
gingerbread uh thingy
um
I hope the I hope it won't be too
difficult I think I'm I might I think
the smartest thing would be to make the
cookie dough ahead of time before the
stream and then bake it before the
stream and then just put it together
assemble it during the Stream
I guess
probably
um
hungry
yeah
an apple
return to ball
I don't want to spend more time with you
guys but you know
this kind of stream makes me
unnecessarily nervous what are you doing
camera what are you doing what what
I know I I think I know why this is the
angle
okay
[Laughter]
hmm
it's almost as if I have someone on the
camera switching angles for me
like in whole talk but that's just my
doing
it
[Music]
okay that should be good oh now it's too
fast too thin
Mamma Mia Mamma Mia Mamma Mia one more
time
I hope you can't over massage this
cookie dough
if if I can then I'm probably already
doing it
let's finish up these ones
these bad boys
huh
okay that one looks ugly
but some of you guys
have to look ugly in order to make the
other ones shine you know
that's my logic
so that the other ones look pretty huh
it's teamwork
move Kiana move your face come on yeah
yeah can you what are you doing
Mommy don't
[Music]
I don't need those special effects
no thank you
no stop
stop
oh my God
what what's going on are you good
boy I'm trying to work here hello hello
hello
calm the hell down calm down you good I
mean okay this angle isn't really what I
wanted but
you can't do anything about it now
Daniel
um
for now
for now let's keep it like that I guess
yeah okay
oh God this one's really bad
why okay why are they getting worse and
worse
why
okay maybe I have to speed up a little
bit because
um we still have a whole more chunk of
this
oh shh
it was pain my head right round round
[Music]
oh good
oh I should have put the rest of the
dough into the fridge for now at least
oh well
too late
are these leave cooking no they're not
they're like a vanilla no tasty dough
I don't know how to describe it
looks like I think maybe
maybe cat hair on my nose
hi chunkers by the way
oh man oh my God so hungry oh my God so
hungry oh my God so hungry oh my God so
hungry I'm so hungry I'm so hungry I'm
so hungry oh my God
oh my God yeah I'm making vanilla keep
fun
vanilla and Austrian Christmas cookie
[Music]
um
here this is what it will become for
everyone who came in later welcome to
the Stream
with bacon Christmas cookies
[Music]
damn it this doesn't fit
you're too long oh well I'll make it
work I'll put a little bit of you on
here and a tiny bit of you on here
you want some cookies too chunkers
huh mom
meow meow meow meow okay
oh
my uh
what I what do I call it the thing that
you put into the oven the one that I
place the cookies on what do you call
that
cat under like around my feet oh
no a baking tray yeah my baking tray is
looking pretty filled up already nice
too I like the look of it it's like I'm
a bakery
[Music]
for sure even though I'm a fast food
chain show
okay
[Music]
we got that one down
but we still have this huge chunk
uh-huh
separating
and let's do this
yeah I'm getting a pro at this now hey
that's so that's a weird uh is this 16
to nine
that looks really long
the camera aspect
that's a lot of dough yeah I'll be
eating cookies for days which is
probably another reason why I shouldn't
make more than two types of cookies
is it your phone it's not my phone
it's not my phone it's a webcam
[Music]
it's a webcam that likes to bully me
and stress me the hell out
so that I can panic attacks
about my camera dropping
okay okay
gently gently okay five
somewhere here five
suddenly here I like that I can use my
pinky as a measurement
okay
putting them into shape we have a system
now I'm not part of your system
I took the cookie dough and I threw to
the ground enough for it to the ground
[Laughter]
[Music]
sorry sorry about that I'm gonna put you
back into the shape I already add you in
the shape and now I gotta do it again
don't play with
it
Rachel I only know this song because of
a clip
um
[Music]
I saw I I already told the story before
but I saw a clip in my YouTube
recommendations what was it something
like the title was Cali's iPad Kelly
threw my iPad to the ground or something
like that and I was like hey why would
she do that is she crazy what's her
problem
so I opened I opened up the clip and I
listened and then I understood okay this
is a meme reference huh so I listened to
the original song and yo how have I
missed this
how have I missed this until now
and then I I didn't I I only listened to
like maybe three songs
of that group
of people
um
one of them was the the one with Justin
Timberlake the the mother what was it
mother mother lover
I need to listen to mordo but I want you
guys to
um see my reaction to it so every time
when I watch a new one I'll watch it on
stream
I must say I quite like those songs
[Music]
that works
okay wait was that supposed to be one I
guess so
foreign
already from tilting your head oh are
you good should I try to fix this
should I try to fix the angle manually
by changing it on obs
or are you okay with this
it might switch itself again on its own
we good we're good we good I mean maybe
if I hit the camera maybe it will fix
itself
[Music]
when I touch it when I move it like I
don't know why it does that I guess it's
like Auto adjusting itself depending on
how it's uh angled
thinking that I needed to be in this
angle
but it's not it's not true I don't need
you like this
[Music]
let's go come on it's gonna be faster
it's already been
almost an hour oh my oh my
God yeah I don't want to move it too
much
do you guys want to get a massage like
this from me should I massage your your
fines like this
imagine this could be your chicken thigh
if you join kfb today
only the best Champion finds at kfb
hellions
look at them look at them being excited
for getting fried from being turned into
food into fast food
don't worry I might turn you into fast
food but I'll eat you up slowly
foreign
[Music]
and then this one oh God
damn
it's too long
okay
[Music]
gorgeous
gorgeous are you guys curious about the
taste of these
unless you're like Austrian or maybe
German
probably have never eaten these before
I like how many of you try to uh
recreate the
the Austrian German dishes that I made
before
the case of spatzler
I saw some of you guys on Twitter
sending me pictures
recreating the dish because it's really
not that difficult
yeah
I'm not only motivating myself to cook
and learn recipes I'm also motivating
you guys that's nice
nice
[Music]
oh by the way today was
um
Senpai 3D stream with Christmas Santa
outfits it was so cute and if you are
watching it live then you might have
been super surprised that I was a guest
um I called in to let them do some poses
like they they said Kiara like we want
you to call into uh get us to do some
poses
and I was like when I was thinking about
what poses to make them do it um I was
like
I don't want them to just do any kind of
like basic boring as poses
hello and when am I gonna move again
there we go
so I thought what could work what would
be funny and then I had I had this
Revelation this in amazing idea to have
them do some like meme poses yeah I made
them do the think think pose from that
Netflix show
Invincible was it
and uh
they actually did quite well because I
sent them a picture along as well and
they were able to look at the picture
while um I made them do it I described
it that's why they did pretty well it
both of the poses ended up being pretty
perfect
um the other pose I made them do
specifically I let them do poses that
are perfect for couples yeah yeah smart
Kiara the other pose I let them do was
um from Toy Story the one where uh Buzz
Lightyear is like showing what was the
other dude uh showing him like oh look
memes memes everywhere butterflies
everywhere whatever like
like pointing into the air yeah Woody
yeah yeah the one with Buzz Lightyear
and Woody you know what I mean don't
jump
you guys know the meme right
my show
yeah rather than doing the basic cute
poses like oh please get on all fours on
the ground and look up or or please do
kill pose with one leg up or so
I thought they called me for a reason we
gotta be Innovative here we gotta make
it interesting
[Music]
Christmas is
yeah and I was like and girls trust me
people will love this they will use it
on Reddit
I hope I hope you guys will use it on
Reddit please do
and if I ever if I ever get called again
for one of these
then trust me I'll think of more meme
poses
yeah I'm glad it worked out so well
they turned out so good if you don't
know what I'm talking about I I posted
screenshots on my Twitter
before the stream so just go on my
Twitter and and look at the most recent
tweets you should be able to see it
there also I'm gonna drink some water
here I have a
you know these Coca-Cola glasses
[Music]
they got a nice color
you wrote for that thank you
yeah yeah
I think that was from McDonald's
every now and then they sell them
um
good afternoon
used to collect those yeah I have a
couple of them
I have a couple of them
I'm so hungry okay
[Music]
okay I'm almost done I'm almost done I
have so many
oh sure
[Music]
oh damn damn it
can you go here
quick quick
[Music]
okay okay beautiful beautiful
I'm running out of space on my baking
tray
oh that one's perfect that one's perfect
I have it I have the feeling in my hands
and I I'm like really good at this now
um
what the hell is this what the hell is
this Gordon Ramsay gonna yell at me
again do it properly piano don't do it
at all
no that's ugly forgive me
[Music]
okay okay we're almost done we're almost
done I have a little little bit more to
work with
um
your shop come on shape moon shape
here we go
gorgeous gorgeous
oh dear all gorgeous
[Music]
um
ah fixed it
stay like that please that's actually a
good angle
okay oh God was that a cat hair
oh I do have a bunch of cats oh God
[Music]
um
I'm gonna
I'm gonna wash my hands really quickly
before we continue
getting too much here but wait I don't
wanna I don't want to move too much here
[Music]
okay stay stay stay
or you know what I'm just gonna take new
ones
because these are going to be words I
don't know if the cookie dough likes it
when it's wet it's probably not
[Music]
I mean I got 50 pieces why the hell not
use them
50.
50 okay
my hands are moist
[Music]
oh God I can't get it properly
oh my God
[Music]
wait a second
give me a moment
are we good are we good
uh what the hell
let me readjust everything
hi
what is this the right direction
[Music]
is this the right direction the camera
is so naughty
heart Challenger
[Music]
I'm not hurt why would I be hurt
side
okay
come on
[Music]
um
I don't know if I'm turning it into the
right direction
okay this way this way this way
[Music]
yeah this is really not made to be like
this
oh God
oh God okay
perfect I think I made it
[Music]
okay okay I'm good you good camera
oh no oh no it's so unstable it's
[Music]
super cool
foreign
okay right now we put on the gloves I'll
be right back
[Music]
a fresh gloves
fresh camera angle
let's see if this one looks good
[Music]
foreign
you're okay
[Music]
oh my God
okay I'm back I'm back
okay maybe I really should only make one
type of cookie on stream and the rest
after the stream goes down
stop
calm down oh God oh God
yeah
it's like when I move too much it will
like [\h__\h] around
oh God stop stop
no
oh
my my cookie dough
get down dude
foreign
I love that song
[Music]
now I'm gonna
let's get this over with
[Music]
it could have been longer
I could have been a little bit longer
glitch in The Matrix
I think yeah because it's so unstable it
keeps on doing that
like a tiny Shake will make it think
that it has to switch the angle
knock down we're almost done
did you guys watch usada pecula senpai's
new outfit reveal
oh it was so perfect
the new outfit is so cute
I like that she has this denim jacket I
like that she put some denim into it
it works so well
[Music]
and it's kind of like more for more food
it has some fur uh over over the jacket
so it works for like the cold season but
also for the warm season because when
she takes off the jacket it's just a
summer dress
hmm
[Music]
so cute and I like how she can have her
uh bunny ears tied up
it's kind of looking painful but
stop it it's really cute
[Music]
optimize your PC says Dell run our suit
of the optimization tools now to ensure
your PC blah blah blah
now now is not the time
no it's not the time Dell oh you guys
probably didn't even hear it but my
windows was talking to me like
oh my God
that's like someone is doing some
special editing on my stream
okay
okay I'll make I'll make one
different one now this is kind of a
scandal to be honest but I'll do this
for you guys
for bearing with me on on this horrible
cooking stream
every food every [\h__\h] dab it switches
the angle
I want to make a heart
stop
[Music]
stop stop
so you want to stop touching and it
stops
what are you doing
[Music]
okay
two more these are the last ones
last stop oh boy all right no more no
more
okay
fixed it
yeah
the last ones they shall be beautiful
oh no that was a cat hair oh no oh no oh
no
where'd you come from
probably because I touched a webcam and
there's a lot of
cat hair on the webcam
oh dear
okay last one cycle
would you guys be very disappointed if I
only make this one this one type of
cookie
I'm like so nervous about [\h__\h] up the
other cookies oh man
[Music]
but we have finished it uh
Victor
I would I would still I mean I have the
the cookie dough so I would still make
it for you guys and then post it on
Twitter or so
um you think it's okay well let's see
um I'm not 100 sure yet but let me put
these ones in the oven and then take a
bite and then we'll see how we feel okay
oh shh
[Music]
um
I want to take a photo of that
[Music]
oh my hands
oh no here we go
[Music]
okay
okay I'm gonna put them in uh it said it
said
oh
[Music]
nine to eleven minutes
okay
and then finish it up with some powdered
sugar and vanilla sugar and that is a
one one package of vanilla sugar mixed
with 60 gram of
uh powdered sugar I have no idea how
much that is I will not measure it
[Music]
but yeah let's throw it in
should it be like in the middle
[Music]
oh yeah
let's go
okay and then let me prepare the
powdered sugar
[Music]
I never know which one is the floor and
which one is the powdered sugar
I mean this one is it maybe
and then
[Music]
how do I do this
foreign
[Music]
oh maybe this one
this one it's my my rice cooker
container
mush
okay
are you guys looking at the time because
I wasn't are you guys looking at the
time
can you just tell me when it's been like
10 minutes because it says 9 to 11
minutes
[Music]
can you guys help me out there
uh I mean it's been probably two or
three minutes by now
hahaha
I didn't set a timer
uh yeah so maybe uh it's it's the full
hour or one minute after the full hour
Maybe
[Music]
okay
come out oh
more
is there no more in there are you sure
I hate these packages
[Music]
oh it smells so good
I'm empty okay
so I love vanilla
and then oh I don't have a spoon
let me get a spoon
why do I put these
[Music]
it has a heart a heart cute
unfortunately this one has Reflections
so gotta be careful
okay so
[Music]
take the sugar how much is 60 gram with
a teaspoon you guys know there's
probably
um probably some hints on Google
probably some descriptions how much uh
it would be with a teaspoon
and
uh four
eight eight
ten ten gram is one teaspoon
oh how much did it say 60 gram so six
teaspoons just wing it yeah good idea
let me just destroy some of these
crumbles
[Music]
oh my God a cat hair where did you come
from
free I'll just
that's not a full spoon
kind of lost count
I lost count
[Music]
maybe like that
and then I'm gonna mix it
[Music]
oh yes oh that's vanilla sugar already
kind of reminds me of the consistency of
the texture that they're gonna have at
the end
hmm
um
[Music]
no no I put in more than three I put in
more than three don't worry
how many more minutes they still don't
look finished when I look into the oven
2 gram of sugar
really two
two way
three three more minutes okay should I
put in maybe maybe a little bit more
oh my God camera I'm gonna fire you
actually I tried so many different
webcams
and they're they all suck I wish I could
just I wish I knew how to set up like a
proper camera so that I can use it like
in OBS I'm gonna look up how that works
eventually because these [\h__\h] webcams
I can't even Mount most of them on a on
a normal tripod or whatever
huh
horrible
[Music]
okay
okay so I'll put this in oh in here and
then we'll like put the sugar on top of
the
the vanilla cake pop can you stop
oh [\h__\h] yeah
let me put that away okay
okay everybody
calm down for a moment
yeah
foreign
you like my sleeves
[Music]
he's just trying his best the camera
I don't know about that
okay let me put that here
[Music]
ah I'm so excited for my breakfast let's
go hi smoothie
oh did you hear that guys
don't
play with the cable no
I understand you want to cuddle but
please do it with my legs and not with
the cable then
oh baby
nice movie
yes I'm baking cookies you won't like
them oh now she's cuddling with my legs
oh
stop
meow meow it's time
um
they don't look quite finished yet maybe
give them one more minute
I'll keep an eye on them let me go there
I'm not sure how dark they should get
though they look still pretty bright
now wait two more minutes maybe
[Music]
in your chair you can't sit on this
chair as my chair
[Music]
okay
see if I should turn it off yeah it's
okay I just want to show you the the
result and then we could okay
for a moment
just for safety
okay
nice headphones thank you I like my
headphones I've been using them for a
while they are from Razer hashtag not
sponsored
bye
we're cooking headphones yeah no that's
the cookie I made headphone shaped
cookie that's right
[Music]
can I smell cookies I smell I smell it I
love it mmm
I need I need something to put them into
that in a box
[Music]
I bought specific paper uh like but it's
called put that board papilla they said
to put it into a box that's uh lined
with up here
I don't know why it needs to be this
paper but okay apparently like something
with the hydration or whatever all my
cookies done
ah I see the tips are like getting
darker that's good I guess one chicken
one second
[Music]
Maybe
this
honestly I think they need more time
they're not supposed to be this
um soft
[Music]
maybe maybe
I don't know why the timing is not
accurate but maybe because I uh
didn't put them at the very top I put
them like on the second level from the
top yeah I know at least one thing that
they're not supposed to be top uh soft
they become firm after they cool
thank you
is that so let me see maybe my mom says
something maybe my mom wrote me
something
shut up shut up the phone
um no mommy mommy how do I know if
they're good how do I know if they're
done Mommy Mommy quick answer me
[Music]
um she's typing she's typing
uh
should they like do they need to be like
hard or is it okay if they're so soft
Wendy okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
when you spreads the head content yeah
mama
uh
[Music]
okay
taking the thing out now
and then while we are still warm uh
I'm gonna put the sugar on top of it now
[Music]
okay whoosh
um okay uh
[Music]
okay wow
what's up
sometimes there was sugar even going
through
[Music]
I'm not sure
I feel like the vanilla sugar is too
thick
[Music]
water
okay
[Music]
over here
Marshall High will help for sure
[Music]
foreign
okay and how do I show you this I'll
take a I'll take a photo for myself now
[Music]
okay okay
wow
wow let me let me send the photo to
jenma and then I can put it into OBS oh
Mom was writing to me on Discord too I
didn't notice
oh even Jenna was telling me like the
timer
okay
okay okay okay okay
I'm gonna put that on the screen
um
us so far my mom wrote to me that I
shouldn't move them right away
um once they're out of the oven because
they will crumble
so I'm giving them a moment to cool down
I just have one issue that you know the
thing that I was like
um
uh uh uh you using the powdered sugar
with I think the vanilla sugar is too
too fat to go through
[Music]
um
so I feel like there's barely any
vanilla sugar on it
but this is what it's looking like
[Music]
this is what it's like right now
oh man hey look the shape is perfect the
shape is fine
um
[Music]
now we will have to do a tasting test
and hope it still tastes like vanilla
somehow
[Music]
otherwise I'll use another package and
just like sprinkle it on top of my hands
but when they're already cooled down I'm
guessing it won't stick to it that well
anymore
looks good I wonder how long I should
wait until I eat one
um let me prepare the Box though
[Music]
20 years
oh to cut this
uh
[Music]
sorry I'm like a little bit AFK here and
here but
I'll put some in here and the rest I'll
eat now can I already eat one
[Music]
oh oh they seem like they have the right
consistency now A texture
to take one
oh
[Music]
there on it how did you get there
okay
[Music]
I'll show you one second
um
[Music]
John
I will try this one now I guess
[Music]
hmm
no no I think
I think the vanilla taste is good enough
it could brown with me a tiny bit more
but I think the there was already a lot
of vanilla in the dough I suppose and
I'm not surprised that it's good because
I did make the dough
so I guess the only thing I did was put
it into shape
there's not much is it can we take it
now I'm like oh it's my breakfast
foreign
[Music]
thank you
that's right
[Music]
no height
here it is
[Music]
um
oh God
[Music]
I'm glad it's hand hairs
one more
[Music]
man now
um
[Music]
mmm
motivated most of it
mother bed
[Music]
um
my shop
yummy
[Music]
okay you know what I will try to share I
will look up an English recipe I will
try to share it on Twitter if you guys
want to make this by yourself I'm sure
you can do it it's super easy
oh God I'm feeling so hot I need to
drink some water
wow
[Music]
I don't know if I shouldn't like more
cookies ah
I kind of want to but I'm already like
exhausted at this point
Tire me out so bad maybe I could make a
part two maybe I could make more
Christmas cookies like maybe not next
week but
um
the week after
or if the whole gingerbread things thing
for some reason fails completely I'd be
me
then I could
um do it instead of the gingerbread I
just kind of want to improve this stupid
camera setup
somehow if I could improve it until the
next stream then it would already
um
be very helpful
[Music]
New Year's cookies I guess no honestly
these links are algon we don't only eat
them at Christmas so I guess it's okay
foreign
[Music]
get an articulating arm that can hold
your camera what do you mean with that
articulating arm what is that I have I
have a tripod that's like movable like
uh like um
uh like a dynamic tripod I don't know
what you call it
um
there's another rotate setting oh is
there maybe
I don't know
and oh man I feel so hot
you know what
um
I think
I think if we end it here I'm gonna do a
super chat reading stream later to read
some more of the leftover super chats
that we have because uh I still got time
I think I have nothing else to do later
in the evening so we could do that I'll
take a little break and then uh we'll do
a super chat reading stream probably
um
and we can do it while eating more
cookies please
yeah I look I have to look at the
expiration date for the other cookie
dough that I have and depending on that
I will decide what to do with the rest I
really really want to make those cookies
for you guys as well
because they they are very special
they're yummy they have Jam inside
um
yeah I'll also ask my friend if maybe I
can get some help with the camera
positioning it's just uh
yeah I just wanted to be stable on top
from like a bird's uh bird's eye point
of view
that would be helpful oh man and uh I
need I need food I need to eat more food
I'm so hungry cookies
[Music]
yeah
don't quote me like that
quote me out of the context what the
hell does that mean I want to be stable
on top
what does that mean
bird's eye yes if only I could just be
like
if I only if only I could be the camera
I me my eye if I could be first person
camera that would be so cool oh you know
what I could put a GoPro on my head
but I feel like he would sometimes even
see my pajama pants legs so that's maybe
problematic in theory that was
interesting but hmm
in fairy in theory
[Music]
yeah I mean is there like a like a
button to turn it off
I could like always turn it off whenever
I make weird movements
green screen fans green screen
beds
hell yeah
[Music]
oh man okay
um yeah I guess I guess that's good
enough I mean I'm gonna make my schedule
after this stream as well I'm gonna put
up the schedule for next week and I can
say the music video for my song cover
with Ina has been finished so it's all
on time and it even still sometimes it
makes some tiny changes if need be I'll
check in another I already checked it
and it looks it's so fun I'm I'm gonna
tell you one thing now
it is
in some way I guess
a fully animated music video
I know that is
animation photo animation I guess it is
I think I think you can call it that
I think it is a fully animated music
video I think I'm correct in stating
that
it's not made by you and I don't know
it's a new person
um whose style I fought really really
fits the the song and the original art
style of the song like it's actually
quite a similar uh art style so so
there's so many different animations you
guys are gonna love them so much I can't
wait for you guys to use the animations
wherever on on Reddit on Twitter on your
discords or whatever
um no no Ina didn't draw it no no no no
no no someone else did it
I I commissioned someone to draw several
many many many many animations for this
music video so I'm really excited to
show you guys it will be I think on it
will be released I think on Wednesday I
think on the 22nd was my plan
[Music]
yeah on my channel because I organized
it I'm doing this thing where I am
putting up song covers with every Hollow
myth Member First was Cali can I move
again excuse me
first was Cali and then I did now it's
Ina and the last one will be Ahmed and
for every one of these song covers I am
doing some you know special song Choices
special music videos and all that can I
move please hello
ha hello
hello
[Music]
it seems ah there we there we are there
we are
[Music]
um
connection is bad by my connection my
face connection is bad
oh well oh my God I feel a bit bad for
only making one type of cookie
I feel I feel bad about it yeah
is it acceptable
is it okay is it forgivable
please don't feel bad it's all good it's
okay I mean they turned out great
and it was fun making them into little
snake shapes
yeah noodle shapes Moon shapes
mmm yummy I wonder how long they are
good uh like how long how long
um
how what's the expiration date on them
once you bake them also because they're
self-made so there's no weird stuff in
it
usually at one week
one week
one to two weeks
yeah I mean I love these cookies so much
I probably have them all eaten up in one
week definitely also I think I'll give
my BFF some cookies tomorrow
I'm planning on meeting her tomorrow
do you guys wait do you guys want to see
one thing though oh man
I said I will show you guys those cookie
shapes right the cookie cutters that I
purchased because there was literally
nothing else on the supermarket let me
show you at least that so you can see
what what we might try out next time
[Music]
thank you they are reflective but not in
a way that you can make out what you see
so I think we're good
[Music]
ah but wait wait let me get these two
okay okay
okay
um for sure is this
is this good
[Music]
okay
okay so holy moly holy moly macaroni
chill okay so I said for example I got
this fish shape
I was the okay
um the thing is the Lindsay algon have a
specific shape they're like round with
like uh swirly things around like it's
not a perfect round shape it's like
swirly and and in the middle you have
like either three dots or one free One
Big Dot that is like open and you see
the jam uh through it yeah so I just
wanted a [\h__\h] simple round shape
that's all I wanted but the only things
I could find was this and then shark
and it made me think of good as I was
like okay I guess I'll make a gura
cookie
and then oh my God this is so ridiculous
this is this is just boring it's a heart
I mean I guess you could make the link
to Alden out of this as well somehow
by having the jam look through the the
keyhole
boring as hell and then we have
um now this one I like because I like
alpacas this is an alpaca with a scarf
and a hat
but what
what the why why
it's so normal [\h__\h] cookie cutters is
it too much to ask
and then we have a dog a pug a pug out
of all dogs a [\h__\h] pug with also a
scarf and a Christmas hat and I also
found a huge ass dog bone
and now because we had something for
good at I found something for Cali as
well actually so I bought it even though
I don't know if I'll use all of these
stupid stupid cookie cutters
unbelievable look at this
a Cali cookie a deadbeats cookie so we
have a shark
and we have this and maybe for dog for
Ahmed we have we have this one
the only thing I'm missing is a inner
cookie cutter it's not like I was
looking for these but this was literally
the only thing that they had
um
so then I was like oh for [\h__\h] sake I
called my BFF and I was like yo do you
have any freaking normal cookie cutters
I looked everywhere I guess the normal
ones are just sold out all I could find
was these ones and she was like yeah let
me try to help you and then I was given
a tree okay
a star okay nice perfect and
this is it this is the one that you need
if you need a lip if you make Lindsay
algon especially this one is perfect
because you can kind of like do a funny
thing here uh see this I don't know how
to use it
I don't know how exactly it works but
um yeah
with this one you can make the linta
organ because it has three holes in the
Middle where you will see the gem
through it because it's like a two layer
cookie with Jam in between and from the
top of it you will see uh already the
gem color poking through
and it's a round shape with these swirls
yeah
like this but yeah I guess these work
together
maybe not this one is a bit bigger I
think anyway yeah so once again BFF
saves the [\h__\h] day
[Music]
saving the [\h__\h] day and the other
thing that I didn't find in the shops
either
yesterday
was a noodle noodle thing a roller
so this one I also had to borrow
um from my beloved
friend however now that we're not making
these today I guess I will buy my own on
Amazon for next time that we're doing
this yes
do you have any pose requests to end it
off with you want me to do some funny
hand poses
if yes I think there's a lot of hand
emojis
just show me show me the icons the
Emojis on the chat and I'll do what you
want
I already did got him
what's a jazz hand
this one
hey
Mahalo aloha
or call me
flip off the chat no I cannot do I would
I would not do that but I Can Do I Can
Do the Fox One
and they're rocking rock and roll
oh my God
what else is there
oh oh
pray
[Music]
oh
this one this one we do when you're
lying and and you you don't wanna you
don't wanna get into hell for lying
[Music]
oh
get them into nice shape
[Music]
um
or like twiddle the thumbs
I'm waiting
this is how fast can you go how fast can
you go
[Music]
thank God
this is more like money isn't it when
you do it like this it's like money
money
foreign
numbers one
one
two
three
four
five
wow I don't know how you're gonna use
that but you're welcome
oh
money money
but yeah it's super chat super chats for
you guys for everyone here so
so wow
Make It Rain baby
make it rain
okay I can't think of anymore uh uh uh
Illuminati uh
uh rock paper scissors okay let's do
rock paper scissors everyone are you
ready and
there will be a delay so it's not really
fair
okay are you ready rock paper scissors
rock paper scissors
Duncan phone
[Music]
Duncan fun
rock paper scissors rock paper scissors
rock paper scissors
can't keep up can you wrapping positions
I win
because the stupid camera works wonders
for me right now
I can't see what I'm doing can't stand
[Music]
up
I'm thinking of what else I can show you
uh
many things but I'm too lazy to get up
now so I guess
I only won once congratulations
I'm glad you're actually being fair and
not cheating
what's this pose it's just something
like like a fighting pose
wasn't that like a greeting for some
kind of sports uh fighting Sports
oh Facebook
brofist
wow
mommy come coming
up here
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
mmm
um
[Music]
I can't think of any more animal chips I
don't know how to do animal shapes with
my hands but we can't do it yeah oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] wait how do I do an animal how
do I and
um this is a butterfly
um
in this design
[Music]
I used to know if it's um how I make
like
foreign
let's make a no that's too long how do I
make a short
[Music]
a rabbit yeah
wrap it pickle
pickle tie my ears to help
show us a bird uh oh wow
how about that how about that
uh uh
[Music]
pretty bad it's pretty bad I'm pretty
bad at this stuff not very impressed
maybe maybe a fish maybe uh maybe no uh
uh no
um
[Music]
oh god oh chill chill
how to make a how to make a
I don't know
now
and with that everybody I say and German
we say I'll be nice then thank you guys
for watching as I said I'll be putting
up a schedule uh today and I'll probably
be doing a gorilla Super Chat reading I
think later in the day
um maybe maybe possibly yes uh tomorrow
will be my day off I will not be
streaming tomorrow uh I'll be waiting
for my Christmas tree
and a meeting with BFF I think and yeah
uh what else oh yeah uh some color of
Ina coming up on my channel next week
next week and we're also doing another
cooking stream like this uh we're gonna
do a gingerbread house building uh next
week as well
um uh I forgot which day but yeah sorry
for the lack of cookies we made some and
they taste great oh but more will follow
eventually yes I will um promise yeah
thank you promise we didn't do that one
yeah
and you guys also promised me one thing
that you'll be here with me next week
and the following week and especially
yes
thank you
okay chill now chill thank you
yeah
[Music]
thank you for coming
thank you guys thank you thank you
[Music]
bye -bye
foreign
[Music]
every time I do these cooking streams
and then go to the ending then you guys
are like oh New Ending but actually this
is an old ending it's just the only
ending I have on my the only ending
music that I have on my on my laptop so
have you realized that this is not new
it's just what I have on my laptop
yep but I'm working on something new for
sometime soon yeah
foreign
[Music]