[Music]
e
come on come
on you can read I know you can do it
come
on come
on come on come on come on go on come on
[Music]
ah I see you have awakened me from my
Slumber is it time to reenter the world
of
Li I have risen from my
heart I see it is time to return to the
world the world of is
is it
time let's go okay okay okay as you as
you wish As You
Wish
okay wait
pause okay here's the thing
though in order to get there we have to
lose consciousness somehow um the first
time we did that it was done for us I
don't remember how it happened but um in
order to get back in there we're going
to have to lose Consciousness again
right right how are we going to do
that how are we going to do that
[Music]
Bonk okay we could we're all going to
have to do it
though okay um
okay do you trust
me look look at me we want to play in
the isai world yeah okay it'll be fine
we just got to you just got to trust me
okay
okay it'll be listen it's only going to
hurt a little bit and then we're going
to get to play okay just just eyes on
me uh three
three
two actually I'm not I'm not going to
count you in cuz it's just going to
stress you out um okay
um
one
3 4
[Music]
oh yes you're finally awake good
don't worry about me I was just mumbling
to myself it was not that big of a deal
let me go in here and unmute this I
think I'm really caffeinated cuz I'm
pretty shaky I don't really know
why why am I so
shaky oh I don't like it ooh ooh ooh
wait I got the trembles ew
[Music]
let me check one more thing all hold on
hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on
hold on hold on hold on wrong coffee too
caffeinated way too
caffeinated let me boost my own
volume
okay welcome back to the world of Li
style Li Style
my name
is I am the bearer of the red hat I am
the appointed point of
the
Scarlet wand and I'm holding this pot
because I I locked
I I did not I I needed
money I didn't I needed money and I
needed to figure out the map so I
knocked myself out again and I came in
here and I did a fetching time thing I
went and did a gathering Quest and now I
have this
pot there is another another of whom of
which of whom who Dawns the red hat of
the appointed
Point did they put on the hat did they
bear the Hat because once you bear the
hat at the appointed point of the
Scarlet wand you must not ever remove
the Hat of the appointed Point otherwise
you will
die fauna is now an appointed point with
the pointy point of the appointed
Point she mustn't ever remove her head
or she will die she will
[Music]
perish would you like a pot I have this
pot
here I have a pot let me unmute myself
in game too I have a
pot okay so check out what I figured out
right
I kind of understand how the map works
so we shouldn't get lost so easily
anymore the pot is what you use to cook
things with which is pretty cool um but
these flags the green the Jade Spoon is
that way along with us the the the the
the the the Scarlet the Scarlet wand and
then if you go if you if
you the closer you get to the colors
something something or other will
change yeah pretty much is you if you
get to the the center point here I don't
even know if this is the center but I'm
going to call it the center if you get
to the Jade the Jade
Arena that usually means you're near the
center and the quest board should
be the questing board should
be I swear I knew my way around here not
even an hour
ago
here guys it really is you can does it
perhaps work if I just like burn it like
this with
my business model yeah okay lock into
trade
hello thank our sponsorship has arrived
serf GAA
VPN
huh hat the appointed point you both
haveo interested in a lottery ticket a
lottery ticket of which time would you
be interested in gambling and partaking
in a lottery so you buy a ticket and I
guess the proceeds go to supporting the
library did you know that once you wear
the hat of the appointed Point your
memories are shared I feel like we've
already had this
conversation what no you're
what did she try to enter she you tried
to enter sevens but you had a double
seven you couldn't enter that right I'm
I'm a bit fuzzy I had a bit of a a
concussion
who's watching the Vlog who's watching
the
Vlog I was watching your Vlog and she
was watching her Vlog memories perfectly
how unfortunate like a high of Mind guys
can you me each other's mind wait okay
wait GA think of a color tell think of a
color she thinking she's thinking of
blue how did she know it's the Hat of
the appointed point you know you mustn't
ever remove that hat or else you will
die I should get one of these hats okay
okay
what about you you die I will also
die okay I know if I remove the Hat you
die and if you remove the Hat I die we
both die money I leave the Hat on
forever then gotcha guys can you like
gotcha yeah can you like put your heads
down
and I don't know if that's the same
gambling as everybody talking about
there's a different
one yeah's created her I'm talking
and then there's Implement are we oh I
saw a vlog about
it oh you
did a limo are you limboing under
us can you
go it works wow we also flexible very
impressive very very cute I got the
knees fauna do you want to show us your
mark I haven't seen it oh yes yes it's
it's still a work in progress and we
mainly sell lottery tickets at this
point are we all
going F Mart is open wa it's open oh
wait you owe me a you owe me a place to
rest my weary head oh yes you may rest
your weary head in the floor of the shop
okay IED that and I I I wish to have
you right weird I love forgot about that
part with the the head of the appointed
points the sharing of memories could be
to turn around
like the sharing of the sharing of the
appointed points could be could be could
be also powerful but also also world
ending you guys I don't I don't think
how do we tell the others that once they
Dawn the Hat of the appointed point this
sounds like a good deal it's not a Goa
gotcha once
once the percentage chance of you
becoming a head of the appointed point
it's not it's not a you would like to
buy some it's not a box of fashion we
could we could negotiate it's a curse
but mainly it is for lottery tickets yes
what is the benefit of a Cher you won't
fit through here I
suppose that's fine don't worry check
this
out are these just available I just have
to duck now that's
then you have to go out and get it
yourself is it is it that much trouble
yes I'm not sure about I'm not sure
about the safety of this
establishment it's kind of breezy in
here why yeah well it's a work in
progress May more lottery tickets are
purchased then that can go towards the
betterment of fart wait what do you mean
I thought the lottery would go towards
the library does it not go towards the
winner go towards the library was this
mentioned before for well check check
the fine print of your
ticket I will I think you should put a a
sign down where it says like please wear
hats when entering like a hard hat you
know like on a construction
[Music]
side Excuse Me Miss the vine prin says
it says that you get 30% of the jackpot
winnings but you just said 10% no the
library gets 10% this sounds exactly
like recently
so 40% doesn't even go
towards the the jackpot is huge huge
jackpots big wins in the lottery every
day okay then after taxes what well I
don't know if you have to pay taxes the
king doesn't know about this Lottery and
i' like to keep it that way and I think
you all would too we can go you wait you
just wait until the queen hears about
this the future Queen the queen is the
Queen the future Queen you shall treat
her as the curent Queen the The Tam
tenders lady
oh proposed to her so she's accepting
his proposal then of course a banquet of
course she
is we have to think of what what would
we give as a present for the like a betr
of how about a lottery card a lottery
ticket for D ters two lottery cards two
lottery tickets yes I don't know I feel
like that's embarrassing I feel like
there's nothing you can really give to
someone who's going to be Queen when you
are the status that we
are indeed Heroes we're saving them
though like what like a blenders if they
can't get one
themselves but it's the thought that
counts and you could put a as long as
you make it personalized what goes into
a blender I feel like should give them a
card no fire inside I'll put it out
sorry sorry that's just the Phoenix
happenings every once in a while
accidentally I'll turn the AC on oh yeah
I can't again who
who it was the
[Music]
AC anyways F that's messed up man
what you what what you're you you're
taking advantage of people that can't
read that's what the library is
[Music]
for the
library you didn't mention they have
read it's a library of course of course
M doing something for the local
businesses M what are you doing for the
local businesses why are you on her side
because
wand intimidating her hat sorry what
she was trying to scam you though no but
she's on my team so as long as she wins
I
win like well she she's my mother she's
my brother it's okay takes all my money
we will expose this scam on her Vlogs
and then you go down Expos sounds like
free
advertising make sure to write about it
in the paper so everybody knows
no one I'll hold on to my ticket I'll
tell the queen about this wait wait
before you tell the
queen would would you be interested in
joining the
lottery no it's it's only 10 gold perck
I think it's a really good deal uh you
get a German
discount a German discount what the heck
what's a German
a German is uh it's like one of the side
quests that I mentioned earlier yeah I
want I want to go on this side quest to
learn ger Germany yeah
Germany Germany don't fall for another
scam of theirs I can teach you Germany
privately all of Germany buy the tickets
I feel like ticket need multiple pink
sources multiple but if your Germany
isn't in the right Germany my Germany is
the best
Germany I have the superior Germany
okay look like you have a hole in your
roof my good sir do you need you do you
need do you need any
assistance you're not ready cuz you
haven't bought a ticket yet right that's
you ticket you you can just
come on I wait are we all going to are
we all going to learn about Germany now
yeah okay oh no not about Germany we're
doing the side quest to learn German oh
yeah that's what I that's what I meant
okay okay uh this way okay
coming good question wait I remember I
have a memory step number one okay have
to talk to this
NPC okay everyone gets on their
[Laughter]
hores he doesn't say anything in
particular it says I can pee your Shield
if you want me to yeah that's not very
German he also says it in German
no oh look look closely it says it right
there scam this this is just another
scam over there I understood perfectly
he said I can be your Shield if you want
me to my go I can understand German
we're absorbing she did it oh wow that
is very impressive okay next one next
one right this way wait a minute wait a
minute wait I'm not okay I'm ready I'm
ready I'm ready sorry I'm absorbing
everything Cara get on your
horse no no come with us come nine N9
n99
why would we need these NPCs to teach us
German when I can teach her German
privately cuz real like this is a video
game and this is a shortcut in real it
takes too long but this way we learn
it's like it gets like transplanted into
our
brains
999 can't argue with that 999 okay the
next NPC is right here
keep up I can't keep up where
where go horse
go oops every
time Speak oh he's
[Music]
saying did you understand what he
said I understood it what did he say I'm
getting bits and pieces here
[Music]
it says I'm supposed to be working
please
don't
oh what was that oh what was
[Music]
that what was
that wow it's working it's working
wow I think M already finished the
[Music]
quest what does that
mean um um she's saying it
worked
uhuh it means that I speak German she
says wow M you you're natur
[Music]
with me you'll get the quest
reward it's
working he's your request
reward what do you get for learning J
[Laughter]
German wow she got some
[Music]
bread oh I'm so I'm so happy we did the
side
quest ha it's so easy to learn
D
Dell that was amazing I learned so much
this world has everything I'm so happy
that they implemented this honestly I
think it's very nice yeah I feel like
they should they should set this up with
more
languages um where car go yeah where did
you go she I'm I'm I'm out of place now
I
feel I don't know I don't know she went
backwards I think or I have no idea I
wish we had like
a
locator like a like a radio that we
could use to call her and ask her to buy
a lottery ticket something like that she
was almost folding I think she was very
close to buying the lottery ticket
I think if we hadn't got distracted by
this Great quest I think she would have
bought a lottery ticket you know who
hasn't bought one
yet my fellow pointy I don't need to buy
one if we share the same I I I let me
see that's what you might think but in
reality you do need to buy one for even
your contribution sweetens po little
everybody else
so can I can I eat you down for four
tickets four for four tickets that's cuz
you know how much money I have donation
of four tickets get out of my get out of
my head hat wearer listen we got to set
some boundaries here I'm very impressed
my it's it's only once a day and then I
won't bother you about it again until
until tomorrow after the drawing yeah I
will buy one ticket adapted to the
tongue one ticket I will start with one
from feel after
that okay what got it it's like
something clicked in your brain it's
very impressive okay what numbers do you
want but I have to clear my throat a lot
before I do it so I'm not going to do it
three numbers yeah it's a bit of a
difficult set up I would like I mean I I
would like
like I would
like how do I I don't remember how to
make wait what number what to what
numbers what to what what's the maximum
oh one to nine
ah let's
[Music]
do
uh three
three sorry that made it sound like I
was
to okay you quiet I keep but you're so
quiet I'm quiet I will send you
okay okay your lottery ticket in the
mail you should see it oh you put me up
I'll put you that be just 10 gold this
up at you up oh that's why you were
trading me I see you're put up I
understand and
now five five and TI oh a fun fact one
fun fact oh just one oh okay okay that's
okay yes thank you for your your
contribution to our local libraries I
mean the memor wait wait wait I should
get paid no matter what right me that
the other day Scarlet one gets a pie no
matter so technically I'm getting a bit
back right yeah yeah you know the you
don't sound very sure when you say yeah
no exactly 10% for the guild
[Music]
boy 10% for the guild everybody in the
guild separately or
together together
together you know when when one of us
succeeds we all succeed
right a rising tide raises All
Ships I don't know how I feel about a
Salesman that I can hear smiling when
they talk to me
what full of joy you too can be full of
joy if you partake in the lovely those
are the only options the salesman guy
ripped me off about my car insurance
goodness I'm so high up you turn into
there's no cars here the lottery is not
insured so don't worry no insurance
scams here not
insured I don't know you don't have to
pay any extra for insurance
[Laughter]
wait have you ever seen the thing that's
like that's like boys love to drop
things from like giant Heights is it
based on that like dropping rocks from a
CL like that is that what it's based
on I don't know I saw a video the other
day of like this group of like 10 guys
all carrying a rock just to throw it off
the cliff and they got so excited about
it y ice breaking
yeah the ice cream Ice Break boys will
be boys a grown man throwing a rock
in no it's the thing there's like
compilations of it like satisfying
videos but for for men I guess fish PA
be like I support it the pool fish they
get their
heads I kind of get it I saw this video
where this like these people were
bouldering and they had to you know
loosen up or get rid of the really loose
rocks M and they got rid of this one
like part of this rock and you it drops
and you're like oh it's not that high up
but then it keeps falling and it keeps
falling and you realize it is really
high up it was
crazy I think the ice breaking is really
satisfying I think when you go somewhere
and it has snowed and the snow is
totally untouched and you put like a
full first footsteps that is very
satisfying the
crunch crunch when like no one's been
there so so far so it feels like you
know you're the first yes because it
gets so
gross it gets so gross after like enough
people walk through it it's extra
seasoning no not that wait like the dirt
the dirt shaved ice is shaved ice real
real real real snow
yeah yeah sh picture is better then what
you can get from the machine and the
nutrients extra nutrients nutrients it
boosts your immune system eat some
dirt oh the dirt IM me yeah ladies Minal
ladies I have a question would you be so
kind to accompany me I would like to see
if I can also get a red pointy hat the
appointed
points59 money how do you guys is this a
guild thing no you just need a gble
thing yeah okay I want a hat too wait
why are you now so excited about
gambling yeah what with the lottery I
don't care about money I only care about
hats but
you the appointed point she's going to
know everything saying she's
Guild what just a library there's like
Barnes & nobl you can just buy books now
Kindles I got a Kindle what's a Kindle
good I did it I
haven't I got it like a month ago
you keep talking about how you have a
kle but it's still in the
box I have a it's there like looking at
[Laughter]
it I got a
case dud you didn't even put in a
case no I I bought a case and I and I
put it in the
case I did an activate you turn it on
yet did you did you put on a protective
foil no is there one I think so actually
it still has the factory peelies on it
it it has like the default thing on you
could turn it on and like read through
the instruction man on the Kindle I even
traveled with
it I had I had to take it out of TS
[Music]
okay hey at least you have
one yeah soon you'll read from let us
know when you use it let us know when
you turn it on I also brought like a
real book with me did you read the real
book I did I read a little bit of it oh
my gosh till I could read no more use
the Kindle as a bookmark for your real
[Laughter]
book okay I don't
remember I think the gabbling was here
this way Main Street across from the
blacksmith
yes I won't I won't speak German anymore
I don't think she likes it here so it is
gambling just so you know M so if you
buy one there's a chance that you don't
get a hat I already bought two and I
have is it the surprise box yeah yes
okay I bought it going to open it
together good luck how do you open it
okay so you have to put it in your hand
and then right click
it okay okay ready three two
one and then you have to pick one it
didn't
work wait you pick one each one of the
squ is a CH your H
bar hold up I think I'm doing something
wrong yep oh oh there go holding it
you pick only oh shoot you pick one and
one of those has a hat behind it only
one has a hat four four of those I
think what else can you get a
box I didn't get anything what are these
I the Hat she I didn't get the I didn't
get the Hat what I
get alert what we do what wait what I
get what' I get what I get what I get
what you didn't get anything hat I got
the Hat you got nothing you got nothing
nothing don't worry about it it doesn't
work you got the Hat it's not going to
work no no no no
no what there's no point in wearing it
what wait what's going on what's going
on so ugly anyway I did I get all these
want to wear it did I get everything one
I'm going to pass just showing you what
you didn't get it's
like did you wait you should think very
hard before you put that on your head
think very hard wait wait a minute I why
can't I put it on my head don't don't do
it don't do it what
is excuse me right click
the the Hat of the the Hat of the
[Laughter]
appoint okay now you guys have to stop
talking and only use uh
telecomunication okay here's here's the
deal now
the head of the appointed points has
been has been dawned by a member outside
of the guild which hasn't ever happened
before in the history of this scarly
wand it's fine only been here for a day
it's fine it's fine it's fine um I knew
she was sorted into the wrong Guild I
knew it it has to be
Destiny it has to
be I wasn't Ming when I said you're on
another
level wait I agree now no my creative um
would you say you're a
genius knowledge do you seek
knowledge I I do do I mean you have a
Kindle I I do do Kindle but an unused
Kindle yeah but it's like she's seeking
it still you know I still seek it it's
just I I got a little distracted as all
yeah because she's so creative and
creative types often get distracted yeah
I was sleeping I was sleeping a lot and
dreaming yes and I was having the
craziest
dreams yes the craziest dreams I've ever
had I think we have to all three of us
should touch tips and and and finish
the the D of the the Hat of the
appointed Point
ceremony in the tri
formation they're like flamingos down
wait a little bit back moving little bit
okay okay up down all the way down all
the way down further down all the way ah
there you
go wait a little closer little closer a
little closer you can make a triangle
you can make a
triangle wait back
down
triangle that points to CE I mean the
green one can I go in the middle yes you
can
now this is my
tppe I live
here
oh what was that well that inant TP can
I do that I saw power me only oh only
you the TV of hey it's your special
thing I sensed a presence around the
presence of death well welcome to the
Scarlet wand m
is that a safe way to hold a knife what
up I guess I guess we've multiplied I
what's the word two time in wait I I
said this
earlier I'm doing a different type of
two time and two time and hat wearing
I'm a two time and hat wearing cape cape
ad just just know if you take the hat
off all three of us will
die really
really don't I believe you okay don't
test it okay I believe you I'm not going
to test it I don't want to die that's
that's that's cool and you totally
wouldn't use it against the Scarlet one
Guild right because that that would that
would potentially potentially eliminate
two of the members the existing members
of the Scarlet one and that would be
catastrophic catastrophic the all of all
of La all of label would fall before us
and and then the king would and the I
don't think she's listening
anymore
well well this could go either way does
she have does she does she share the the
lottery now I I don't know I don't
know I bet they're behind this I bet
they're in on this they know they know
they know what's going
on oh hi
hello who what
now where
watch out don't hit me with your horse
again
horse did everybody I think everybody
went
out I think
everybody
H are you going I
left wait where is
everyone they didn't are you passed them
oh
God ah
where did everybody
go wait did M go at
though they're in the
cafe I tell me m didn't go
out that money 200 money oh let's see
well M went out I am a little curious I
guess not I mean I I have a lot of coins
so probably shouldn't tell you that but
yeah I have a decent amount of okay yeah
um sure more tickets means more chances
true I'll start off with 10 10 seems
like a healthy
amount okay shall we hey what's with the
whispering is that Kiara Holan it is you
C be I told you about this no no you
have to understand I I was I was the one
scamming them I I was the one that was
going to scam them for their tickets and
I was going to sell their tickets people
oh that is kind of evil though that just
continues the evil would been hilarious
especially if we like make enemies and
then we can sell the tickets to the
enemies for a higher price okay I agree
I agree it's just a pyramid scheme The
Jig Is
up oh what did you say we couldn't hear
you our bgm was a bit loud so we
couldn't hear your Whispering oh really
okay yeah just trust me on this Ki Oh it
makes perfect sense oh okay
okay I trust the bom that we have yeah
of course and besides it's me that's
losing money not you um but you can say
I told you so later how shall we make
the trade all right I will trade with
you that's 10 tickets for 200 coins
please and you may choose the numbers or
I can give you a random assortment of
tickets
200 ooh okay um I'll take your's maybe I
should choose no I will go ahead and
leave it up to chance
okay I'm muted don't worry she can't
hear she can't hear they can't hear us
don't worry we're muted 200 200 though
wait what 200 coins no don't I couldn't
can I see your special magic spell I
haven't seen possibly a mute myself and
let them know what I know I shall not
they're
connected I just don't want I don't want
M I feel bad I feel bad we we're
connected now I I can't can't leave I
can't leave somebody I still at the T
Tavern
I oh are you sure you didn't just take
it from a miniature Recreation of New
York the city no
like ancient tree having Ace
transaction it's just taking a while if
you could just lock in uh you will find
your tickets in your mail box mailbox
delivered already
[Music]
what
Communications not as
impressive is very
Advanced that's so cool okay I okay cool
oh that's nothing what you'll never take
me
alive H it has like 30 seconds it was a
scam run
no hey it wasn't a scam now I have to
delete all these
tickets what's
that hello to profit a failed
transaction took the money wait she took
the money she took the money now I have
to I have to I have to take back all the
tickets I sent her I can't believe they
would scam us like this what color uh
Guild are they from
again wait
are you in their
Guild who Guild do we have a
spy what oh wait Scarlet hat adorned
spy I'm of the coin of Ember no Amber I
see and who's in your
guild uh the lady of the
orange the
bay which which one which which orange
the Phoenix of or kiaha of the orange
the K of the orange the
oranges and the b h and the really cute
cat oh the really cute cat I see yeah
the super cute cat yeah very cute when
you P purse very cute that cat very cute
cat Okay well that means that she can't
be with the with the messenger of death
be on the messengers of death side
because they're not in the same
[Music]
guilda of the oranges with
her was kiava the oranges with the
messenger of death yeah oh that's a
little concerning for me Isn't
it unless you convince kiaha of the
orange to purchase a lottery ticket to
Aid in the the wait a minute what did I
miss you both now are for this whole
loty ticket
thing but you're part of the SC now
because of your hat give the Hat about
24 hours and you'll come around what
benefits do I get now that I have the
Hat in relation to the lottery ticket do
I get a percentage of the percentage
that you keep of the 30% do I get a
certain percentage of that
30% well when the library wins everyone
wins yes you got to sell me on this
Library a little bit more
it it looks like a laundering scheme at
the moment put your even where all the
where all the resources have gone to and
how little books there
are but the lottery hasn't even had a
single day yet to benefit the library
but why is the library already so large
with so many riches except so happened
before we arrived in this land we're
just trying our best to to repair the
damage that has already been done to our
system but do you have trust in this
Library that's already so sketchy or did
you remove the people that change it
from the inside M we have to be the
difference we have to buy physical books
by encouraging people to gamble and
throw their life savings away yeah we
only ask for a meanly 10 gold that's but
you encourage even more that
is I think this is part of the Hat
taking over potentially oh my gosh am I
feeling
empathy am I sympathizing for those that
fall into gambling patterns which I
canot relate to because I got the Hat on
the first
try well wait the Hat has one more super
crazy buff whenever you're losing in an
argument you can say but I have the
point and then you win
automatically this is
true that's right this is true so quick
you guys say I have a point so that she
loses at the library argument yeah I
have a point I have a point I also have
a
point well we have two points and you
only have one point so but I have V
point she's right she does have the
point kwaa of the oranges kwaa of the
oranges what a good point she pointed
out she pointed out huh appointed
herself to be the one to make the
point we have to do a quest are we okay
the dungeon opens in we don't have to do
anything
right the dungeon opens oh soon oops we
want to do time flies when you have a
point I wish I had a hat what's the
point we'll get you your hat we'll get
to that point don't
worry good one
maybe we can find someone they can lend
us money I only we knew somebody was
really heavy Pockets more lottery
tickets and then we can't look
suspicious we can't how dare you how
dare you m leaving our guilt behind to
join this scammer Guild I will never
forget this I will Revenge and I will
tell the
[Music]
queen
uh-huh I understand everything that just
happened because cuz I was I was reading
your mind throughout that whole
[Music]
conversation
no my hat tells me these are not real
tears real
not prove it my hat tells me that that
that is real notot
I wish She's So
Mean I she maybe she was jealous of your
hat that's true probably I said I said I
look look keep all of the oranges I got
a hat wouldn't you say that I have the
point and then I was going to go and
tell you guys that she said I have the
point but she she wouldn't did
that are you okay you sound like you're
choking I'm okay
okay um it's it's okay I'm sure K kiar
will come around uh you just have to say
I've got the point more often yeah
you're also taller than she is which
gives you gives you more more more
dominance right so use that as higher
I'm higher you're much taller you're
right yes you guys are right you guys
get me I'll never betray you you guys
totally get
me my hat says otherwise but I
appreciate
it is the Hat thinking further ahead
than I am it might be head the mind is
very powerful like I do have intrusive
thoughts that I think that's something
you guys should consider I think things
that I don't want to think I just got a
really weird urge I don't know if I
should act on it
are you guys influencing each other in a
triangle we might be like one person has
an intrusive thought and then the other
person that window looks so
breakable I didn't I wish it
was yeah it just looks it it isn't
actually I know
oh I how do you throw stuff again
Q I don't think they even throwing is
not allowed in this King you can't throw
because you get fined for littering did
you know
that F coin fined for littering wait how
do I test this I don't know but there is
a
fine I believe you I believe everything
you say that's good I think it's because
we are the heroes we are hardwired not
to do
crime maybe there's like some Force
inner Force stopping us
doing bad
things that's what it's called
conscious cons yeah I think it makes
sense and
also I thought about this since last
time M did you do the dungeon the first
one I did do you remember how in the
entire dungeon there was not a single
stain yes do you remember how the queen
and the all the people in this town and
country are like oh you have to defeat
stains they are be really evil and then
they send us on a dungeon Mission and
there's not a single stain don't you
think that's sus specious the skeletons
not count as a stain the skeletons were
not stains there were skeletons there
skeletons mhm somebody somebody that
other team maybe they were in the wall
the king somebody does somebody did say
something weird to me actually I can
take you to
them oh it could be perhaps I want to
hear weird things a break in the in the
Matrix just or some something like that
follow
me how did I get F there wait hold on
how did I get there wait this
way this way this way this way something
is happening something is going
on whoa is it
you okay he said something weird oh you
see oh she is saying something weird
there's a break something is
happening NPC talk text cute three I
feel like this is a message for us that
we need to
decipher NPC talk. text. cute3 what
could it mean what could it not
everything is what it seems
perhaps I think the three stands for the
fact that there are three guilds that
are probably in cahoots with a kid
and that there's only one Guild that is
doing the truth that's what the text
stands for you know text as in like
scripture the the truth yeah yeah talk
talk lying and can they're all NPC
except for us
except it's fing together I think I see
in this kingom a mystery is a foot and
it's to us the
one what is three
backwards
three uh
ear e right withit the number of the
word it is e e could it be saying Q
T could it just be calling you a cutie
is it maybe it's not that
deep why would it be
unknown yeah can we really unnown s for
the she's wearing the Hat I've heard of
people having names that basically mean
unknown like saying what the others are
saying I feel like I feel like she's
she's putting us on a red herring like
on a wrong path I feel kind be wrong I'm
sorry I just I
just now she's Bing I just won't tribute
I guess
[Music]
okay no no no no no all right I
apologize the making me feel stupid or
making me feel like I'm betray you
guys the Hat it's the Hat can make us a
bit it could have been I'm sorry the Hat
gives delusions of paranoia it does it
does it's a side effect the Hat the Hat
oh the Hat yeah it was the Hat
sorry it wasn't me it was the Hat I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
too thank you I'll consider forgiving
you you think the answer is in the next
dungeon it just might be perhaps it
could
be the dungeon that opens in 2 minutes
in two minutes maybe it would be worth
exploring that dungeon so that we can I
was shocked I thought it get to the
bottom of this conspiracy perhaps
dungeon time mayhaps it's for enough are
you joining us I will have to leave you
I will not be doing the dungeon today
but leaving us to the dungeon I'm sorry
I'm leaving I'm a little too scared to
go in
there oh we'll Scout it for you and then
you can go in yeah let me know how it is
with a guide we'll write you a nine page
document that gu thank you thank
you we'll miss you
healer oh God die no don't
leave we will miss you terribly but it's
okay can I can I lend you the
Apple I wonder does that work she I have
something to remember wait no where' it
go did you take it from
me where oh it's in your train trade
box my trade box the chest if you click
on the
chest that's oh what oh what
now I think we must go to Atlantis
without a
heal do we have food do you have food I
have I have I have a lot of food okay
that's wait but I can get more food if I
can cook
it I have a pot as long as you have
enough to survive the dungeon you should
be fine is 58 bread enough to survive
the dungeon I think
[Music]
so yeah 12 of them have the which makes
them
stronger this I think this is the German
bread too M what's the machine called
that cuts bread in ger in
German
Mach Mach
that's
amazing machine bread cutting
machine I think
yes that's it that's how do you say it
is oh it d d
is do is is is
is is
that's is yeah
yeah is that's
is D is r d is
R what is our St student everyone she is
the pride of our Acy I'm so proud I'm
like a
sponge she takes in knowledge you have
three extra tiar now to store brain
stuff in so take advantage of it hat
wearer yeah shall do I got to pick my
next language
carefully maybe it's whatever this Li
talks maybe that's not if you learn this
language you might be able to out of
this simulation I think it's ruined for
me I think any attempt to understand him
is ruined you guys maybe not feel too
good about about my decoding attempts so
I it's okay oh
oh let's test it in z d
sorry yeah the dungeon the dungeon okay
good luck my fellow Scarlet wands win it
for us we will win for making money for
us thank
you you foring me about
scams wait next let's make a an
MLM okay in the shape of our hats a
pyramid true oh
yeah um all right do you have go to the
coast and speak to Corin of the Scarlet
wand as the next
Quest I do probably not what's it say at
the top how do how do you check go to
the oh go to the oh I do oh I do I do I
do okay huz where is
people
hello okay it's this way how long do
dams take I have about an hour
the first one took like 30 minutes so we
should do this easy did you guys have
big brains um fairly well my Scarlet
wand the will Scarlet
wandw well is
fair the fairs have been
welled which way do we
go this
we must go to the next area to the coast
hi to the coast to the
coast
sunlight it is
bright
away which way is the
way I got so much money from killing
[Music]
things that is the best way to make
money I mean I only made 50 but oh well
it
seems stronger
weapons eventually so I think the
blacksmith has I can hear you can you
hear me
no what okay it's cutting out the horse
the horse the horse connection is not
very good no it's not we it travel is
faster than the speed of sound than the
speed of or oopsie the speed
of I think
the oh oh what you guys is this the co I
see the coast oh it's so
pretty way
he's so cute Hello one of your people
yeah he has the Hat oops wait this is
this this is your people it's the
Scarlet W
guy our people M our you here to
investigate the mysterious light hour
you can see it there rising from the
waves the locals are quite atir with
curiosity we are short something of
great import lies there in mayhaps a way
to unlock more of your memories
mayhaps but fear not mayhaps as is our
duty and our calling we have been
speaking with the locals and gathering
information in Intel to would seem there
exists a magical object known as a
rainbow Coral cluster which would allow
one to breathe underwater we believe
this to be no mere rumor as the Guild
Master was able to find texts among our
archives that corroborate this story
should one obtain such a what's talking
I'm not getting the same text wait where
am I wait am I just behind hold on oh
should
should according to the text you can be
crafted from Rainbow Coral shards and
refined magical energy you need not
concern yourself with the latter good
hero our Guild Master will gladly
provide it but will you Aid Us in the
search for Coral shards that are
iridescent as a
rainbow so we got to find Coral shards
and bring
them wait he should have said iridescent
such as our coats you know our little
capes they're iridescent too when you
move and they kind of look cheetah print
is oh yeah that's true little
bit
teed
they I'm going to pretend I understand
wait we have to
find Coral 10 rainbow Coral
shards okay I can swim let's see I can
swim okay okay it's just
this is
it it's just this we all have to get our
own right oh yeah wait that's not that
many oh wow that was very difficult them
I'm getting them I love cor
wall o cor
[Music]
wall
o Ru
is they we spawn very fast yeah that's
good easyy got to go all the way back to
oh God oh God oh God oh God R it's okay
wait how do you give him the how do you
give him the shirs you got to go all the
way back and talk to rubies talk to him
oh
oh oh oh no we have to give it to rubius
we got to go all way back to rubius too
many people to keep track of a true
RPG we must go back and forth
there
[Music]
okay Rubi Rubi really feels like RPG
with fch
Quest all the way back oh my ladies
would you per chance want switch to to
what to to which to what uh form a party
so we can be on call in the with the
magical call device I'm sure that sounds
[Music]
useful okay let's let's do it once we
get to
rubious do your best horse bra
that
hello
hello hello wait why is your so little
oh never mind it's look like a pony for
a second what mean little he's perfectly
average size you carry an average size
person wait
the party has split the party has
split are you going to
[Music]
f is that me fom my looks
closed wait for
me we lost m
[Music]
oh
no we lost remember we
lost she
went I can call her and see maybe we
have more people to add to our
party yeah let's see is anyone else
online from our
Guild possibly oh shy shy is online okay
I'll call Shy okay
okay upon receiving word from my
colleague on the coast I immediately
said
about picking up she's not picking up
she's in a call already what she talking
to yeah who is she talking to there's no
no other guild member of our is here
right now oh haa is online still what
she's calling I'm going to spam call
her she will pick
up wait I'll send her an SMS real quick
Ruby is just build something into my
forehead what did he just
do what he did something I wasn't
reading what he said I didn't I don't
understand what he
said a
horse hello you were scared we must have
we could have lost you you did lose me
but I found my way back that's okay
don't worry that's nice oh I've been
expecting let's see what the NBC has to
say okay oh do you want to do you want
to read it out loud for me as well I'm
way oh
okay I can't tell what accent this guy
is this the British no he's not the
British one is he no that's not a
British one this is the Royal one Royal
okay okay upon receiving word from my
colleague on the coast I immediately set
about making the necessary preparations
for
crafting with these shards you have
brought the preparations are complete
now if you will give me but one
moment ping ping what finished I do say
more Arcane prowess astounds even
myself so this is that's okay so this is
a rainbow Coral cluster an object I had
only read of now brought into existence
but don't laugh at me Miss but my very
hand
that's
okay I can't hear him anymore rubius
please sorry
sorry sorry I had a quick screw stick in
my okay but I should not sh should
not I you sound like a kid
[Laughter]
bro I'm one of you
kid do
you I sound like a kid or they sound
like a kid back like yes yes
please a fellow
child ah but I should not bore you with
my EXs you need this exaltation ex
exaltations exaltations you need this
for your quest do you not wizard you
sound like a kid skibby wizard here you
go this will allow you to freely explore
the depths of the sea use it well thanks
for stopping by nothing a payment or
reward as far as I am concerned
curiosity is its own reward oh no I hate
that I know it's so
overused ah but there is one thing I
would ask of you and that is your safe
return from this Quest I can think of No
Greater way to repay the a now then
off with you I expect good news upon
your return
Excel Excel
Excel
or what Excel Exel
what what M or that oh sorry
Junior oh wa that was Wo whoo whoo whoo
that was that was weird your name is j
weird my name is Junior yes short
for was this for I shall try to call uh
shy one more time okay Darwin
Roosevelt Caprio J wait should Darwin
Cecilia and I should we make a
party before we go
back I've never been to a party before
you've never been in a party before it
tickles a little bit but tickles okay
I'm eventally preparing myself you have
to press the T and then
accept but there's there's nothing to
you once you
get we the tea
train there you
go t what's your guys's favorite tea
flavor if I may ask hot cinnamon
spice W it's very good fun I don't think
I one I don't know what my favorite is
cuz I put so much honey in my tea it
just tastes like honey hone is good
though sugar water yeah it's basically
sugar water sugar water you said that
sugar
[Laughter]
water okay oh investigate the Ocean
Temple dungeon then speak to the
SK okay um uh I don't I don't want to
decide what we should do next so someone
else decide I will stand on my horse and
ready up should we I will let my horse
Grace should we do the dungeon do we all
want to do as three or should we try and
invite we can only have one more person
I think we can have I the long as the
dungeon can be completed within an hour
I can do the D um yeah I think yesterday
only took us like half an hour yes and
we were only three hopefully this one
isn't
hard I'll try calling her one more time
we can have five total we can have five
people five total five
total without a call for
the oh my God my throat I can't finish
the sentence you can do
it let me see we can shiy of the Scarlet
wand
please we are summoning you my
calling is here wait where oh not here I
mean I just been here in this
world yes she is she she hello oh that's
not shooting dear oh hello are people
hello
hello hello please call again okay I
will call her
again I want in on on this
hello
hello ding D D D D D D D D hello oh
hello hi hi member of the Scarlet wand
would you like to join us on our
Expedition um trying to think of what to
say to that oh she's doing the dungeon
of the underworld uh gaura of the red
head ah I see ah okay we will discuss I
wish you the best luck we will discuss
and call you again good
luck good
luck um okay she said call for insurance
next
time um okay I guess she's doing the
other dungeon for now
so should we try it as three
should we try I think that's okay I
think everyone there's a lot of people
online so I think everyone will
find yeah yeah I think it's okay yeah I
think everybody will at least have a
group of
three yeah because I think two is too
little probably that be so
impressive and Nissa is online later too
and she's probably going to also have to
do that one again so we can see maybe
I'll be online and then I'll join them
again too okay let's go back to the
ocean
away get the SE away with us wait I
don't trust myself I'm going to follow
follow somebody yeah this way Whoever
has the
map we fine
yeah we have no heels but we should be
fine we should be
[Music]
oh we should be good and well and fine
and successful ful in our water dungeon
Atlantis Atlantis wait where's my
where's my guide oh
okay listen for horse
[Music]
noises where are we all
going this way we're back back in the
car okay are you out oh yeah yes
everybody's going hello are we all going
together I think
so
group is your horse have
turbos does it have what
turbos oh
turbo yes it does
who whoa what model is that horse go so
fast yeah it's this
way I have F you again this one who I
learn
this oh
boy I sure hope I regain some memories
in
Atlantis the real is hot
Atlantis it seems they collect
Coral Ru Corin it is the the Hat of
appointed
points the think very carefully if you
ever have given a chance to Dawn the Hat
of pointed points think carefully CU it
suck out your thoughts just think very
carefully sucks out and someone else the
red fiery hair I already spent all my
I'm
Elizabeth Elizabeth your hair is she got
them yes your to return to
Ruby oh it's it's I don't know yet
sometimes it makes no but I is pointy
what's your name and your hair is very
today my name is Darwin Roosevelt
DiCaprio
J J
call me Junior for sure no don't worry
about it
I'm want
call call me whatever you want I'm just
going with the B you
[Music]
know that's scary I mean it's not
scary it's falling to me it's deep it's
very deep I like your hands a
lot I'm assuming we follow this line
of's my party is my party is being
social I fear
this oh gosh did I unlock her memory
could head
Thee I
get it again I think I'll I'll take part
in this dungeon and then I'll try
getting another for a Please Don't Drown
I don't know how to save drowning we
don't have a Healer
anymore for some reason I wish to break
break have you break a leg you can
breathe underwater now m i mean
Darwin I can you can I could do I I
thought I could do that already it's
okay under
water this nice oh the rainbow Coral
cluster can I have to hold it in my
breathe underwater you are
free as long as it's in my hand I think
so IM was pleasure to meet you are you
also going into this this isn't working
yeah is everybody going to the dungeon
part with my horse I think so let's go
together to the dungeon this way I meat
this way thee or is it
done by the time I come back can you
watch thisit you have the
map oh do you think it's in the water I
thought it was in the water like you
follow
the can we hear each other in the
water that's a good
question are you okay me I'm okay I'm
just dying
a yes please
well I can't wait anymore I got to know
I got to look I got to
see this is a well ocean dungeon I'm
supposed to regain my memories
here so I've been
told o
oo oh that's really
deep let's go here and I think it it's
here oh you are here
hello
yeah maybe something here but nothing
half I think we have to swim
out but might might my my joints do you
think this is salt or seaw water my
joints are very very sensitive to sea
water oh I didn't think of that
um do we have any okay could I like
grease you up in a your joints oil I
could if you if you could oh I was
called hello if you could I arrive and
if wait like M called me oh take take
your time um um yeah hello M
uh some Ocean Temple dungeon to come we
both trying to get to the Ocean Temple
dungeon we don't really know we are in
like a little island but we are on our
way there so do not fear we are going to
be there soon we're on the
way maybe where are
you are you with the fire where you
tried making meat
should we come back to you making horse
meat okay we come we're coming back yeah
she was can't believe she killed her
horse okay we'll be there in the
second no no um yeah let's go here
okay um but yeah no you can't we'll be
there in a second
M you can't you can't grease me up but
if I I have a request if I turn off at
any point would you mind rewinding me
please of course
thank you okay then we're good I think
okay let's do you run on batteries or no
no no you are your crank power yeah yeah
I run on crank power yeah it's all
automated I'm a
machine so sometimes um I can crank my
wind up key myself M but um sometimes I
forget and then if I run out of juice
it's kind of like I go into a Kuma
I I see so if there's any malfunctions
like salt water then sometimes I need
Aid that sounds scary what what if I
don't know how to revive what if I can't
revive you what if I can what if what
if it's okay I think I believe in you
yes it's okay M I don't know how to hang
up well it's almost
[Music]
there we have to crank that soldja boy
I'm sure that that that'll help
right don't crank the so M was like are
you supposed to hear this right
now I was hearing some things oh I just
I I you answer the phone you go no you
can't grease me up yeah you can't me up
I can't grease you up no you don't need
to grease me up okay do you have your
meat are you ready for a journey I yes
I'm
ready okay let's see I think it's just
right here if we follow those lamps
maybe that wait let's make a boat a boat
boat that would be safeer for me
personally you're right true
[Music]
true can I swim I'll swim behind you
guys something something about it I
don't know how to make how do you make a
boat how do you make a boat do you want
to make your own or do you want to sit
in mine like a pass princess only two oh
but only two people can sit in one boat
a y princess oh you want to you want to
okay I'll be passeng your princess what
if it's at the bottom of the ocean
oh then we'll have to jump off the boat
we go for a dive we'll make it really
quick so the water doesn't have time to
settle in your joints cover your ears so
that the yeah the water doesn't go into
your brain ooh rusted aaton
brain all right oh my land I want chipot
way this way give me Chipotle I want
Chipotle Chipotle I've never Chipotle
how does it tast like tastes like salt
salt in a good way
yeah the the spice tastes like salt yeah
it's
salty okay let's look
at I feel like I'm not swimming very
fast can you not
run or maybe I'm going as fast as
possible oh maybe this is it you have to
follow the lights down
that might be what it is follow the
lights
downward I'm holding control shift just
makes me go
down oh wait
no double tap
W nah where are they going they're
looking at the map but maybe they went
too far there she is there she is there
she is wow
no that this way this way
dummy they look like a
ship with the when I have hat with a
cone yeah with the
hat oh my gosh I can't remember my words
right
now wait this isn't where it is this is
the end of the
world let me see this there's an island
over there that that there's multiple
Islands
[Music]
I think we have to follow the light
down oh where guide us creature of the
ocean please this
way this way won we this way this
way the game design it speaks to me it
says follow the light
this way my fellow party
members follow the light down down we
go down
down ringing any bells here something's
starting to itch
ooh this doesn't look familiar at
all it is pretty
though wait where did they go other
there diamonds and Lapis and and red
stone now we're in a group call would
you want to also join the group call so
we can hear each other when we're like a
little bit separated oh yeah yeah yeah
how do how do
I uh so you click with the phone and
then you press on group call
they've been falling an awfully lot
o thank you very nice thank
you nice I wonder if looks really cool
that was really cool like the wall of
water and then we go into nonwater I
think that's very coolly done it's like
Atlantis what that
word does it mean something to me and my
brain
at the lamp that tises oh before we
ready I just want to get some water one
sec
okay I have what I do have water I have
a lot of water there's lots of water
here how much water can you drink at
once can you chug drink water
in I haven't tried I think it's like 14
like red plastic cups of water is like
the max you can drink before getting
water poisoning or something you can
drown
you have water poisoning isn't it
drowning like above water
drowning water poisoning dry dry
drowning what am I thinking of dry Dr
dry drowning is a another yeah it's like
if you drown in a puddle sort of thing
no no no that's not what that is is like
you get too much nose yeah yeah yeah you
get too much water like up your nose or
in your mouth and it goes into your
lungs and then you die like after
swimming in the
pool yeah dry drill scary slurp slurp
slurp slurp slurp drink your water okay
let's ready up I'm
ready go wait I'm not I'm ready ready
ready wait you're not ready oh you're
ready okay ready ready yeah okay let's
go in okay Enter
dungeon it work did it work did it work
did it work
work oh my
this oh a pre strategy meeting what's
your special attack it's the winge of
civilization the
wips
DPS DPS DPS DPS and tank wait who's tank
who's tank I believe I am tank you're
tank okay what is she has CC she has
Crown control not me I do CR control
what does yours do mine is is like a
point I don't actually know she has a
point
automation she has a point a different
point wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait there can be multiple points
made yeah because I'm also part of the
scallet wand so it's
[Music]
F this this world is too complex for
me the noise is really deep it really is
I
fell oh my
goodness look at this this perhaps once
existing
civilization it's very Mossy I don't
remember that oh wait there's a book
here I
know in ages long past there was a land
of Untold
Prosperity its technology and culture
stood at the Pinnacle of civilization
but then I mean who catastrophe struck
and what had taken a thousand years to
build was erased in a single
night oh no oh
no for me it's still rendering wow how
did that happen it start this loading in
how did it happen I one night it all oh
my goodness are those aircrafts or
Dolphins I think the aircraft I think
that makes the most sense a not air
Dolphins it's a it's a boing
747 it's it's like the Beluga plane you
know I've seen that these natural
enemies no no no oh yeah Dolphins
wouldn't dolphins be a shark's enemy
they would never put Dolphins at the
center of Atlantis that would be highly
offensive oh wait wait wait you are
right look at this sharks the the the
fin is this way not the other way that
means they're sharks no I think it's
aing 7 plus7 no no it might be it might
be Shar dream
liner I see I see oh my goodness is this
one a
hammerhead no I think he's just shaped
like that is it just
ugly okay don't say don't call the plane
like that he's not a
plane he's he's a perfectly normal shark
it's the plane okay wait but riddle me
this okay if you hold on to the fin of a
shark's back and it swims and then it
jumps out of the water and isn't that
technically flying and isn't that
technically a
plane don't you think I have a I don't
think it's flying I feel like it's
exertion and then immediately
falling so are you saying if you're on
an airplane and it crashes it's not it's
not flying it is if it is going down it
is not flying
well cuz that's why there's flying fish
flying fish can suspend themselves in
the air and that's what gives them the
title of flying fish versus any other
fish that will breach
to uh eat something for example fall
yeah that makes sense I see okay maybe
they are not
airplanes we will need further Evidence
lots of good points here many many many
points points made
today what that this is is it a puzzle
um
Arrow key look like baby blocks and I'm
not sure if I should be offended yet hey
wait nice job oh the Rings the Rings oh
the Rings they're baby blocks who built
this
freaking oh oh we have to like oh okay
but what are we doing what which way
does it want us to do I think it has to
go to the middle so have
to wait can do it too wait what is this
can I can I do it I want to do it is
that it you do it Tower what is that we
have to make a tower I think green
bottom yellow and wait that's not our
colors kind of of can you not stack them
opposite and I
don't I think it has to be so we have to
[Music]
get a green
bottom how do you move it though yeah
how do you move the one from the middle
away that doesn't make any sense it
won't let you stack them the opposite
way it has to be the big one on big
bottom but there's only one way to
go what if I stand on there's another
button somewhere maybe there's another
one a secret button a secret secret
button wait wait wait wait wait wait no
never mind yes yes wait I got it I think
she's got
it then can this one go back
[Music]
and and and then it goes It goes there
this one goes there and do you pass this
one all the
way yay we did it you did it very nice
thank you for the brain power I've never
seen that puzle before I remembered I
remembered how it how just Stu baby
blocks oh Memories the memories nice the
memories I guess this is some type of
what that do is it just for is it just
for show you miss I think it probably
open the
way
oh oh
just like the airplanes wooo just like
an
airplane I landed that one the
entire audience clapped all the
passengers clapped when I land I could
hear have you ever been on an airplane
where the passengers have clapped yes
yes really yes yeah during a
thunderstorm thought that was like a oh
okay that kind of makes
sense okay um please reach for us SCA
with the land sunk to the depths of the
ocean one might think this was the end
yet where one people had been wiped out
another took its place and lived a new
happy and peaceful
life ah this place is so
boring perhaps even a bit too peaceful
I'm getting out of here you'll see day
after day the little girl planned her
Great
Escape little little
girl
escape she really said get me out of
this town this place is boring
oh I
remembering oh time trial no parkour
time Park parkour parkour we love
parkour one of the laws of the Scarlet
wand is that every time you do parkour
you have to scream parkour oh my gosh
this
I was doing that yesterday it's like
meant to be it was meant to be it was
meant to be meant to do this
dungeon looks so
cool oh do you think this is the reset
maybe is this a dummy lever what does it
do maybe it's like fail adj Okay who
wants to go first wait but there's a
thing that might hurt wait no no no it's
a blue lever that turns off something
over over there oh really they're color
coordinated how did you do that
oh oh then the yellow one is here oh
wait how did you do that what okay I
right clicked it
ahuh oh you can't have your item
equipped okay O Okay yellow is open
yellow's open oh you're right it is open
open I thought it was just a glitch for
me all right maybe it's purple this one
that's green or do you think that's the
reset oh wait wait that might be green
over there
no yeah oh oh wait a minute okay so so
we have to split up
probably I
see if you you see if you go over there
the green ones oh wait but there's no
wait can you turn the lover back because
I think I removed the blue I might have
done that oh I might have removed the
blue oh dear oh I'm stuck okay I think
this is now do you see the purple
somewhere over there across the pink
over there oh all the way there oh I
think I messed it up cuz I ruined the
blue can we back track okay I think no
no wait M you stay here wait you stay
there there there no where GAA is like
in in her Direction
come here I press this button and then
the yellow floor should come back if I
do
this yeah now you can go to her or she
can come back can you you should go to
her are able to undo the blue one
because I think that I didn't I make
this blue disappear I don't think so I
think that was just reset I can make the
blue disappear so I will turn on the red
now and no
wait are
you
okay blue is on now yeah so I can switch
the
green so someone can go through
there I will go through uh you should
keep the G yeah okay there now I can
turn on the red and so GAA can go to the
purple no to the blue to the blue now
you at the blue should I go to the
yellow through this yellow
one um uh let me see wait wait look look
no I think no no no no no just do the
purple no okay I go yeah I I'm going to
kill kill myself please don't kill me
wait hold on I we can talk about I'm
scared I don't want what happen to girl
happen to me
yeah okay okay I'm on my way back one
second what about what about the pink
one over there oh I guess it's up oh I
see I see then there's three
doors maybe this is a shot is is it that
one if we get to the check if one person
gets to the checkpoint and everyone
kills themselves we could also just we
could do that if somebody's at the start
they could joink the blue I think I wish
I could I can do the blue one yeah I'll
do yeah it's like blue yellow please
don't stand on anything I'm activating
it okay did it work yeah
nice is it it I will
touch touch touch wait there's no
checkpoint to
touch yes here okay okay you can die now
uh it was nice serving you can
thanks did it work hello you die yeah
I'm here I'm here with nice
huzzah wow so smart Geniuses of the
Scarlet wand very impressive
and Junior this reminds me of did you
guys watch that
show where legend of the Hidden
Temple this is Legend of the Hidden
Temple is that the one that was in
niclodeon is that that one yeah I
remember that this is literally Legend
show or all the faces like in the show
yeah it's it was a yeah it was a reality
show where kids would essentially do
exactly what we're doing right now and
then they would win really lame prizes
like tuna and roller
blades
yes hey that's something imagine SPID
games but they don't die and they're all
kids you get tuna sponsored by Sun kist
and then they fight and then they get
really hungry and it was called The
Hunger Games they grew up and then
became the Hunger Games then they became
the cast of The hung
games in season 2 episode 4 Jennifer
Lawrence took part in the temple show
she was on the silver monkey team are
the purple monkeys are are you guys
messing with me or did she really no
sheing when cilia says that it sounds
like it's true so I know it's not wait
on
Google I need to switch out of deep l i
mean what what what's deep
L LA deep under the
ocean out can I BL last to this lore
real quick oh my gosh she is she is good
at
lying
what ooh Challenger
approaches there was no nice way to put
it the girl was sick of the underwater
Kingdom and she tried constantly to
leave it behind no they got me again yet
with the guard being ever watchful this
was anything but easy she'd probably
been caught by 100 time 100 times by
now oh wow even so giving up was the
last thing on her mind each failure
instead served as inspiration for a new
attempt am I just going about this the
wrong way yeah I know what I'll do next
and so another day of planning
began she was busted out ooh you a plan
I mean this person is a planner this
young girl is planning a a little girl
little
is a a planner I respect a plan honestly
sometimes you got a
plan all this look at this mumbo jumbo
is this another puzzle it looks like
trap it looks like you got to do stuff
over there to unlock stuff here and then
there's treasure over
here what's going on oh that's so cool
what is this so I think we have to make
the guy go here the the the the guy that
stands here in this little trap oh if we
press this button he follows the arrows
that's so cool wait that is actually so
cool and he probably now we have to make
it so that and where do we want him to
go do we want him to die in here uh we
want him to go in here I assume yeah but
it's he going to die if he does that no
he probably activates this so that it
opens and we can activate it so open
something else oh okay
okay okay can we interact with them oh
okay yeah what do you think happens when
he goes on the gold do you think that's
a wall what isut him yeah should we try
yeah test round test round then go forth
Warrior oh he has to light them
up okay uhoh to light them up and most
likely you can't have him go wait no
he's going over it multiple times and it
doesn't turn off
okay how do oh but you can't do you
can't do all of them oh no no it's just
because he's out right now how do you oh
okay he's an atlantan
guard okay so we have to do it in
advance so he touches all the gold
ones my brain hurts I understand now so
should he go
which way should he go maybe this
way this
way all the way around here go like this
here did I go through here
yet I can't remember what I just
did and then he goes like
this through the
gold oh
this oh I think what about this way like
here
M here wait no no no what I do what did
I do hold on hold on never mind never
mind no you're right you're right and
then he goes to the right here yeah and
then he goes here he goes through this
one and he goes here and he goes here
and then I think he goes here there yeah
and then he go
there and
then here
okay send him let's send him wait which
one wa I don't know which one send
him the right one the right one the
correct one the correct one
okay that's so
[Music]
cute wait but still
oh okay it opened this but there's
nothing in there maybe it opened it on
the other side too it's a it's a it's a
lever like the floor is a oh it's a it's
a lever a button oh oh wait does someone
have to stand on it or something that
happened over here it I think it opened
this did
it no it didn't there's a
chest yeah can someone stand on the
pressure plate yeah I'll do it but I
think we can just send another guy and
make him go this way instead I think you
have to stand on a pressure plate then I
stand on this one then somebody gets the
treasure maybe okay I'll stand on it let
me see let me know what
happens oh are you standing on it I'm
standing on it nothing happened okay let
me try wait there's numbers them again
oh numbers you see this mov
in in the first dungeon you remember
this was like you have to fill the thing
up
oh is it that again I think so cuz the
lights just went
out what we need to hit it five times to
open the door 1 2 3 4
5 oh did I mess up blue to green we're
missing
two wait what numbers are you seeing I
saw it light up I didn't see the the
blocks are the numbers we have to have
all of them light up for that door to
open so one 1 2 3 4 5
oh um them are
open but now none of them are one two
this there should be 1 two three oh wait
is there's an arrow here maybe there's
something up here
too did it turn a light on okay turn two
there oh there's something up here
ah I think it's a is it a mze what is
this
oh it's another pressure it's another
pressure there but what kind of maze is
this water the
water it's a water elevator no is it was
it
time okay so water comes out here we
probably still have to do something here
where you guys were so we definitely did
the first one
correct I think we have to activate this
what is this here
see were you able to do anything when
you pressed anything here I I think it's
the the thing over there is what made
these three light up can somebody come
stand on this so I can go up the
waterfall okay I'll stand on it pretty
please thank
you oh
what's up there do you want to up go do
you want to try to I want up e please
wait for all party members before
proceeding it's a door but not all us oh
is this the last thing you have to do
maybe it's the last thing now we can see
what's up
there wait do we just have to make him
go in a
circle if he goes through the the dots
twice the little guard man oh was is
that it I feel like maybe we can make
him walk here and then we can make him
stand on the platform wait but if we
want him to go in a do you want him to
go in a
circle can I try making him go through
it just to see if it works at all yeah
quick okay actually that's an idle
meeting oh actually no I'll hold it I'll
hold it I'll hold I'll hold off the
Mee just let's see if this if he can
stand on it at
all there's no way
what and
it wait but what about what about this
thingy I think that is a treasure there
might be something extra but I program
are you running the thing
here oh my head is
spinning I think I don't know how though
because like here is an arrow as well
but that Arrow automatically goes up
there so I don't know like I don't think
we can go in here
right no no we can't can we stand in his
way so you can't oh should we try that
can we not switch this when it
oh can you tell me what happens when
what happens when I stand on this does
anything happen anywhere no oh wait do
it again okay I'm not standing on it oh
never mind never mind and now I am
standing on it no there's does the
pressure point turn the arrow somebody
asked yeah can you wait is is the
pressure If you reset it can these be
changed
okay let me try like if we turn them off
yeah I'll
try cuz maybe after can you change it uh
no you
can't well so there's L lanterns here
right here and when we turned all three
golden squares this opened up and then
on the other side there's let's try what
you said where we like Loop it so he
walks over the gold more than once make
him go in a big
circle he is in a loop oh no that didn't
work because earlier we tried making him
go over it and he kept walking over it
but nothing happened oh wait oh this
can't happen
wait no no the can't no wait
[Music]
what okay let me try standing on this
one more time what
happens oh think I messed up oh it's GAA
can you check if the one that's the Pink
Arrow is now editable the one that is
like in the middle it is
not
oh we need to find more
lights
yeah oh what about that
one what about this one
here that's just that's just a
checkpoint I'll do some
investigating outside the box everybody
SPL it up
o it's time to look for clu I'm seeing
something
shiny
shiny oh there a
entrance oh oh I think that's just for
the the backing of the oh treasure like
ooh
gold oh
uh girls what if we reset we make him
turn on all the lights yeah and then we
stand on the no I just don't know what
did what happened when we stood on the
pressure plate you know don't know what
is oh this one this one cuz I feel like
this one opens up this
door don't get it the pleasure pleasure
plates have to do
something I don't know what do they do
should we try this again let's just see
what happens exactly okay so let's make
him go through all golden ones okay go
here wait did I mess it I I feel like I
edited it but I can't remember what I
did did you guys fix
it
remember um so he goes like this and
then he goes up here and like this and
like this and then like this and then
here and then here and then how many
plates are there one wasn't it first he
first goes through here like this
way should I edit it goes this way then
he goes here then he goes I'm sorry for
making fun of the baby block game I want
to bring it back now he goes
here and then this way wait wait wait
wait I'm sorry I I changed something I
shouldn't have I changed way he go he he
goes this
way can I press oh my God wait I can't
count
okay
okay the thing is like we've already
figured it out we're trying to go for
the extra treasure we want the treasure
but not everybody can get oh yeah you're
right yeah wait this just for the
treasure oh oh wait this is going to
work he's I messed it up I messed it up
I messed it what did I
do do you think if we go through the
doorway it'll bring us to the next room
or is it in here yeah I think so I think
this one is just a treasure so
let's
U I think I okay so I think it's like
this so he goes like this this this this
this this imag there's a button back
here one two here and here press all the
plates at once that's what I'm thinking
we can't get to this one then here
up there and I touched the shiny
I'm
okay are you okay
yep okay if we can't make it we we just
keep going it's fine all right we can
role play getting the treasure
yeah oh no wait have him stand there
wait did I do that why didn't wait wait
wait did I do this why is he oh do we
want him to Loop did we intend for this
to happen
what if I it looks like there it only
lights up one at a time okay or like
it's only
three um and send him in
here uh could you stand on that platform
for a second in the middle this one yeah
just let me see if anything happens we
have to make him stand in the one next
to
me yeah but nothing happens when you
stand on it so I don't know if that's
really it you know yeah and when we made
him stand in this one all it did was
open up this
one if you well we can try
Okay somebody save him he's in a loop I
killed him I killed him okay so let's do
this do you want to have we got have we
tried getting him to go in
here him in this one somebody stands
there he stands there does that make s
do that make
sense um do you want him to go in the
which one well I don't know I guess
there's no point because some because
somebody could just stand there yeah
okay let's make him go in the right in
the right
[Music]
one he has he's like special in some
way my brain oh my God wait but if he
goes okay so he goes he starts here he
goes here and then he goes here and then
he goes here wait is he still on this
one go and this one wait they standing
on this one H this one I
remember uh he has we have not made him
stand on the middle but we have made him
stand on the right and when we made him
stand on the right the middle door
opened
up the middle try it again wait but do
we oh wait but he's going to Loop now
then we want him to go into the
middle oh yeah yeah is he going to loop
again yeah he's going to
Loop okay sh
him everyone's
waiting okay let's
see oh like that oh wait what oh okay
that was something we needed to do guess
ding but nothing L up and how come you
didn't how come you didn't complete the
thing wait wait undo undo oh does it
completely reset everything is that what
it does wait no it doesn't completely
reset it because I'm stupid I'm stupid I
D die we have to make him he has to
light up
everything three because then we're
liting I get it I'm stupid I get it but
he can't go this way now if we want to
go through here it can't be the way that
I add it so it has to be here turn here
up here okay but up here up here and
here am I okay to change this I don't
want to mess wait no on what I think it
completely resets everything wait can I
do thing are we can
I hold on he can't we want him to go
through here so we can't have him do the
route can go to the middle and also you
know what I mean
yeah because unless we find a different
wa here can go try
something how come it how come if we go
here it doesn't do the ding but if he
does it it does the ding yeah stop he
has favoritism where's cooking hold on
what's with that okay okay
wait
no wait no you supposed to go through
there oh wait wait it was
almost uh just reset it and then move
this
one I think you got
it wait
I legitimately don't see I don't
understand this I don't see how he can
go through everything oh wait wait like
this okay do it again wait go through
everything and go into here or go into
where
mid but he has to do all of
them I don't think he can he's not going
to get that one though oh he's not going
to get that one
wait see it does the ding if he goes in
there but what is the ding doing is not
lighting it
up I'm firing in all cylinders and
nothing's happening what if we um um
light
wait should we try working backwards so
this one has to be like
this uh and this one can go like this
this one I don't don't think he's
supposed to go to the
middle what if he went to the very
middle I don't think he's supposed
to yeah if he goes to the very middle
then we can we could just keep going we
can't get all of them if he goes to oh
that middle if you if we do that middle
then yeah we can keep going we just
won't get treasure we won't be
cool what I
want want the treasure the
treasure okay okay let's use our brain
power okay okay so we want him to go
here in the middle so he start uh this
has to happen this has to go here um and
then he goes like this like this like
this like this like this was good this
was all perfect the only problem is I
don't know how he can go
here wait if wait which way do you do
you want him to go into this one or do
you want him to go into this one yeah
yeah where you no no no the the one you
want him to go still yeah but he also
should touch all the golden
ones oh I think it like this
no I mean chat says it's possible but I
don't I don't see how it's possible
because I'm to hit all of them and also
go into the middle
yeah can't can't do this cuz yeah I
don't think it's it's I think it's
actually impossible can't change tracks
while he's
moving CH the cooking with gas
now are struggling just does the ding
thing for him cuz he's
special he supposed to go into here and
somebody goes into here and we just have
to figure out what it is that it's an
both of us going into their activates
what's an I hope it's not a thing where
you need more than three
people no no they said it's everything's
doable with just one person
with one yes
okay actually I don't know how the
puzzle earlier would have been possible
but I okay I'm going to reset it so that
he goes into the far right one about
that one
though oh wait what was it he goes this
way this is kind of easy who says this
is
easy they think it's easy cuz they don't
actually get it are they fibbing
they're fing are you guys did we try
standing on this platform while he's
standing on that platform have we tried
that have someone standing at oh I don't
think we did should we try that does it
have to do with the
story the story you want to try yeah
I'll stand on it at the same time okay
let me just uh move
him I guess it okay I'll try standing on
it and nothing happens I'll move him it
one will be our eyes looking at the
lights I will what am I supposed to do
send
him uh no just look if the light
anything happened to the lights nothing
has happened now that nothing's
happened wait is no one sending
him do you want me to send him
yeah send let's try send yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah wait what the
no wait for what what do we wait oh wait
wait wait wait he miss it we didn't miss
it wait
wait wait what happened what was that on
he went onto the thingy they did it not
light up
hold up it did it just doesn't no it
didn't why didn't this one light up hold
on anyone light up when we standing on
this wait what wait what happened wait
hold
on why do he go this way wait wait wait
he supposed to go this way why was this
one oh hold on left wait let's try let's
try that
again wait what why is it Chang oh no I
did
that TR again now this works
cuz now we left this is the
S down wait something light up I think
this are you talking about this yeah
dude yeah
dude okay we
have
three still just three wait wait wait
what is it do wait wait
wait what happens if I stand on this
okay wait don't do
anything stand there now stand on the
middle one but m is already standing on
the middle one yeah I'm on the middle
outside what one
outside like I my chat is gaslighting
me I saw people in my chat that didn't
realize like never mind H I think they
thought we were just trying to get the
three of them to light up but didn't
realize we that was like the first thing
we
did wait what if
you CE stand on the one and the one at
the colum B no the one at the colum B
just opens up that was the door I think
yeah I'm going to stand on it anyways
let's see you didn't mean this one
nothing
happens this is just for this door I was
show the previous puzzle I don't know
why that would have anything to do with
this one still have to go me to
go you can go when you figure out this
puzzle he's definitely supposed to go
well I don't is he supposed to go he
must go
here but no this is just if you don't
want
that where is it is it even that I don't
[Music]
know Callie's do this hard what the heck
man
wait I thought people say other members
already cleared
it no no that would be too
complicated guys unless it's not guys
guys there's arrows in the Maze too we
have to make him go all the way around
here shut
up stop we didn't I even went oh it's a
maze but then I was like looks cool oh
can you reset can someone reset the
thing the guy please wait where do you
see it didn't even give us any hint that
it would include the previous puzzle
though doesn't walking through a door
usually signify that you know that
puzzle's
over what the he it's from out here we
have to all the way back okay okay we
got this guys we got
this okay um so we make him
go
here send him out this have to maybe
maybe but how does
he okay so we make him go here
instead right is is he is he lined up so
he would actually walk here no wait go
where go where here where could I
standing oh so he goes this way he goes
this way you want out there there's no
way but he still has to go through the
all the colors doesn't he okay so he
goes like this I can't think I need to
go to an I don't me
I can't think like this oh gosh and we
said it wouldn't take an hour it's okay
I thought it wouldn't it's okay we're
going s too difficult okay it was cuz
you you guys have fun yesterday isn't it
oh are are you going to go to The
Mastermind are you going to Google or
you scammer oh no I'm going to just go
to an island meeting I'll be right back
okay you want us to wait for you no no
feel free to consider thinking of what
the solution could be feel free oh okay
we P let's let's try going this way and
try if we can fix it make this man walk
through this hole so we can get that
damn box I'm tired of waiting for this
puzzle man here puzzle man walks I was
wondering what these little doors were
for and then he walks through and he
hits another
light but he can hit the light that's
fine this is no I want him to hit this
one are you kidding me oh that's what
you mean oh yeah and then somebody has
to and he goes here I'm going to go here
to see so once he's okay I'll activate
the green oh
God okay are you safe I am
safe okay so he goes over
there now he has to get past the yellow
Bridge we have to turn the the
red oh this is
complicated okay um yeah can you
go oh oh can you activate yes the blue
one for me
yeah and then I hit the blue again oh
the green
right uh I think the yellow
one the yellow one or so you can go
through go through I'm fine okay and now
go through the yellow one and then
activate the blue one there the blue
yellow one blue
yellow okay so now he will go here so
we're going to have to do that while
he's walking I
think oh my
God shall we just try let's just try
okay I think you should handle these
colors on that side and I'll I'll I'll
carry the handle the colors in the
beginning okay uh I think I remember
yes okay so he's going to come in here
he's going to walk over here and we're
going to use yellow first okay uh
where's yellow can you reach yellow
where is Yellow there oh I can reach
okay uh don't do it yet
okay or or actually can you do it once
just so I see what
happens oh yeah okay and then hit it
again and then he goes through ah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I think this is good isn't it yeah I'll
press I think this will work I will
press the button and I will walk with
him press the button let's do it
stand close to the collors he can pass
through
lasers he's very
strong I'm pressing he's walking but
he's first he's walking over the first
three
Golds o he's walking he's walking he's
walking okay now he's going to come to
the
Maze and then he's going to he's going
to go through the M oh my goodness look
at him go he's going to be where you are
oh my goodness and going go this
way yeah I think this is it oh my
goodness that must be it I don't think
we have to do anything let me see if it
lit up the
yep yep that's it here just has to light
up one
more
s it worked it worked it worked wait a
minute you can come to us SCA I'm
here already there give us they all box
it's it's lit up but no
yay what's in the bo it's for brain
bigger than their hats it's it's my
mixtape oh no it's for all of us we all
get one
right we all get one it's reflect o wait
how we use this is it movie
time no yet not yet now we have to go to
the
middle okay oh right right right that's
at the end one more
face what do we how do we use this can
you sing it for us if you want to you
don't have to uh do I remember how it
goes um
oh I don't remember
how oh she has Amnesia I have amnesia I
don't to remember it makes sense okay so
now we want him to stand on the thingy
right because we all have to get up
there yeah
just sending am I is it ready yeah uh is
it I think
so yeah it's
ready is it
as long as he comes this way yeah I
think he's
coming I cannot believe that's what that
was no wonder we couldn't I I would have
never I no I wouldn't have either I
would have assumed like why would it be
stuff from the previous
level but that door that or that opening
that Arc shape perect estimated I
underestimated how much credit they're
giving us I would I
I there's no way they would do something
like from before no cuz I'm always like
it can't it's not as complicated as I
think I'm like looking stupid cuz so
it's probably so easy but I'm making it
so complicated and it's making me look
so stupid no I mean to be fair the tower
sck it was a b complicated oh that was
in I see that was it it could be your
power
I think it is cut scene time
y I didn't download it yet I got to
download
it the portion of your
memory I
remember he REM um okay should
we wait for m so she's ready oh you all
want to play it at the same time yeah
yeah okay I'm downloading it sorry
that's okay
one second one second puz it wasn't even
that oh when you think about it it
wasn't even that hard if we had oh like
once you know what to do it's not hard
but yeah the puzz itself isn't hard but
using your being like I guess we're so
used to
playing video games this felt more like
a real puzzle compared to like a video
game puzzle you know yeah there were no
giant arrow pointing Us in the right
direction no ingame Maps so they tricked
eyes just just just an our AR thingy
perfectly sized for him I was wondering
what the mini doors
were yeah my registered to be
honest can I point something out though
of again no stains just saying the
kingdom that's fighting the stains and
trying to make us destroy all of these
dungeons tell like they're in the
walls they in the walls they wear the
golden Stepping Stones
yeah okay I'm ready if you guys are
ready I am I am ready
ready I got my
musical okay I'm ready are you guys
ready for a good
scene you want to countdown yes
please oh three you want
me you you come down you no you f wait
no I feel like G should do it course
yeah that's good uh a three a two a one
[Music]
go this
stinks I'm out of here
[Music]
I
remember yep every time King's force
field is just too strong
ahuh that's when I had an
idea I may not be able to break through
but I bet that Geyer's old Fork could do
it and then I'll be
free I or so I
got ahuh
h i St L Now or
Never let's see what this thing can
[Music]
do no I did
not finally
My Story begins
[Music]
here I why did I think you were like the
queen of Atlantis you were just a little
kid
that just stole the king's Trident he
wasn't using it anyway I thought you
were like royalty or
something I
I Comm no that's not true didn't you see
I was I was I was in charge of multiple
different events I had to sit through
bank and organized paperwork and and
Royal meetings he just didn't share you
a secretary no I'm I'm I'm just a I was
a baby I was a I I I didn't steal
anything I could have asked but I didn't
you borrowed just borrowed I borrowed it
stealing their their protection Weapon
made it so that everything broke
afterwards no no I wouldn't do I don't
think that's what happened they didn't
have anything to protect themselves and
you made it really easy for the enemy to
destroy weapon no they've got a force fa
didn't you see they're they're safe but
the hole patched up
afterwards then explain this say I have
a point
I
um you know I don't remember I wonder if
we're going to have to wait for the next
episode to uncover the rest of the
mystery oh she has a point good point we
have a point all three of us have very
good point and the pot Point true
yeah well that was fun I just nice to
visit my brain hurts it was nice to
visit home oh that was lovely a little
brain fry but oh well I'm mad at how
simple it ended up being well simple
complicated it's it's
complicated arrows and colors type of
it's a type of thing that when you see
it you see it but when you don't see it
you're very confused
exactly when you're in the thick of
it yeah then it's kind of confusing when
it all falls on your
shoulders where are we now oh we're back
at this place okay yeah we we want to
leave
we have to swi back out uh I think so
yeah I think so you want to go to the
tavern once we go to the tavern I'm
going to eat some mutton and then I'm
going
to using a horse just to get to
there time is money time is
okay wait give me give me be in the
world of RPG
[Music]
oh wait you guys can hear me
run I was
just back here get hooking back here
what do you
do I'm just reflecting
on just made reflect just like
the oh there's so many boats I don't
think we're the only ones in that
dungeon we weren't really the only ones
that thought of
boats no but that's why I have the coral
so you can breathe under the
water can I be the passenger princess
again what's the name of the one who
drives the driver the captain Oh that's
the hor I'm the captain please call me
Captain oopsie I've I to for what I just
did I laughed at you and then I went and
did the same thing you think these are
other people's boats oh wait wait
actually I'm going to take this boat so
that probably someone else's so that
they have to swim yeah
perfect are these boats again are we the
first ones there's no way we were the
first ones through that there must have
others people say others got through
it but did they do the extra stuff or
did they just keep going no clue I don't
know my gosh wait you're such a fast
swimmer first one's with the
treasure
ah are we y okay I feel much better
about myself because we got we we could
have finished really early but we
decided to go the extra mile exactly we
got any our recollection what are we
supposed to do with it go to the tavern
and we blast our Tunes until we get
kicked out is that what you do yeah you
can play it in or we can play it here
too or we could go back back let's go
back let's go back let's go to the
tavern
Tavern was you guys know after you work
out and then your your muscles feel like
tingly and
weak M that's how my brain feels right
now kind of
hurts hey I feel it
too Scarlet w
doesn't that mean that like my brain is
going to get stronger now my name is
Junior it
should think further into the future I'm
Junior oh my lady you are being ambushed
oh my lady they really love you here I'm
getting my butt kicked my
queen okay follow the sounds of the
horses this way we're going to go play
our Victory music
wait does the
previous did the previous dungeon have a
song
reward I so oh I did not get it if but I
didn't pick it up I remember seeing it I
don't remember wait where you guys
here I didn't even see it if there was
one I think I
saw the tavern is it's from gambling
it was the it's theaa I got it on my
first
try that
hat all right let's play this bad
boy want to listen to some
tunes it might be if you haven't done
the dungeon it might be a spoiler oh oh
spoiler
Al I think you can repeat
dungeons no it's okay I I have a party
later oh who also have not cleared it
but thank you fair Scarlet wand yes
Scarlet wand together strong this
is okay I'm going to mute my own bgm
wait I can't hear it oh because I turned
the didn't we turn music off wait oh I
hear
it oh my gosh it's not AIT style it's
just
it let's go
they got good sub subwoofers
here yeah oh my God what is that
beautiful voice is this what clubbing
feels like where the
[Music]
STW
wow W St
[Music]
oh that's so
pretty that's enough Val you how much
can I sell this
for a million dollars do you think but
can we s
yeah oh never mind I was wrong I didn't
see the I didn't see uh Mor one I just
saw these the non-fiction you can buy
them but you cannot sell them oh
lame shop we sell anything to be
honest don't know why we can shopkeeper
FAA although
she to come back she's just selling
lottery
[Music]
tickets why take all's money she's not
looking you have 895
coins I have the urge to gamble would
you would you would you like
300 I can give you 64 Mangrove blocks no
what I don't want mang block steel I
have a pot what do you want how do
I how many coins do you guys have I
have9 what how are you guys all so low
because we
532 F in our life we have never gambled
in our lives I gamble I want a cute hat
like this like you guys have oh buy one
one I just buy them I just buy no no
it's a g you you it's not guaranteed but
you can do I do the surprise box God we
might have another oh
no this seems like a mistake did you buy
one yeah that's a lot of money what you
get what you get what you get choose oh
God oh God oh God oh God I got
construction supplies box oh oh okay I'm
yay y I don't show we good job good job
our money into more money I have the
urge how do you do that should we try
have you done it before try turning off
no I haven't you haven't no I haven't it
better not be the lottery tickets no no
no no no no no no no no do you remember
the library I think do you remember what
it was was it here it is taking to the
library oh this this is it is this one
way yes I shall follow you do you wish
to Triple your
earnings I wish to Triple mine no
quadruple mine join our partyup you can
join our party call
Nissa
yeah yeah
excellent I have to leave in like
soon uh yes I'm in quickly double your
money and quick quick quick quick okay
wa is where did she go
oh oh yeah in the she is okay okay I'm
coming we're coming come to the giant
Yellow
SP we're
coming I was so ready to to gamble all
my money away yeah let's do it you don't
know that you could be making all of
your money back and then some that would
be nice I want to get a cool hat too you
get a cool hat I don't remember where it
is I don't remember what the pit is what
is the pit the Pit's not this right is
this the PS the other one yellow one
it's it's yellow yeah the yellow
one the Ember coin people one Fair
straight oh no I know who you are now F
do you know where the pit
is I can't believe M that's okay or
Junior is is a
[Music]
girl I don't remember I don't remember I
don't remember what you named me but my
name today is Darwin Roosevelt DiCaprio
Jr decaprio Darwin Roosevelt DiCaprio Jr
pun was that it pun
pun oh here it is Bow Bow Fair maidens
bow bow
okay we have arrived okay we are here
but M isn't yeah she's she's lost yumy
oh it appears that my party has found it
but I have been distracted by your
beauty
[Music]
oh beautiful R many fingers R many
popsicle Fingers um so let's see I must
now go bow bow should we wait for a
moment good bow bow good bow bow yeah
maybe bow I'm so sorry I cannot listen
to everyone at once where are you guys
we are calling for thou Fair Maiden
where are you what do you to I am around
the
Coliseum huh okay drive right around the
Coliseum try finding the white yellow
building the yellow big yellow yellow
building around the Coliseum oh God how
close to the Coliseum has started the
first oh that's okay you guys you guys
do that and I'll I'll go get
yell building what what's going on I'm
done a full circle uh right
click stand still come to you choose
your
color where what do you
see I see trees of green enter your
amount in that bar and take the paper on
the right okay okay oh I was not going
to find
this okay
yeah yeah okay I I bet on
two what color that's okay this is the
pit uh blue and
red ooh wait
both yeah I don't know you could hide to
hide my chances you can just go for the
next one we'll we'll let them we'll let
them feel the odds out and see what they
are Canon's
firing okay oh
wow okay
oh oh it might be over for me if this is
red I'm going to lose my
mind what color did you
do I did red and blue I picked
green green always
win it's uh it's in the
cards he seems like he in the on except
if it's red I going to lose my
mind wait are you betting on which one
stays yeah Green Oh my God oh my gosh
how much did you bet
Nissa just 100 time 10 wait how do I get
it how do I get it okay M you can talk
to him you got it automatically you can
talk to him and then we make a b and you
talk to him again the color you want to
I don't decide how many coins to bet the
can will start firing
four colored sequences with shot after
six shots only one squ will remain
players win winning players will receive
a payout based on the multi multiplier
listed for the color they bet on
okay
bet I'm going to
bet okay I bet okay so red is times 10
yellow okay I'm going to bet green I did
green yellow green 20 on
GRE 100 on
all if how do I do this how do I do it I
don't know how Minecraft works okay so
you right click it and then do you what
do you see do you see the paper and the
little window I see I see paper yes
there's there's a little line and you
have to type in 100 or whatever you have
to be really fast and you just press on
the that's how you do it you'll have to
join next round oh
okay it's okay I'll help you it'll be
fine it's this one was the B out and you
take the paper take the right grab from
the right oh I
see
green this is let's go any
color which color which color not spare
believe m- green will win I believe in
it
mhm uh-oh now watch this I'm watching
watching very
closely oh I would have won wo 500 coins
I'm out of money oh f ma narissa
ravencraft could you lend us some money
maybe wait I want we are one I have to
become I have to become rich join the
game choose color I'm sorry away but now
this time this time I'm going to do
green I'm going to try blue this time
I'm going to do okay I think I
did
okay or should I do two should I do two
different
ones I N Go all I don't know try it I
need money I'm so bored
how how did you all become
poor you're looking at it this is
probably I probably put this the wrong
way I a little bit all my money that's
okay all right I voted on Blue what did
everyone else lost 50 coins that's okay
I did not do that the right way that's
all good that's all good build character
if you picked up the papers and you did
it right no I didn't
know oh no
oh
boy oh that's not
good I really I really I really I really
I really I
really what did you bet on what did
everyone bet on green green no what' I
do I did green and
blue okay green ch
come on
green if I lose this I'm doing one on
each color oh Green in the bag let's
go I get I make some stuff back it's not
it's not totally over okay are you
kidding
me no freaking
way I think if we give back our Quest we
get some money I lost 50 but it's okay
I'm going to go and get some cuz I'm
broke on go get some money wait how much
did I have before this didn't I have I
had like 500 something I think I lost l
yeah what color did I just vote on I
don't
know fun now now now try Mr Mr Big
firing Cannon surely I can't this time
one of each one on each color oh yeah
let's go I can't lose
now yeah you have to
win
surely is going to shoot me which one
did I
do which one did you do my last my last
one I don't know that's what I'm saying
I don't remember what color I I think
yell Oren I think if you press T you
should see what you did
no it just tell say how many coins yeah
oh never
mind okay
okay wait if it's red and you bet one on
red what you get if it's 10 times and
you get 10
oh that's
bad that
[Music]
the did you bet red M I bet
yellow I got 10
coins 1 time 10 oh my God I can eat
tonight I'm so so happy that's it that's
it for me that's it I know what I'm
doing tomorrow but that's it for today
gambling I have
1,495 coins let's go don't tell F she'll
send you a lottery ticket yeah she'll be
like o this girl sure will fall my
little I he coins in your pocket narissa
I I wish to sell you something it might
oh I buy a lot of from oh
I'm going to go turn in my
quest okay I follow where do you go for
that Scarlet wand I can get there
without a
map I
promise it's this
way you get to the the the Green Spoon
and then you go
all this
way and then you end up rubius hope this
is right you're a pro I spent enough
time finally I
understand wait when are you doing
you're doing this later right the yes uh
with Ena and Callie the Reaper ahuh
yeah San
cup what all righty well I don't have
any money he didn't give me any money
for
that oh no where's my
money you don't have to give me anything
you offering I don't know how to give
money
anyway that's okay give me any money
it's okay hello
okay are you sure I could throw you a
hundred like a you know some CH charity
money it's the least I could do if you
really desire to give me some charity
coin I will not charity
coin I will not gamble it away I will
not of course of
course I will I don't know how to trade
it's okay it's okay don't worry about it
I'll go beat watch request you have to
accept oh oh okay fairly well Maiden
thank you fairy well in the dungeon of
Atlantis good luck and think outside the
box don't let your brain hurt you can do
it okay goodbye goodbye I'm going to
fight to death in the
arena how do I get into the
arena oh okay then go then go for
oh that's a lot of people I don't think
I want to do it that that many
people too many
people ah run hello hello
hello I like your hat I really love your
hat only I hope I can get a hat like
that how much money do you have I have
two MO two coins
okay I have 11 so we're not that far off
okay listen if I get 10 coins I'll buy
you hat H about that no no this is
attached to my head if I take it off
then I'm going to die and two other
people will die now cuz we're all
connected I see it uh then it's okay you
can keep your hat I'll one day I'll find
the same heart one day you can buy
it
yeah we got your record good oh you
found it
we got it how did your brain quite the
it was quite difficult yeah we took us a
while it took us a while
too because the the the the the gate
signifies the end of a puzzle so you
wouldn't backtrack right but then it
backtracked anyway like why why what why
we had to backtrack we had to there was
no choice there was an obvious treasure
hidden good job you know what so I'm I'm
glad you made it out of that uh the
glass Hall of Atlantis the force field
the the thing the force bubble field
yeah I'm glad I'm glad you're free in
the world now to do whatever you please
yay but I shall not support the scam of
the Red Hats so that's another story
what' you call me I'm the scam of the
Red Hats
uhhuh
well
I
okay okay
people uh they might be in the arena I
wanted to go there too part of them
might be in the arena fight to the death
good
luck what are you up
to
I don't
know I was going to side quest or
something or maybe maybe
uh maybe wind down for the day yeah good
luck then with your quest thank you Raa
good luck getting your red
hat yeah I hope one day I'll get the
same big hat I hope you will I know it
thank you thank you for believing see
you around how do you say goodbye in in
[Music]
Italian how you say how you say byby in
American uh that's a good question in
English
how you say that you
[Music]
say yes see you later
alligator see you later alligator byebye
[Music]
T I'm happy you guys told me to say
something cuz I was going to say like um
I love Twinkies or something like that
that was
[Music]
fun that was fun I have
um I think I finished a side quest or I
started doing a side quest just to get
familiar with the rest of the town but I
do think I'm going to end I'm going to
end now cuz I am I am rather tired um I
am rather tired if you can hear it in my
voice but um thank you guys so much got
to make potato salad I have almost all
of the ingredients for potato salad
because I went and I found I made sure
to find the the garden we have to get
eggs and beetroot who puts beetroot in
potato salad though I don't know in
carrot why I don't know um but yeah guys
thank you guys so much um I hope you had
a nice time hanging out uh and uh I I
don't know I would assume I am
participating in
the in the the rest of the days but I
also don't know
uh I will I I'll let you know if I'm not
but
uh yes thank you so much thank you so
much as always I hope you had fun thank
you
[Music]
for thank
you have a lovely rest of your day or
your evening and I will see you for some
more Minecraft sometime this week
absolutely tomorrow another dungeon will
unlock of some type and more secret RW
revealed more secrets will be revealed
thank you guys so much I will see you
around have a lovely day have a lovely
day okay
goodbye goodbye bye
[Music]
bye goodbye