[Music]
Did you sneak in and use my tail
? Today, Haru's
Happy Pumpkinty is
leaking behind my back. I still don't have enough legs.
Dance song,
happy or not, but I can't do it.
Please forgive me. We're all selfish. That's not it. You
can run away. It's okay to be rewarded. There's
no way home. Until the morning comes, the fun party
is over.
[Music]
No, it's almost
time to wake up.
Until the night comes again, I'll keep this day in my heart. I'll be happy. I'll
forget about Halloween
until tomorrow. I'll head towards the night that will become. Even before I go to sleep.
[Music]
Just not
Happy Halloween Our Nori no Pa
Happy
Halloween Ishi
Happy Halloween Until Morning
[Music]
Rise