[Music]
foreign
Among Us
Among Us Among Us Among Us Among Us on
screen Among Us Among Us
hello
it's just me right now because we're all
here to talk to you individually and
convince you to purchase
only if you want to but they are pretty
good right
I can I can talk to you here until
um 15 minutes after the hour at which
point I will meet up with the rest of
the group
yeah do you see do you see do you see
everything look I even have my very own
fauna official fauna among his merch did
you ever think the day would come when I
have look there it is on the screen
twice
official
serious fauna Among Us merge it is cute
too look
isn't that cute look at that cutie the
cute green one right there
no one on the left is okay too
well I am here to tell you about the
Among Us ex all I've emerged because
orders are about to end so for the cover
main emerge
um
orders are available till November 28th
at 11 59 PM jst so I believe that is uh
like a little like remember 12. a little
more than 12 hours from now or something
uh not too many hours left
so get it today if you want it
um there's a bunch of stuff there's
keychains and stickers there's acrylic
stands there's plushies
there's
I think there's like a scrunchie
is that the yeah the scrunchies with the
the Among Us ex-hole life of the
um
inner sloth side
those ones you can look at their website
for more details and there's also the
hollow live Cosmic Cube which you can
buy in the game which I have actually
they gave us codes but I didn't realize
they gave us code so I just bought it
myself and then I realized that they
gave us codes but I had already
purchased it I had already
spent my money
okay that's okay because it's really
cute
cute in-game stuff and I believe it's
kind of like a battle pass so you have
to play to unlock the thing so hopefully
I will unlock some today can I show you
my
my among among
what do you call them they're called
crewmates but what's the singular of
Among Us because we all know they're not
really cold
crewmates they're called
among uses
among I I know don't you want to call it
a mangai but I said be plural really
a singular Among Us
hold on let me
oops that's the Discord icons look you
can see the people I'm playing with the
lovely people I'm a mom
let me turn this off for a second hold
on let me organize my screen
this I'll leave
um I think the code is like covered
automatically now so don't really have
to worry about that
I think I can put this in the corner
and it's not too distracting
look it's me
actually at me the the resemblance is
uncanny right now
look at this
we're twins
no no no no no I'm not suss I will be
closing the chat when I play unless I'm
the Imposter I haven't thought about my
strategy though
I actually have one idea
oh I should have I meant to collude with
someone
ahead of time but I forgot
to collude
um so I don't know if my strategy is
gonna work I don't know well I might
I don't know
I might try it
damn someone is that legal and Among Us
is that cheating
um
here's the The Cosmic Cube you can get
many cute faces and cute outfits oh and
they also told us that perhaps if enough
people downloaded and are interested in
it then
um
there might be additional ones in the
future with more talents which would be
really cool because I'm not in the
Cosmic Cube not yet but who knows maybe
one day
a fun Among Us fauna in Among Us
this is like the only time when you're
I'm allowed to make all of these memes
normally I feel guilt every time I'm
making Among Us reference but today
ain't no no
we're playing among us so we can make as
many Among Us references as we want
fun not in all mangas
sauce
they put fauna in my Among Us
real
2022 real
you can buy it
don't forget
you can buy look right there you can buy
it
foreign
I feel like the last time I played this
a year ago wasn't it it was probably
more than a year ago because it was like
pretty shortly after debut
that so that makes me kind of sad
but nostalgic
yeah the the en collab
the Irish Council Slayer yes I didn't
get to be the Imposter at all before I
wonder if I will have my time to shine
this time
we're just doing them standard Among Us
not proximity chat so you gotta get all
your mind games ready
um what's my strategy I think of my
strategy if I become imposter it's okay
about you guys you guys want
paddle on me writing my strategy I think
I'm gonna use the old classic of uh like
follow people around but then like turn
off the lights and like pick someone off
when the lights are off and then be like
whoa what happened
that's so crazy how did they die we were
all we were all in a group together what
how could this happen
that's so crazy
but we'll see that might be risky
I really loved the strategy where you
all stack
together and then you'd like kill
someone in the stack I love when that
happens and then you like don't know who
did it because there were eight of you
standing on top of each other oh should
I try to get everyone to stack what if
I'm not the Imposter I don't know anyway
I think I'm supposed to go
rejoin everyone hold on hold on
hello
sorry
yet I just said hello and I was just
preparing for the social anxiety of
unmuting and saying hello
hello
okay mine's on
um hello
hello
and sick
um
hello everyone hello it's on your mouth
is second generation how's my voice
thank you
[Applause]
I really love that it's so fancy
okay
what's up the red I'm tired um
the red I'm gonna Channel my sleepiness
to being the best rat that I can hello
oh my god
oh no you silly you totally silly so
sassy
okay
there's Bale's in the room yet I don't
see her in the room no I'm not isn't it
yeah
okay
we are hiding why are you hiding I'm shy
do you want to hide with me yeah exactly
you're trying to make it compared to
everyone else exactly oh and beauty
beauty is is you're just beautiful fauna
you don't yeah that's how I feel about
these Among Us yeah
you were born
I'll join you've convinced me
you've been returning to nature
clothes we don't have any clothes yet
oh my God oh my God okay next
to uh hello it's me Oro cronie from
Hollow live English Council ended I'm
going to kill everyone
yeah
sound effects the sound effect is
sending me
they say crony's low but I have her on
Max I can't do anything else
just talk louder or something
enunciate speak from the stomach chroni
[Music]
how am I think you're too low
yeah
well I think that needed a bottoms but
then nothing happened
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh say again crony is is this loud
enough now yeah I think you sound better
okay yeah
hey hey I guess it should be fine
me too
he already did let's have a fun
promoting theme everybody
audience with her I'm feeling fired up
already amazing
thank you for bringing the energy that
we need yeah we need that caffeine help
by your energy
[Music]
feeling in your eyeballs who's panties
next
time
[Music]
[Laughter]
we did not only
it's amazing wow amazing intro
[Applause]
so early
hello oh hi I'm Nash from Whole Life
English I have a stuffy nose to go men
you didn't register to me that you were
saying oh hi I thought you were saying
Ohio but then you just cut it halfway
because you could be bothered today
she's just saving letters I am saving
time here come on
I mean it would take too long the room
is gonna disband against himself
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you mean
oh I have to get rid of chats don't I oh
man okay I'm
I can still talk to you but I cannot see
you and I feel all alone
my friends are gone my chat is gone
um
okay
streaming without Chad I missed you guys
I just have to imagine what you're
typing oh no I just have to imagine what
your time being already I think they're
gonna vote me out because I don't know
what I'm doing how do you play this game
again
go to the big shining arrows
Santa I don't think she's the Imposter
oh
um oh oh everyone is here what everyone
am I thinking I actually we do feel
naked
um
wait isn't there a map
oh I have tasks in here oh
incredible
look at me doing my wait how do you do
this one again
oh
look at me doing my tasks
um
I'm just gonna go and try not to die
oh it's crony she did say she wanted
again oh no
I should have known
she did say she wanted to kill everyone
where'd she go
not crony girl
did she vent
there's that crony let's observe her
Swatch and see
what wait I can look at Chad again
actually oh
hello guys
you have returned
oh I still need to do my tasks though
it was truly a blessing in disguise is
anyone else dead I remember last time oh
Ollie is dead oh no
body to move me just walk by
last time I also oh hey are you gonna
report it oh she reported it
hi I missed you okay I'm muted but I
missed you guys but I'm listening to
their meeting
oh two buddies yeah there's yeah Ollie
and milona died where was everyone I
[Music]
I just arrived on the shield
made several times wait Bales you're
muted in case you're trying to speak
your music
I'm sorry
sorry um
[Music]
the body I need to look at the map okay
so I was in storage
I wasn't
sure
the red that leads to electrical and
then yeah yeah yeah
and I
am going that direction
the body
oh
you were there
so I didn't really notice anything like
I was checking samples
three seconds before that I when I found
the body why did you not report the body
if you were there
I'm so tired
that doesn't make sense there was
something there I didn't even go to the
road the whole time
[Music]
yeah we were on the right side yeah
oh Adam
it shows
oh
it shows how many imposters remain
usually people play with that off right
although maybe only the pro Among Us
players
after that
just doing my tasks
oh oh that was fast
enough
report where were you guys
[Music]
killed her
um
you know
Anya and Zetta whoa
there's still one more imposter I'm kind
of suggestions
I don't know if that's just movement
okay well you know okay fine
yes I am the Imposter but guess what
who's the other one you know you know
who's the other one I'm gonna kill him
I'm gonna give this the Innocence the
win so
um
it's actually Luna what
is open postures no I'm not
gonna kill I'm so sorry
really
nice try
I don't buy it I'm not buying what
you're selling huh oh right you can just
count
foreign
it's harder than you might think
and this one huh
okay
are my tests don't know
the lower engines
oh
are these at new tasks oh no
[Applause]
what
do you smiles
what happened again the oxygen the
oxygen calculated so embarrassing yeah
that's kind of so bad
guys I just want to say if someone is uh
someone is being choosing as imposer and
the Imposter said that the next imposter
is someone don't believe it
which means that they're going to be
innocent the only two people remain they
were Kiara
between the two
we both did so much work for us to win
that all right right yeah
he had no hesitation to kill anything
yeah yeah I love how you made me into an
existence
[Laughter]
thank you Ollie like when I was about to
walk over and Anya was there and I was
like crony you just got in so much
trouble
it worked out though I'm also sorry to
everyone in advance but hey that's the
game
man I was like when when you guys were
in the discussion and Courtney was like
no it was like people were there and
then everyone else seemed not convinced
and I'm like she killed man from here
guys
[Laughter]
sufficient eyes that was so funny yeah
I couldn't see it because I was doing
like tasks
and then like I was like okay
were the ones in the room yeah
and like I was like I was hoping I was
hoping that Zeta would say something so
that I didn't ask me I didn't see it but
I was really doing task yeah it was very
lucky that ran the funny thing is that I
was like I was about to go out from that
room so if only you had waited for like
a few more seconds I probably wouldn't
have thought that yeah
crony learned her lesson for next round
right yeah twice
[Music]
oh my God
okay I've hid you guys again
I'm scared this time
why I'm scared what's happening what if
it's movie and Ollie
okay there's many people in here
oh shoot this one
oh
oh second try oh the lights are off it's
me I'm the Imposter I said I was gonna
do this
I'm kind of scared oh we're at the
lights
they're in here right why is no one
fixing them
oh
oh no wait
where's that oh
no Ronnie
definitely not me imposter twice in a
row
it's very dangerous
in a row right yeah yeah and I was
trying my best trying to turn it on but
people kept turning it off
but if you wouldn't have just admitted
immediately that it was you then I
wouldn't have known because there was so
much going on
you don't you shouldn't run away
I was I was in there I was in there
because electrical was out and everyone
else was right yeah yeah yeah yeah how
could we know it was her we don't know
if it was her
the animation of chronic killing it okay
yeah I saw it I don't know because like
I saw it the way I saw a movie but like
I don't know
no no no it's not Mommy I saw granny in
front of my eyes killing it really
unfortunate oh I saw chaos
but Luna said crony just incriminated
herself right away I mean you could cry
oh
yeah
you it's you exactly who knows
well I think it was great
oh is that oxygen
yeah
um
this one
oh it's normal okay it's good
I'm gonna do this
I sure hope I don't die
oh I have a task in here too
I sure hope I don't die when I'm doing
my tasks I sure hope a suss The Imposter
doesn't come over and kill me
I sure hope I don't see any dead bodies
all alone in the mid Bay
um
let me do my scan I think you're
supposed to let people view you when you
do this
be plus
why not a plus
um
unless we have animations turned off
oh shoot how do I get in there oh it's
oxygen
okay I saw Kiara
but I don't want to chase her because
then that seems suspicious too
this is my last task oh my
I don't trust this I don't trust this
why is she changing
[Applause]
I don't think she's the Imposter because
that would be crazy
but also why was she chasing me because
it's movie
can I open this
I'm scared
there's a baby
okay okay there's a lot of people around
oh
my she's dead
she was chasing me and then she went off
to the right side of the map okay good
night you're running around yeah
I thought that she was the Imposter
because she was chasing me but
she sorry it sounds so suspicious right
now I know I do but
me and chasing me around the table but I
almost called a meeting because I was
like that's kind of susp and I was like
oh it's mume so it's just probably just
being normal yeah it's probably
yeah
why did Ollie called a meeting just to
check
actually I want to do a little promotion
did you guys know that the holiday
production
collaborations
yeah sure today
um why did you go to the electrical for
like one second and then you went out
immediately
oh I was just checking to see what's
inside
why won't you check who's inside why
can't I check who's inside I can be like
oh someone's there why won't I don't
know man that was dinosaurs yeah yeah if
you don't have any tasks like and inside
the electrical then why would you go
inside because I didn't want to see
what's inside and see if I could stick
to anyone
I mean Ollie and me we're like going out
of the room why why didn't you like go
with us instead
sorry where is this intense
and like I was only we're like going out
but like you you like you you were like
going inside for like one second and
then you came out immediately
yeah because I don't want to get like
fine someone then why didn't you go with
us
well because I don't want to get killed
there
last time last time we were all in
electrical we got somebody got killed
[Music]
people for that
well
are we hanging out wait I don't I don't
know if I want to stick one
um
I guess as long as there's two of us
here oh I didn't do this task
oh they're leaving my bud
this is my last one though I think
oh wait admin
I can only do tasks do you get oh wait
no this is probably the same task
probably
hmm
[Music]
also I sounded
incredibly suspicious in the last
meeting but I don't know how to not
sound suspicious
um
where'd everybody go I'm a little scared
finger on the report button
oh
how how do I get to that oh there's
people
is that uh
uh zero
nine six one five
I'm frightened she didn't kill me though
I mean not the dad
really means anything
oh
what does it mean what does it mean the
door shut
oh it's people it's everyone
that thought
in the engine
foreign
just teleport to storage
it's not Anya or orzetta wait is it Zeta
wait a minute it's not awesome
or was the Kiara in there
I feel like I should call an emergency
meeting
um
um oh I don't know how to play this game
though
foreign
what up hello I was watching the admin
thing when we were all in the admin room
and then I saw someone teleporting from
storage to the to the main lobby
in the vent but I don't know
it wasn't the three of us who were in
the admin room and it wasn't oh yeah it
wasn't me phone and Kiana you know what
what's interesting is that Zeta came
after that
yeah I came from yeah but I wasn't I was
like
walking I was walking I don't know I
couldn't see anyone teleporting though
but that uh Zeta was like yeah I said I
came to admin I came in because I saw
you guys think
I was just security we were doing stuff
interesting so that's interesting I'm
I'm suspicious interesting
took to arrive at their destination
but um I'm just gonna say I finished my
tasks yeah
the wiring okay so so
yeah let's let's pick up for those who
finished I do kind of think it's bedtime
who haven't finished the task
s
sure sure okay I'm gonna I'm gonna go
with Moana Senpai then uh I'll go with
you guys too if I can
no I hope you like space accidents
[Laughter]
let's see what happens
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah cause that was so sad I didn't
teleport by the way
it feels lag I don't know
I can't have been the pain
can I just mentioned
they were trying to sing a Taylor Swift
song
[Laughter]
I thought you were just ignoring me on
purpose I have no idea how that song
goes I didn't even know that was a song
until later on oh my God
I'm standing there and he wrote jump
is it
do you want to try a different map or
stay in the same map girls
[Music]
might be fun okay
there you go
thank you
thank you I don't see nothing one second
one second we're just map everyone will
be able to use the excuse that they
don't know the map well so they didn't
know where to go oh I'm in exactly hello
I never know where to go
um
[Music]
okay bye everyone
Ollie she's so funny
oh shoot it's this one wait don't you
have to do this
or was that a thing in the old one
is that a lie
I used to play Among Us and I thought
you're supposed to go touch that but
maybe I just look suspicious now
oh I don't want to feel like I'm chasing
Ollie she might get scared
foreign
why am I so suspicious in this game
I'm just doing my tasks
I'm just going to the tree
wait no not the tree I'm just going down
here
being the most suspicious as possible
huh
not crony again well she's not the
Imposter office
why didn't you report
Ed
right away yeah that was awesome
nearby I think
no I was from the office and then it was
on the left room right left room of the
office I think so I was in the office
and then I go after you I know you're in
the right room Anya yeah
it was like it was dark so like I didn't
see it
like I saw that I was right behind you
you seemed a bit sus
I was right behind her oh she was like
acting a bit sus in that hallway right
before she entered the right office so
in front of me it's Anya yeah but I was
behind you
so I was yeah
was actually on the left left-ish side
of the of the office I saw her and I was
in the office I was in the office and
then I saw something going away
yeah I was inside the office
I saw you I didn't go towards the office
I passed by you and said I think yeah I
think mommy is near Communications or
something yeah I passed by mume though I
passed by mume as well
I don't know man I don't know
Senpai Muna Senpai was like around there
but I don't know
I didn't see it first yeah they and Anya
are kind of teaming up against Muna
oh my God are we folding well I don't I
don't know I don't know if there's
enough information for anything
um
[Laughter]
said nothing in this meeting hmm But I
am suspicious of Faye and Anya because I
cast suspicion on them and then they
voted for me
yeah and Muna but honestly I'm
suspicious of everyone
um
wait I don't we're there right there
they're both right there together
what the heck I don't want to be with
both of them
Cali is here too
that's good
oh no the lights are off we're about to
get picked off one by one oh no
the card
the lights
oh they're back somebody got it it
wasn't me
oh yeah sorry
that was so cute beautiful song oh no I
can't look at the map wait can you hold
like the map button I know you guys
can't answer me because I don't have my
chat up right now
you can like hold the space bar or
something to bring up the map
Maybe
a tab
tab
I'm scared who was that who was below me
oh
I feel like I've been alone the whole
round that's probably not good for my
suspicion levels but whenever I play
this game as the crewmate I'm just like
I know I've done nothing wrong
hello everyone
are we dancing
oh
they watching I don't trust her
I feel like Santa wants me to follow her
or does she think I'm chasing her I
don't actually know which one it is
which one it would be
am I chasing people right now
what does this mean what is Among Us
communication mean hi Ollie
I need to go to the specimen room
hi Ollie I won't kill you I don't think
it's you
I'm just going to the specimen room
um
the comms have been sabotaged
well hello Anya and Ollie hello
wait did I finish my oh I know the comms
are sabotage that's what happened
I need to go up here
are we going together
we're playing Follow the Leader right
now
uh wait this
this would be really hard as the
Imposter if I don't know where the tasks
are
oh and this
this whole in the stall
I have one more task
but it's all the way on the other corner
of the map
we might just get another task win
or are they all done they're probably
all done oh
we go to the other one go to the other
one oh gosh
wait is
oh no oh that's a lot of dead body
where where's the body
where I wait where am I I'm here uh
security electrical
cutie oh
yeah I didn't go there
oh
fauna and Ollie yeah
yeah we were from the specimen oh wait
and we met up with Zetta yeah yep on the
way to the Bay was suspicious of Muna
and I didn't see her the whole round no
I was with Mommy before but I go with
Mommy before yeah I didn't see but I
know not at all I was in the boiler room
still doing my task
but hmm
yeah I didn't see mermaid too but wait I
don't know you guys
um
I was in the in the with suana and only
before fauna only and Zeta we made right
and we're just like standing there yeah
we actually we did dance together in the
emergency room yeah
and then final went to the specimen room
and then we met up with Anya and then we
went to the laboratory I was mostly on
the right side of the map the whole time
yeah me too so I can't be on the left
side of the map
um where are you I thought I saw you oh
yeah wait you said right side right who
yeah
left side
but we don't have any imposters voted
out yet right that's kind of bad yeah
yeah nothing kind of bad I mean they're
also really close to finishing tasks I
don't know man I'm gonna go with Luna
Senpai because yeah
you know and barely sussing her
and and I mean if you die you can do
your task faster so it's a win-win if
you're not Impressions I'm already done
with my test so I'll just follow people
around
like one more one more I have like one
more
[Music]
okay
oh no I
I'm worried
I have to go
over here
I think it's okay to go alone
I'll just go really fast
so fast
oh I see this is how you do it oh this
is the one I was interrupted before oh
oh was I the last one
tell me you scared
wait who is it
it was moomy she was chasing me at the
end
anyway
did you like that friendly I'm not
really good at being imposter guys no
I'm not either and it's pretty cold here
it's really cold I was thinking wait or
can we not kill again do I have to
report before we can kill again oh
yeah
would you like to explain friendly
yeah it's a new moment haven't you I'm
here to explain why did you miss it you
should have prepared
hi gaslighting is the victim's fault
okay
yeah
who intense I'm missing one person
who is it
uh get in here
that's okay
all right well I think we can at least
squeeze in one more round yeah maybe we
can do one more and then we can play
okay let's yeah
the next one okay I'm on crewmate again
no impostero mogas today oh it's this
thingy this oh what the heck
did I do it
I didn't do it
turn it
oh I did it
oh wait but we should have watched to
see who didn't do it
oh cause this time is the one
I think
um I'm just running away again
oh door closed door closed
um
how do you open it
oh
everyone is here
oh I won't mess with this
wait but they're not fixed what oh oh
they're fixed
all my tasks are over here
Treasures go
I'm just going
it's the worst that could happen
oh gotta install my auto Clicker
mummy
what you doing
what you doing Mommy
it's not crony guys no it's not cronies
[Music]
why did you not wear it then no I was on
the security cameras
[Laughter]
um
well I saw her on the security cameras
it was mermaid standing over crony's
dead body and also Muna running away
[\h__\h] crony earlier to creep her out
but you were right there when she died
why didn't you report her right then and
there right yeah
but that was her natural state
is
the poster you will have reported me I
didn't see her body
was out no it didn't
do it guys
so I don't know I have no idea
um
because she was running she was like
there and then she went the opposite
direction so I don't know if she really
didn't see it or she said I don't know
it'll be all okay
wait okay
um
I feel oh my gosh
[Music]
okay I don't I'm not so sure about that
one
but I don't think Bay is that much of
like a master liar
Hanya
oh I did it
but also oh no
mermaid could have just not known what
was happening
you know
okay I'll go to this one
oh someone's there
who is there
it was that okay
it was Zetta Zeta did it
that's good to know
I have to go to the specimen room that's
so far away
through the specimen room
after go
anyone want to come with me
well I can go alone that's fine
that's fine I suppose
oh no no oh no it's Simon Says
I'm afraid I cannot help with the tasks
I'm doing Simon Says
people beep beep
beep beep beep beep beep beep beep oh
they got it okay
I'm done with my tasks let's go find
friends
let me through please
I'm gonna be so suspicious it's bae
oh
that means that Bae is not the Imposter
right
I think oh we're like all here
where's Muna where's the Muna oh
no
we split the party we split the party it
was fine
uh-oh
should we go
I guess we're going
well she's probably doing a task so it's
probably fine
oh wait on the outside oh they got it
I don't think it's Ollie because she
probably would have killed me by now
am I being suspicious chasing her though
we're friends right
get us with our cute faces oh our cute
ooh faces
we're all here where's Muna
oh there she is
hi Muna
where's tasks left
this is a this is a hard place to be as
the Imposter though when everyone groups
up together I feel like that means uh
you need to give people more tasks or
something
can we view the thingy
the thing in the shows where everyone is
or the security cams oh we're almost
done though
I think that we're good
was Mermaid The Imposter every round
poor movie
[Music]
oh the lights the lights
I wanted to do a stack kill but I'm not
being Foster
oh but look it would be a perfect stack
kill right there
oh
Among Us Among Us
good job
good job again
[Applause]
anybody
you did walk over my mom everyone
after moving uh get out everything's
like it's so hard to kill everyone yeah
together yeah everyone is just like
going
together
[Music]
and I was like bro this can't be real
you see people's names when they're
watching somebody that's not I just saw
your your character your colors
yeah yeah oh yeah oh yeah then you
should be able to like see the colors
um yeah it's really Opie why are you
looking
when you guys were like in the snack
what I was like about to kill you guys
when you guys in fact but but you guys
instead not in like one step but have
like a different size so I just like oh
this is hard even though I do it
everybody should be off on their own and
isolated at all times honestly
maybe because yeah
can we just maybe do one more round and
in case someone gets imposter who
already got impossible before we restart
are just gonna try but it feels like
yeah okay so yeah all right okay
all of you okay okay so someone gets it
again okay yeah if someone gets it like
people who already got it already Okay
Okay
[Applause]
[Music]
we could just do the emergency meeting
and cast okay yeah I'll be throwing it
[\h__\h]
well
well though I feel like it narrows it
down too much
is it is it
well I don't know if we're playing
I don't know if she was memeing or not
all I know is I'm doing my tasks
oh
is that way who is that I didn't see
what that was
I I saw someone but I don't know who it
was because I wasn't looking at the
screen but there was someone running
Rockets right oh yeah yeah by the
Rockets sneak me oh me me me I I was
stalking fauna and then it got dark and
I lost sight of her but then I saw crony
come from the opposite direction
and I started stalking her wait where's
the body again I think yes
the rocket oh uh it's nearby the
laboratory
that's so far
I've just been in weapons all I'm saying
is that I'm like on the left side of the
map
did whoever was did they cross paths
with you or did you see they were
running to the left
interesting left
from the right to the left interested
however I don't know I don't know
I wasn't sure if we were playing or not
this round so okay I will fess up
I I did get it again what
what but like
should you cast me out now
should we just restart I feel like we
have too many times
we'll just continue like that
oh imaginary kill people I will just act
as if I did it
so like if I'm imposter again should I
just out myself
too many people and like it narrows it
down too much so I'm not sure we can
really do that I mean we could just keep
crony around
oh I'll just not kill anyone I'll just
be sabotage
sabotaging
oh oh that was close OH
Close well at least she's honest she's
very honest at least
honest yeah
I don't know what's happening
oh wait it's crony is she actually not
gonna kill anyone
I don't know what to believe anymore
I'm surprised that they were not
suspicious of me though
I've been so suspicious the whole time
foreign
no CO2 hide nutrients no radiation just
a little radiation in some water
and a little bit of this
oh
and a little bit of
this just quickly before the seismic
stabilizers fail
just just
quickly quickly quickly
I kind of oh
no oh
you have no idea
in the hallway on the left side of the
map like between like the tree in the
hallway yeah
she's in like the middle left oh okay in
a hallway wait who was with someone was
with me at stabilizer so they're also
safe
um
I I was walking up with you but then I
went to the left and then it was coming
from that area but I guess she didn't
she didn't touch it yeah why would I
touch it yeah
that's okay
yeah anything can happen it must be the
other imposter
Fisher friends not food God I I have no
idea skipping
I kind of really anyone have any leaves
I'm just gonna try to keep honest
at this point
I just said that and then muted herself
immediately
[Laughter]
[Music]
I did report both bodies but it really
wasn't me
foreign
I
feel like I did see I haven't been
paying attention
I have just been doing my tasks
look at my little legs it's all Among Us
legs
are there lights out here
oh
oh I know these are just regular tasks
who needs lights though
who needs um
oh here
um
are we going okay I guess movement is
going
okrs scanning I don't think it's her
then
count my tasks are way over here so
I don't really trust Bay either though
oh
who's dressed oh why do it
I knew I shouldn't really trust they
wait crony's still in wait we didn't
vote crony out my butt
I bought everyone you're running past my
body my dead body
oh
she's like amnesia
foreign
[Music]
hi guys
spin spin spin spin to win
do not get as many experience points
when you die though
I feel like I was getting some good
points
but
let's haunt moving because she extended
that I'm suspicious
oh I will haunt you forever a movie you
can never get rid of me can ghosts fix
the lights I don't think so right yeah
no
oh no that is so devious holy moly
so crony actually not killing it why
didn't Grody get voted out
hi Kiara
it's a little bit of a precarious
situation here oh
uh oh I have a I have I have a theory
like Romeo and Juliet
Juliet I have I have a very big Theory
so I was assessing uh
ume and fauna at the very start because
they were the nearest people after I saw
Muna senpai
and since Connie came out I felt like oh
oh it has to be someone that didn't came
out after meeting Anya
um and isn't the type that would be
um going on herself doing duties just to
get in anyone's trust if she's an
imposter so it couldn't be heard it
couldn't be me so it's either KR Senpai
or bae
but that's just yeah
I was scared why was impulsory I could
have killed you right I feel like I
didn't hear the difference between Van
Lines I don't know if it's just because
I know she's lying right now
I really it's really kind of dwindling
to the final people my learning here if
you waste the thing we're gonna we're
gonna lose by the way she sounds more
aggressive
um yeah inside the weapons is that
weapons like you better choose someone
like between weapons
still here
that's cool
okay I mean I don't know why I'm still
here to be honest
and not killing anyone I appreciate the
gesture I've just been sabotaging but
like really big problems the other
imposter doing a very nice job
[Music]
foreign
who is this
Henry Stickman why is he crying crying
his dad died why is his mom
his mom died
is this someone's baby
really
oh no
that's so sad does the little Among Us
do that too
did Ollie have the little one
the little Baboo yeah
[Applause]
I'm sorry
[Laughter]
you stopped me where in the back
that was not a killing spring
[Music]
my spine when you did it respond to the
ones who stayed alive and finished the
tasks yeah yeah
honestly I was done and had to finish
the tasks I think it was me
no can we do one more if that's possible
since it was hard for the other imposter
someone read but I wasn't looking at my
screen I was like were they someone red
but I didn't know
uh yeah but is it possible to do one
more since like that that one round it
was just pretty much one imposter
[Music]
um
one more round and then what do you guys
just want to do hide and seek I don't
think it's fun
and the killing time is like 10 like the
lowest 10 seconds and pretty much they
have to try and kill every everyone
before they finish the task
[Music]
s
yeah yeah so you have to you have to say
um and you've set the the running speed
to the fastest whoever's making the room
and then you count to ten if you're the
Imposter and then yeah okay I have the
player speed on Max oh my God that is so
fast
and no reporting the body right yeah no
reporting no report okay
10 seconds yeah no it doesn't get any
longer wait do we have okay do we have
to do task yeah yeah yeah yeah so the
point is to finish all the tasks before
you get killed okay
[Music]
too little yeah
so wait so how many should I do
of course you should be good or two to
four
yes much
everybody no reporting um
do you want to do the normal one for now
it's Clay
lower imposter Vision as well oh we're
not gonna mute ourselves by the way
right yeah until you're done okay
go wild yeah the lowest
screaming
[Applause]
good morning
it's me I'm it you better run wait do I
give you a head sign finally
[Music]
the game
scared
uh it's impossible meant to die in this
one I have no idea
oh God
yes
[Laughter]
you need to lose you guys though the
visuals
what is everywhere
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God oh my God oh my God I'm dying
play the elevator music oh my God oh my
God
oh
god
oh no wait what do you mean I haven't
killed anyone in a while
come on come on come on come on
where's everybody
dangerous place
[Music]
wait is it only is this only me and Bay
now
is
this
go grab a coffee
um
I don't think so we can haunt her hole
oh
[Music]
no sense I just wanted to hug
wait am I allowed to sabotage
[Music]
am I allowed
[Laughter]
[Music]
you're so close oh no it's actually
harder than I thought
oh no maybe
five seconds I don't know so we're gonna
have five seconds give them five seconds
I think it's good I think it's well
balanced but it's a
four three
two
one
more time
oh no
thank you
possible
[Music]
wow wow amazing I don't think that would
work so that we would win what what
that's fun we should try again so
someone else can have a chance to be the
lucky killer because it's fun
okay
should I change something any
improvements was actually okay
I messed up a few times if I hadn't
messed up I would have won so it's okay
I think okay you have to play well if
you want to win it's possible
who's it I don't actually don't I don't
actually want to be it so please no
thank you wait we should restart it's me
again
well we could just do an emergency oh
yeah
okay
goodbye
yeah
[Music]
we have to wait
why don't we just you know doing the
marketing
[Applause]
you only have a couple of hours left so
if you wanted to get it
do it do it um
let's do it
just
do it
do it do it
the car is
saying do it is incredible me
[Laughter]
all right will it be fun again or I hope
not we learn easy
oh yeah
we're the Cosmic Cube oh God for the
Cosmic Cube yes
[Music]
oh
it's not me it's me oh my God
should we do tasks during the countdown
or no no no no no no no no no okay
stop counting okay I'm counting please
wait what
okay
you guys are confusing me
oh no it's not good oh my goodness
it started oh man I think it started
I have no idea what should I do but
[Music]
I'm over there
the
Keystone that is broken
[Music]
well this is peaceful in a way I guess
I'm definitely not in the cafeteria
right now you don't need to go looking
for me
[Music]
I can't do the card
God damn it
no
um
[Music]
so sad oh I feel the views so small
not in the cafeteria at all
every time
oh
one more time and boom finally
[Music]
all my fault
my hands are shaking
oh it gets hard when
there's only a few people left
I got two more tasks I already mentally
gave up on that one baby
oh
come on this one
you are scary oh my God
[Music]
I'm so sorry
wow that was fun
did anyone it's me never get imposter I
didn't I never I never got one only an
onion me we are first
it's not fair oh that's cute I'm going
to sue someone I don't know who but I'm
still probably Susie
or hello
so this actually means milk in Indonesia
oh wow
excuse me uh
it depends that you can at least give
you can at least just say
uh something dong
added
[Music]
mama
oh my God
I will marry you or something like that
[Laughter]
sorry
anyway guys
right now it's gonna end soon
yeah
in like 12 hours I think so make sure
you grab the merch guys
[Music]
oh yeah
cool
more t-shirts
[Music]
yeah very nice
guys yeah thank you so much
thank you
[Music]
so much
fun for you guys too thank you yeah it
was really fun thank you thank you thank
you everyone
[Music]
bye bye
foreign
[Music]
thank you