[Music]
This old, hungry Tato is
still lying in his bed. Is he not in the
best condition? No, he's serious.
This is the number of times I've said that.  If you're
not feeling well inside, please cry.
That's why God
heals us.
[Music] No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's pretty dignified. No, it's
sentimental. Knight Nerunoke.
This is what I'm releasing in a 140-character poem.  If the bat is determined, it
's decided to be 2. I'm sure I'm going to get away with it like this,
no matter how many losers there are. Naturally, running away is the only thing I'm
good at.
Sabo's only mouth is quick to catch prey. That's right,
lying is also easy.
[Applause] Sadara Dojo
It's disgusting, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I've caught a lot of fish, no, I'm hungry, and I'm not motivated, I'm playing with my phone again, and I'm lying in bed pretending to be dead.If I were to do it, it would probably be a lottery, so why don't I do it?  That's because I'm a bit of a fool,
but to be honest, before that guy hit me,
I'm rotten because of Beck, I've been in a
bad mood lately, please be honest, Shakyamuni
Buddha
[Music]
Thank you for your hard work