[Music]
do
so
[Music]
wow
oh
[Music]
smoothie
meow
[Music]
mm-hmm
cake
[Music]
there we go
wait a second oh wait a second
wait a second wait a second wait a
second wait a second
a second
this one
okay
hello
i'm a bit low energy right now but i'm
sure
it will come to me the energy i want to
try something out remember when i had
like the other screen
that was like just
graphic screen not
not like a proper background like this
and i had this
this table
with my legs on it and i was wondering
like because that is attached the legs
are attached to the table if i can't
somehow use it here this one
wait a second
let me try something
oh filters
color key
green
okay okay oh
i mean the table is not the same size
and the
perspective is maybe a little bit
different too
[Music]
stupid green outline
um
something like that
and then
i pull that
down
to
where the other desk is where's the desk
uh here
and then i get rid of the other desk
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's not
not perfect you see there's like a
some behind the scenes stuff going on
here
um did i have the legs just just the
legs oh
god but if i if i want it to be as so
big that it fits this you know that that
weird
shadow it has on the sides
then
my legs will be so big
yeah it's not gonna work right now i
think oh well
[Laughter]
okay desk come back thank you
my body
okay well it was worth a try it was
worth a try i would say
oh small too small
yeah
uh i have an energy drink in my fridge
and i'm thinking about drinking it but i
usually don't like drinking energy
drinks because they're so unhealthy and
and even when it's one of those super
tiny
cans
um that's still a lot for me and i only
have like a huge monster in my fridge
and i feel like it's such a waste
because i'll only take like a few sips
from it
and then the rest will go to waste you
have like 600 supercharged i don't know
i didn't count
and i don't even know what's a lot
anymore like how much time it takes me
to read 100 super chats
don't drink those garbage
yeah energy drinks i i really don't
drink them at all um especially not
after i joined her life with my previous
job i
drank energy drinks
every once in a while whenever i had an
early shift when i had to get up at 5am
or so
um
but yeah with whole life
i've been
just sleeping as much as i can whenever
i'm tired and you know the good thing is
that like if i ever don't get enough
sleep i can just move my stream
and then i don't have to suffer through
a lack of sleep
uh by going to work
now with with my previous job i couldn't
just move on the day i couldn't just
move my shift so
so uh something had to be
done about that so yeah that's that's
really oh
that's really one of the best things
about this job is just the freedom to
decide what to do yeah i'll turn on some
bgmo
schedule
[Music]
what was this again i got some new audio
stock tracks what is this again i i
i named it
powder powder powder pp what was that
supposed to mean
wait what is that supposed to mean para
para pipi
[Music]
dance
now i get it
[Music]
isn't this cute
yeah i was looking for a bunch of cute
okay let me let me let me show you all
my new audio stock songs i was looking
for like cute i guess
um cute songs that also work with super
chat ratings i think
i mean and i and this time i named them
so that i still have the original audio
stock id with it so if you guys really
want to know i can give you the numbers
too if you're curious i have a whole
collection now
uh
this one
this is in there
and then
just one
uh electro energy a tropical
and the thinking time
and the tick tock cute
okay okay i think these are all my new
ones okay so so so we have papa
papa cute right
um if you want to know the number it's
793 119 and then there's this one
[Music]
isn't this cute
i named this one poncho
audio stock eight eight five nine four
zero
pop uh
i can see it a little bit yeah
this is very cute i think
this is
cute
[Music]
i was thinking really deep for audio
stock i noticed that um even though the
audio stack audio stack audio stock
database is like insanely big
um i've noticed still
some girls using the same tracks
overlapping which is i think
because they
only use the most obvious
keywords and then don't go further than
the first page or the second page of
um tracks but i went much much deeper
this time so i think all of these are
unique or at least no other whole life
members using these then i have this
positive ending
audio stock
i think i would use this
at the end of a stream when it's ending
positively
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you everybody for watching today i
was wonderful wasn't it yeah oh that was
a great game it was so good i think i
would recommend this to everyone thank
you to my friends and my family for
supporting me for all this time yeah and
in german we say i'll feed us in see you
on the next game
[Music]
bye bye
you see what i'm getting at
[Laughter]
uh this is one one one seven five free
then i have calm cute story time
audio stuck
[Music]
you like this one for super chat reading
of course i would play it a little bit
more quiet but yeah
it's so cute
yeah i like this one for super chat
indeed yeah yeah yeah this is one four
five nine four zero then we have electro
cute bounce all your stock
i love this kind of style
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god it's just so good
yo
then i have elevator cute audio stalk
elevator this is elevator music oh by
the way that one was one two four five
one four then i have elevator cute
[Music]
hi it's so good it's so cute
it has a few very um not so noisy
instruments that are kind of like
tropical sounding in there i don't know
if you heard it but thanks for the
membership yeah this one is good for
super chat too
then i have happy niche joe audio stock
so every day ninja joe is everyday life
but that one was one one five eight zero
four four if you're interested
[Music]
i think this one i played uh
in my
valentine's card stream already maybe
did that
maybe i did
not
huh it's hard challenge only
really
i feel like i prepared this one to play
it
oh wow
and then
that was a 796
and then i have joyful cute everyday
audio stock
this one i used somewhere no
thank you for renewing your membership
[Music]
did i not use this one i feel like i use
this one already
[Music]
and this one i did
this one is uh
one zero four nine four one four
then i have tropical cute audio stock
[Music]
oh yeah
so good
[Music]
oh my god
it's so good
this one is seven nine five four nine
six just in case someone needs it yeah
it has a good build up and it's very
very joyful
very much vibing to that one are we on
the beach yo it's so good
i love i don't know what instruments
those are that make it sound so tropical
but i guess there's like some i don't
know bongo type of drums
and so on
uh
i don't know it's so cute
i'm just vibing just showing you my new
my new tracks
finish city one it's finished already
that's the city rendezvous is supposed
to be like that no we're doing a we're
doing a new one
for the members only and then we have
thinking time audio stock
[Music]
foreign
oh cute
this one is 982598
oh that really gave me some time to
think about it
the last one is tick tock cute calm
audio stock i'm trying to add like
good keywords to it so i'll find
whatever i need when i need
knife earlier will help
so there's on this tick tock cute calm
audio stuck
[Music]
do
yeah
yeah that also someone said it in the
chat but it does indeed i can i can kind
of low-key imagine it in
if it would be changed up a little bit
but there's a base of this this track
that i can imagine in a tails off game
you know in one of the older ones maybe
like i don't know something like tales
of symphonia like when walking around
the city
or so i don't know i don't know
it would still have to be changed a
little bit but i can kind of see it yeah
uh oh these are so good i was looking
for some cute type songs to use for
super chat readings and for other
purposes so these are some that
i'll be using because i get so sick of
using the same ones again and again uh
so quickly so yeah there we are
oh
[Music]
i just got the confirmation for the for
the next whole talk
uh
get a guest
and next hotel guest seems to be excited
to be on
a whole talk yeah yay i like it when
they're motivated
nice
yata
[Music]
which one are we gonna use now which one
should i use maybe the elevator one
[Music]
is this too loud
any hints no
no hints
[Music]
we're already 30 minutes in no we're 26
minutes in okay
and five of those were we're waiting
time
we have a lot of time today i think it's
gonna be totally
easy
yeah we're gonna take it easy today
originally i was thinking of playing
like a short game and then reading super
chats today
but if it were a short game it would
have to be something that i finished in
like one hour
um and i um i do have like a list of
games short games that i want to play
every now and then eventually
but
uh
i don't know didn't really fit in today
and i didn't feel like mario kart i
think we need some time before wait the
i want to play mario kart again when the
new pass comes out the one with the
million tracks it didn't come out yet
did it
yes i'm blushing today
sliver in the aisle no i don't wanna i
don't know
like constantly repeat those kind of
games you know if i want new ones but
there's not an endless amount of games
um that are that short and good for
streaming and interesting and
that we can actually play and have
permissions for it all at the same time
planet coastal planets yeah yeah all of
those but i want to play those but i
would feel bad about like stopping to
play them after one hour i feel like i
would want to play them longer than one
hour
um
but there was also this this one game
don't worry i already bought it and
bought it it was free and downloaded it
what was it called again
uh
[Music]
he'll take it health taker
it's already on my desktop
i already have it ready for when i'm
gonna when i want to play a short stream
um short game
hell taker yeah you guys have been
recommending it to me whenever i ask for
a short game recommendations
and it's free of charge i was surprised
to see it's free of charge
you guys know it of course you do
it's only an hour long like for real an
hour damn that is really short
did you see flair's 3d rest yesterday of
course i did i was watching it on my tv
screen
i liked um i think i liked her
performance
of phony i think the most i think that
was the one that i liked a lot cause
like she
suddenly had this
cool
cool aura around her
um the whole performance was really cool
and i know she prefers to be called cute
but
i'm gonna be honest here
i think that for
the overseas generally speaking i think
for the overseas audience
um
rather than a cute lowly lowly type of
character uh
a cool
or mature or like normal normal looking
normal as in
h looking normal
uh type of
character
uh
is more
generally more liked in the overseas
audience while within japan in the
youtuber
audience in japan i think generally of
course there's exceptions but generally
generally like a cutesy type
voice with the cutesy type design
maybe low-key lowly type
is generally more popular in japan of
course as i said there are exceptions um
to the norm but that's just the
impression i have so
[Music]
as i said there are exceptions
i think for gouda there's a lot of
reasons
um that
brought her to where she is now
i don't think it's only her design i
think it's it's many many factors that
played into that um
[Music]
yeah yeah
many many many factors
not that i i like both um to be honest i
like both
cute design i'm a sucker for art and and
yeah generally character designs i
really like both the cute lonely small
type of character
and the boobylicious big
lady character or the cool character or
the normal
uh
kind of
normal girl next door character i like
any of them you know i like all of them
um
i don't really have like a specific
that's it type
um
because like i fall for a lot of like if
i look at
if i look at
um for example atelier
games
there is the ones that are peter
and cute with like twin tails and and no
chest
and just cute style i like those
from from the visuals but then i also
like you know the cooler types of
yes mommy type of girls
i like them all
yeah and then because i like them all
what really comes is the personality and
i mean this i mean this you guys are
always like personality
no i mean it
um
no i really like i really like them all
[Music]
i really like them all i appreciate the
beauty of great character design and
great art
[Music]
no one trusts and believes in me man
but but for um
i understand why federer always wants to
be perceived as cute but i
i think
she is very cute
but i
kind of like her more as a cool type of
chick you know to be honest
i i like her cool attitude
no
[Music]
i don't know
i don't know she's just
hmm
i think her singing just
when she sings when she sings cool songs
she just blows me away
her cute songs are cute too
but maybe maybe it's because i am
a girl
but i personally get more charmed when
she sings cool songs
yeah it hits different times
[Music]
well anyway
so i did see her pretty reveal and very
very very happy for her it all went well
though the part with um the shiraken
was so cute so funny man they
they look like they had so much fun it
was so good good to watch that
um the video on the top right oh that is
if you look up
uh
my name
and um
either mean girl or
uh
jingle bell
or kana udu
then it should come up
it's it's not on my channel that video
is not on my channel because i can't use
the audio on my channel
because it's copyrighted but it's on a
different channel jingle bells rock that
was it
yeah
it's definitely worth watching it with
the audio so thanks for asking it is in
my playlist i think yeah in my in my
music playlist maybe
[Music]
ah
you're gonna make sure
[Music]
do you plan on taking down your
christmas decorations what christmas
decorations
oh the only christmas christmas
decoration i see is that minecraft tree
behind me and that one i can't really
take down i still wanna stay in this
office because
i'm too lazy to clean up the other one
and it is still kind of cold
um maybe when it's officially spring
that's when i'm gonna move back into the
usual office
[Music]
internally chris is no it's not
christmas i mean
yeah just because of that train but i
took that i took down all the other
decorations and i changed the intro
again
so
it's already
pretty much back to normal guys
valentine's is a winter holiday yeah
it's kind of weird i whenever i think
about valentine's i i kind of feel like
it would fit better in spring
i think it fits better in spring why is
it why is it in wintertime what the hell
it doesn't fit
i think oh yeah oh yeah on twitter i was
like
exciting exciting
right
what does that mean i can't tell you
i can't tell you but um two things two
things came up before the stream
that made me feel excited
two two things that
um
i've been working on
and that you guys gonna eventually
eventually know
new ultra screen i don't have it yet i
don't have it yet
um
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
wait wait wait wait wait first
first let me tell you the reason why the
omo cat uh review is not on this
schedule for this week is because it's
on the 1st of march um
wait a second first of march for
me
but it's on the 28th for northern
american times i'm actually getting up
really early for this one
um
and tomorrow i'll be putting up the
tweet for
um opening up submissions
to take your submissions
so you guys have like one week
to send in the submissions and then on
the first for me the first for sea times
the first but for
north american times the 28th
it will be on my channel yes because
i've been organizing it and i've been i
invited everyone
um
yes yes cali and omo cat will be there
and we'll together judge
uh harshly harshly
[Music]
how you guys
combined the omocat merchandise with
your personal clothes and how you put
them together and
uh how you took photographs of them
yeah
where'd you send in submissions there
will be a hashtag on twitter so you can
send it in on twitter
twitter
only i would say because i don't really
know where elsie would submit it
um
yeah
and i'm like i'm like a post on reddit
as well i think
good thing i don't have any merchandise
that's not a good thing
do you want to participate
any news on the next world of darkness
session
i was wondering too like if there are
plans to continue it because i think we
are close to
like the end of like this season or so
anyway
um
but i don't know i haven't really been
asking um
kelly has been doing a lot of other
things um planning a lot of other things
maybe maybe i don't know
maybe she doesn't feel like
continuing it right now maybe she feels
burnt out on it or so i don't know
i haven't heard anything about it in a
while
it's been a long time we should probably
finish it up i was thinking so too
because like
i mean it's already been so long
that
you kind of like
um
how to say you lose touch with the story
and
what's happening what's going on
if there is so much time in between yeah
[Music]
uh-huh oh she did say she did talk about
it on stream
so she at least still has it on her
radar that's good
sometime in march
[Music]
she'll do a recap stream and then the
finale
oh i forgot ttrpg was the thing oopsy
[Applause]
yeah i can't can't judge you uh can't
blame you it's been a while
[Music]
yeah we need a recap stream too i think
i mean
i mean generally i i remember what
happened until now
um
i generally do remember
but
but yeah it's just gotta get back into
the atmosphere and all of that and
i'll i'll probably never really
understand like
or like know by heart
what my skills do and when i should use
them and all that but oh well
um
motion
oh very very very
curious today aren't ya
not gonna blame you but
uh
i'll keep that for
chit chat in another stream like what i
received
because i finally received that package
that my neighbor had because i was on
vacation when it arrived and then i came
back and then they went on vacation
apparently
[Music]
yeah
so
i finally got it now after they came
back
i received
[Music]
keep missing each other yeah stupid damn
it
every round i need super dark no
i'm not planning to just kidding
i really will
what did i say in the tweet that and in
the in the schedule
what did i say
what does it say guys chickens have you
looked at it
what does it say plus chit chat
[Music]
let me chit chat how how the hell are
you guys complaining
how the hell are you guys complaining
about
this i can't read
something
oh
chicken brain
or do you just want me to go you you
don't want you could you're like haha
you haven't read the single super chat
but then if i were to just read the
super chats from beginning to end like
without any chit chat in between you
guys would also be like
today's stream was boring
[Music]
you're just trying to make fun of me or
something buddy
bonnie
why haven't you been clipping recently
[Music]
buddy where are the clips
bunny
[Music]
morning
i've been waiting for your clips
have i not been clippable recently i'm
quite busy oh man
that's okay
as long as you're still
at kfp
and um
still loving me
still supporting me every school
you stole him to translate for you
that's why you're busy because you're
working for another kfb employee
that's why you're busy buddy
yeah
i guess okay that still stays within kfp
i guess
um that's that's
tolerable
sir buddy excuse me i was the one who
gave him that name and now i'm getting
bonked for not saying sir bonnie
[Music]
hi
i'm above him
i am the empress
i can i can call him whatever the [\h__\h] i
want to call him
[Music]
i can say body type
small cute booty
butter chicken you're still chicken
after all you're cute and fluffy and you
meant to be hugged
yes yes
master bull no no no no no tyrant excuse
me yeah
tyrants joe
that doesn't even work well with
the name
like something like potential whatever
it works really well the tyrants drill
does not work
[Music]
potato
love me some potatoes
okay let's read a few super chats and
then we can continue
with the chit chat
uh i haven't even scrolled down to where
i need to start where do i need to start
[Music]
investing
now running away from the conversation
i need to indeed start at some point
[Music]
monopoly
this is gonna take a few hours
[Music]
of pokemon legends
pokemon legends what was before pokemon
legends
[Music]
youtube is getting really slow the lower
i go on my list
the slower it gets man
[Music]
so
is my new vibe
i saw someone
uh clipped it and put swadu and the
shuba duck dancing on the piano
the cute hair dance
it looks really cute
uh the cookie
the cookie baking stream i also need to
read i think right oh my god
what have i done
[Music]
uh another kyle carrot version alright
alright alright
no i'm so stupid i hate it
thanks for the effort but i can't listen
to that it pains me makes me suffer
i thought it would be
something cute like like the one he made
for pakora but no
no
i can't bear it
listening to that
[Applause]
kiana hates cow carrots serious
oh paige unresponsive oh there it is
again there it is valentine's cards i
have to read those too right
[Music]
oh my
i really didn't know i saw
one of those fan made videos before on
twitter but i watched it without the
audio just a little bit like while
scrolling for twitter and i was like oh
it looks interesting i guess i saw the
crony one
but i didn't like click on it and and
and listen to the i didn't read
valentine's cards really
hallelujah oh then wait okay
yeah i just didn't listen to the audio
so i didn't know about the meme
oh i was looking for a dreaming [\h__\h]
just super chat but yeah right it has no
super chat it wasn't monetized yeah yeah
yeah that's right that's right
that's right okay then we start at the
baking cookies stream now
uh
[Music]
um apparently this is the second time
that i use that art i usually try to not
do that but when it comes to cooking
streams i really don't have
much fan art that fits that kind of
situation and i've been doing more and
more
so guys
please uh i need i need more
cooking baking doing something fan art
[Music]
i need it
yeah considering that my whole theme is
like
kfp but i guess yeah i never really made
it clear that i'm the one making the
food because i'm not the one making the
food
um
[Music]
i'm sorry
stink fig you're bad art
[Music]
i'm very picky when it comes to
gonna be honest i am very picky when it
comes to what i use for my thumbnails
uh
so that's that
that's the other problem i am very picky
um
oh
first thing i see understandable have a
nice day
[Music]
commission amen
i'm is busy but the the amen vr chat
collab that i said that we will do
um
will happen when she comes back so she
currently she told me she's not sure
when exactly she comes back
so we can't plan it but we're both aware
of it and she'll let me know when she
knows for sure when she's coming back
and then we'll do the vr chat collab
with the with the two
um
exclusively
made
uh 3d models
[Music]
thanks for the sugary sweet cover with
amiga you two sound so cute and the
music video is freaking adorable you and
emma are my aussies and have given me so
much joy so anytime you two collab it
just makes me so happy i'll always be
cheering you two on
thank you
good taste naveed i mean you have good
taste
um
i'm glad that i finally got to do that
music uh washankava with
i think it was good that i left her um
for the last because first of all best
things always gotta keep them for the
last haha just kidding
um but they do they do say that um
better safe for last right that's how
you say it
but also um
if we would have done this one year ago
i don't think
it would have been this quality
uh also for for amma's singing because i
think she got better
[Music]
save the best for us
yeah so thank you for the support
navidad
thank you soon
[Music]
glad we could do it really
jay catch monkey dance and looking for
the top thank you and looking for the
top thank you soon
i actually have diabetes oh really
oh
so thank you for the warning i took some
metformin but you're really you really
have diabetes but i have to do that
before every stream of yours anyway i
love the music video and you're six seas
oh sexy dances
what what sexy dances that wasn't really
that sexy cute voices and tons of
references need to watch more to find
them all thank you
oh
man i i hope it doesn't disrupt your
your life too much i really don't know
much about how diabetes works the only
the only source of information about
diabetes i have is scrubs um because
turk
has diabetes at some point
and that's the the only way that i ever
got to know something about
diabetes
because i don't know anyone who has
diabetes in my like private life
i've never gotten to know anyone i don't
know maybe people who have diabetes just
don't make a big deal out of it but i've
never heard about any of my
any of my friends or
um
[Music]
acquaintances who have diabetes
same
but it's not that rare though is it
i know it can be really bad and it can
be
very manageable
it's rare in europe than in north
america
[Music]
there are two types i forgot the
difference as long as entering
[Music]
about diabetes is that
so my impression is
[Music]
that you kind of develop it when you eat
too much sugar but then but then but
then in order to survive you sometimes
have to eat sugar to
survive but
i don't know
that is type 2
because turk sometimes
had to eat something sugary
to keep his blood sugar level high
then that's type two that you get it for
eating too much sugar and then you stop
eating sugar but you still have to
somehow eat sugar sometimes that is i'm
actually correct did i explain that
somewhat correctly i thought i would
talk total [\h__\h] now
type one genetic type two back ah
ah that that's the difference between
between type one and time two ah
[Music]
ah
genetic is much worse
[Music]
not just sugar but also some stuff like
high fructose corn syrup
i hope this corn syrup
i freaked out corn syrup
isn't someone
called high fructose corn syrup
and kfp
that word sounds so familiar to me
that's all i can think of
wait who was that
where's the high fructose corn syrup
where is that are you not on your ship
that moment this this moment is your
moment and you're not here
unbelievable
[Music]
oh man
high fructose corn syrup it doesn't
sound dangerous
high fructose corn syrup what is that
what is that in german
tell me tell me
my nephew has type one and seven oh i'm
so sorry for your nephew man what the
[\h__\h]
oh it's used to lots of sweet sodas ah
oh
as much way
it has cord in it how bad can it be
if it's plastic
[Music]
is
i've only ever heard this word before i
think thanks to chat
but
listening to the german translation of
the word i don't think we don't even
have that in our products like generally
because it sounds so unfamiliar to me in
german
it doesn't seem like an issue
[Music]
american thing
your food is so unhealthy america
damn
people of america
your food is so unhealthy man
dude
eat kfp burgers they are very very
healthy
they got salad in it
yeah salad and
tomatoes
and pineapples and [\h__\h]
yeah you're supposed to put some veggies
in it
[Laughter]
a burger
it's not just it's not enough to put two
buns there and then a piece of meat in
between no
no
it's in our salad suit wait what
[Music]
high fructose corn syrup is in your
salads too
[Music]
the [\h__\h]
why not because because
[Music]
thanks for spreading misinformation what
was misinformation
[Music]
in the ranch oh and the dressing you
mean
[Music]
i offended someone oh no oh [\h__\h]
everywhere
[Music]
i wonder why i wonder why it's so
different
in like because i feel like generally
um the types of foods that we eat
are similar like i mean europe and
america it's just the ingredients that
are very different like we you guys eat
pasta we eat pasta
you guys eat burgers we eat burgers
no we we have like similar
we have similar
cuisines
but still it's still differently
prepared
cancel already
anyway oh thank you
nine months let's go
anyway anyway let me read super chats
for god's sake for god's sake
thank you for the rest of the chat thank
you for another amazing cover have been
listening to it all day can't get enough
of you two singing such a cute time
thank you
i'm glad you liked the song and the song
choice yeah it's a classic very classic
vocaloid song
has been around for a while
but i thought it would be
cute as a as a collaboration
song cover so
yeah i hope you enjoy it a lot thank you
for your red super chat and your support
thank you
[Music]
and we're talking about dreaming tutu by
the way
[Music]
it's not been it's been an hour oh but
no but i already started reading super
chats a few minutes ago okay
hey
me
listen
girl
trevor j duncan for the pinky
happy belt or two pinkies that's one red
one
happy valentine's day i'd like to place
an order for the most delicious burp you
have in store
you know the one with ties thicker than
the thickest lasagna
arms like the finest cooked noodles eyes
that glisten brighter than hot buttered
corn
jiggles like pudding
voice that scissors like bacon of hope
hearts heart that's sweeter than any
chocolate i think everyone who has
diabetes just is about to die by reading
this super chat
and this spirit that burns hotter than
kfp's ovens that fancy feast for my
heart eyes and soul the only one i would
call my oshi plus a side of cookies
please
[Music]
yeah um bye-bye people with diabetes
description
thai is thicker than the thickest
lasagna arms like the finest cooked
noodles
eyes that glisten brighter than hot
buttered corn
jiggles like pudding
voice that scissors like bacon of hope
let that sink in
[Music]
i love that meme
that's one of my favorite memes ever
[Music]
i had to
but don't
[Music]
let that sink in it's cold outside yeah
yeah are you not enjoying my joke
i think we're all enjoy nature
what does she have to say in our office
why not it's very very helpful
like
bendy very bendy
very very useful
i can always wash my hands when they're
too sweaty sweaty spaghetti
don't you feel sorry for that sink
no i didn't have it on standby i googled
it
okay yeah thank you trevor g um
i'm glad you didn't end it with
some kind of way to twisting it into
genma
so thank you for that but still
i think you're going a bit too far
trevity
[Music]
for the red super chat new song
did you enjoy it
i hope you did thank you for listening
to it a lot
thank you for the generous donation i
appreciate it
for the red super chat hi kira the new
song cover is amazing my favorite cover
song is bokudano asiato this song is
making me feel warm and part of the
reason i become to kfb really by the way
mail please have a cookie boss ah i
actually have my box of cookies with me
on my desk so that i can snack on them
when i need to
is jenna available no she's not
[Music]
mine
anyway thank you akker um i'm surprised
it's it's makes me very happy to hear
that you're like
it's been very very very very overlooked
i mean i definitely could have done a
better job at singing it but there was
some time pressure back then because i
made it as a quick
birthday present
for hookah papa
but yeah i'm glad that you're listening
to it thank you akker thank you so much
mwah
looking on the asia is awesome thank you
yeah if you ever like
feel like oh okay
song covers and original songs are also
bouncy and poppy i want to hear her sing
something chill like a balaad song then
it's time for you to listen to bokorano
it's in my music playlist so if you
haven't listened to it yet
do it do it do it
[Music]
thank you
and originally like that oh i would only
really do that as a as a song that's
part of an album i think not as a single
release
because i think it wouldn't do well as
as a single
[Music]
from a business point of view
um
but yeah
i have to think about
whether or not i'm able to make an album
anyway
because i don't know what's involved in
that
yeah and what the cost is
[Music]
no it's not a tease i really have not
even discussed anything about it at all
i'm still like to be honest i'm working
on a single right now and then i already
have someone in mind to
create another single for after that
like i know
uh who i want to ask
next so that's that's already another
single lined up
um
maybe
maybe summertime release i don't know
so
if there was an album maybe at the end
of the year but i don't know
yay
a physical album
i would love that too to have something
that i can
hold in my hands but in this day and age
you know everyone's getting music um
digitally so
i don't know like if since um
if it's someone like kelly i think it's
worth it but for me i don't know if
if
you know
i don't know
yeah
i don't gotta be honest i don't believe
in it being successful
[Music]
um
unless unless there's something that
comes with it like you know how i think
i mentioned this before
but like
when i was an idol otaku
uh
the cds that they released the idol
groups that i followed they always
included like a a ticket for a raffle
for a handshake event
or something similar
yeah lottery for concert so for
handshake events for release events
release concerts
stuff like that
and we can't really exactly do that um
waffles i love waffles now raffles not
waffles
i love waffles too i wish i could
include waffles in my cds
see these still sell pretty well
um
if i ever put out an album
for that i think i would try to get it
um
get a physical release going
[Music]
maybe in the shape of a waffle
yeah i would see it as some kind of
merchandise too
[Music]
why does my
why is my face feel so exhausted
recently i feel i felt this way after
holo talk too but even worse i felt more
exhausted than this but my face right
now feels like
i
feel so exhausted so tired
i haven't done anything
yeah i think besides yeah
maybe because i'm smiling too much while
i'm talking i try to smile
to have some emotion going on you know
i should just
talk without emotion
[Music]
cause i look i look cute all the time
anyway but i i feel like i
[Music]
recently i've been having less and less
energy
i'm not sure
what exactly is causing it
but
it's like a lack of energy and and
um
a little bit of a lack of
motivation
not exactly motivation but like
something similar to them
it's hard to explain
i don't i don't know lack of vitamins
maybe probably
probably
uh
yeah
um
i'm fine though but i don't know like i
literally just came back from a vacation
so like i'm like what what what do you
want what do you want buddy
what do you want i just went to a
vacation
[Music]
i think my body wants to live
in a vacation place at all times
[Music]
sunlight [\h__\h] sunlight
you think sunlight would help but then i
put my plants in front of the window to
get some sunlight and they still [\h__\h]
die like it's not always the solution
i've been trying to save this plant from
dying for months now and it's just not
working
nothing i do works
nothing
it's just decided to be a zombie plant
forever maybe i should give it to ollie
she would be happier about it i've been
watering it i've been trying to water it
less and i've been trying to water it
more and now um i wonder maybe maybe
maybe it was not humid enough in the
room so now we have a human humidifier
here anyway
working really hard
the switch locations i switched it from
living room to office
and it's still in pain
still like now it has reached a new low
it looks like completely dead
um i should probably cut off all of the
leaves because i read that if you don't
cut them off they will suck like
the life out of the plant i don't know
how to explain it
[Music]
let's talk to it
i really left it on the balcony no
because i thought it would be too cold
outside but but it's getting
steadily warmer so i might give that a
try
[Music]
trim decaying leaves i've been doing
that since the beginning though and it's
still been dying
now i haven't done it in a while and i i
do see
one new leaf
um sprouting which i haven't seen in a
while uh for this plant specifically
so maybe this one leaf maybe i cut all
the other leaves and just and just pray
that this one leaf will do the trick
have you tried switching it on and off
again i wish it was that [\h__\h] easy
i'm i'm really not a planned person i
haven't really
had much plans over the course of my
lifetime
when i was living at home obviously my
mom was taking care of plants
but yeah
my mom said that
i should like she said she would do it
whenever she comes over but she said
that it probably needs to be re-plotted
like
put it out of the i'm not exactly sure
what it what that means but i think you
put it out of the pot change the soil
completely and put it back into the plot
or into a different pot i don't know
but
yeah i don't
that sounds good but i don't know how to
do it so i'm just waiting for my mom to
come
[Music]
put it out of its misery yeah and add
some race pups to that go get a phone
[Music]
oh why not get a cactus
stay i mean they're cute and all but i'm
not gonna decorate my whole apartment
with cactuses i want some proper plants
here looking good there's i have a
different plant that is insane like i
barely even give it water it doesn't
give a [\h__\h] like no matter where i put
it no matter how much water i give it
it just thrives it's amazing
it's so big now that i'm like [\h__\h] what
do i do like
it's getting too big for its pot i think
it's turning into a [\h__\h] tree
huh i wonder if i can
like cut off one part and then put it
into another pot and then continue
growing it there
i think that's a thing but i also don't
know how to properly do that
trim it i don't want to hurt it
i don't want to hurt it um
you know what that's actually
i guess something that we could do
[Music]
it's gonna be a [\h__\h] mess
oh my god i'm so sorry
that i didn't mute myself
i am i am anguishpant i am
[Music]
um
i need a massage okay
[Music]
the return of the crack it was a nice
one that was like a triple triple like
i'm like an ice skater but i do it with
my neck a triple lutz or something like
that
[Music]
oh baby it's ripple
anyway
[Music]
anyway anyway
delusional dreamer thank you for the red
super chat we're never gonna we're never
gonna read these super chats aren't we
ah
thank you for the red super chat here i
leave my final well
i had a heart attack you gave me a shock
like the first
can i show you like how
how this is
how this super chat
breeds
um
at this
[Music]
here here i leave my final will i had a
heart attack
[Music]
for listening to dreaming to do
jesus
jesus christ
[Music]
too small
it starts like this
thank you youtube for
formatting it like this we're gonna
leave my final will i had a heart attack
for listening to dreaming tutu
are you kidding me
both the writer of the super chat and
youtube are giving me
a big shock here how dare you
[Music]
okay it has a fatal dose of cuteness and
it
at the last moment i realized the
tensions plan that makes people respond
to chicken and hiring in kfp world
domination by streaming dreaming choo
choo
i realize potential plan that makes
people respond to chicken and hiring in
kfp
what do you mean i have no crazy plan
like that
no
[Music]
no no no no no no you're a delusional
just like your name no
i don't have any crazy plans there's no
just take off your tinfoil hats
there's no secret plan or strategy or
whatever
thank you for the rest of the time keep
on listening to dreaming choo choo
please thank you for the support i'm
glad you like it it is very very cute i
know
wow thank you
uh sometimes keyblade thank you for the
rest of the chat never really celebrate
valentine's or most holidays in general
you definitely showed me how it's
important to have fun and celebrate
these moments because they won't be here
forever yeah true
we can't all be you happy valentine's
boss i hope my valentine reaches your
heart thank you happy valentine's day to
you too
delayed but still
yeah i mean i i understand the people
who don't really celebrate valentine's
or isa or christmas and to be honest
easter and valentine's i wouldn't
celebrate either if i was not a streamer
um
yeah so i told and get it if you don't
really care about it
but it's always fun to have like a
reason to
make a day special
together with you guys i think um
i think it's good to do that because we
can make special memories and we can
have like themed streams and all that we
have a good reason to do certain things
like making chocolate and so on
yeah
so
i will continue doing so and even though
i don't care about easter we're gonna
have an easter stream
yes
don't tell jesus don't tell him
[Music]
um
he's always listening nah
yeah
[Music]
i did i did pay my
church taxes but i'm
not part of the church anymore
[Music]
i'm gonna start eating a cookie
yeah there is
at least in my country
there's a church tax if you're a
certain
at least a certain religion
cookie
but
i was like there was a at a time where i
was really broke
and they send you this letter asking for
a certain amount and they do write there
that if you can't afford it
feel free to discuss with us and and we
can talk about it i was a student um i
think and working at the same time and i
barely had any money so i was like i'm
not [\h__\h] paying this i don't have
money to even feed myself
um but then it kept on piling up and up
and up and up and eventually i was like
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h] i'm paying it and i'm out
now
could have probably discussed
it
but it sounds like too much of a bother
it accumulates yeah it does and
i didn't it's not like i even made any
use of
the church but anyway
[Music]
let me see
if this still tastes good because i
haven't
eaten one in the past two days i know
shocking
[Music]
yeah
i mean
it's definitely still edible
[Music]
i feel like they tasted better
the best one was the second batch
on the
on the very day where i made them
after letting them cool
that was the best one
i made too many cookies though
just too many i can't eat them all alone
before they go bad
that's my problem
[Music]
freeze them
how
how do you warm them up when you freeze
them
i didn't think about doing that that
sounds crazy
freezing the cookie
never thought about freezing a cookie
[Music]
microwave
and but won't they just be soggy and
[\h__\h]
all right
or soft
[Music]
you just leave them out in the oven
yeah in the oven i think it would work i
guess
but in the microwave
[Music]
oh man there's just so many gatherers in
my apartment recently it's been really
bad even because my cats are shedding
[Music]
i'm thinking about
hiring a cleaner for one day
i know i know it sounds crazy
but i i have quite a big apartment
[Music]
and
it's just i suck at professionally
cleaning i can like shallowly clean
but i think i want to hire one for one
day it's not really crazy
for for the person that i was before
whole life it was unthinkable i thought
that only millionaires hire
um
maids
it takes a lot of stress off i think
they would just do it very properly and
and that's what i desire
one time proper cleaning
just one time maybe in in
in half a year or so or one year
that's all i want
i thought you guys would think it's
crazy too but actually i'm surprised you
guys
agree do you have an air filter i have
one in every
room one of those
because i was i was heavily
um
pressured into buying one for each of my
rooms by um
someone in kfp
why would you think it's crazy because
it's just not it doesn't maybe it's a
culture thing but it just doesn't sound
like something
someone would do unless you're a
millionaire i don't know
[Music]
hiring a maid is common here eh where
i had a mate before and i'm not that
rich what
where where are you
it's kind of unthinkable here
i've never heard of anyone
in my country before that has a maid
[Music]
unless they're rich as [\h__\h]
not very unusual n a fairly common in
the u.s
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
i just feel like
i feel like my mom would probably be
like why the [\h__\h] do you hire a maid why
don't you just clean the [\h__\h] yourself
and she has a point in case she wants to
say that to me right now in case she's
listening
or she would probably say kiara i'm just
gonna come over and clean your apartment
and you pay me instead herself
okay
that's an option too
if you would come over mom we can do
that too
we can do that
[Music]
she wanted to help me out like that
before
[Music]
mom would say the same to me
definitely not wrong but but
but but
fine
but but but i do think that people who
do it as a job definitely know more
about cleaning than i do like how to
clean certain surfaces like what
you know
and and and and and how to get certain
stains out
or
[Music]
you know how to wipe a window properly
i've i've never
never cleaned my windows before
but they look fine to learn
you're that messy no no no no no
i do have one problem oh god wait stop
me someone [\h__\h] stopped me stop it i
need to read super test
stop talking stop talking stop talking
stop talking
stop talking stop talking
right super jets
um
stop talking
where was i
uh so let's keep light here's the kiss
for you thank you
bro fro thank you for the red super chat
happy valentine's day takanashi hot
wings
i know you're quite a busy beautiful
stunning bird and many chimpanzees have
already asked you to be their valentine
or even want to marry you and now it's
my turn to finally ask you my aussie did
you have a great day oh for april
good job good job good job
it's good
good that you ended it like that
smart this is a smart chicken
[Music]
thank you very very much
er
actually no
i don't think
because valentine's is not really a big
thing here i don't think anyone has ever
asked me to be their valentines
but but don't worry for the sad thing
it's just because no one no one really
celebrates it and also because i was
unpopular but anyway no it's because no
one celebrates in you okay
[Music]
we don't we don't say
we just don't we just don't say that
phrase
um
anyway
[Laughter]
yeah yeah i'm taken by my cats yeah
i it's not like guys
no
whatever um
[Music]
the outfits you made for dreaming
chit-chat hello cute can i design lip
outfits when oh
oh like if i were to get a chance like
that i would put much more work into it
but
i don't know doesn't
doesn't really seem like something
that's gonna happen um
unless actually you know for that for
that thing that i wanted to do that
vr chat project i will probably just do
some really simple themed um
uh uh clothing designs for whatever the
theme is of
what we're doing
oh by the way
here we go another tangent but maybe you
guys can help me
because i've been looking
around on amazon and outside of amazon
like what options i have for you know
the punishment device
and i just didn't really find anything
that would really work because the
electro i've seen the following things
electroshockers where you put your hand
on and you tell a lie
but that doesn't really work for the way
i want to use it like ideally
i would like
like
i would like something like
just like a small
keychain type of size
thing with a button on it and you push
the button and and then
it
lets off a little bit of an
you know
um
but even more ideally than that would be
if i could control it manually over
wi-fi or so but i there's literally
nothing like that
so i was thinking maybe i need to give
up on that electrocuting option
um
do you guys have any ideas one's for
is dogs on your hand instead of your
neck a dog
ah do you use it like when they do
something bad and you need to teach them
does that even work on humans like is
that not too weak or so i mean
[Music]
why are we talking about it because
because
because it's a fun project and i just
need to find the right punishment device
excuse me
shock
color
or dog
oh god there were some other suggestions
besides
um
anti-bark dog color
interesting about automatic barking
collars so what that only works when
they bark i need it when we laugh
oh is this one of something you can
activate
the dog's dog color air mesh various
colors and sizes for small dog dogs like
dogs coloring cat puppies
wait how does that work
that's just a dark color color color
color color color
those are just dark colors
[Music]
okay so besides
electric
devices
you guys have any other ideas
[Music]
make them this girl's bark after they
laughed i'll be like yo you have to bark
and then they bark and then they get
electrified
it doesn't sound very
useful
doesn't sound so efficient
full-sized dunk tank
hitting them with a stick well that
won't work because we're not there all
in person if they all had someone stand
by to hit them whenever they laugh
behind the scenes
i guess
but that also doesn't really sound like
i want an easy solution so that the
girls don't have to do much in order to
make it work
yeah we're trying i'm trying okay if you
don't know what the [\h__\h] i'm talking
about i
previously brainstormed an idea
that is uh inspired by a japanese tv
program
where there
where five comedians are stuck in uh
for 24 or 48 hours i always forget i
think 24 hours
um
in in a in a building where they
continuously get entertained
by other comedians and some skits and
all that and whenever they laugh they
like people run into the room and
forcefully slap their butts with a bat
and so they're not supposed to laugh but
yeah it's cocky not sky yep so i want to
make that into a vr chat collab where
it's also a theme like for example they
had like police themed or they had like
i don't know um
a
hospital themed teacher themed
anything really
school themed yeah i think they had a
school theme too
yeah but the question is like what can i
use to like
one thing that we could also do maybe is
we don't um punish them right away but
then i feel like they're just gonna
laugh continuously but we just count
their laughs and then punish them at the
very end by like looking at how often
everyone laughed and then
everyone will probably laugh so everyone
gets a punishment
but the one the more you laughed the
worse will be a punishment like i don't
know playing a really bad horror game
like bad is and really really terrifying
or yeah eating a spicy ramen on stream
or so spicy peppers
yeah
i guess but it just doesn't have the
same effect because like the the thing
the thing what's so funny about khaki
not sky is that they laugh and then they
get hit and and
them getting punished is like also
really funny you know
that's that's
that's the funny thing about it too
yeah the immediate feedback exactly
that's what i mean
just tell them to activate a shotgun
when they're caught well i thought about
that but i couldn't even find something
that would
fit that either like a product because
like i saw the
the one that that i supposed lied
supposed to be lie detectors but that
doesn't really work because they would
have to always have their hand on it and
we're not playing a lie detecting game
so it just doesn't work it's called a
prank buzzer i think i think i thought
about using that but wait a second
[Music]
um
man amazon
and buzzer
what about this one
88 thingies
as cheap clockwork hand butters go it's
okay the spring has gotten a bit slack
something to do
as a gag gift or for a bit of a love
it's not bad
lots of fun using it how are you using
it and having fun
cheap [\h__\h] just got this looks cheap and
nasty and and the same as i ordered this
looks like it will break too easy don't
think it's worth opening the packet
but see this is also the problem all
these products are [\h__\h]
i can i'm worried about buying them
[Music]
are probably the best that but then they
have to bark what the [\h__\h] how do you
how do you imagine that to work huh
shock color wi-fi
that sounds very very um
yeah bye but yes let's look it up
shock color
wi-fi
[Music]
i it doesn't
doesn't show anything for me like the
wi-fi thing
[Music]
doesn't seem to be a thing on my amazon
it just gives me normal dark colors
[Music]
wait what about this one
an automatic and type no
that's automatic again but like can you
do it like manually that's the question
[Music]
ah
it says no shock
only vibration i want a shock
i want a shock
[Music]
ah well anyway think about it guys maybe
if you have some other suggestions it
doesn't have to be an electric shock you
know it can be something else too i just
don't have any idea what what what it
could be
um if you have an idea feel free to send
it to me on twitter
actually
[Music]
um
the best thing would be if there was
something with an immediate feedback but
worst case we're just gonna put all the
labs together
someone is gonna count them i guess and
then we'll reveal it at the end
and
uh depending on what each person
um is good with or bad with so for
example good as good as punishment would
not be a horror game because she likes
horror games
yeah so then maybe she would have to eat
a really really insanely spicy ramen for
example
or
if someone's really bad with sports like
me i would have to do a ring fit
adventure stream or something but
yeah i guess that's fine i guess that's
fine i i wanted to be a bit more
terrifying than that but
[Music]
wasabi challenge yeah for me honestly
everything works i'm bad with sports i'm
bad with horror i'm bad with spicy food
you can combine it all if i'm the one
that loves the most then you can have me
eat spicy ramen while
doing ring food adventure and watching a
horror movie at the same time while
working out
and eating spicy ramen
i will probably turn into ashes by the
end of the stream and just decide to not
revive anymore because i'm like [\h__\h]
this [\h__\h]
[Music]
i'm out of here no more
that's the ultimate punishment for me
yeah
adore me that's a good idea we'll have
one person eat a [\h__\h] dorian on
stream let's go that's a good idea
that's a good idea that's good
yes yes please i hope that's not me
the good thing is that i'm planning this
collab so i'll be the one
um
i'll have some influence in who gets one
punished
[Music]
make him read embarrassing things no
that's boring not for this one that's
that's fun for like a different stream
but not as a punishment for this it has
to be more
more painful
[Music]
a counter countdown for each laugh
oh you mean
like i mean like a maximum of 10 laps
for example or a lot allowed no but then
because i no that's that doesn't really
work because like i plan out a certain
amount of
um like skits and prepare them all
then
if it all ends before that because i
laughed too much and i would be in
trouble
remote paint is difficult
but i want remote paint i want to
control it with a whole control center
[Music]
i want to decide when to shock my girls
why is that so hard to understand this
is it really so bad that that i want to
shock my gen mates remotely for wi-fi
whenever i desire it whenever i feel
like it
[Music]
i don't see where the problem is
alma could probably help me
alma could probably help him with
technical issues
[Music]
no we'll get it to work eventually like
the worst
um worst case we'll just do the thing
that they all get punishment at the end
or like after the stream in a separate
stream
that will always work
but as i said if you guys have ideas for
an um immediate feedback solution let me
know uh we were reading super chats by
the way
and i want to show you
um because we're talking about the
dreaming tutu
outfits
[Music]
wanted to show you it's
like boring because it looks exactly
like they turned out to look like but i
will show you
my
draft
[Music]
design
yes it looks exactly 101 like what they
ended up being
so that's amazing
i didn't think she would do it so
one-on-one perfectly
oh yeah i think some people don't really
know
like what the [\h__\h] those white socks are
that amma is wearing those are called
loose socks they used to be very popular
with students in japan for their school
uniforms they're like really really long
socks like
i think like they sell them as like 120
centimeters 160 centimeters long socks
and uh they give you this like
this look that they're really loose
and uh girls love to wear them i drew
over the models
yeah and i i thought it would look cute
i like those loose socks they're not so
popular anymore now i think um
do they have pockets no
ankle warmers
i guess it's similar but i wouldn't say
it's the same thing
yeah i guess we could have a full set of
these for all the girls um but for now
it's only for the streaming choo choo
song cover
so
[Music]
thank you i kept the rabbit simple
because
obviously i also didn't have that much
time to
um create it and ring it and all that
and i didn't have much time to design it
i was very busy um but i feel like it
made sense to just have a simple uniform
that's good enough i thought it doesn't
have to be something crazy
detailed uh
yeah like our
normal
outfits i don't know
didn't have to go that crazy
yeah
um
[Music]
adorable thank you
uh it turned out to be
pretty brown in the in the final product
i kind of feel like i wanted it to be a
bit more red but besides that it was
like one-on-one exactly
what i i drew on the model so that was
pretty impressive
oh and this it was missing it here but
she added the
the my feathers she added my feathers
later on very cute though
oh but look overall brown yeah yeah well
i guess it works because it's all about
chocolate and i don't know
i don't know i think brown
is a
nice color sometimes depends on how you
use it
[Music]
underestimated color
anyway
that's just something i
wanted to show you guys
so thank you daisy for the red super
chat that's how i got to that tangent
i wanted to show that
uh right away when i started writing the
super chat but how did i
how
how did it take me so long to get to
this point
[Music]
how did that happen why did i
talk about
the other thing
[Music]
what
what happened
[Music]
i don't get it
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
uh daisy here's the kiss though
dear kiara thank you so much for all you
do i want you to know that you are my
happiness and i love you more than
anything ever you're so cute
you're so cute that's me saying it to
you that's not written in the super chat
love you always forever the amitore song
cover uh was extremely cute the envy was
divine exquisite
your singing was incredibly beautiful as
always i just love your voice so much
you and ame sound absolute absolutely
amazing together i really love
everything about that cover thank you
i do agree we do sound
very very cute together very good
[Music]
um
she
i said this i said this like a few days
before it came out but when i heard her
voice recording
um
i noticed that she was kind of like
maybe maybe subconsciously maybe on
purpose i'm not sure but kind of like
imitating the way i sing because she
asked for a vocal guide from me so i
recorded her parts as well and sent it
over to her to make it easier for her to
also pronounce the japanese words and so
on
um
and and she sang it so
cute oh it's so cute and there's like a
little little verb learning from her
bird mother
how to sing
we're so cute
what did i think of the mv oh
i actually
didn't get any
direct feedback
i think on oh no a little bit i think
on discord but mostly
wait a second i think i
did a little bit
wait a second wait a second wait a
second
[Music]
not much
threaten i'm going to give feedback
maybe i should
save it for post song collab yeah yes we
still have a collab plan so we can talk
about the music we did there as well i
guess
because it was mostly a surprise to her
she didn't see the music video until the
premiere
um
yeah
[Music]
it was quite the reason why i kept it a
surprise is there is actually a reason
i normally would have shared it with her
beforehand
there was a little surprise in there
that i didn't want her to see or know
about
but i feel like now it's melted into the
music video so well that
it probably doesn't really seem like a
surprise
yeah the kids
because i sing this part um in the in
the bridge i think it's a no it's not a
bridge it's the the break part
the slow
quiet part
and the chew
between that and the chorus the last
chorus was not in the lyrics but i added
it and i asked kana
to yeah that's all that's it i asked
kanoru to
have me give ame a kiss on the cheeks in
the exact moment when i say two
and that
that was
i wanted to keep that a surprise but i
don't think
i i i think it's just the whole music
video is so lovey-dovey
that
it makes like no difference
[Music]
it's just
the power of the lovey-dovey is just so
strong
all together it doesn't doesn't stand
out that much
[Music]
yeah
it's like
[Music]
that was all
that was it
but
anyway
it's all good don't worry i think i'm is
just you know the type of person to
not
like
i don't know not talk so much about like
like oh via text you know
i'm not bad or anything
she's just not that talkative via text i
think
she's just very chill yeah and uh
um
but we did talk a little bit yesterday
about some things
[Music]
oh man do the teammate teammates miss
ahmed
she's been gone for a while she's gonna
be gone for a while huh
oh man those poor teammates
they don't have a direct line to ame
like i do
teammates is there anything you want me
to tell her from you
[Music]
now's the time i can deliver your
message to ahmed
[Music]
i'mma's been posting in memories post oh
really
how to get good apex you're gonna ask
her that now from me
i'm a doco
yeah it's so long
the gluten thing she did yesterday was
weird huh
what did she do
that stupid meme the people who still
use it nowadays
i feel like not everyone even knows
where that comes from
[Music]
i feel like some people just picked it
up from others and they're just using it
without knowing the origin do they
[Music]
it is um
i mean now it's now it's fine now it was
funny but i feel like during collabs
where amma is not even part of it
and people are like where is ahmed where
is thomas like
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
i mean i still i still have some part of
me still humors it because it's still
somehow
somehow a little bit funny to me
[Music]
but hmm
not exactly necessary
[Music]
oh
oh my god i need to read some more super
chats but two hours holy [\h__\h] okay okay
i'm gonna go through this now um
speeding a little bit
[Music]
i need
rose may be red salty wart must work
must be wrong today
today
oh should only have sweet just like your
cookies and you thank you gordon ramsay
happy valentine's day to you thank you
for the pinky high fructose corn syrup
there you are in my super chats at least
happy valentine's day carol much love
thank you much love to you too i hope
you had a lovely valentine's day thank
you for the pinky
wait i can't zoom there is a korean
super chat
[Music]
i've been waiting to hear you and i'mma
sing together forever and you didn't
disappoint with dreaming tutu kiana
thank you for the lovely song and music
video and i hope you and kfb have a
wonderful valentine's day thank you
we did have a lovely valentine's day i
mean i got a little bit sappy um in in
the night time
uh on twitter
uh but besides that it was a great day i
had a fun stream
um
yeah i'm fine i'm fine
or was that the following day was that
the day after valentine's day
sometime during that i got a little bit
sappy but
besides that everything was cool and if
you always wanted to hear me and i would
sing together you actually could have um
done that earlier because ame often does
like karaoke streams where she sings
together with um clips of other members
karaoke archives
which is really cute so you could have
already kind of gotten something out of
that but this is the prop the first time
where we probably are mixed together
into one song and yeah i guess it's a
different thing so
understandable
no people say sappy nowadays
yeah
i i learned it i picked it up somewhere
let me use it
thank you daylight night
after most prime donkey channels
sunkishing cruise duncastion for the
pinky happy valentine's day to you and
kfb happy one year anniversary to heart
challenger yeah i still listen to it on
my daily work commute what thank you
also congrats on the new cover with emma
it's cute and everyone did an amazing
job by the way may i have a cookie
did i read this before someone already
asked for cookie before
people say sappy all the time okay good
i saw you sappy there we go
here we go
people still say okay okay thank god
that was someone else oh okay
okay
i guess people just really want those
cookies understandable they
they looked really good i think like
when they were melting in the oven that
was beautiful to look at man
i i'm really interested in like doing
more stuff like more baking now now that
i know how to use my kitchen machine and
stuff and i know how i used to no now no
now that i know how to use the scale
it's uh
very very helpful to know how to use the
scale so
i want to make more stuff
i want to make a cake yeah and i want to
make apple
stores but that's
more cooking than baking i would say
it's missing yeah the one that goes like
that mixes stuff for you
oh
or maybe i also want to make my own
bread
[Music]
i know you can cook bread in a rice
cooker but
i wanted then you still have to make the
the um
the dough for it
outside of the rice cooker right so i
could use the kitchen machine for that
and then put it into the rice cooker i
don't know
homemade bread yeah
[Music]
i i don't know if i said this before but
i remember when i was still living with
my mommy and
there there was a time where um
my mom's
boyfriend
was like really into making um
a bread and and he got this
bread machine and uh yeah it was
smelling so good all the time and it
tasted so good
that fresh self-made bread was heavenly
i will always remember that
what what
yes bread machine yes
[Music]
happy valentine's day kiara i wanted to
tell you that i really appreciate and
admire you your cute sweet hilarious
hard-working and kind heart and just to
name a few traits so naturally you
became my aussie very quickly uh you
know i thought i'd share this on this
share this on a special occasion because
i'm usually a bit less expressive oh
that's okay
thank you for trying you did a good job
thank you for the sweet kind bird thank
you shane i wish you a lovely lovely
valentine's day too always way too late
for that but
maybe maybe i can send these words back
to the past and change your
destiny
hope your valentine's day was great in
any case thank you for always supporting
me you're so sweet thank you
[Music]
thank you
tyson thank you for the pinky as
delicious as i'm sure these cookies will
be they're nowhere near as sweet as our
amazing potential
shut up
happy valentine's day kiana thank you
come on
might be true but yeah
flirty aren't ya a flirty fellow
[Music]
they were amazing though man i was so
proud of those cookies i told everyone
told my friends yo i made the best
cookies ever
i told all my friends about my cookies
so proud like because i usually don't do
stuff like this i don't cook that much i
don't bake at all
yeah i'm just getting started with all
of this
i was really excited
i want to make um
what's the next fruits that's in season
i wonder
what fruit is in season now i want to
make a pie
or like a tart i want to make a tart
like a fruit tart
[\h__\h] dorians cherry
cherry season really
oranges i ate
i ate oranges today or like actually i
didn't eat them i drank them
i today
focus the tangent guys be careful
stop me after this one
today i for the very first time used my
juicer that i had my juice pressed my
fruit press would you say they had
lying standing around for like
months now and have never used before
[Music]
but i realized even
two two big ass oranges
barely even give you
a full glass they only give you like
half a glass of juice am i doing
something wrong
yeah freshly pressed juice is amazing
but
yeah you need so many for one glass so
while i was doing it i was wondering
am i not cheaper off if i just buy
finished orange juice what the
[\h__\h] it is normal okay i thought like
well maybe i'm doing something wrong
yeah free oranges are
maybe a small glass yeah but not like a
tall tumbler tumbler glass
fresh is nicer yeah
that's to be true
or
[Music]
two two three oranges for one guys i
used two
humongous oranges and it was
not enough to fill a glass
by far
it's ridiculous yeah
[Music]
used to fresh squeezed orange juice when
we had orange juice oh well that makes a
lot of sense if you have an orange tree
then you also have a lot of oranges so
yeah that makes sense
what's the taste worth it
um
i've had better
maybe it was the oranges i thought i've
had better freshly pressed orange juice
many times before it was kind of
underwhelming
i should have maybe cooled it too
because it was kind of like room
temperature so it was like um
[Music]
oh i should tell my mom to get to making
to plant an orange tree then
that would be great
because then she can give me oranges
because orange is like the one good
thing about oranges is that they seem to
um
uh
what's the word
they seem to survive much longer than
other fruit um i think it's probably
because of the
the
[Music]
skin
yeah they keep along
they don't expire for a long time
they preserve longer yeah
um
skydo
i'm always so sad when i buy bananas or
or
berries or so and they immediately
die
i hate it
i always regret it
okay okay back to super test
uh delusional dream with angus and
butter is dancing
hey boss i heard you needed me and
can i ask for permission to be the
official kfb stick of butter
i don't need a race this is for the
glory of kfb
hell yeah of course i mean i don't
really understand where the difference
is between your guys's sticks and
our
chunks of butter
i mean i've you guys sent me some images
afterwards on twitter of what sticks of
butter look like and i mean cool but
it's
i don't i i
[Music]
why why is it
i'm a bit confused but it's okay
they look cute the sticks of butter look
cute i'll give you that
yeah we have blocks you guys have
don't i'm not gonna question it anymore
but thank you butter for taking part in
the creation of my cookie making and
you're welcome to become the stick of
butter for kfp
[Music]
yeah they looked cute i don't know the
packaging and the shape it looked cute
okay don't don't ask me
it's not my fault they look cute it's
their fault
so thank you for the pinky and then we
have
[Music]
ah
thanks for the pinky happy valentine's
day kiana i would love for you to be my
valentine's this year hope you can
accept my feelings thanks for everything
you
everything you do to make your chimpkins
happy thank you too
you all are my valentines this year we
were my valentines this year
thank you
very sweet of you thank you for the
lovely generous support i appreciate it
thank you
randall
norris thank you soon serve robert baker
dancing
[Music]
um
hmm
put down your leg and sit straight
thunderstorm harbor line package and
cranes are tasty dancing ultimo mk zero
dancing for the pinky
[Music]
oh wait two pinkies that makes one red
one so valentine's day eh i guess i have
to be flirty now but only for today okay
oh
if you're the sun you can call me the
moon
because your radiant personality and
blinding beauty slaps me right in the
face and makes me smile
i guess you really are like milla that
would make me jude
because you dragged me into this crazy
beautiful adventure and i'm here to
support you till the end
yeah i'm really bad at this anyway
here's the kiss as a repayment for the
last two
[Music]
you're putting a tails off reference in
there is for me as a tails off fan i
guess
um
good because it seems we share interests
yeah it tells of cilia an attempt was
made it was charming definitely thank
you for your love and your support
happy happy valentine's day
kind of late from my side i'm sorry
about that
[Music]
we'll work on those flirtations though
sonic master 2008 duncation stratified
duncan petrichen duncan boohoo 723
duncan
[Music]
um
it was useful mathematics class
oh when i was doing like
uh conversions and stuff
oh you're welcome thank you for watching
my cooking or banking stream thank you i
hope you enjoyed it
thank you
for the pink super chat no no
ah are you here now you're here now
thank you onion
thank you as well
glad you're here now as well it's a
shitty time over there i think do you
not feel sleepy
and janna
please don't force yourself if you feel
sleepy okay this is just me
endlessly
talking and talking and talking and
talking and talking
you're fine okay
2 a.m in korea
oh but did you guys see
uh
my korean bros korean bros
did you see that
on friday free broadcast of unarchived
karaoke
this one this one
it's at
8 p.m
in korea and japan 8 p.m
so you can watch it if you missed it i
sang three korean songs yeah
so please make sure to catch it if you
missed the other one okay okay
okay okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
actually
[Applause]
looks like there's
not so much in the beginning of the week
but like thursday and
and sunday and friday are all good for
and although i mean pokemon is going to
be a long stream so it's starting at 11
p.m is probably
yeah bye for sea
[Music]
a little bit of
staying up late you guys are used to it
aren't you either staying up late for me
or waking up early for me
it's tough being a
kfp member
thank you for the pinky
adding to tk's extra large wallet
tk is me
extra large one oh yeah because i said i
have such a huge wallet i want to get a
smaller one yeah
i have this cute bag that i really like
but my wallet doesn't fit inside
sucks it sucks
[Music]
you need a smaller wallet
and a credit card i don't have a credit
card man
i need a credit card
i'm too lazy to get one
[Music]
i will put that in my wallet then that's
a small percentage of it at least
[Music]
thank you thank you
now is dangerous
oh by the way since this was super chats
about the
where i was also coming up with the idea
of doing a stream where i review
uh and we guess what um who belong who
the
who the belongings belong to
of what's in the bags oh my god can i
form a prep sentence for once like what
the [\h__\h]
you know the idea with the contents of
the bags
of the whole live members a lot of
english members preferably
yeah the first stream
i
immediately uh like before the stream
before that stream that baking stream
i wrote
a plea
and i have not received a single
a single submission so
i think i have to remind them one by one
and ask them
number one
yeah um
not a single one
i don't know if they just forgot it and
we're like looking at it and we're like
i'm gonna send it eventually later or if
they really don't want me to look inside
their bag but
there must be at least like i don't know
three people come on fire people and
then i'm gonna
ask some more from home live japan to
make it worthwhile
i feel like nanaji would definitely
participate in subaru too i think they
would both
send me
what's inside of their
purses and elena would probably do it
too so let's [\h__\h] go
they would do it holoburps are always
there for me i'm sure of it
never would jump on it no doubt i think
so too
i'll try again i did give them like a
big time frame i said yo it doesn't have
to be immediately maybe just in the next
two weeks or so send me something
um maybe i shouldn't have
made it so
maybe i shouldn't have made such a big
time
frame
how many keyboards can they fit in her
bag
they may send it at the last minute no i
think they already forgot which is
understandable there's always a lot
going on i should
i should um
message them all one by one and that
should work
deadlines are helpful for getting things
done definitely
ah
definitely
i'm also really bad when i don't have a
deadline then i like to
push and push and push whatever i have
to do
[Music]
good thing i stay late for tantra's big
chocolate cookie pizza and some mercy
yeah it definitely was very close to a
pizza
thank you chunky chunk i don't think it
was much of an asmr but i'm glad you got
some asmr out of it
thank you soon for watching my stream
hope you enjoyed it
thank you for the big red super chat
jackson fb thank you for the pinky as
your economist i can safely say that
having these cookies on the menu would
be very profitable i totally don't just
want one for me
yeah cause you guys if you work at cafe
you can eat for lunch and for dinner
like in between you breaks whatever is
on the kfp menu right
so i know i know you guys want those
cookies
i know you want them
it's understandable
if if i had something like that at work
i would eat it all the time too i think
until i get sick of it but that would
take some time
breaks
eh
no no who said anything about eating
your friends i said you can eat what's
on the menu
i didn't say you can eat your friends
and your coworkers no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no what the hell guys are so weird and
confused chickens
sasuka
for the pinky tanjoy is orange chickens
are fake i cannot rhyme so i make it
quick oh
valentines are here red and bright
but they still pale before phoenix night
her challenger became one year old a
song made of sweet sound of pure
gold wow
i'm impressed dad wait there's more wait
but wait there's more now we dream of
choo choos all day and night thank you
and ahmed for making this day a delight
i should end it here my brain is fried
uh chicken feet tumbleweed countryside
[Music]
i love dad
i love i love that
you're a [\h__\h] poet
yo i want to give you back the money you
you paid for that super chat because i
feel like i need to tip you for that
[Music]
orange chickens are fake i cannot rhyme
so i make it quick valentines are here
red and bright but they still pale
before phoenix mine heart challenge
became one year old a song made of
sweets and a few gold now we dream of
choo choos all day and night thank you
and ahmed for making this day a delight
i should end it here my brightness right
uh chicken feet tumbleweed country sign
chevy bang
[Music]
it sounds beautiful both as a poem and
as a wrap thank you and slavic fellow
you have a talent
oh my god did i just what did it really
have so many super chats or did i just
waste an insane amount of time
with tangents which one is it
why did it take me so much time
next up is
this one
might have been both yeah
[Music]
okay
for this i'm going to go faster i think
cocoon
looking for the top duncan
[Music]
yeah um you know what that that has been
very helpful um your quote retreats have
been very helpful with stuff that i
missed and yeah because
um people barely use the japanese
hashtag these days like even japanese
artists use the english one i've kind of
stopped you looking at it regularly so
if you have the time to quote retweet
them
if you think i didn't see them yet
it's been very helpful so thank you for
that looking for the top thank you soon
petruchen dangashin kakun dakshan for
the pinky i'm string parasite thanks to
you oh
yeah yeah good song you made me addicted
to this song wouldn't it be amazing if
someone were to cover this song man what
a dream by the way totally unrelated
question are you planning to make more
cover songs this year when a guy yes yes
yes
actually me and dana
already decided on the song now
pretty much pretty much decided yeah
um
because we wanted to do or i wanted to
do magnet with her originally but can't
do that song
for
copyright reasons i guess
um but we've we've figured out
which song to do and
i decided to put a special twist to it
so
yeah but but it's still going to take a
long time because right now
i'm working on the on an original song
and the thing with nineteen is coming
out maybe next month and then i have um
another song cover coming out
probably also next month but i need to
time it so that it doesn't clash with
the sun covered with energy
um so that's
actually two sun covers
one cordable and one alone
and then i already also have something
and another
solo sound cover in my mind
that i wanna do
um but i'm not sure when to release it
[Music]
that one is kind of open
up in the air right now and then there's
the one overlaying it so we're thinking
i was saying we should just release it
whenever we go on that vacation so that
we have something to fill up the days
where we're gone
um
yes but yeah um there there's a lot of
music recently that i wanted to cover so
uh
you guys are gonna have a lot of song
covers coming from my side in
the first uh half of this year
this is not mega man music this is a
eurobeat version of my first original
song he no tony
to motivate me to read faster
hi
[Music]
i know
would be more motivated if i played it
at two times speed
that is interesting
waking up early fact number one thank
you [\h__\h] and true for a sec thank you
for the red super chat
tanja i'm finally old enough to work
illegally oh but i don't wanna maybe
hide please
stop it
[Applause]
maybe hypothetically speaking someone
capable of drugs advice can be useful
for you oh you know a very good german
word here
all needed precautions will be taken up
will be taken to prevent
oh my god any damage to the kfb image of
course
what do you mean what do you mean you're
old enough
legally to work
did you turn like 18 or something or 21
or something or do you mean your
membership has reached a certain point
[Music]
did you have a birthday
too loud sorry
not to
to work
what is the legal age to work
i don't even know that
[Music]
i think you're in the chat so i'm
waiting for the answer
[Music]
i don't see you
i don't see forzak answering my question
if it was your birthday you got to be
more clear about that i want to wish you
a happy birthday
[Music]
where would he go
where did he go
[Music]
this is your birthday i saw you in the
chat just a moment ago
sneeze for super okay
a bag
where's that
excuse me
is that better
sepa is trying to notice you
boss is trying to notice you
we've lost him guys
lost him
where'd you go
where'd you
go am i blind i really don't see him in
the chat
[Music]
well if it was your birthday then happy
birthday if it was not then i guess not
uh
if you if it is you if it was your
birthday then you're welcome to tell me
later on and i'll sing you a belated
happy birthday but i'm not gonna sing it
if i don't know for sure
thank you voice for the rest of the chat
i'm waiting for you to come back i'm
waiting
thank you
where did you learn that german word
though
it's a good word
surprised you know it
stratis
and squiggly mustache
pirate chicken boss i'm going to kidnap
i mean borrow some of your employees so
i can cover them in chocolate as the
late valentine's gift for mama inaudible
[Music]
did he really do that
kidnapping i do not take lightly so
if you really did that then
by the end of the day you might
be lacking
one or two hands
and i'm being nice here because i first
was about to uh to take your head
so
but i think the right punishment for
thieves is
cutting off their hands
back in medieval times
so i think i need to chop your but but
well if it's a takodachi they don't have
hands so i guess i have to take your
head
i shall take your head
if you really stole a chicken
is a
huge crime that cannot be forgiven
the trauma that you must have caused to
these chickens even if they may have
forgotten it five minutes later
it is still traumatic traumatic for the
first five minutes so
i will not forgive the pain that you
caused to my chickens
so i didn't even know about this super
chat it came like days ago
and yesterday i mentioned that we were
just gonna
go on another war with uh with the taco
duchy so i guess i just kind of felt
that this was coming
we have short-term memory
memory do you i guess you have forgotten
about it yeah
[Music]
my lovely alzheimer chickens
yeah you have birth brains
what did we forget about
you forgot that you forgot something
that's the worst thing
oh my god that happened we're watching
arrested development and
job
job job job
he's just so hilarious how he
he takes this
forgets something pale
because he needs to forget something
but wait how i can't even explain it
anymore i forgot but if you watch
watched arrested development you will
understand it was really funny
it was so funny
i can't i can't explain
[Music]
but he keeps on going back
because he i think he forgot that he
took it
i think that was
the problem i forgot i forgot what i
forgot what it was about
i just know it was so funny i forgot the
the
interesting part
yeah he gets stuck in a loop it's so
funny
ah
so good but i also started re-watching
um the marvelous mrs maisel because the
new episodes are out and i watched i
started watching the first few seconds
of it and then i was like
when did i last watch this show maybe it
would be a good idea to revisit
the first seasons and so i did do that
and it was a good idea it feels very
fresh to me right now
that way
um because now it's not even like all
the new episodes are out yet they're
releasing them
weekly i think
so until i'm done
re-watching
the show again
they might have all the episodes out
hopefully
[Music]
any reason why it's easier for you to
rewatch shows and replay games
[Music]
i think for games
i would
um
have
a harder time forgetting
what it was all about
than with tv shows like i feel like for
tv shows
when i rewatch them when i have a lot of
time in between the last time i
rewatched it
i
uh quickly
not quickly but like maybe if there's
like a year in between
of me watching a tv show
then i forgot
[Music]
not everything but like roughly what the
show was about
no the other way around i remember
roughly what the show was about but i
forget the details so it's good to
rewatch it but for games i feel like
i feel like it just doesn't have the
same
effect am i the only one here am i the
only one
i feel you there okay
yeah there might also be the passive
versus active aspect that might be it
too i don't know i just don't feel like
replaying games
especially
jrpgs because like i already know the
twist of the story and so on
i mean i might know that for tv shows as
well but
it doesn't
i don't know
if it's for example if it's a long show
like seinfeld or friends or whatever
or scrubs or so
because they have a million seasons i
actually do often forget the twist of
certain episodes and so on and how
exactly it went down so it makes sense
to rewatch it it actually feels like
sometimes a very fresh experience
[Music]
yeah it depends on the game like
something like i don't know
minecraft obviously you can play over
and over and over again
and um i think
i think something like pokemon
if it's been like 10 years or so i
wouldn't mind replaying pokemon
or wind waker hey hey hey it doesn't
always apply i did say i want to play
wind waker again on stream
because wind waker
is just very special to me
so it gets a
special excuse a pass
because you like rpgs if you like
shorter games it might be different
maybe yeah because i feel like a shorter
game would also be
more forgettable
oh i did say the thing about the wii u
store but you're welcome to remind me
again when it actually happens but you
can still buy physical games right so
yeah
oh my god i need to read super jets
[Music]
i'm british thank you so much for your
british boys
really you thanking me
you're welcome british friends
second thank you soon
okay thank you
[Music]
that is one sassy goodra oh the [\h__\h]
goodra that didn't let me catch it
stupid [\h__\h] good job make me so mad
wasted my time
so much
unbelievable
[Music]
british here too we love it
oh wow thank you so much for liking my
beautiful accent mate
oh
we have a school lesson here fun fact
cookie does oh i already read this one
during the game play cookie dough's name
probably comes from kokito
which means i think therefore i am
originally said by this this character
it means something similar to that whole
you can only prove your own existence
thing she was going on about um
thank you again
i found that very very interesting and
it reminded me of something and i still
can't think of it oh [\h__\h] sake
okay and then we have a lot of blessing
super jets duncan
[Music]
yeah it's a similar super chat from
previous stream
thank you
thank you soon
w
[Music]
and then there's flush chats lots of
flush cuts
i think tai chi sends a red super chat
in between the flush chats
thank you
thai many words indeed
uh
what happened here
was i just started in an idol meeting
vivi cordanga soon
okay thank you
this was when i was ignoring the youtube
chat because you guys were mean
dominique
[Music]
that sounds like so much oh my god
are you sure that's correct youtube
17 oh my god
holy [\h__\h]
18 months will be in seven days oh
wait that's uh
one and a half years
wow
one and a half years of membership
[Music]
hello members
damn
you weren't there when i was talking
about you also four sack is four sec
back
i'm keeping track i have a list of all
the chickens that should be here
and checking if you guys are here
attendance list
i wish oh there you are
what do you mean i wish so was it your
birthday or what
you need to you you need to clear up my
confusion
[Music]
i have so many cat hairs on my nose
i ate those spoons
wait i still don't see an answer
am i too intimidating
[Music]
i'm i'm like looking at the chat 24 7
right now
i just i don't think i'm missing it
maybe i'm too intimidated
[Music]
potential
did you guys see the video kinda would
remain
i had a feeling he might make something
out of my kpop singings
singing tries yesterday
i can't [\h__\h] speak english give me a
[\h__\h]
book with words in it
give me a vocabulary book
oh my god
sometimes i just
just can't a dictionary that's it
i know that word but in this very moment
i couldn't think of it
i mean every book has words in it i
think
not every okay not every book but most
books have words in it i want the one
that's a dictionary
but you guys know me so well that you
knew what i meant
wonderful lovely
lovely
we're just in sync now
we should make a boy band
real super chats no not now no no i'm
too many i i'm
i'm wasting so much time
[Music]
potential i have to leave for work but
thank you so much for the stream i had a
blast and i wish you the best of luck in
the final quests of this game can't wait
to see what your party looks like by the
end anyway take care i love you thank
you
yeah last time we successfully finished
like that that one part of the story but
yeah um we will continue it this week
supposedly but i will move it if i don't
find time
to um
you know
um do the prep work necessary
if if i don't have enough time then i'll
move it to the following week
and then we'll just play something else
instead that's my plan
um
[Music]
thank you for your understanding
yeah because i need a full i heard that
i need a full pokedex and
to be honest i am pretty busy this week
so i'm not sure if i can really do it
but we're just gonna try
i always have a pokemon trading session
that is the last resort i guess
yeah
the last resort
thank you though for the support also
glad to see you here today as well thank
you for watching my streams i appreciate
the support thank you soon for the pinky
i'm gonna skip the sneeze chats thank
you
and cruise thank you
thank you so
uh much is this
[Music]
i sneezed so much apparently
i'm gonna skip those because i am
wasting so much time when did the
purpose run out oh i can't say
um details like that but
oh right wait that's why i can't oh
[Music]
anyway i'll i'll i will i will i will i
will finish it we
we will we will we will we will stream
it on sunday
[Music]
never mind dad never mind
i will do it on sunday so if i don't
have enough time to prepare then we will
have to have a training session
yup
yup i guess so no i didn't forget i
didn't forget i actually knew i was
aware of it but i forgot for this very
moment but i wasn't aware of it before
yeah yeah it's gonna be fine
jacob 47 else thank you how far sana
by the way
with the story
has she been streaming pokemon lately
is summer gonna be okay
i know she's been taking a lot of time
uh on stream
i guess she does a lot of side quests on
stream
she hasn't been streaming at all oh man
that means she's probably not gonna
finish pokemon
on stream huh that's sad because she
loves pokemon so much
oh man
no man
maybe maybe maybe she comes back in the
last three days or so
and does like 24 hour streams of pokemon
that way she could make it
[Music]
from the future i hope you rested well
after your pokemon stream
i think i did i don't even remember
anymore
did i rest well
it's honestly now been way too long
i feel gore i think i did thank you for
worrying about future kiwawa dragonfire
so sweet so considerate of you
wow
the
[Music]
thank you for the pinky for two thank
you saying alf
and midazen thank you
not yet though not today not now
vivi cordangischen celebrian speaks
duncan daisy
off the table and another one bites the
dust
goodbye you go to the super chat
graveyard i never want to see you again
never
and now we have a lot of collabs super
chat so it shouldn't be that much but
i'm gonna take a fruit candy one of my
normal ones not the not the miracle one
i i want to use up the normal ones
for now
i'm fine
okay can i wash my nose like there's so
much cat hairs on my hands and my nose
and everywhere like in the air and on my
pants and on my t-shirt and everything
thanks for the membership welcome
and also that other member for renewing
your membership beautiful
beautiful profile picture
i'm gonna wash my nose
takes one second brb maybe i'll i'll
cuddle a cat before i wash my nose
before before
[Music]
okay
i gave chunkers some
head scratches and and chin scratches
she's losing so much fur it's crazy
[Music]
my cats are sleeping one is sleeping
in a cardboard box that's junkers
and one is sleeping in my closet in my
underwear
compartment
it's it's perfect because it's like like
a
like a cat bed it's like a hole
yes
make an extra cat with excess flare
i already did juxta jokes on you
i have three cats now
bamboozled
the great filmmakers
wait no no no i write those
and we're at monopoly now
um
[Music]
i want to say
i am
i do feel bad about
how i got too
a little bit too emotional at the end
there
or too salty
um
but
uh
i i actually
i i got something for a moment but then
i was like
not sure
what to do afterwards because i i didn't
want to like
um
like
because because the problem is like the
stream
uh
not the stream but like i'm it's been
streamed on my channel
but when i'm the first one
to
be kicked out of the game i'm i wasn't
sure like
what
how do i continue
uh
what
yeah
um
[Music]
uh
supposed to be salty oh i think i think
when monopoly is being played in real
life that uh
everyone gets very salty except for the
person who wins i think that is pretty
normal but um
yeah
um
[Music]
anyway we're all good i'm just uh
i want to play more monopoly
uh and and try next time to first of all
not lose and second of all if i lose i
will do my best to
um handle the situation differently
it was a lot of fun up to that point
though i think i think
i think so i had a lot of fun
[Music]
mm-hmm
so i want to play more monopoly but
uh
i guess i uh not immediately i think um
i don't want to do it like every [\h__\h]
week i want it to be maybe next month or
so
another monopoly collab
it was very interesting to see
how everything was falling apart though
yeah
i haven't played monopolies in such a
long time like
i
completely
forgot how this game plays out at the
end
[Laughter]
it was quite beautiful to see everything
fall apart there
we had
we we stood no chance at all
none of us stood a chance
yeah i think i was already like
extremely unlucky in the beginning for
uh going last and then
in in after me going last when everyone
already had properties i land on someone
else's property like my first few turns
were pretty unlucky i think especially
the first one
[Music]
yeah i thought so too
and
as it might sound
weird but i think that already kind of
set things in place there
yeah i am
but don't worry i want to play monopoly
again
i will play monopoly again
there is no possible chance
your timeout what
there is no possible chance that i will
be
fourth place
two times in a row right right maybe
third place but
i can't be fourth place two times in a
row
let's see i can't be fourth place if i
invite a total of five people
[Music]
i mean i could still be morphing
but the worst i could be is fifth place
then
doesn't make it better what if i just
play monopoly
with two other people then the worst i
could be is food
[Music]
um i was thinking about that too but
that's just
it sounds like fun if the rounds were
like shorter you know
because if i play with you guys
for with the same let's say five people
for three hours i feel like it it barely
gives other people a chance to
join
aki senpai does that though you can try
to join one of aki senpai's monopoly
games
yeah the games take too long however
there are other rules that you can
choose
and i want to look into those and see if
they are more fun
[Music]
i thought it was fun i thought it was a
fun collab definitely
i want to play more i'm just sorry that
i
reacted like that at the end i couldn't
hold back okay
i was trying but then the more i tried
the more i struggled
[Music]
sorry about that guys
i do i do see my um i do see the problem
[Music]
bona's grandma
nah
didn't get to talk to them yet maybe one
day
if i visit america
[Music]
gotta do a tour through america
so uh did i read this chunky chunk thank
you for the red super chat will there be
any friendship left after the stream or
will this ignite the first holo ian war
oh i think we're good we're good we're
good we there are
um
no friendships
that have been destroyed
wait that's a weird way to phrase it no
friendships have been destroyed we're
all good it was just a game
yeah
maybe in the beginning
some salty feelings but it's all good
it's just a [\h__\h] game
there's no way that a game like this can
destroy
the bond of a generation
yes
[Music]
so thank you
for watching mwah very shy cocoon
thanks for the pinky
hi um i uh so you see um i like you okay
bye okay
aren't you always shy
thank you soon
bjorn duncan freeze the frog duncan
russell oh dingles thank you little
pinky
is this where i place the bed my money's
on the bird
thank you
is the money on me for me losing or for
me winning because i thought it was um
very funny don't worry guys i
i'm not um
i'm not mad at you guys or anything i
just find it very
funny how you guys you even you guys
don't vote for me to win in nepal
you don't even bet on me winning like i
get it because until now i've been
unlucky in these type of games but
but if it's about luck how can you be so
sure that i'll be the one losing if it's
just a game about luck guys i voted for
you thank you
my favorite for you thank you
thank you
yeah they did underestimate kuda yeah
they definitely did
everything everyone thought uh ina would
win and maybe fauna it makes no sense
but
it's just
people and their biases i guess
but i like
see
i guess i i have to respect you guys
for being honest
um
you vote for what you really believe and
not for
[Applause]
for the sake of
just voting for your aussie you know
so
i guess i raised my chickens truthfully
and yes
and i'm so proud of you guys for doing
that that i would like you uh to publish
a list of who voted against me and who
had voted for me just so that i
can you know
um honor the
the the truthfulness
and the honesty
of the chickens who can't
just because of that
[Laughter]
no
my jokes on you i already have a list
anyway
[Music]
let's read more super chats
tim tracy
[Music]
john smith
daisy
[Music]
it doesn't matter if you were right or
not
i'm
i'm so proud of you daisy come here come
here let me show you how proud i am of
you
come here
won't you come on over
[Music]
i made a big hole in your back you might
want to go to the hospital
that was good
[Music]
so many of the super chat people are
betting on me
[Music]
sweet good to see nietzsche
i still think chad is gonna win but i
have faith in the short never doubt my
sweet tattle
thank you for the pinky but i'm so
confused when
[Music]
you think chat is gonna win
who is
[Laughter]
and taco is probably a typo for taco
[Music]
why would chat win
i mean
[Music]
chad wins by watching
potato
my sweet potato
well niche in any case um you had faith
in the short and it was um
it was good that you had faith in the
show
one of the few people who had faith in
the shark
[Music]
and tp thank you for the pinkie i bet on
tension winning the phoenix lux
shouldn't be as underestimated
i am quite lucky in other games like
minecraft for example
uh
but
these kind of games i don't know why
i don't know why i'm so
unlucky
[Music]
weird isn't it
single player look
yeah i guess so i feel like i used to
have more luck than these days i used it
all up in the first season of
takanashikiya at hello live english
[Music]
can you see
rigged [\h__\h] ring man
the ping it's the thing
you used all of your luck when you
captured pocket with one rabbit bowl for
example yeah
oh man
oh man dice rolls they [\h__\h] the dices
i was it was crazy though when i was
playing the game off screen i said this
in the beginning of the collab but i had
eighty percent of my roles were double
uh
double dices thingies
and then in the actual collab i mean
there were definitely times where i was
so broke that i didn't want to
move anymore but if i had all these
double rolls in the beginning then i
think it would have helped me buy more
houses right in the beginning because i
feel like um
was it kuda or one of the others who had
indeed a lot of
doubles right in the beginning and were
able to buy a lot of [\h__\h] while i was
just having shitty rolls all the time
[Music]
that was a thing too why did i have so
many doubles in practice when i was
playing against myself
ridiculous
[Music]
was the rate somehow higher for double
rolls when you play
privately on
on your switch then
versus online play
hmm
[Music]
everyone dodged their properties
really was it that
bad for inna
[Music]
i loved how everyone was
feeling the terror
of the creation of shock road though
that was too real everyone was like
terrified of
going to the shark road and making the
shark road bigger than it already was
[Music]
yeah
bathroom security thank you and coy
thank you for the pinky tentacle sending
support to our priestess hope everything
will everyone has fun
[Music]
uh i don't know if she saw that but she
did have
good luck actually coming in second
not bad
not bad she was standing strong
for a long time so
maybe it was your support quickly that
helped her through it
thank you for believing in me and i'm
sorry for disappointing your your
support man
thank you don't no one i will
i will remember that
oh well
man
justin fine duncan brown
sushi
fanatic function
fanatic not feminist fanatics fanatic
evidence called duncan and that's duncan
alexandrian the diamond double jones
dancing for the pinkies
[Music]
don't worry kia i wonder for you even
though your luck may be terrible and you
have a bad track record for party games
i'm 100
sure you've got this
oh i see i see what you smuggled in
there
but you still voted for me even though
you didn't quite believe that i would
yeah win but thank you
it's all good though
i'm just joking guys you can vote for
whatever the hell you want because in
the end it doesn't matter as we've seen
in the poll
it doesn't matter
[Music]
it doesn't matter whoever has the most
luck wins
and maybe a little bit of knowledge
about monopoly
i know that game
i don't think i've played it before but
i am aware of that game um
[Music]
chicken nuggets uh guys
guys
[Music]
serve yourself to me with some sweet and
sour sauce please
um please
[Music]
why is there not a bucket with chicken
nuggets on my desk at all times and i
prefer chicken nuggets over chicken
wings by the way
[Music]
how about you guys
same
wings
same wings
same wings same same same ring
tenderloins wings wings
[Music]
drumstick vines
that was not an option
wings swings
wings lots of wings
i just feel like nuggets are easier to
eat
so the experience of eating is just
more enjoyable to me
i generally don't like eating things
with a bone in it you know because uh
yeah i don't like
eating
all the weird looking parts sometimes
there's weird looking parts
so i just roughly eat around the bone
but i never really get to the bone part
i'm always amazed when i go out eating
with people and they order like chicken
wings or something like that and and
then they really literally
just leave the bone
it's like
wow your dog amazing
just like callie
[Music]
did she say that
did she say that interesting
[Music]
it's kind of weird i know but that's
just how it is okay
[Music]
oh
you're definitely boneless let's go
[Music]
thank you chick i am a chick duncan
avraham was done putting together
around
the cute master dance the property names
are based on the street names in
atlantic city
nj there is also some attractions on the
boardwalk which includes a carnival
stand called stinky feed you mean
if the language
that is chosen is american english
because nj stands for new jersey right
that's not
that's not england is it that's america
though
yeah yeah yeah yeah
because i chose british english just for
fun i don't know i didn't think it would
have an impact on the map for some
reason i didn't realize
so my map was differently different from
theirs
now i'm curious what the names would be
if i chose german if it would be maybe
like
maybe they would do berlin because it's
the capital of germany
[Music]
and i probably would not really know any
of the street names because i have been
to berlin a few times but
i don't really know much about berlin
streets and popular stations and all
that
oh my god that came out of nowhere
i do remember those names
oh there's an austrian version really
i wonder if i've ever seen that before
thank you
[Music]
i heard you need rent will this help
darn those loan sharks
oh jesus
i appreciate the fun i really really do
thank you i should play monopoly with
you maybe maybe you would be kind to me
and let me win
without without making me notice that
you let me win
give me the impression that you tried
thank you it's
it didn't help much but
the thought
it really touches my heart thank you
jesus
and wings cbd
drive seven eight nine thank you
only thank you
soon
[Music]
literally just someone slamming their
head on their keyboard name thank you
chris cheese man danke garen of kfb
dance
[Music]
don't worry
you want in our hearts
wow
love you
no one thank you
[Music]
so sweet
did i did i win you in your hearts and
did i win your hearts
did i
i hope so
[Music]
thank you
thank you very much
[Music]
for watching
we're getting there guys we're getting
there
[Music]
i shouldn't have tangented so much in
the beginning i
i feel very tired but it's okay
maybe i'm getting too old for this maybe
that's why i'm so
exhausted
[Music]
yeah
okay next up
we have the ferret
from snail and super jacks
yes
so many of you guys said that that was
the best
whole talk ever i mean
people kind of say that
every time but you also every time say
this one for real
no i mean it i mean this is real i know
i always say it but this was the best
episode
[Music]
obligatory
for real this time actually you always
say that you say that you mean that you
lied to me the previous times but or
just it keeps on topping itself right
yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh
[Music]
actually
um i asked for the assembly um to
if she wants to do that singing part as
well and originally she considered it
um i feel like it would have been better
even better if we would have had that
singing section but
um
she kind of uh then decided to
not do it after all because um
she
couldn't find
or think of a good
[Music]
video to play
in the background of you know i usually
have like a music video or so playing in
the background but there is no full
music video for her original song
smiling go so i said how about a live
performance i did that before too and
but then she was like ah
nah
there's nothing proper and i'll i'll
perform it on the following day in 3d in
my new outfit anyway so
yeah let's just not do it so
why are you blushing the question is why
are you not flashing why are you not
blushing
anyway
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
have been even better with a musical
performance but but it's okay she had a
whole
pretty
um live concert
the following day which i hope you all
saw because it was great
ah she did sing
she did sing some beethoven though yeah
yeah yeah the european anthem
that was great
i can sing that one too
i think
not now though not now i'm tired
it was so cute i said that i said it
before but it was so cute with shitake
and construction so i was so cute
you're so far behind girlfriend
what you've been up to
but it's okay that's not that far behind
monopoly is not that far going
okay let's read whole talk super chat
[Music]
um
i don't remember what you mean
[Music]
i showed up for hold up but the bank has
foreclosed
my branch and isn't letting anyone in is
it true you mortgaged kfb japan to pay
off monopoly debts it's fun our
attention now no
no no don't worry moto-san i would never
never never never give kfp to a
vegetarian
no that is the last thing not even the
last thing i would i would never
never [\h__\h] do that
can't give it to a vegetarian they don't
know what they're doing they'll turn it
into
she'll turn it into
a vegetarian
kfb kiara no not my name will be gone
too probably it will be
uh pranas vegetarian
[Music]
burgers so that will be
f
v
b
that just sounds
like like a full spot for a
[Music]
sounds like a soccer um thing in germany
i feel like i heard that before
no no no no no no i mean of course
everything's already vegan
and the chicken is already vegan no yeah
of course fauna would be perfect to take
over kfp and i i i sorry i got confused
i got confused i got confused
didn't mean it like that
yeah
uh
anyway
thank you for the red super chat
don't worry though your job is safe
everything is good you can continue
working
please continue working i need you to do
your job
for the pinky
[Music]
i had one birthday oh
i guess i did my thai curry yeah yeah
yeah i think it it tasted so good and it
looks good too um but
you know how i tweeted out
that i forgot to put in broccoli
and then
i got a lot of
tweets
[Music]
yelling at me that first of all berkeley
in thai curry is unthinkable and second
of all
that what i made is not thai curry
the
thai
uh curry
[Music]
uh
what do you call the people who know
wine
uh i forgot
apparently i'm very the police okay that
works too the thai curry police
tried to arrest me
and i have to say
well
maybe
it's not 100
the exact ingredients that you guys use
and maybe it's not spicy although i
didn't say that they would go crazy if
they knew that my thai curry is
not spicy at all
they would kill me
but it's still a thai curry
because i used thai curry uh powder and
thai curry paste okay and most of the
ingredients i would say are still very
much
thai curry
okay and i just like to customize it a
little bit
the broccoli just because i like
broccoli and i thought it fits well i've
i've had like a lot of different
variations of thai curry and i know it
might sound scandalous but i've had thai
karu thai curry with mango and thai
curry with pineapple and all the way all
that kind of stuff it might sound weird
but it tasted really good it's just you
know a little bit of a
customization adding uh
veggies that you like
or fruit even that you like
apparently serious savory is business i
only really said thai curry to
make a difference between you know
japanese curry
or
well
thai curry and indian curry
to give you a rough
category of what
i
tried to make
because there is certain bases
that like if like if i were to if i
tried to make an indian curry would
taste completely indifferent same with
the same with
uh a japanese curry japanese curry is
like a whole different
world
to me
[Music]
what is different well have you never
eaten japanese curry before
i used to dislike japanese curry because
the taste was so crazy different
but now i love it
now i love it well yeah
yes
whatever the maybe the
you couldn't even see like what exactly
i put into that curry and it's not like
i
wrote it on
in the tweet
[Music]
and yet and yet apparently this was
definitely not a thai curry well how do
you know what exactly i put in there huh
huh how do you even know
but okay whatever whatever the [\h__\h] you
say
[Music]
basically i was just trying to
categorize my curry because indian curry
would be different japanese curry would
be different too
these the thai curry police i'm sorry
but
you should never eat
thai curry in europe then because i
guess you're gonna have to arrest
everyone
you're not gonna be happy with the way
europe makes thai curry
i think
i can assure you my thai curry tasted
really good you would you would like it
if you wouldn't think about the fact
that it's thai curry maybe
if you would just see it as a separate
dish
maybe then you could accept it
[Music]
and
me making it not spicy is just a
personal preference because i really
can't eat spicy food
besides that i think a lot of people
in europe make thai curry spicy anyway
it's just me i really can't eat spicy
food
yeah if i'm cooking just for myself then
why would i make myself suffer
[Music]
brandon
for the pinky okay i'm back thanks for
waiting
welcome back
[Music]
welcome back patrick duncas
thank you
all right
holo talk once again back
on its feet
next episode should be um
the the week after this one
so we're going fast we're going at the
originally intended
pace
yes
i used to slow down a little bit but
yeah next episode is gonna be
next week
yeah
guess guess guess guess
[Music]
pretend
buying songs in the infinite tangent
feedback loop glory to kfp oh yeah
[Music]
well we had
the longest episode ever the longest
whole talk episode
ever because
both me and her
i was holding back a lot it was mostly
her this time but still dangerous to put
me in the same spot
she was tangenting a lot and i was
sometimes accidentally supporting that
yeah i couldn't even fully translate and
she would start a new tangent
it feels very familiar
yeah
we
had so much
to talk about
it's like that as well off screen like
it's just like we can endlessly
endlessly dig for tangents
together
[Music]
there is no end to it it's beautiful
it's beautiful generally but the whole
talk
i needed to
uh hold her back because otherwise
otherwise
it would have been way way way too long
and a whole top needs to have a system
okay i know we're usually not part of
your system but whole talk
i need i need it to be organized okay
and
and all that tangent thing really
exhausted me i was so
done after that whole talk episode
because i need to stay really really
focused you know
when i do a whole talk
i'm very very concentrated when i do
that
it was really exhausting
yeah
need a podcast of you too
a podcast huh
i don't
i think i said this before but i don't
see it i don't quite understand where
the difference is between
um a podcast like you know cali has been
doing it or coulda did it with ahmed
um
[Music]
compared to this stream right now how is
this not a podcast if that's a podcast
i
cuz like the way i know podcasts was you
know on the radio you can't see
uh what's going on but you can like
listen in it's like a radio show
and they chit chat about all kinds of
topics but then
uh putting video to it for me takes away
the podcast
[Music]
i aspect this is designed to be watched
later now i have ah
[Music]
very structured you all bring in topics
ah
[Music]
so um i see okay i guess so
hold on
[Music]
well then almost anything could be a
podcast
if it just needs to be structured
almost all of my streams are podcasts
then
should i name it podcast do you guys
think it would be more popular then
i feel like people
like the word podcast
it kind of brings in
new people i feel like
[Music]
maybe all of my streams for now and
should be podcast i'll write next
podcast instead of next stream on my
twitter
yes
please call it datadon no i will not if
i were a japanese speaking streamer then
i would i totally would
but i i i feel um
kind of cringy using
the word that's done
to
um
uh
describe a chit chat stream but then
again i wish we had a better word for
that in english because i don't like the
english choices of words that we have
for this genre of stream
i wish there was one that had such an
impact and such a ring to it as that's
done has because chit chat just
gets close to it
but not quite and free talk i like even
less because i think free talk sounds
like a
[\h__\h] google translated robot word to
me i hate that word
it's like did you really not have any
better word for that
english language
free talk really
that's what it's gonna be
[Music]
if if i had to choose then i would say
chit chat if anything but
open top yeah fine but it just doesn't
sound as good as that to them but then
again i don't want to use that song
because it's a different language and
people who don't speak japanese will not
understand what it means and you'll have
to one by one explain it to
them discussion no that doesn't work now
invent your own word now
[Music]
i can't
english language has
not enough proper words for some things
[Music]
do we have a proper word for that in
in german let me think chat's done is
like a
we have a proper word in german for that
[Music]
love
um
[Music]
coffee round is kind of a cute word for
that i feel like even if you don't drink
coffee
tea time
anyway whatever it just doesn't work it
just does not work
[Music]
on the marshmallows
um
[Music]
sorry guys my energy is
not here today i thought it would come
eventually but it just doesn't come
i am a cheat damn cushions at 17b
[Music]
m
and cute anime girls are the best
dancers in yamadas
noob froggy
[Music]
no it was not set by our kitten it was
death here
best whole talk so far i always love
your chemistry with flair this was less
of an interview and more of a job done
collab can't wait to have more flair
tony thank you soon
yeah we just ever since that little
minecraft collab that we had um
spontaneously
we've just been
always hitting it off well we just have
uh
this is what happens when you put two
people together who like to talk a lot
and tangent a lot
[Music]
yes
i really enjoy that it's like um
this type of
chemistry i don't
think
i really have with anyone in whole life
english
we have different kind of chemistries
but this one where where
we could talk endlessly endlessly
without even trying
i don't really think i i have it in all
live english at least not that not
naturally like
for for when i talk with flair i don't
even have to try
it's like a fourth and back forth and
back forth and back
and for
the whole live english like we we still
managed to have
conversations and stuff and fun streams
but i feel like i need to
try harder
yeah japanese members are very very very
chatty he
makes it very easy to have a
conversation on the stream
they are very chatty and and they have
this tsukumi and bokeh thing going on
that
um
i feel like everyone finds the their
role
in
[Music]
i not sure which one i am though but it
just happens naturally everyone
there's always someone who becomes
excited me and someone who becomes the
bucket
you make it seem so effortless yeah yeah
yeah
i'm both yeah it depends on who i am
with
i think when i'm with
well i have english i'm mostly that
tsukumi and when i'm with whole life
japan i sometimes turn into bukit
[Music]
so yeah i would love to collab with for
there again definitely
next time perhaps on her channel because
the last two ones were on my channel so
maybe on hers next
46 thank you soon spanking time thank
you for the reservation best holo
tangent ever so cute and funny flair is
wonderful and i love your chemistry
thank you
thank you thank you i had fun being with
her glad you enjoyed this holo talk or
holo tangent
thank you
so
much function fried screw thank you
for the recipe this is the most
wholesome whole talk yet your chemistry
will flare it's just off the charts i
don't want to finish it just it's just
too titty
[Music]
it has to finish at some point if i
didn't have to translate anymore
then it would have been fine but
guys gotta consider
how the talk is supposed to be
a certain way okay but don't worry and
we'll collab again this will not be the
last time don't worry about it
[Music]
thank you for the support i'm glad you
enjoyed it
[Music]
very sweet
guys am i getting too old like
it's been four hours and i'm so
tired i've been tired since before the
stream it's not like i didn't get enough
uh
sleep
and and i've been like
i can still take um naps but
but like i can't sleep
too like long anymore in one go
[Music]
my face my face hurts
i can feel my face when i'm with you
and i love it
[Music]
oh i haven't been taking my little
melatonin in the past few days should i
take it does that help me the fake sun
[Music]
the season
take vitamins maybe i should
maybe i should
[Music]
oh i don't have energy man
vitamin d
[Music]
that makes sense
makes sense
[Music]
why am i definitely pregnant that
how's your diet
not much different at all from
usually from like months ago or a year
ago
if anything is getting
better i think
because i
cook more and more
[Music]
pumu
great
[Music]
um raw veggies
do i cook healthy food and i cook normal
food
curry with veggies
i think curry i mean is maybe not
extremely super
healthy but it's not unhealthy is it
it's not unhealthy right
[Music]
i i've never really
ever since i moved out of my
mom's place i
i think i've never
eaten that much
red meat so
i i've always had probably a lack of
iron length
yeah
[Music]
but
shouldn't be that strong now because it
should have been an issue in the blood
test
but the doctor said nothing about my
iron levels so
or at least it wasn't at least extremely
starting to hurt your brain okay
well it could be anything
i hope it's just a temporary thing
because i want to do my best
i want to work hard
but i just lack the energy
i don't know
and the tenacity
[Music]
getting old is permanent
foreign
[Music]
okay come on guys unarchived super chats
let's [\h__\h] go
on aircraft karaoke i mean
here beautiful art beautiful
so gorgeous
beautiful
i know someone invited it
psycho
i dm that person who sent me the
full-size version of that art because it
was so low resolution
so if you guys are wondering how did i
get such a high resolution
i asked for it
[Music]
oh yeah apparently it was the
anniversary for my king song
[Music]
no it's okay there's not much left
but thank you the
shin chao danke shin vitaya ventoglo
jones thank you for the red super chat
uh
super excited to listen to today's
karaoke attention it feels like it's
been forever since the last one yeah the
last one was christmas though or uh new
year's the new year is one
i think
[Music]
and i'm happy to announce that i'm going
to be taking a two-week vacation at my
second job
am i your second jump
or
you mean the other jump that you have
in preparation for elden ring
wait are you taking two ways off from
your actual real job or kfp
is your actual real job your second job
[Music]
cause that would be i mean i understand
if you take them off from kfp but if you
take two weeks off from your real job to
play eld in the ring holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
damn
respect
are you here now
is he here
ah obviously kfb's why you're you're
actually taking two it's a gamer
vacation
i mean if we have vacation days then why
the [\h__\h] not right
damn
wow you must be really excited for that
game
what if you wait two weeks if you
if you take two weeks off and have
nothing else to do then i don't think
you need two weeks to finish that game
do you probably not
i'm gonna play that game until i pass
out
well um i don't know if we can play it
on stream by the way i haven't heard
anything about it
i wonder if someone's gonna play it if
even if we get permissions
we originally planned to do yakuza next
so
not i don't know
i'll decide
i'll decide oh cali tried
[Music]
okay
i thought i thought bamko was involved
[Music]
isn't bank on the publisher
yeah the developer doesn't matter guys
it's the publisher that matters that
decides these things
but i guess it's bamako and from
software oh well i don't know
i don't know uh about uh
why and even if i did then i wouldn't
talk about it but
yeah it's fine if we can't play it then
i'll play
uh
[Music]
will be a long playthrough series again
oh yeah i can use my key arsenal again
i have so many weapons from last time
so many
exciting
yeah maybe i'll get some new ones too
guys you guys were like on a roll during
the yakuza arc
you guys were on the [\h__\h] role making
so many weapons
[Music]
anyway thank you bataya and i wish you a
lot of fun with eldon ring it seems like
you have your priorities right by just
taking the uh taking weeks off of your
main job
second job and not my job the kfb job so
i suppose you're gonna be still watching
my streams right right right
a good good
man or woman whichever but thank you
thank you
lexington alliance and tai chi thank you
for the red super chat
thank you
thank you thank you thank you yes okay
good answer
tanaka thank you for the pinkie seeing
you on the piano gets me all emotional
because it reminds me of your outfit
reveal
oh you mean because it failed once
um thanks for making my sunday afternoon
extra special 10 so thank you or or
because just it makes you positively
emotional or negatively emotional
[Music]
with oh because of sad sparks oh
but you said your outfit reveal
and you do you then you phrased it wrong
well okay
[Music]
yeah okay well well thank you thank you
for watching my unarchived karaoke
stream
it was fun
it was fun to finally sing songs again
and like so many random ones just
whatever
came to mind
so
i hope we can do it again and i hope
you'll be there again
thank you
have halloween next time next time next
time
every levine songs will always be in my
heart and in my consideration
don't you worry about that
[Music]
need some time to load the reading
spanking hand thank you for the red
super chat kikiano okay wow okay
my favorite
hope you love the uma cat merch i can
confirm it looks even better with cat
hair
i haven't unpacked it yet um i'm still
wearing my
millions of old t-shirts as streaming
attire
um
but yeah my omo cat merch is probably
only gonna be worn indoors anyway so
it's unfortunately destined
to be pajama wear even though it could
be so much more
hmm that is sad that's the one thing
that's sad about the omo cat merch
release is that
us
ourselves
we can't quite
wear it i guess
outside it's yeah
yeah
i'm still shocked that my mom refused to
get some omel cat merch i told her mommy
i can get whatever you want do you want
a t-shirt or a hat or a keychain and she
was like no no no
i'm like mom
why she's usually like so
so supportive
and and but i was like mom but like like
she has this huge [\h__\h] garden
and um you know it's [\h__\h] exhausting
to
uh work in her garden like she has to
like cut down trees and [\h__\h] so she
wears like
really really old
raggy clothes you know so i was like you
can i don't know
wear my own cat t-shirts for working in
the garden for example how about that
you don't have to worry to go to the
supermarket or so
and she was like no
i don't know why she really didn't want
it
it's not like anyone has to see you wear
she didn't want it
[Music]
man
but but i did get
one item um for a friend i asked if it's
okay if i can get one for a friend
yeah i didn't want to ask for too much
i think some girls actually ended up
requesting like every single piece also
from other members but i felt kind of
bad about
asking
for everything so i mostly
i did get certain other items that were
non chiata but i'm not gonna say which
ones although there might have been uh
there might have been an ammo
and maybe maybe actually forgot did i
order an
maybe i did um
who knows um
the you know one i
really just really like um
from like the
design
yeah and you guys know i had this issue
with um what were they called track
jackets or so
i really don't like the
i'm gonna be honest here i don't like
the the for me personally i don't like
the
the type of
fabric that is used for
uh gouda's
jacket and i think kelly's jacket was
the same
uh it's kind of like a sporty type of
jacket i don't like that shiny fabric
i don't know i don't like it
yeah i like the hoodies way more
but that's a personal preference
i did get um for some items i got like
all variations
but now that i have them for example i
have all the variations of the hats but
i'm like
these are just decoration now huh cause
like i'm not gonna wear them while i'm
streaming either not gonna wear them
outside not gonna wear them while i'm
streaming
i can't wear a hat while i'm streaming
i have my headphones and [\h__\h] okay this
is the immersion broken but
um you know i love hats
i do i do but
wear them backwards during pokemon ah
that would probably make me feel more
like a pokemon master wouldn't it
this display on the wall yeah i'm
probably gonna do something like that
like display them on a shelf or
something like that
or maybe
maybe when i'm old maybe when i'm like
80 90
million years old as a phoenix maybe
gets maybe at some point
uh
when i'm sitting
on my balcony
in my
wibbly wobbly wiggly wiggly chair
maybe then i'll wear my omo cat merch
because no one will give a [\h__\h] then
although people might be why is this 90
million year old
90 million years old
uh grandma wearing such
flashy colored
cute clothes
it's been 84 million years
[Music]
hmm
doubt humanity would even be around them
hey
knock on wood don't say that
i don't want to be alone in 80 million
years
why is this granny wearing such no no
but in 80 million years that would
probably not be considered trendy
anymore
in 80 [\h__\h] million years
we guys
we we would probably wear some like
water um
liquefied clothes i feel like we would
wear liquefied clothes or something
something crazy like that or air
we would wear
air that covers like
it wouldn't even be a fabric
but it wouldn't be invisible either
i know some crazy [\h__\h]
cloud clothes
anything or we would we wouldn't wear
any clothes instead we would not even
look like humans anymore or we would all
become robots obviously
[Music]
or we would all
by then also live on other other planets
or
or there would be no more planets we
would just chill in space
um in space suits although by that time
we don't even need spacesuits anymore we
have evolved so much that we can breathe
normally and walk normally in the middle
of the
uh
space
yeah
yeah my optimism
[Laughter]
will be uploaded to the matrix yeah
we'll just be computer data and we'll be
living inside of pc so that would be fun
maybe oh my god that sounds also
interesting and actually
[Music]
logical that sound plausible in in
maybe let's not say 80 million years but
maybe in a couple
thousand or one million years
we would be able to
upload
um no excuse me
the people from
300 years ago would have never thought
that something like the internet would
exist now that was crazy that was a
crazy thought back then not even a fault
like it was unthinkable so we now have
to think about the unthinkable and
giving you guys a 1 million years time
is very very very close to greek i
forgot the word generous it's very
generous
i think we would be able to do it in
5000 years
upload our
our data
onto a pc and that would save us from
you know the earth someday exploding
eventually
we would be
on a usb stick
[Music]
and continue living
inside of that
[Music]
then this this uh this tin foil theory
has given me some energy i feel like i
can read more super chats now
shh i got some energy let's go
zero pendrick and duncan cream cheese
latte and elisa
[Music]
sorry super chat's going slow because i
have to translate
should i read your full name or are you
fine with me reading only one part
[Music]
i want
wait what does this part say
[Music]
something like that she's singing the
song thank you nobody no bunny nobody
nobody but you it's a great song
for the pink super chat i'm glad you
recognized the song i think it was a
very famous song
in korea
back then
so i'm not surprised that
uh you guys recognized it
yeah yeah
i think one of the girls was pretty
pretty popular
when they were active
[Music]
in japan release songs in japan too like
specifically for
like under japanese label or something
or version japanese version of them like
i don't know they had like japanese only
songs and stuff
[Music]
and thank you for writing your name in
uh
english letters
saves me a lot of time thank you
saying tell me by one of those next time
oh tell me it's one of the few songs
that are in caravan
in the in the software included yeah
it's a
it's an instrumental that i can indeed
use so
you might have me sing it eventually
thank you thank you overwhelmingly and
then there is a
[Music]
i wonder because it wasn't a shitty time
for korean viewers i wonder if though
if me singing those korean songs
somehow
maybe reached
the korean viewers anyway
maybe you guys have like
a different
website
where you talk about there was this
other website right neva
i don't know where where do korean cave
people talk about
me where they neither
they need to know my korean cave people
need to be
reminded that i sang some korean songs
[Music]
on card you guys use this card
nah
i can't stock it anyway because i don't
i don't
i need to
first learn how to read and and
write korean otherwise
i ain't going nowhere
[Music]
scattered yeah
i hope you're only saying good things
about me
thank you
[Music]
so much
thank you for the pink super chat i
recommend song will the circle be
unbroken
by a shock infinite elizabeth version
for karaoke's last plus song and also
play game two someday please
oh a song from the game bioshock
that is a very specific
request
game songs from games usually
usually don't
have
[Music]
instrumentals
like
made available for us to use like that
so it's very difficult i would have to
commission
an instrumental
for me to sing it
even on an archived stream so
yeah the chances that that's going to
happen are pretty much different
oh my god
my pc lacks for a moment especially
since i'm not planning on playing
bioshock for now i'm so sorry
maybe in one or two years you can get me
to play bioshock but
am i back to normal
[Music]
yeah the world clinched out for a second
my whole pc lagged for a moment i guess
that's why i was a robot
sorry about that
[Music]
sorry that was my pc that was not susan
back to normal okay
[Music]
thank you
lose your cypher
hi hello
foreign
[Music]
i always say shitty time
and dominique thank you for the pink
super chat
it just just kind of okay you don't even
want me to play the game
[Laughter]
if you get me an instrumental that i can
use then we can think about it
but yeah the problem is that i can't
just use any instrumental for my karaoke
streams
um
i need we need something that we are we
surely have the rights to use it like
on
paper basically directed at us
and for a simple karaoke stream it's not
worth it getting an instrumental done
because commissioning an instrumental
costs usually
uh
from recent experience
something like 200
to 300
bucks
if it's recreating uh
a
already existing instrumental
maybe someone would make it for a
hundred
but yeah
probably not
probably i mean i feel like some people
would make it cheaper but
[Music]
not for someone like me
which is okay like
quote whatever the hell you want i
respect that
sometimes i feel like some people would
um create things cheaper
for
people who can't pay as much which is
totally totally fine
adjust your price however you like it i
respect it
um so there's probably
people who would make it cheaper but
from our
or my experience
getting recreating an instrumental is
quite expensive so it's just
i would i would make
if i would do a kind of okay stream
like that with
instrumentals like that i would i would
not profit from that at all i mean
generally i'm okay if i don't if i lose
some money on certain things that's fine
for me because it balances out in other
ways but
it just makes no sense to do it you know
yeah
ah
for the membership
[Music]
yeah
negative stunks
negatives it is fair it makes sense for
example if i do like a song cover for
that it makes sense
um if it's just like one song you know
um but for a karaoke stream where
there's like 10 to 20 songs being sung
and uh uh i have to get more than
one song if it's just one song okay but
like i i don't feel
this
specific need to get one specific song
made for us for karaoke when there's
millions other songs out there that i
could sing instead of that you know what
i mean it's just
it's just not
necessary
i don't have a song that i feel like i
must sing for you guys or i will die no
matter what it takes i will get an
instrumental done and then it can't even
be archived anyway
most of the time unless it's a japanese
song
if i can't even archive it then i don't
see why i should
buy an instrumental for it you know what
i mean
[Music]
thankfully thanks to karafan we already
have a big big big library to choose
from
[Music]
can we buy an instrumental and gift it
to you
yeah but no guarantees that i'll be
using it if it's a song that i don't
know or that i don't really like
if it's something that i wanted to sing
but couldn't because i had no
instrumental then
then i would use it yeah
but i feel like
i don't wanna
i'm not sure if you guys should be doing
that because i feel like i don't know if
the song has a special meaning to you
maybe but other than that
um
is it really worth it i don't know
i can record an instrumental oh if you
yourself play instruments
let's go
all the power to you
[Music]
what i did
want to do before
but got really difficult now
um
you know
this whole change
happened
around the time
of the
fancy party dress outfit reveal
and
that one was also delayed a million
times right
and um
i wanted to
i got this background with this piano
right so i was thinking
after my outfit reveal on the next day i
wanted to do a special piano version
only karaoke and
it would have been unarchived but that's
okay because i could have still used any
instrumental that i found on the
internet there's so many um piano
versions of songs on youtube
so i would have just used that but then
i think it was like a day or so a day
before the outfit reveal i think
something around that
the rules kind of changed for better or
for worse
and
now i cannot use any
piano tracks anymore
there are a ton but i can't use them
so i would have to get them commissioned
or
eventually maybe find a source
like a channel or so that
wants to allow us to use them
which
hopefully
hopefully that will happen
well i wanted to use that piano and the
themed piano cover stream
yeah
it didn't work out so i had to
kind of cancel it and plan something
else
i wish i knew music to play for you i
wish i knew music to play for myself man
there's so many skills that i wish i had
now i wish i had mixing skills i wish i
had video editing skills like sick video
editing editing skills i wish i had
graphic design skills i wish i could do
so many things that i need now that i
have to keep on like asking other things
other people other people to do like i
don't mind commissioning things but
sometimes it's just things would go so
much faster and and kind of efficiently
more efficient if i would be able to do
it myself you know
yeah
damn
nah my graphic design is blood doesn't
look professional
oh well
rmt is really better
rnt yeah she plays sick guitar yeah
ukelele yeah it is indeed in the corner
you're not wrong with that it's
definitely in the corner if it's crying
i don't know let's break down the chats
go go go
uh
okay dominique for the pinkie duncan
thanks for all the songs the fun times
you were making my birthday weekend into
a truly unforgettable one it was your
birthday
i continue to flap my wings to support
kfb and we'll cheer you on on any stage
let's go kp let's cheer her on thank you
but we should cheer for you
[Music]
is
it's been four and a half hours
[Music]
thanks for the streaming today i woke up
during the night mission your voice and
song are really nice i want to marry
someone like yada someday oh
always you're the best kiara thank you
marry someone like me
hmm
i'm happy to
hear that uh
you feel like
that's the type
that's uh the type of person you would
desire to
to marry i'm glad i'm like a desirable
type of person
thank you
thank you wonderful material really
same actually
come on
thank you oh you have no idea oh
oh you guys have no idea
you guys have no idea how
how annoying i can be sometimes nah just
kidding i'm not that annoying
i feel like um
maybe i
um
i feel i feel like in my daily like
everyday life i'm very very chill and
quiet i just watch netflix all day and
play some games and
eat yummy food
i don't wanna
i don't wanna like
do [\h__\h] all the time
[Music]
i think i'm
i'm lacking a lot of qualities that are
annoying in other chicks
that i can say
[Music]
and i like to go on vacations a lot so
isn't that chill
uh
[Music]
i'm i'm just kind of lazy most of the
time
and and and i'm easy to please with food
like um
i don't
i'm not very picky when it comes to no
okay i'm picky with like
certain veggies and stuff but generally
like i'm fine eating frozen pizza you
know
i'm fine with that
or fast food
don't care don't care give me fast food
i'm picky in some ways but in other ways
i'm not picky
anyway thank you savage
[Music]
donkey
is tanjo kiara today is my birthday i
just celebrate myself without watching
listening beautiful your voice in this
stream i hope everything what you do
goes well and you will always be healthy
and make everyone happy
it's your birthday i should say those
things to you thank you are you here
you are here
happy birthday
it's a korean super chat so i'm gonna
sing in korean
rbc
[Music]
happy birthday
please
stay healthy
and stay in kfp
it's that easy only two things
two things can you manage to do that
stay healthy and stay in kfp
it's not many
requests not much what i'm asking for
yodo school thank you for supporting me
[Music]
and thank you for the
red super chat we have an emergency
attention with some fire
thinking we have an emergency
i think we have an emergency my
kfp
tencho
is on fire
are you listening
are you watching me
that's actually the those two sentences
were actual lyrics so
didn't even change that
thank you thank you thank you thank you
can put the put the sticks down already
put the light sticks down chill chill
chill
thank you yeah this is normal this is
normal i'm always on fire
don't worry about it anton m
thank you
takodachi thanks for the pinky thanks
for the banger songs tanja also
yesterday on my birthday what is
everyone having their birthday i
completed the final dish from the kiara
cooking challenge i started this month
oh i hope you're happy with the results
and hire me as an industrial
sp
i mean chef at kfp
oh you wanted to say spy
oh
you gave yourself away there sir
[Music]
if anything
i'll make you a chef but i'll have you
cook in chains
no no no not that easily no no no you
think i'm stupid or what
thank you though
and happy
little bit delayed
delayed belated the latest
birthday to you yeah
so many birthdays wow
congratulations
[Music]
i hope you had a wonderful birthday
hello police i would like to report a
murder because keala is killing it
please don't call the police on me they
already have me on the radar because of
all these people
reporting me to the subashubab police
please don't they'll misunderstand they
they don't understand jokes
please stop
normally
don't know why everyone is so round up
about that lily allen song you were just
talking about wholesome monopoly right
why didn't you finish first last time
potential
what you mean because i uh
i finished i guess you could say it that
way that's a more positive way of saying
uh that i lost first in monopoly i
finished first
yeah i reached the finishing line
as the first person
[Music]
thank you for letting me say it in a
different perspective abby not a cult
wow
you are one of those people who see a
half empty glass and you say it's half
full
[Music]
i'm confused i was crying because of
symphony and once again you nailed it it
gets me every time not only the lyrics
but your voice it just hits me it's even
more i loved it and now i feel
threatened um no i mean how's it going
casual
vivid akiana thank you what came after
what came after symphony
i forgot apparently it was a threatening
song i'm sorry about that fro fro it was
not towards you
didn't want to feel make you feel
threatened
[Music]
thank you doll for listening
and yeah it was i i told you guys it was
a hot mess of a of a set list it was a
roller coaster
um
[Music]
a wonderful gift for all employees
it's best welfare in kfp and we're here
for you thank you
you sound like someone's putting a gun
to your head while you're saying this to
me
i am really really really
genuine about this
doesn't sound so genuine to me i think
we need to get more emotion out of your
way of writing things
out of your message
maybe try again
we don't want anyone to suspect anything
the way huh
we want people to think kfb is a good
place to work at
and no doubts no doubt i mean why would
people doubt it of course there's no
reason to doubt it but i need you guys
to be uh good at conveying that
[Music]
pinky and just fabulous
too bad i didn't sing fabulous from high
school musical but i think you said that
super chat when i was singing high
school musical
[Music]
i love that fabulous song but i sang it
before i had to sing something different
this time and i'm probably never gonna
sing high school musical ever again
[Music]
i how did i not realize that that was
disney what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
taco madonka should miss wisdom
but don't worry i didn't get bonked yet
i made it running around on sunday sucks
oh
on sunday well welcome back
thank you for
trying to make it to my stream i'm glad
you were still there
if you missed a lot of it there will be
a rebroadcast probably at a bad time for
you because it's gonna be six a.m est
but yeah there's always probably some
people out there who clip it so
um
[Music]
good song
always fun to sing that one very much
glad you enjoyed it too
uh
[Music]
thank you getting confused here it's
been too long i'm tired
[Music]
peanut butter chocolate flavor oh my god
you guys
went so crazy
with the reese puffs meme oh my god
raised by spring
[Music]
well i'm glad i know the meme now i'm
glad yeah
thank you for teaching me chat
flannel blizzard fancy duncan sharon ll
926 dancing wallet says i am misery
well that's maybe because you're sending
a pink super chat you might want to
consider your life choices if your
wallet isn't misery i don't want your
wallet to be a misery
okay be careful
but thank you for the generous support
thank you
storm blade thank you vivi corey eric
schmidt
doom slayer dragon dangerous and
seventeen two seven thank you
thank you
john
i'm almost done guys
[Music]
please never take off of mrs takanashi's
wild ride
take me off ah this has been amazing
beautiful hilarious and i think so much
whiplash that i need to hear a
chiropractor me too please
you weren't kidding about that set list
this is why your karaokes are amazing
thank you wonderful phoenix thank you
too
i know you guys uh
i know you guys probably think that my
song choices are a bit too
uh generic
but
but but
i enjoy it okay so i hope you guys can
enjoy it with me
nah
was good okay
[Music]
i know i know i listen to a lot of or
used to listen don't listen to music
anymore for some reason but i used to
listen to music and it was mostly very
um
basic
i know but at least it's songs that most
people know and i feel like for karaoke
streams that's the best when when
instead of me singing only songs that
you've never heard of and don't vibe
with at least
you can listen to some songs that feel
familiar to you uh and maybe nostalgic
you know
[Music]
i'm so exhausted thank you typhin
of london
[Music]
instrumental that i could use i'm really
sad about that not being available
i was practicing her songs thinking that
surely surely his songs would be in kara
fun but they're not
kakundan
cruz
[Music]
thank you papa
thank you i am exhausted so i'll leave
it at that but thank you
and we're done
we're
done i am hungry and i'm tired and i'm
exhausted so i'm really sorry guys
but it's it has been five hours
it's not like it it's not like i zoomed
through it in one hour or so which i
probably could have
which i probably could have but i want
you guys to
get something
out of me reading super chats not just i
don't want it to just be a core you know
i want you guys to
[Music]
get more than just a stupid thunder [\h__\h]
but now i'm dead
i need food
and i need to
rip off my face off of my head that's
what i feel like doing right now
or smash my head i want to smash my head
[Music]
well you have to
uh you see the schedule we'll have a
late stream tomorrow we'll make a song
when we'll use an audio stock
instrumental i'll go through some before
the stream i'll choose a good one
and then i'll do my best with your help
to
write
song
[Music]
okay lyrics go now i don't feel good
i don't feel good i'm gonna
thank you guys
and you guys were spending your time
with me while i'm reading super chat
[Music]
is unfortunate that there were so many
streams
where i couldn't read super chats
i don't want this to happen too often
but sometimes it does i just
i need to try my best to read them after
each stream
members only i'll definitely be able to
read them
for hot glue crafts probably not because
i'll be
maybe i can set it this one up because i
don't need to cook maybe i can set it up
at my
office then i can use my
normal setup and then i can read simple
chats for that one too
[Music]
i might try that
i might try to set it up here
[Music]
because that makes things easier for me
in terms of
transition to super chat reading
[Music]
for tony gardic phone i won't be able to
read super chat though
but yeah this week is looking better in
terms of that
be careful with your cats oh don't worry
my cats usually
stay away from me when i stream and just
sleep
in my closet
all those movies will be every once to
the last movie it becomes really needy
and says hello but generally they stay
away don't hot glue your hands
don't worry i'll be wearing gloves
anyway they were actually pretty helpful
last time when i was about to burn
myself
it will be fine oh by the way if you're
wondering are you wondering what that
will be hot glue crafts i mean obviously
hot glue crafts is going to be hot glue
crafts but i want to make stuff like
stupid items like uh i don't know a hat
out of
out of hot glue or a ring out of hot
glue or a bracelet out of hot glue
or a shoe out of hot glue or
a fork out of hot glue
or
anything
yes
yes we're gonna make anything out of
vodka
[Applause]
yes
he has a shoe for my feet yes
[Music]
but only
if
as much as i can only with a
hot glue we're not gonna use other
things for it
[Music]
i'll make a chicken out of hot glue
maybe too
bird cat
hot glue merch let's go
a crown could do that too
[Music]
yeah what else what else could we do you
guys are welcome to give me ideas
maybe
we could do a hot glue photo frame
we could do uh
ah i've seen something a hot cool phone
stand actually seems pretty
useful and manageable one of the few
things that actually could work
a hot glue phone stand
you know to or ipad stand to keep keep
it up when it's when you're
um
i don't know
on on sitting on the table
that's actually one good idea
[Music]
baking paper yeah i was thinking about
that too i have baking paper no problem
also
one of the reasons why i'm doing that is
because i had this huge bag of
glue sticks right
and
even after the gingerbread house i still
had so much left over like 90
of it left over
or 95
so i was thinking
i could use it all up
in that hot glue crafts hot glue craft
stream but i bought even more glue
additionally because i wanted i wanted
those as
sparkly sparkly colorful
glue sticks so i bought a bag of
colorful
sparkly
glue sticks
as well
so it won't all just be the same
low-key see-through milky color
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah i will use the the colorful
hot glue additionally
rainbow
yeah we can make rainbow hot glue crafts
[Music]
we can make christmas tree ornaments for
next year
yay doesn't that sound good um
yeah sounds like a weird stream can't
wait let's go yeah i thought it would be
a cute idea and uh a good way to use up
my hot glue
but then i still
uh bought more
and probably will still have leftover
glue afterwards but that's okay yeah i
always need hot glue sometimes when
something breaks so
[Music]
now this stream is ending now
just wanted to let you know about the
hot glue craft stream
who are you
hi
so please watch the streams this week we
have a lot of fun streams
of course looking forward to the most of
the holotoy
hollow tori garlic phone collab
finally checking that one off of my list
oh break a vase on purpose and fix it
with glue
yes
i might do that
okay thank you everybody for watching
have a nice day and in german we say
avidazine
auf wiedersehen
[Music]
thanks for enduring enduring it together
with me
[Music]
yeah thank you
what's
up
[Music]
do
on
[Music]
do
you