[Music]
[Music] It's
starting, it's
starting
So it's almost time for the next live show.Today, I
appeared with some really good BGM, but I hope you all like it.
How are you? Hey,
can you hear me? BGM.
Too good. I
didn't say this. I haven't
played this new type of BGM in the opening.
Today, I'll
tell you, Subaru.
As for the Tales of Arise series, I've been playing Tales
of Symphonia and Tales of
Tiramisu, and I've been
asked to play them, and then I
received a call from someone who was going to be the official ambassador for Tales of Arise, so today I'm going to play Tales of Symphonia and Tales of
Tiramisu.  I'm calling you, Official Ambassador of Arise.
Now, please appear. This
is Mr. Kihara, who is such an idiot. Can you
hear me? I can hear you.
Well, I'm here. No, no, no, hello.
Nice to meet you, Sensei.
Wow, I can't believe the
day will come when Subaru-senpai calls me Sensei. Sensei.
Maybe I'm a little nervous.
[Laughs]
Please. Yes, I'm probably fine today.
Many times.  I'm working as an ambassador, so it
's okay. As expected of a teacher. Yeah,
the volume, etc. Are you okay? Everyone, are you
okay
? I hope you're okay. Please introduce yourself. Yes,
Holo. Listen to Live English version Takanashi  I
'm Chiara. Well, I've been liking health for a long time now.
Bandai Namco noticed
last year, and I'm so glad they noticed. I
got the offer last year, so I'm going to write the English version of Tails from now on.  I
became an ambassador.
[Applause]
Tiara, I really like the Tales of series. I'm
sure I'll talk about it a lot from now on, but that's
one of the reasons I fell in love with Japan.
Yes, it really has been a big part of my life.I've
recently started to like it, and I was really happy when I saw it.Tales
has a certain flavor that can only be experienced in Tales.  [
Music]
That's right. Today, I
'd like to go a little bit simple and talk about how we're going to go about it, but
first of all, here are some slides. I
'd like to talk about some of my memories.  However  Let's
talk about it, after all, Subaru and
Chiara, my favorite Symphonia
Who do you like?
Memories, memories, etc.
I was really
young when I did this, and in fact, I
used to have a GameCube. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, my mother at Christmas.
My brother and I went to Japan and
bought Continuation Sinfonia, and
my brother was the main one, but
I participated in that battle.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, that's a game where you can play together,
so you can fight together, and I
started to really like the story, and also the way it looked.At
that time, it was my first experience with an anime-like game,
so I
thought it was cute.  I
fell in love with the way it looked, and when I
found out that there were many other games like this, it was amazing.When I
learned more about it for the first time, I realized that
there are anime-like RPGs out there, and I was like, ``Wow!''
When my brother wasn't playing, I used to
play a little bit myself, but I was still a
bad gamer, so I
couldn't go all the way to the end by myself, but I was able to
play a lot with my brother, which was
really heartwarming to
Subaru-senpai.  I
still remember this scene, but it's
like a famous scene from Sinfonia, isn't it?
There's coffee
in the lower right corner of this scene. I'm really getting goosebumps from that scene.  You
stood up
[Music] It
's not a bird, it's
this, it's this. When I thought of the Clerk series, I started
thinking something like this, but
then I found out that that coffee cup was
being sold.  When I
heard from a listener that some kind of fancy coffee cup was on sale at that time, I was
wondering if I should buy one.Well, it's a
mug, after all.Sinfonia.I wonder
what Lloyd is.
At best, what I like about it is the way it shines, and it
creates something. There's Lloyd creating all kinds of things,
and Kratos
' kindness, and there's a
scene where Kratos tells Lloyd that he should be healthy.  I
love that line so much
that I still
often talk to my listeners about it while playing that RPG. She's
cute too, and the relationship between the two of them is
great, too. But also, Lloyd and Lloyd.
He's quite childish, but
what he does is like a hero after all.And what
's more, it's like the warmth of this parent and child.What's so amazing about
Sinfonia?It was
wonderful to be able to touch it.That's what I really
liked.That's
why I like how everyone interacts with each other.  Also,
Shina is
so cute,
and the scene with Shiko Boruto
made me cry a lot,
so when I started talking about it, I couldn't stop.  I do
n't have any, so I'm going to go to the next one, but I
played Abyss, Tales of Tia Abyss, and it's
wonderful, wonderful, wonderful. I
have fond memories of Abyss,
Mr. Kihara.You know, Abyss is something I can play.Originally, there was
n't a console game machine that could play Abyss.
So I've been trying to do it quite recently, or rather in the last five years.Actually,
I've wanted to do it for a long time, but it's been quite
recently, but I feel like I haven't gotten to the end yet,
so please don't spoil it.
[Laughs] That's how
long it took for me to not be able to do it.But I do
know a little bit about Subaru's
first
Tales of series was Abyss.It
was Jiavis, but I'm not
sure if it came before that.  I feel like I'm about to
cry.
[Music]
No, but to avoid spoilers
, Subaru is the first
character to
feel this kind of strong motherly feeling.
It's my
first time
doing live commentary for an RPG,
and
every time I do it, I cry until my T-shirt is all messed up. It
was really good.
And every
time, I feel deeply hurt in a good way by Tales of the
Abyss.  After the live broadcast is over, it's
like looking at the sky, it's amazing.
There's something so moving about the feeling of emptiness.
No, I really understand that. It's like watching the sky.
When I finish playing a game once, I feel like my life is over and I'm like, ``
What should I do with this?'' I
think about all sorts of things.It's the
same with Symphonia, which is very easy to understand, and the
same with Abyss, but
after the Tales of series is over, I don't know what to do.  What
the world is like, what is the world like?
Thinking about all sorts of things like this, I'm
not immersed in the appreciation, but it's amazing and makes me think.By
the way, I don't mind
RPGs.The
tiara is that.  I
joined Sinfonia, but the ones I
liked the most
were 1
and 2, so I would definitely like them to do 1 and 2 in the future.I
guess I didn't like them.I wonder
who the members were.Someone
likes Xillia.  I feel like I've heard something like that, Kirara,
maybe Chiara.By
the way, what part of it is easy right now?I
especially like that one in Xillia, and for some
reason it's amazing.  It
's dark, I feel like Kinari Nana Terrace's games are
generally a bit brighter,
but in terms of the story, in Xillia,
by the time you get to the second game, it's
dark, and the system is amazing, and it's
different from usual, so I felt like I was that way.  The
story changes as you make choices. There are
n't that many, so it stands out. I
see. When there are quite a few branches, it
gets me excited. Yes, that's right. I
also like the basic system of regular Tales.
But this was different from usual, so it
really stayed in my memory for a long time at home.Oh yeah,
it's so memorable.I
cried so much.I
cried so much.It's
not like I'm doing it for the sake of crying.Tears do
n't feel good, but that's the
feeling.  Something like Subaru, this Tales of
series, Abyss and Symphonia,
something like
that. It's okay, I'm sorry.
Maybe Subaru just has too many memories of this Abyss.  I'm sorry,
but if the senior who sits there is
praising me like this, I'll pick it up again.I have no choice but to pick it up.I
can't stop, so I'll go next time, but yes, let's
go.Next, let's go here.Yes,
which slide should I use?
Yes, it has changed.Okay, well, today.  Actually, I don't want to talk about that old
tennis game, but rather a video about Rise
,
so for that reason, the official management team has already
prepared a guide for us to check our understanding of Arise.
Confirmation test That's
right,
test Subaru even though I haven't done it yet.That's why I'm
here.First, I explained to Subaru-senpai about the Neyroro Rise,
hoping he would like it, and
then at the end, I took the test.  I'm going to get it, but it's
about understanding, understanding level,
understanding level. It's okay, it's so
owl-like creature. Let's
join forces and take the Arise understanding test.
Yes, this
street is not that nameless one.  It's Ford  I
think they said "Furu" in Japanese on Hulu.
[Music] It
's not Fururu. I
see. It's really cute. Tales
always has a mascot of some kind,
right?
That Rise mascot is...  I'm Fururu, so
today I'm going to talk about a lot of things about Rise,
so at the end, let's work together to
take a comprehension test and get a good score.I've
prepared it.As always, I'll do my best.I hope it sticks
in your mind.
Let's do
our best.Video First of all, let's
play this and that.We've got a new video
for RPG fans who want to play Arise.Teacher,
there it is, you have to see it.  Let's watch it together. It seems like
this is the world's first time for a cat to be
streamed. It's the first video ever to be played, so let's
watch it together, Professor.
Okay, I'll just shut up for a second. Yes,
by the way, that Subaru is making his usual noise.  I'm
watching it while I'm watching, but the teacher is watching over me.It
would be helpful if I could get it.It's just a
daily life of sounds.Okay, let's start
with this.First of all, this is what it will look like.Okay, let's
take a look at it.It's the world's first
introductory PV, Arise.  Let's take a look.Here it
is.How
far can I take it?
I'm going to take it away to stop him.That's
good.I'm Lena.You're the one.I'll
use the flaming sword to defeat all the Surds.To that
end, I'll cooperate with you.  The promise that we will meet
I want to fight, you're
so beautiful, I've
already made up my mind It wo
n't end unless I give up
And one
day I'll be able to break down the wall
Wall When I
see your face, I can't leave it alone
[Music] I
want you to
[Music]  ] I've
searched for you.
I'll defeat you for your release. It's
not easy to overcome it.
But if you overcome the pain, the
day will come when we can understand each other.
Even at the very end, I will never give up.
There was,
just a little more  I'm
going to let you dream because
I
want to spend more time with you,
other girls.
Our journey
continues.
Now is the time to Arise.
[Music] Now
let's talk.
[Laughter]
Girls are fleeting.  I'm already a little
nervous, but that
white girl has that pink hair. Pink
paper, ah, it
's Shion. Her name is Shun-chan. That's
right,
but she's quite different from our Shion-chan.
Yes, it's about personality and all sorts of things, but also being
freed from slavery.Yes, this is quite a heavy story.In fact, it
seems heavy, it's a very, very painful story.But
before I get into that, let me say something about this story.  The
video is mostly from the movie for this main game,
but at the very end there
was a DLC video, so now that new
bundle has
just come out, uh,
Taser Rise Beyond Dawn.
Now
is the perfect time
to start playing Arise because a new bundle version that combines the main game and DLC is coming out with Delsea called Beyond the Dawn.
Um, at this timing, I'm
also
going to touch on the new bundle version.  So yeah, yeah, it's
going to take a little while until TNC comes out, but if you get the battle now, you'll be able to
play the main game right away, so
first of all, it's really long, so enjoy it.  I
think it's probably the best time to release it because you've already finished playing the main game.
Just at that time, something
new will be released as downloadable content. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, I
see.
[Music]
Just at the right time.  As if it were a continuation
of that, you can also enjoy downloadable content.If I
do it now, that's right.I think there were a
lot of things that caught my attention in the video I just saw,
so first of all, what kind of
game is Arise?I want to promote it in various ways.
First of all, let's
talk about the characters.I think you were interested in them, so I'm curious.It's
amazing to see that face covered in steel.That's the
main character.I
think it's okay to put that slide next.I wonder if it's
a little late for me.
But this white-haired one is the
main character, and he says, ``Alfen.'
'
Remember, it's the
star Danner, ruled by the neighboring star Lena.'' I heard it.
Dana
is the name of that planet. Dana and Rena. I
wonder who their names are, but they're planet-type. That's
right, that's right, so they
're right next to them. I see. They're
on that planet called Dana, and they're
torn apart as slaves.  They live a life of a kind, and they
also wear a tortoise mask made of iron that they can't take off.It's
like that mask is a sign of slavery,
but it's not.There are a lot of them out there.
Well, not everyone wears it, but
actually, Alfen
has lost
his sense of pain. He doesn't feel that kind of pain, right?
And, um, this
is fascinating, but
he also has amnesia. He doesn't know where he was born.
No, I
don't know why the Iron Tortoise is wearing it,
and I don't know why I lost Currency-kun. I really
don't
know anything about myself. I do
n't know anything. Of course, I don't know anything about myself.  I
don't care about my own suffering, but I
really care about that other person's punishment.I don't
want anyone to suffer, and I
get really angry because of other people.This person is like that a lot.
Well, he can work so hard for others,
or
rather, he feels like he can't overlook his plans.He
becomes very passionate.He
has a very, very good heart, and soon he will fight a
big battle to lead Dana, who wants to be a slave, to freedom.  to  I'm
getting caught up in it.Yes, let's free Dana,
so I see.Who is the
slave?Yes, yes, that's right.This
is the main point of this story.Here, you
say it in the style of using a sword.Yes, let's free Dana.  Seriously,
this thing is so cool. This is a sword made of flame. Is
n't the sword really cool?
Moreover, this sword seemed special. When I
looked at it, it seemed so special.
How special is this? It's probably best
not to spoil it too much.
Okay, so next time, you'll
find out how to do it at the very beginning of the game.
No, but
stop for a moment. Let's
talk about Dana from Cat Slave Planet.  There were a lot of them, but I guess the
worldview is unique after all.That's what I
thought when I heard about it, so I'll leave it here.I
understand the worldview, but
since there's an anime, let's
take a look at that too, teacher.  I see.
Ok, I'll be silent again.
Excuse me, please. OK, let's
do this. Let's do this.
Let's understand the worldview of Tales of a Rise.
Let's watch the anime together.
This is it. There's a
lot of water.
The water is so beautiful
[Music] It's so
natural, isn't it? It's quite natural.
My stomach is pounding, but it's quite modern. The
land of Dana was surrounded by rich nature, where the vehicles were protected by spirits.
Exploiting the spiritual power that resides in things and lives that suddenly came to an end.
That's what these 300-rank
Rena people have continued to do in Dana. They're
quite in control.
Why did you save me?
[Music]
New Life  That's all
we're looking for.In any case, we have no choice
but to keep fighting.If we had that flaming sword, we might have some chance of
victory.The
sword
is the key
word after all.This black one, but only if the two of you gather together.  I'll
fight from now on, I'll
fight desperately to win the
world and
my future.
[Music]
Teacher, I
have a question for you. Teacher,
the world can't be saved unless the two of us come together.
That's right, it won't
work unless these two, Shion and Alpen, stay together for the rest of their lives.  Well, I can't tell you the reason because it would be a spoiler. I'm
curious, right? Sensei.
Shion-chan
is a 10 user. I guess that's right. Let's
take a look at Shion-chan for a moment.
It just
came out, so I'm serious,
but besides Shion-chan, there's another woman who looks
like a keyword, and for
a moment I could see Nekata, a woman with amazing golden hair, but
up to that point, she's the
heroine of Rise.  So, how
do you say this in Japanese? [Music] So, how do you say this in Japanese?
[Music] So, how do you say this in Japanese? [Music] So, how
do you say life force? So, how do you say this?  I
'm from Renner, the planet of the aristocrats, so I
'm from Lina, and there
are five bosses who control Dana in the heavens.This
is Lord Rolls.The
bosses say that in English, but it
's Japanese.  It's a
little bit
sharp.
During the game, you keep defeating Shion-chan, but
in reality, everyone who touches Shion-chan
feels intense pain. First of all, if you
touch Shion-chan, it hurts a lot.  I
won't touch you. Even if I wanted to hug Shun-chan, I
couldn't. He's involved in a curse like that.
Alpine has no sense of pain, so
this would be a good match.
As expected, that Shion
is a little special.  But yeah,
yeah, uh, that prefecture, the
flaming sword,
just like what I said earlier, I have to say something.
Spoilers,
wait a minute,
uh, I have to say this now.  I
think I saw it in the video a little bit. Now that
Alfen is
able to extract what he can touch,
he
pulls out a weapon from inside Shion-chan's body. He
pulls out something from Shio-chan's chest.  Moo
's Shion-chan is
emitting a vast spiritual power of flame that was hidden inside her body. That
's right. It's all made with spirit arts. So
Shion-chan's prefecture was created through spirit arts.
We're going to take it out from inside, so
these two people have to work as a pair.Oh, I
see, they're stronger when they're together.There
's something about it that when you
touch it, it hurts.This
is the cause.  Is it some kind of thorny curse?The
cause of it is so
true.It's a
curse.I want to do something about it,
but I
can't do anything about it.So
Kokoton and Alphen met by chance.  An
opportunity has arisen to end the 300-year slave rule of the Lena people.
So, is this really an
invitation? Sensei, this is the
slave planet Alpine and its ruling
planet Lena, and
Lena's planet Zion are joining hands.  It
's not the end of domination, but it's not a peaceful symbol,
but it's something like that. I
understand. I'm glad you understand. I
think we
can do something about it.  I'm
a little concerned about this, but
Alpen is the only one who
comes into contact with Shion, right? That's
right.
Shion-chan is quite like that. When I
imagine it, she seems a little lonely,
but she's used to it, so it's pretty easy,
especially at first.  I feel kind of cold
about Shion-chan. She seemed a little
strong-willed. Oh, and
by the way, did you see that Shion
also had a gun? She wasn't
cool, she was cool.  In
particular, when you hit a flying enemy, it's
good to use it like that.Shion
sells the flying enemy with Shion, then in Alpine, you
go close to it and cut it.It's like
that.  But
yes, just now, in Shion's
chest-high
scene, I
thought the sword was coming out of the vortex of flames, but apparently it
was coming out of the baby.
But it's just because I don't feel pain.
Doctor, I
already had some friends with me, so let's
see if they'll watch it too.
My explanation is a little lame, but
I'll try.  Let's go, it's really easy to understand.
Teacher,
it's really cool. I
mean, I thought the battle scene was really cool. I was
watching it a while ago, and there was that one-on-
one fighting scene. It's amazing.  It's
cool, and it's not like that airplane,
but the design of the flying thing is crazy
. I
really like it.''
Subaru, yes, it has some futuristic
aspects. I'll
probably see it in the next slide.  That's right,
this
is a friend of Alpen and Shion.The one on the left
is the linen.This girl
is actually a Danajin girl who has been active in the resistance for some time.Maybe next.
Okay, so basically this kid ca
n't use spiritual powers, but he's learned
magic to resist Lena, and he's
good at very, very strong impact magic.
[Applause] He's one
of the members of the party who can use magic.  It's a character. It's a
magical character.
Look at
it. Ah, I see. It's
with Rimmel-chan. The
House of Councilors is super cute, so I
think it's okay to say this in the game because it's not a spoiler.
Collect fururus.
There are many different kinds of fururus. That's why it's
good to collect a lot of fururus.
Something might happen if you collect them. They're
so cute.
There was a really huge fururu at the Tokyo Game Show the other day.
Yo, let's stop talking about the Tokyo Game Show.
I wasn't able to go. I
wanted to go, but I'd like to see you at the game next time.
[Music]
Well, Law is on the right.
Lawis.
Although he is a slolier Seesorian in the land where morning never comes, he acts as a surveillance police that can be used by Rena.Although he
is from Dana, it seems like he has joined Rena's organization on Dena's side and is
serving Rena.
Actually, the
craftsman
is an enemy at first, and he
stands like an enemy, but
Roan is good at close-range impact, and
uses super and quick impact. Yes, he can match in one hit.  I'm
going to be playing with my own hands,
especially that's something that's something
that's, and if you
attack a hard person today, it will
be broken today, so first attack with low
and break that equipment like this.  When I
heard that everyone was going there, there were quite a lot of strategies put together,
and there were various positions depending on the character, and
yes, there were quite a few strategies.
There are many ways to do it, but the
one that does it this way is the smartest. I
see. That's why I'm good at it.Next
Slider-chan,
it's on the right, but it's okay to do it on the right.
Or the right one will be erased.  This is Kisara-chan.
What is it?
Kisara is originally a ruler, Rena-chin, and a
slave, Dana-chin, who
coexist amicably,
and there are some countries where they live happily together
.
He is a Danajin soldier who is a much better friend of Shuu-kun in Menancia than he is in other places, and belongs to the Imperial Guard because he sympathizes with his ideology.If you
look at him, you can probably tell by his cat-like equipment,
but he is from the Sohei clan, so he is a member of the Imperial Guard.  He
's a tank who is good at controlling and protecting his friends by controlling an extremely large house made with technology.  I
think it's pretty sacred in the character who can warp anywhere, the character is different, the shield is different. It
may be the first time, but you
fight mainly with the shield. Stand up,
push, push,
burn.  Well, there's also a race,
but I
'm fighting mainly with a shield. It's
cool.
And the one on the right is this. I
talked about those five bosses, right?  It
seems like there is a boss who is controlling the situation.Is this a
spoiler?
Even this person is too sweet.It is written here, so he is
in a big position, but he is
having fun and interacting effectively.He is a
conscientious person.I wonder
if he has left.  I
guess I'm quite a hobbyist, artist, and collector, and people around me tend to see me as a strange person.When the time comes, I can use a
certain technique,
and since I'm a redactin, I
can also use spirit arts, but it's kind of weird.
I have it. I'm sure it's transcendental. I
use it. It moves pretty fast, and it's
easy to use. The
clothes are pretty noble. I
just noticed one thing. That
's right.
Well, these two
are together.When they meet, they're together.I
see.They're
connected for some reason.They're
connected for some reason.Hmm,
well, that's probably better not to say it.  I
think it's great.It's amazing.I
feel like I'm trying to find the right line right now.But it's
difficult to understand.Even
if you're giving spoilers, the level of explanation is quite high.It's
a little difficult.I'm
already a teacher.  Please do as you wish, Sensei.It
's dangerous, but okay, for now, these
six people
will be our party.And
these six people are all from different countries.
There are so many different things like where we live, we all have different ways of thinking, and we all have different ways of thinking, and sometimes we get into quite a few fights.You know, we're
six people with very different personalities,
but what will happen at this party?  I
wonder if we'll be able to get along, and whether we'll be able to fight together and achieve what we want to achieve. I don't know. Even if we're in different positions, I think we'll be able to do it to some extent. Well, that's just a guess, but I guess that's just a guess.
There are people from Dana who serve Rena, and there are
also people who have been in Dana for a long time as part of Danah's Dara team,
and
there are also people who live in the country where Rena and Dana live happily together today.  Teacher, do you understand that
reality is different depending on the character and their
values are different?The
reality they see is quite different, so their values are also different.Well
, I do want them to do something good about that.
yes  I
mean, you're a genius, Subaru-senpai.
There's something I've never done before, but I've never done it before.
From now on, are there any
characters you're interested in?
Ah, good.
I fell in love with you too. Tsukura-chan is amazing.  I
guess this big shield is really
cool.I have a really
small one and an 18 limo version of Perfume.It
comes in a set with Perfume, so they both have a scent.  I heard that you're
going to do it.
Hey, there are some goodies like that.
Next time we meet, please bring them.
[Laughs] I
think you should take a look at more about [music], so I
guess I'll watch some videos.  Now, I'd
like to watch the video, so let
me know when it's finished. See you here. A quick
farewell to Kihara and Hashibashi-sensei.
Now, let's watch the Arise battle together.
Here it is
[Music]  It
's over.
[Music] I'll
finish him off now.
[Music] He's
super stylish. I'll
fight him.
But the
combos are amazing.
Subaru can fight like this, too. It's pretty fast-paced.
[Music]
It's
really weird.  It's
really weird
[Music] The
relationship between the two of them seems interesting
[Music]
Did you see it? Teacher, I
thought I should watch this one more time.  It was really
worth watching. Isn't it cool? It's
cool. It feels really good when you connect a combo. That's one of the points.
Well, in fact, in previous Tales games, it was
common to guard against enemy attacks.
But in that Arise, everyone
except Kisara doesn't have a guard, so
instead of that, there's that dodge button, and
that
booze counter is the
key to the fun, right?
Counters,
yeah, there are counters that I've avoided. Of course, Exora can still block with that big shield, but yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes," there are counters that I avoided. Well, it's basic. Sorry, sorry, but like my senpai
said, the combos seem to be a lot of fun.
"  That's what I was saying, but this too.Yes, it's
certainly a familiar system from Tales, and it
's a fun system to hit the kelp technique,
and what's more, I really like that one
too.  It
was in the video, and there
was a big scene where Shion-chan suddenly did something like this, and
when it came to something like a combo technique, she
said, oh yeah, that Peya-jutsu, a boost attack, a boost strike, etc.  However, this is a pair technique where you work with your friends. As you
work together to use room techniques, boosts,
tag material strikes, etc., you
can have fun battling at a very fast pace.  I
think we'll be able to take out more and more enemies.
[Music] That's
our image. It's okay. It's okay. The chemistry is
gone. It's okay. You
can attack the combo and activate it with one button on the way.
That's it.  It seems like you can do it with one button. Um, it
was in the bottom left, but in the bottom left there
was an icon of that member, and if it
was glowing, it meant that this girl
could use this bazaar in the renewal, for example, so
during battle.  It's
good to add something like this once in a while.For example, a
low punch
comes out, but if you use it at the right time,
that
equipment will break, so
use it in such cases.Use
low to match the enemy with strong equipment.
For example, in that renewal, there are techniques that can stop the
enemy's spells, and there are
many such
techniques.If you use them at the right time, it will be
very powerful.  I
'm going to clean it up.The teacher
had a lot of really cool techniques, didn't he?It was so
easy to perform that technique that even Subaru could
do it right away.I wonder if
everyone can do this with Subaru?I've seen
some battles in other Tales games.  There
may have been some parts that I thought were difficult,
but Arise was really easy to remember, even though I'm no good at it,
so I think it's very easy to understand.
Moreover, there were combo techniques
and techniques that we had seen in the series so far, so it was quite
exciting.You can
also connect them in the future, and
even people who are playing this kind of game for the first time are
wondering what to do.  It means that even those who have become 100% can easily
pull off big tricks, don't you, sir?
That's right. Do
n't give up. I'm
relieved, sir. There's only one thing about Subaru that I ca
n't feel at ease about.
That's what I'm about to do in the
comprehension test.  I
can't rest assured about this.
Are you ready? Senpai, are you able to manage your thoughts?
Please leave it to me, Sensei, just a little. Subaru. I
'll answer without looking at you. Ok, I
think Subaru-senpai can do it. Yes,
then.  First of all, if you
have any questions, I can give you hints,
so please feel free to let me know.First of all, let's start with the
first question.What is the
correct combination?It's really a
test-like question.Please
wait a moment.
I get it, so it's Alpine's side. She's
a slave and the lever is Shion-chan's, so she's
the master, so this is 1. Is it 1?
[Music]
[Laughter]
Let me explain again, Lena and Dana are
sitting next to each other.  It's
been 300 years since they invaded and ruled Dana on the planet. The
Confidence is
divided by five rulers of Reina known as the Sharp.
Alpha and his companions
travel to different places.  I
see that you will be contributing to the fight to liberate the Ordinances.Is your
technical ability high?
It says that you unilaterally invaded 7, but that's
true.I do
n't know how much I can say, but
don't worry, it's not at all like that slide.  It
says that the number 7 is divided into five, and each one is in control.Teacher.It is
divided into five.Yes, yes, yes, that's right.Then, the
next question is, what are the
characteristics of the terrible Zion?
Which one is it? I don't have the qualifications. I can use a gun. I can use the power of termination. Or I have a small appetite. I've come up with a rather delicate question. I guess this is a characteristic. Are there two answers? Which one is it?
Huh? 2  Isn't it 3 pieces?
But somehow, I do
n't remember if it was explained that the ability to use ``is the power of spirits'' or not, but I definitely used 10, so yeah, that's
true.
Yes,
Shin
used a gun.  If you
call it with a boost attack and do a linked attack, it
will use tune, so it
will shoot down aerial attacks.Yes, I said that,
but yeah, there is no junior high school,
so we haven't met.The
world of Arise is
familiar to increase.  It
's not a spirit,
it's even Hoshino. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it. I can't read it; I can't read it; I can't read it; I can't read it; I can't read it.  I
love to eat a lot, so I'm
not a big eater. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I
think there was a slide where she ate a lot. Also, Shion-
chan, Shion-chan's Jun
is the result of Rena's technical ability. This,
one more time.  Please tell me, Shion-
chan's gun was created by Rena's extremely high
technical ability. I
wonder if only Kokone-chan can use this.
What's more, Rena people
can use techniques using spiritual power.  The
power I want and this. I'm sorry. Do you understand
? In this question about the spiritual power of the stars, I'm talking about pixies and other fairy-type spirits. This is a trick.
Yes
yes. Sorry, it was complicated. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
LINEstamps are
popular.  It says a little bit about the release.
This person's question is, ``Shion eats.'' Let's
stop doing this, Sensei.
Maybe he just wanted to show it to me. The
next question is. Which one is wrong?
Yes, there are resistances other than Alfen among the Danachin,
or the rule of the Renachin
has continued for 300 years, and the number of people using it against the school is
suddenly increasing.There are still 7 Kisaras,
but I am satisfied with my life.
Or
Rimmel is good at fighting and is the only one among his friends who can use guard, or Rimmel is
good at attack and magic.Which one is wrong?Is
n't it a girl who is the only one who can use guard?
[Applause] That's a
really nice thing to remember.No,
everything else is correct.No, that's what I was
thinking, isn't it?Ro-kun is a fighter, but he
doesn't use his guard and has a lot of spirit.I
thought he was going to get in.That's right.It's
true that Mr. Sensei.  This is the gift of teaching.Ah, that's
good, that's good, but wait, there
's an explanation.Teacher, I'll
explain everything a little bit.I
think everyone has understood by now.
However, in this game,
only Kisara, who is holding the vertical position, uses guard.The
exhilarating feeling of seeing the enemy's attack and countering it is
also recommended for those who have played DAYSoffar so far
[Music] I
resisted more and more.  The
rule has continued for 300 years, and there's
a lot of things about it.I
learned this.I like it.Actually,
this
may have been more than a question.Ah, more than a question.Okay,
Professor, I
have more to explain, so that Central Harim...  It is
said that Mochizuki's master protects the Menancians, a distant and coexisting country, with a shield.This is a bit of a
battle scene, isn't it?It's pretty cool.There's something
amazing about it.The
only one who can control the guard is
Kisara, who has a shield.  It's like this. Yes, that's what I mean. It's really
cool.
It's cool. It's fun. It feels good.
Well, once it's decided, the
[music]
thing
is already [music] fun. I basically listen to other Tales.
In games, I
always leave the magician characters
to the computer, but
I've tried using it once in a while.It's surprisingly
easy to use and fast, and the
pace at which it casts magic is fast.However, it's
true that Subaru and Abyss have done quite a bit of that.  I
think Symphonia uses Lloyd and Luke all the time as main characters,
right? I
think they basically only use main characters, but Arise uses quite a few other characters.  Once you
feel like using the characters, I
think it will be a lot of fun if you try using them. Try
using a lot of different characters. Moreover,
Mazinken Shunji Shion-
chan came up with the idea of mastering the familiar techniques.  Gane Heart Lace
Circle Resurrection
Holy Dance Thunder Blade What's this? What's
this tall claw? It's
like an attack. What's this?
Limb Selection Some words look familiar
.  I
like the Grand Dasher, the one where the dirt turns into a bar, and the one where the tiger turns out to be a bar.That's probably why it's
Subaru.Subaru has new human rights and what else?
Everyone uses that Subaru a lot.  That
guy used to use it a lot to evade.What is
that? It spins around.I wonder if there's something like Rayquazan.
Yes, Subaru's most memorable technique is Rayquazan.
Well, maybe there is one. I
thought it was something like cutting through the sky while spinning round and round, but there are so
many different
techniques. I'm sure there were techniques, but this one...  I don't know if it happened or
not, but I don't remember it, but it's
a lot of things.I'm looking forward to it, as there are some techniques I've used before.Yes,
please try out all those characters and
play.Yes, I'm interested in it.  I want to
play the game.Oh, I've
tried it, but
what should I play if I actually want to play it now?
Thank you for the good question, teacher.It also comes
with the new DLC for 6,800 yen
+J
Plus.  I
recommend the Rise Beyond edition, which will be
released on November 9th, but pre-orders have already started. If you
pre-order now, you can download and play the main game right away. As I
said earlier, you can start playing it now.  I
'd like you to make a reservation.By
the way,
as a bonus for early purchasers,
special costumes for Alpen and Shion will be
available from November 9th.You can see them in the next slide.They're
really cute.That's how cute
these
costumes are, to commemorate the release of Tenjou Balance.  It
was also in the illustration of ``It's
great to have a matching set.'' You really have a lifetime to live, but
every day
when you play the game, you go back to your whole life.They're
so cute.
By the way, I'm
sure there are quite a few people who are watching this stream who have already played Arise, or who have bought or played Arise.
After all, should I look forward to this
new downloadable content
?
Hmm, well, I'm in the same situation.
So it's almost time for me to be able to play Beyond Down on CDLC,
but it's coming soon in November.  I
think it's coming, but here it is.The
new character that appeared at the end of the previous PV
appears.The main story is a new story.The
play time
is about 20 hours,
but there are a lot of quests and
loads.  It seems like there's more volume than that. I'm really looking
forward to it. It's going to be
released on November 9th, and it's DLC, but you can pre-order it, and it
comes with the bonuses I mentioned earlier, so
check it out. Yes, it's a lot of volume.
Yes, this cat is a new character. What a
new character. I'm
so happy to have more
characters. If you've played the game before, please
give it a try. Yes, this one too. There
are trailers and other things, so
please everyone.  Even when the broadcast is over, please watch
it. It's a very mysterious, mysterious existence. It's a
mysterious existence. I
can't understand much just by watching it, but everyone.
Think about all kinds of things.What kind of person are you?
Everyone is thinking about
whether they're your enemies or your friends.Is that a secret?Well, that
's fine.I don't know
what to do about that.  I see. I'm
looking forward to it.
There's a [music] set, so I bought that set,
went back and bought it
for 6,800 yen
+ tax. This set is genius.
Now is the time to play Arise.There
's no choice but to play
Arise.Even if you've downloaded it, you haven't played Arise
yet.If you haven't played the main game yet, it's
best to play Arise first.  Yeah, probably.
Yes, of course, that's what we're going to do now. It's
not too late now. There are
spoilers, so please play the main story first. I
see, everyone.
By the way, I wonder if there are quite a few of our listeners who have also completed Arise.
I also completed it during the distribution. I played it all from the beginning
to the end,
but yeah, it's downloadable content. It's
pretty amazing when it's around 20 hours long.
So I'm looking forward to the DLC. There
are people who haven't played it now.
Start with the main story, then play the downloadable content.
Clear the main story. If you've already enjoyed it, please
enjoy the downloadable content.
[Music] I
really wanted to play it. It's
fun, the characters are really interesting, and
Fururu is cute, so if you wear it, you'll be crazy.  I'm falling in love with you  I'm
sure there's a lot to look forward to now, so I'm glad they've already done it. There hasn't been much DLC for Tales so far, so I
can't wait for it to come out, but I
can't wait.  Until that day, I
will continue to watch Subaru-senpai's journey through Tales of Lies.First of all, the
main character who is lost and the
heroine who feels pain when touched are both
unique and good.  I
think it's interesting to look at the historical story of the emancipation of slaves from various standpoints, and I think it's interesting to
see the characters.I think there are a lot of attractive characters, so how do they
interact with each other?  I don't care about that, and after all, I
've heard that Arise's gummies are amazing, so there's a lot of gummies too.I've
heard so much that gummies are serious and fights are dangerous, so the ocean is still there.  I
'm really curious about what happened to the
gummies. I wonder if Subaru was really that concerned about the gummies. It's
okay.
When I asked him about it on stream, everyone couldn't wash them and it was funny. So it's really funny.  The
first thing that came up when I asked what was interesting about it was
something like Arise's gummies are terrible.I
don't understand either, but what do you mean?
Yes, yes,
garbage is the best. We are all saved by gummies. It's
true, I'm a little excited to see what kind of gummy will come out. I'm
sure there will be some.  Well,
let's play for a while and see how big the gummy is. Well, I'm
starting to wonder how this story will turn out in the end, so if I
were to play Subaru, I'd start with the main game.  I hope you enjoy it.
[Music]
So that's all for today.
So,
Mr. Kihara, thank you very much for today. It
was a bit difficult to explain in Japanese, but I
feel like you understood me. It's amazing. That Kirara, that
Japanese girl.  If you say it's not, it's that, but
Chiara, her original Japanese is kind of
like that second, or rather, it's like I usually bought it.I don't really like it,
but it's amazing.The
characters are speaking in English.  It's normal  That's
right. Thank you very much, teacher. We
did it in English. The
voice actors
were really good. Oh, yeah, that's right. English.
Seriously, but the senpai will do it in Japanese
. I'll do it in Japanese. Thank you.  Thank
you. It
was fun. I was able to appeal to today's seniors. I was able to
explain the characters very well.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Yes, that's
all for today.
So, what should we do at the end?  Do you
want me to accompany you, Chiara-sensei?
OK, I'll go with you. Do you want me
to accompany you? Teacher, I'll see you then. I'll see you soon. See you
bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
[Music]