[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
a
[Music]
[Applause]
e
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
oh da
[Music]
what what did I
say k
kid Kitty Kido k k just Kido Kido I
don't remember
k
[Music]
key are you now with 1080p okay
nice F too
small F too small to
perceive I can give you this one
kid the game sounds are so loud in my
ears ah so loud wait where do I have my
I wonder where I have my
gun no
no where's my
[Laughter]
gun look at this ah back all of you
kneel in front of me and show me your
dedication to the Frog Overlord that is
me frogy waa I hope you bought the
merch you bought the merch
right
yes or if you
prefer um
uh uh ah
no if you prefer I can slap your butt
too slap slap slap
slap yeah froggy bble again it's been a
long
time thank you for welcoming me back you
guys you guys look so beautiful I love
to see my little tat Poes you have't
grown at all ever since I left you my
little tag PES so small you
you so so small oh I think you can maybe
tell so so so
small the gun has no trigger of course
it has a trigger the trigger is you cuz
you're triggering
me okay guys we're going to start the fr
week we're going to play games lots of
fun frog games because frog games are
the only ones that matter
obviously H is the sound okay cuz it's
so loud in my ears I wish I could make
it more quiet but I think I have to have
it this loud for the sake of
entertainment it's quite loud really oh
nice
nice ah that was made too quiet how
about
now I have a fum glass let's
[Music]
go uh better that's better okay tell me
tell me I mean this is just the starting
screen music
[Music]
so m
okay no I didn't drink the fum
ew no I would never do such a thing now
that's crazy we're going to move a
little little bit over
here I'm just going to use this as my
gaming screen because I feel bad if I
don't you
know um make use of this scen but I
realized even
um we don't talk about this but even
when kiata is back which of course she
will never be she has a frog Cape which
would be really good to use with this
background perhaps
so not too bad to continue using it I
think she'll never be of course never
never I will not let her take control of
you guys
again she is not the right person not
the right leader for
you now
um
[Music]
what does this work yes it work this is
this is game why why does game
have is this like part of the game the
top the top bar looks a little bit funky
to
me ah
oopsie uh uh I I want to my
[Music]
bger oh oh my God ah where' that go like
I don't know do we where do we put it uh
ah wait I need to put my
merch merch
go merch
merch nice froggy waa is becoming
official streamer just like her
predecessor is that the
word frog bad Tech all the keys are so
sticky is it my hands is it my hands my
everything thinging is so
sticky princess is oh my God English
look at the
frogs look look at the frogs a frog frog
maybe I can find frog bird
somewhere do you think there is frog
bird somewhere here I'm going to take a
fro candy already cuz froggy wa voice I
tried to be a look little
cuter
[Music]
fry W it's been 5 years
no frog bird frog bird I miss you come
back to
[Music]
me
no
a how do
[Music]
I
cute I me you frog bird frog bird wrote
to
me last night and was like oh my God
you're so cute
and then I said look frog bird you're
included in the video and also look at
the background you're included in the
background your name is there and she
was like oh my
God or how frog would say oh my God no
how would frog say like like sounds kind
of like kerit right oh my God no what
what the I don't I I can't
impersonate he
he
he he he he I never said she I have a
lisp I have a
Lis yes it's um
because
yeah sorry for I I I should know what
gender frog bird is I know I know better
than
you is this screen big enough guys I
think I could
uh change
n just keep it like this but I I wonder
if this top bar is supposed to be there
it's so
weird wait what did I
do I just do like this okay
yeah you need to see me too yeah very
important thank you you get the point
don't think it should be there I mean I
can cut it
but it's kind of cute it gives me these
point and click Vibes because this is
the point and click game look frog cute
oh my God is this the whole game I'm
already entertained by it but no it's
probably not the whole game I would be
fine if this was the whole game if this
was just like You observe the frogs
everyday life like a screen saver
yeah it's a hand drawn game and it's
yeah it's like qu qu should I come in
front of the screen guys what you
[Music]
think I'm so
bigy you light up my like nobody
[Music]
else
you know you beautiful yeah W froggy wa
listens to One
[Music]
Direction froggy W I have One Direction
fan you don't know you
beautiful singing towards frog
bird you like the villain I am
that song is a banger nothing wrong with
it oh we got raided oh thank you thank
you kid I right I forgot I'm supposed to
say
kid kid kid k k
[Music]
k hello I got little hands and that is
why you should
stay
welcome
[Music]
welcome Paul
nice I can put my hands together that's
one thing waa can't do she can't do
unless she 3D properly but she can't do
it as easily as me in her default form
I'm in my default
form okay let's get started oh this is
short game so we can read uh the
leftover super what the [\h__\h] is
this it's a peanut with a microphone
what the [\h__\h]
what can I do something already
wa
what what is this transformation from
frog
to maybe it's frog bird that fa gave me
a brain ah yeah cuz normally frog not
have much
brain but now you have brain and that
make you
grow impress
iive I got to go after it qu qu he looks
so
funny wait so point and click this jump
off
oh W look at him go look at him go can I
eat fly I want to
eat stay here stay here oh it's flying
away from me it's flying away from oh
when you get too close it makes this
like oh cute oh the music is
[Music]
Chill can you hear the beautiful inspect
am I frog
detective I thought this was different
game you feel a breeze coming from the
crack can I pick up this Leaf no look
how he
runs oh we can jump I feel like normally
people would go to the right side by
intuition but I went to this side I hope
that's
okay oh that might be dead end right now
anyway what's this red oh it's ball oh
what what what the [\h__\h] did I
do was that like some
lever can I bring it over no I don't
think so I can't go around it but now I
can maybe
fly I get the
leave
[Music]
yay
ha amazing I totally knew what I was
doing there that you probably can get as
well you fly fly come here
fly no fly
no give
me it's okay I have gummy worms
talk wait I candy in my mouth it's kind
of hard to do the sound now it's just a
frog okay just a frog just a box just a
frog you peanut
man why did you give me brain life was
happier without brain canot y it's
snail oh am I in the way oh sorry sorry
I Mo if you give me fre ah I already
have two oh now let's
go
oh he went back with a funny sound we
still have a frog in your for right now
it's
okay it could be worse hey yo inspector
looks like a good place for Lily Pad a
cuz there's a leaf over there wait Lily
Pad where would I get another Lily
[Music]
Pad the
last the the last one how do I get there
choke the mother isn't this game so cute
though wait I see something there isn't
it so cute oh take is it a
seed wait it is a lily seed really they
look like
this it looks like Yoshi's Island a that
hand drone style
mhm yeah it's all handron it's a really
Charming little game
I got the last one y that was that was
kind of like you know a nice riddle but
manageable for froggy waa brain very
good very
lovely hello snail friend I have I have
Lea for you yes you can do it here do I
give to you oh
Lea he ate
it
oh what a delight isn't it just like
those gummy worms if you find any Gummy
Worms make sure to you know bring him to
me I'm helping you out here don't forget
about
that see you later he roll away goodbye
snail
man
Y what is this
chicken I thought y'all or TP now
there's no chickens allowed here
anymore oh
rain hello I just saw this wait is a
duck I think it says
qu maybe it's a
duck he saw a strange fairy passed by
here oh my gosh it can only be the
one it was heading towards the
town I think it's a duck then that is I
can forgive if it's
a too small
what do I become
small stick
nice
fire maybe grilled
frog the tops of these wooden thingies
look like
eggs what are you
doing
no I must burn it wait I look like Frog
King For a
Moment is it is it too loud by the way
the music I feel like became
louder it's long oh no can I go in
here oh my God cute this is so
cute why do I hear a cat
purring where where is the
cat oh we got a sheet or fabric cat
maybe under the blanket no I can sleep
until night aha maybe if that seems like
something we need to do
eventually I hear a cat puring I
like my cats are purring so kiaha cats
are purring so much K they are in love
with me I think or they're or it's their
soothing um Power they're sad that that
[\h__\h] is gone so they Tred to s s
themselves okay maybe I'm a little bit
stuck now oh wait I can do something
with the fire wait
just uh it will burn up quick if it's
just a stick a I thought I can make a
torch and then burn this
part A but
no if it's just what I don't know ah can
I I can
craft UNL wait that's how you make a
torch
waa it does look like a
wow learning
survival 10one oh now it's gone okay but
we get to go
through is it donkey or
bunny I'm falling weed my whole garden
got covered overnight this is going to
take me all day maybe I can help him I
don't know
no but we can go into his house which is
a little pot also very
[Music]
cute wait I he purring again and again
there's no cat what is this
phenomenon where are the
cats nothing in here that I can
take oh I can read this it's a book
about gardening chapter one finding
seeds seeds can be found in grassy areas
Kido it requires a Keen Eye to spot
one oh yeah I have to agree was uh
difficult to see the one that we found
previously what
fishmen look at these
fishmen they they constantly look
upwards must be a hard life for them oh
thank you for the Super Chat and
come atlantans Fishman the Fishman
Sakana
Sakana and now SL
down a
custom what what what wait a wait I can
take the can I take the droplets but
anyway I'm not a customer but are you
going to sell me something
hello hello welcome to fish shop plank
bottle and the sink whoo sinkstone is
very expensive I don't think I have any
any money do
I don't ask me why I got it can
I hey you way short coins get serious we
get lost wrong get out
sh no money where frogy waa get money
where oh bounce
bounce hello do you have money for me
can you spare a little Co coin for the
froggy wa wa frog coin maybe it's a
simple life you know my brother is
always dressing about everything I wish
he could relax a bit
more he doesn't care about the frog
coins
STS destroy that bridge she wouldn't do
something like that now I'm supposed to
fix it why is it always me I'm I don't
think it was ah but for that you need
the
plank I don't think it was the fairy
that seems like you
oh like you're spreading some bad bad
rumors dark cave up and the
swamp the swamp to that side not a hold
and here you need uh another seat
perhaps
but I caught the drop let's go now can I
put this blank here so I don't actually
need to oh wait maybe I have to buy one
cuz this only covered a little bit of
the
space do you ah wait no he's not really
growing
anything I trust your fellow animal over
f f f
f drop something drop
something what could no wait now that I
don't need the fire anymore can
I
yo I got money but I was also hoping to
get the remaining planks but I guess
it's not really considered planks but I
get a coin okay one coin wait we got a
drop again maybe we needed how do I get
over here I never
drop there's a there's a seed over
there I'm still too small
swim I can't swim froggy waa is bad
swimmer apparently I think that was part
of the lore was
it I them there wasn't there a book in
here
too it's a
diary I lent my backyard out to fish
shoping town he wanted to store some
Goods there and that's all fine but he
dropped a key in the water yesterday I
hope he will find it soon a key get off
for here I suppose there's a ah there's
another plank over
there a key in the water but I can't
enter the
water wait I can go up here I thought I
couldn't why com
one let's go kid oh that looks
[Music]
delicious but I guess I'm not supposed
to eat it maybe you can exchange
for
something
hello can I look don't touch my special
stone is in there do you know how
expensive that
is give me
something well you don't he doesn't have
anything for one coin wait can I sell
you water here
take no what a B BM
[Music]
no not looking so good
guys we didn't talk to
him hey BR if you find me
free worm number
one take which will not give us the
secret yet but it's one step in the
right direction he liks the
warm this one's locked too but we didn't
go in here did we oh I can't
can't oh my God I'm
stuck I think
I'm
stuck I
bre
oh
[\h__\h] I got the one from making the the
the ground wet which kind of does make
sense that's amazing kidle now last one
I don't know what about the weeds no
like wait maybe I got to be closer
no hat how do I help him with the
wings there's a worm in the jar I saw I
saw but when I go
inside he's out maybe I maybe I again
need to put some
water thank you r on frog
and thank you what is this can I like
put it
uh I drank it
no it's
behind thank you for getting the merch
guys thank you so much oh I can't go
behind then we got all the worms which
will bring us further
K did
you potato
seeds
[Music]
yo amazing potato potato now you give me
secret meet me in my house at night I'll
show you something cool
o secret randevoo did you guys get the
merch I was I'm trying to ask you a
question did you guys get the
merchandise well not get it but like did
you order
it give
me yeah thank you I'm so happy so many
of you say that you really like the
merchandise idea this time I'm really
happy to hear
that where do I put the potato
seeds maybe when the weeds are gone over
[Music]
here otherwise I don't really
know end of the week I'm getting ah yeah
cuz I guess it's the end of the month so
you can wait for your for your money
from
work from your from your workplace to
come oh hello sorry for sleeping in your
bed CLE but you don't mind right I I
made your bed really slimy it's
comfortable trust
me oh I I knew it I knew it a patch of
fertile soil take this put potato seed
and grow grow
[Music]
big wait I'll add some water and maybe
we have to wait until the next
day n NY I'll order new merch soon I got
Ki was travel tag and travel book in the
main last week let's
go I don't really care about that cuz
that's not my merch I
guess well thank you though thank you
time to frog mimir I just came from
mimir oh you're still fishing huh
fishing is a 24/7 kind of job huh you're
not biing tonight maybe I should have
used to make I maybe like a worm but I
don't have any more worms I don't know
if there will be any more
worms was there was there a bed in here
oh yeah hello wait I don't think I
entered this house before I should be
off to bed but I keep hearing something
wiggling ah is a
worm another
worm oh my god let's go kidle worm worm
worm here ah
wait surely you'll give me something in
exchange
gnarly
gnarly let's see if I can catch
something with
this oh here we go mine mine mine mine m
my mind you don't need that anyway right
cuz you can't eat it you can't eat it
so okay I know where to go oh the fire
is on again
H yes we got a plank
and don't think you can do anything with
that why is that here there's a crow
Quon
Quon looks broken
no okay so all I got was another plank
for now new B yeah there's quite a few
BS that's so nice to see no no not nice
to see I I I I hate
BDS I hate
birds with all my
passion F
Birds they suck cuz they want to eat
frog
occasionally m
danger okay
now I think it became
bigger looks a bit thirsty okay
okay you must
grow more
more ah I got the put
wait I thought it was grow so big that I
could step on it but no now I just have
a potato and I don't know what to do
with this
potato nearly fix keep it up I'm trying
kid is that a
steak meet me in my house at night I
show you something oh wait I forgot
about
him
okay I need a room to sleep in it's so
nice that everybody lets me sleep in
their
beds oh this is pretty nice
of
[Music]
them yeah you like my plate of worms I
like my plate of worms don't you dare
touch
it uh
no no don't sit there
that H okay okay okay which house in
here no can't go in here ah it's open
during the night
I think thank you oh my God why did he
go upstairs I was like oh only he is in
here but it's a two floor twostory home
man I'm be off to bed soon got a long
day
tomorrow let me go let me
climb hello is this is this this
our W the V place this is my
telescope wait I I like how it goes
through the this
thing when I take a look yeah but also I
want to read your book it's a diary um
what are you doing okay okay okay I I
I'll sit and I'll take a look peek I PE
through the telescope
kiddo how to can I move
it I don't think I can move it ah
water water on the tree
why is there something supposed to be
happening
here maybe maybe in the future
oh it's a p and click and I can't ah
wait ah wait now I can move
it what am I supposed to
see let's look around around around
around he's still fishing that's fine
he's just a hardworking
Fishman wait I just realized the irony
of a Fisher man
fish somebody stop him no what is he
doing is he opening the door oh that's
actually
great that's actually great okay what
are these like music locks that I like I
saw these music notes elsewhere
too I wonder know what that's
about it run into the tree I've got to
find a way in there well now now we can
easily go in there cuz now it's
open wait how to go
down how to go ah wait here oh a
different I no it's the same optical
illusion
uh you don't know
how oh no
okay we got to find other things to do I
have a potato I have a coin and I have a
stick
surely one of these things will be
useful right here's also one of
these can you croak I I can totally
croak that's what I do all day wait we
can burn something again no actually we
can't cuz I don't have a
cloth but I feel like there might also
still be something to do up
here wait I can go up here it's a nest
but there's no egg oh no h maybe I need
to put something there potato would
probably not help
right
potato can I put the stick there I can H
just one stick is not
enough it won't even it won't even take
one at a time
the
coin can't go
up what about you
no it's okay it's okay froggy wble we'll
figure it out K two combined sticks I
need another stick Duck's house late
tree town was I in here
before hey help
me I keep worrying about my little you
lost an
egg which is maybe the one that's up
here normally I did not take it though
maybe it's
underneath can I poke
it or or someone's guarding the Egg and
I have to replace it with the
potato use the
[Music]
potato ah maybe should I should I
actually put in here no uh doesn't
doesn't doesn't react I think
no but maybe we really have to replace
it
somewhere wherever we find the egg in
order to
get uh the egg
maybe maybe that will be the way to
go maybe we're going to make it daytime
again who
knows oh look he looks so cute when he
sleep
K good morning
kid yeah I'm already playing FR
detective why are there Wheats
again how is this possible also why is
there can we talk about the monkey up
there what is he
doing Monkey
[Music]
Business I'm
lost
I wish I could buy something I still
only have one coin it's not very helpful
maybe I can throw the potato no can I
throw the coin
[Music]
no maybe there's an egg
now I
check it's not visible
but there no egg
no B is open again hopefully bear will
have time to look at my ladder soon bear
then I can start searching for my egg
bear you mean that thing is that
supposed to be a that's not a bear
right that's not a bear is this a
bear I kind of thought it was something
else but maybe you're I guess cuz he's
also trying to fix the the um
bridge but can he maybe only go and fix
the the the ladder when he's done with
the
bridge fix with the stick I tried but it
said I'll need more than one
stick can't believe I'm
lost you guys have not played this game
have you maybe I can did I try to poke
this can't poke
potato oh wait I can go back here did I
try this
before
uh can't can't reach
anything uh
significant rain played this a little
bit
really maybe that's what I'm thinking of
uh when I think about uh I I remember
cuz I requested perms for a couple of
frog games months in advance actually
planning way in advance and then I saw
somebody
playing uh one of my frog games I was
like
H I'm glad somebody else gets some
enjoyment out of my frog games
kidle I think I think I don't know what
to
do coin in the nest I did not get a coin
out of this
huh wait maybe I make it wet no maybe I
should burn it I should burn it but I
need the cloth again then cuz I can't
make it
bur it will burn up
quickly the mouse have smear frames what
does that
mean did you try climbing the stair I
did I think it said I can't
no cuz it's
broken
huh looks broken is broken kle
factual
roasted potatoes I mean nobody asked for
that but can I combine them
no I could use it as fuel I guess
but no no roasting of potato but nice
idea Kettle nice M roasted
potatoes oven oven potatoes open fire
hello naan cotton thank you thank you
uh did did frogy wa say
[Laughter]
d what about here no something about
this mushroom is sussy too like I feel
like I can use it to bounce off of it
but I can't get on top of it in the
first
place is this frog just kada what the
hell are you talking about of course not
maybe I need to run through more grass
cuz sometimes it drops seeds
right wait let's read this dark C I read
this before here take no C no potato no
coin
no I I know I said I I Ribbit dirty I
know but what about fing somebody try
the chest in the watering can
house uh uh can I go in
now it's
locked can't enter now and at night
they're protecting it
K oh [\h__\h] I'm I'm lost developers do
kid the model looks like good thank you
for people who don't know it's not the
first time I used it can I put the
potato in here no there was frog week
before but somehow somehow this [\h__\h] K
she regained control over everything
again and then she put me in that stupid
glass bowl again and I was I
was I
was I was stuck in there and it was so
dark and so scary and I was all alone
again and nobody fed me gummy worms I
only got disgusting small small
food was not good at all
I never want to go back there again yeah
the whack ass crystal Prison also I
think I'm allergic to her stupid cats
because my nose is itchy my nose is
itchy it was a clear glass excuse me I
want to dramatize my situation so that
you feel sorry for
me feel sorry for
me it's it's rough out there it's a
harsh life for frogy waa I need
everybody to buy my merchandise so I'm
not um financially dependent on her
anymore I'm
lost okay let's go into all houses again
and
see if if there's a hint
a book about gardening Oh chapter 2
huh no I mean that doesn't help me does
it frco dial
tears I bought a lot keychain on the
convention oh thank you I don't think
any money of that went to me but thank
you nonetheless thank you for supporting
the
artist
um a too
fix the bridge need free
planks co wait we can buy black we can
bu black we can bu black oh my God I'm
such a genius let's go get
off I was like oh another
Fire Let's Go a free
gift a a pouch to a to store my coins
I'm going to become rich kle oh my God
finally the
plank
yooo repair frog now we can go over here
what is this can I drop
no a new house a teapot house and I can
sit
here hey it's a CO it's a coin
yeah okay let's see who lives in here
who wasn't able to you know go anywhere
cuz of the bridge was broken a
frog frog frog bird is it
you she's always an old frog he's dying
is he dying oh
no oh young frog finally you right but
alas I have become terribly ill please
seek out a cure from me visit the crow
who lives deep in the forest she will
know what to
do she so maybe it
is let me read your
book it's a history book long ago
Kingdom blah blah blah H it's really
long and [\h__\h] waa don't read stick
inventory full okay I drink
okay nice ah totic totic we can f the B
oh he's fishing here now and trying out
a new fishing spot so Bear's taking a
look at the duck's ladder finally
apparently some Fair took her egg
away why would she do that she wanted to
go look for it but the ladder was broken
too I hope she finds it against no wores
I got it all on the
control the duck is
swimming
Bear's taking a look at my broken ladder
so I thought i' go for a swim kle
hopefully I can find my egg once it's
fixed don't by
me I'll find your egg and then I'll eat
it
kle h i was supposed to fix don't you're
so useless I'm fixing
everything ladder
part
wow so can
wow I want top of the
world now I can go here and we can look
at this and there's an egg red
egg why duck egg red why what a weird
block oh again we're not going to do
anything with that
okay oh I took the coin pouch still
takes up a slot but
okay M I can't go past I have to get rid
of this Coin Block of of this music
block first I guess
anyway
hello
uh hello what Old Toad is sick I'm I
think I can help I have told medicine
recipe and my booket in my house in the
forest here you need this to get there
huh a seat ah we got a new seed and what
is
this there's a partner thing okay I
don't even know what it's supposed to be
also I think this monkey is not alive I
think this monkey might be a
doll
okay perfect another seat where am I
supposed to put this seat
uh he said something in the forest where
is this
Forest tree to okay probably not down
here but let me check again if there's
like something down here
ah later we need to fix something over
there too kid all return to
[Music]
Monkey okay must be something on over on
that side
[Music]
k a oh wait maybe if I sleep for a night
then these people will be somewhere else
and they'll realize also that the bridge
is fixed
maybe uh yeah wait where the hell is
this Forest that he talked
about left side above ladder there was
something and I can't reach that place
can
I I'll take I'll take a drop I'll take a
drop what do you say about me fixing
this you fixed the ladder now we can
visit the forest again a wait a second
wait wait why did I not go
here
Forest gets access to letter completely
ignores what's up
there a we reach a different chapter too
okay Lily py let's
go it's kind of
unnecessary I think to put this here
because the fact that we're able to go
through the
tree I think we through for doing that
we got the the seed so it's connected
it's intertwined kiddle but logic is not
something I care for anyway kiddo
another seed I can enter this little
bird
house finally access to the bird's
Chambers Kido Kido it's a recipe book
you scroll to the ladder T aha to
Medicine I the crow house one green leaf
a fresh life worm lasting one
golden
fly he wait was that at the
end I was done reading when I heard
fly uh cook well for best effect okay um
coin go in here two
coins can sleep wait I forgot
it was a worm and a fly and a leaf
right Green Leaf Life worm golden fly
cook okay cook the pasta oh hello are
you here now I already L the k for you
oh thank you I found the
recipe I have none of the ingredients
but I can only be found in the forest if
you found one just put it in the kettle
over there kle okay I'm surprised I
still don't need my potato
kiddo oh looks like a good place for
little
pad what is this other thing though ah
it's wait optical illusion it's just the
plants over
there okay okay okay okay
tomato wait I can roll the tomato and
it's going to be like a lever
again wait
where where tomato
go
oh the breeze coming through the crack
yeah but uh last time this was easier I
just moved it a little bit and it just
worked oh what do I do with this
tomato maybe not for
now maybe somebody has to eat it or so I
don't know ah we need another lilyat and
there's the
worm
ah what's
here let's go and what's
this no nothing
okay okay okay Building
Bridges
get
ta I am frog I have special skill to
grow Lily Pad immediately
okay we have the worm there's another
fire here maybe I extinguish and get
frog
coin yeah now we have free
stks okay uh I think that's all over
here always always bring a little
droplet with you you never
know what might come from it here Worm
but if I put it in so early now and if I
really need a long time to get the rest
of the stuff then won't it be super
overcooked maybe I should eat it maybe I
should eat it
instead no must resist must
resist away from my eyes I must not look
I must not perceive worm get out of my
eyes get all out of my hand
[Music]
okay yes I'm hungry frog always
hungry wait I can go down over there
nice oh ah here
too oh oh
oh go this way there's
flies fly Paradise oh about right they
let go away from me and there's no
golden fly but maybe if I combine flies
ah you can catch them let's go combine
fly no maybe if I have all
[Music]
flies
M come here come here
no
now my inventory is full what do I do
can I eat I can't eat
what but
what how how do I get a golden one fly
sighting spot yeah my favorite spot a
rare fly was seen on this island because
there were no other fly wait a golden
fly that's probably just a uh um the
glowy one that I have in my back WR too
no is that not what it is it was very
easy to spot so maybe I have to go here
at night time because it's a
firefly oh
wait okay no more flies oh no never mind
never mind never [\h__\h] mind
no come here come here come here a got
the golden one it's from Harry
Potter okay I think my idea was really
good to to like just come at night time
to you know think of it as a
riddle cuz it says a rare site so people
only see it at night that's why it's
rare and it's actually not a golden fly
it's just uh you
know you know I'm I'm such a genius and
they did not use my genius kiddo I
prefer you better me
too me too kidle we got the golden fly
what was the last thing a leaf right a
leaf shouldn't be too
difficult
[Music]
M wait you can't go up
here well then then that makes
absolutely no sense what it
fight
okay
I wonder how it
taste okay okay
okay well the Tomato in I already rolled
it there but it didn't react wait I'm
stuck I'll try it
again oh no wait we didn't even check
here there's also a crack
[Music]
here the cracking the SN e you're also
kind of a
kraken how you doing do you want a
potato oh wait you would want a tomato
No snails love tomatoes don't they hello
again I'm so hungry but this time for an
orange an
orange I can feed you the remains of
takanasi
Kiara gladly we shall Feast on it
together
orange orange no more
orange no more orange
what a waste of a golden fly I would
love to consume it
instead but cannot do what's
this
ah see look at that it was over here
oh okay
wait I need something heavy to put there
but I don't think I can't put the Tomato
there can I
[Music]
what the hell is this wait is this
actually an orange wait wait wait I just
realized remind me of orange
actually it's a little bit too red
actually on maybe it's maybe it depends
on my screen cuz on my other screen it
looks more
orange it's an orange
orange
ah how do I transport this
how I guess I
guess I guess it might be uh transported
once the air comes out I can make it
fly if I roll it over the wind M but
that still means I need something heavy
to put on
top ah hey another Lily Pad space oh
also it has a button over there what the
[\h__\h] is it with my potato
kiddo I'm really curious about the
potato I would try putting the orange
all right wait I just put it there and I
leave it there and then I go to the
other side
ah
I didn't think about that
kidos kind of smart you know it's kind
of
difficult no
no yes perfectly covered
kle let's see what happens
SK oh
what a coincidence it's going exactly
where I needed to go
H this must
be uh uh
sufficient it might not be Tak but it
kind of reminds reminds one of of her
and
honestly snail has not much brain either
oh I see oh [\h__\h] I stuck there okay so
they might think this is takanasi
Ki orange equal I know what to do I know
what to do guys I know what to do
Kido this goes here and then Lily
Pad everything is coming in
place yay get look look look look
[Music]
look there you
go you're so welcome wait is there
something to over here
no
okay
interesting this game is so cute and I I
I do like the
riddles here take take
orange I don't know what to think about
your very specific taste buds it's kind
of annoying but okay very demanding just
like me I found a
mutual orang okay okay I'll move out way
he can roll I
like
coin coin stons coin stons FR coin
stons where does this lead me to the
live
[Applause]
yay now we have all the ingredient wait
can I jump down from
here
I think I can
yes we can make the
medicine and save the
life okay got to cook well maybe it's
fresh toad medicine use a container to
take some oh no I don't have a
container it's over it's so
over wait wait the shop was selling uh I
think a bottle or a PL
and now I have exactly four coins which
is I think exactly the price that it
was it's not frog frog F or k over I I
think K Over is better yeah hello I
would like to purchase your best bottle
bottle oh wait it's five no
what
F what do I
do what do I
do where can I get more
Stones I must get more Stones it cannot
end like
this five what the hell I mean you know
they got to they got to make a living
somehow okay so I understand I
understand I still have this potato
why will no one buy my
potato somebody please buy my
potato what do I do what do I
do chest in the yellow house but I can't
enter it during the day and then you
mean this one
right during the night it's
protected water in fire is
coin are yeah right but not all the time
I can't I don't think I can get it
twice no no
no but maybe on a different
fire uh surely yeah there must be
another fire can
I no this fire probably not was there
another
fire water in a fire why because stks
was there
fire fire but didn't I
already get this one
[Music]
yeah
okay different
one yeah of course only ones that would
be
crazy maybe I saw a fire over here
[Music]
no dude do you know
anything orange was so good yeah there
there's not more where that came
from infinite money
glitch no wait was
there
no no
yeah and down
here no I don't know maybe we should
look at this place during night time cuz
I don't think we saw it during night
time
yet right good
thinking I think I
think what else would the the bed be
here for huh it's too uncomfortable to
sleep oh I guess bird has many feathers
so bird does not need comfortable bed
but wait if I sleep over here and make
it night time here well it still be
night time when I get
[Music]
there hello hello wait shut
the
no okay I think one of these had a coin
inside before maybe it was that
one also we still need to figure out
what we need to put over here there's
something missing there still
[Music]
so
n
[Music]
what's in here at night oh it's locked
okay that frog is a
chicken it's still spooky I understand
wait he never fished there before either
did
he what do you got I'm trying out a new
fishing spot so you seen this weird
music box yes
there's one of them right in the way of
the duck's egg mhm I've been wondering
how to get rid of them beats me great
thank you very much uh I also don't
[Music]
know there's one right here
too and I mean it's not the potato right
that's going to lead me to
Victory
m
what a helpful
guy potato wait no I thought if you drop
the droplet on the glass it will make a
nice
sound fly above above where above can
you give the potato to the rabbit I'll
try I'll try well where is rabbit rabbit
sleeping now
right wait there's some people in here
too
uh we
[Music]
not go to sleep so I can look into your
chest my coins are
there wait a
second how do we make him sleep while
we're they still in here or do I sleep
right cuz I wake up maybe and he'll be
gone and also he'll be
inside oh no I can't do this I'll be
I'll be
forever Bad Frog
no
no no I can't accept myself like this
oh
oh oh I've been wondering what a I bet
some music is the way to go too bad I'm
not a good singer wait do I see
something else now
[Music]
maybe wait the bird is
singing maybe maybe we need a bird to
sing I don't
know
I hear birds
singing I don't know what I'm supposed
to see
here I can sell the potato to the fish
what really well now CH one after
another we now have enough money it
might be stolen but you know that's okay
nobody knows
that we might be the number one
suspect but here I'll buy the bottle
[Applause]
[Music]
other
one I might be on the wrong oh wait no
no no no it was here it was
here Crow making soups
oh is that a fly sweat yes
yes come and get
some I'm so fast it can't it can't
detect my
movement listen do I smell oh salvation
smells so good here take
enjoy it was a lot of work K all slurp
Goble I feel so much better oh look at
him old frog now maybe he can tell me
some wisdoms about the
stones young frog thank you for healing
me now tell me were you transformed as
well yeah but I mean I'm quite happy in
this form actually all the animals were
given a brain most have forgotten they
were animals at all what do they think
they're
humans you you saw the fairy go into the
old tree right then you must follow it
maybe you can convince it to turn us
back it's been locked with a music not
Stone ah perhaps you could sing to
unlock it I don't know if I
can yes I will teach you now watch
closely I learned to sing singing frog
press the Frog button to start singing
okay
oh
[Music]
colors wow what want wonderful now to
open the tree you must sing an ancient
Melody it consists of five notes but we
don't know which
[Music]
ones
interesting according to Legend the
melody is found within the sing Stones
sing stones are magical Stones each one
holding a certain note when put together
they will teach you the ancient Melody
you must ENT out and find those five
Stones only then you can open the old
tree here you'll need this to learn the
melody I've kept it safe until a hero
like you came around it keeps track of
the sing Stones I found okay here we go
guys here we
[Music]
go so okay we got the s
stone but wait what am I supposed to do
with this let's go to one of the
stones over here oh hey why are you here
again I'm blocking off the force for you
so you don't have to go back there makes
it a bit what do you mean makes it
easier
huh because are you saying I just really
don't have to go there anymore and you
don't want me to look over there for
things that oh things that might
not be useful at all like saving my
time are they trying to save my
time thank you I kind of wanted to go
back though wasn't maybe there was still
something I guess there wasn't actually
so
[Music]
what it it went away it went
away I don't know if that was like
coincidentally the right
sound or if any sound would have been
fine okay EG M inventory okay I eat
fly oh big egg that that is so heavy I
have to put it back to the nest
or Hello Duck I have
eggs
all I could find was this weird music BL
oh I'll never find it again no no no
[Music]
no my egg oh my
egg quick put it in the nest okay
okay there it is tucked in safe and
sound and ready for me to eat it later
in the night my egg is back did you do
this thank you so much let me help you
the duck joined me press the duck button
watch
let's go
duck oh my God it's the end
game oh [\h__\h] let's
go how do I get
off can I not get off a there we go what
is this what is this what is
this what is
this
huh kind of sussy oh
oh
oh a seed this is a carrot seed wait we
have a carrot and an onion and a potato
are we making like
[Music]
Curry
up here I can't
go swi
swim the big big
ocean maybe a small pond for Humanity
but it's a big
ocean for a duck and a
[Music]
Frog can't frog s to not all of them
swim did you not listen why is it so
loud I make more
quiet did you not listen to my frog tear
list
yesterday there's tree
frogs oh oh oh wait can I now land on
top of the lily pads oh but I can take
it anyway new
coin Lily Pad I don't think I even have
a little pad of thingy right now so
that's
fine there was a te list in the talking
stream yes why yes oh look at
that
oh
huh a hole opened
up but what am I supposed to put
there oh will we find out later cuz I
don't know now
the
potato I mean if it's not possible I
don't think it will let me put it there
so we can just try if it will react to
the potato but like nah I don't think so
we're supposed to cook something but why
did we get the potato so early anyway
wait it's still open wait it's still
open never mind the underground
who
[Music]
oh oh but
ah what would I put
there where is this
[Music]
anyway cuz we can activate the breeze
over here
kid there is a fire which means money
but I don't have a
oh the color color
red
nice and
warm diary what the text man my Royal
days are numbered
Royal I have fled from my Palace into
this lonely wet cave my Throne my riches
replaced with bugs and water drops
oh but one day I shall emerge and retake
the crown yes I have hidden it well I
shall be king once more H obviously I
can't sleep on there there as we
know we can activate this but it will go
away
right how to get up
[Music]
here can I like just
play so
[Music]
beautiful but
okay maybe this is a little bit too
early for us it's a text bug can I eat
the
bug H I would love to leave the duck
here and make the duck go
fly but no he's so nice for spending all
this time with
us when we fly does it make you fly out
of the bottle or something like that I
don't know W
oh some new fishing place isn't it nice
I'm trying out a new fishing spot how
did I get here while I'm a fish I heard
that rare stone is hiden
underwater so I'm trying to fish it up
oh yeah please do but I lost the bait
you gave me earlier if only I had
another worm anothera
worm I cooked my last
worm wait worms usually I get them like
from wet spots but also sometimes
not where do I get warm there's also
still a chest over here but I need the
lily pad there's this Lily Pad seat here
though is there
not
doio cute frogging about a year ago tap
tap froggy on it tap tap froggy you made
a cute frog game I want to check it
out tap tap froggy tap tap froggy I need
to remember tap tap froggy can I eat
egg wait I wonder what he says about
that
thing new project just keep coming this
button used to operate the
G gay sir excuse me gay sir on top of
this CLI but there's a part Miss
how am I supposed to fix this I don't
know question I have not found anything
yet that would work with
[Music]
that we'll figure it out oh yeah wait
talk to m a
minute
music again I don't know if I
coincidentally got the right color uh or
if just any color would work but there
we go I opened a new pth FR M yeah oh oh
oh
oh Lily Pad
[Music]
again quack quack
quack button here new
house locked this another one of those
noty thingies and I probably can go
around the back
there and swim
I do you see what I
see I see space for a worm but I don't
even have space in my inventory oh wait
there's a chest coin F yeah but I wait
maybe it's not necessarily for wor maybe
I can put like a seat here
no but I can't throw away these seeds so
I cannot not get a worm from it either
now oh search
oh how what do I
do
potato you guys are so focused on the
potato no not potato is already grown
guys don't you
remember the trails the month that's the
same taex that they gave us for the worm
so we need to get the worm first before
we can plant anything there but maybe I
wasn't supposed to get all these
ingredients at this
[Music]
point oh yeah wait I can grow the other
ones in the same spot I guess but then
we weren't even told yet what to do with
it
so I I will just have like more F but
actually I guess if I if I put it in
there then at least I can uh oh I can
swim here too at least
oh it's danger frog which is actually a
crocodile frog with
teeth wait I can go here I can take
this what
how how I just roll where where it
go but I was thinking
[Music]
um if we put the seed in there then at
least we have an inventory slot open and
then we can take we can get the worm we
need a water droplet though then what
what do I
do wasn't this supposed to be like
something for the the thingy I don't
know lily pad
pad I have for the yellow button
H I thought cuz that looks like you know
the things that they showed us okay now
we have some air over
here but what
for right the duck the duck here
Co nice and some lore or a hint it's a
diary I miss a
AP aie so much aie is my stuff that ah f
a it's a
monkey he made me feel safe even in the
dark but I felt like I had to grow up so
I threw him up a cliff near the bunny's
house and now I just want him back back
so badly I'm training to jump up Cliffs
but apai oh that's the crocodile cuz he
is like jumping up and down so he's
training for getting the plusy Oh I
thought he was scary but he's actually
just like doing his best
kid Just Like
Me Maybe maybe he's fine maybe we can
talk to him
[Music]
but apai is really high up uh every
night I quietly hope he'll come back to
me yeah of course we have to take care
of it apparently AA is really hardcore
and also sleeps on hard
surfaces
interesting okay can we talk to him then
I'll I'll give it a
try but also we need to grow the
seed I'll I'll get there soon
hopefully
I thought he was like guarding this
place and I if I go closer then he'll
attack me hello talk no what's this up
there oh I can't I can't talk to him
he's also just ignoring me rude I'm on
the mission to help you and yet you
ignore
me I was wondering how we get back um
through here
here okay let's
grow some
veggies but it has to be night
time
so we
slip
me hello sorry for using your bed and
now sorry for using
your stuff okay onion
water and then we have to wait a
day while this inventory slot is open
for
me I go unless it doesn't allow me cuz
I'm apparently afraid of dark
[Music]
tunnels you I okay that's that's that's
okay I
guess I think I can just make it daytime
and then just not pick the veggie
yet
yeah why am I so scared aren't frogs
like night active
anyway does it need another water I
wonder I need another water actually for
the uh worm to come
out yes nocturnal no depends on the spes
I guess
[Music]
so Wawa is a little bit nocturnal at the
moment Wawa wake up H froggy Wawa of
course WWA also stands for froggy
Wawa at the moment I wake up pretty
early but uh not out of my own
will sprinkle the water w who was this
Worm for
though I
don't um somebody wanted a worm Fish
Guy Fish guy
was where right
now my nose is so
itchy h i
o my noise
is somebody help me on the island
okay where's my nose I I have no
um
uh
look can you
[Music]
see
hard to control my body excuse
me small nose but probably bigger than W
nose so
[Music]
Superior I have warm wait so we give him
warm and he will get out the thing
that's down
there oh [\h__\h] let's
go oh wait I have to give it from
Land
[Music]
garly get get here we
go Ah that's what we're looking for
that's what the other like yellow thing
and soon that we can put it in here we
have a sing Stone slap thingy I don't
really understand like why I need like
these little thingies um when I can
already sing but uh sure I'll just you
know let it
happen we will we will understand
eventually how all of this works do I
still need to go back into the
hole anyway for
now was that Lily Pad uh
in a place where I could even pick it up
or was it
uh at like a a height level where I
can't pick it up I think I can't pick it
up get a droplet again there's a fire
you can put out down there down
here wait water no don't
go no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
super frog Mario thank you for the Super
Chat I'll finally catch up with super
chats don't worry I mean I might not be
able to read all of them today but I'll
get started underground there was a
iight ah yeah but wasn't that also no it
was
[Music]
reachable okay let's see but that will
just give me a coin
anyway tiple thank you I'll see what I
can do I'll tell her maybe I'll tell her
I'll go to her grave and tell her grave
then I don't know if she'll hear it but
uh worth a try I
guess and it's just a coin but we'll
probably need
it we have free coins wasn't the last
item you can buy 99
coins at this pace I don't know if we
can get 99
coins so this
[Music]
ball what about this do we get like a
power to jump eventually because
otherwise I don't know how we're going
to get
there right the gator will tell me how
to
jump
[Music]
ah right speaking
of M wait what's next now there's like a
lot of things to keep in mind let me get
my I don't know should we get
my should we get
it it needs water
anyway should I get it welcome
Raiders
okay uh okay
me get Lily ped which was I think I
think
over on this
side and
[Music]
then I don't
remember small small memory oh wait we
already here here here here here I
remember we already had it out the open
and I couldn't pick it up now I can pick
it up and now um um um um wasn't wasn't
there several places where I could put
it
okay some pieces of Kiama in my
FR here we
go clap clap clap clap clap clap clap
a
chest a coin yeah okay I guess we'll
need it but
like it doesn't bring me anywhere right
now I feel like eventually I guess we'll
just get like like 90 coins at
once like oh big
treasure okay visible disappointment you
now I don't know the only thing I can
think of is uh yeah
[Music]
the the the
onion is it okay if I take the onion
now I must take onion feed snail monkey
snail snail
snail the snail ask for something now
music nodes door next to watering can
next to water you mean you mean this one
oh yeah I guess I can open this but it
looks like there's a
double no no this is the big
one this is the big one where I need
like a special code
right
um yeah there's the final one but was
there another one somewhere we got the
one over
[Music]
here we're still too small for this by
the way I wonder if we able get there's
there's also still some stuff here wait
did I check out this side I could have
put the Lily bad thingy over on this
side as well but I didn't wait there's
something here I didn't check that out
yet o oh no ah I thought it was like a
golden seat that I can pick up no it's
just a a a button that I already
activated never mind
[Music]
kenel need another Lily
Pad dude you're always so
helpful maybe if you change your fishing
spot again it might be a good hint for
me of what to
do but I'll go here I'll talk with the
old dude again maybe he has a
hint hello again young frog any luck
finding those sing Stones yeah I got one
you might need some more help first well
Crocs diary said he misses his stuff
animal yeah it's up a ledge near Bunny's
house maybe that broken button has
something to do with it though bear is
probably not going to fix it on of
course not he keeps notes on his repairs
in his house maybe that could okay okay
thank you he did give me a hint
nice uh so his house is is was it the
can though was it the
can in that case I can only go at night
right was it the
can ah the one by the
bridge oh this one this one this one
this
one it's a to-do fix the bridge fix the
ladder fix the button need something
yellow thing from materials
chest probably not
what can we put out this uh Fire by the
way
yellow thing
from I think I have a sound
bug can I is this
have that sounds like a sound bug to
me
bug let me reopen the
game that didn't seem right to
me I eat the sound
bug one thing I'll say about kiaha is ah
wait the sound bug is still there
ah oh
[\h__\h]
uh deaths
[Music]
help death
St oh [\h__\h] game
crushed
uh cuz I I muted the music in game and
it didn't change so I have I have to
mute the game on
Windows move
away I close game
again I want say one thing I want to say
about Ki is
[Applause]
that the song It's
amazing
uh help maybe if I re-enter
room
ah ah it's so
loud
[Music]
why is so
loud sound bug go away try going into
water
okay ah no not
helping let's exit
area
somebody contact the
developers I restarted the game
twice contact and
develop
peace there's some like deep cleaning
going on or like drilling or some kind
of construction going on over
there I can't make it go
away any deaths here any doesn't even
have to be this game death any deps at
all who can help
me oh maybe bear is finally fixing
[Music]
things
maybe I have an idea what if I I think
it came didn't it come from the once I
picked up the
droplet what if I drink the
drop it's the cursed droplet
maybe de here but not kind of it's gone
I fixed it I'm the game death I'm the
game de what wait if I pick it up
again okay okay okay we just have to
bear it until what was I going to do
with this anyway
uh I have to burar it until I drink it
or like use it that's okay that's okay
that's
okay it's the water drop but what what
was I going to use it for which
[Music]
fire
uh some bear's house ah okay okay okay
that's manageable
yeah
okay oh [\h__\h] I think we did that before
for oh we may have done that already
okay this kind of threw me off uh what
are we what are we going to
do what's next I guess let's take but
nobody told me to get these ingredients
in the first place so I'm just going to
leave it there for
now nobody told me what about uh he said
yellow thing in
chest right and snail won't let me
through anymore let talk to him
again there's a part missing how am I
supposed to well look at your notes for
God's
sake oh I I don't what what what what
chest
what n
n what could it be where could it
be I feel like this is really sussy I
want to like look inside but that's
nothing ah my chat stopped moving a
there it
is the wobbly water is cursed get off
the chest in his house but it's locked
isn't
it maybe at night
time you know maybe I don't know maybe
at night time he'll be in here and I can
talk to him and open it no I need a key
I probably need a key shut the
Mother Let's test this out it is open at
nighttime but you don't understand I
need it good thing I was still ah uh
good thing I was still
awake yeah is it the
light no he wants a
carrot
yo okay okay okay finally but the
carrots it was not the one I was uh
growing okay we have we we're not
making we're
making ah maybe I can only grow it on
the next day we need to go through the
the weed face again
maybe No Cry K No Cry who wants the who
wants a pure onion who wants to bite
into a pure onion then
huh okay he pulls out the weeds I go and
put something else in
[Music]
there those weeds are
insane I put some
water finally we're cooking and it's not
Curry sadly we could all enjoy a pot of
Curry
together of all these ingredients mixed
but no these idiots only think about
themselves so we only get the separate
ingredients it would be so much better
if we have them all together what the
hell do I have the potato for eh you
tell
me droplet please thank
you finally I have a purpose again and
pluck it's a carrot yay I like carrots I
like them I like carrots I've noticed a
lot of Japanese people don't like
carrots like so many Japanese
people they're like I don't like carrots
but I feel like they say it's
specifically Japanese carrots and they
say Japanese carrots taste different and
yeah I could agree they tast they taste
different but from someone who likes
carrots who are not from Japan and uh
I've also tried Japanese carrots and
yeah they're a bit different but I I
still think the base flavor is the same
and so I like I like them I think
they're
[Music]
fine carrot fries are actually very good
carrot fries I I think I had that before
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I made
that before a little bit with a little
bit of honey I
think froggy why I so cute you're so
right you are so right
sir carrot noodles I don't think I had
carrot noodles before carrot cake I had
carrot cake before but I think cake
should be like you know more on the
sweet side even though carrot cake is
not really Savory either but you know I
don't know I think like I think I talked
about this before but I feel like you
know yeah here take the
carrot yeah yeah I understand I
understand you can't sleep with a with
an empty
belly Japan Bros don't like eggplant
also I really I also don't like
eggplants at
all as soon as you leave I'm off to bed
here take this what did he give me a
coin oh thank you as soon as I leave
you're off to bed but can I
reenter yes ah look at him sleep so cute
but I feel like if we like just I don't
understand the logic here he himself
wrote into his diary that he has the
tools that he needs to fix the thing in
his
chest but it it did sound like he's kind
of confused about it but like if we told
him if we reminded him
I mean we shouldn't be reading the diary
in the first place so we shouldn't have
this knowledge but like why doesn't
he why yellow thing from materials chest
like see he knows what what but wait
what does it mean probably not what he's
he's so confused let us do this job for
him he himself has the info though I
don't get
it okay we can't we don't need to grow
anything anymore kle because we already
have everything kle
now now we put this thing on
here there we
go
wow oh this feels so good this is so
satisfying oh wait chat is oh there you
are you disappeared so fast oh what oh
wait not here crocodile is on the other
world a [\h__\h] monkey
[\h__\h] monkey
K I got a [\h__\h]
monkey I did indeed get a [\h__\h] monkey
K oh I was about to say oh yeah right we
can't go through but it lets me go
through because of the monkey cuz oh not
only the crocodile feels more Brave
having the monkey I also feel more Brave
thanks to the monkey I didn't read the
text properly but I think that's what it
was
saying oh wow magical monkey powerful
monkey oh wait is he sleeping in here
right now um well no I am
huh wait is he in there anyway cuz he
locks it like for sleeping for safety
that would make
sense ah hi nice to meet you you look
like me but are apparently very
different ignore the duck please um I
don't want you to feel uncomfortable cuz
of the duck only green people are in
this room right now don't worry I want
to talk to him first how'd you get in
here I can't just see I'm trying to
sleep I know what you need and I have it
and you shall thank
me
properly accordingly apie AP is that you
oh AP I never should have thrown you up
that Cliff thank you frog you returned
them to me well there's no need for me
to train in the swamp anymore I'll join
you we can jump we can jump we can jump
I
guess H but ah okay not anywhere just
where it
applies okay well there must be a lot of
places where that
applies not here look at this look at
this can I jump up here no
okay can I use it somewhere here
though would that be oh wait here
obviously he taught us how to jump we
don't even have to go on his back we
just
know
look look guys look there it
is
oh we got another sing Stone I love this
game it's so cute oh my
[Music]
God come come come come come come yes
follow me follow
me um was there another
place I mean here we could access
before anything
new
firly after all I get to see you come
here come here you little [\h__\h] I
glow I [\h__\h] glow let's
go what what is this effect for H as
long as I have the Firefly in my
inventory i glow I
glow what do I do with this glow
glowi well let me check down here really
quickly if there was okay we can go we
can go
ah wait I guess uh with the glow now
that we don't have the
um the [\h__\h] monkey anymore you would
assume that we can't go through the
tunnel anymore cuz we're scared but
maybe that's what the Firefly is for
maybe without the Firefly I would have
told me ah it's too
scary probably
right
okay uh what's
next we got rid of the monke okay uh and
maybe we just need to
sleep because my work here is done let's
see what what he says I'm glad ult told
to save the snail blocked off the way to
the forest but I guess you don't have
any business
there I guess all right May let's check
the places that become available to us
now over on this side we could go back
again over here and I guess we have
business there because it's not like
telling me also a lily pad I think yeah
Lily
Pad
but
uh I guess we don't need the Firefly
right now can we get it in other
places oh or or we a we can probably get
it again
right I should still be glowing if I ate
it make should glow from my
tummy can
no n just a [\h__\h] coin oh my God
that's what I ate the Firefly for really
isn't it [\h__\h] toxic to
me isn't that [\h__\h] toxic to
me
unbelievable qu wait we can go into the
cave um there was something there
to
climb the ball the ball I don't know if
we still do we need to do
that so many things have opened up to
us so
exciting can I jump onto the
no we have ball what do I do with this
ball ah ah we put it over here so we can
also use the wind I
guess look wait I just I didn't look
until now look at us we're all on top of
each other
[Music]
stacked secret room oh no oh no it's a
jar it's a jar it's a jar guys no
I'm
scared this is terrifying and we get
this okay I have to be strong I have to
be strong I can do this that's it that's
it
okay oh that's the shop isn't
it I got this i got this thank you I'm
out already it's okay I feel I feel okay
I feel I feel Brave I surv survived I
survived Kido but that was the shop
wasn't it I didn't realize until I left
the
room I usually eat cooked carrots
instead of raw ones because I'm a
ticken wait
you how far back in the vault are you or
is your comment
lagging
no wait I can feed them
too and okay so we did that we got three
out of five droplets oh my
God okay what else um over
here right right right right
right quack quack
indeed it's just a
coin eight coins 91 coins to
go okay let's go to the first world
maybe cuz I don't know if there's
anything else
[Music]
here there might be
but yeah yeah yeah let's go back to the
starting
Area Nether water can house you can jump
oh ah yeah right
wait I already stole a 99 coin
item
what I stole a coin but it was was only
one
coin there's a
door a dumble
door not a dumble door I can see if I
need a stupid Firefly
again I can wait it's only on the other
side of the map but now I can't go there
because now I don't have the Firefly huh
is that what you're
saying I wonder if it's worth going to
the beginner's map the beginning now
first before we go there throw it up I
have never mind it's not because of the
Firefly I still have like oh there's a
lot of fireflies though I still have AP
In My
Memory the fireflies I
ah but then what are they
for ah wait I guess they are for that
room because I went in and it was just
pitch black
I don't need them for feeling brave
sorry my mind is very
confused it is a curse to be this
smart sometimes too much brain that's
why we need to become just a normal frog
again I Choose
You y yellow
yellow
yellow wait I can't mother eat
Firefly I'm going to eat all these
fireflies I'm going to [\h__\h] die by
the end of the
game okay four out of five the end is
near the end is near
automata so all these puns and I don't
know what to do with them I could go up
here but there's nothing here huh is
there
no and right there was there's a ball
here too and I have it no that that ball
is just on the button is
it must be on the button okay okay I
think that's
all all that was
necessary then I take a firly and we go
to the dark place
[Music]
Kido yeah that was I I looked very
thoroughly question mark So I think
that's
all maybe in there we get the last piece
maybe
maybe yeah let's see what's
inside oh it's another
cave
where can we go oh I cannot land there
oh no I
can it looked like it was grayed
out
uhhuh hey it's a
coin ah wait okay when when your
inventory is full it goes into the pouch
uh on its own if it's not fall then it
doesn't
great why no
jump oh hey why no jump I should be able
to jump
here ah here very
specific there it is the last one what
do you mean man just go directly into
here if the coin can go directly into
the pouch why can you not what am I
supposed to
do I I can't get rid of the Firefly
no what okay I need
to I need to get rid of the other things
first otherwise I can't pick up that
item they have soft locked me I wonder
if this happens to you no matter what
you
do cuz that would be like big brain it
really forces you to to like fix
everything before but I don't know what
what there is to fix
now nobody needs anything click and drag
I could have clicked and
dragged no way no way sell potato s
potato sorry I had I'm a be in my
throat the fire fir
flies the endless fireflies are getting
to
me that was my third Firefly intake I
think okay I'll try to sell the potato
you guys are so hung up on the
potato if 10
million he does want wait do I get
99 coins or
one one one
coin one one
coin what do you mean one
coin are you for real now I
mean at least I get an inventory slot
again
oh someone broke into the shop at that
not me not me my stone it's gone oh what
am I going to do you don't need the
stone I need the
stone I've added a new item please take
a look
oh oh oh that's what you meant with I
stole the 99 coin
item so I don't need that I don't need
that amount of money anymore Kido but I
need two more
coin wait something is in my bro
I need two
more every
time
[Music]
[\h__\h] hi
smoothie your hair is maybe choking me
could that
be H she's doing a stretch on the
ground smoothie my sweet baby
potato you worth one coin come
here did you wait is she here cuz she
went to the toilet again could it be did
you go to the toilet are you just saying
hello cuz you went to the
toilet
me yeah he's so
soft
nice cat
break right at the time where I'm dying
she came to say goodbye but I will still
survive goodbye smoothie goodbye I gave
her a hug and now she's gone she's
leaving I don't know I didn't feel any
any wetness on her butt this
time but I like how you're picking up on
my vocabulary and saying poopy whoop
kid okay so we need two more coins
hopefully my throat is chilling
now two more coins for the key the
key could be for something that I don't
know what it is for um but what was I
doing uh I I wanted to pick up something
I need a
firefly if 10 million
fireflies would go in my
tummy I would probably die
[Music]
tonight wait that's
not that's not
fireflies oh is it is it a firefly and
it just lights up at night then I can
pick it up now
you little [\h__\h] come
here have I been eating fireflies all
this
time no it just says fly now but let's
see if it lights up if I let it become
night otherwise I'll just come back at
night other L it will just be a nice
snack
right okay
okay qu qu
it is not glowing so I has
snake that's fine too we need to feed
ourselves because of a I can go
[Music]
in come here come here come here come
here I got it guys why my throat like
this by the way I felt really guilty cuz
I saw so many people saying they're sick
so many people like qu Quon and so on
but then I also saw other people who I
didn't meet really uh say that they're
sick people who I didn't hang out with
so maybe it's just generally it's just
you know things going around
I still cuz also I didn't get genma
sick she I was around her the most out
of everybody and I didn't get her sick
so oh okay Firefly fire
[Music]
five yeah but like it really feels like
almost
every H member got something okay it's
not that bad but uh it feels like
it
[\h__\h] it feels like I can't
breathe I
got
the moment when you're a frog and you
have a frog a frog in your fro a
frog a frog you can even say fro with th
because I'm going to say it all the same
anyway fro fro all the
same all the all the same all the same
it will go away it will go
away it will go away I what we're
supposed to do uh maybe now I can open
this oh wait wait a
second what I do how do I
know
[Music]
whoa
maybe okay
okay
but
that no which one is the highest
anyway wait so close no
yellow
no
huh I need I need to listen to them
again no that's that's the
lowest so that should be the fourth I
[Music]
think
no wait uh is green higher than
blue
ah [\h__\h] yellow red
[Music]
green
purple
huh what if you don't need a ah I guess
so it does sound very
[Music]
off
let's
go frog
frog get frogged let's go
yipp I did it I a
composer a
musician it actually worked oh my god
let's see what's
inside what oh that little [\h__\h] is in
there
maybe he won't notice
me you little [\h__\h] get
wrecked how'd you get in here take this
no no no no I could not make make me
small make me small please no he make me
go
outside
huh I wonder
maybe I can sing at him or I can feed
him an
onion oh [\h__\h] I tapped
out he reacted to it what what happened
a bit
more I'm so cute that was so sweet wait
so wait did that already do the trick
though maybe huh oh yeah I did I feel
terrible I gave you all a brain oh you
already came to the
senses that Ain right having a brain is
no fun at all I'm sorry I want to make
it right okay that was
easy please you have to convince
everyone to wait now I know he'll change
me back and then I I become small frog
again right and then I can go through
the small tube and that way I can go
[Music]
back sorry I'm all over the place
now but that way I'll just go back maybe
that'll just be the ending like me
reuniting with my other
Froggies please you have to convince
everyone to change back if you bring
everyone here I can undo your
spell
everybody I have to convince everybody
sounds like a trap almost but okay I'll
I'll try first of all fishing
man just a fish oh yeah I kind of
figured I'd come but I want to fish some
more how much
more wait there's some people awak in
their houses anyway
right what T the fish you're wrong I'm a
successful I'm not saying these things
not at all I'm a successful businessman
kid I get out of my sight what how do I
how do I convince
them what I'm just a bird oh it's me
saying because I'm trying to tell them
you have a brain now but you're actually
just a brain that's what I'm saying ah
what does that even mean it's the that
fairy and must have hexed you you stay
away from me frog how do
I how maybe I
sing
Oh dare you [\h__\h] go I am a
[Music]
Genus that wasn't that scary okay I'm
ready
yay oh I I I'll get like a big kga line
is is that how you say that wait okay
just a fish no no here does does any
note
work yeah just sing it
away beautiful frog
sounds oh really some some frogs make
some
nice sounds don't they they sing at
night too don't
they look at the Smart sing wow that's a
big group so I sing for you this is
pretty easy if all I have to do is sing
to them then that's easy I thought I
have to convince them in a different way
and it's going to be more difficult and
do you want to get up can I can I wake
him
up the bear is fast asleep okay no he
has to be
awakened during the
daytime all right I need to sleep too
then I guess oh can I get you you though
while I'm
here
[Music]
yeah is dangerous and can make us lose
our
brains that's maybe a good thing I make
you brain empty and then you shall
forever follow froggy wa without any
doubts Kittle the reading was getting
really boring I'll join you all right
that's what I thought okay let me go to
daytime I hope I don't have to be in
nighttime for any of these
people but this one
surely will like my song the power of
music not
friendship yeah there are not any
projects left so yeah come on join
me we will all make sense I can't even
see the shop person but I'll just wait
is he
here
no wait there's no one here is is he
only here at night
no who was that
anyway I already got him oh okay okay
okay and what about the sick
froggle we need to take him with us he
wants to have a brain free life again
with what you say is true but I can't
join you I'm already much too old but
please do help the others no no no no no
you don't really mean that do you
you have to join me yes yes I will not
leave you
behind you're not too old
no come with me your last years shall be
spent in brain empty
[Music]
style one more I feel like there's more
people though the only the crow is that
really all we have
left but Crow have more than more than
small brain maybe
Crow this is normal life form of
crow let's not take away his brain this
is how he's supposed to be they're
really smart oh yeah what about the
snail snail is too big I
guess is this really a good end yeah
well I feeling I feel like I'm leading
them into like a Game of Thrones
Cathedral explosion kind of
[Laughter]
situation well let's
go I didn't I did it also I know I know
I know I didn't watch the trailer yet
people sent me the trailer and I
know they
announced they announced
finally
finally it's a
ritual yay no brain style they look
funny wait the fish is going to die the
fish is going to [\h__\h]
die I feel like the bear looks the
funniest wait the crocodile so cute too
we're all so cute
[Music]
IQ dropping happiness
Rising
yay I'm free
freedom is this really the end of the
game I know it's a short game so this
could be the
end I'm home Frank friends do you still
remember me
it's me fry
wa I beat the game
yay I indeed beat it in 2 and a half
hours oh 2 and 12 minutes which is uh
below
average nice the one time where you're
happy about being below
average world record not quite but
[Music]
return to frog 17 out of
20 oh wait yeah wasn't there ah the the
key item that I could have gotten ah
it's okay it's okay I don't I don't need
it also doesn't seem like you can go
back I
think would I have have to oh I think I
would actually really have to restart
from the beginning
now
no no no no I
refuse I refuse that would be crazy if I
knew that before then I could have
thought about it but U I didn't know you
can't go back to your
actual playr that you did until now now
you know guys if you want to give it a
try just just so you know don't end the
game before you have all the
coins yeah the game is finished yeah
finished another does this go on on
froggy waa finished games list or Tak
finished games list
H will it count for both of us it was on
takanasi Kiana's YouTube channel mind
you so it counts for both of us I would
say just because just because I want to
take over her big game list it's really
impressive you
know now you guys better stay because
we're going to rate super chats a little
bit if you don't mind I I think I really
need to catch up quite a bit I'm pretty
behind does anybody know where I need to
continue wearing it that beach Le leave
everything H where did she
stop let me pour some water no idea the
myth
oh that's not not too far I
mean the froggy wble hoodie is calling
for me help yeah just a reminder the
link is in the description but I
yesterday I released the froggy wa
merchandise that you guys really seem to
enjoy already the idea of it
and currently waiting for samples but uh
yeah we have a wobbling froggy W
keychain which is so
cute cute and you can add it to your
keys or whatever and then here is the
most adorable froggy W it's me it's me
and yes um we did end up changing the
eye color a little bit that's the only
change we made from the original design
cuz my um eyes are no they're supposed
to be a bit more on the pinkish side and
yeah and the hoodie hoody or parker I
think I called it Parker because I think
there's a difference when there's a
zipper I think it's called a Parker but
I guess it also depends
on the region and the language I don't
know cuz yeah this one has a zipper uh I
I I I felt it was really important for
it to have a zipper uh cuz it's more
convenient in my opinion you can kind of
use it like as a jacket when it's a
little bit cold outside kiddo Parker is
more of a British thing
oh I have some British blood in me of
course
froggy
Canadians also say Parker okay okay
there you go there you
go who did you drink maybe you should
are you saying the blood the British
blood inside of me is from somebody else
I'm not a
vampire no
no that was such a cute game wasn't it
you know frog wink is like one of these
uh times where I can play some cuter
chill games that maybe normally I
wouldn't play but frog Wick gives me a
good excuse for it but it also kind of
like restricts me to play um frog
related
games but yeah they're also often on the
shorter side yeah so there that was a
lot of fun today it's ch cute game that
needed some
appreciation we found a
bug that was really
yummy
yeah hair in my
mouth yeah I could play games like this
whenever but uh I mean frog related
games I keep on purpose for frog week
so yeah I hope the deaths will enjoy the
bug that I found I I donate this bug to
you game devs I wonder if they have a
Twitter then maybe somebody can send
them a clip uh the the the the publish
publisher I guess I guess is it the
publisher or is it the it's from sock
pup games or whatever that was called I
think I got the red socer pop
games maybe they have a Twitter
maybe Dave the DI super chats no I
probably didn't read them let me let me
take let me take
um what do you mean few deaths have
taken notice what do you
mean let me let me check also let me put
on some
[Music]
bgm uh what what could be
good how is these hey I have a
DM oh
okay I frogy while
hungry okay let's read some super chats
efficiently un like that [\h__\h]
kada I can do
better let me put this smaller and I'll
put the Super Chat
Reading
Writing oh guys you know what I've done
I've done something weird
uh cuz froggy waa has small hands
right I tried opening the
door it keeps fading in and out I feel
like really I feel like there's really
something weird going on with the
[\h__\h] audio settings wait then let me
put it into OBS it might be really loud
for a moment but then you'll hear it
differently one moment it will be loud
okay one
woman look at this finger free
free okay wait
fre
two one no go don't go
one yep there we
go can you hear it is it nice is it
balanced I want
you I warned
you
I warned you so nicely with my
fingers Pleasant
[Music]
right okay so I did something I you know
small hand but I live in Kiana's home
now which is for humans and be she's not
a human but it's built for humans
obviously and uh her door opens so
like it's like heavy I don't know when
you know those doors when you have to
pull them towards you uh while you wow
all these motions holy [\h__\h] so you you
put the key in you you turn it and but
at the same time you have to pull the
handle towards
you ah PGM too loud
okay I pull it but like even when I pull
it sometimes it's is not right and it
doesn't open so I noticed my hands I I
don't know the hand where I put the key
in when I twist it like this and then I
pull the door this hand I kind of
strained some something inside of the
hand and it hurts and when especially
when I put the Thum in a specific
position I I I pulled something or so it
really hurt to pull to open the door I
was like [\h__\h] this hurts I was getting
really
frustrated it's not about oiling the
door it's just like this stupid
mechanism I kind of want to change
it I almost want to go to like a cuz it
always bothers me but like today and
yesterday I couldn't open it properly at
all it felt even more difficult than
usual can I I wonder if I can change the
lock into something different that just
has a different
[Music]
mechanism but that probably is kind of
expensive has anyone ever like done
something like that like change the
locks to a different type of lock in
their in their main entrance
Door Well w would be okay with it well
la never coming back so it's not her
decision I need to make this place
suitable for
frog yeah I wonder I wonder how
expensive that
is yeah like a I think digital lock
would be super
cool like with a card or
something M door hardware isn't
expensive they did it for my apartment
before I moved
in
[Music]
oh no I can do it I'm allowed to do it
but I just don't know
how okay maybe I'll ask cuz it's really
annoying me
so much for reading with hey I'm on it
I'm on
it digital rocks reason to hack are
super
unreliable what do you what do you
suggest then if that kind of like
twisting and pulling lock is not good
for my
hand and digital lock is not good either
what kind of lock do I need maybe just a
normal basic
you know but the twisting and pulling I
heard are like
more safe right look at my hands look at
my hands look at my
hands fingerprint lock for real on the
door that's so how about I scanning
lock then somebody will kill me and take
up my eyeballs and then put them in
front of the door and scan it and steal
my
cats you have one of those what like a
fingerprint really that's a thing now
what the [\h__\h] that's so
Hightech I'll I'll check with the with a
lock smith guy in the future maybe I'll
check transplant a chip into my
head a Twist dead bolt what the [\h__\h] is
that what the [\h__\h] is
[Music]
that
fingerprint I don't even like the
fingerprint um unlocking function on on
the phones I don't even like that I I
wouldn't want to put that on my door
that's so weird although that would be
kind of interesting like if I ever like
bring friends or family over and I like
let them into the door I want to like
show it to them but how do
you how do you if you want to give
someone else a key do you register their
phone prints too huh but it would be so
cool to show them like let me open the
door for
you beep and they're
like this is the future cuz i' I've
never seen something like that before so
surely they haven't seen something like
that
before some have spare Kee of the powers
yeah cuz I guess they're like power
dependent m
what is a Twist dead bolt isn't that
what I have now cuz I have to twist the
keys wait no wait that might be
unrelated okay comprint and number code
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah must be a
connection because you know if they kill
me and just use my finger they cut off
my finger they don't even have to kill
me to cut off my finger I can just cut
off my finger Yakuza style and then go
to my home and then put my finger there
it has to be more it has to have some
numbers
too I have a num pad luck but mostly
just use a normal key a so you have like
an option of doing both not
all what if I forget the
code so
dramatic I always think of people
killing
me
no I I was thinking one day if I die it
will probably be murder um but recently
I think that I'm probably going to die
uh on air travel
so yeah that's just a white woman
cor nor more document I honestly really
cut down on the True Crime stuff I cut
down on it a lot cuz I noticed after
binge watching a million of them that
it's
[Music]
really at some point it really feels
like depressing or not depressing but
it's like ah this is too dark I'm I'm
done with this dark ass [\h__\h] it's
crazy yeah but then recently I watched
uh one for the first time in a while
actually it was just like yesterday
but it was
fine but then after one I was like okay
this is enough this is enough for a
while BM
ah now it's looping
K my flum
is very smooth these
days it feels very
smooth frog's
life frog
them that's good allergy I don't have
allergies I swear like this kind of
annoyed me I I got sick uh after I came
to Japan like 3 days in or so which I
really think comes from from all the
traveling and my immune system being
[\h__\h] and then I got sick and I was
like you know and I started noticing on
the Koke day the Koke with myth day I
noticed I had like some like bee in my
throat just a small small and then the
next day I I already knew oh sus there's
barely anything there but I know this is
sus and then the next day I already had
like more symptoms like a runny nose and
like um headache but the headache I
completely covered it with uh pain meds
over the days and look at my hand it's
so
cute and um
yeah and then yeah so nose running and
then throat really really hurt um so
it's just trying to not strain
um but yeah and then JMA was like oh
it's just allergies and I'm like no I
don't have
allergies and I got it like 3 days into
my arrival and I I I know I I really
don't have allergies I don't have CA
show get no I'm really sick like it's
actually dangerous
concerning and yeah I I
know I don't catch i c my nose yeah yeah
yeah it's
here I no I don't have all this okay I
don't I'm was just sick
okay we don't have allergies maybe I
have an allergy but I don't have the
allergy that everybody else has that she
thought I I might have kfuo just because
she has it she was dying she she
constantly her eyes so red but she she
has you know contact lenses in
and every day every [\h__\h] day every
[\h__\h] day she does her makeup no
matter how little sleep she has and how
little time she has and every day she
washes her hair I'm like how do you you
don't have any time you don't need to
wash your hair every day I don't wash my
hair every day at all and it still looks
nice like eventually if you stop washing
your hair every day it will also not
need to be washed every day because it
will like just eventually like you know
re recover the oils and
stuff and it will just like you know not
needed L anymore but you have like made
it to need it but anyway the makeup also
like how do you have time for that all
the
time but yeah she really takes care of
her
visuals and so yeah and and and I saw
her eyes really red and her suffering
from cun from allergies po Poland
allergy and so I said why don't you just
take out the your eyes look so red you
have to take out your
your CES and she was like no no I no I
can't oh my God that must hurt so
much why why woman
why
why okay I'm going to read super
chats you may Believe it or you may not
believe it but I will read super
chats
cute hands
Skittle so let's let's see if those look
familiar the the ones
from D Dave the
diver Dave the
diver was a while
[Music]
ago this slime is so
weird
[Music]
uh I got beef with allergies we fighting
next frog frog is good
diver I'm fairly certain you read them
all oh you think so I did nice good job
P Tak um who is dead
um good job I guess oh yeah and the
Heart Challenger ones are like you know
I can quickly look over them
though I mean already did was there any
questions cuz I already signed all of
these I don't remember if there was any
anything in
[Music]
particular I don't
wait did I finish did she finish these
she did
right
did
she wait did she no wait no no no no no
no I did the Valentine's ones but I
didn't do the wi thing ones I got
confused
okay okay so I I I completely forgot
about that I'll get to
these I was even thinking of doing
froggy waa polar Awards but then I
realized you guys are probably going to
be spending like the ones who are
capable of spending um I'm probably
going to be spending a lot of money on
like merchandise like this and also like
we have other merchandise coming out
like the the the these Badges and those
thingies and there yeah there's a lot of
stuff going on right now so you guys
probably want to save some money so I
was like let's not do Polaroids even
though even though froggy Polaroids
would be super nice maybe next time if I
do frog week again then we could do
froggy W wa po one
another
time yeah cuz I that is that's really
really a rare
occasion frog froggy waa doesn't appear
so often I'm like a rare Pokmon so I'm
sure you guys would want a froggy
waa we can have chickens and Tadpole
costumes for
[Music]
so anyway I shouldn't talk like I'm
going to be gone because I'm obviously
here to
stay oh wa let
me so we have
the because Ki did not read these cuz
she doesn't care about you guys she
hates you I love you she hates you I
love
you I love you but I cannot make a
heart yeah just remember she hates you I
love
you don't ever think about her again she
is not worth it get oh you need me in
your
life okay okay nice
nice no don't think about her you have
me am I not sufficient oh [\h__\h] I don't
remember these
buttons don't think about her think
about me
K she's not coming
back that's why I'm reading these super
chats okay here we
go here we go here we go are you ready
here we
go Jacob
47 Dano maybe Dano is
good I don't remember if I had a special
word last
time D
no D that's kind of cute
n 55 D all Travis H 45 gaming D all
wings CV D for the pinky hey myth just a
reminder that Cali has agreed to
cooperate with any cosplay requests per
her VA stream time stamp 55 thank you
for the
K
huh what's that about like how ises that
what do you
mean what do that mean
oh
huh are you telling
us
huh that we can dress her up there or
that I could have dressed her up on the
stream neat
context I don't get it g I'm sorry wink
CV I mean I understand she said she will
cosplay or something but why are you why
why did that
what huh can we make her a
frog she did learn how to make the Frog
noise so that's already the first step
in the right direction k s St z r l KJ
np15 free garlic marus
men or I don't know Michael
H Callie's Grill
friend Whitebeard than it
all I don't know how to read
this go trans
late I don't speak
language
oopsy that was probably very wrong than
it all for the rest of the chat myth is
the best thank you I think at this point
goba joined us yay go
go that was really a nice surprise
wasn't it overall all like it everything
was so chaotic cuz we were
uh we were like pretty
spontaneously asked by staff if we want
to do an official program with all of
myth on that day around that time I
think we would have been like in the
studio prepping everything and all that
around the time wait can I get rid these
things and and then yeah we said like
okay yeah let's do it everybody like
agreed but then the it was kind of
cancelled it was like oh sorry I guess I
think they I think they
overestimated they wanted to do it but
then they overestimated how little time
or underestimated how little time they
had and then yeah they said okay sorry
we can't do it and then I was like okay
can maybe girls we should maybe still do
uh an off collab cuz we already reserved
time and why not still you know meet up
and yeah do something together and then
they they were like yeah okay let's do
it but then nobody said anything so I
was like okay okay I'll take charge and
we can do either and a talking stream or
how about the want to switch all
together that that that bigger one that
I played for but I didn't bring my
sitech so I don't know I suggested that
first but then uh then I I didn't really
hear much feedback so I was like how
about
K and and they were fine with Koke so I
was like okay okay I need everybody's
songs that you can sing so we can do
like a Whole Life archive K and all that
so yeah I planned
everything and it worked out I'm so
happy I'm also really happy that goodie
B made it in the end she was like doing
some work getting some work done before
and um we thought that she wasn't able
to come at all but then she came in the
most perfect timing and of course she's
always welcome so I'm glad that she um
came after all cuz like she wrote me a
message I saw it popping up but I I was
while while I was singing I think but I
wasn't sure
like I I didn't have time to look at it
but I saw something I was like that's a
message from goodie ball h
and I didn't answer but she was asking
if she could uh join after all if we're
still doing it
and even though I didn't answer she
still joined thank
God yeah she's always welcome I hope she
knows that and she came in at the
perfect moment and you I feel
like
like this way it was almost better than
having her in there from the beginning
even though I would have also liked to
have her in there from the beginning cuz
then I could have like included her in
the lyrics splits from all the songs but
this way cuz everybody it added way more
to the hype everybody was like oh
where's GAA okay I guess it's just fine
too with four out of five I guess I
watch
you and then and then nobody at that
point nobody expected G to show up
anymore and then she shows up during
reunion oh my God
like she did it on per on purpose oh my
God and this way was way more hyped and
like wa holy [\h__\h] and you guys were all
really emotional about
it and everyone everyone liked this
anime moment
yeah it was great it was great yeah and
because she came in so late I I I feel
bad for maybe putting some pressure on
her but I thought you know obviously we
want to hear her sing too and I didn't
want her to just like sit around there
obviously I felt like maybe maybe it
would be good to give her you know some
some moments where she can
sing
so I like pushed her to sing
something yeah it worked out
[Music]
great
yeah
and you know even times where I I don't
want to like sound
too bossy or anything when I do stuff
like this like also with am like when I
say I say to am likey am can you like
get close to the mic or like sing louder
cuz everyone was in the same distance
from the microphone but you know I think
me and cie cuz we like you know we
trained more we had more vocal training
before and we make a lot of music so
like we automatically already have a
louder voice like it's just like
something that we just like you know and
we just have louder voices when we sing
especially and I notice with people who
don't have much singing or just general
speaking experience like public speaking
or whatever or or streaming I mean
streaming experience they surely have
but like stuff like this um especially
if you don't have much experience with
like like singing into like a real stage
mic on the on the real stage or so cuz
there you really got to be loud like
especially if it's like a pin microphone
you got to be really
loud but all this experience I think
made me and Cali be louder and and then
that's why maybe it seems like you know
it was only one microphone though they
set up like one microphone in the middle
of us in the middle of the table and we
were sitting around the table but there
was everybody was in the same
distance so it's not like anybody was
like unfairly positioned or so but
that's why I was telling like a can you
be a little bit louder cuz people also
in the end cuz I make the stream I
organized the stream and I put it
together people will like complain to me
I've had this before and people will
complain to me and [\h__\h] at me for not
like equally because people come in here
even if they don't if they're not a fan
of me they're here to listen to other
members mayhaps and then they're
like why did you not fairly do this and
that I'm like I'm
trying but yeah so I'm like can you
please come a little bit closer or sing
louder
yeah yeah yeah I want to make everybody
happy too you know I want to want
to make all the communities that that
are in this space I want to satisfy them
and I want them to have a good time and
all that so I tried my best to balance
everything but sometimes it just doesn't
work out uh that easily yeah it's
difficult with like volume control when
there's so many people and also when
there's only one microphone if there
would have been more microphones I maybe
could have changed each knob on its own
but we just had one which is fine though
like normally that should be fine to
have one microphone in the middle of us
shouldn't be an
issue shouldn't be a problem
normally being at the corner of a square
mic what do you mean Square
mic oh ah yeah yeah you mean cuz the the
shape of the microphone was kind of
square
m yeah but we were all kind of at the
corners CU I can draw it for you if you
want but it got a little bit better when
she moved when she scooched a little bit
more towards the middle of the
table but we were kind of all same
distance and same position cuz it was a
square table and everybody was sitting
on the edge of the table on you know you
know how it works we know how a table
works yeah but I think it turned out
okay
yeah yeah they're a bit more quiet in
general you know I'm it's just
embarrassed to raise her voice exactly
she's like a shy type she do be
shy but her voice needs to be heard cuz
it's cute Amy is cute I want to hear Amy
voice it's also for me you know I'm am a
gosling so I'm also speaking from the
point of view of an amig Gosling I want
to hear
me yeah and she she really improved a
lot with singing um so that needs to be
displayed as much as we
can yeah it's a thing it's a thing that
has occurred several times so it's just
you know a mix of interesting uh
characters but that's what makes myth
myth
oh I sip some
water yeah yeah yeah it did make me feel
really fuzzy and happy this whole K
experience I'm glad everybody enjoyed
it off collaps you know we can't do it
that often and it's it's always it
always feels like really weird cuz we we
we talk at each other's faces directly
we can look at each other's faces it
always feels so
like but it's special moments that I
like to cherish and so I'm glad it all
worked out in the
end my meetups don't happen often
yeah it don't happen so often so I
thought it was important even if the
program was cancelled that we still do
something together you know don't get
the chance that often yeah
the plushy has a gun yeah so do I so do
I me love yeah I'm so happy to see all
the support and love for us yeah after
the stream I was catching up with like
all the comments
endlessly and making the community happy
makes me happy too though I feel feel
like um very full my heart is full my
Coco is
full Marcus menaces oh wait I still give
a kiss to that
person marus
men Michael H Neil Persona Michael
Hong thanks for the pink sticker D very
cute very cute you're also excited I can
tell
Bishop I am
[Music]
a even when I just not even use my thumb
I can feel when I just like press
control and
C with my pinky and my pointy finger I
felt something in my
thum
H maybe tomorrow it's gone but this was
like early today in the
morning it's like hours ago like over 10
hours
ago it still
hurts I'm hungry I feel
[Music]
sick
okay I can't say these names they're so
hard to
pronounce the gummy worms the gummy
worms no I don't have compression gloves
no only compression socks Mar medic
[Music]
than
sush Michael H Dy Michael H D Dy F that
just came out
naturally uh 026 2234 what's this code D
running in the 20s
D
Hakuna thank you for the red super chat
thank you very much for this lovely K
it's really nice and blessed way to
start into the day go my go yay I think
goes really early for you up somewhat
early thank you for joining this
legendary moment
[Music]
nonetheless you I guess I'll give you
kisses too or or did I maybe lick you
guys for red of Jets did I possibly do
that
like
[Music]
I did did I do
that I may have done that
[Music]
yes I sound like Yoshi but when I do
that it doesn't come
[Music]
[Laughter]
out murf laser d elwi b d Santiago
Martin thank you for the redp CH this is
so beautiful our bright parade so so
good thank you our bright parade is so
hype I think I mean this is partially
unfair maybe because like shiny smile
story and what was the other one those I
just have heard so often maybe that
plays into it that it's like less hype
at this point but our bride parade is
like number one hype whole life so I
keep mck rer yeah those two are still
nice if anything I think I prefer
hearing K mcky Ridder over shiny my
story yeah OBP
has now OBP is just like even not
considering how often we have heard the
other songs I think our bride parade cuz
of the freaking
Orchestra and the way the the song is
written it's just oh my God
everybody agrees even I've seen so many
people really
enjoying our bright parade yeah connect
the world the Ian song that one's nice
too yeah but I haven't heard it in a
while I haven't heard it in a while they
need
to make Japanese Senpai sing it just
kidding I think that will be
difficult we'll hear it again sometime
for sure
our briad bre is the best full grip song
no contest it's so good anyway Santiago
[Music]
Martin you know you know what I told you
guys love my tongue before it's actually
difficult to get it out so far that um
the the capture thingy reacts
Studio D thank you for the r
CH man it's hard being a frog with a
short
tongue it's hard car s thank you for the
rest of chat I love M I love her life
thank it all me too me too me too man me
too It Ain't Easy being green hard to
guys but for real that's why I eat gummy
worms because they don't try to escape
from me you know they're easier to catch
cuz I just have to open a package and
then then do kisses instead no it's okay
I need to make use of this
tongue what that tongue
[Music]
do thank you
caret oh
[\h__\h]
I feel like I already feel like um like
the muscles in my tongue are building
ah it feels like a workout for my tongue
to like really push it out
there I'm going to have some tongue
muscles if I do this more
often and Steven
T or t Toni I don't know than
AR D left
D Max D CR D for Pinky man bright parade
what a banger song to Rive at the
airport with oh ah just before my flight
to Japan thank you for literal years of
good memories looking forward to the h f
and many more good memories to come with
love a you were on your way to Japan at
that time damn feel like that's really
nice like it's like a like an opening to
your
travels amazing thank you D all I hope
you had a lovely trip you should
probably be back home by now I assume
most everybody probably is home some of
you guys went home so so soon after and
some of you guys stayed a bit longer
like
me I know froggy waa hello Tad PS hello
you get it you know what's
up
hfb gang is still there what do you mean
like
who I've got one mutual Cinder
pan I left on Monday after f it was too
early I left on Sunday day I think and I
didn't uh get back until
Monday you know it took me [\h__\h] long
time
going to grab the plusy now and thank
you
get I saw some of you guys were worried
about the the size of the Parker but
that's also one thing I was considering
like you know we can only do one size
but the fact that it has a
zipper means you can you can kind of
just like throw it over and you know use
it as a jacket that you just can't close
perhaps if if that's the
case but at least maybe you can still
leave you know wear it without closing
it I don't know maybe I was thinking at
least like you know that
extends the
usage if you're more on the on the
friend shaped uh side
maybe I don't know maybe give it a try
or use it as motivation to lose weight I
don't
know the arms might be too tight yeah I
know I don't know I don't know how big
it will be if you had like one size
stuff from Japan before then you can
probably
imagine but then just get the plushy at
least we've been losing a lot of weight
for this
moment buff
frog I'm quite slim and petite so it
should fit just fine slim and
petite wow I'm slim and petite I think
it will be too big for me
though but am I SL slim and petite maybe
I am compared to um like
men generally generally
speaking but I'm I guess on my own I'm
not that slim and petite I don't know if
I can slow me
[Music]
considered oh
right now I'm peti peti frogy
wa small small ziply thank you for the
pinky man I love myth and boss if you
see this no this is a different ziply or
yes I'm working at the same time
whichever works better as an excuse
don't fire me please I need the money
for SUP us wait wait wait what do you
mean what do you mean why why why are
you trying to make
excuses is it because you were telling
me that smoothie that you won't be
around anymore that much CU you got at
work are you just like saying oh don't
worry about me oh I saw my boss checking
out the stream at one point so it was in
case he'd catch me watching the stream
on company time oh you thought he might
see your super
chat I thought you meant me with boss hi
smothie oh she flopped she flopped
here take my leg oh she's attacking my
leg oh
no that's
tinkly
tin she love
me she love me but she attacked me what
does it
mean
[Music]
stuck okay I love
you I love I love the
fluff I love
[Music]
fluff okay no that was just the sound of
her nail
like her like pulling it out of the
chair okay anyway D please
I hope your boss didn't see you and just
have a box ready at all time and then
hide under the box and then he will see
the box and he'll just say ah just the
box and then he'll move
on even though I didn't play the game I
still find it very amusing to just say
that just a box
joke Michael
D
masak flaming pants Cruz
sh no name d thank you a or a d Richard
G D and M for the pinky great Steno
always fun to have this off collab shame
we perfect time for to show up perfect
song to end on sorry my my phone was
covering the the the message
uh prepare yourself for Poppy's playtime
good I will definitely hold you to that
so far she's not holding me to it and
yeah um I realized too that there was no
song with
Ena but uh that's because M the songs
that
she claimed were the only ones she could
sing within whole
life where uh ghost right and uh
what was it was it Callie's song what
was it the other one no it was her own
song I guess I guess just her own
song Violet yeah just those two so and I
mean I can sing Violet a little bit but
I
thought cuz I already probably going to
pair up with the others a
lot um because they have some songs that
the others can't sing you know you know
you know I was like thinking how do I
get a good balance um and I wasn't very
confident with violet or ghost anyway so
I just paired her up with
c and Amit I
[Music]
think yeah yeah yeah so unfortunately
that resulted in me not singing with uh
with Ena but that doesn't mean
anything that the thing is that's not an
original song and I I don't know if I
could have sang it safely in an archived
and the theme was whole life songs so
you
[Music]
know we totally hate each other
yeah okay I'm done with those super
chats I'm sorry they took me so long
they weren't even that many oh my God
I'm so
[Music]
useless okay um
there is the waiting room there's H NOA
there's the one from yeser hey it's not
that
much besides the waiting room wait I
kind of thought I streamed more
since
h
Huh huh that's not so bad that's really
not so bad
huh let
me finish the hold on so C
first ah sh wrong I opened the stream I
meant
to save the
[Music]
thumbnail I you know it was
so such a hurdle to get my Photoshop to
work on my
iPad cuz uh I had to log into my
Photoshop account but my my Adobe
account I didn't know the password I
didn't know this I didn't know that I
didn't
email so many like forgotten passwords
and I had to react to
it ah there was so many hurdles and I
finally got it to
work and then photoshop on iPad I don't
know what it is maybe it's just because
I don't understand Apple products but is
kind of difficult to use on the iPad it
would be a little bit easier if I had a
keyboard Maybe I'll buy a keyboard
eventually um but at least more and more
I'm I'm making my iPad more
useful for traveling so that I maybe
don't have to bring my laptop all the
time yeah but this is a very
scuffed very scuffed thumbnail but it
looks cute doesn't it which is only
thanks to the art that's the only reason
why it looks
cute
I didn't want to keep on asking others
to make thumnails for me cuz I really
needed a couple that's why I just was
like [\h__\h] it I'm going to try do it
myself this
time a drawing stylist for the iPad yeah
Ena also told me like ah you have an
iPad right you should you should you
know draw regularly on the iPad and I'm
like well I mean it's not about you know
I have a tablet at home here
here you know it's one of my screens I
can use that but yeah for traveling when
I'm on the road and all that the iPad
would be nice I guess to be able to draw
on it and I saw you know I saw people
draw a lot of cool stuff on iPads and
you know did tell me that the pen
pressure or sensitivity is even better
on the iPad than on a freaking Wacom
tablet which is
crazy that's crazy but I don't have the
pen for
it I would need to buy the pen hope we
get more H to collabs I've been telling
the producer behind H toi which is an
Ian producer been telling the whole time
H to new song when this last one did so
well and
yeah I've been met with agreement of
course but it's like um I guess there's
a lot of other projects to be worked on
and that's this is like kind of on the
back burner
maybe um but it's definitely in the back
of their minds
so I think there will be more it's just
uh the question of
when
yeah and
[Music]
what I know I know cuz like honi like
was I I'm so happy because there's a
part of me that felt insecure um like
this is like you know know my unit that
I kind of created and so I felt kind of
like some sense
of uh what's the word being in charge
what's the word for that again
[Music]
um responsibility yeah just
responsibility I guess of making it
succeed and then I also felt like I I'm
not that popular so I don't know I don't
think I can bring that
much of like uh like views to the MV and
all that on my own and so I'm like I'm
the leader but I can't I don't even have
that much power so I was like really
worried about that felt insecure about
it um you know you know I want I want
also like other people in the unit like
superai especially cuz like she is
really popular and I feel like if I
bring her if I like make her be part of
a unit like that then I don't want to be
await I don't want to
be I don't know you know what I
mean I just wanted I I wanted to be
comfortable and easy for her and like
not just extra work that is not even
worth doing you know what I mean but
then then H Tony turned out to be a
success and really popular with people
and the song uh like really became
popular too so I think
um it it went okay it went pretty well
now I'm again kind of scared of like
going into it again um but I I don't
want to um miss out on it either so I'm
definitely going to give it another try
if if we do get another song and all
that um but I definitely feel a lot of
pressure cuz it's so to say a unit I
created and if it fails then it feels
like I failed you know what I
mean but thankfully people love holot a
lot and see a lot of potential in it
just like I
[Music]
do do you think they will accept me even
though I'm a
Frog people say frogs taste like chicken
so I'm kind of a of a
bird what will happen to hori
now it's okay I'll dress up as kiaha
I'll CA play kiaha it will be all the
same I'll just be really
small
h
h h amphibian do we have any other
amphibians wait what are amphibians like
not fish
right what's an amphibian besides a
frog amphibians are really difficult
man we don't do we not have any
others oh my God we actually don't
je frogs and salamanders what the hell
are
nudes I don't have any nudes for you
frog you a nudes don't exist you don't
want to see what's behind this hoodie or
this
onesie
what the [\h__\h] are
nudes I should Google it send
nudes wait what nudes are just not cute
a
what
NES oh what do you mean they're hella
cute they're like a mix of a salamander
and an axel from what I can see
oh my God they're so
cute what what's the German name for
this is a nud lizard nudes are sometimes
confused with lizards but they are
definitely not these reptiles what do
you mean these rep because they have no
skills only thin damp skin throughout
which they can breathe and they move
much more slowly also lizards like all
reptiles do not breathe in water so it's
like a water
lizard cute I'm on
Mo oh the German word I've heard before
definitely oh mo and that's cute that's
really cute oh I see a picture of them
on a hand are they always this small or
is this bubble
bubo oh there's some bigger ones wait
that's [\h__\h] cute that's so cute who
the [\h__\h] said that this is like a uncute
axel this is maybe even cuter to me than
an axel
axelon look
like
this never mind
not they just look kind of
e they look ew they look like
[Laughter]
ew
e you take that back
no they're cute in
Minecraft maybe in other games too but
in
[Music]
reality guys I want you to see look look
at this let let me do an eye roll what
do you
think does it look
good I think it will will be a good
reaction GIF
GIF show it to me
afterwards I need to see cuz I can't see
when I'm rolling my
eyes you felt
that click your
oh wait when do you what time What's the
timing in the
beginning but then the GI GI needs
sound I kind of out of reflex
I I do um click my
tongue wouldn't say quite often but like
more often than Japanese people do and
then when I do it in Japan everybody's
like always so
offended I'm like sorry it's a reflex
like it's like way more way more rude in
Japan I've
[Music]
noticed yeah when I'm just like even
when I'm annoyed towards myself or so I
do it or like when I'm annoyed I like oh
anything
really and then the sucking sound I
think I have from Japan though I think
this it's like very very popular
Communication in Japanese
language and I picked it up I was like I
think a lot of Japanese members use this
but this is not this is not
offensive
it's like when you're
like in a difficult situation or like
anything that's like o or or yab or very
versatile yeah yeah Aqua Sena uses it a
lot yeah why am I not reading super
chats guys
why like Peter after he hit his
leg no
doesn't he go like well I guess he does
suck and then he goes
like something like that
right that's that's like like he's just
very really heavily breathing in
though please continue yapping Yap y y y
y yum y y y
[Music]
y okay I'll read the read them I'll read
them I will read the [\h__\h] out of them
there's not so many there's only seven
no wait there's more there's more Jacob
47 than you H anniversary merch go I
also finally got merch and it fit quite
well I was actually quite concerned um
when I got the merch um I I I took two
suitcases that are pretty big two two
two and and I I left half of them empty
pretty much pretty much
almost yeah yeah pretty much
half Timmy is fine I actually he fit in
so comfortably I I still had so much
space I first put everything else in
there and stuff like the whole Little
Talk cup I like uh got rid of the box
and just like no wait no maybe not the
whole T cup other stuff though I got rid
of the box and just put it in there to
like save space like the tumbler M and
then and yeah I put everything in there
and then I still I had even though I
brought so much I had four pairs of
shoes I think and two coats which one of
them I was wearing but you
know yeah I had a lot of stuff actually
and and then I was worried about the
merch not fitting in but oh my God my
Tetris brain was like wo on full
drive and then I was able to put the
chicken in pretty comfortably it didn't
have to be like smushed
much and now he's in this room with me
he's looking at me actually
hi he's he's in the
corner he's watching
me he doesn't know that I'm going to eat
him
tonight maybe maybe I'll have mercy
Maybe I'll Have Mercy I think
[Music]
about he's cute
though I feel like maybe he should have
been a little bit more
round originally they were a little bit
more egg shaped and then they were
adjusted to be a bit more round I don't
know maybe they should have been a
little bit more round I'm not
sure they're pretty good though pretty
pretty nicely
shaped pretty
cute did you pre-order your I'm not
going to I'm not I'm not buying my own
merch they're going to give me one for
sure but I'm mind blown by the
figma the like the pictures of the poses
and the expressions are really nice and
I did not [\h__\h] know that you can put
the sword into the [\h__\h] shield and
then you guys are like everybody's like
oh my god oh you didn't know
what really concerned with me and I'm
like huh and then some people sent me
pictures of examples of
uh references of how like it this kind
of thing has been done before in like
Japanese like what do you call these
things
to
to and then I'm like oh it's a
thing it's no no I understand like I I
saw the badge changing when I have it
out and but I didn't I thought that was
just you know a cute little badge didn't
think it was actually possible cuz yeah
I never saw it combined before and
suddenly it's combined it looks so cool
and and now it makes sense why the sword
is so
small and you guys never brought this up
before when we talked about the sword
being freaking small and looking like a
toy and like a candy corn
um Halloween
candy the reason is because it fits into
the shield and you never brought that up
so I didn't know
either no I am froggy waa what do I know
maybe Tak knew about this I did not know
about
it we waited to see to conf
confirm damn no yeah somebody brought up
the reference sheet but then another
person was also like oh I never saw that
before and I'm like like that that's
there I didn't notice and I also didn't
notice it's so small it's like not even
colored I think that part wasn't even
colored was just a little sketch I
didn't notice that at
all yeah but now
sh come on like the badge is just a
badge didn't think much about the badge
just being you know I the badge is just
to me it was just a gimmick cuz when the
swords and The Sword and the shield is
not out there it combines into the badge
yeah that's a different
story but now I have to
say that that's so dope to me I I I like
the weapons a little bit more now now
now that I know of this
function
whoa
P that's pretty
dope and I learned about this after 3
and a half
[Music]
years makes you wonder what what else is
out there that we don't know yet I mean
you guys guys all act like this was so
obvious and that you already knew
[Music]
it shut the [\h__\h]
up I hate you I hate
you let me let me be fascinated Okay and
like
how cuz like okay why did let's say was
obvious why did it take until the figma
to actually be put into like visualized
reality why was this never a thing in my
freedy wut why why was this never a
thing in any promotional image any
anything anything why was this never a
thing in merchandise before HH why was
this never like used this gimmick that
seems so important and like shows you
how these weapons work and how why this
why the sword is so small and all
that
yeah no I mean mer I mean like stuff
that the company makes like for example
the badge that just came out badge or
whatever pin whatever it's my sword and
my shield like on top of each other why
not together you know stuff like that if
if that is a like possibility then why
not how can I ask for something that I
don't know is
possible man you guys
suck you guys are you think you're so
smart you think you're so smart get off
of your
horse get off of your allmighty horse up
there get down here this instant
it
no
anyway the figurine is really nice that
was really
nice really
cool go get
it was a long time for this fingering to
finally come out really a long [\h__\h]
time fre when was this first announced
like three years ago it's been 84
[\h__\h]
years the Nando Nando still in the works
yeah when will I stop being gray waa the
gray graduate from Wawa the gray waa
become Wawa the colorful
rainbow
one out of seven
scale that's not something that
everybody gets
right W of Many Colors two people say
that is that actually a
title you know that if you press a
button on the hilt the word lights up
and it makes a whoh noise when you swing
what the [\h__\h] are you talking
about why are you lecturing me about my
equipment all right let's move
San calls himself San of Many Colors
after he stops being ripped in the book
only
right that's many colors that seems too
friendly for Saron what who does he
think he
is many
colors does he even pick become colorful
because like when they're the white or
when they're the gray you actually see
it in their outfits but that's I guess
maybe just a
movie does he get a rainbow
[Music]
Rob that's kind of ridiculous for a
medieval fantasy thingy where everything
is pretty subdued and gray and dark
and not
saturated It's Magic why doesn't fit
sand though what's with the LEDs yo
wasn't the LED strips
[Music]
suddenly that's so
funny that is so
funny we're ready for the
[Music]
Rave h
man I am entertained are you not
entertained I am really
entertained I have the
RGB the Lord was that he called himself
many colors due to splitting white light
like the rainbow and gandal thought it
was foolish to destroy something to find
out what it was made
of but that's just science
Gandalf
Gandalf kind of wack
back that's that you need to do stuff
like that to
learn of possibilities and
stuff and isn't there a lot of light
isn't light and endless
source so you split a little bit it
doesn't mean that he got rid of all the
light right otherwise then yeah if
that's the case then if he [\h__\h] it up
and there's no more light because he
made a rainbow out of himself then okay
I get it okay that's a problem but like
surely there's more light out there he
just split a little bit of light
[Music]
I it's explained a lot in the
books why want the green he's a Prisma
he also had two blue Wizards that went
not yeah I know I know I I watched them
like deep deep lore stuff about
them uh s was trying to expand his
powers beyond what was intended by the
higher
ups falsely considered himself exalted
simply because he took something in
Harmony and broke it apart he didn't
really do
anything
oh shows the Hub and s's actions as by
splitting the light he is making it and
does himself lesser and form
lesser y'all are interesting we should
make a lord of drinks B book club just
Among Us Among Us just Among
Us no what I saw I saw
Shi watch Lord the Rings and then
they're also having a collab right and
another a watchalong collab they're
doing a lot of watchalong collabs were
they watch the next one too right I'm
not invited for some
reason even though I would I would say
I'm one of the biggest Lord of the Rings
representatives in all
life uh you didn't ask I didn't know it
was
happening invite yourself no no maybe
it's for people who haven't seen it
yet maybe they just haven't seen it yet
and I already saw it so that's not not
my place but uh yeah I'm I'm happy to
see I'm happy to see they are uh getting
into it more and more whole life members
are getting into it during their time in
whole life didn't guda also get into it
during her time in whole
[Music]
life
amazing amazing no I'm fine not watching
it with them that's okay but I just want
them to know after they're done watching
it if they want to talk about it with
someone and let let them know that I am
crazy about Lord of the Rings I watched
it many many times I would like to
talk she spent the whole first movie and
she chat did she even watch
[Music]
alongo what she just or did she actually
watch oh ah oh yeah just she's seen it
before okay so she didn't watch it in
the moment
[Music]
though speaking of movies I I watched
new
tangent I
watched the new WKA movie in
airplane
and I have to
say this really makes you think um I
actually I was
like hesitating to watch
it because yeah there's a new one so I
saw in the movie selection in the new
movies I saw the Wonka movie on my
flight to Japan I was like I I didn't
watch it I just saw it was there and I'm
like H new is this new or is this old
but then I think of the
the
Wonka like not theme park but like you
know that experience that they had that
went viral because it looks like [\h__\h]
and I have to say that
honestly like influenced my mind into
thinking that if that is [\h__\h] then the
movie is probably [\h__\h]
too because in some way I don't know I
feel like that repres presents it and
then the probably the movie is [\h__\h] if
they can't get something better done in
reality then the movie is probably
[\h__\h] that's what I was thinking so I
must
say they should sue them for M
representation it just kind of like put
that warm in my brain and I would like
to have it in my tummy so I don't know
why it's in my brain but besides the
brain warms I ended up on my flight back
watching it CU I was like well I don't
have anything else to watch like I watch
these other things that look interesting
now I don't know what else is
interesting so I'm just going to watch
the Wonka thing and see how it is and it
was
amazing I really liked it it was really
cute it turned out to be kind of like a
musical so I think Nissa would enjoy it
too it was really good I really liked it
and I I was like what is this this is a
remake or so before I watched it but
then I I realized um because I was like
um didn't I watch a Wonka movie like
when I was a child is this the same
movie or what turns out I think it's a
prequel I don't remember the contents
anymore of the original Wonka movie that
you know everybody watched when they
were a child but at that time the Wonka
Factory was already like there existing
right so this new movie is about how
when he was quite a bit younger I guess
when when he like creates the whole
thing it was a prequel and it was really
nice it was really nice and I [\h__\h]
love the oal loas
OAA and the OA looma is played by this
famous actor what was his name
w h GR
he is so good and it's really
interesting how they um like did this I
think they basically put him in a green
suit Green Green Key suit um because it
seems like they only recorded his head
and then separately animated his body
that's what it looks like but it's kind
of funny the way it comes together is
kind of
funny yeah Hugh Grant is the OA loopa is
so
funny he's so funny like these kind of
characters the sarcastic like I don't
give a [\h__\h] kind of characters are
always the best ones
someh he's so
good yeah his hair is so funny he really
reminds me of the small king or whatever
from
Shrek in terms of being small and
looking funny and his attitude
and his big
head far red yeah Lord Falk guess he's
not a king he's just a lord huh now that
I think about it his title is Lord he
not a king [\h__\h]
weak he's just a lord I just realized
that he's just a [\h__\h] Lord what you
want h
[Music]
a huge ass Castle but just Lord that's
actually kind of impressive but yeah
anyway that's why he wants to get
married no princesses so that's what
makes you a that's not what makes you a
king that's not what makes you a
king
fantasy
Rose she's she comes with a better
status yeah that's at least one thing
that would probably up his rank
anyway don't even get me start started
on like medieval ranks and all that
[Music]
I
if he marry her and her parents die he
become yeah okay so like completely
through her bloodline
yeah so
thisn okay uh where was
I oh yeah oh my God I went on like 20
tangents just because of hokan's Super
Chat talking about anniversary merch and
me talking about how I packed it all all
into my
guys I went on 20 [\h__\h]
tons holy [\h__\h] I don't even know how we
got
here ah
damn
[Music]
damn which is so funny
because hokan hokan made me waste so
much time but he's probably not very
amused
G is
uh
European and that's the time is
ticking probably like hurry up and end
your stream
lady but you're the one who' made me
tangent even if you didn't intend on
doing
so wait you go by frog can these days
don't you frog can so funny y' yell with
your froggy names you're looking so
cute tangent more no I don't I don't
want to oh no frog and not frog can huh
that's you right some of you guys I
don't really I'm not sure if I recognize
some of you guys some of your names are
kind of a
stretch like who is
this who is
this who the [\h__\h] is this
Franklin you're missing out why are you
not frog Clin or FR froggin HH why are
you still Franklin you're too
normal it's mine wait where it go is
mine too much no I you're
miffin which is is quite a stretch but I
still recognize it even though I don't
see your guys' profile
pictures I change it later okay good
oh yeah you should change it El Dapper
cabalo I recommend El Frogger cabalo to
be your new name can't think of a good
one frog
weed could also be naid fro frog fretti
froget forget about it Navid fretti
would be good
too
I need to read
some I need to read some CH I need to
read some
chat
K sounds good frog
[Music]
frog
corrosion oh that's good yeah you you
guys can use kle as well if that fits
better in your name
wait du
du d k d d
[Music]
or
d d goose
[Music]
yeah rad is
difficult you can maybe also just add
something rad of the lily pads or Rad
Rad pole oh my God is that tadpole R po
oh [\h__\h] oh okay I'm I'm
that's amazing I'm oh my
God okay I have to
read phone thank you for the r of CH
than it all the painful irony of tal
streaming and an hour that normally be
great for my time zone is that my
getting dragged out to touch grass for
my birthday means I might end up missing
the whole stream as a result so I'll
send this ahead of time just in case
love you bu thank you well at least I
had had a couple of streams at na
friendly times which is really really a
rare occasion hope the I hope the na
Bros enjoyed that um but yeah happy
belated birthday phone con are you here
are you
[Music]
here are you here hello
yeah congratulations I hope you had a
nice birthday did you still get to watch
my stream even if not the birthday is
important you
know it's nice to touch grass on your
birthday there's nothing to feel like
regretful about in my
opinion El froger Cabell amazing
amazing
perfect I got home like 10 minutes after
that no okay that feels some kind
of bad but at least the VOD was ready
for you to
enjoy yeah happy birthday F I wish you
all the best thank you so much for your
support
[Music]
La
pink thank
you
and
Channel
[Music]
and
d g d d I did get some I did get some
fan mail too guys and also got some like
one that was really really
old uh I think from
2022 but I think the reason why I got it
now partially I think is because it it
it was
combined uh with
something that was kind of like a gift
normally I shouldn't be getting
gifts but maybe it was given to the
staff at an event uh it was not just a
letter so I was like yeah that's
probably
why maybe although there would have
probably been other chances to give it
to
me before now I don't know
why it's okay though I got some stuff
again I have to look through it
though yeah I didn't unpack anything yet
I I only unpacked
like
2% of my suitcase
stuff I'll be setting it l soon okay go
go go go go go go go do it do it do it
do it do it do it now now now now now
now
like socks no what's that unpack just
uh my
iPhone and
charger
and M that's pretty much
[Music]
it
okay Sal d py
d and Travis age 45 Dano ooh Happy happy
I I already said happy birthday to your
uh daughter nice random collusion Dy all
put that into the clip instead what do
you mean d all anyway thanks for the
pinky spanking D all good night kfb good
luck acquiring
way I really enjoyed
thato horon no game for the first time
in a
while it's
nice
too bad you can't see my stretches cuz
my hands are too far thank you for the
super chats
guys can't break 10K ah skill
issue G
sh good stretch Big
Stretch and
Bishop wler wler than pet okay thank you
for the red chat
[Music]
on is it working it's working thank you
so much oh thato there you
go pretty unrecognizable if I wouldn't
have given you the
name rad pole oh my God it's
perfect can can
H
[Music]
yay Tass
pole we're frogging stand back they're
frogging yeah thank you petza for the
beautiful red jet no text though it's
kind of sad kind of lonely you're not
giving me any reason to tangent huh you
must have
known D it on anyway
[Music]
Michael H D Michael H D IO
happy I am looking forward to playing
Yakuza next week again the qu artist
thanks for the pinky Temple of Doom is a
but the kid in it ended up not getting
another role in Hollywood till
everything everywhere all at once in
2022 and he won best supporting act
for until
she
that took a
while but nice said with the first time
he returns he already gets like an award
for it although just yesterday I watched
like a
video about how Awards award shows are
just [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] um cuz they're rigged anyway
and it's just like fancy Hollywood
people congratulating each other again
and again and
again and then they talked about how
um what's the name again of this guy the
British guy from The Office who um
hosted the was it the Oscars or so or
the Grammys one of those shows he hosted
and then he roasted yeah Ricky he
roasted everybody and then everybody was
like oh my God my my Coco is bro but
people loved it and the numbers on the
the viewer numbers what what what you
call it we're insane so he got invited
again even though he even kind of
insults the organizers as well but they
got you watch the same video yeah I like
that channel they called him again and
again like the ratings yeah again he's
really scandalous says a lot of crazy
[\h__\h] but ratings are amazing they call
him again he's like I'm not going to do
it again but they gave him a great deal
he does it again he's like I'm not going
to I don't really want to do this like I
don't care about this shitty show he
kept keeps on roasting it keeps on
making fun of it and the people there
make some
crazy not even jokes it's just reality
but like just
roast and I think he did it five five
years in a row in the end until he
finally got
dropped but uh
honestly I didn't watch these I only
watched those like little Snippets even
until the end I thought like like what
he was
saying I was entertained by it and I
thought it was
good give those Hollywood actors a
reality check for [\h__\h] sake yeah yeah
tell them their movie is [\h__\h] tell them
their movie doesn't even deserve to be
on here tell them is all
rigged
yeah yeah good fre out of check so Ricky
big U big uh for that it was very very
very
entertaining
so
yeah but then you know I think that that
kid the fact that he got an award as
best supporting actor I would think like
he deserved it so I would think not
everything is like completely rigged and
and people don't deserve what they get
at this Wars but in the end like it's
there's so many wars and it's like it's
all just for
H show it's all just for show in the end
it's all like so
[Music]
superficial and space waterful
d could have done this in 5 minutes and
yet I do it in a [\h__\h]
hour H animation judges admitted to not
even watching the nominees they just
asked their kids
what for like what you mean for animated
movies in
particular I mean it's nice that kids
play a part because they're the main
audience I
mean why not let the main audience be a
judge of
it
uh to push their skills to chase
them yeah but then again it seems like
pretty difficult to get to that level
even if you're a great filmmaker like
this is like it seems like it's like
only like for Hollywood people and
getting into that seems like something
that's not really easy it's like getting
into whole life you may be a great
YouTuber but then getting into to whole
life is like really difficult you know
doesn't mean that you're not a good
vtuber but it's just really
difficult there's other words that are
more impacting than the Lo
cars it's just uh it is just an event
for rich people to dress up in crazy
dresses and stuff and Blitz and glamour
bling
bling to take some nice pictures and be
the talk of the red
carpet I think for them for the
celebrities that might be the thing that
they look forward to the most they
probably don't even care that much about
those stupid Awards probably care more
about like you know being the
talk uh with their with their fancy
outfits I don't
know I mean I'd like to have an occasion
like that to dress up for as well I
don't no but I'm sure it it Strokes
their ego nicely to dress up like that
and feel like the elite that they are
have that be confirmed how Elite they
are and how rich they are and how
they're in an exclusive kind of
environment
yeah oh my God need to stop yapping and
spitting facts oh my
God yeah who are you wearing what do you
mean who I didn't I didn't kill anyone
and wear their skin on my skin that's
disgusting what are you implying is this
true crime documentary or what am I
being do I need a lawyer I'm not wearing
anybody I do I need to call a lawyer I I
don't I will not talk to you anymore U
from this point on forward I don't
remember anything I don't recall
anything I don't have memories of
anything except for positive things
anything that incriminates me I do not
have a memory
of I played the
fifth I will now go Kidd got to keep
some super Deads for tomorrow right this
seems like I cannot get [\h__\h] done
anyway that's not a thing in
Austria yeah but um we're
talking u u um this is a um what's the
word this is a
the
uh this is a
no this is
a
no
eggs no this is
[Music]
a I'm so close the word help me
sign
s scenario why can't you [\h__\h] help me
guys you always help me why don't you
know what I'm trying to say this time in
this scenario I am in America is what I
was trying to
say damn feel like I just birthed a
child a
tadpole
scenario how can I well
context should have let you there I
blame
you I blame
you okay now I go I'm done my J here is
[Music]
done qu quack qu
quack I'm looking for
no I need to remember
these up here it's
done
[Music]
okay I go tomorrow tomorrow we going to
play frog
detective which is I think in the desert
I watched like a little bit when Amma
played it back in the day she was like
on a scooter in the desert I think
that's all I remember we will crack okay
so we will indeed I hope you enjoyed
fing come back I'm so cute I have cute
[Music]
hands bye bye and in
frogy language we say h ribbon i ribb
[Music]
d i can do that on my own too
though
at least I bought
[Music]
them yes I can bye m i
RI
[Music]
fun