[Music]
go
one two say no
[Music]
oh so
one two say no
[Music]
ch
B
[Music]
one two say
one two say no
[Music]
what my n Go
bang M watch my M go bang
hey
welcome momies you I
[Music]
sparking a life English and
today we're playing West day five of
seven days to
die I spawn inside a car very
nice says good night and stay safe
cat you up in the
morning
oh why are we all spawn in the same
place that's really funny oh she left
again hello everyone today we are
playing more it is day five I don't
think a hoorde will happen
today um so today we will work
on strengthening ourselves we do have
a new trade route at the
bottom that we can unlock and I think
what we should do is we should have a
new house maybe down there
because things are starting to get kind
of
far so I think maybe that's what also my
leg is
injured yeah probably go there today
well let me TR
this
hello
hello good morning good
morning how you doing I'm doing good I
just woke up like IRL you mean
yes good morning what a great time to be
awake yeah with my friends here in a
zombie apocal lives gang needing to
survive it's the best time to be awake
what's the plan today
Chief um Chief I'm
Chief uh no I think uh personally I just
want to gather a lot of basic materials
for armor kits um and then also increase
my Forge improve my Forge by making a
little Bellow for for it and just making
some doing some
quests yeah do you have the the special
quest for the trade at the bottom
yet uh no I don't have it yet okay well
you might get it soon since we have been
doing all the same Quest together so you
probably yeah I think maybe like once a
couple of us have that Quest we should
all go down there together yeah yeah cuz
that's another that's another
inventory to lock maybe some good stuff
oh oh okay yeah then well JMA just
closed JMA
no so when she opens up we can get one
or two more tier two quests I would hope
that that does the
trick one or two more wait oh yeah I
guess does Trad wct close at the same
time too yeah okay they should have
different opening and closing times busy
buiness baby I guess we can collect
materials while it's
closed yeah just like raiding random
houses
maybe oh there's a coyote over there
coyote coyote can we can we T the doggle
you like bones you like bones or
something do you want a bone do you want
I want do he'll kill you
yeah where did that one come
from all right beautiful blood explosion
why did we lose so much HP for nothing I
have one HP now oh god oh yeah can I get
a party invite please oh yeah shut I
hear more zombies what's going
on it's just in my
brain no I hear it too oh oh he's up
there oh oh oh he's
coming
oh you thought it was one of
us I'll leave it to him I'll invite you
to the
party thank
you yeah seems like today we'll be a
pretty small group again okay uh so I
probably can do like everything together
in our small group
hi okay shall we go like towards some
houses
maybe oh fauna has a quest oh fauna has
a quest oh we should do thate yes yes oh
it just two of free okay no
[Music]
problem VA wake up wake up wake up it's
morning
now her glasses are shaped like a like a
beetles beetles
eyes do you know what I mean Beetle
glasses yours I guess
so they look funky on
her oh press F press f for what oh
flashlight oh oh yeah I have night
vision goggles I hope they will come in
handy sometime that's cool black and
white though hello hello hello good
morning good morning
sunshine wait why do you know I was
asleep well you you just standing there
with you know we just assumed like you
were you know asleep standing up mhm I
thought you were listening to me I was
talking about how I was taking a nap
right before this so I just
to did you yeah I did but maybe it
wasn't a nap for me maybe it was just oh
sleep a ho a whole weep been sleep yeah
oh oh what is this well I hope you had
it good nap it was kind of a non restful
nap you know I feel like their naps are
never restful for me
oh like I have to I have to sleep a
whole sleep a nap you didn't get your
full REM cycle yeah exactly yeah
understandable uh we were thinking of
first of all you have a quest over there
still and JMA is closed so we might as
well do your
quest um sound good yeah I can't do tier
three quests yet so I just got to rely
on you you guys for now is this one in
tier three oh it is yeah scary we can do
it and besides that I just want to you
know gather some basic materials for
more armor kits like duct tape duct tape
Duck duct tape and I have quite a lot of
oh yeah we need all the kind of basic
stuff and yeah I said it to people
already but it seems like we're going to
stay a pretty small group today from
what I've heard so we can do a lot of
quests together have sounds good yay
does anyone here have any
farming
SK I guess
not no I the only farma was sh yeah I
was thinking about trying to learn some
far farming cuz I feel like we should
get a big farm yeah maybe maybe you
should we you should also learn farming
hello hello
Domo hi I just got the game I'm good I'm
trying to join your party so I can see
where
you we are at the like this desolation
area yeah maybe maybe a rule of Thum is
to have two people on on a skill each so
like one backup one yeah and other for
like when they're not online so yeah you
can take a farming I'll try to get a
farm going watch the video well actually
to be precise I watched one minute of
a it's better than nothing that's good
enough okay and hopefully we'll find
more farming magazines to bring you up
quickly yeah yeah yeah there might be
some at the house because I don't think
Shia has looked in the house yet so we
might it might be there oh yeah I think
it'll be okay cuz uh the farming perks
are in fortitude which is what I've
already speced into
so to easily get the
perks okay um
so well Kelly I already said it like
twice to the other girls now but um uh
today hopefully we can find a lot of
basic materials to get more armor kits
so duct tape glue all that kind of stuff
uh and and fabric yeah and and we're
just going to do quests in our small
group I guess cuz we're probably not
going to be that many people yeah Quest
find magazines for fauna and I want to
at some some point I'm going to make a
Bellow for my Forge to improve it the
forge yeah just basic things need books
for that or just materials no I already
it's just a couple of materials oh I'm
dying of hunger me too I have I'll give
you I'll give you food if you can kill
me what what why would we do that
because I'm at like 20 HP and I don't
want to fail the
quest oh won't you fail the I guess
before you
start true enough oh oh oh oh oh please
set me on fire
yay you were not on fire what food you
got uh only raw food I guess
I give you I give you a can of
stuff a can you have to share the one
can between the
two that's not possible why no I'll eat
I'll eat one raw meat or maybe maybe two
raw
meat maybe three raw
meat the Rel is pretty far away there
she comes running yeah we're we're
pretty far wait you came oh is that you
huh yeah oh there you are did you come
with a helicopter or something no I
started running immediately from the old
house oh wow you you r a long way oh
yeah I did okay then let's go to fauna's
Quest cuz she's the only one who has one
it seems it kind of is that the one
that's really far away no it's not that
far it's just up the road let's do it
anybody have any tea oh I have
tea do you have diarrhea yeah maybe I
shouldn't have eaten the r meat the raw
meat gives you diarrhea too here you
go that's why the cooks got to cook it
yeah oh maybe I can try making a mini
bike too today dang maybe I'll learn
some cooking think we should have three
Cooks oops sorry yeah maybe yeah I think
I don't know we could consider like
mobile cooking like bringing a a cooking
grill with
them that would be useful is the issue
really that we don't have enough cooks
or is the issue we don't have enough
cooking stations to make food at the
same time uh efficiently I think the
issue is we're not home enough to yeah
make and we don't have enough
ingredients should we make a home next
to the trader just for food cooking I
think we should make a home next to the
fourth the third the new Traer that
we're about to get I think cuz that
one's way more down south too are you
getting poked by the bird fauna yeah
can I hit it no not with the bicycle it
has been tested
already he's going to get it eventually
oh that works
too I missed all my shots dang it oh no
is it here well the fact is that you you
tried and that's what
matters well yeah kill that bird
focusing on fists isn't so helpful when
the bird can fly huh yeah it's not you
can shoot
I'm in trouble I have an infection by
the Zombie by The Bird oh my gosh I'm in
bad
die maybe it's time to die FAA I guess
so I guess there's not XP debt after all
is there apparently hey bio you're a
knife guy right yes I'm a knife guy here
this is for you this is called Knife Guy
I think you're subscribed to this thank
you you're welcome wait should I
die no there's no penalty we kill you
yeah okay cool all right here we go it's
going to be swift I'll make it quick
okay that wasn't very
quick wow you can do the splits fa oh my
gosh we can we can Farm exp like this
apparently because we get exp by killing
each
other freaking way that's just wrong n
is
cheating I do not support that
strategy there's supposed to be
penalty but I think we don't need to I'm
just saying it's there yeah good now
keep your options
open okay let's go to funa house Quest
house okay Fun Quest house let's run it
Y is it this big tall apartment no it's
a little further into the neighborhood
oh Kelly have you been in this
neighborhood already
little bit you know we dabbled around
here but nothing too much might be good
to get a house here though multiple
houses yeah or in the as people said
probably I guess at that point we can
just make it in the next area yeah oh
true what May snow I already have tier
three the new trador is to the South Way
South of
us is it this house I don't know which
house is this house maybe this one right
here just the garage
oh I'm
starving oh no it's not this one this
one is four stars so it's oh
okay oh yes oh angry dog oh they're
coming oh very angry dog oh jeez doggy
oh
doggy dog my hammer is toig there a wolf
uh-oh
holy those guys are really hard to fight
takes so
my are
really wolves are really hard to beat oh
God difficulty Spike it's because it
might have been a random wolf no no it's
because we went into the four star
house that the four that the house over
there gave us a great
start those wolves are really really
really hard that's crazy
we those the other day oh
god oh oh my God I need imagine the XP
will get though if we kill I know yeah
Quest failed I I think I can kill it if
where is he if someone distracts it I
can kill it okay oh go he's right
there oh oh oh terrified Terri no no no
no I died on top of
me my leg is
broken oh no
oh is he dead he he dead oh he died did
I not get that exp because I died
immediately oh
no dang it always risking my dang life
for what for nothing for nothing oh he
just some loot
bad meat not the best ammo for you guys
some
chili at least legendary Parts
explosives legendary Parts can I have
those please wait why am I picking these
up uh we already have about three
legendary Parts I just need them to make
the best baseball bat on the
planet oh he dropped legendary Parts yes
not
surprised these next level shotgun
shells enemies are going to be dropping
legendary stuff good to know thank you I
will use them well I will never ask for
legendary Parts again probably until we
start finding a lot of
them thank you did I level up
oh okay so no quest for us as normally
might as well yeah that's rough I have a
point oh
pumpkin oh wait 4:00 a.m. it opens again
oh you want to go back let's go back and
grab go back let's all grab quests from
that Trader so we can like do like four
quests at once yeah that be a good idea
I was going to do this
one I'm getting
upgrades
nice what kind of upgr get upgraded 20%
faster punching
ooh from the bar brawling book oh we're
going the wrong way around around around
I'm almost finished with bats and
shotguns on my skill tree nice
werewolves drop legendary Parts oh is
this a
werewolf oh I guess it was a werewolf I
think it's a Dire Wolf is what chat said
they're called dire
wolves then I would like to see more of
these actually are you kidding me yeah
more
legendary yeah I mean we can we can kill
them you know if you find a good snipe
them St
yeah the best way to get them is like
just stand stand on a car or somewhere
high up and just blast them maybe but
could it be that it only showed up
because we started a tier three Quest
and it spawns due to death oh that's a
tier three Quest cuz it never showed up
before tier four no we were in the we
were in the tier four house like we
walked in the tier four House's
territory and the enemy spawned from the
tier four house I think the house was
tier the the house the house next to us
was like four skull four and a half go
oh that's what you mean oh okay makes
sense
yeah oh wait hold up did you guys finish
all the tier 2 quests did you get a car
no it didn't give us a car car it's lame
I think cars are quite a bit later
probably cuz first maybe Mt bikes yeah
you guys are a bit ahead of me I went to
go help the others yesterday so I think
I only have tier two right now sorry
about that but I'll try and take some
you should a special jobs opening trade
route did you guys get that that is the
next one oh yeah yeah oh is the way okay
well I accepted it yeah you should see
the new Trader in the
map cool have you guys met him yet
nope oh maybe we should go meet him and
then we can do
more clear is oh I chose that Quest
too it's the
stronger infested zombies show up I
think yeah we can go do the clear first
of
course I wonder if Bob will give us a
car I think CI if you want to catch up
to us maybe later fauna starts a farm
and I do some other crafting stuff then
you can I'll run some sol quests okay
sounds good so sounds good I'll do my
best to rush them I'll help you I like
you don't have sure if you got nothing
else to do B you're definitely welcome
for me I'm just I just want to get
experience and level my combat since I'm
focused on killing so and looting houses
looting houses for
Stuff killing is about the only thing
that I can do as well right now though
I'd love to learn to cook a little bit
more got oh here F here's some dirty
one I really like how we get on bikes
it's
just look at
that you throw my trash
away the Grim Reaper that checks out oh
yeah Grim Reaper loves
killing oh the tier frequest are in the
different region oh are they oh should
we go where's
mine do we all have opening trade route
should we go down
yo mine is really far on the uh west
side towards TR
W that home it's like in a part where I
don't even have the map yet it's like to
the left you see
it so far yeah I think me and F took the
same class so we have it in the same
location
yeah um what should we do should we go
do you guys do you guys all have opening
trade route though no okay let's go to
final one first then maybe me and wa you
guys took some tier one missions no I
took a tier two cuz I don't get tier one
clear oh those are old old ones from
Trad I see ah yeah the three direct
quests we can have simultaneously I
guess oh another
hold okay well you guys lead the way
I'll just go where you want to go look
at out we're such nerds
here got we the nerd gang
from we're so strong though yeah they
better not mess with us yeah they won't
be laughing when we punch their faces in
no no no when I bodies full of lead
yeah oh I wonder will she even give me
tiree uh if I don't do my own tier 2
quests but someone else's tier three
quests I I I'm thinking that that won't
count to my uh we can still do your we
can still do your tier 2 Quest just in
case so far it's okay we can head over
there we can do it yeah on our bicycles
yeah of course and then we can all open
the trade route together yeah mm be
nice scariest biker gang so scary
zombies are super fear us women love us
but I got to imagine us on one of those
like cute bicycles with the tassel and
the pink handles and
everything yeah yeah yeah like that how
do you do that x
x yeah we're all ringing the bell yeah
imagine if a ton of zombies come find us
now cuz of the Bell they're all
attracted to the sound of the
Bell oh shoot I don't really know how to
ride this bike properly hold up wa I
just got a lot of exp because I forgot
to turn in my
challenges yeah right I always forget
it's a nice
surprise there's a hole
oh there is a hole
there oh my God enough had enough
bullying
today fortitude and strength away with
you
zombie are you kidding me there's no
way I just I'm running into everything
did I forget how to ride a bike all of a
sudden I think I'm I thought you don't
forget that kind of stuff exactly I
forgot for a second that you're supposed
to use the mouse never mind to steer you
can switch to the other steering to
too
yeah man In fairness though I didn't
learn how to ride a bike until much
later in life me too oh me too oh my God
oh my God ladies I never learned as a
kid I learned later neither I learned as
an adult
this doesn't seem right uh
bye I fell through the world for a
second me too me too me too well we have
the we share our experiences we're so
connected intertwined our Destinies wow
incredible as newbie bike
drivers at least we didn't die though
that's cool yeah o oh I think the server
is
lagging that might be it I see it's left
it's not on me cuz my iceb has been
really bad today too I might drop out
like accidentally here and there uhoh
beeping
ISP yeah be like that all right so rude
in your
bike what a nice little
house oh you guys found it I'm on my way
yeah it's close to where you
are these zombies are crazy the burn
ones pretty strong too that is a nice
house if it was closer to the trader I'd
want to take
it can you imagine living in this kind
of house like just out in the middle of
nowhere no one to bother you and it's
like a nice pretty chill house this is a
very high level we got it we got this I
just realized I think the biu FAA me
gang we never cleared out our inventory
are we all still pretty
full I can hold a couple
things hey really
yeah I can hold a couple things wa let
me let me give you some stuff then um
sure I don't want to throw this away
because everything can be useful uh here
I put some things down oh there's an
upstairs you can go up from the
garage oh there's birds watch out thank
you okay thank you you're
welcome let's kill him
oh
hello I don't know why this game
continuously makes my sound cut off my
disc a
[Music]
strange ooh I hear them I don't see them
yet oh I see them
now rattle them rattle
them hello oh well oh hello oh that's a
big guy nice he's
dead
ah curtain
I need to make it a new hobby to get rid
of the curtains cuz I need those
fragments oh yeah better up beds keep
forgetting M oh beds too yeah ah it
gives me wood and clo and clo
Furniture yeah yeah yeah yeah oh yeah
punch it punch it a big get rid of those
cushions oh oh why my bike huh bike
thank you you're welcome I don't know
why it said bike that was weird he's
dead if you use a wrench you get pipes
and springs too wow
oh
hello oh there's a zombie right behind
us they do Be Here There and Everywhere
Boo this knife is probably you probably
have a better one but I have this knife
oh I'll take a knife
is he dead no he's not he's living it's
on the
floor oh I don't see it kind of Blends
in with the
floor mushroom spores I'm good it's l
the fridge of the fridge did someone put
put a bed roll there is it glitched um
can you yeah can you pick it up I don't
see
it oh thank you we have to break these
spikes
if you break them once they don't hurt
you right spikes just once I don't know
if that really works I don't know must
test it
out well let's try and move through here
I bet there's still some zombies in here
oh you found the easier
way oh there's a hole in the floor
here oh yikes whoo wo wo
wo oh another
one he's dead nope he's not he's still
crawling
oh okay go in
down if you're brave
enough o
tunel secret tunnel ooh get him in the
head rattle him he's still
alive yeah yay oh he dropped loot what'
you drop he dropped a lot of stuff I'm
going to take the baseball mag if you
don't mind and then can I please have
the athletic outfit please yeah sure
everything else is you guys's oh you're
still wearing the Primitive outfit get
whatever you want thanks got to get
fashionable oo I'm looking super
fashionable there's crates here oh that
seems bad oh gosh there zombies in here
W wo wo wo wo oh yikes
don't you where are
you we can take them okay me
through yay we did it sorry we're kind
of late to the party sorry about that no
problem we got
it a bit late oh black dye that seems
like might be kind of nice M wheel for a
bike maybe oh does anybody else want
their their weapon to be have a flaming
tip
that's cool it's pretty useful I think
you can do it with your bat I can give
it to you see you can try you go sure
let's try I dropped it thanks uh let's
see where it is oh thanks let me see
does it really work for bad there's a
bunch of stuff in here a locked chest oh
I have lock pcks ah this let's
see oh never mind I don't have lockpicks
well just time to break it I guess this
is a schematic I can read about
it maybe we can make
it car parts tools D I think I have
these things we can try and make
this we'll make it when we go back to
the
house he's working on
it here we go uh you be working on it
this is why we want to learn lockpicking
I have lock picks oh do you I can I can
do the lockpick thing I think I have
points in that here you go thank
you good
luck 50 gas cans I have 50 gas cans I
have more than
that I I think I'm out of skill points
chat y it work what
let me see we
got boots oh here's bullets for cie
thanks always the shotgun
shells is anyone doing Salvage
tools uh yeah I think I am yeah okay
Salvage tools yeah I have 14 all right
here is this and
vehicle oh thank you I also put some
ammo that's not for me floor ooh thank
you bam bam bam what's
this and we don't need a helicopter we
got propeller hats we flying with these
bad boys
no I I think um if I make the nerd hats
on a on the maximum level they're going
to look even crazier I me right now they
don't look crazy at all yeah but they're
going to have some weird like
construction around it later on that's
cool I want that whole body it's exactly
what I want we got to crouch to get out
of here I
see oh I love
that where was this this was just a
little underground bunker where do we
down door over here I think we might
need to yeah break open a door that just
go back to where we were though I think
so not we tra down here should we build
a ladder or there there must be a way
out has to
be maybe a ladder or something almost
almost
open um oh H it's it goes in the oh no I
go for that that stairs
nice A little silly but more locked
doors we can open
them what happened why did I get hurt
did I hit you there's no way uh it might
be a way
you know I also accidentally hid people
a lot let me let me see if I can
activate this same if I hit you your
health will be much much
lower it's good co is the same Quest
yeah
easy same Quest oh then we can't do it
right away do it right now it's
available in 30
seconds okay okay yeah you missed ke
already our way around Miss some keys
they had some keys for us well oh well
you know we're a bit Savage we take
things into our own hands yeah Kelly do
still have some space I think so wait
let me see I'm holding some useless
items like u i don't use these so are
you sure it's useless yeah it's just
some 50 bones I'll take the bones cuz I
think I had a stack no I didn't have no
the bones is what I gave to you oh you
gave me the bones okay I'll hold on for
you does anybody have any small stones
yes I do
oh yeah you can
take thank you what are you
making I'm going to cook some potatoes
with the
stones yeah Stone potato rock potato you
need bones to make glue and Tu glue you
glue out of Bones yes but you need water
which is the issue we don't have a good
supply of fresh water
yeah I
see but yeah everything's
even the things that might seem useless
we got to collect it all I I I mean the
only thing I don't really know is what
Rotting Flesh would be good for besides
getting us sick true oh it's for farming
oh okay there you go see everything
everything's
useful does anybody need some food right
now I'm good think I'm okay I have one
can of
chili I have a lot of money I probably
should use it yeah I've been buying food
at the Traer
okay I'm going to start it
now okay it has
started what what that would
happen what what ited
my
potato no maybe we'll come back when the
quest Quest is finished I don't
know
no Bye Bird than drop
hey it gave me more potato car if you
want to try it
again oh my God it's so noisy up
there it's
[Music]
gone well now we know yeah now we know
man I purposely put it on the like the
lawn I thought it would be far enough no
that's still apparently part of
area that's okay
sad you learned a
lesson can't figure out where the next
area to go is is it
oh go down this way it's up
here oh yeah I'm over here trying to
break
wires uh you can just come up here and
there's a way down you don't have to
break the wires nice upstairs no but
next to you come back hello hello I
thought that was a weird mattress or
something what the heck
oh yeah you get job down
smart
sorry might be right next you took all
of my health away all right let me give
you a kit let me give you a med
kit oh no wait oh he scared me I hit
anything with the bat all right hold up
I got a med
kit I don't I don't have one I have a
kit it's okay I have one I have one okay
sorry two hits
baby one hit gone now I may have given
it to somebody else that I
smacked oh there's a lot found armor
parts nice and Raider boots
Sal iron too wow everything's useful got
to destroyed this whole
house G's going to wreck the whole house
now we're thinking like
apocalypse survivors hello it's an enemy
right okay yeah that's an
enemy I have to D the
hats I really got to make sure it's an
enemy yeah look for the propeller hats
it's the main thing means
friends yes I know how you guys got in
there do you go friends
ouch
uhoh I fell down the hole oh everyone's
here ah I finished again yay
y there's a lot of stuff in this room
again and more loot again I think how to
get
out oh
well oh I got ammo bag
got some kaha ammo Planet the
hunter well I'm cucumber but these
things look good yeah me
too see I'm going to wear my Raider
boots what out make sure to get all the
good stuff girls
yep loot loot you know
it oh just kidding this is much better
than the Raider boots wait can I wear
the Raider boots of course you can for
you you almost have a full set then or
do you already I think I need the gloves
the gloves I'm making for my primitive
armor is better than the the athletic
outfit really a little Health bonus oh
you made a pretty high level one
primitive outfit yeah it's level four I
see we'll make you something else at
level four when you give me armor kids
okay well I found armor parts so I'm
adding them okay I am totally cucumber
but I have stuff people
um I'm outside but yeah after this Quest
maybe we go back to our house first yeah
get rid of stuff and
then maybe we can do the wa wa quest
that's really far away yeah did I read
this
already you
already oh
n apparently apparently I I learned
water
purification I don't know what that
means that's
bigo
yeah make the Clean Water right yeah I
don't know what that means but I think
that's good for us probably can you not
make it before no it's a diff it's a
book that I haven't read before so I
don't know it
means we love pure
water we
do oh I can I can create pure mineral
water pure mineral water is different
that different I guess so
so water
game f why you walking so slow I'm so
encumbered she's being deliberate oh
okay it looks like maybe you also need
to go an ID meeting really
urgently water from Rock yeah level two
water or is that better water oh I guess
so yeah it's it's bottled pure water so
I guess yeah we need we need hold on we
need water coal Golden Rod flour and
crysanthemum for it that's kind
expensive we only need one of each
though
let's head back shall we Quest first
yeah first to the trader then home and
then after a while maybe I mean I can do
that Quest also alone probably but maybe
with c yeah we got to open that Trader
at some point
too yeah oh it cures diarrhea and gives
you stamina regen so it's good water
pretty good
water
nice almost at beast mode oh yeah we get
a mini bike next I think is what I found
out M so we want to definitely want to
get want to meet Trader Bob and do some
quests does he give it to us or do we
have to make it I think you have to do a
bunch of tier three
quests and then he'll give it to you I
he gives it to us and there's no point
in making one my we got parts or some of
us got Parts
yeah want a mini bike also apparently
the water good because it quenches 60
for 60 thirst so it's a lot more maybe
they say you get a box for some mini
bike parts oh and then you could craft
it if you have the skill it seems like I
do have the skill for it so I'll be
making mini bikes it seems I didn't get
many bike parts did I miss it I think
you took the nail gun right a oh I guess
we have a lot of cards a lot of cards
true enough you got to decide what you
want I'll keep that in mind I'll get the
gun is
nice that's a nice
weapon help people do lots of that water
it is the best water source in the game
oh okay nothing compares to water
straight from the pond true right it
feels so wild drink as much as you want
I like to if we can get a if we can get
a flower farm
we we're good with everything else we
need we need Golden Rod and [\h__\h] that's
it and
[Music]
cor the hard part oh wait did I go too
far but the chrysanthemums and Golden
Rod they grow a lot in the wild where we
used to live yeah mhm oh honestly I
think we have some seeds anyway for that
we can plant it when fauna gets faring a
bunch of them fauna stays true to her
name after all makes us some flowers and
stuff to work with the plant
[Music]
in I've started to remember the road f i
i don't need to check the map I know
which road you go to the right Road not
left follow
you you turn it the creamery that's what
I remember people said thats really good
does did anybody get and learn uh the
Sham way secret recipe before I did okay
good cuz apparently that's the one of
the best foods in the game wait but if
it for example sham sandwich that'll
give you that's different that's
different is sham just bad or I
mean oh apparently is it what is sham
you use the rotten flesh for that oh
good really we're eating rotten flashh
that's why it's a secret recipe they
don't want you to know it's
[Music]
zombies yeah it's zombie meat zombie
human meat oh
yucky guess I'll get these I think it's
off brand spam maybe oh well I'm
dropping a book for two books for you I
have a
book well interesting I'm she she wants
me to she gives me like a nail gun
potentially but there's no optional like
mini bike parts yeah that's what I got
that's what she did for me
too maybe that's
separate maybe the mini bike parts are
at the next Quest person like not her
but someone else does someone like rifle
world uh shotgun AP slug ammo maybe I
should get this one guys can I use this
with my
shotgun are these the the good rounds ah
I got the opening trade routes nice we
should that we should go home my yeah oh
yes yeah
penetration yeah vehicle expanded
seating mod schematic ooh will this work
for bikes I bet it will should I spend
$2,000 on
this sure for the truck Quest
clear super rare I'm dropping a book for
you f now ventory ma'am oh thank you
need a couple first aid
bandages got a lot of money oh shotgun
weekly stim pack there three did she
just say all these did she just do a
Fallout reference or stim pack an actual
IRL thing D Pack's a thing yeah it's
real
[Music]
a see what else but maybe that was still
a reference cuz she's like oh we still
on half stim packs go somewhere else
ntim packs are in Warhammer
too the way she says it for the emperor
for the
emper very excited about that buy as
much as I
can player vending machine oh wait
something you have to
learn a player vending machine that's
awesome I want to sell things to people
can you do that yes player vending
machine 6,000
6,000 do you think that will be worth it
will we buy stuff no we already give
things free to each other yeah we we're
a we're a good Society we share
everything we help each other fre for
free we in a different
world I have to go to meeting I'll be
right back okay have
fun see you ooh sought off shotgun mod
I'll buy
that ah yes trad's got what um there you
go thank you make things go boom make me
proud I will that was really fun when
you were throwing Kaboom things around
in the last is really
strong so I'm I hope uh before the next
rate I'll just make a bunch of
explosives and I'll
help sounds good what is
this nice double barrel shotgun quality
3 we can make make a stronger
shotgun uh that was this work with my
fire sledg him
there well I didn't realize yesterday
that you had to hold the left button to
throw it farther but now I know how to
throw it so it'll be less of an
issue yeah it did always go pretty close
huh yeah apparently you just you can't
tap the button you just got to hold it
to throw it fire but now I
know okay
all right I'm going back to to our house
new house okay sounds good and I'll
probably do some sorting and try to make
the Bellow and then um I might need some
help uh as well with making uh well
maybe I can I can make the baseball bat
don't worry about it uh yeah I I think
like weapons I don't know if I'm like
specialized in making weapons it's
mostly armor yeah but if you need like
for the baseball bat if you need any
iron or so you can take it from the
forge okay I'll let you know let me know
Chad if I'm wrong if I should make her
bat I don't
know I'm back I I can make level three
bats as the thing so maybe I should
focus on
that thing for you to learn oh the the
expanded seating for vehicles is like a
recipe okay you want to give it to me
now or at home yeah I'll give it to now
okay since you're the vehicle master I'm
seemingly the master of so many things I
feel the
pressure you I want to make sure I'm
here every day so that I can be of
use I
know I'm very committed to this now me
too what's this stuff on the
ground it's nice to have a handful of us
who are like strong so we can
car yeah we feel that
responsibility yeah we're strong and we
can carry but we are directionally
challenged yeah no I had no clue where
we're going are we going the right way
to the yes whoever whoever's in front is
going the right way good we can go
figure out the trader uh later on the
new Trader yeah yeah I want to take some
time at home to just figure out some
crafting stuff yeah I want to try to
Farm a bit okay so little Quest break
yes
yeah might do a quest solo though so I
can catch
up
Bike
World Oh no you're fine I thought all of
our bikes were going through the world
again or something no that was pretty
funny that was a blonding moment oh I
think everyone's
Frozen oh really uhoh server lag uhoh oh
yeah looks Frozen to me too I
just Road P okay I'm going into the
ground now okay I think it
refreshed yeah we hadn't seen a ton of
server lag in the beginning but now it's
kind of starting to pop off a little bit
more yeah I wonder I wonder why like
there's fewer people playing so you
would think it wouldn't
be is there such a thing as like a just
like a reset for the server I me
everyone's P seems
okay oh
is it because we're like exploring new
areas I don't
know they're saying new chunks I'm
excited to see what the new trador area
is like is itnow Desert like desolated
snow snow well it looks yellow from from
the little prev at the bottom it looks
yellow the swamp the
swamp could be this area is a little
ressing yeah I'm tired
this but Trader Jen is there and she's
so cute true only hers place is good but
I'm tired of everywhere else
yeah yeah even though I haven't been in
that area for that much in not long but
I feel sauron's gaze when I'm there and
I the I
see yeah he's watching all of us every
single step
no I'm
home good thing we have twoes who's
going to fill all those trees when gigg
is not here no where's where's our our
gig our Beaver wife Beav husband
Krypton repair kit is iron and duct tape
I need to make some repair
kits oh yeah me too
soon is there any duck tape around we
can make some uh I have one yeah I'll
just drop one for you
thanks thank you thank you need more
cloth
fragments ahuh okay oh there's two
farming books in our
house oh I'll read
them any cooking by chance sure let's
get some stuff started now we have two
cook books in here today yeah I think
we'll all have always have two cuz we're
always here yeah we just need
ingredients iron where did my iron go if
I can use the iron I'm going to help
myself to some of the
iron
ahead okay I'm just going to grill a lot
of meat cuz I feel like we have
plentiful of that it's
true wish we had more eggs so I know
oh I think I collected some on uh on my
way outside would be good some raw eggs
nice can always use more
food so you can make forged Iron by
putting regular iron that's like in your
inventory into the forge yes yeah it's
cool as long as the fires are
lit nice okay
yeah they already how many do you need
um oh I'm just throwing them in there I
just have so much random iron in my
pockets that I just threw it in there in
this melting oh kiaha you should read
this too I
think okay unless you already have read
it oh I might have already read
it oh no I guess I
didn't all right or duct
tape should I hold on to my own Iron
parts or should I contribute them make
it a like Community thing we can we can
make it a community cuz I'm just I've
just been putting my iron there
everybody needs yeah iron thingies so we
can just armor
parts uh I I just like when you put iron
in there you still have to go into the
menu of the forge and then um click
forged iron and then craft them it
doesn't happen automatically but I just
put a 100 pieces of iron uh forged iron
into the queue so now it's cooking
up but yeah any any leftover uh forged
iron can of course be free to use
there's some in the chest right next to
the forge C okay thank you need to
remake my bat so I'm just going to take
one duct tape need more clay
control oh where's the
clay need
iron craft wrench
why and leather I need leather tooly
clay clay clay clay
clay how to make
clay you have leather right there I have
I I dropped some off I think we we have
we have
some ah uh how many you need um I think
for my bat hold on just a moment I want
to make a baseball bat um hold up if I
want to be level two I need one leather
okay I put some back into the chest
thank you what was I doing 30 forged
iron that's so
much well I'm I'm cooking a lot of
there's a lot that's cooking right now
yeah yeah I
put's just need more
iron I can make vegetable
stew good
yes
yes smelt the clay
really
okay do I have to pumpkin
bread wa I'm going to try and make that
tip that fiery
tip wait I have one you don't need to
make it I have one in my oh really like
I have the actual mod not the schematic
hold on T the the though okay I leave it
to
you I don't know if it's worth using
beer to make pumpkin
cheesecake wait is that really something
you have to
do I think you should keep it to to use
it for your drunken fist I think that
would be more
beneficial I can make pumpkin pie with
no beer
I'll make two pumpkin
pies yum
yum me disassemble my
bat
oh there we go uh I'm oh yeah I want to
try making the good
water oh
yeah uh we need the good
water Golden Rod flow
for iron mind if I take this for iron oh
we have so much yeah take it thank you
I'm crafting a lot right now do we have
also
coal oh we did at one point oh we do we
have a lot okay I can actually make
quite a few if I have plain water I just
made an item that makes our Forge 50%
faster oh y
yeah can I put it in oh do I need to
make a better Forge to use this turn off
the forge ah ah okay
okay 50% faster let's go wo nice we'll
be zooming Kelly what are you waiting
for right now more more
iron um I'm waiting for my bat to be
made oh okay okay just going to take a
couple
minutes fany to much
faster fancy
toilet you maybe when we get to the new
area where Bob is we can get a mansion
o I want a
mansion but this base is really solid
with the forge and everything oh wait
sham is is made of horrible ingredients
what's a made out of I don't think I
want to tell you the rotten
flesh that's one component is it also
made of like dirty water well
no murky water maybe you got to tell us
the truth rip the band it's made of
Bones animal fat and Rotting Flesh
wow SS I make a ton of it I can make
yeah make it make it what we what it
takes to survive
a maybe the virus or something I don't
know maybe maybe if we you know eat the
parts of the zombies we'll grow more and
more immune kind of like a vaccine sort
of thing oh true how the infection in
our
bodies yeah I can see where you're
cooking see Le put it
back can put my magazines so many nerd
magazines we don't have anybody learning
robotics though oh I'm learning it oh
really why I put some there oh thank you
cuz nobody else was learning it so I
thought yeah nobody wants to do the nerd
stuff but if you want to do the nerd
stuff go for it I'm a nerd at
heart yeah go for
it my armor level is at 89 out of 100 oh
my gosh wow that's crazy soon make the
level seven the maximum level armor wow
you're going to have to help us all out
with that yeah but all for all of that
first of all I I will need more armor
kits and legendary armor parts oh yeah
that is true so it won't be that easy
legendary armor
parts I want to make the maximum
baseball bat with the legendary okay
molotovs aren't that bad to make I
should make some Molotov those are
nice oh and pipe bombs are bad to make
too okay that's
good here's my baseball bat okay
modify oh yeah soul faithful wait that
was already level three what there's the
die
oh
well oh wait that not mine oh that's not
mine okay
I my okay it's fine baseball bat check
it this one level two
baby this is exciting oh my gosh I can't
wait to kill more people I mean to help
my friends and get strong yeah yeah
pmel Pete wants took on 50 zombies with
just a club and he would be proud of you
clubs deal 50% more damage attacks do
200% more damage to stun enemies power
Texs have 100% chance to knock foes back
down this is
big oh that's going to be big I want
that what should I do next
[Music]
guys um yeah I may need to run a little
bit a few quests on my own I am game
stage 44 you guys are
49 oh so I'm going to go do
Quest but let me know and you guys want
to go to the new Trader okay okay
okay for what mechanic
parts wrench for what what do you use
the rench for cars maybe
I wish the new Trader was a cute girl
but his name is Bob he might be cute
yeah Bob might be cute you never know
yeah but when I think of Bob I think of
like a trucker you know hopefully he's
nicer than trador though he's got to be
right he's got to be Sonic car to take
them
apart
there breaking down anything like elic
or mechanical okay did anyone take the
cloth part oh yeah for a moment uh but
I'm putting the them into the chest next
to the forge
[Music]
okay
um oh here I have a schematic for you
you can craft
headlights for
cars okay if somebody wants a headlight
for their car
car will be useful does anyone have a
car
yet in the fut great when we get
one ah on the microwave anything
Elric I just don't think Trader Bob's
going to be a cute trucker that's all
I'm
saying the the if you need the cloth
fragments they're back in the Forge
chest okay
thank
you got to make some
explosives four grip mod
schematic yeah we can all get in a car
and go to missions
together it sounds like
fun road trip with a car it might not be
so problematic anymore if our house is
very far from the trader or
so that would be great craft this item
can't wait to throw Molotov out the
window of the
car
violence always go to
violence I was going
to you guys said I had this grip yeah
for the
sledgehammer is getting a little late
is there a better version of this chat
that I already
know let me
know
gosh every time every time sure I just
want to hear my friends voices in the
background while I Traverse the the pl
Grant you courage thanks Big Ups the
courage if anyone has handgun parts
please give them to me I feel like
there's some in the old house hand Parts
yeah there's uh in the in the armor
chest oh
desert armor uh armor ammo in the new
house oh
okay don't think any that going to get
rid of
it pretty cool I can make a magnum gun
now
who hit by a cactus
quick before you start getting
fast I'm going to try to make another D
collector but I don't know if there's a
better way to collect water um so what I
assume is there are mods to mod the DU
collector on the right side if you look
at the Duke collector you can buy those
from the Traders um so might want to
stop by the trader and see if they're
selling any of
these I see things that helping I good
to have more anyway though but I will
see about
mods so long you did drop a lot of stuff
though oh we have forg steel that's big
put the stock on your rifle the stock ah
I'm getting so
strong I'm going to steal these people's
curtains are you raiding houses yeah
just a little bit just a little house
raid killing time huh need some need
some cloth you know mhm wait for stuff
to cook
oh they all came back to
life glue as well I mean now we have a
good amount of cloth lying around but
glue yeah do we still the bird we have
34 glue in the that's pretty good yeah
I'm going to make some duct tape at it
though if that's okay M yeah I think has
the best use for
it oh hor is
good okay do not stand on the
forge oh did you catch on fire
yeah they've got a
peleton wow fancy I know they are fancy
at the
Harrison motor tool parts that could be
good oh hello oh hello I need something
to
drink you
dead no drink there's some coffee I
think yeah I just want to drink pure
water I'm going to go to where you are
cuz you're by the
water just drink the coffee or the fancy
water and the bi boo m
uh no that's a waste you're literally by
the water I'm going to go to you okay
okay where there uhoh that's
bad some
water there's a lot of them oh that's a
lot of
zombos byebye oh God that's bad that's
very bad and what are you doing Kelly do
you die don't die no I'm alive I'm alive
oh
Jesus oh he threw up on me I might die
after oh it's the vomit guy that's not
good dang I was feeling so cool Bo Ste
I'm going to die eat the vegetable eat
the vegetable eat the vegetable no
no dang I thought that they would make
the zombie number go down a little bit
maybe for
me were you trying to solo a quest huh
yeah I wanted to solo a quest I got
pretty close I wonder if it's cuz you're
in our party the level I don't but
you're the only one who started it right
so
yeah can you make steel I had a really
cool moment though um uh possibly I need
to check when I'm at the Fort I guess
but uh Quest I can do it my bat's very
strong oh hello hello sir oh yeah I mean
it's just um Iron and Clay if you can
make about 40 steel for me I would be in
your
deck y when I'm home I'll turn into the
queue F where are you I'm B water I'm by
the pool by the pool oh we're drinking
pool water it's extra
delicious I might as well finish getting
loot did lure all the zombies out so
I'll probably just loot the house and
leave oh
nice yeah getting a wrench was a good
idea
ohw pool
party
yeah hat
please and I'm going to go down to
the Traer the new one smells like fauna
wait we should go together to the new
one okay you want are you guys ready to
kind of go I want to go okay yeah I
broke my lock pick second back to the
house one more time to put the stuff in
the queue thank you guess I got to do
this the hard
way Zip Zip Zip Zip Zip okay we got it
that's enough thank you so much I
appreciate it let me we got so close to
unlocking it is this going to explode oh
oh dog dog dog oh dog
alarm Okay fa will take care of it
it
didn't
yeah it
didn't yeah have loog picks I wonder if
I can make loog
fix I think generally brute forcing
things open is the way to go I had
enough though I almost had enough I one
short well let me wrench the thrilling
game play Chief
thrilling ooh ooh wrenching a car gives
a lot of good material it does do you
have a wrench too F you I do
oh I found one really early me oh really
I made one level three
wrench no
ladder there we go o feels like
Minecraft now we're almost halfway there
wait can you ask the bird nest for eggs
thing for eggs can't you just open it
normally well they don't always have
eggs oh that takes maybe you can smack
them
shooting nope doesn't work well maybe it
does my b
o x does more per
second watch loot be
terrible okay I'm coming home again okay
I'm just looting some houses nearby
while I wait for you
guys
[Music]
okay
um I wonder if it's still worth it at
this point to do the tier 2 Quest at all
or the one that I have or should I just
I think maybe we should just do the tier
three I think it's worth it if we keep
just yeah let's definitely do it in a
group though yeah I feel like we can
steamroll if we're in a group but uh one
by one's a little difficult at least for
[Music]
more yeah we really need more water yeah
we should it these days yeah next time
next time I see the mod or the the tools
for the to help the things go faster
I'll buy them yeah I'll just look
to
uh wait what's Crucible
required do I need ah don't need this do
I need
this what is
this the thing under Steel
oh that's called a Cru Oh I thought it
it meant I need something Cru Crucible
isn't that a word crucial oh crucial
crucial I need I I can't make forged
steel yet because I need my workstation
level to be higher oh okay by quite a
bit so it's going to take a while
still almost got it Lads dink dink
dink I will just just look for Forge
Steel in the field then hopefully yeah
or quest uh reward could give it
too but no Repair Kit Repair Kit won't
work on
this on
what on my axe oh it
should whoa what's this music so
ominous when's the
next R ra raid zombie ra 28 28
probably okay still got
time how long do we want to play today 4
hours
again Hit The Sweet Spot with the 4
hours okay it's probably fine just need
to keep our eyes on the day so that we
know you know what the 28th is the next
Rush right I feel like if we play for 4
hours it'll be right about there at that
time so we'll do it probably need to do
another
one well then uh I don't know maybe
until ingame
Day
26 or so
nice yeah maybe that'll be
good all right I guess I'll head
towards
the trader Quest open
I will also go that
[Music]
way I can buy the 15K oh maybe I
will for small stones H is it always at
the
trader if we get some uh how much money
15,000 that's a lot of money I'll need
to get some donations from the others
too 15,000 for what what you me The
Crucible if I buy The Crucible I can
make the steal way earlier I have
8K 8K I have like 9k but that's my like
all of my
money if we put a few KS together we can
I've got buy the
Cru think I have some money as well
paper cash
here I'm actually really close to the
new Trader uhoh okay well I'll take my
money if the trader sells crucibles I'll
buy it with some combined money is that
how you make a car no uh maybe as well
indirectly but with The Crucible I can
make for steel Forge steel is probably
the higher tier of weapons like the next
I also found some Forge Steel by the way
in my ratings oh I would like
please okay what's a good path towards
the new
Trader well maybe that way um just come
where I am it's in the desert yeah but I
don't see the roads on the map because
they're uncovered not not
uncovered I'll find my way Crucible um
what I'm doing is I'm going to go to the
path to trer Jen and go past the road
there that's what it seems like it's
pointing
towards
okay
Anvil oh Anvil I can make soon four more
workstation magazines I feel like I
haven't read a workstation magazine in a
while yeah they seem rare
mhm
oh excuse me I'm bringing a bunch of
food I can't hold any more I can't hold
anymore I canot hold any smart bring the
food well I'm cooking a ton of
spam
spam we'll have lots of spam he what
about the Sham way stuff sham I mean ah
okay
yummy hey I want to see how much better
that is other food I don't think it's
better I think it's just cheaper so you
can make more of why is Trader Bob not
friendly oh he's
mean yes scho showed up when I got to
his house
huh what's wrong Trader Bob you don't
like us is it because he's
closed I wonder oh he might be closed
it's like 2:00 a.m. let's ride together
okay maybe I'll just kill a bunch of
rando zombies to level up that might be
helpful stay dangerous to go alone for
it's dangerous to go alone take this
oh need to focus on repairing my axe
right now
Bob
Bobby goodbye jenma we don't need you
anymore
no we always need you speak for
yourself yeah do I do really need her
but she wants me to move on so I guess
I'll move
on quite
literally I finally am being pushed to
move on to a new manager did you girls
know after all these years with
jenma oh yeah fin you piing the same
they're
empty no restock restock
but good
thinking very important always have to
check yeah those are the the best spots
for magazine oh it is a desert
area not the swamp no it's not a swamp
[Music]
unfortunately juice what is
that oil shale Gemma will be
remembered she's still still doing a
little bit of stuff for me but mostly
it's PMA now I have named my new manager
PMA yes because she's pretty pawn p and
yeah very Pawn she's cute though who dog
oh it's a
fox e wait I'm scared the new area
surely there will be more werewolves and
stuff running around oh God steal their
part oh yeah there's a lot of scary
stuff
here be careful
ke Kelly stay
hidden hang on I'm always there
no please don't die come on I'll be fine
I'll be fine it's just a bird where's
the
bird sick of these birds and then I'm
walking into the spikes oh god uhoh oh
there are dogs bird comes out when I put
my Bat Away
awesome the music is getting scary too
I'm going to
die not bleeding anymore I'll be okay oh
no I won't the sky is red yeah I
suffered a concussion I'm almost there
please please oh we were riding for the
night if we came earlier the the Bob
probably wouldn't even be open but now
is perfect
time yeah I like this kind it's pretty
yeah wo wo I heard I heard a woof woof
woof that's rough buddy these cactuses
by the way the cactus do not play
around okay I won't punch
them though I want
to yeah that place looks like it would
have laser s mod or yeah I guess like
antibiotics and stuff just lying around
look good I got a laser sight mod by the
way can I have it oh
yeah laser sight
here you go wow oh the sunrise here is
beautiful
than what are you doing desert after all
getting more spam
ingredients you should open
soon all right I I'll also keep an eye
out for spam ingredients
advertising
wo he sounds friendly
enough he says they've got sales show me
the sails Bob are the
Rings what is
this no
uhoh uhoh I'll get one of these where my
bike
what's he doesn't respect the AFK yeah
dang it I was looking at my
inventory he does have forged steel so
that's
nice what oh I like the music here doggy
it's chill right mhm not a lot of really
good healing stuff let me
get oh they don't like fire they run
away when they're
on a little more water chicken
soup whoa oh did you DC
oh
oh I bet your nose is so high in the air
you can drown in the rain what else they
got can you hear me yeah uh you went
like cut off a little bit yeah I'm dying
my in is dying oh no
I'll be back okay got
magazine oh thank you uhoh doesn't look
like there's anything for the forge
though
sadly I wish it's not selling the what
was it um there the
sea
no oh these are for
[Music]
you thank you he's actually super nice
bu supplies restore power night only oo
night only quests yeah those seem
fun
hello
hello why don't you take a look for
yourself oh did you get the buried Quest
too
fauna uh I don't think so I think I got
a clear Quest oh okay okay infestation
Quest nice I got a buried a buried
treasure dang it I can make quality 3
but I just made a quality to baseball
bat um I got a digging Quest if anyone
wants to dig a hole together sure yeah
could be
fun A Little
Cucumber I love digging holes with my
friends yes clo can I just take his
stuff did you take it
yeah oh my gosh I don't think he seems
cool with it
hello hello hello we can hear
you please hold on to my
hands otherwise the void will suck me in
again I don't have I don't have much
room in my inventory but he is selling
the stuff for water collection oh I can
buy
maybe
exp can make some room I could probably
give some money too if if need be oh do
you have the steel Callie yeah hold on
here's five forged steel oh thank you
hopefully it'll help you out that helps
a
lot my chat's still not Reviving hello
rise way H they're so
dead chat where are you I'm alone
robotic drone medic mod o that sounds
good flying field medic
what I can't afford it it sounds good
though it does sound good I don't think
I'm at that point yet
yet by the way there's a lead car
battery
here I see you Let me refresh this if we
do end up making a car you want vehicles
more
parts there we go Kiara wants
hammers yes hammers hammers okay I'll
hold station
magazines nice okay I will will be back
in the game in a
moment we will await you with
anticipation yes he has an anvil he's
selling an anvil but I could make one if
I get threee more work oh so you have to
you can have a drone and then you can
put this mod in the Drone yeah but I'm
not close at all I need a robotics level
76 and I have 13 so oh 76 wow
yeah
course I feel like a
Bano on
me
show Quest too why do you mean Quest
failed oh because I'm not in the party
you for work oh yeah I got to get you
back in the
party one of you is the leader now
someone's got to be I'm not the
leader bi's the leader make sure you
invite
gaha
work die
die I receiv received the party invite
all right but there's so many monsters
out
here get inside I'm
coming I like how they respect the
boundaries of this place because they
don't walk into the very widely opened
doors oh this music that's playing
hellad over
here let me check the guys
watch where is he egg I found
egg can you break it and get more eggs
try it big Central
Area I heard
that ah oh I missed wow yeah talk to him
he's nice he's not like wrecked that guy
sucks
oh that potato looks like a rockster I'm
not taking
that it's a baked potato though isn't it
re there's a restore power night only
Quest interesting sounds too complicated
yeah it's not night I took a buried
treasure Quest though I have a shovel I
just took a clear Quest did anybody take
an infested clear Quest I think I did uh
oh hello um I'll take a clear
maybe
oink oh he is selling Forge steel if you
really if you really
but I think I'll just wait and see if we
need stones small stones we can just
loot it
somewh yeah for
sure would you guys like
food I would always like food fauna okay
I've got lots of food I would always
like food come come get some okay could
buy this after I pick up my last Stone
I'll come get some food
one more Stone have I learned
this now I can make a
shovel okay Chow Time what's for dinner
fauna how about some meat stew ooh that
sounds good wait w of meat is it it's
pork I think or maybe deer or maybe
something yummy it's not
zombies you promise I promise ion if
it's okay promise closed if it's closed
I didn't learn it yet
okay me stew and grilled meat wow thank
you so much I do love I do love some yum
yums we hold on to
these I'm holding a lot of stuff though
you have
bandages have a bandage do not but I
will take a
bandage I'm very cucumber does anybody
want R REM some stuff do you have any
cloth or fat or bones oh I have cloth
please carry my
cloth oh I have an extra bone bone knife
sword
thingy this oil we have plenty of oil
back at the
house if someone wants to car the oil
you can carry it
I'm ready
oh our quests are kind of all over the
place oh okay thank you oh thank you
take this oh thank
you magazines oh nice you need to for
the quest shall we start with the ones
that are towards the north okay there's
so bioo CI and mine yes
okay kiaha you want you want to start go
furthest uh away so kiaha is first first
and then Callie's and then mine okay you
will read this here you go you will read
this you will read it are you learning
wiring fauna robotics yes I am here you
go that's for you thank you you're
welcome oh wait let me wrench this
thing all right F let's rench it
together
okay yeah that's how you collect the car
stuff huh yeah
crunches why are you hitting it
hold that's not how you use a wrench it
worked why do you use it differently
that's weird does it not
work different technique it still
works shall we go to um Mor's digging
Quest or we're g to go to Kias and then
work our way to the right sounds good I
follow Kiara
really far away I'm sorry about that
that's okay that's fine I actually have
two tier three
clears oh oh one from one is pretty far
too we love quest in quest more Quest
than marrier and I brought a cooking pot
and Grill so ni hopefully we can have
some snacks maybe just keep it away from
the lawn keep it from far from the house
Z yes I wonder if we can just go
straight this
way do cacti carry water they should
like irel they do right yeah wonder if
we break the cacti if it gives us water
probably not that's a big Factory I only
got fiber from it
sadly spam ingredients yummy yummy C m i
dinner can't wait for for tonight's
Ste yeah ah they drop Yuka fruit I guess
when you smack them nice oh here's some
more
dinner no not roadkill not again please
the chefs are
crazy our chefs are insane making us eat
roadkill it's the only way remember how
hungry you've been this will cure our
hunger oh you go found an actual street
that leads the right way I went for the
Wasteland like I didn't even take a
street W this is this is the max amount
of skulls this is like fall oh my God is
this our Quest no no no it's not a quest
yeah this is where they're making the
Sham they're dogs be careful they dogs
outside look more more more
food I a little scary here though I feel
like we should keep
driving really strong zombies here
there's lots of food
everywhere bye-bye
zombie this is the real Fallout right
here yeah doesn't give me Fallout Vibes
that much you don't think so I don't
know not the desert gave me Fallout
Vibes the desert this gives me um a dog
dog that game where the Wawa and the
iris and the gobaa is in in the game now
oh EDF yeah EDF part I'm looking at
right now gives me id fud oh yeah I see
what you're talking about yeah someone
said be careful for landmines and now
there's a bear scared there's a bear
land yeah landmines it could be honestly
I've heard there there's like traps the
further you get in I have a perk where
if I step on it I don't activate wait it
till I'm not scared
nice this area pops off at night though
okay I have
arrived more or
less let's see how strong the enemies
are oh she's excited to see
me zombies are strangely fast here you
check these these newspapers you guys I
was about to you guys scared
me o it's kind of a high level Place yay
find something good I found more more
handgun Parts I need like so
many I wonder what's for
dinner sorry stop right there lady I
need to stop you right there we need to
talk about your bicycle riding skills
you're
endangering around you hot lady want
out is she back hot lady
[Music]
back
no okay should I start the quest she
flew ready all right here we go ready
let's do
it we got this ladies
oh green that rad mod might actually be
good to use here not Li insted it I
installed something oh gosh that's
oh
she's when your friends start oh he's
not dead and there's a bird and inside
there's a
bird boom head shot oh they really want
fauna understand the bathroom uhoh I
hear oh there he
is
nice he's dead I'm going to check the
toilets for Faun oh yes there is water
here
I brought the P so we can all drink
water
nice yeah the toilet
are there's a lot of axe in here he's
very very very infected oh God he's oh
God the Hulk is here people the
hul there's so much action we got him no
you didn't he's still alive he's still
alive
oh gosh some green
ones oh oh Father you here
God there's some fake fauna cosplayers
trying to give me hugs fauna the green
ones the new green ones but I can tell
them apart I know who's the real
one yeah you know my hair is kind of
this exact
color yeah game oh nice open the H I
have ever
seen I got him really
quick ooh do we have H what's that we
could head
catches might be
upstairs yep my catch is
upstairs oh we're looking for supplies
huh oh yeah oh you we are Tak a
while it is really dark in here I'll go
inside oh are we stuck
outside oh we might have to forcefully
open the door go around bash his head in
I'm going to follow fa I'm going all the
way
around let's just try to not exit the
boundaries
hello oh gosh wait there's scary people
out here how do I get to the other side
found my satchel
H ooh I need to repair this
soon oh watch out this GL where from oh
dear where is that it lit up in here
even though it's not here don't worry I
turned away right at the right at the
last
moment there's a thing oh here he is
hello hello ladies how did you guys get
deeper in
I unlocked a door it's it's it's an
alien oh God
Al God could be oh are they fighting
each other oh each
other y this is not the place to be a KN
you seem
strong wonder if you guys found your way
up here oh nice they found their way oh
no just kidding that's
B why is there there's so many spawning
well I feel like ah for here maybe for
the toilet stuff is there a door oh I
see there must be like a go around I
guess it's less fun I like breaking
through I I'm
scared you have to buy stuff from the
vending machines here can we just break
it yeah who's who's buying stuff from
here better stay with FAA
I'm
looting maybe now it's not the time but
it's always the time on it it's always
the time to
loot uh-oh will they spawn endlessly
until we find our loot no clear area is
a condition so I feel like okay oh
there's so many watch out wait come back
downstairs come back downstairs oh okay
they're outside they're they're outside
the door okay they're all stacked on
each other
ew
uh-oh yeah yeah nice good one bi boo
okay the area is still not clear though
still not clear what okay don't try
to don't try to wrench the vending
machine it gave me an electric shock
silly my goodness you know I was I was
going to try to do that too you know I'm
not giving up on this door I did it for
you it's so um there's some behind this
door I'm telling oh thank you for the
help we're almost done it's better with
two it's better with two people I had
one did anybody bring a repair kit I
do I oh boy
um after the zombie can I get the you oh
uh he Dr armored up enforcer gloves you
guys probably would like this uh armored
up yes for sure I know you probably want
that so you can grab that
ooh you have to parkour up here there's
some there's some loot for or there's
some do I need this got old money and
some corn seeds
hello taking pot shots at him uhoh oh
gosh there's a lot of people
upstairs oh yeah
did you go for the outside I parkour up
yes ow
jeeez I'm bringing them down hello
okay
ooh
thanks that door is locked I can
probably go around though right
beautiful nice job
ladies oh not clear yet I want to shoot
K did I put punch you I'm sorry oh it's
clear now can I get the repair kit I got
one come here thank you there's stuff up
here that we can loot though I think
hold up yeah you go
[Music]
my wa there's there's so many shamway
food boxes oh waa this is a totally new
area up here right for the
looten Rootin to loo Rootin toot loo and
shooting tell me if you find anything
good that maybe maybe it might be
helpful oh boy all right ladies is it
time to break the chest oh no I'm I'm
unlocking it I'm unlocking it don't
cough drink some tea cie with honey I'm
doing my
best uh let's see there are a bunch of
44 Magnum rounds in here VI in
the
okay double barrel shotgun here I'm
going to drop that whe oh really oh I
got a saw off shotgun mod does that
sound like a
Dropbox probably give this to crony
actually cuz crony wanted to do shotguns
I have okay wait are you not doing
shotguns I am I am but I my shotgun is
level uh my Satchel okay I found my
Satchel let's go oh I have armored up
also for you will need those I'm
dropping an armored up as well
did you guys all find your satchels I
did oh I have
Hammer I found my Satchel I have
Molotov those oh yes
please seems wrong to just throw them on
the ground but I'll pick it up from the
ground it's fine hopefully they won't
explode I think this Satchel also might
have something in it or if
somebody hasn't gotten their goods we've
all gotten our Goods right oh I dropped
some I'll pick it up and drop it maybe y
I guess we're good then oh we're good on
good oh uh F I hear some
[Music]
farming thank
you oh should I learn this dudes outside
are really
raging this was a fun one yeah lot of
stuff here yeah we're going to get a lot
more like these I
think B Mission I feel like we might be
way over the other girls's levels if we
do so many quests uh my leg didn't break
I'm good oh oh y thought watch out there
is a zombie down there though I killed
it we're good I'm just kidding I didn't
nice shot to get
him
yeah getting out might be a bit of a an
adventure in here oh just jump out the
window are you sure about that
yeah oh the dogs the dogs are here too
uhoh
well are we going to keep doing quests
do you think yeah we sure let's get the
hold on watch out there's a lot of
zombies where's my bike oh no oh here it
is thought it's like a rush during the
day ouch ouch that's
bad oh gosh there's a lot aren't yeah
there's a lot there's a lot
ow
ow don't die don't die I'm
beding oh my almost shot
FAA okay I deserve it I deserve it
there's still more there still more I've
hurt you many
times oh boy um hold on I'm trying to
heal okay we good we good thank you
thank
you a panic drank my beer uhoh but I
don't understand this kind of
[Music]
situation
um um um oh fine I'll here you go take
my dirty water I searched all the
toilets for you thank you wow
sweet that's how you know you got a
friend I can purify this if we need
it
oh oh I brought um what is it I brought
all the ingredients to make the really
good water so if you have like the
fireplace I can make I can make the
really good
water you have some food for me yes
thank you Mommy here you go pump p Mommy
Mommy
o
uhoh there God it feels so good to do
that oh she's alive
oh um look good shall we go to the next
Quest bird supplies sure
okay let's do
it oh is this the my quest I
wonder I think it
is by the way I know we're all like uh
loot
goblins um if I I I think the past few
class I was always kind of lagging
behind because I was destroying curtains
and stuff um but I won't get workstation
magazines if I don't open any boxes uh
and you girls don't get them either cuz
you're not Skilling into it can can you
like maybe keep like one crate or so if
you see something for me to open like
what well just every now and then okay
if I'm lagging behind because yeah I
noticed I don't get any magazine do be
rampant okay thank you got sh all uh was
it is it all crates because all the
crates have like specific um like this
is a food crate this is a does it
specifically any specific crate or like
any crate not sure where it would show
up bird bird please I feel like it's
been pretty mixed mixed bag of things in
bench ones oh it's a it's a cracker book
so you need to look for Cracker book
crate crackable crates so if it says
that we can let you open it okay
bookshelves too right yeah bookshelves
there's also a supply drop pretty close
but we should get it it's really close
right yeah let's go do that first also
this bird is really annoying
me do you guys see the bird yeah you see
him bullying me yes e vomb it's incoming
e dinner
oh but I I I not no need to always leave
the boxes for me of course because
everybody's looking for something just
one time
maybe want to see if I get lucky oh God
that's how many skulls is that seven
shamway Factory oh yeah the scariest
one they're get the quests are getting
intense for sure M they are but we are
also getting intense yeah oh yeah I
should check more mailboxes
too and those newspaper machines are
really
nice yes we should check those every
day ouch okay found the crate no no no
no leave me alone leave me alone the
bird still bothering you yeah here Kar
you want to open this one what what why
is it there is that the wait we made it
back to Jen's house
oo oh it has a farm bundle and the
crafting sh oh God the birds are B of
birds nice yeah shoot him out the sky
this one for fauna probably oh Callie
this is for you and this one for fauna
and this one
fora o weighted head oh I thank you I
have one of these I'll probably it's a
schematic oh it's a schematic nice so I
can make nothing much interesting just
some blueberry pie and the magazines and
stuff is there another one or just one
crate I think it's just the one oh I
think that's it okay yeah they're a
little underwhelming not going to
lie was on the way go check them okay
back to Berry toly
yeah okay we're going west we have to go
leave the way I got it it's uh just down
the hill I think we can take a a left
East East not
West East you guys are going west but
moris is moris is that way the the way
I'm looking we got to go down the
hill are we not doing moris which one
are we doing yeah I'm going to yours oh
okay it told me to go let's see let's
just see gets where
how make your way over there I'm just
going down the hill they how do you go
down this way bi boo
parkour I mean I I I rode down on my
bike and it was fine was it my bike only
has
44% oh I have I have repair kits for you
if you need to repair your bike
okay I'll figure out my way
down somehow
a bird's following me again I thought
you said go
east it's not West it's East
West or are we going
sth it's
Seas Seas yes oh
Southeast exist what ceas and cease and
CE what's it called ceas
and what cease and assist what and
assist never heard of cease and assist
before CE and yeah I was just trying to
figure out what it was called again
English is a hard language don't worry
about it I get those letters a lot in my
Ma saying really makes any sense to
me especially silly we're silly letter
from KFC and Burger King and
they're all sending me those letters
it's okay that's just that's just how
you know you're doing a really good
job right got some crunch where we going
yeah it's right here we're
digging seen
hes uh everybody is too far away I went
toce oh kill him oh I had a bag no come
on I hate this yes bag the bird
whoa
heue D I was playing baseball right
there wait for I got to
go wait maybe I should
cook oh yeah do a quick cooking session
before we start anyone have small stones
wait there's some small stones I have
small stones I have small stones yeah go
gather them I'm going to kill
surrounding zombies so they don't
interfere I'm going to I don't know how
far I need to put it so that it doesn't
spawn wait can I surely over here should
be fine right surely oh on the other
side of the street will'll definitely be
safe there's cre in there he was alive
he raged all you piece of garbage man oh
he's very strong he punches strong like
FAA
does wait then I shouldn't put my bike
there no my bike will come back right
yes I think okay what um I okay I have I
have stuff to make the really good
water that's definitely orange I say so
chat anybody have spare healing eyes
actually I might be able to make one I
do have some yes I might love to grab a
bandage from you I got a
bandage a little Band-Aid M oops please
Mommy
Band-Aid it make it better please
M thank
you thank you ma'am all right use
this
boo smooch always makes it
better oh cook this is far enough
surely yeah may
maybe I can't really cook anything good
I can make some water though might as
well while we're I'm going to make some
oh do you have normal water okay when
you're when you make your normal water
you can yeah you can use that I'll make
the good water when it's done yeah
actually I could probably make
Spam
spam oh yes sham I mean I'm about to get
a ceas and assist from spam everything
is made of zombie flesh oh my gosh I
think it's
commentary does that absolve you of any
legal
I don't know it's a great question okay
Gua we're over here start the quest I
found a paint brush to paint blocks like
building blocks that's exciting you guys
see the yellow circle yes yes okay good
so the treasure is somewhere in here
treasure and the circle gets smaller and
smaller but every time that uh you dig a
certain amount of holes I guess the
there's a chance for zombies to spawn
ready to fight so that's what
happened oh my God a
jumper oh there's there's nice there's a
one
there we can probably
leave area yeah people with guns are
going to have to take care of the ones
you can get out of the prim
I
just oh does anyone have repair kits I
do I have one I might need at least one
okay
got thank you we can help you
out oh we get clay from these digging
Cliffs nice that's good nice what do we
need clay for uh for the forge as well
ah just good to have in the Forge mhm oh
it says you're getting close oh more
spawns watch
out
hello oh
go
jumper he's
dead
yo getting too close for comfort please
stay
away I need eyes on my back I need a
back eye M I got you my stamina
[Music]
ow has this always been here we're
getting close to the treasure though
nice head thank you wow FPS Pro Taki
K rip ball
blood yeah Sheriff needs a little more
CIO I think I heard oh
hello that's just one just one guy one
gu it's always one guy that one guy yeah
that one guy keep him yeah keep
him we're get close toas more there's a
lot watch out watch out strong ones too
w
w oh well okay oh
[Music]
gosh I'm ooh low HP oh God it's chaos
they're on fire that girl is on
fire make a
gra push the bodies into the grave you
died in a very seductive pose hey
looking
good we're very close I
think so close hry I'll eat some a is
cooking oh yeah get in there yum yum
restum right
there yeah rest in pizza
PE I have one piece of
P I'm going to invite her to the party
oh no yeah yeah yeah more not no to CE
oh no
zombies oh nice one yeah shotgun oh
boy the shotgun going to work too e not
as much as the bat bath the bath you
stinky go shower
smelly smelly cop
man this is tough in peace I
know we are a great
team oh can't mess with
us yeah I think for tier three they get
pretty
deep they said we're getting close to
the treasure so they said that like 10
minutes ago though look you're getting
treasure
uhoh leave us I'm running low on
HP what that one out
jump oh God did you get hit no I don't
think
so yo the hole is as big as the
circle yeah we must be close is we have
to be that box doesn't appear past Stone
does anyone else have any repair kids I
do vaa come
here here fa I got
you uh where my repair kits go no wait a
minute hold on I had one oh no that's
okay need one I think I had two but I
may have given you I may have given you
two repair kits sorry about that people
has one yeah I we'll make a bunch
more thank you get back to the
house
o we must be getting close we must be
right oh getting close to the treasure
oh oh wait
is I think so hold
up
he a little fast right now
oh no not the bullets you
dumy oh
e oh wow I sced his whole body that was
wacky dude that man is in pieces nice
one B baseball
scary hold up I got him he
scary what she's just a cosplayer she's
scary going to be sad you're saying that
about her she's inspired by
you she needs to learn some con rules
about
interaction appropri deodorant and
showering
please it's a public service
announcement it's got to be way oh I'm
oh I'm not doing so well
healthwise my my leg I know don't worry
about the Battle we'll take care of the
B
battle no no
no
gaha have to protect and
attack cirle getting small wait they're
here they're here again they're
out oh they're going the hole oh
God I don't know how far we can go this
is a
hard I can't switch my
weapon why can't is it lagging oh I'm
bleeding I have a bandaid I got it's
okay it's okay I got one I got one oh
thank
you oh yikes oh
man fire
you okay okay okay okay that's okay I
deserve it I've been hitting my friends
all day it's
fine I can take some bullets for my
friends
y oh this lady's still alive hold
up nice okay I'll I'll stay out here now
because yeah yeah I'll be ready with my
machine gun okay you want to protect it
must be close it's got to be
somewhere oh that it oh there it is yeah
that must be it you
can oh what's that dang it people oh
here you can you have it you could take
it was it one for everybody it should be
one for everybody I think it's one for
everyone uh ooh armor triple pocket wa
there back they're back magazine
extended this one I don't want to die in
the in the diing quest wait before you
launch there's a lot of though okay uh
you guys can look through there there's
some maybe you all would like oh sorry I
think I I shot
people uhoh they're all down there oh
they're on the hole
oh they want the treasure
too they are the hole great perfect we
keep good yeah they can't attack us down
there
yeah are they dead they're dead um
there's some interesting schematics in
there Kier if you like making like armor
and stuff like that I think there's I
the pocket armor schematic maybe you
could use no
no what more more
I gotta run I gotta go I think it will
stop if everybody takes the take take
your chest take your chest I could oh
God I'm gonna die wait no I just took
everything out if we can look at it
later yeah look at it later okay I got
it it's over it's so over in a good way
ouch it hurts hurt like a like a last
rush or what going on go
away oh no oh God
oh no no no
no do we fail the quest I don't know why
is
Noe I think we finished it as long as
you grab no no no no no no yeah we
should be fun well that's kind of crazy
still
here oh my God that's
rough every time someone takes their
Quest item it's spawn zombies
apparently that'll do it oh dear oh it's
oh no there's a lot of them still um
okay it's okay we still we still
finished the quest cuz we got the item
yeah are you guys around yeah I'm
around oh my gosh hold on just keep keep
hiding keep hiding keep
hiding
okay this is like the worst enemy ever
why is it so hot
now I already wear my clothes wow he
wasn't flinching at all with my with my
bat hyper powerered
zombies oh nice got some
loot
gosh yay I have some bi boo ammo oh yes
please I used a
lot I leveled up again I got a very very
powerful schematic not schematic mod I
wanted to tell you about it's it's
pocket three which increases your
carrying capacity by three I just feel
like it's not a schematic it's a mod you
can install it into your armor I feel
like we should decide who gets this
somehow cuz it's a very it's a very good
mod yeah I already have pocket too so I
don't need it you're
good
okay you can have it for now like is it
okay
we'll find more we'll find
more yeah we'll find more always if it's
okay with you guys I would like to
install it if I can
but are you are you uh taking down the
cooking station
um was it I can give oh just because we
all died so we almost all of us died so
we probably don't need food water ah did
you guys get your supplies yes I'll make
some food maybe oh can I can I have the
water for the
pure water yes you can cancel the Sham
if you want I'll cancel it oh my God my
gun already almost broken at all these
nerds gathered around the
campfire okay I have a I have a
Bandelier mod
bandier uh reload 15% faster oh wait
it's a you have to read it and learn how
to craft it whoever crafts like weapons
I can I have a magazine extender mod
schematic okay I'll learn those I think
that's handgun stuff I'm pretty
sure I need to get the next level of
shotgun I hope I can get that oh I have
four skill
points oh yeah we we leveled really fast
with those tier three Quest like I'm
already man in well well into the next
level dang all righty
we can uh come back for the fire I made
a marker on the map so okay we can go do
another one okay um there's mine to the
right to the east beast mode oh B do you
want this KN I got
strength oh thank
you wow 10 out of 10 oh my gosh I have
beast mode strength I almost have
completely maxed that that's
big big buff thanks
chat you can become the Beast of
Darkness okay there's one quest to the
eat we can go to and then come
back
intellect yay I'm leveling I'm getting
closer oh I need more repair kits does
anyone have any more I have I have two
left I can give you one one Kara here's
magazine I found it in a pile of
garbage thank you welcome where my
bicyle the other where is it yeah the
other way I'm on my way soon but yeah I
repaired my my machine gun like 20
minutes ago and it's already about to
break again soon yeah we can craft a
bunch at home
right stage
80 what the heck he yeah I don't know
like we really don't need to do so many
quests we could like work on farms and
stuff yeah I need to do quests but
still I personally just need to level up
I'm going to go hit that tror it is
pretty late though oh what should we do
well I'm at my tier three clear already
we can do that and then we can head
back Oh you mean late in the game
already yeah day 24 uh oh but oh but no
28 is when the raid happens comes yeah
oh we're fine still Yes okay I'm going
to go to where bi boo is then I want to
help okay
Finish kaha you should open this
mailbox okay mail box here but I think I
realized why I'm barely getting
workstation magazines myself I I still
need to put one skill point into the
particular I see
[Music]
oh four okay
four it wasn't bad we did we did a oh we
done this one no we haven't done this
one should I'll just activate I don't
know I'm scared is he any
uh pretty good okay it has started we
really got to try and enforce the base
better I think with like Cobblestone and
stuffff is going to be oh they're coming
out of the gra coming out of the graves
oh I've done it this is the one I did
and died oh what on your own no
wonder
oh we might die
too I can tell you what's going to
happen
um in the house there's a point where
like 10 zombies fly out of a room so
okay well watch out I was about to say
get excited how did you survive this
outside hard in the first place yeah
watch out watch
out yeah so it's in here I broke down
the door last time but maybe there's a
different
way
peacefully there's a cooler car with
murky water in it if anyone wants murky
water uhoh well I think we're past murky
water no we're not leaving it
behind by the by the campfire
outside get ready they all come from
that room oh there's a big
[Music]
guy what is this
looks interesting they
ready they're coming okay should we find
backing up outside might be good oh
outside it might be
better
O
Beautiful okay okay the purple guy still
alive almost dead oh you
guys it was just two people yeah it
wasn't that bad why did I get like 10
zombies then that's not fair and did
they maybe send less outside towards you
I have a workstation Wonder uh look here
you go I'm dropping it really yeah
workstation yeah I dropped it go you
lucky bastard nice where lucky there do
you want to open this oh no that's uh oh
yeah that's the right one let's go
there's polymers in here that one you
want to open this no you can open you
can open
handgun
ammo it was a roaming horde I guess I
just got unlucky really oh no
yes well we also
have was someone doing Hammer CH uh yes
I okay I'm going to drop it in the
bathroom in this box is I think you do
you do no wait who did electrical traps
electrical okay good here's the get
hammered magazine on the floor next to
the toilet Kiara thank you so you can
get hammered oh you
CED I'll get hammered yeah only you can
do it Gua being hammered is my St
standard stance right now ah there's a
lot of stuff in this vehicle there's
vehicle Adventures um in this
chest um there's there's Miner gloves
for heavy armor if anybody using heavy
armor it's in this chest H Miners and
kiaha ammo in this chest thanks oh sorry
the chat's been in the weird place the
whole
time
sorry uh
uh wait uh uh we didn't open
this oh yeah the lock chest no it's open
it's open no the passing gas wasn't oh
the one below wasn't open oh
did I'll invite the she logged in don't
CC
B
uh I'm so
cucumber I guess I'll take this
um there a doggy outside I heard a doggy
I like it oh oh there's a there's a
hoorde coming in uhoh from the front
watch out
oh
boy
nice here there's more there's more
there's more coming drop something good
[Music]
oh
nice minor boots minor gloves we have
almost a full
set oh I can't
move oh I am hurt
yeah nice one Kiara burn him yeah burn
him to a Cris so we can make more sham
sandwiches oh I got a
work awesome why is everybody getting
these now I don't know you need brass
for stuff probably can can somebody take
this drop loot I'm so I really can't
move anymore there's Pistol Pete I bet
that I bet you could use that oh thank
you chihuaha here you go yeah your book
thank
you
uh so strong
together
yippe this Closet in here as well as
harvesting tools I don't know if
anyone's using harvesting tools
but no I I'm not
really Skilling into
got okay I'll just take
it I got a bicycle hello oh you're here
welcome yay yay I it on the floor we
have more friends for party what a
coincidence Hong Kong Hong Kong press X
press x x
[Music]
yay why can't I ready for some quests
change some setting chest chat I can't
switch with the mouse wheel
anymore
weird for even more quests I'll probably
have to go back to the new house cuz I
have to drop off stuff I'm pretty much
ready to drop stuff off I want to hit
the trader
first it's closed right now oh it is
closed should we find like a residence
to like because we're so far away from
yeah yeah maybe
maybe C wait you use shotguns Callie me
I have ammo I found a forg head was it
you I think it was ah yes yes here oh
you're getting so many
now wait I'm going to run back to the
fire that's on the oh yes oh the fire
you mean that fire the
campire Oh I thought you meant the caned
fire the canned fire well yeah there's a
fire full there's a canned fire over
here that's fine oh this house is on
fire too what the heck
oh wow lots of fire sorry I was zoning
out we are looking for a house
now um we probably should like probably
the Traer yeah close to the to the Bob
we should probably find a house to like
start hunkering down over there cuz it's
really really far yeah I can bring the
like Kitchen pot and stuff
yeah let's go sounds good did the water
finish yes it did yay nice would you
like some or all yeah yeah I'll take
some I made it for everybody okay
there's some thank
you this way this
way okay back to
Trader yeah well should we set up a new
house I guess we don't need to go back
if we make a new house yeah we need to
set up a new one let's go near the
trader and see if there's a house by
there yeah
although I feel like then all of our
like resources and items will like be so
scattered again and we'll have to go so
far to pick something up and just why we
need to get a helicopter eventually yeah
yeah I I'm going to still try to bring
all my supplies to the new house okay
okay yeah it is tough when all your
stuff is all spread out I wish we had
like ender chests in this game
yeah maybe there's I wonder if car
trunks car should have huge trunks we
can put a bunch of supplies do Supply
runs and stuff MH that would be great I
wonder if we can make cars at this point
we can make mini bikes I suppose but I
don't think we all any of us know how to
make a car yet but that' be fun yeah e
at what CH at what level can I make a
car cuz my vehicle skill is at 31 that
seems pretty good decent start I think
you need three to make a bike so that
you
want oh I can make a mini bike right now
so motorbike what do you mean to make
it wait let me check in a
moment no you can't just repair your it
requires a work C Scrat mini bike well
Two Wheels One Mini Bike chassis mini
bike handlebars engine and elite car
battery it's not too bad old house we
have a couple of those things yeah mhm
and she also uh or Bob somebody will
give us mini bike parts it seems as a
reward
right yes uh oh there's a diner nearby
the
we can hunker down here maybe the greasy
spoon actually I can I can craft the the
parts as well it's a it looks like a
nice
reinforced place they' got
a
uhoh watch out no why
not burgers
fries Burgers I love fries ew to yucky
versatile you the fries no no somebody
the dude was burping at me oh oh okay
maybe I can repair it
here oh wow you cut her head
off pretty
impressive holy all right we're taking
this place over
[Music]
no it's always such a beautiful sight to
behold oh watch out I stabbed you you
might be bleeding uhoh oh I'm going to
die uhoh no oh no if you get hit once by
me you're you're going to bleed out
that's rough I hope my quest didn't go
away it shouldn't if it didn't if it
didn't start it won't it won't go away
okay I can't carry anything does
somebody want to take these things out
of these chests I don't have space what
I get for trying to be are we going to
set up here at least a 10
yeah let's put some boxes down okay I'm
going to make a
fire honestly I might just put the food
in this cabinet here you can put the
fire in the kitchen and then it's like
real RP yeah
ooh works again will I get electrical
shock let's see
no ooh Lumberjack oh I found three armor
parts that's huge night
nice ja better than my current
boots yeah better stamina
regen does anybody have
wood
yes I will also there's a shamway
shipping crate M oh maybe we can use
that crate for storage yeah we can
o oh yeah we can okay we'll just put
stuff in
here why did
re
what H don't forget the land claim box
or the stuff might despawn that's right
oh yeah how do you make
that oh I can make
one the land has been claimed by
FAA there's a Ry in the soda fountain
eat some murky water we boiling some
water I have a shot thing is shotgun
I'll take it you like a shotgun magazine
oh shotgun Messiah is my fave here thank
you to
you any more repair kits on at hand
ladies I don't think so we might I have
one but I might need it
soon oh shoot I might need that for my
baseball Pat too
I'll try and make one when I go back oh
if I had duct tape I could make
one blue I could CRA and cloth I have
extra kniv I I can actually give you
mine I don't need it that soon ooh thank
you my machine gun is on zero thank you
appreciate it oh if I could only pick it
up need coton we will find that in the
desert one cloth fragment I can make
duct
tape oh it's good it's fine 99 mm ammo
on the floor if someone needs it oh I
need it thank
you yeah it's about to be
morning go hit up the traitor yeah he's
going to be open
[Music]
soon oh I hear zombie I got him hello
big tummy zombie I got him medical
journal thank you
yes okay I'm going to the
trader yeah tra Traer Traer traitor turn
in
stuff oh
gosh in quests I'll help you thank
[Music]
you would get me thank you I live to
protect I was just exploring there there
were zombies on the roof you do be
protected they were on our house
the
tra open up Let Me In when do we get to
meet Trader Joe not Trader Bob Trader
Jen let me
in open open open you're late Ann's open
first you're late he's waking up he's
brushing his teeth he's washing his face
faster 5 minutes late
ow ah
unbelievable it's about time seems to be
the vehicle man oh high power Magnum
ammo that's pretty good but I feel like
you get offer Magnum ammo you'll get
offered that yeah you don't need to take
it from me I can get
yeah oh did I make two of these 10
lockpicks uh infection might be better
I'll take the lockpicks wait water
purifier mod allows safe consumption of
murky
water oh that's that's the hat that for
hat oh nice def get
that more hats more magical
hats is a freaking Katana that's crazy a
what a what there's a tempered blade but
you might get offered it too I don't
think it's a katana though
let's
see what does the number in the right
corner in the bicycle mean it says 27%
27% of what oh it's your bicycle's
durability you can heal it using repair
kit
okay you've been busier and a Cat on a
Hot Tin Roof good
job I'm going to break
J feel I'm using armored
up I have a hammer one for here I'm
going to drop the magazines here that I
don't
need oh and a
magazine here you go thank you for thank
you shotgun crafting skill anyone me
okay I need that
awesome
yay I can make double barrel shotgun
quality
six with the legend Parts oh maybe I
should have given the to gigy oh well
next time o she has like a monster truck
in the back here bio here's your handgun
magazines oh thank you does anyone want
a shotgun duck bill mod schematic recipe
maybe I could take that cooking magazine
if there's a different anybody Mor's
going to learn how to cook really learn
how to cook yes I'm going to learn how
to cook
okay I can make grilled corn and baked
potatoes good now I can help thank
you okay awesome all right I will take a
job but I will not do
it I have armored
magazines o I was about to run away
explosive
magazines uh that's UMO I think B yes b
b m bo
boo thank
you that's
big H okay what armor level am I good
question why don't you take a look for
yourself got tap 100 armor level 100
[Music]
y I can make legendary armor if you guys
give me the part yay oh sick
whoa what did I just
do freaking
go oh I leveled
up red te he loves Vehicles
huh he's got all the nice vehicle stuff
also I took some
quests I took some too if you guys want
to run through
quests what did I do oh you're very
quiet right what did I
do oh now you're
better I wonder why oh I can make steel
wait can I make steel Knuckles now
somebody else is looking at their
inventory I can't look through it oh I'm
looking one second okay okay oh uh the
was is it he
has batter up volume say clubs have a
20% chance to ragd doll enemies if
you're interested that's big yeah I'll
let you
lookk I definitely need
that big
hitters okay scatter up volume six
that's
huge okay thank you very much for
letting me know B yeah does he have he
does have repair kits I think buying
those might be a good idea yeah buy
repair kits that's always good that's a
good idea check for Crucible is the guy
selling any crucibles right
now Crucible I don't I didn't see any
when I looked right I didn't see any
[Music]
either well probably doesn't have any
okay I'm going to new house probably not
going to do any more quests today just
going to clean up stuff and do like
productive stuff okie
dokie I didn't realize it's almost been
three hours why it goes by so fast I
know what the heck I didn't even realize
time has really flown time flies when
you're playing this
game
okay do you need help with
anything um I I I just bought a repair
KET because I was like oh no what if iak
a
bicycle um I don't really have I have a
good like um gear or weapons so that
might be kind of nice do you do you want
a a shotgun double barrel shotgun it's a
pretty good one yeah fire twice and I'll
give you some ammo for it here 25 and
I'll give you a little more hold
up
here it's so
far welcome we put that here oh there it
is that should help you the mini bike
PES is
expensive o h mini bike but I can make
the parts too um it's not you cra the
parts yeah the parts and the mini bike
itself
so I don't know if I can make one for
everybody with our current materials but
I can
check I'm on my way w armor
shop oh this is a quest place I'm going
to try it once I'm spending all my money
oops you want to try on
me do you want to try on
youy why not okay okay can you jump here
around and be a moving Target okay okay
T catch me T to catch me this like a
video game tutorial tring to catch me t
t you missed you missed
miss two then you got to reload
it ow oh you did miss that time I hit
you you did hit me didn't kill me though
yeah actually kill me cuz
yeah oh one stck I need to
reload that was awesome good job
yay well Kiara wants to go do some
housekeeping would anybody like to run a
couple more quests with more because I'm
a little bit behind I'm down
yeah that much but now that I have a gun
I bit
yeah we got stuff to do we have
responsibilities
farming well I also can't get on
tomorrow um so I'm also kind of like
maybe I should try and level up as much
as possible oh you'll miss the
raid it it's tomorrow yeah the raid's
tomorrow ah dang it okay well that's too
bad I'm sure you guys will be fine but
the last day I think that we should play
all the way through until a raid
happens okay do you want to do this
clear tier three clear North that's your
quest kie yes okay we'll go
there I I think it's yeah North
Northwest yes yes I'm so fast we're so
fast look at this I'm so
fast it's fine faster than you see you
later Los yay that's not very
nice what the heck next time I stab you
it won't be an accident wait so does
that mean that
tomorrow it wasn't it before yes
tomorrow then the next stream will the
next stream after the tomorrow stream
will be the last one with like two
shifts combined basically yep okay yeah
I think tomorrow since we're timed a
little bit oddly the the hord will be in
the middle so then the last day will be
a little bit longer than the others but
not like six 7 full hours
yep okay last day let's make it count
yeah but we got to look into uh if
there's any way to keep the server alive
until we want to do season 2 or like
keep the characters I don't know if the
server has to be kept active so to
say or if there's any other way to keep
the characters cuz I don't know I don't
want to lose all this progress yeah
right as long as we don't like AFK play
and stuff we should all keep our stuff
right now we can ask them I don't know
because they probably have to pay for
the server and I don't know if they'll
pay for it if we're not AC server gets
like temporarily like put on hold will
it wipe
us yeah we'll have to check that out any
yeah we should ask I feel like they
should be able to save the server like
even if it's not
online should be
okay
season we got we got pretty invested in
it
[Music]
too me Andia
yeah and also got really into it I wish
I could play not yesterday tomorrow
yes I have been playing every day so far
but tomorrow I just cannot sadly that's
fine you need a break too by the way are
you crazy like playing Dark Souls and
seven days to die in one day when you
have scouring in your lungs what no I I
like Dark Souls yeah but do you really
have
to
girl I can relate I understand
you but B do you have scarring in your
lungs no well well I did I did play
elering that one time without a voice
but it's just it's just the you know the
game it just makes you want to you know
got a hole gamer got a
game I'm not doing another stream today
I thought about doing another stream
today but I decided not do so thank God
I'm cooking tomorrow for some
friends cooking cooking let her cook so
they wanted to eat like really uh
healthy stuff so I'm doing like chicken
like really delicious sauce and like
bunch of green
vegetables a bunch of veggies and then
ricotta cheese salad with
walnuts then yingle for dessert which is
like uh it's like fried apple with
Raisin and cinnamon oh yum yum yum yum
yum yum I'm always hungry when I play
this
game I don't eat dinner
before you are the Cook oh you don't
have you don't have to it's over here oh
and then a hole in the ground too let's
go oh oh okay yeah that's easier I'll
try to take it easy I wanted to play
tomorrow so bad I can't uhoh will you
take it
easy spiler she does not take it
easy I'm just having so much fun you
can't be
helped
same I hope we get to play again see if
we we should make a chest that's only
for car parts getting a lot
I kind of want to organize our chests
yeah we need
more I bet we have a bunch of hidden
stuff we can't find it cuz it's all over
the
place
uh creepy lab where they're making pills
that's nuts oh fun I got a I got a
knuckle magazine for you thank
you want a Punchy water
there's a guy in a radioactive suit kill
him what does that mean no he's dead
already Forge ahead I got Forge ahead Ki
Oh okay I'll bring it to you yeah uh how
do you name a box uh hold e and then
drag it to the naming
option
oh kill it dead kill it
dead ow dead sorry I did not see that i'
hit you in the head oh
boy there's a bit of an I don't honestly
know what is C Parts but probably
these oh up here Up on the Roof oh
baby oh there someone there is he alive
there must be dudes are you
alive that was you scared me oh
oh yes there's a lot there's a lot get
ready C
Parts we've got so much
shame oh they all have they look weird
they these are crazy
zombies uh these are kind of wild okay
did not expect that
I got minor boots and minor gloves I
wonder who might like
these oh gosh I'm
Radioactive
radio
radio oh okay he's very strong I'm just
going to be careful wait
and killed him oh there's another
one not done yet though oh is it oh it's
not in there I thought it
was a great stash does anyone have a
um lockpick oh I do there a box here I
got 10 actually I need to use this o I
can make the fort bites now these are
really nice for Buffs fortnite bites
fortnite fortnite bites they're called
Fort
bit uh maybe I don't have the lockpicks
oh I'm Lockpick it all right you got it
B you got this Kelly are you carrying
your legendary Parts on your own like
inventory or did you put them I I
haven't had a chance to go back home oh
okay cuz there's some here in our chest
what is it a Tim charge I have like a
time bomb well oo you have a time
bomb you taking time
bum yeah the legendary Parts though
everybody's eventually going to get a
weapon that they're really really good
with they might want to upgrade to level
six and if you want to upgrade it to
level six you need legendary parts to do
it so I kind of want to see if we can
hold on to them if
possible okay the area is not yet clear
by the way I can't carry anymore it's
not clear there's still zombies around
here oh and I still need to find my
supplies too
okay let's see I wonder
where did we miss somebody oh I also
have to do for me it gives a check mark
but uhoh oh no we did clear the area I
just need to find my supplies okay oh
okay it's confused see I I
see oh you see I'll get break my leg if
I jump yeah probably okay I got mine
hurt yourself nice I'm
done nice did you find yours no I see
her on the map but it's like hiden I
think behind some of these locked doors
probably a little bit organized I know
what this is in your
dreams car parts you need help break it
open the door car parts just trying to
figure out what level this is on car
parts
and
bye oh apparently we can do this Mission
Again somebody took the same one oh it's
it's kiaha though classic oh kiwa's
Mission yeah oh oh yeah I'm not there so
yeah it's okay we can go to the other
one though we can go to the yeah if you
guys want to yeah there's one to
the I'll Follow You Vio for the next one
okay
[Music]
does anyone have food oh actually you
can kill me I do you want to die yeah I
died earlier it's fine kill me oh really
oh okay and
it's sounded so excited about that she's
like yep leave it to me I'll kill you I
was a bit too happy I believe you don't
know about all
that trying to make some space in my
inventory do collector is still so slow
even when two
upgrades come on do something maybe we
have to like make a bunch of them or
something yeah I'm guessing it's it's a
beginner item so we just have to make a
bunch of D collection is there no better
[Music]
one okay I'm I'm back I'm fine I'm
live all right B will Le the way okay
you're 100 on Armor already right Kiara
yes okay I'll just learn them then
extra I can't get over 100 right Chad is
also learning armor as well just for my
own self just a little bit we could
share
them can't go over 100 okay too bad yeah
we'll going to
theast if I were to I I why am I lagging
it's going
insane yay new weapon for me oh God they
look terrifying
nice new steel
Knuckles that bike definitely needs
repairs maybe I'll make
one I wonder what's necessary huh for
what for bike repairs oh just a repair
kit oh really new
nice it's it's one of the options when
you hover over it like with
e just got to click I did it yay thank
you f
yes uh you don't have your Rader gloves
yet do
you um no I don't I'll make you some on
level six level six oh yeah well we'll
go all the
way
e let's
go level six I should sorry for tomorrow
M fored
iron okay it's this one this place trck
stop Diner oh oh this one has four
skulls so what we definitely want CeCe
to be here with us CeCe I'm right here
[Music]
H watch out for the barb wire fence bird
oh nice shot nice shooting text
well I'm very
cucumber F do you have some more forg
steel
[Music]
somewhere house run might be good at
some
point okay this
chest do the trader sell steel yes they
they they sell for steel it's kind of
expensive though but H it's like 150
per I see we need two oh there's already
a doer coming out I bet he'll reset
though when we start the mission yeah
hold on
I may we
Havey
okay getting cleaner here all right I'm
going to start yeah it is you going to
started yeah okay okay it has
started hello ladies I could make it a
lower Lev oh that also needs It's A din
yummy for now okay I'll make it on level
five fauna oh that's horrific okay thank
you oh I found a big Treasure Chest oh
he's
alive that's horrifying he a skelan
zombie oh oh oh there's a bunch of them
hard yeah bring him bring him out here
it might be easier to fight him okay
he's alive
not I believe there's a lot of guys
please move you you're ready lots and
lots of guys in
there I wonder if I can solo the boar Oh
dumper dumper by soloing the boar I want
to I mean that's awesome but you him you
can do it I want is meat I don't know
dream come
true be yeah that dude just won't die oh
there's a bun in the door over here
watch out with the radar gloves you can
probably kill him are they that good run
off mean definitely better than what you
have hello hello there's a locked Crate
by the way that I found okay don't go in
here okay I will unlock it at the ammo
there's some good stuff in there this
medical I'm going to read the medical
journal use one of these just for
funsies are they both my dce
WF but not that
far what you find in there you have a
full
set what's in there I got Treasure
Hunter MOD ex bonus oh I got iron
Knuckles do you use iron Knuckles
f um not anymore okay oh she's upgraded
I have upgraded I found a forge head
too nice
cloth we're always need a new cloth
hunting rifle that seems like it might
be
good and a
crossbow or is down here do we have a
chassis this might be a bad idea no you
got this okay we have plenty of it's
easy just like talk to like say say
taunt him taunt him what there's
more freaking
wait I like three shot him wait never
mind I just him never mind never
mind it's that Qui
a they drop oh I killed him
[Music]
shot I can make a p a pump shotgun now
guys
y Pump It Up also there's some loot over
here bi Boo full of ammo for
you 9 mm it's a right in front of the
counter there a yellow bag yeah oh
40 look look at these
shoes that's some
drip that's some drip I think yeah we
completed the quest the job team oh shy
can
make I guess
not I got to make this how many can this
hold I wonder
pum up the
gy it up why your feet on the I wonder
if we shoot this if it going to explode
which one reload I will make a
pump should we try
out wait wait wa wait let me put my
bicycle somewhere else wait oh it has
hold on hold on hold on
[Laughter]
it did
work o crushed sand wow don't know what
that is but hey maybe it's
useful this one again crushed
sand okay I'm going to tra to turn and
then to clear my storage oh
bunny also like
eased I might go back to the house
make a couple I'm kind of a menace now I
feel
bad come here let me make you even more
into a menace okay I'm just getting some
food for us lots of food where' the
gloves
go wait am I still drunk I should fight
them while I'm
drunk drunken fist brawling
oh this will take a while do it
faster no I have too much monkey WWA
that's me that's
you I'm making a mini bike right now
yay I'm excited to see what it looks
like yeah wonder how fast it's going to
be going to zoom
around Zoom
I'll be the fastest in these lands for
now I'll make more though I think I can
make a couple
maybe Ranger outfit that looks
good let me see if I can make some
bandages it gets laggy when I go into
the it's generally laggy
here a little
more oh it's a little better for Max
Health Wheels oh we might not have so
many
wheels didn't we have more can you craft
a wheel there's Wheels all over the
place all around the desert it seems
like but can you actually pick those up
or do you have to like I'll see if I see
another one I'll check yeah for science
please oh I feel so bad but why why
I'm killing pigs that's okay they're
tasty they're cute though no they're not
even radioactive they're normal then
they're probably sad and thirsty and
you're taking them out of the I guess
they are probably sad and thirsty
yeah okay I think I think Tire only give
plastic if you beat them I don't think
they give Tire tires okay no problem I
found a
more and we can make Wheels ourselves
with a oh quite a oh it takes a few
quite a few things around here bags oh I
lost the bicycle I don't know where to
put it oh
no isn't it
borrowed shouldn't
it where did it go
no oh God it's gone the bicycle I lost
it uh do you see an icon like a yellow
icon for the bik oh yeah I do I do okay
okay okay okay I found it I found
it have to hang out with a lot to make
them like you of course they can like
you go hang out with the boar every
day what am I
doing sorry guys I'm all over the
place that's okay me
too probably go back to the house pretty
soon very far away but it can't be
helped well you can you can use the new
house to temporarily store some
stuff yeah temporary little base don't
yeah it will be too good huh let's use
that for a real car
ooh um any is fine okay this is all
stuff that's good for bioo but not for
me oh I'll take it
still for generators are selling oh
interesting thank you increased visual
magnification here we
go mini bike is being
crafted I'll make one more I think I can
make one more for
[Music]
sure
e h what's that
a furious fist I got a bunch of good
stuff for you guys so I'm just going to
go back to the
house this point duct tape I want to
throw stuff away why is it always a duct
tape wait the
bike it's fine I got enough stuff
a dog what the dog do are you going to
attack me dog do me I'm going to have to
kill it did anybody anybody here in this
VC learn how to make an ex wait was it
me did anybody learn how to make an
extra mini bike
seat I thought you learned did I I gave
it to you did you use it I got a vehicle
expanded seating mod is that for the car
I don't know I don't know does it not
work for the mini bike did you use it uh
I didn't use it I used it but I didn't
make it yet Ah that's it okay okay that
works for bicycle a b mini bikes too
mini bike we can ride together
yay then we save I mean we're always
going everywhere together so we don't
need to bikes eco-friendly e friendly
with the bikes
awesome I heard who's killing dogs I
just heard a very sad dog out oh there
were sad dog noises happening the whole
time at that diner for some weird reason
oh we're in the desert it's strange it's
just they're trying to go for the scraps
and then they taste them like oh this is
disgusting oh wait what am I do then
they run away
again let's make a
couple yep I'm only roed up for seven
more minutes so I got to hurry up and
get home so I can put this stuff
away oh wait oh it makes two at a time
now I think do I put the fuel into the
bike guess
so how much does it
take
fun look at
these thank
[Music]
you I wonder what bonus you get oh but
ah you're not wearing the top but you
have thep no is it worth it to get the
bonus to sacrifice the
XP maybe not on H night I'm PR peacock
that you got that job done not sure they
do say that the set bonuses in this game
are not like that worth it mixing armor
is better red the chance of critical
injuries by 20% I mean that is pretty
good
yeah I think it's less complicated to
just wear one full said so why not yeah
that's true I look pretty scary backone
to take this job looking to
your surely we have more elsewhere oh
hold
up oh no
coughing I'm okay I definitely wasn't
coughing definitely not coughing
definitely not oh I collected a lot so
far
um Yos okay
I think I can make this bike oh look at
that building looks
crazy wait you're not behind me I
thought you were behind me oh me no I
lost you I'm in the I'm in the Traer got
oh okay okay okay oh gosh oh where did
you go oh you went
giant giant
Building looks like a factory
oh God be careful there hey yo heyo what
is that
scream crazy she's at our window she's
in our bushes whoa you guys got a
screamer yeah no wonder they're called
screamers be careful there's another one
coming I she'll punch him it'll be good
punch him with those new gloves
yeah I'm feeling strong
you are and it's
[Laughter]
hoty and F do you have some extra claw
fragments yes oh Hallelujah wait another
screamer here you
go where are you I'm almost home in the
the bathroom the former bathroom ah
thank
you hey zombies I will defeat them okay
she closes the door behind her I'm on my
way girls stay back I'll
take wa but but it sounds like a lot are
you sure I'm strong okay probably let me
just drink some
beer oh there's a zombie in the house
uhoh uhoh that's bad I I'll take care of
the one
inside your oh the door was open oh the
door is gone exp let's go the door is
gone oh he's thr oh it's a police one
inside the house K are you here too yeah
I just got did you show up oh hi seconds
ago
hey welcome home oh he's out oh there's
a okay yeah
outside are you kidding me yeah we need
a new door in the back
uh yeah that cannot be
safe is it
over I think so I think so I have some
ammo for you
kiaha thank
you go so much stuff this BM is kind of
cool they can keep this
running yeah I put some Furious Fists uh
in the books thank you yeah books
chest what am I doing powder
how about all right um two
bikes crushed sand I don't really know
what that's for but I'm going to put it
in here maybe give to people people hey
you didn't hear it a car battery bio yes
I shall donate to you the
second uh bike because I'm sure you'll
enjoy it yay thank you
I will not cash it into a fly actually I
think I can also make an extra seat for
your bike so you can also take people
with you I'm coming
home I'm excited what am I lacking ah oh
if only I had more if you can bring me
more cloth fragments I can make you a
bite an extra seat okay I'll take him
I'll take take a lot J has
one well then God there's some good
stuff in here can I dye the bike surely
I can put some color on
it to make it
distinguishable wasn't there some dye
um
okay I guess I'll make it Pink iron in
that
Forge or can we have yellow dye yes
there is yellow dye oh then you should
take the pink D beo I'll should I die
your B your bike pink yes
please it'll match my bikes yeah it's
more it actually does look more purple
than pink so that's
perfect where was the yellow
dye uh let me check if if you're here to
buma
has oh wait I found it I found it I'm
blind to make some duct tape do do you
want any more more yellow dye cuz she
does have some oh no no okay no
need do we have any Clays the oil
ugly clay uh I think I put most of the
clay into the forge seven duct tap dang
how do we get more clay um digging the
ground gave a lot of clay of you be sure
to tell your friends like anywhere yeah
I mean when I did the digging Quest gave
me a lot of clay just from
digging wonder how many shotgun parts we
have do we have a shotgun parts
ladies I am trying to make the best gun
in the
world oh I'm outside I'm going to dig
Mountain wait are you behind the house
or where I'm behind the
house 44 steel can we sell stuff oh we
can sell Stu
maybe we should just focus on a new bat
instead for now oh wait wait wait
wait where is the
seat did I leave this ah wait where is
this wait
for one
second CE I have armor for you for me
yeah for
you are you giggling qu are you let me
see I I'm coming back home so I'm going
to the house come over here F okay y we
got to take a test ride maybe not I'm
going to store my shotgun parts in
here get Ona wait it's locked heard of
what LO this maybe we got to be in a
party you got to unlock it gas it up oh
how how
to
wait unlock and let me put some gas
in this looks so gross the bottle on the
side
go bye
suckers we're out of here [\h__\h] this
apocalypse oh my
gosh here they go y honeymoon sunset
yes we need to pick up gigy somewhere I
know a we had a third
seat no I don't think so this is pretty
romantic I look like your
bodyguard scary bodyguard is this even
significantly faster than the bicycle I
guess so it better be if it uses fuel
right yeah yeah you would hope it feels
pretty fast this is me on I think
maximum
speed nice there was so much before now
it's gone speed of seven b this is speed
seven bicycle with speed five
oh wait wait wait let's race one sec on
this Main Road let's see how big the
difference is oh okay okay but wait I I
can give you the new
bicycle although it doesn't have a
second seat on it yet need to make the
second seat oh no I wanted to see the
difference between the two the normal
bicycle and the bike all
right
okay all right you got a head start okay
three one
go
go I'm coming for
you oh here we go oh
it
lagged I'm taking
over okay okay chovsky
yeah chy kovsky Cecilia
[Music]
IM that is suy should not be taking
rides with anyone in tacore Cheo
I always in
[Laughter]
[Music]
pain yippee
uhoh
yippee oh not so technologically
advanced anymore are you
C me no I I stole this bike so what can
I
say engineering genius
takana one more robotics oh I hear it I
hear the engine I think your robotic
thing has I was told some uh fauna is
replacing your robot or something is
this it what what what was that I don't
know chat was saying
something can't believe take this
CeCe you think I can steal from
R3 can stealing too you yeserday what is
that oh thank
you we're not really Ste what I have
nice big water drinky people I'm going
to put your a purple bike outside for
now once I get more cloth fragments I
can put the seat on
it uh where is it
here I have
five there you
go I think you have to ah wait you have
to uh put some gas in it press e and put
gas and also unlock but uh you probably
don't have any gas right now oh it's
locked yeah oh I guess I have to unlock
it for you there you go
o is there gas in it there's 2% of gas
in it oh w
am I always carrying the gas does it not
go into the bike guys is this my gas
right
now let's give her a
stack
um yeah so ladies can we make a limit
water it does go in okay um kind of kind
of yes cuz I'd love to make more glue if
we could we have more water it's just
very slow I see we can make more d colle
and then buy the upgrades but o that
might be a good
idea what do you need duct tape or what
yeah I'm making duct tape how many do
you want let's see I've got four so I
just need three more for the pump action
shotgun okay take from uh Forge
chest thank you are you having fun I am
having
fun
fast let's go
a sorry sorry there you go wait do you
take damage when you drive into people
uh I out try driving over her I took
damage when I hit a
[Music]
[Laughter]
tree we should put like a spear on the
front and you can impale the zombies
could have sword we had shotgun parts
somewhere dang it
possibly
[Music]
shot how many cloths do you need for
that seat got to take these level two
ones how many what how many cloths do
you need for a
seat
[Music]
um uh in total 100 cloth fragments okay
I that so keep hit curtains and hit uh
sofas and beds
everything uh what am I
I think I can make two more
bikes you got shot
[Laughter]
really
you shotgun parts
here six all the I wonder if at the old
house there's any shotgun parts there
might
be I'll go search I do I need
more I thought you were dead
is gas usually coming back for more huh
yeah oh no there we
go going to the old
house is there even a point in dying at
black oh mind these are empty could
check the trador
huh
tomorrow if only I had handgun
Parts yeah it seems we're all looking
for certain weapon parts I wonder if the
Traders have them though we might need
to just go check the Traders yeah I wish
they had them more
easily yeah a bit hard to
find seven shotgun parts is just a
lot oh that's a lot yeah yeah yeah that
is L
this for Pump Action level one oh yeah
yeah oh there's 39 cloth fragments next
to the forge yeah I know but that's not
enough that's the only my remaining ah
clo put some in too we're at 58 now okay
okay we need 50 more just just a few
more um so I'm making two more bikes um
but I guess today we're ending soon so
these bikes anybody can use them
tomorrow and then the day after too like
y whoever I'll just I'll probably make
more bikes tomorrow again if I have time
bik thank you yeah thank you no problem
everybody will have bikes at some point
that's
all yeah no one bike should definitely
be Callie's bike but Call's done online
tomorrow so that's just you know what
I'm thinking maybe I'll die this bike
black it will be yours but tomorrow
somebody else I guess can use it how
about that y sounds fine to me I'm just
very
[Music]
grateful oh okay whoa that's a a golf
bike yay bike I love like it
yeah let's go I think your bike is very
recognizable like a lawn chair taped to
a lawn
mower wait it doesn't even look so black
in reality what the
hell that's lame I'll unlock it
and oh okay uh your bike is outside we
only need 24 24 oh nice
didn't know we had so many parts to
really make so many mini bikes yeah I
made a couple couple parts uh the the
white mini bike needs some gas so it
might not work right
now but yeah feel free to take those
bikes and have fun with them don't break
them yay thank you okay I'll go try
finding
some cloth and Y gas
see gas
yeset maybe oh dear oh dear I can help
cook
hungry we've got
food who who WR bicycle
bicycle me cute bicycle bicycle
bicycle yeah we're really we have a good
stock of food so far very nice yeah I'm
cooking some stuff
too that would be helpful oh there are
tons of car batteries back at the old
place too oh there's a lot of good stuff
here
oo what time do the Traer Clos like is
it already closed I think it's already
closed if I if you find gas and
cloth please bring
it gas and cloth you got it gas gas the
old house also has more mechanical parts
or Springs or electrical parts and short
iron pipes uh or even headlights any of
those kind of things would be okay I'll
bring them helpful I mean I I don't need
them right now but headlight all right
I'll hold on to them gas as well um yeah
and mechanical Parts electric parts all
the gun
stuff you're doing a quest I'll come
with so I can find some stuff okay uh
it's a little
bit far though 45
vehic we can we can raid houses on the
way to find
stuff okay
okay cuz I'm just looking for supplies
right now
anyway yeah I think it would be nice to
have like us and stuff and just have a
good and the chairs probably also really
handy because then when we to when it's
more than a couple people tomorrow then
or on the last day then
Hyo in your inventory there's like a lot
of stuff like handlebars and then take
it okay how about the forg steel I know
you want forg steel though uh I need
four for seal so four there's nine I can
give you four oh there's there oh okay
well done if you give me my four you can
take the rest thanks okay I'll get i'll
gather it together for you
yeah I don't have any
corn I find that unusual
mhm the
water some Marky
water
uh oh I hear something
outside yeah he goes
raw no eggs either
I think there are eggs here at the old
place let me see if I can take them oh
there's one one
egg a single
nothing okay let's let's loot this
public
school oh heck yeah
okay we can jump over oh can we jump
over oh we can jump over oh yeah we need
a new back
door before we
end oh I can make a lot of steak and
potatoes yeah make a ton of baked
potatoes people push me oh okay fully
intact cars okay okay well I'm just
going for whatever's
close is it
working it's working here here climb
climb up this this I I'll push you down
the slide oh okay
okay what what are you
doing ready get play I'm ready I'm ready
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
push let's go to the school oh it's it's
so dark I can't see anything this one's
open to the left let's loot the
schools what oh CL fragment oh yes great
nice think we're going oh
hello
nice oh I'm bleeding oh I stabbed you I
stabed you I stab that was my fault that
was my fault I walk in front of you oh
take a bandage he'll stop the bleeding
attack anybody
else I made it just a time I used it I
used it you didn't kill me this time
don't worry
yeah cars give so many
resources I learn how to make
be oh I need
the
thing nice we did not die I do hear oh
they're they're by the door they're in
the door who is this okay well it's
locked so I don't know who thiss to wait
oh they unlocked
it oh
[Music]
no my go 300% damage can you make it
what the cam station 300 300% damage wow
whoa that is
crazy uh oh it's workstation level 50 50
oh oh okay leave it to me I'll get there
eventually no not yet but hopefully
soon do you guys know who has who owns
the crate in the basement level of the
first house I think it's
from not the one that's in their bedroom
though it's
laundry oh are you dying
oh five bottles of chamical which are
hard to find oh to make the wor
them I wonder where you get those I
should have been saving my beer I was
chugging it for for
nothing I have one bottle of beer that
I'll gladly give you oh there's so
many they do want
to yeah it's night time so it seems like
the on outside are also oh there's a
giant bear oh oh my God there's a giant
bear
oh what
it's like two people big
beer it's like as big as the boar in
that other bear a bear a zombie
bear oh wow I'm not surprised that's
kind of
horrific oh my God I see it oh my God I
see it oh my God they're having a good
time you think we can kill
it it's chasing
me
no my leg is broken
uhoh
water
any oh there
of e e oh God I'm Radioactive radio here
we go
again it's better for the environment to
use my bicycle I
can electrical parts oh it's day
six it has just begun
boy so yeah I mean I think we were going
to end in like 20 minutes anyway yeah
yeah s are you okay yeah I'm behind you
I'm trying to get this bird of you okay
I'll just keep
King keep kiing him but you're pulling
way and way more enemies I
think
en stop stop cting in a big big circle
small small circle small circle okay
okay okay okay I'll I'll start shooting
okay I have to heal dang kind of see why
they weren't cooking takes a long
time
ow ow oh okay watch out watch out it's
okay no it's okay they're distracted
eating my body okay I'm going to get
them all die die die die die
die never mind uhoh uhoh that seems
rough is it worth it all that death for
nothing well we got some good
stuff find any shotgun parts no dang
it I just need four
more oh God oh my God there's too many
of
them okay I'm going to ride away I'm
going to kite them on my
bicycle my bicycle oh man okay yeah kite
them kite them on your bicycle I'm going
to take them out one by one okay I'm
going to do a line back and forth on
this big
road you a
l they back and forth rather than a big
circle oh no
[Music]
no
uhoh when bread fed died in this house
we pump
pie
a yippe the door is back
[Music]
they so
slow we better get hecking exp for those
nobody needs
those for three
on uhoh it's over
it's giving me Minecraft Vibes right now
sorting these chests are you sorting
there's a lot to sort there there really
is oh man oh there we go
wow was nice
to
scrap
palus
no it's so go
over seems tough yeah we had a we had a
hoard
hoard okay it's only like six left seven
yeah we got
it I almost leled up so that's actually
pretty
good I can't be there to help him I'm
cooking cornbread right
now it's okay combre is important as
well oh yeah
oh I got
[Music]
rest I already know the secret recipe
cuz F told
me secret recipe oh for for sham sham
sham secret recipe I guess I'll make
before I end game
e what is that
sound why is
it is it yucky
sound my shot's broken I can't I can't
help I guess hit him oh nice yay level
I'm getting just so
distracted no I going to stab them while
they eat you
yeah I get him sneak up on him give him
the old one
twoo
ow okay I think we're
good any of
them just grab
this get six leather from scrap and
Furniture that's
awesome yeah it seems like we really
need claw right now
mhm honestly leather to everything every
material in the world what was that the
old house should we go back inside and
get some more cloth
yeah it's daytime now so hopefully they
won't spawn so much yeah let's just
ignore the giant bear there's a chair
there wait cotton crops
for
youo
mm we could make a cotton Farm oh my God
that be a good idea I don't know if it's
worth it I don't know cloth more duct
tape
yeah I got eaten by a giant dog oh
that's M there's a giant dog in the
school so watch out in the school in the
school yeah they went to the school
that's right
okay okay I'll
just that's where they went oh I'm oh
it's
over dirty cloth uh puddles puddles on
the ground can be
harvested beds also give cloth they give
like 10 or something if you destroy a
bed and they're pretty weak so maybe we
should gather as much cloth as possible
yeah
you know the school is not it's not safe
anymore there's too many inside the
school uh we might just want to head on
out so many
stuff oh I found the giant okay okay
okay just getting my stuff and I'll come
out
F get swarmed over there sorry I wish I
was there to help out let's go let's go
to like a house area because I think
that will be more yeah school might be
too many no I'm I don't have I don't
have a gun anymore so I'm kind of
useless oh do you need a repair
kit yeah let's get out of
here 4 a.m. I'll go to the traitor
really
quickly oh
my mini bike I don't know maybe we
should get out of this neighborhood and
just like find a solo house okay
okay
oops gas
pumps
no okay uh I guess we can pick up the
car pick it up as a I'll just try to
wrench everything storage that I can
find this won't give me steel right I'm
going to come on the little train that
could you can do
it well if that bike is waiting for me
maybe I can go yeah drop stuff off and
[Music]
swiftly this area is also six six heads
oh maybe you might want another friend
there to help out yeah we just we we
were riding on a road and there was a
giant hole in the middle and we fell
into it
oh do you have your bike I have it okay
okay
okay let's
see I'm going to put the forge Steel in
the crate next to the
forge
um okay I'm going to put all this
stuff I'm back on the seat
okay what did I come here for watch out
there's another hole
in the ground no don't oh okay
okay no road range people
please okay let's go to the east we'll
head toward the Traer I came to sell
here okay
clay what do clay
become farms and Forge stuff yeah right
yeah cool okay very useful everything's
useful nice a
spring the mod
somewhere
okay CU I'm good to go
there's so much in the way here people
keep
driving keep getting
[Music]
Stu we need a we need a monster truck
yeah we can put big big truck yeah want
like a school bus so we can all go
together yeah school bus would be good
this sounds
cute okay well I'm coming
he had so much steel I I bought a bunch
of Steel what a Ste black mini bike I
think this one M actually yeah that's
yours zero gas maybe I should put some
gas really Ste he really
yeah oh there might be a gas in the in
the car chest at in the kitchen car
chest okay think
is there yeah there is here I'll add
some
more one one full one full tank is 1,000
gas apparently 1,000 and I will get you
through it for a while it seems okay
thanks what was I doing
oh let me load it up
first yeah you know
how yeah I did it no worries
okay I'm going to go find them okay I
repaired my gun it's fine okay I only
have seven ammo though yeah I R I'm
running out of ammo
myself let's loot how do we can can we
make ammo yet is it can I can make it oh
you can okay okay there's a lot of
couches maybe they get C and the
curtains as
well I'm going to yeah goad I think nice
oh yeah the curtains give a lot of
give some as well okay Dam it are we out
of duct tap again yes probably no we're
we're getting there though I'm going to
work on getting a cotton farm and
then uh our water production is much
higher now nice though we're still
honestly if you ever see the water
purification Parts if you can buy them
we can always use more water I think H
water purification part
okay okay seems duck tap don't give
they're expensive where do I quickly get
duct tape CH oh screamer armor parts and
springs he's got everything I need but
expensive nice um do you have a single
cloth a single cloth I do not oh
we can look we have one more we have
enough for your chair there's a backpack
in here no be careful behind more you
saved me I like 6 hp right now okay one
hit and I'm dead she's
dead Springs are pretty cheap o let's go
upstairs I mean is it even worth it to
make a farm cuz it's so expensive to
craft the seeds I guess I'm like
confused on the ratio here
I feel like maybe seeds is something
that we have to like find mostly or
maybe if it grows once it keeps growing
I don't
know when you when you use it does it go
away uh I think it goes away then I have
no idea that's weird maybe you
need I do have I should I should make
you a level five farmer set behind you
behind you oh yeah maybe I should wear
that
if you can get me armor kits I'll make
you a farmer set but I think we have one
piece of the farmer set already not oh
my the best Traders are selling armor
parts by the way at this are you at a
Trader now yeah can you check if he's
selling duct tape let's see duct tap you
see no I'm going to go check out Jen
though next whoa you must
wo that's nice look so cool
careful don't run into it uh I found
serrated blade scha do you want that oh
sure cuz you do sword knives I
mean okay oh I think I already learned
it oh okay give it back here you go
maybe Bob has shotgun parts he
might is that better I think it's
better uh to which Traer did you go
Kelly wrecked I'm going to Jen now okay
so wrecked didn't have any duct tape no
duct tape sadly a lot of armor parts
though maybe like four or so I have 15
duct tape I can give you five I just
need one oh okay yes I can give it to
you oh that's big I
think yeah do I need to wait let me
double
check do you guys know if like if you
have an item um two I need two okay I
can give you that thank you
also Cy if you find a a crucible let me
know okay I'll check and let you know SP
wait we need we need one more cloth you
said a singular cloth a singular cloth
okay I have a lot of cloth but I'm not
at home but I will bring it home chest
struggling with the simplest things I'm
going to go check Bob first and then we
can head home see if Bob has some stuff
we
need I'll go to
Jen cuz she's cute I like
her yeah she's nice Bob's not bad though
he's friendly
enough oh yeah I guess so on the ranch
compared to what's his name
RX don't know his nameing terrible
ter I wonder who the next traitor is if
it's another cute girl
I hope hopefully oh I have to repair
fingers
crossed I don't know how often like
stuff respawns I think it's every day
maybe
w uhoh
b party fou party fou for
B apparently Crucible is pretty
expensive so we might need to do a bunch
of quests to get a bunch of coins yeah
up but he doesn't have it right I don't
know I'm to go check the other Traders
okay with your sick bike yeah that's
right I'm fast
[Music]
now disassembles your
bed hey said you could do that just
kidding disassemble away oh can I break
a bone can you take Quest from Bob
CeCe um I think so well I'm just giving
back quests so I must be able to right
oh yeah yeah yeah good I don't think
I've ever taken any from him but maybe
through you
guys greetings Survivor slap myol call
aan oh he's giving me a
bicycle I don't need it anymore hello I
needs forged iron
oh ammo crafting
bundle she's got shotgun
we
see lots of armor parts but what's about
okay I can't take any quests but I can't
see his in oh maybe it's because he's
busy oh I am I am talking to him okay
okay I do that
first now I don't think that she has
anything that we need
okay what are you guys looking for I'm
at
Bob shotgun parts for me what does you
need
Kiara I just need one duct tape right
now happy oh two two yeah I have are you
coming home soon I'm
coming
okay it's so far are you on your bike or
on the bicycle I got a bike let's go
home CeCe
good actually maybe I should fill this
up she's got for steel
though oh wait I have no
more ah Crucible yeah but I don't think
any tra has a crucible right
now okay Bob has shotgun part apparent
he does how many let me
see let's what rev your engine
Survivor that's big
I have no money
though I'm going to have to do a
quest go she's so nice even when I don't
buy
[Music]
anything I'm looting I'm getting lots of
stuff might have a problem my bicycle's
broken he has five shotgun parts I can't
afford them though oh that's okay that's
as much as I need okay I'm going to go
do some quests how expensive are they do
you know
450 okay I think if I do a a couple
quests I might be able to get it wait
your bike
Broke
bike oh no splint is not needed it's for
breaking your leg let me get on my bike
and get out of
here take some quests with her tier two
quests tier two
quests okay you guys doing any quests by
chance following my own path that's good
that's good I I really respect that I
would like to do more Quest cuz I'm
broke
now but I'm GNA go to kiaha First yay
thank
you
okay it has been about 4 hours we're
stopping at the end of day
26 okay okay
did you girls no um you probably did but
when you go to the challenge window did
you know there's a second challenge
window what what you
didn't milon oh my gosh XP points oh I
didn't realize until now chat told
me thank you K there's a bear thank you
K think I can f the
bear no problem I mean you you killed
the boar very earlier yeah this is a
bear well is it a is it bigger than the
boar I think
so I think I think you can do
it oh I need three points okay I don't
want to drink the beer
though this could be bad the bear is
very cute oh the bear is
scary he's got more reach than I do uhoh
I'm aning him fisticuffs oh no the bear
you can take
him I'm clipping inside of
him ah There's a Zombie teaming up on
me uhoh
boy I'm
dying oh oh
Magic that just Camp really Rocks come
on
now o okay okay well solo clear for myy
surely I can do it right oh wait we're
heading bear
nice have you didn't start it yet we're
like heading over there we can do we can
do your quest with you real fast yeah
I'll wait I'll just wait here
some
Stones oh my
goodness I exhilerating
do you feel powerful I do I killed a
bear here that's pretty awesome oh he
did hurt my knee a little
bit hello
meone it's over here the
quest oh is fauna not in my team oh Faun
you're on your own Journey okay I'm I'm
fighting bears in the wilderness in the
tundra f is fighting bears bare
fisted hello is here Hello's
do all right what I wanted to ask IIA do
you guys know if you have like two
weapons but one is higher level like I
have one five level five item and one
level three item how big is the
difference there the I wonder the higher
tier like the like for example if you
have a bone knife and a hunting knife
the hunting knife will be better than
the level five bone knife but uh if you
have the higher number it's going to
definitely be better oh
okay yeah but like a level one baseball
bat's better than level six Club I think
oh yeah M watch out I'm going to stab
you watch out it's
okay no worries and also we got to grab
supplies we have to get the supply just
one clock just a single cloth are you
still looking for a single
cloth kind of one I think I have cloth
hold on let me check I don't I don't
apparently cloth is a hot commodity that
we often forget about W look at this
game set up am i g
set
oh I didn't realize they let you reread
books in this
game yeah they let you reread books so
just make sure that it's not an open
icon I see I see make sure it's not an
open icon yeah if if the if if you have
a book and it's a open book icon that
means you've read it already oh I see
if it's a closed book you have not pay
more attention to that oh he dropped
loot what' he drop shotgun parts oh so
batterup volume six I've already read so
I don't need that but you need to drop
legendary
parts so but if I read it I still get
exp it's just it doesn't really teach
you anything new I don't know who else
is trying to do clubs but maybe we
should leave it for them is it really
that bad in here doesn't look that bad I
wanted to do clubs but I'm really like
so I'm not anymore yeah I got to wait
wait look look at it
I wait I just saw you where did you
[Music]
go he's dead
no he is wearing a helmet that's rough
oh oh wow he really you off the top of
the oh clear just got to find the
supplies now h k look look look yeah
look at my look at my spe
no I like your spear it's
very uh robust and looks like he can
poke things really good I think someone
Satchel is up here
uhoh might be mo you get up
there
parkour hardcour parkour oh there's a
ladder parkour there's a ladder
somewhere there's another bear how do we
do this get it I don't know if I can
take a second
bear can't take two bears the first bear
kind of wiped me
out
oh okay my satchels around here I
think
oh
that oh my goodness she's like shouldn't
you be done streaming by now
hello movie is like
late it's early it's breakfast time it's
breakfast time for
smovie all right is that a this is a
bookstore
H bookstore book it's a
bookstore abandoned one and half stars
but there electricity we did it find
River supplies Oh no just a peek
well it is time to end now
yeah end a sec it's I just want to get
the duck T yeah I I give you I just got
to find this stupid Supply I can't find
Quest real quick my
either yeah can turn in one Quest and
then stop so many books though we really
do need to do a season two it's just too
fun
yeah 7 days isn't enough
yeah what are you talking about we've
been here almost a month yeah 21 26 days
I can't find this I can't find mine
either okay I found mine never
mind I don't know how I'm supposed
to oh okay I got it I got it okay I'm
done okay hold
on mine's like super close but like
where is
it oh it's raining cats top of it
yeah he'll he'll have the shotg oh dang
it he'll have them tomorrow but I won't
be here tomorrow oh it
resets it
does you think he'll have shotgun
parts when I come back it's
a I hope
so can I mine the
carpet no
somehow Furniture keeps on disappearing
in this house and walls
too okay I found it y nice okay now I'm
heading back for the duct
tape where are we anyways oh my God
Traer
gen oh this
is's mine's here I'll head back to my
Tre so many books you guys are going to
be soy y oh boy f with the books hey yo
when that restocks we should go together
again
[Music]
tomorrow more book huls I'm going to
leave I didn't explore the whole place
cuz I'm a little
[Music]
scared good I got a bunch of books good
good good and I'm really
slow let's park this bicycle
actually that's a good parking spot
anyway but can I make it stand
up okay
where's okay wrong
way is that the it I gave it a is that
the
Kelly Kelly you're on your bike right
now right I got got off of it oh I'm
just turning in a quest real
quick
okay can we name bikes I wonder that
would be cool that be nice no we can't
I'm
confused well the colors will be a
giveaway whose bike is whose
but this one confuses me let's see I
don't want this it is Callie's bike
right yeah where did other bike
go I I have mine right you have the
purple one I have the one all CeCe on
the white one uh I have a bicycle G's
bicycle where did the other one go sell
these I mean it's my my my bicycle my
bicycle I don't mean oh there's one
right here that's yeah yeah that one's
from cie it seems AIT I think know
Callie has her bike doesn't she with you
Callie you have it on I have my bike
with me oh okay never mind then that is
the extra bike okay okay here you go
duct
tap go really fast too being so excited
about duct tape I
know the simplest things this this game
makes you appreciate the simple things
in life it does
Real uh I'm
CRA to
right and
then last but not least last are we
still one cloth short from a seat
CeCe I have lots of cloth I also have
some more cloth now yay I'm coming home
too okay oh you can make cloth from
plant fibers I should do
that at least I can maybe I write a
recipe no bikes allow
here and then for making a level seven
how do you do that Trad Bob he's just
down the
road Trader Bob is actually really close
to Trader
JY doesn't exist oh
okay um what time should we play until
you guys uh like now we should probably
end it now I'm almost home let me drop
off the books at
[Music]
least of
course
yeah two shotg parts and then I there's
a for ahe for like four more hours I
could I could totally play for another
four hours play for four more hours
but that's why I thought maybe the last
day should be like a super long day or
something but I also know you guys have
to sleep yeah no I don't mind I don't
need sleep I think um story Wise It's
probably fun to end it on a on a hoorde
right on a hord yeah yeah and one long
episode I think it's fine having the
last one be longer 4 hours it does feel
a little bit short I know right I I
thought that seven days would be the
perfect amount cuz check out these books
everybody oh books
bookies Anna brought a ton of book they
in the book crates
yes how many how many I'm going to take
a knife
Guy and
um and a handgun okay thank
you also you girls wanted me to make the
seat right with the cloth yes
please okay uh drop the cloth off of the
chest then I shall make it the forge
one uh yeah okay oh I put 70 here
earlier they're gone uh yeah they're
with me don't worry oh okay I'm going to
the rest in there I put I put more in
the wa okay bab he does not have shotgun
parts does he only have them for certain
people well Bob wait no why am I
learning that I'm Max yeah Bob Bob had
Bob had like three shotgun PLS but it's
okay I make stuff for everybody don't
worry dang it I think they are
gone what am I making seat
right their stock changes each
day take it missed opportunity I'll just
have to check tomorrow Springs Springs
spring what if I can make
a oh oops
thank you for the books my heart
bobk you okay I'm going to jump off guys
it was fun than for
playing up I won't be there tomorrow but
I'll be there on the final
day me sadly but I will I will be back
I'll be back I always am back byebye see
you
around byebye but a
finally yeah see you guys for the finale
then uh hopefully I won't be too
underleveled but it'll probably be fine
I
don't is there something that we should
be looking out for you in terms of items
tomorrow shotgun parts shotgun I need
shotgun parts and forged
steel yeah we everyone needs forged
steel though yeah so but we have a few
but yeah mainly that shotgun parts
really need shotgun parts for the for me
m
yeah okay I guess that's it for me all
right I'll see you guys on the last
day day bye everyone peace bye bye bye
bye and the extra seat is finished
yay now we can have even more people on
the bikes uh people I am the house yes
please okay I'll be outside did you
I'll I'll give the part to you you can
modify it okay I think you can so uh
there you go thank
[Music]
you
my you guys realize I can't find my bike
anymore how do you know where it
is our bike wait can you get on I just
want to test it
yay uh it's locked oh have to
unlock oh do I have to do it okay it's
unlocked look at those
nerds nerding together let's go oh ow
hey careful you have a passenger on
there thank you I love that there's a
drink holder there is there yeah oh yeah
there is That's So Cute that's what all
the duct tape is for is the light even
working uh in order to build this bike I
had to put in a light part but when I
look at it it honestly doesn't look like
has to turn it on no I don't think
so no or F press F press F oh F turns on
my night vision oh H maybe maybe no
maybe it's just our own love right all
right cool awesome we got a lot of stuff
done I have one armor piece that's
levels the maximum level level six oh
only one it gives me a lot more uh space
in my inventory too oh really yes cool
awesome oh yeah so now um I have a level
three Nomad outfit that somebody can
inherit from
[Music]
Me Maybe we need another chest just for
armor stuff because chest is a mish
mash yeah I wanted to organize
i f I'll put the fist in the fist or the
magazine box thank
you um where shall I put
uh I feel like we're in a pretty good
place yeah
yeah tomorrow horde
going
down yeah although I don't want to get
too cocky about it
yeah lots of food
cooking how about like bandages and
stuff like first eight
bandages how we looking on that we could
use some more probably we could use more
we need Aloe really I
think which I can also work on we can
also use some more ammo parts so I can
craft more ammo so we have plenty for
The
Horde yeah I'm just waiting on
crops oh aloe is in the desert maybe I
can go collect
aloe next
[Music]
time and then I can collect cotton to
make more cloth for
bandages although we don't have much
time until the The Raid oh okay let's
log
out I always carry this but I never use
it let's go
byebye okay byebye byebye had fun with
you girls yeah fun see you tomorrow see
you tomorrow byebye
byebye good game so we don't AF
[Music]
okay look at
that b said H maybe I won't play every
day and then I ended up playing every
day I already quit the game I I
remembered every day to quit the game
it's already closed
out it's addicting it's
[Music]
fun it's fun like collecting and making
yourself stronger and um all that
[Music]
stuff it's fun to work as a
team now I've become K I mean I are I
feel like IA I've already been as bad as
Kyla seeing as Ian
REO
DTA and now this
everyday grind grind grind grind grind
gr I've been Kyla I feel like I've been
Kyla from the
beginning just another version
if there wasn't if there wasn't a time
limit on the days I probably would be
playing longer as
well but we have to we have to keep uh
limits or else the hoorde will happen
without
us
okay
let's tell let's play how long we can
Yap
today let's let's play the game shall we
play stalling with bble let's play
stalling with bble oh boy oh boy another
episode of stalling with be what what
are we going to do up about
today
[Music]
okay parkour civilization we already
talked about parkour
civilization how does it feel like to be
the number one pker in the server you do
know that a lot of my kills were people
asking me to kill them
right I watched the clip of all my kills
so far and the majority of them was
people asking me to kill
them watch the clip watch the
clip watch the clip it is is a clip
video of the VOD watch the
VOD fake you guys are fake fake people
Watchers you can't you don't know that
most of my kills came from people asking
me to kill them when the vods are here I
thought you were here live I thought you
were watching every single one of my
streams live I thought you were keeping
track fake you guys are
fake fake people
[Music]
watches uh inside person thank you for
super Rock frog orange Justice
emotes watch my n m for me to go
B
um Moonstone thank you for the super
rock rock Moon demons thank you for the
super rock rock I read this super I
don't think I can talk about it out loud
because uh I don't want to get in
trouble with the company so I will not
read you super out loud but I do know
about the stuff and
wow I do know about the stuff and wow
and yes but I don't think I can mention
it out loud just to not get in trouble
potentially so thank you for the super I
did read it um and I do know about it
rock rock
it's just a little
risky
um so thank you for the super rock
rock uh hi B this is a bit late but
congratulations on the move to Japan I
haven't moved yet by the way this is
this is going to take like a long kind
of maybe like 3 month is process so like
I'm not I'm
not moving already I I'm just telling
you cuz I started the process but like
I'm going to take my no stop that is
wrong stop spreading the wrong stop
spreading wrong on the
[Music]
internet I'm not even in pad
yeah dang it
[Music]
uh I am jealous you're going to have
easy access to family Ticky now yes I
cannot wait for family
Ticky
congratulations thank you thanks thanks
everyone thank
you thank you family tick is so nice
I'll go get one after after this stream
thanks
[Music]
everyone I've already started to imagine
my
life when I move I'm going to when I
when I when I um I'm going to stream at
8: a.m. in the morning right and then
I'm gonna finish stream at about like I
don't know
five six seven eight hours in Whatever
Whenever I finish stream it'll still be
the afternoon and then I'm going to take
a book with me and I'm going to go to a
coffee shop and then I'm going to read
at a coffee
shop and and people watch as my reward
for like after after stream that's
that's going to be I want that to be my
routine
yes I'm going to look so
cool so
are so mindful yeah that's that's that's
my that's
my goal lifestyle in Japan is going to
stream stream for normal people time
after normal people time it'll be in the
afternoon the jst going to take a book
with me going to go to a coffee shop
going to walk to the coffee shop oh I'm
going to choose somewhere near a coffee
shop I don't think that will be much of
an issue to find somewhere near a coffee
shop but I'm going to find somewhere
near like a nice like local coffee shop
going to walk I'm going to and I'm going
to take the book I'm going to stay at
the coffee shop for an hour and read and
enjoy the atmosphere yes that's my
that's my
[Music]
vibe while wearing a cute outfit yeah
Normie what's wrong with that doesn't it
sound like such a nice little
lifestyle you
know I've always I've always admired
people who like sit in coffee shops for
like hours being like what are they
doing what are they working on what what
are they what but they they look so cool
like they have their like labtops out
and they're like working on their on
their stuff and and like using the wifi
and they're like they have their whole
setup in their own
table
[Music]
Yeah working on their
manuscripts okay fine how about this
then we'll make it a little we'll make
it a little bit more nerdy okay I'm
gonna I'm gonna after stream I finish
stream and then um it'll be the
afternoon in Japan and then I'm gonna
take my my backpack with my steam deck
and my Nintendo switch and then I'm
going to go to a coffee shop and then
I'm going to order my coffee and play my
Nintendo switch for an hour at the
coffee shop and people watch and then
I'm going to open my steam deck and play
my steam deck games as well there we go
is that better
is that better there you
go that's a little bit less
Normy more realis scky
[Music]
ey coffee sip sip play game yes
yeah that's that's my that's my dream
lifestyle
y actually don't do that I think it's
Jaan that is considered very rude like
talking on phon is I don't think so
people I that one time that one time I
went to I went to the coffee shop by
myself people were on their on their
like on their devices all the time
and and stop I think it's pretty
normal there are there are
like specific spots
where
um Papa even okay even even um what was
it
even like family restaurants some family
restaurants have like Signs being like
make sure you don't loiter but then I
look next to me and see like people on
their laptops working so as long as like
the place isn't super full it's fine
like if if the place like I saw when I
went to like a family restaurant like I
think it was like uh
it was either Jonathan's or or Denny's
but there were signs on the table like
don't don't uh don't loiter or like
don't you know be don't put take don't
work too much or something like that but
then I look over and the table next to
me has their laptops out and it's like
business people like working on stuff so
as long as as long as the place isn't
full it's fine as long as it's like not
a busy day is totally fine and it's not
like I'm going to be blasting my Switch
music
out I'm going to be using headphones and
stuff I people do not want to stand out
I I don't want to stand
out um which is why I thought maybe a
book would stand out less than a
Nintendo switch which is which is why I
was thinking book at first
but yeah
[Music]
why you go to a library because coffee
shop Vibe there's
coffee I want my aesthetic drink I want
my aesthetic I want to sip tip my
aesthetic drink and read my aesthetic
book okay
[Music]
I feel like all the cool girls are doing
that in Japan cuz like whenever whenever
I would like walk around at like the
train stations and stuff whenever I
would be like close to a coffee shop it
would just be full of girls sitting on
the seats sip sipping and doing doing
various girl things like hanging out
together
and yeah feel like that's what the cool
girls are doing going to coffee shops
and sip sipping with their
friends wearing
sunglasses I don't want to be a cool
girl I just want to be B but I do really
like the idea of just being healthy like
being
outside and being a
Vibe you
know the healthy part is like get it
going out of my house that's thing that
I want to be healthy
about cuz when I finish
stream it's too now it's too it's too
dark to go outside too dark
dark can't do anything it's too too dark
outside's
[Music]
Skelly how about before stay well that's
that's the best thing about if I move is
like I'll wake up good morning oh wait
let me just walk to the com beanie
really fast before stream to maybe get a
snack maybe I'll start eating before
stream will you guys approve then if I
start going into the comy and like
eating before stream oh my gosh no way
[Music]
wow
anyway uh yeah thank for super rock rock
good luck and have fun to say bab also
thanks for expanding P civilization L
yesterday no no
problem I know I know people are like
eat breakfast because like you need
energy throughout the day but I like
survive throughout the day without
eating anything really as you know so
how much of that is valid because I feel
like I have enough
energy I feel like I have enough energy
to not eat breakfast and still have
like a good you know bouncy bouncy
people energy throughout the day how how
much is that is that true
anyway I never eat
breakfast I'm not hungry in the morning
[Music]
well
yeah and we're talking about daily
schedule like
here my first meal is whenever I finish
stream so that's like 10 11 midnight
1:00 a.m. 2:00 a.m. 3:00 a.m. somewhere
around those lines if we're talking if
we're talking about my schedule
now wait you haven't you don't know that
I've been like that for a
year wait you did you didn't know
that girl dinner
[Music]
uh razor blad on thank you for the super
Rock Bo people watch your health for you
to drink thank you well do coffee counts
coffee coffee counts is that my first
meal cuz I have coffee um mostly every
day bab it messes up your metabolism but
my metabolism is fine
but I think metabolism is a genetic
thing it's part genetic some people
can't some people can be
okay is it not well I feel like my
metabolism is fine
[Music]
coffee stunts your growth well hey well
I didn't start having coffee until until
like way later because because they
didn't my my my grandma didn't let me
have coffee I didn't I didn't start
having coffee I love the smell of coffee
but no one let me have coffee so now I
can have coffee whenever I want so now
I'm going to drink it whenever I
want yeah and look I didn't have coffee
but I'm still short okay it doesn't
matter it didn't matter I'm still
short it's in my jeans I just have short
jeans it didn't matter if I drank coffee
or
not dang it
um Robert Panda thank you for the super
rock rock B please pretend I put
something witty here I can't think of
anything I finally was able to watch
stream happy way to end the day here's
my tax thanks for your tax wow that was
so smart what you just said
fascinating wow interesting
oh wow I never knew that that's so
interesting wow thank you thank you so
much for
that very very
cool uh three D thank you for the super
rock rock uh D4 thank you for the super
rock rock C thank you for the super rock
rock um birdie thank you for the super
rock rock B be careful not to let a fly
fly into
[Music]
the I swear I'm not going all as as much
as you think I am that's just the
tracking it's just the tracking of of
the 3D I'm not going all okay maybe it's
like slightly open and just going oh
okay it's I'm not going all all the time
okay dang
it thank you for super Rock of this
awesome yeah thank you for the super Ro
Bo hi buy today is my birthday hi happy
birthday I guess happy birthday to you
hump whatever happy birthday to you hump
I guess I hope you have a good birthday
happy birthday dear Pebble hump whatever
I hope uh it's a great one or something
happy
birthday to you rock rock thank thank
you for the super rock rock uh thank you
for the super rock rock Rob blue thank
you for the super rock rock um burying
be in the sad with no limbs was really
difficult but really cute fun and cool
time wait you did that I want I've never
been buried in the sand with no Lambs
before I wanted someone to do that to
[Music]
me I I so oh wait yes you did oh wait
yes you did yes you oh wait wait that's
a
spoiler uh the the beach episode is out
the the beach episode wait no spoilers
okay you're going to have to you're
going to have to go through the bble
route you're going to have to go through
the bble route to to
um find out what
happened yeah no
spoilers yes you go the bble route pick
bble find out what
happens you're thank you for the super
rock rock Rats on the move people please
have full go look after you uh they
definitely will but the goal is to be
able to look after
myself I'll definitely have a lot of
support from everybody but the goal is
for be to be able to take care and
become a strong independent rock
yeah but it is nice to have lot of
support and friends
around will you so call is Japanese B no
you can't call you have to go in
person it's even worse you go in person
to set it up
so that's going to be a thing the
horror in person yeah in person one of
the first things I got to do in Japan is
it when I go there I got to set up a
bank account but you have to go to the
bank in person and set it
up
yeah
Mama same thing with phone I got to go
to the phone store and set up a phone
and a Japanese SIM card that's another
step and then and then after banking
phone then
it's then it's
apartment yeah then it's then it's place
then it's finding finding somewhere
to house yeah and then you got to get
the utilities and internet and stuff
like that and then you got to
do you got to do furniture and and
um but you know I was I was going
to like move sometime this year
regardless so if it wasn't if it wasn't
wasn't moving
for like Japan it would have I would
have moved I would have taken time to
move somewhere else because I just want
more space to do stuff like home 3D yeah
so I was going to I was going to I was
going to move
regardless of Japan or not so I would
have had to take the time to do that
anyway and to run away from
ISP yeah just because I want more space
for things like
[Music]
3D it was mainly it's mainly a space
thing
yeah more space for be
merch more katas
[Music]
um D4 thinkk you wait hold
on no I'm not there yet Cesar thank you
for the super rock rock m and d thank
you for the super rock rock Virgil
statue no again I'm not getting the
Virgil statue that's too much that's
too
weird well not weird but yes
weird it's too it's too scary
add sunglasses I don't feel it it feels
weird I don't need it why because it's
like a it's like a big
statue I'm going to get jump scared at
night I'm going to like forget it's
there then like ha good boy ah and then
I'm going to start like smacking it with
a baseball bat because I didn't know I
thought it was an intruder or something
it's too scary
maybe I'll get a plastic I'll get a
plastic chair
though ah y thank you for the super rock
rock instead of expanding on game L to
St you from leaving what's a game lore
you haven't really read much on but you
want to find interesting to know more
about rock rock congrats on the J move
ah
Warhammer
definitely I guess is the big one that
we're all talking about
um if only the hord thing wasn't
tomorrow because if the hor thing wasn't
tomorrow I I probably might have skipped
and played Warhammer instead but the the
hor thing is tomorrow so I guess I will
play I will play
uh 7 days to die
tomorrow but I really I really just want
to play for
[Music]
Hammer why not both
h i could do a gorilla
stream let's see what kind of what
L I want to know more about dark Souls
Lore cuz I know a lot about Elden ring
but I don't know too much about Dark
Souls there's a lot of flavor text in
the in the weapons and the items and
stuff um there isn't one yes there is
Dark Souls Lore you just have to dig
it's not outwardly there you just have
to dig to find it and I kind of like
that kind of World building
uh
um re lore is pretty interesting
actually
um I love I love Ari games where they
give you the Lord dump at the very end
like there's a lord dump
room uh I remember I remember seven and
eight having that where like at the end
of the game you get you get a l dump
room and Bam there's just so much more
that you get all at once
Lord for Final Fantasy games are always
interesting like seven if I if I was
more into seven I'd be interested in
Final Fantasy 7 lore but I don't know
what's going on now it's it's like
timelines and and blah blah and uh
wow and like the the rebirth rebirth
what I wonder what's going to happen I
wonder what's going to happen cuz
uh seven has some interesting well it's
namora
so thanks
Deora Kingdom Hearts B like first
time how want a bake car all Ender
stream B will make us suffer I mean you
could leave whenever you
want but I feel like there might be some
Pebbles here who you know want to wind
down and talk cuz you know I haven't
been able to talk to you during the
collab so this is our talkie talkie Appy
timee
[Music]
I yeah I was talking to Mom
SEI um about
like growing up and she's like yeah
we're kind of the opposite of each other
a little bit where she has short hair I
have long hair CH wear pants and like
not cute clothes and I'll wear cutie
clothes and that's my style like our
styles are totally totally different
yeah
so
yeah that's what we were talking about
how like I never really got the
knowledge of like girly stuff because
yeah we're
totally totally
different mom
cuz Mom zi says like she never kept her
hair along she would ever since ever
since um when she was a
kid um she would keep it short oh yeah
she Tau me about Milo Buck or whatever
or Milo bus apparently
um but Milo existed when she was a kid
and
and there would be like
a they would bring like Milo to to
schools and they would have a stand that
sells Milo and all the kids would go
crazy for it because for some reason
when they made the Milo drinks in the
school it would taste so much better
than if you made it yourself something
something like
that so she was she told me a little
little bit
about
that Milo Truck Yeah Milo truck and
apparently she say like I don't know
what they put in it but it tasted so
much better then like if you made it
yourself event for all SE
children oh yeah she knew about oval
teen too I have never tried oval te I
only tried
Milo it's like Milo
oh condensed milk yeah condensed milk is
a secret I love condensed milk that's
why Vietnamese iced coffee is my
favorite coffee
cuz that is the condensed milk that's
the secret strong coffee plus condensed
milk the best
uh D4 thank for the super rock rock I'm
picturing people reading three copies of
Knife Guy magazine in Japanese coffee
shop I want to I want to live an
aesthetic
life that is that is my goal I wanted to
live an aesthetic life I want my you
know at home my PC setup to be like
super comfy and you
know one of those you can make like you
can make like a video of it like of how
aesthetic your your setup is and stuff
and then I want
to be aesthetic when I when I go outside
wearing my cute dresses and uh reading
reading books at a coffee shop in the
rain spark Joy
yes but I don't want to live an
aesthetic life to become an influencer I
just want to live it for my own
self-fulfillment you
know ew going out while raining what
going out while raining is the best oh
my gosh everybody hated it when it
rained like and like when it was like
boom storm boom but I loved it I loved
going out it was so fun it was so fun
going out in the rain and like when it
was storming it was raining so much in
Japan and I was like oh I love this
[Music]
weather even even when like like someone
the funniest memories where like me and
Sh having to go out into the rain
together and then the rain and wind is
blowing our umbrellas backwards so much
that it would break and we would just
like like wa this sucks yeah this sucks
great memory
yeah I would have a blast
[Music]
um H I thank you or super rock rock well
baby how many months has it been since
the move glad you're thriving in Japan
I'm not a Japan yet what
uh now do Elden ring Lord part three no
you
you no I
[Music]
refuse dang it you're gaslighting
everyone oh yeah they're from the future
[Music]
maybe um pet than thank you for the
super rock rock if you go to a
restaurant with family are you able to
order off the kids menu with no
[Music]
problems
yes I know you have a small appetite are
you connected are you concerned when you
walk in JP like the police might tell
you to go to
school um no I don't think so
because there's
school uniforms so there's a distinction
between school people and me people and
since I'm not wearing a school uniform
then the the police will know that I am
not a school person so
yeah po would only ask if like you're
walking around with the school uniform
maybe
so as long as I don't wear a school
uniform I'll be fine I do do have one
sailor dress though which is really cute
but that's not school uniform that's
just fashion so I don't think they would
mistake it I don't
[Music]
think wait no I have two I have two
sailor dresses but but but but they're
first of all they are so like one of
them is like pure pink and that is not a
school uniform so like they would not
no that is not that is not a school
uniform color so it would be it would
not
be distinct as a SCH
uniform I you fan Pebble thank you for
the super rock rock randomiz thank you
for the super rock rock hi people I
noticed the gem on your left ear shows
less now that you're on 3D more I miss
it taunting be able to do something to
stall wait what you want to see
it there now you can see it are you
stalling
there you can see it
now
m i do notice that I use my 3D more
than like the other I members but you
can you can see me move
more with my
3D and I can do more funny things with
it and the tracking for like my mouth
movement and stuff is not that
bad so like I feel like this is this is
2D but
like upgraded like this is my default
but upgrade the only thing I'm missing
is I wish I had
my I do miss
my but my mouth attacking is like really
good with this
one and I can do things like turn
I can do funny things like look at you
[Music]
from from
above
um but I
mean you know once once winter comes
around I'll start using my uh New Year's
outfit more too and like
then I won't be able to well then I
won't be in 3D
so winter is
[Music]
coming but yeah for now I'm having a lot
of fun with my
3D I like using it I wasn't I wasn't
told to not use it so I'm going to use
it because the tracking is really good I
can do things like
turn and do more silly I'm
silly I guess that's why I like it so
much I do miss once I get ah it's
perfect apparently it's still in the
talks to add her so
hopefully they'll say
yes I flap my wings
yes hly you can tell when I move more
cuz you can tell when I
fidget more with this one I think cuz
like it really
can see whenever I do
just can tell when you look at CH you
know what I'm changing back to 2D I'm
changing back to 2D I don't want you to
know when I'm looking at you I'm
changing back I'm changing back
tuty Boop
ha now you can never tell when I'm
looking at
you
ah
ah ah my eyes
back sure we'll stay to deep for a while
[Music]
well I still I still can
smug I can't look I can't look all the
way down but
[Music]
I have a
nose it's
around okay anyway
H
oh
ha ah wait wait what stop stop that okay
uh wow why let go let go let go let go
let go let
go stop let go
why
Okay
we okay anyway I got distracted we
distracted me again
uhuh uh uh gold gold jeel thank you for
the super rock rock hello people I want
to improve your tie tongue twister if
you can try this better not be the same
tongue twister where it's dangerous
[Music]
Mama yes it is it is the one
it's it is it is it is a grandma one no
no thank you thank you thank you
no no
if you can say it five times quickly mom
SEI will be proud of you rock rock but
if I say it wrong then Mom SEI will be
very very
embarrassed and I most likely will say
it wrong so also you I should have known
because you said these nuts and tie at
the end of your your your super chat so
you are trying to troll me
haha I knew it I knew I've already been
I've already been almost tricked to do
it
once I aware now you cannot you cannot
trick me haha nice
[Music]
try I li thank you for the super rock
rock Miss Kaki you've been denying the
whole allegations by our reporters
uncovered evidence of a fly actually
flying into your mouth on stream August
is 2023 Elden ring 11 1940 how did you
respond that was one
time that was one
time and it wasn't all it was I was
talking I think I think I was talking
during during when I so it wasn't even
an old problem it was a talking problem
okay
yeah I was yes I was talking so it
wasn't an old problem so that's my
rebuttal it wasn't an old problem it was
a talking problem so what you're saying
is I should never talk so no flies can
get in
[Music]
uh ter thank you for super rock rock a
Blake tutor or emo fun I thought your
swimsuit would be one piece for a kid so
this is surprise why does it have flaps
though also merch arrived will eat
Pebble merch soon please eat Pebble
merch why I like two piece it
one piece is cute but I like two
piece two piece
cuter and frails yes ideal is two piece
with
frails spoilers well you don't exactly
know what it looks like so if you want
to look you want to look look you have
to pick the bble route yeah pick the
bble route
[Music]
tmy they yeah they already released I
think U let me check X Twitter
[Music]
did whole live Ian post
it oh
yes yeah go booked a resort island trip
for Hall life English talents and hired
a vacation manager to help them you join
16 talents in their vacation to the
tropical island and Choose Your Own
Adventure style
viia oh
what's what's my witty quote
tweet help help me help me help me do a
witty witty quote
tweet about
it how do I promote
myself with this
um life's
beat oh COI
[Music]
tummy I think I think that would
actually work
it
would Beach
boo you know what I my brain is empty so
call Kaki
tummy post done
okay I couldn't think of anything else
at the moment so I'm just done Ki tummy
I'm
[Music]
done you didn't think I would do it yeah
I would do it I did
it now go go
go play bib boo
route can thank you for super rock rock
do do do you like my swim suit isn't it
cute it's very
B now I got to go play everybody else's
route to see what their swimsuits look
like
M yeah it's a YouTube thing it's like a
YouTube choose your own video adventure
thing
yeah How Stella thank you for the super
rock rock can you do smug face today
too I can
[Music]
ew what's
that go
shower you
[Music]
stink that what you
wanted you're
stinky ah
ah so much ah I miss my
ah ah my
beloved well all over here is pretty
good as well
um a thank you for super rock rock hey B
I've been wondering do you have an
official gem type for each color B in
prison naho some of them are easy to
figure but others are a bit tougher okay
uh red is
Ruby
um yellow is top
has
uh green is
Emerald
uh orange is what's an
orange
gem what's an orange
G
uh
topaz then what's a yellow
gem Amber I guess
to Yellow is TOA yeah yellow is to
what's
orange Amber I guess Amber
Works S I don't I don't know Amber is
different Amber is not exactly a dam
it's a it's a thing from tree
sap isn't it yeah Amber is not a d it's
a thing from tree it's threee resin it
could be
citrine
citrine uh one's green is
Emerald cyan
is
sapphire
uh blue is
Aquamarine and
then
uh Sapphire more blue but I think I
think aquamarine Works more because or
lapis Lai oh yeah lapis
Lai purple is
amethyst no okay all right uh blue is
lapis
lazery C is sapphire because Sapphire
comes in many many many different colors
didn't you know there's literally aquam
Marine is Lily S I want to use sapphire
in there though I like
Sapphire Sapphire is can come in purple
pink there's a lot of different
sapphires so I'm going to do I'm going
to do Sapphire for
sad and then and then lap is Laz for
blue and then amethyst purple there you
go it's be s
it's be it's be s b
side and then and then
magical goddess B is Diamond obviously
and
then
um what is it will be of his
obsidian or Onyx I guess it could be
Onyx too
[Music]
Onyx is B okay Onyx
that there that's your jams for prism no
Mah thank you for your
question m in a thank you for the super
rock
rock it's weaker than be right though
but default beu is beu light none of
those are default beu is is a thing beu
beu beu is beu like and pris N beu are
not none of them are default beu so like
would be he
[Music]
my m a thank you for super rock rock
Kingdom Hearts lore but the now ended
mobile game both of them is completely
required for the next game actually both
had really great endings yes it is
actually because the there's that
girl
sta who's from the mobile game and
you've already seen her in Kingdom
Hearts 3 and and Kingdom Hearts 4
preview that girl she's from the mobile
game if nobody knew who that orange
haired girl was um and master of Masters
is obviously going to be there
and stuff and then there's that that
other girl and that brain guy and a
brain guy is probably going to be there
too because sibling or something yeah
so if in summary what what the watch the
L video summaries of the mobile game
because the mobile game uh lore is
actually quite
important you just watch it
[Music]
yeah and some we do your homework so you
can know what the beep is going on in
Kingdom Hearts
4 cuz there's bunch of characters for
example that that random orange haired
girl with twin Tails who's like where's
where is she from who appears in Kingdom
Hearts for the the little mini trailer
the teaser see her name is sta she's
from the mobile game
you wouldn't know that if you didn't
know but she's also her voice is also
in Kingdom Hearts 3
and she
is mentioned in Kingdom Hearts 3 because
she is the friend
of two of the characters and part of
their plot is they were trying to save
her because she was yes the star was not
Chia it was not okay but anyway she was
still mentioned in three because she is
a friend of two characters in in the
main Kingdom Heart series and it's part
of their past so you should know who she
is
anyway I thought she was the star she's
not the
star
huh who is the star that
I thought she was the
star I the star the musical game
confirmed she wasn't the star well there
you go there you go you got to play the
musical game too you got to play the
rhythm game to get the lore for the main
game okay look at that you have to play
the musical rhythm game to get to
confirmation yes anyway
every game is Cannon and includes
lore black a thank you for super rock
rock can't wait for the pl potential
collabs and off collaps will come with
you living in Japan in the future you'll
get to hang out with your Senai more to
milk milk yeah I can't wait
and it will hopefully force me
to improve my
nongu thank you let's go
study um tring thank you for the super
rock
rock hi people greetings from Argentina
good night good night
greetings Neo HRT thank you for the
super rock
rock uh bble if you had the cast and
Hall Ian members as Elden Ring
characters who would who would play who
and
why can I be
any no I would be I would be
tarnished I'm going to I going to be the
tarnish oh Cece's going to yeah Cece's
I'm I'm
tonish CeCe
is
Ranny um
[Music]
oh G's blind
perfect sorry
dzy dz's blind CeCe is R
[Music]
oh sorry about that
Haka bails is
bail iris's iris's Moog who's
Mika wait no there's twins already okay
so wait who is who is Michela and who is
Melania
no Iris is
moog full m with Donna M oh yeah full m
okay so so uh
so f is Mika and mococo is withon
it'll makes sense the back
seating
uh Mia
that Nissa
because Nissa has some weird thing with
fla that I don't understand
[Music]
um yeah I don't
know it does it doesn't really match up
too
well but bble bble is the tarnished I am
the
tarnished and I will make I will become
the conort of
Cecilia I
yes sure is Gideon oh I guess
maybe anyway continuing on D thank you
for the super rock rock I like your 3D
all so much I printed it on 5 in photo
and pinned it on my desk now bable is
all always watching me
oh always
watching
always but but but but but have you have
you seen have you seen where is it have
you but but I could be Ranny have you
seen the best art of bab of all time
which is
this by Mo
Mama
yeah look at how cute Mo Mama did this
and oh look I'm cracked in everything
it's still
perfect I'm just going to keep this up
here because I just like it you can
stand right there Rony
be I'll move over a little
bit life life wife life wife
wife hello
hey get behind me you're not allowed to
be in
front you know I should make this my
phone wallpaper I I've needed an update
for a phone wallpaper may I use this
[Music]
okay
anyway
[Music]
um C over thank for super walk walk want
you to know that Aurora Borealis
activity has been especially active
during due to Stronger geomagnetic
storms I really want you to see one and
lately opportunities for those in the US
have gone up ooh I guess I'll have to
research if it's possible I want to see
one I want to see
[Music]
one thank you for the
infamous Aurora
Borealis I want to see in your kitchen
in my
kit taste haunted thank you for the
super rock rock Mo thank you for the
super rock rock may I see wait is this a
meme why are you saying may I see it I
don't know I don't know why are you
saying
that may I see it why in the kitchen
huh may I see what steam HS oh I think I
I've heard of the steamed H's meat may I
see it
she doesn't
[Music]
know I think I've heard of it before
question
mark Ste CS in the kitchen in this type
of year I might have to watch it to
refresh my
memory may I see
it yeah I I I think I've definitely seen
it before but I think like I don't know
maybe I didn't pay too much attention to
it
may I see it steamed
hams
[Music]
um one de thank you for a super rock
rock cute swimsuit in
the in the beach episode unfortunately
it proved that the hips did inde Li and
it was all dress no if it's the
artist sometimes beo is drawn in art
styles that aren't
accurate okay it was there are many
different artists and and sometimes you
know the art style doesn't match the
actuality
[Music]
you you just have to wait give me give
me my
3D swimsuit dang it give me my 3D
swimsuit
it's not just a
dress your voice acting has really
improved over the your PR thank
you face po thei thank you for the super
rock rock y thank you for the super rock
rock if people was buried in sand with
all the limbs Bur and only her head left
she will experience the hardship of
Pebbles every day hopefully she has
enough sympathies to make her lives
easier
no that's a dream to be buried in sand I
feel like it be so relaxed and just like
being buried in the sand just being
like I don't know what you guys are
complaining about because that's the
dream to be buried in sand and just be
like ah
so yeah I don't know you guys are
complaining over nothing I
think birdie thank you for super rock
rock bab if you curious about what's
under the pebble's bed or what's inside
the closet are you going to do a pebble
room review sometime I want to do that
but I want to give you more time for
more bbo merch to come out cuz I feel
like one year worth of bbo merch is not
enough like you only just got your uh
your
um B birthday stuff
right yeah so like I feel like I need to
give you more time to get B Bo mer to
set up your bab Bo stuff
yeah oh yeah Mom se's Bab merch birthday
came in and she was like oh yeah I got
the cup I'm not going to drink from it
though and I was like oh you're not
going to drink from it are you sure she
like no just for display display only
did she eat the pebble I don't think she
e the pebble
either oh like you should drink from the
cup M she's like no no I'm not going to
drink from the cup
yeah she sent me she sent me a picture
of it she has she has the if you got
both the cup and the pebble [\h__\h] the
pebble
[\h__\h] uh sits fits perfectly on top of
the cup on top of the BB boo mug it
fits the pebble can sit right on top of
the pebble a be mug it's very cute
together
here I'll send you a mom sty picture of
of her stuff I don't know what this
means
mom hold on
I want to send
it to damt so I can get it off of
Discord
uh all I check the picture check the
picture okay
[Music]
I just needed to transfer the pick thank
you you can ignore this
[Music]
this is M shi's merch
what does cough your me mean mom what
does that mean
nine M what does that mean what are you
trying to
say press N I guess I guess she also
likes to press
nine also look at how many Pebbles she
makes I think this is her hobby now just
collecting little stones and making like
a a little pebble
Pebble collection and she likes to send
me like pictures of her arranging the
pebbles in different shapes like there's
another picture where she arranged the
Pebbles into like a nine thanks
Mom yeah she likes she likes he likes
the Pebbles a lot I
guess Mama but yeah that's that's her
that's her merch got her merch
[Music]
thanks
mom
um cool thank you for super rock
rock um K thank you for the super Rock
Rocky thank you for the super rock rock
M thank you for the super for rock
rock um as I am not artistically
inclined to draw something please accept
the Super Chat as an award for being top
in the top tier of people who
understands Kingdom Heart Lord thank
you it hurts my brain cuz I have to save
a whole section of my memory to remember
Kingdom Hearts War cuz it's just so
convoluted so there's so there's like a
space in my brain that has to be
reserved for that because it's just you
got it's got got to separate from
everything else because or else it's
going to get all confused in so the KH
drawer
yeah thank thank you rock
[Music]
BL a great new thank you for super rock
rock this rock is super cute in all her
outfits ha thank you thank you I think
so too
[Music]
um I've ran out is there anything you
would like to Yap about otherwise I am
going to BU by time to dive into nearl
oh I love near
lore oh there's one
more I've only played automata
though I Al I also really like draging
guard read
lore it's connected it's kind of
[Music]
connected it's all
connected
Yaro you're mad
M
um yay thank you for the super rock rock
mom se he loves this pebbl so much maybe
she can give us the limbs we wanted no
she won't give you limbs
no she's going to text me isn't she
she's like Babble give the Pebbles what
they want
no
no don't you can't ask Mom sey I'm in
charge of you I'm in
[Music]
charge h
okay yeah go play the B Bo route
on the this thingy I am out of here now
I will be
playing um more 7 Days die tomorrow
because of the H thing so I will be
continuing tomorrow mhm and then the
last day is the day after I believe and
then uh we
will get back to regularly scheduled
bble uh Alan Cloud this week
is five asmo
on
Thursday so that's the
thing plasmo announcement oh
yeah I will not be playing at VR though
since it is a
collab no gorilla plans well last thing
is 7 B die kind of starts close to bble
time so like if I wanted to start a
different game at like 400 p.m. I would
only have an hour and
then and then I would have to
[Music]
swap because I play I play the entire
the
entire time and then now it is 11:00
[Music]
p.m. schedule happening this coming week
yeah yes I could schedu it
up I'm grindstone collab this week I was
like
KY h
a let's
collab so we will
mhm
um cool thank you for super rock rock a
quick note the grandma one is absolutely
okay to say in the D direct translation
Grandma eat long again her drool drips
drop Dr it's already a tongue twister in
English how am I supposed to do her
drool drop her drool drips drop
down and there's nothing bad you can say
only gibberish confirm with Mom SE
please okay Mom SEI is okay if I say
this tongue twister if it's okay I'll
say it next time
rock
rock yes we're doing Panic cor I believe
I'm kind of nervous about it
because jump scares but I will try to be
useful she said she said she said it was
an as bad
as as the hour I think she said it was
easier than to hour so it's to be okay
it should be
okay I think I
hope it's easier but
scarier I'll be
fly I'll be
fine you had it rough yeah I did have it
pretty rough with
devour because I'm not good with dump
scares where it like takes up your
entire screen
[Laughter]
FNAF I can't do
F I mean I guess I could but I can't I
could but I can't I could but I don't
want to
[Music]
maybe I could if I turn the sound down
if I turn the sound all the way all the
way
down
maybe did you get PS Silent Hill too let
me
check I don't think so because I didn't
get a notification that I didn't usually
I get the notification
so I think it's still
pending yeah it's still
pending but I think this weekend
apparently was a a holidayish weekend in
JP or something like
that so like some of my stuff this
weekend that I wanted check just pending
or something yeah it's all it's a
weekend in JP right now so I have some
stuff pending
pending also in Thailand
oh it's a public holiday oh
oh it's Thanksgiving today in Canada
Happy
Happy Thanksgiving
Canada what what is kind of to do for
for Thanksgiving what do you guys
do do you have you eat
turkey turkey you e is it the same thing
same thing we do oh almost same
[Music]
turkey less football
L football turkey with maple syrup wait
is that actually true do you eat turkey
I think well I guess turkey with maple
syrup would make sense because like
there's like honey glaze and stuff so
like a syrup glaze would make sense for
turkey
[Music]
tasty I eat it
I love turkey legs whenever whenever I
go to like a an amusement park or
something I have to have a turkey leg I
just feel so powerful like holding one
of those giant giant turkey legs smoked
turkey
legs the big yeah it's interactive food
you remember how B loves interactive
food I love turkey lakes that reason cuz
you feel so powerful you're just
like and then I'm like ha it's like
Monster Hunter style yeah Monster Hunter
style do you finish it a I do my
best I do my
bad I mean that's what I do that's what
I do myself for Thanksgiving is I make a
singular Turkey Leg for myself
s since it's it's usually just me on
Thanksgiving I will just that is my
Thanksgiving dinner is I will just make
I will roast a singular Turkey Leg for
myself and make some mashed potatoes on
the side and that is my Thanksgiving
dinner roasted turkey leg I've Gotten
Good at it though I've got good at the
turkey leg
[Music]
thing yeah let's let's share turkey legs
together P
was let's all let's all roast turkey
legs and eat turkey leg together
for
Thanksgiving wow well the thing is
I don't know I don't know if it's common
with Asian families but my my family
really well my family really doesn't
really celebrate
holidays very seriously anyway
like we we celebrate holidays very very
casually I guess yes
so yeah celebrate it very very
casually so if Thanksgiving just eat
food that's it eat food Christmas well
Christmas we just Christmas
tree presents like the normal sound to
things but like we've never really we're
not the type to go like all out
on on like holidays and stuff it's just
like casual
[Music]
celebration what's my favorite
holiday I like Halloween I like ch
man I
[Music]
yes I wonder if Santa
will eat my cookies this year last
year I made cookies for
Santa and when I woke up
none of the cookies were
eaten
man maybe this year we'll see maybe I
haven't been a very good
people look look look cies were good I
think I think they were good
cookies but there wasn't even there
wasn't even a bite in it so Santa didn't
even try
that so then I had to eat the rest of
the
cookies
boy okay anyway
[Music]
I should go get some dinner and stuff
and go about the rest of my day day time
day I you I'm not
asleep I have to go about the rest of my
night late night night and then I'll
sleep my day just started
[Music]
I have homework to do today I think yeah
I do I do have homework to do
today okay thanks for the Yapp Yapp Yapp
yappy yappy yappy yappy yappy yappy
yappy thank you for watching our 7 Days
St thank you for the yappy yappy yappy
yappy y let me check
for soers to make sure I didn't miss
anything and and we will
U oh okay Daniel Victoria thank you for
the super Rock bye uh thank you people
for the
stream and the comfy Sunday night happy
comfy Sunday I hope you're Monday will
be good uh don't be late to work um
don't be late to school make sure you
did your homework uh um and I hope it's
not too bad of a Monday cuz sometimes
people hate Mondays uh so let's start
off your week
good rest well see you oh yeah some of
you have a holiday enjoy your holiday
Monday what out thanks
everyone
be
later oh I also the 2D has the up eye
I miss my up eye my eye
smile this isn't how the eye
smile I can't wink properly now I can
wink properly huh
huh huh see you later be
[Laughter]
all I'm I'm send you a secret message in
Morse code be later bye-bye he
[Music]
oh