[Music]
all
right
[Music]
we're
starting my
game we left it again oh I wonder I
wonder every time I change every time I
change on OBS it probably crashes okay
this is so
cursed we're ready oops not
anymore if you guys see do you have AO
PC no I don't this has never happened
before recalibrated on my on my screen
for some reason that's crazy she can be
behind
me next to you wait Can you can you move
yourself um to the to the right maybe to
the right right is can can you move
yourself is I don't think I can
um right side look look on YouTube yeah
yeah yeah look on
YouTube um you should be on the right
side is oh I guess I guess the placement
is like different yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah you a little bit a
little bit a little bit to
the there we go a little bit to the left
there we go I think you're too too
big I'm a big cut means B cat yeah but
you're in too you're intruding you okay
no get out of
here is that
okay
um I I think it's
okay yeah it's it's all right it's it's
okay with you it's okay yeah it's cute I
don't we're all set I think okay today
we're going to be playing
boot roulette
[Music]
multiplayer we sound we sound with our
yay it's almost as if you're playing
some kind of Teletubby game but is it
not
no it's be fine okay I'm here see okay
okay she's here she's here good yeah I'm
good okay when was the last time you
guys played this game when it just came
out
when we first started playing it when
was it I
forgot um yeah like a while ago April
is I forgot how to play
it I forgot too but I remembered right
before the stream before the stream I
practiced like one round really really
yeah yeah have to remember you're so
serious there a competitive what is this
you want to shoot us that much huh I
thought we around you want to kill us
you want to murder us and get all the
money no you know there's only one
person in this room that I really need
to you know take care
of no but so you know just to make sure
that everything goes according to Kaku
you know you know you know you're going
to change yourself okay I know this is
Ana's chat but you guys better help me
count as well oh my God imagine chat
like counting for all of us oh my God
please help us oh my goodness yes I'm
getting like OCD because like this side
here is like cut like yeah hold on
should I move like over here and then
I'm further away from ra oh you can you
can you can move back I think it should
be fine okay okay okay
boundaries thank you social dist social
distancing social
distancing let's introduce ourselves
then okay I'm I'm like above in the game
so hi everyone it's an moisa from Hol
life ID second
generation I'm going to gamble
tonight oo gamble for your
life I love gambling mhm
don't
we you wish I love you as much as I love
gambling won't be able to tell if you
didn't tell
us okay you want to go kiaha Oh Me Oh
wow after you me below me at the game
why are you below me at the game you
you'll be below me at the end of this
you'll be lying on the ground bleeding
out no that would Beed don't you worry
okay uh warning for everybody who
doesn't know me and Ana have a thing
going on where we say we hate each other
it's of course a joke but you know don't
worry guys we just hate each other so
much no it's not a joke I hate her so
much there's no particular reason it's
just it just kind of happened but yeah
I'm Ki from H life English myth yay we
it seems like we're kind of like a
Europe gang versus uh ID gang right
let's go let's
go it's time to fight
Okay who wants to go next um I think you
want to go hello everyone I am from
English Justice and I'm a big c means
big trouble for you Ana
and e
[Music]
e brain Ro
everybody bra I stuck in my head again
what did you do saying that my voice is
quite low oh really did it turn yeah I
um I don't know they're saying that okay
okay um can you can you talk
now
everyone is it is it good now is it good
now is it any better is you be
maybe maybe should be
mhm okay nice eventually scream okay
okay beautiful yeah is at like um 200%
now
my
yeah okay
rainy okay attention please I'm Pia
rainy from H life ID generation to same
generation as Ana actually
am I going to be on today of course it's
myself say my
side no we're all on our own let's have
fun guys let's
[Music]
go back shot back shot
rouette back shot
rouette
okay by the
way hi hi do you guys see the start but
cuz does any of you guys see the startop
button cuz I don't see the startop
button only Lea table
and it just hit
me I don't see either it just hit me
that oh wait I left the room by mistake
oops oh there back yeah how did you
start this how do you start
this find players to play with I I don't
think I don't think so this is the game
this is the think about this this the
game this is the game so we just start
playing now guys let's go round one
amazing oh let's try to go to the main
menu maybe we start the game from the
main menu oh return to main menu and
then okay really really no I'm not
assuming oh I I press return to main
menu yeah but now you're not in our room
yeah the when you girls are pressing
that
you're leaving the room yeah you're yeah
you guys are leaving the room
okay okay
multiplayer I'm going to go to
multiplayer again I didn't realize there
was no start button I also didn't
realize like it just hit me like when I
see I'm like wait hold on don't worry we
have four brains we'll figure it out
we'll figure it out easy
no like are you are you the host are you
the host now should I make a new room it
it doesn't yeah let's just make a
completely new room so that has the host
again oh okay okay
mhm yeah cuz I didn't have any any
button either now even though I might
have been the host officially I don't
know all right H H hmer okay okay this
will be quick this will be quick this
will be quick I'll post the code um on
Discord yeah I don't even need the
code oh yeah um okay so I host table oh
wait I know why we have to put in the
lobby code because the the button for
join with Lobby ID is like a copy paste
like it uses
your sug sug amazing need the code okay
we can you join now we hosted
on it no what the same code or what okay
I'll give
you I'll give you copy Lobby ID yes yes
yes thank you okay that's a very long
code I'm here nice okay I'm in too can
you start the game now
or maybe Lea table no not Lea T table no
table Lea table leaf table is exit
Le now you have like kick and stuff
that's new right that's true that's true
but still no stop then wait is it like
loading hold on is it like there's like
loading loading dots under my Lea table
dots click those I'm clicking them
nothing is happening oh anther
no this feels like a Deja Vu you know oh
there we go start game it was
loading oh there we go
there what there we go I'm not here
anymore why why where go I got kicked
out main menu main menu main menu
restart
restart restart restart PR press ESC
disconnect disconnect disconnect
disconnect okay so it does work yeah
that works it does work it does work but
I got St all right I'm going to I'm
going to um I'm going to okay the code
is the code is on
Discord I mean okay all right is a new
one yeah today we curs by the way from
the
start start G
start all right okay there we go that
was that was short that was short that
was we go four players yay yay let's go
let's go nice let's go I don't remember
a single thing about this game is so
loud the club music it has to how to
play wait there's a new item that I have
no idea what it does what the heck oh oh
shoot I don't remember what these are
what what is that wait for some reason I
cannot I get so many of the samees
select anything you have to click the
inside of the B you have to click the no
but there is no cursor there is no
cursor in my there's no cursor no
nothing wait
what yeah well I don't have a cursor
right now anymore either you you didn't
take out your items no
yet no a I guess we can I guess we can
restart I do have a cursor when I click
ask you know just for the main menu oh
it dis gu the game is bugging look I
wait you're not using controller right
no I'm not with controller okay I can
try to disconnect my controller just in
case but is this mode Bugg no it doesn't
work either all right I'm going to
disconnect and then I'll try out let's
make a new room I'm so sorry
everyone you can try restarting your
game just in case that usually yeah that
usually fix that usually fix restart the
game for
sure I mean it's a new mode it just got
released like a few days
ago okay another one okay give me a
second sure yeah it's Mouse okay
okay I did play the game before
so like it it was working perfectly
so yeah I think single single mode and
multiplayer mode
well I'm glad we we we disconnected
because my items I I didn't like them
there was no
variety yeah I think I think my items
were were kind of you know my items were
kind of spicy I got like something I've
never seen before I got like something
I've never seen before I am in the room
again okay oh there we go okay start
game ah start the game is about to start
hopefully this time works yeah
okay come
on here we go let's go round one four
lives and four it oh nice okay good oh
yeah there's an item that I've never
seen before Oh man now my items are free
items wait wasn't it four items oh I
guess it's like randomized yeah
randomized like depending on how many
you know that's girls no
no okay who turn is's turn is that why
we're looking at her guess so okay are
they
still what and then you you choose which
one out of the free you shoot for though
it's
for wait what the h i misclicked okay
oops I mean I mean I mean that worked
kind of work I guess yeah don't you get
another yeah she got get your item
hey it's time to shot oh my
God no you wasted my oh my goodness oops
you wasted
it okay it's R now it's rain am I last
what the heck
what's beard do I
forgot uh it it ejects the current shell
Yeah so basically just thrs out what's
currently inside
oh oh she just casually sh
her
okay hold on
so okay let me c oh she calling huh wait
so it's
like fourth shell from now or fourth
shell from like the first
one I think from now but maybe think
now
um this will go well oh
okay now you get another turn
yeah why you looking at me don't look at
me
is this going to be a thing where
everybody gangs up on the one who
already has the lowest HP just to get
rid of them I mean yeah that's why I
shot you that's pretty much why I shot
you not because you're my
enemy yo sorry I was looking for the
server and I just got disconnected I
think oh really
no um I was looking for so many servers
wait now because I got shot twice I kind
of lost track of what I think I I think
I still know is it like it's hard to I
was
Atty
[Music]
the you can shoot me shoot
me
aha she's calling ah I'm using this uh
this new item oh the new item I thought
that was it's kind of it's not really a
new item it's still to skip your turn
like uh um cuffs but you choose a
specific opponents okay okay okay
[Music]
anyway yeah yeah go go go
go you're
crazy I had a
feeling let's go so rain you got
disconnected uh yeah
earlier oh okay only in VC only in VC
yeah
okay wait why skip the
turn because I put the Jammer on you the
item no not
[Music]
me okay why are you so
excited I am excited that that last one
was going to be a live one cuz I used
the cell phone so when R was looking at
me I was like no no there's so many
beard on the
table blanks okay no four Tre okay four
four four live three blanks four Liv
okay okay it's my
turn
um I can use this oh no it's not my turn
yeah it's turn yeah cuz we're like oh I
ejected
alive oh I see
no I feel like this is going to be live
one who's going to shoot who
shooting
shooting things from shooting
me I was so it was going to be alive
tree lives
tree ah there's another new item I think
snaps to
what swaps turn order a so it goes the
other way around I don't know that item
is it like inther
no wait did I just fuck ah I thought I
thought the beer I don't know sometimes
I get the beer and the cigarettes
confused I feel like the beer is going
to heal me but the cigarettes heal you
oh
yeah that happens uh well then I'm just
going to wait what the beard dolls try
I lost
count okay
okay
no oh the polarizer is it okay let's see
what's ins is that the new item's name
polarizer oh oh I'm going to kill myself
no you're not going to do it because you
know what's inside I know what's inside
well
well who I'm going to
Sho maybe
Anna what never
[Music]
mind my turn it's your turn yeah I
changed the rotation of the did rever
yeah yeah yeah yeah well it's got to be
a live round now right no it's got to be
it's
50 no
no you believe you
believe why are you looking at me I know
I don't want to go for the lowest one
necessar was supposed to be my
turn understandable that was that was
unfair okay sorry I have a bunch of
items now what the heck there so many
item so many items we do we got to
use okay one
31111 wo wo that's crazy okay
uhoh hey you're you're ejecting you're
jck why are youing oh I mean you know
okay wait imagine if this one is a blank
one there's no way
right well I don't
know there is a way I got to use my
items another one cuz when the round
ends like it was the one it was the
blank one
I'm scared I'm so scared I'm so scared
no no no no no no no please don't how
much he do have no no no no let's make
the game longer let's make the game
longer
Ana longer how how much longer do you
want it to be let's just a couple more
rounds come
on yeah no no my God
Jesus
RP it's so funny well well
well my revenge will be bitter not
sweet they be W for it oh my God you Ed
you didn't use to oh my
God I'm alive violence alive violence I
just of violence violence is
always they do hate each
other
yeah this one's going to be
fun two two huh all right it's my turn I
need
toy making enemies
SMY SMY
Smokey I'm going to do okay what like
two and two right yeah
yeah
noting was that my screen is black and
white now that I'm dead so I can't
really tell the colors apart really
yeah was that also a live one was that
live I guess there's no more there's no
more blankies yeah yeah I know I know
you'll do that I know you do that ah I
guess
not oh to change your rule I no I I
messed up I messed up I the wrong one oh
blanks wait so this one this one is
alive right wait I thought it was all
blanks what did she use oh cuz it CH she
changed I think yeah I the polarity is
this is this I I lost count is is this a
live one is this is this A blank one
well I
mean I guess it should be alive cuz
otherwise it would be end of round yeah
you know what I'm I'm going to why don't
you try on me yeah
just oh okay oh okay then okay oh oh and
you got you can cut it up too right oh
my
God is Hardcore oh
God out from blood ra do you do you want
me to keep you alive
or I mean you know what R still has like
four lives like that's going to be a
[Music]
what I never shot you once pleas never
shot you once remember that
yeah but now you're not going to go
for no no no no I never good things
don't come from shooting me you tried to
shoot me once I me the marrier the you
know the marrier the more fun right I
guess so shoot me
there that was bad that was bad as r
okay shoot
me okay whose turn is
it all
right I hate
you no feelings no hard
feelings no hard feelings stop no hard
feel
no just a little fun game you know she's
calling
someone she's calling someone what the
ghost said wait was it was it tree tree
I think it was tree tree she killed
herself nah
[Music]
she careful
please has
confidence I'm going to try
[Music]
another okay okay okay I know how it is
oh no oh oh no she can see she has the
third eye I do see I have the good eyes
oh she has the thing though oh
[Music]
no she's healing back up you should have
killed
her I spared you right I yes you're
right yeah I didn't kill you
okay okay this is
Hardcore okay wait I wonder can I can I
steal your items
Kiara oh I think yeah I think so taking
from the
dead I'm going to try I'm
curious oh I can okay no but why don't
you take from the other members because
like the less items they they have the
less heal they have to succeed oh wait
you have a
yeah
oh
okay
okay she has so many knives I don't even
know how yeah stealing from her but then
she keeps getting more
mhm I'm a treasure Trove too Moment of
Truth uhoh Moment of Truth hat you want
to reunite me do you hate me more or do
you
do you hate me
more oh my God be like spare me please
don't kill me I mean you won die she
won't
die but again again you go for the one
that she couldn't die again you go for
the choice that makes the game longer in
killing one yeah cuz you know the merer
I learn from my
Lon you know I don't know I don't know
what it
is what's the what's the what's left I
don't know I lost count too I lost count
I lost count I kind of lost count I'm
not going to tell
you fine wait I'm going to I'm going to
I think I know I think I know I'm going
to take the
risk wa is finishing those jobs for me
thanks okay hello I'm scared she's going
to kill me I am a ghost yeah I knew it I
mean there was only lives right so just
in case I'm going to do
this you going to heal up uh-huh and
then okay yeah okay okay
okay let's go hunting us I think she's
winning yeah I'm going oh my God I'm oh
my God I'm dead that's a lot of
inverters ooh that's a lot of in that's
a lot okay
I am so dead ID show down oh it's your
turn
though oh is that wait is that the new
item what is
this how do you use
that what is
this big how do you how do you
select I don't know how do you use
[Music]
to well
inverter is swap spooky spooky spooky
big cat what's going on what's going on
didn't you c as ghost prite yesterday it
kind of fit wait what what was a ghost
prite yesterday on the was it a corpse
briide I think I yeah it was a corpse
briide oh corpse briide yeah I play as a
ghost on Halloween oh my
goodness yeah it was so cute had like a
whole cute aggression every time I see
you
uhoh what see see right every time you
see ra yeah every time I see yeah every
time I see ra well I'm going to die I
think wait why is it TR turn again
what what why why did my turn get
skipped is it cuz of the the G on you oh
oh I see that's what oh that's what the
new item does okay
okay okay what is it okay it's over it's
so
over black and white do you have any
last
words
uh kind of forgot what the inverter does
actually what does it exactly do does it
turn live to black or what um the
inverter
yeah it
Chang and vice versa blank and VI
[Music]
Versa I'm round two we got five
lives just slowly remembering over I got
a new item is that the okay cool
items kind of
cool welcome back everyone welcome to
my turn okay well then I'll take a look
I guess I'm Al I haven't played this
game for I don't know I'm just slowly
remembering what things
do uh I don't even remember anymore what
the what wait what what is going on huh
I swear that was that was black I'm
confused that wasn't red my my color in
the game is wrong H wait what
no I guess you can try um
shooting someone when it's blue if
that's the case maybe maybe it's Red is
life right R is it was like gray or like
blue grayish I
swear yeah blue grayish she'll be bad BL
ouch it's definitely not red
no I'm so confused what the if I was
streaming I would check my Vlog
[Music]
but
feelings that's exactly what it looks
like it's my oh I lost
count okay our universe wait so I lost
count too lost
Sor
um um no this this
same face is this a new
meta is this a new meta
guys well well that Happ thank God thank
God I got a magnifying glass I need it I
lost I lost C okay four four wo
wo let's take a look good life for blank
well okay
I I saw the color okay let's let's try
let's try yeah yeah yeah uh wait let me
heal first four
life no four life for blank
yes okay this
this nice nice nice okay um now I don't
know what's in next but I'm going to
race for the biscuit yeah ooh
ooh haa you buy
[Applause]
little no
shot no shot okay okay okay wow let's
see you guys are remember I remember you
remember do you remember I I'm already
I'm already almost crazy once stop oh my
my God yeah yeah yeah yeah what's going
on she's confident oh my good skip the
she's going to jam someone
okay yeah no you know the merrier the
more fun
I'm no I mean you used the knife that
means like you know I only have one life
was to use a knife on
is always but you shouldn't say
that I'm just I'm just showing that I'm
neutral around here
right establishing my stance you see is
that so or maybe you should have gone
for the overkill you know like you never
know feel was like it would feel
probably are really important yeah
that's actually pretty
hard yeah right what about I do it
anyway
oh crazy cat
lady how could this happen
tradition
why ohip ah you made me skip my turn I
see yeah yeah yeah no this should be two
blank two lives so it's
5050 you're counting I I also lost count
again oh my God so
you don't even know you're still cutting
it off oh I'm going
to I'm going
CH not me though I just shot
myself that's
true well this is always the first time
for
K what mean first time you shot me
before I'm pretty
sure I was your first shot today I lost
P wait I lost
H okay if you don't shoot me I tell yous
sorry what if you didn't shoot me I tell
you yeah I won't shoot you okay it's one
life too blank one life too blank but I
heard it too
now she doesn't trust
me she doesn't no no she just wants to
know what's first yeah oh yeah true I
mean there's still two possibilities so
just to make sure you know oh oh okay
safe safe oh I see how 5050
now okay you why does Kiara doesn't have
a HP yeah I oh where it is where's my HP
how much do I have maybe you'll find out
if I shoot you no no no
oh wait I live I where's my
HP yeah for some reason for some reason
it
disapp the moment I di your H
disappeared
I four Lives four four two that's spicy
oh hey your life oh jammed yeah heal up
heal up heal
up you're telling me to heal up now that
you shot me no it's kind of like it's
after
care that's brutal raining it's after
care well anyway I got to make some
decisions here exactly oh
[Music]
jamed oh
she she High
chance
yeah
y guys I lost count I don't know what
the amount of bullets are I still
haven't shot waya a single time just
saying wait why why why I skipped it
because I made you skip
it oh yeah cuz you jam I can't see your
HP
too is it spicy wa so if you're Jam you
can see your HP and also
you well
[Music]
oh but wait so that means probably the
next one is alive I Shota
[Laughter]
[Music]
earlier kind of up to you she going
to fine got
it so rude it's time to be brutal
ra so rude okay
so let me see I'm just making up for all
the times you shot me wait I show you
ler one time no minimum two times
minimum your first turn your first turn
was me
today oh yeah it
was I
love what
the hello
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
interesting interesting
[Music]
reloading o fun okay that's easy load it
up
way oh healing okay o she's strong man
just's
H what was that again I'm going to steal
from the
deading Ste from the dead I'm getting
overkilled here I'm getting bullied
Ana's just chilling the whole time no oh
there's stealing from the dead um well
who you going to
shoot Kiara oh no but then ra
what's up you a lot alive so no hard
feeling no hard feeling she said take my
Advent no hard
feeling it's thrilling if everyone why
am I looking why am I looking I know
exactly what's in there I know um waste
it why did I do
that wasting my item okay let's let's
even it out a little bit sorry thank
you after all I did for you I love
you a too many items on the
table
yum oh Tut 5050 Tut okay okay okay okay
tutu let's see first I
like I like your how's it going Shar
thank you it's cold don't do that it's
cold here I need it is cold please I
need someone to die together with me
okay please
alone oh man she going
Jam don't be like that I feel like I
got oh Spic do a little bit of damage
here a little bit someone needs to die
this
round someone has to die moreal for
everyone is it is it for you
HP
this wait so is it 21 right now I don't
know now it's one life too
blank oh she's smoking one life too
blank
yeah why Won't Anyone die with
me what did I do it seems like she's
here with us still I know think I can
still hear
[Music]
voice so brave I know I'm taking the
bullet for all of us 5050 now all right
hey 50/50 yeah yeah yeah one life one
blank a damn it um well I got to even it
out L I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry now we all
we're all free I think we're all free
are we free no I'm I think I don't know
good okay so this one is
uh this one is
B oh okay yeah she's keeping oh it's
empty
okay we need to learn I don't like these
items we need to learn from ra she's
been keeping calm every time four four
four four oh that's a lot okay surely
someone dies this
right Sur we Sur we someone it's still
my turn cool
okay wasn't 4 four I already forgot
yeah short this time someone someone
dies right see
interesting
interesting well it's time I see it
she's going to
get oh okay
is it time for
violence it's time
death you can see us from the
heaven the mafia
bossy welcome to the
land it's somebody has a magnifying
glass you know at least we can still see
I still leing
from the
dead okay again when when the phone says
a number is it the one from now for from
the beginning from now from now from
now it told me a really far one but I
have more
phones
okay wow okay that also really
far oh she has so many phones yeah yeah
she got
like cool I I'm not even going to try
counting oh
you okay you got a B you must have seen
the second one or
something maybe this one may maybe this
one it's
[Music]
5050 nice okay what items you don't you
only have two inverters and one oh I I
misclicked I think respect
G well how did you
know she miss apparently apparently she
miss um I knew that that one was a blank
cuz the phone told me yeah the phone
told me uh as well
before five
six I guess I should try
yeah I had a
feeling let's steal another phone to
make very
sure you're stealing from the dead how
low can you get I think it just told me
the same one that I was told from last
round was like the seventh but now it's
like the third or still great
you're not keeping C are
you so I'm going to do something that's
maybe stupid no no it might not be
stupid come on please please please
yes well then
interesting okay yeah okay okay
now yeah but at this now at this m M
yeah yeah so
[Applause]
this oh we get items
nice are we reloading or what yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
oh oh those are some good
items
no oh that's going to be fun okay why no
magnifying glass
50 okay I got some phones no don't tell
me the sixth one tell me me the first
one she has so many
phones okay but I I believe yeah
yeah oh my
God it's one versus one yay
yay oh no wait wait what was that a
magnifying
glass wow what was that what the no one
has a good item here
oh are you jamming
me are you jamming
me I
[Applause]
guess are you healing
up she didn't even hesitate the upia
boss no she didn't even
hesitate I can't do anything Dam it why
are you dead you should have stayed
alive
well well first we had the ID Showdown
now we have the y or the Europe
Showdown let's
[Music]
go that was
F that was F dang for
y good she going to use it for
G for gaja I mean understandable I will
too okay here we go again last round but
then hopefully we'll do more rounds yeah
do more I think okay good items good
items man my item
look four lives to
back four
two my items wait what's wrong with your
items how come you only have two no she
has threee two inverters yeah two
inverters and one freaking freaking
phone fine I I'll use the
phone but who was phone mhy
mhi okay what what did it tell you
no I'm not going to tell you why would I
tell
you
okay I
feel no way no way no sh no sh no no way
it's like two blanks two two freaking
blanks no oopsie oh oh well that was
unnecessary aha
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
um what item did she
use
polarizer I used the turn inverter oh so
it's back to
Ana the the the rotation changed okay
okay all
right um this one this one should be it
okay go obsessed with
me you guys love me do you I do love hat
all the this yeah this is how I express
my love see yeah oh really I love you uh
no thank you it's fine her love language
is shooting okay oh wow wait how many
that was already free shots right
mhm no it's 50/50 is it yeah it's it
should be um so only one life round left
I think yeah
think oh she's jamming she's on her
phone yeah who's jam oh way is way is
jammed oh
jamming got Jam how unfortunate
[Music]
jamming
to jamming to the spinning
[Music]
C come on ra shoot your
shot do it do it do
it her brain is
spinning
miscalculated oh
my it was 5050 this is
huge
uh so wait is if it was 50/50 is it that
certainly don't don't don't even don't
even I didn't show you this I didn't
show you I don't know I just I don't I
want to I I I don't I I I have to make
everybody my enemy not just one person I
guess that's fair I see how it is I'll
remember this totally fair I'll remember
this oh wow wow wow wow wow wow this
game won tell us to be filing is it just
one blank ah I don't know maybe there's
three blanks ra what do you think I
don't know I was I was I was looking
away oh
no okay how do you are you jamming me
now okay I I who you
Jing you got to make this one
count oh my
you know this is how I express my love I
mean I hate you so not next time buot
roulette one versus one you and me
collab stream sure if can
win fight
me fight me catch me outside how about
that is she going to shoot I don't
know why I'm almost dead do your not and
now you're giving it back to
Anna what I never show okay
[Music]
but I mean you know this is like 505050
and uh
I I can make it to even if even if this
is alive that means there's only blanks
left and it will come back back to me
cuz I'm first turn you
know it's a 5050 yeah this is 50/50 one
versus
one okay that means only BL yourself now
okay I get new items it was it was all
live
on me
again I miscalculated nice she did
nothing calculated it Kara did nothing
wrong o no three liated three Liv
blank that's a lot of blank
yeah heal up girl heal up yeah yeah yeah
I
will let's see what you girls have you
you've got lots of
beers that's so kind of you you didn't
need to do that you know you didn't need
to do all
[Music]
that okay back okay okay
what's
that she stop speaking
human she's speaking
Phoenix
no what let go let's go oh my God the
power of the cat
meme no I'm as lucky as
oh my
[Music]
god oh back backwards spect oh wow all
right all right
listen what you going to do I'm going to
shoose
filing you're a lot of no you jammed me
K
you
yeah my turn got skipped she's goinging
on her what I
do
e who should I
shoot well me me me go for me go shoot
me yeah go go
go
why Try Me Oh
don't don't don't take it now as Revenge
you asked for it no I was sure it was
blank never mind wait wait wait I forgot
what's in how many are left I confused
you didn't die bamboozle I ejected so
many phone no wait
no I see never mind yeah I think I know
I also don't know I don't know I don't
know anymore Chad you have to count Chad
yeah it was right okay oh but we get new
rounds now right yeah we items new
rounds yeah new items okay I got to use
my item
wow don't like these items but so many
beers yeah where's my magnifying
glass oh okay short one oh
okay two healing up should be able to
count with that
smoking why does everyone have a
magnifying glass but not
me
ouch ouch just a scratch nothing
personal scratch nothing but a
scratch
um H I don't even know how many lives do
I have wait so it's 5050 now right yeah
yeah yeah yeah um maybe it's 21 I don't
know k no it's one one
I know it's
5050 oh okay now it's one live just one
100% yes you sure it's one live you sure
it's not a blank I am 100%
sure no I know what
you're oh wait oh wait
okay what I'll actually also Jam the
turn I just want to use my items so now
wa your turn will be the next
turn why are you why why are you tying
my hands like this I didn't I did not to
this wait isn't this all going to be
reset when the last round is out I don't
know but but it will still be rain's
turn
right I no I have no idea I think it
will be rain is yeah yeah yeah wa a turn
man let me play like my items
are my are full W lives for it's
full okay fre
four wait what it's from again I lose
track again oh yes okay so it resets all
the jams and stuff that I did okay okay
cuz I I did make her skip but now it
resets
okay Sor I wasted my item give it to me
take thank you okay well I thought you
were going to take my magnifying
glass oh you have your own you have your
own yeah I have my own that was a gamble
you used the knife
for hey not
me you shot me earlier give the others
kid a chance
everybody I didn't
get I didn't even get this cuz I kept
getting jammed
true not the
wayy I'm just secet please shoot
me not doing I'm not even doing
anything you could have kicked someone
out of the game right now and you chose
not to well she was begging me so that
works yeah that works with me I
[Music]
forgot I forgot
shoot uh I forgot too we're so
[Laughter]
useless if you don't shoot me I tell you
you can use me as an
item Joker bro what the hell I don't
even know what bullets are there I
uh I'm not even doing anything bro like
my turn never comes I'm just waiting I
believe
you it's the gamble it's your turn on
you fin I spayed you before I have so
many you too there was that wasn't a
blank I knew it was a blank come on come
on I I see I'm never going to trust you
really ever again yes never what never
never again it just told me the same the
same turn like two cell phones just told
me the same turn are
you about the bullets so I'm like I I
don't care anymore it's gambling time it
doesn't the phone doesn't care because
it's a new I tell you if it
don't um okay wait hold on it's be I
don't care man I'm just going to I need
to use my
items oh I need to use my items shoot
what okay
okay I can't count I I I I lost count I
don't know what what's in
there I know
I don't know man
oh I'm always here like I'm like I'm
looking at the camera like I'm in the
office I'm like what I
do Mushi MH please tell me what's inside
okay no heart feeling
okay
never nobody has a magnify glass is this
because I cigarette is that it but can I
have a phone
sure how unfortunate there's no blank
left what it didn't even tell me
anything oh is it because only one is
left and I know it
already two left I think I think so why
did the phone say how unfortunate wait
no maybe that means there's no only only
blanks
now wait then ah damn it ah damn it I
should have I should have inverted show
me show me show me 100%
no it's empty
yeah un I
should wasted no why why where's my
secrets where's my
secrett
fory please you be
ra can I stay alive please for one more
round please hello y
uh
okay really
yeah that's so nice of
you big do you trust her I haven't I
haven't shot you at all I think right
like this round at least you just didn't
have a chance to
yet wow there you go she's so overpow
she has 5 HP now has 5 HP
[Music]
you're going to win I deserve to
leave and we down
yeah wow oh my goodness what's happening
no my eyes what was how many bullets I
didn't even I don't no you it's now oh
really yeah I'm going to take the
risk or already shot me so oh it's aind
okay oopsie I remember
immediately I lost count I know I lost
count as
well at least I stole her
knife sorry stealing is stealing from
the alive worse than stealing from the
dead disgust no
a let me
[Music]
see I'm nervous I know
like I yes yes no shoot
me I can shoot you no don't oh
okay wait so what does the remote
do only one way to find out I you switch
to turn no no why did you do that no I
just wanted to know what it does cuz
I've never used
it I've never used it I think this one
is going to be a blank though t no I
want to
live it was alive whoops I'm
sorry I'm sorry it was alive what I
forgot wait oh my God
what's what do you mean oops if you're
testing it out don't test it on the one
HP
person well that Happ no she's a go
she no heart
feeling oops no heart feeling
she only fair cuz ra has five HP yeah
you got to get her down got to get her
down you know she has the most HP in
here we got
equality let's
see oh you now it's
blank but at least I don't have to count
anymore
jailing could pet my cat she shot me
like thce people come on let's be real
here you can shoot her Ana invert and
shoot
rainy really in and this is targeted
violence what I'm saying Ana invert and
shoot
okay okay not me though
okay invert remember remember to invert
invert if if you shoot me she's going to
she's going to fight you but if you
shoot her you're going to have a chance
to win again G
yeah that's that's what I'm thinking
so you're going to kill me for nothing
but you have so so many
HPS all right it's okay I can shoot
myself be a
[Laughter]
later no at least this will make it even
you
know they HTE me no this is the first
time I'm shooting you this round
everybody hat that was my first shot
that was my my first Trot that J this
round for this round at
least yeah what did you say that was my
first shot at you this
round okay fair fair enough yeah yeah
right fair enough what was that
32 three Liv to
blank oh she's using the cell
phone oh
oh oh just taking the risk I don't know
oh shoot
there
okay someone is about to die avenge me
Ana you know what to
do oh my
[Music]
goodness I'm okay I was just having a
brain rot moment brain rot moment no not
that one which one which one then which
one yeah has everybody in this room
played Tales of Symphonia before
oh I've never played the game no damn it
well then my brain w doesn't matter oh
no there you
go I am
[Laughter]
here
together together in death two no four
four not even death was part
it's I don't have a knife that's the
thing like I was going to say in Tales
of Symphonia there's a character
called but uh yeah in English they
pronounced the word I think ana ana
pronounced his L's name who was it I
don't know like rainy Rainey and it
sounds like how the name is pronounced
in t Symphonia and I thought they both
have silver hair and I thought they were
never together in the same room together
so I thought that Raina is May
the Rainer from
tesia yeah nobody understands what I'm
saying yeah but the spelling is a little
bit different it's an a instead of at
begin like yeah but they say R rainy
rainy rainy rain rain
rainy yeah yeah yeah and she has silver
hair just like you is it
you I will not believe it until you're
in the same room
together
well well I'm not going to use this
but
ghost no more Reverb they took my rever
privileges away what oh my goodness who
took
it me cuz I have selfcontrol
no you jacked me why would you do that
oh it's so over
[Music]
you're using the knife no a she's
killing you
no this is so brutal I bar really have
any use I don't know if that's going to
work so somebody has to die it's only
two people
left ouch oh she you're still alive
you're still alive yeah I'm still low
but not much longer guess you want me to
die what the heck I don't know somebody
has to die
I'll try oh my God I
got she's going for the
overkill my items were so
[Music]
useless my items were so
useless
man Mafia always wins oh wait what
again again again yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah most resource most wealthiest
least
careful least careful care well oopsy
I'm not even there I'm just I'm just
vibing you know I did not deserve much
treatment I feel like well the next my
items my items were as though despite
can you guys give me a moment I go grab
some water one second I give me a I want
to change to shirt it's too hot be yeah
yeah yeah one
moment all right I'm just going to get a
[Music]
drink I have
mango with some jelly and grapefruit
this drink jell mhm jellies what
flavor it's like a drink um so it's a
mix of like mango and grap grapefruit
and it has little mango pieces and it
also has like little sweet fruity
jellies oh that's nice okay I'm back oh
hello welcome back that was fast I girls
mww MW mwww MW
MW I don't know about Ming
you you know I saw in the beginning of
the stream somebody in the chat was
saying like oh is kiata wearing a a a a
KB
does it look like in in this like cut of
me May a little bit like the upper part
I think yeah kind of looks like yeah
right a little bit so maybe I am ID oh
hello welcome Hol Live ID gen Hol Live
ID Gen 4 is Kiara
and I guess I girls I have a question
yes is January February very nice for
Bali oo I don't know I want to go I
don't know cuz like Indonesia's weather
is you know can be
spoil uh stormy I don't know every huh
more like a little bit unpredictable
yeah kind of
[Music]
unpredictable no
no when is best season again when is it
best again for Bali
M I think like middle of the year is I
don't know
summer I don't
know I know why don't you know I no no
no the thing is like ID people don't
even keep track because even though
whatever whatever SE it is the weather
is always kind of wacky you know yeah
it's really wacky July August
August October march to May okay well
then any case not now huh mhm damn it I
need to go on a
[Music]
vacation yum y yum just finishing my
jelly jelly yeah I'm having like this
little um mango grapefruit drink with
jellies in I want some now
[Music]
fancy jelly
I'm back oh welcome back back welcome
back let's go let's go let's Go's go
okay okay okay let's
go the game is about to
start let's go okay do better this time
let's go let's I I will win this time I
swear I will win I will
win okay I'll I'll ride I'll oh truee
lives I guess we start with like three
four five like three for first round
four for second round or
something sorry okay
uh three two three
two okay two three oh my
turn we're we're all going to be locked
in this round I'm locked in locked in I
locked in well I got to make it sound
stop Ste stealing from the alive jeez
what the fuck dude is in front of me now
oh
okay it's okay I stole your item but I'm
not going to shoot you rainy you know
that's yeah that's a that's a better
choice right oh I wonder who you're
going to
shoot don't be so predictable why are
you so predict
theall I mean you you you were kind of
asking for it not going to lie no I
wasn't I just you shouldn't have say
that you shouldn't have said that you
know
oh so locked in oh my God she locked in
now I don't even have a magnifying
class
no p no why would you do that
nice onece one not
nice
[Music]
um ah these items are not going to help
me well I don't know I mean yeah
actually let me uh swap cuz I'm pretty
sure it's you know it's not certain but
it's pretty
sure no yes yes yes size two blanks I
think seriously
wait does it invert the next one or all
of
them oh you writing them
down oh I inverts all of
them no it it doesn't like the no just
the next one yeah just the next one what
oo
spicy H
nice only the current
shell just the next oh man where's my
cigarette where's my
cigarette okay Tre Lives four BLS four
tree huh oh it's oh it's my turn yeah
uh oh no
oh
oh oh oh so it's 5050 now yeah it is I
see it fun
[Applause]
okay oh how the table
turns I'm going to gamble
no
luy saying hi to my
[Music]
neighbor Hi Neighbor you guys know what
to do with that
information she's using violence so
now I'm I I I Ana look at what I'm going
to do uhhuh I'm going to shoot someone
else okay
okay oh so that you so that you as a
streamer are longer in the
game
sure yeah remember okay okay I'll
remember that I'll remember that oh want
your screen to be black and white from
the alive huh that's what you're going
to resort to
yeah what's better stealing from that
I'm stealing from
alive I think um if you steal from the
alive somebody said that the punishment
is worse or something really oh yeah
probably
no
wasted
wasted oh I lost track oh my is isn't
there like to too left yeah
yeah yeah
y
uh I do have CS but it doesn't matter
anymore cuz anyone cuz you haven't got
shot you haven't got shot the whole time
so you know I was
just I was shooting you cuz
yeah no hard
[Music]
feeling oh we'll see about hard feelings
it seems
oh serves you right wait I died let's
see what do we have this
time you can't for don't I died from
that don't mess with Raina
[Music]
okay have HP left okay
wow I have so many stealing item
thingies but like nobody has magnifying
I HP left I thought I had
two oh
well what I forgot the bullets what are
they oh R used the
knife wait actually let me steal that
dang
it dang it thank you I didn't see
that that makes
sense yeah
yeah let me take one of those stealing
from the alive people these days they
have no shame yeah let me take let me
take let me take that God damn me again
I don't know just looking for
the girls are fighting someone else had
a phone too huh wait what did say I
didn't look I didn't look what did it
say oh my God oh my
God have you used beers by the way yeah
I I haven't used them yet I'll I'll use
now one Please eject a blank one damn
it no
helping I don't
know let's let's try let's just let's
just try wait where's Ana I'm
dead
dead even relx you didn't even realize
I'm
dead guys guys guys want the count now I
have no idea cuz I can't do anything
people are stealing my
items
help my
God stop knock me please what's
happening from the dead okay good good
better better no problem stealing from
the dead huh I'm already dead why
would't you do that to
me why no reason
me was I jammed or so oh I got
jammed oh yeah you got jammed oh wow
okay good you're going to shoot me right
well it's 50/50 now I guess I have
nothing
else I have nothing El I can
try oh I you me
right right what
sorry
[Music]
5050 this is I never started
it
yeah ghost again well this is getting
spicy I am a goh
welcome the of the
Dead no unfortunately it's not I got
jammed I got jamed really cool oh you
got jammed I don't know what is this is
this A blank or is this a h oh uh it
could be
either
oh guess we'll get a new gun we'll get a
new it's whole authorties fighting each
other now wait what no hey wait what my
violence no oo police police you
won no no no no it's not over yet oh
it's not oh you're not dead let's see
who gets the best
items oh please be my turn why is it h
turn it's going to be my turn right
[Music]
a my okay
okay this this should work this should
be okay okay I see the color oh yeah
this is my win I don't even have to
smoke because I can cut wow finally one
round win for wa how did I do it oh
yay nice nice
first time first time win o
money I use this
money to I plug please
I new cat we're alive round two baby
round two it's round two time all I want
is good item I'm
always
love are you oh yeah except for that
last part s I had to do it
okay my items it is what it is you
understand it do be like that oh wait I
was still with the ghost
effect oops my items man you don't like
them they're fine you have a healing
item yeah true at least I have a cette
why everyone hates me this time no it
was a blind out I knew it would I knew
it will be a
blank I knew it will be a blank that
that's why shot you no why would you do
that she took that as an insult oh my
God I lost I lost track I don't even
know man ah shit now let me go can I go
back oh no I can't go back no no you
pick you pick up the shotgun you got to
shoot damn it I could have cut it um
okay
well I don't know like I don't know I've
already lost two HP yeah I could I could
make your suffering even shorter or
but no like I didn't I didn't try to
shoot you this time Ki why do you shoot
me this time it's just evening it out
you know no I'm feelings blah blah
[Music]
blah okay is a new gun right yeah okay
yeah it's a new gun oh
W okay that's spicy spicy
oh rain oh my god um shoot um shoot I
don't know um shoot I don't
know was that supposed to be a
pun shoot I hope you know who you're
shooting no why won't you do
that stop stealing stop stealing
people's
items that for real
I don't get
it
ah no hard feelings I used the song I
had to shoot someone I can't shoot
myself with
[Music]
it
okay you used to be so happy when we
shot you now you're not so happy anymore
when I know that is a
[Music]
bank
slur I don't know that didn't really
help
there's still two don't worry L you have
a couple more lives as a cat
right
[Music]
extra what what do you think it is I
don't know do you know what it is you
don't know I don't I don't I don't know
what that is yeah I don't I I really
don't know what it is okay so no
heart no heart feeling
M okay yes hard feelings you cannot
decide whether or not I should have hard
feelings I mean I mean you you were the
one who wanted to gamble with it so I
just you yeah you wanted the co you're
like a lawyer you're always using what I
say against
me but I use your actions against you
not your words me lady
okay uhhuh um you know what that means
girls
[Music]
you're switching it oh okay what was
this ohot I'm pretty sure that was a
live round yeah that was that was that
was a live
round okay yeah I
forgot that happen you're still making L
of
sweat full
inventory a big cat no cuz like oh
oh that's fun like the phone says how
unfortunate that's why I
forgot I didn't understand that before
too but yeah MH uh but what does it mean
when it says how unfortunate I thought
it was like oh maybe um there's only
there was only one last round left and
yeah yeah they're not going to tell you
if there's only one pretty
much okay
okay
okay what
I mean she's going
to I
mean I could end ra right now but I
didn't even that would be Overkill so it
feel like I haven't even shot once
during this round it literally
haven't okay I will not can I can I
around thank you yeah then don't shoot
me just one one round deal one round
deal one round deal don't shoot
oh
sorry sorry thank you so much so
[Music]
generous I'm I'm scared of her WRA yeah
oh she shot her now she's healing back
up she's going to
win that's not my fault I wasn't going
to say
anything no stop
stealing someone you should have killed
her no
no what what did did what you did did
you just inject did you do yeah should
did no did okay oh well you just that's
[Laughter]
bullshit what' she do I don't know man
she switched without knowing so we don't
know what it will be she
gambling me
again your luck is insane
what what what even did I do nothing way
you did nothing wrong you did nothing
wrong getting the item
stolen i' I have received zero money and
they're taking everything away from you
didn't do
anything
okay wait I was kind of what's the word
when you're like helping out in in the
killing of someone even though you don't
want to I kind of
helped by
leaving I will
remember I I will keep in mind and I'm
an
accomplice you stole you stole my item
so that's for it oh it's a showdown okay
I used them for a good reason you stole
my
item like a goh is talking to me maybe
I'm crazy
[Laughter]
I mean I talk to P so I
guess
okay oh you know what's left in
there
round o wait L is still alive o yeah
yeah she is how many lives does she have
I don't know
one but then I would waste my two shots
again no she has two she has two has too
cuz I didn't use my
knife I only I only
check I guess we can make
sure no it's 2 Hp she has 2
[Music]
Hp I'm serious I'm
serious I I I don't know honestly she
she she does she does have 2 Hp I saved
my
knife
wao oh man
do you have a stealing item on you um I
don't think so okay good cuz I got
really good items
no no oh but this
is I guess I can use my phone mhy
[Music]
mhy what did it not give you good
information yeah as always the phone
always tell you like something that's so
far in the
future okay oh sipping sipping are you
sipping towards what the phone told
you oh yeah you are no no I'm not stop
in such a waste why are you injecting
everything I see you don't want us to
die you don't want either of us to die
you're so sweet I don't know that's why
you're ejecting all the live
rounds I can gamble like what you going
to do I gamble cuz
it's
well
oh oh yeah okay okay okay okay my gamble
my gamble worked okay yeah I didn't know
what was it I only got information of
the last one which is like bullshit wow
it always giv me like information of the
last
shell your turn your next turn is
skipped nice and I'm checking what's in
here that looks red to
[Music]
me oh but wait are you still skipping
your
wait yeah yeah I I'm skipping my turn ah
but I don't have an inverter
yeah
no yeah you can steal any item too
yeah get that out of here give me a new
gun give me a new gun game what is there
still one one more there there's still
one more yeah there's still one
more
all okay still kind of
scary please give me a cigarette please
please please
I'm so scared treat treat this could be
anyone's game now because I got one HP
and you got two oh but it's my turn no
it's my turn no no there's no way way
this is right oh but I don't have a
saw n
[Music]
oh but you have a saw and you have two
magnifying
glasses oh no I don't have Inver you
you're going to win you're going to win
I don't know you never I don't know how
you cannot win now oh yeah I'm going to
win close call
okay well do you have any L sword
[Music]
uh everyone's last words just well
done well done yeah last round this yeah
last round then that was cl let
go Ana to Showdown yeah an to Showdown I
won that means I'm
stronger finally we're back
are time waiting
huh okay good
items who starts
[Music]
oh bring you
ohain she stole my item no she stole my
item my magnifying class
oh she
knows she knows she
knows oh a wait to say
something she's okay was just making
sure you're not muted no no she's just
locked in she's just really locked
in
hey I see okay one left of course
greetings no what did I
do what did I
do now it's
greetings man oh yes you stole my item
and that's what should do first thing
first your item I still still
okay but still you shot
me
[Music]
true it's congrats on winning bam you
know oh I have two
adrenalin
a okay you can steal from the living
yeah I can steal from from the
living hey everybody takes my magnifying
glass yeah CU you're the only one you're
the only one who with magnifying glass
no one for me like no
respect no respect man
no one else has mag magnifying glass you
know okay oh my
God
hey they're just going to make me lose
again
no wait Anna did you use a beer
too um I wonder I
wonder who
knows you know a a saw shot is just like
a kiss on theek cheek you know like you
have two cheeks so it's like mwah mwah
greetings who got jammed who got jammed
I no it's Wawa isn't it no oh yeah you
got jammed
bro loves jamming
you
um try it
oh what got ejected I don't
know wait
oh I
misclicked oh you mis never mind I'll
try
there she got it out for me I missed
I'll remember that I'll remember that I
miss I
misclicked I will remember kaha you
killed me from the beginning you
remember me of
course
I it's time for your villain
AR jammy
me oh she's back now she's back
back oh she's mad she's not
talking she's not I'm trying to remember
I'm trying to
remember
hey I didn't know how many HP you have
so it's it's just
um wait I lost Town me
too I'm just going to eject this then
is
this yeah BL yeah I knew it mhm all
right let's go new
gun new
luck no magnifying glasses on the tree
okay
okay okay okay I see how it is wait it's
going to be it's going to automatically
be like anyone like the others turn even
though I ejected with a be I thought it
was going to come back
yeah what I actually don't know I don't
know what oh she I thought it was going
to come back to
me cuz like jacket with a be what the
fuck that's what you get that's what you
freaking
get what
lucky oh my God oh my God I respect the
gamble though I respect the gamble
yeah oh
man no way that was so
unlucky
jeez too much gamble is not good for you
DN
[Music]
sorry lots of violence
happening just locked
in
oh no not my
items okay the Le you could do is to not
so
focused I don't think you're going to be
needing those items
anymore let me
live sweet
dreams POV is
over black and white guys now what did I
do now he
red right yes now should no I thought I
thought the gun was going to come back
to me cuz I used a
beer
no we all make mistakes I think we all
have made mistakes we all made mistakes
that is buck shot ruet in a nutshell
yeah dang
it that is not bushot roulette it's book
book shot
roulette B we're all Boke Tanto Boke
shot roulette
[Music]
you look at me you think I will help you
you think that will help you you help
me you kill me you shot me what are you
talking about I need you guys keep
fighting until everyone dies shut
me until everyone dies keep fighting
each other she wants my ra I'm probably
done
I'll probably die
[Music]
yeah well first of all first of
all what's
that yeah I I knew I knew I knew that
would happen he hates
me I knew what's more
important healing
or uh
wait how much HP did have I don't
know I don't know like two HP I don't
know I think it
was oh ah
okay what she
do I will take you down with
me wait did she die
yeah oh welcome to the land of dead well
it's okay you have no choice but to kill
me got good a close
look taking a close look what is it what
is it oh are you stealing mhm switch
room okay rip Tak
or make it interesting shoot
yourself no
way bro let me have it all just this
wait is alive why is she
alive I I had two
lives lives yeah yeah I told you she had
two I actually didn't
[Laughter]
know no I thought I thought you used a
knife
well I I I I I'm I'm dead now so oh
bye-bye wait can I say the last
[Music]
one you going to
say win let's go wait did we I think we
all got one win at least yeah I think
so beautiful
oh results
oh careful careful no one was every
resourceful everybody was careful today
yeah okay like it's most resourceful
like um the one who holds items the most
or what I'm not sure does that mean does
that mean I didn't use as many items as
everyone
did I don't know either that or you did
use your items quite a lot did do you
feel you did
I think I think I did I don't
know I don't know
actually well mean I have no idea what
chimy means
shimy where' you read that I don't
know wasn't there wait did I read
wrong I feel like there was one but I
don't remember H chimney me means you
smokes a lot oh oh
yes who smoked a lot I know
was oh yeah let's go mafia boss
[Music]
Mafia wait what it's a it's a meme a
Holo meme where long time ago P not not
that long long ago but Pampa had like a
stream where she had other members
impersonate her um and then some people
tried to really sound like her and say
something that would sound like her but
others said things that are really out
of character so
yeah
said which is like what a Japanese
person would say to get cigarettes at
the store number 37
please I
see yeah
okay I was play more honestly but but uh
yeah probably playing enough I don't
know it's fun though it's fun okay so do
we make that as our last game or do you
guys want to go one
more I'm okay with it but you guys got
to
peek unless somebody doesn't have time
I'm good I'm good one more one more one
more one more one more one more weast
cuz we we already we already are now
familiarized ourselves with the game I
this game is better at destroying
friendships than than Mario party I
think if
anything man yeah I feel like Mario
Party is more violent than this game for
some reason no the thing is like because
it's like shooting and everything we
Channel our feelings with the banter you
know whereas Mario is like
Mario part is a lot of like unlucky
moments this is here I feel like our our
Des is a little bit our
hands I'm am I bugged out I can't oh I
can't put down my items oh oh I guess it
was the same bug as the one R
encounter I'll make a new I'll make a
new room then sorry sorry yeah it's okay
no it's not your fault yeah not
your B I could pull up the magnifying
glass my second item even but I couldn't
put it down oh that's weird okay I made
a new you're still a ghost on wait what
why are you still a
ghost hello uhuh you still have a echo
oh oh I still have the
echo don't you hear it
yourself no oh yeah I don't I don't hear
my voice in my
headphone okay I I don't know I don't
know how you do it like I Tred to to
hear myself during the
streams I can I can do it either yeah
it's just like oh man I'm listening to
myself I hate myself
no I guess there's two types of people I
guess
yeah do you hear yourself I do I do oh
you do oh you do yeah a for me it's too
distracting yeah for me it's too
distracting as well I see I see
different opposite for me I guess it's
still loading come on game it's still
loading oh my God
my probably bugged out again oh man I
mean like I'm pretty sure my connection
fine cuz I'm like here
yeah it took a long time like last time
I made through I guess we just have to
[Music]
wait come on come on
we GNA go like that for the whole
[Music]
night it's not loading beautiful it's
not
loading no try again maybe we can make
okay I can do
that all right turn to menu oh shoot I
accidentally went back to the main
menu oh yeah that's also what I did just
in
case just in case it not work out wait
did you already send a new one no not
yet she did
okay a it's so cool okay I'm going to
host AC too strong I wish I had
AC I can't leave
anymore I send the new
code okay go W let's freaking go
yay okay
loading
loading the game doesn't want to be
played anymore no it can't be it can't
be it can be like I'm going to I want to
go idle meeting what if I go idle
meeting and suddenly the game loads you
know I mean it's fine I mean I think
it's going to a little longer yeah we
can wait
okay okay well well I'm going to go and
pray if I go it'll Pray when I'm back
started yeah hopefully okay yeah well
I'll get water I'm out of water okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
okaya cover to yeah I love I love your
Oreo cover you really do yeah I do
a okay I'm back it's so nice when I
don't feel like I have obligation to
stay on my desk because there's other
people who can entertain the chat
[Music]
a loading drink water guys drink water H
wait you
know we can wa yeah we can
wait H maybe maybe new table cuz I feel
when when the game worked then it like
loaded immediately right yeah
true I mean if this one doesn't work by
the time rain it comes back I maybe
someone else someone else can host
instead of me I can't to host
yeah what are we
doing T I make another leaf table uh
table seems kind of sus when it's not
like loading right away yeah yeah oh wow
now are you so fast is it are the H yeah
yeah yeah okay okay just like straight
up made it oh there we
go sorry sorry sorry
I'm too eager to start sry I didn't
know we'll play without you okay you no
no no no I'm going to make a new
one here you go wait is the same want to
play with me anymore okay that's fine I
guess the same the lobby no longer
exists it says oh oh no no you go go
okay okay
Yosi Yosi okay I'm here being so here
the fastest now we can go now we can go
no it doesn't work let's do it
again it doesn't work doesn't doesn't
work Ana are you cursed Ana I I might be
what the heck okay I do another one okay
or it might just be the game like being
like new it's 100% the game yeah okay
okay there you go oh there we go y let's
go
yipp
Y no mercy going to kill each other y
thank God I'm
not it's kind of like you know except
more violent
mhm hey like which game let's go therapy
oh what kind of therapy have you
experienced I mean kind of smoking
installing the gun to shoot your friend
is free yeah
true the game is even giving us like
beers for free wait shoot it's it's a
black screen on me oh yeah it's not
responding I guess oh yeah something
should be happening right now but it's I
think yeah I think the game Flo is on my
side okay let's do that again okay
serers are broken okay we'll get him at
some point the thing is we could
disconnect just fine right mhm
okay the game the game is
too hold on we'll get him okay an you're
coming I'm here okay let's go hopefully
Works come
[Music]
on come let's go come back the game CH
waiting for players okay okay we're
here are we
yeah yeah
yay uh it's not loading for me oh no
what oh no oh it's loading now for me
okay you're you're stting the game so
hard now I know I'm just like hello
that's a lot of inverters what the
heck does it work oh no it's like oh no
it's it's laggy for me I I I don't I
can't yeah it's not it's it's it's uh
okay Frozen again oh yeah it's frozen
again bro they don't want us to play
anymore maybe we
should I don't think they want us to
play anymore okay let's try let's try
restarting the game everyone and then
yeah can you guys I'm going to restart
mine too okay I'm closing mine and then
we're starting again mine if it doesn't
work then we call it a d I
guess that's fine I'm pring so hard
right now please Moment of Truth Moment
of Truth all right who's going to host I
can host wait my game is taking a long
time to launch okay okay okay yeah I
think it's
a come on all right want to play
roulette let me gamble it's a very fun
game I really like it yeah I need to
gamble
if you want to make a if you want to
make a short a shorter version we can
make like instead of three rounds we
make two rounds oh yeah okay yeah yeah
okay sounds good oh wait oh is oh okay
there we go hopefully this
time my
[Music]
on it's going to be
okay
trust it was a blank one there's there's
live rounds and blank rounds when we're
starting the game oh there you go this
is a blank one oh no it was a live one
nice but for how long but for how
long waiting for players waiting for
players
it says waiting for players there go but
it's sus this is sus it's unstable I
know yeah like it's like taking a while
mhm okay okay three rounds let's see oh
three rounds I put two oh never
mind oh no n NY what for me it it won't
yeah I I can't put down my thing again
no
no I can if I disconnect what happens
like you guys can play and I can um no
no no no it's fine we can go for the day
it's okay we play a lot okay you want to
try one last time but I host sure yeah
sure there's always a one more time one
more time one last time I can it doesn't
it doesn't make sense cuz if like the
connection itself doesn't work then I
wouldn't be able to do anything right
yeah no it was bugy for me to remember
yeah the first time right yeah the first
time it's just this is just
about yeah I think I never had a bug can
go so far okay there we
go European server okay okay okay
starting get starting let's see at least
99% of gamblers quit before they that
was that was
quick that was quick see
you okay okay
okay okay what so far okay yes okay yes
oh oh nice
[Music]
[Applause]
yes and I like my items too I hate my it
form form huh going to be fine let's
go
okay okay what do we is my turn yeah
it's your turn okay well
okay third
one okay
so oh I I I'm sitting in a different
spot from usual it feels weird yeah I
like the spot are you on the right side
you don't like being in front of me you
oh my
God I do like being in front of you but
I don't like this position yeah it's
like weird
right changing every single time is
weird mhm and when you when you start up
with threee HP is that your max like can
you heal up or to four no you can't heal
up
okay
uhuh
oh okay should I look again now or
should I risk
it uh I don't know
I'll shoot this time I mean
no yes
[Music]
yes looked again okay I'm going to use
this oh okay where the helpful I mean
you never know when you actually need
that item right it's okay to waste a
turn you know
what so that
means wait so that means
oh yeah those chances were
high and
then oh okay ohing it out the phone must
have the phone told me oh my
[Music]
goodness my God it hurts it hurting
it's okay da I love
you it's my love I'm already dying
great oh Tre okay
okay oh
D 5050 oh she smoking I should have
killed
you I should have killed
rain could you have though yeah cuz I
used my knife and she only had 2 Hp left
right
yeah who's
less yeah
theose yeah it's it always
happens
oh hold
on he checking again oh my
goodness spicy
another one huh I'm going to I'm going
to take a risk she's hogging the shot
gun I'm
dying uh sorry I need I need I need to I
I need to I don't have any I don't have
any I need to
leave sorry what
she shared yeah now she shared it oh
she's using the phone
okay oh
no
[Music]
uhoh I could end your live right now
yeah you can end someone's life you can
end someone's life you
know are you going to me next don't you
think maybe well maybe who
knows I going to be
nice I'll try Okay mafia boss isn't
supposed to be nice I know like she
could be lying yeah are you lying
K I don't know I don't know she
question are you playing Li bar or I
don't know what game we're playing right
now
okay I hope you
remember I hope you
remember put me out of my misery
now impossible she spared
you I hope I won't regret this nobody
has a healing item
why wait uh what's
inside I
oh my oh my wait why am I do I
[Music]
could okay you know
what we'll do something fun why my
item that's not so nice of you that's
not very nice wait did I cut it off or
did I I didn't I didn't cut the shotgun
off right no I don't think it used to
not I don't think you have a s yeah I
don't right but but maybe I don't have
it anymore cuz I used it but no okay ah
wait
what has a full
health
yeah no why are you looking at me you
stole my item already I'm too nice you
stole my item already come on nice to
be okay I'm like what what I say I'm
just stating facts you know like
somebody here
I'm not telling her to shoot her you
know I'm just saying wait I
lost I lost count she's an adult she can
make her own it must
count kind of scared so I'm just going
to going to throw it wait
what what you yeah oh yeah there was
only one
left and they let you cut it and then
they ended the turn I'm confused I lost
count so I didn't know two one M
[Music]
want man this means I get no I I should
have shot
myself oh yeah then maybe you would have
the start something next I forgot the
beard I forgot using the beard I have so
many
choices I forgot I have so many choices
oh
ooh o people need to tell me why they
have why I have to spare
them okay me because I'm a okay
rain merciful I'm your gmate I've been
with you here ever since the start right
we we went to the mall together we have
a pretty strong bond you
know that you a moment ago
literally yeah I didn't even shoot at
you this round rain it okay well um
here's what I'm going to
do um
H I'm going
[Music]
to I'm going to shoot the one okay wait
how many items do you have Raa I don't
know I can see it I I'm L to your you
have like um four maybe I have three no
actually I have I have the
beer and two you have two of each I
think mhm two beers and a
inverter okay you have two beers k k how
many beers do you have I don't I really
I don't know I I can't see either yeah I
can't see my table either I can't see my
table either yeah well I
guess um Kiara no I I just had mercy on
you I could have killed you moment ago
literally me too I I sprayed you did I
didn't shoot you this round I didn't
shoot you this round it didn't even pass
mind cuz you're my precious
genade this so
hard when La says she spared you you you
still had like how many
HP well I guess I got targeted before
that was not fair just because I won the
first
one um I still need to make memories
with you that's true right oh come on
I'm the new one let's make memories
right now no see let's make memories
together in the
afterlife are you planning to die
anytime
soon just
in oh man wait it's my turn right oh
yeah
back to
you
okay all right since I used the knife
it'll be a waste to
shoot this is
crazy I don't know I used the same logic
so
iess how many oh three four oh my God
that's so awful that's that's going to
be fun oh man that is this is not fun
yeah that is this is not fun I'm sorry
wait why should I say sorry you're
you're my
enemy yeah you're my piy
oh okay
okay what you doing I don't
know oh my
God see It'll be useless don't trust the
phones I
know no what you doing
no
[Music]
no yeah yeah but my have seen that
coming oh well
well
well well oh
what what okay
well je she has the better items though
she has a faor as
well okay
I'm going to fulfill my promise to ra
we'll see each other soon yeah you guys
will see each other soon I want to meet
you any in the after
live we're
together we're together to
me please
understand we could have make memories
right now you decided to do to to to put
an end to this oh no this game
memories in the land of the living right
now do you agree are you changing your
St no you guys dep situation you guys me
are you
sure be ly forget everything that was
before let's live in the now and I the
present I don't know about
that oh you killed
me I know but I did it out of love
sure that's what they I believe you I'm
sorry it's okay trust is earned I will
try my best to win your heart exactly
you got you got to you got to earn again
so
romantic she swing the night no saying
nice words that was no
hesitation like just shooting
immediately you got to earn my my trust
again this is a tragedy love
tragedy
doomed
toxic no oh my God Ste my
glass stop that was my only
glass oh no why won you do that
beautiful I mean I have a cigarette
okay
chimney so much yeah for the chimney
achievement I I know
man oh it was a
live hey I don't know
what I lost
count no no
way no
way my G to
work I have
noidea I think I know only yep oh my God
no the gamble doesn't work I don't know
what what is it
now
no I I don't know what is it is it all
blanks yeah it's blanks okay
yipp let's hope we get better
it I like this I like this okay okay
okay I think are not that bad
uhhuh oh tutu that's easy to remember oh
yeah Tut Callie's cat
well that's very much you guys know the
the Tik Tok cat there's also a Tik Tok
cat named Tutu Tut
yeah I love the Tik Tok cat Tut tutu
seems like a popular name for cats yeah
I guess super
cute I don't know any other cat that
chers Andie I'll try my last you mean
baby and
Beauty o
o oh my oh gambling for the spirit of it
oh yeah
doie doie doie doie doie doie doie the
all right gambling paid off for you wait
what about your love you two What about
love you it's a little bit of a there's
a little bit of
toxicity hey you are the only one with
magnifying going to steal the magnifying
glass no fighting over me fighting over
my things
okay
interesting how many HP does K
have how many do you have what is this
tox relationship that I'm having with
everyone what was I Jam um yeah let's
find out I
guess yeah I think I'm good this is so
toxic okay when is my
turn I don't know I have I ever oh you
had full HP okay I don't think I
ever just one blank just one blank can I
have a turn why is it I never get the
turn I want to have a turn
please just one
BL oh hey don't steal hey chain smoking
okay it's not healthy for you yeah it's
not healthy for your lungs bad for my
lungs uh who am I going to
shoot she don't even care about it of
course you do those two they got
something going on and it's not
really of course you guys are
so
well shoot me if you
dare of course she's not going to shoot
that offer doesn't that offer doesn't
apply anymore
that'll she'll shoot she'll last round
well oh she's locked
in I mean you know she stole your Sak so
finally that's kind of deserved you
know finally we we bonding like that
Rainey you don't understand you just
we're just bonding yeah uh I guess
so yeah we we making memories in a year
we're going to remember special kind of
memor I don't think I can remember if I
di you remember oh when you sho me do
you remember that yes Ry I remember when
you shoot me with all your pass that's
so funny cuz like sh in B Indonesia sh
in Indonesian means like kind of means
like convering it's got It's got yeah
two meanings yeah and the other one is
like yeah confessing Your Love uh like
Kaku yeah like koku
Haku sorry you guys are having such a
nice conversation that I just shoot you
it's really rude I know PR rude okay I I
wasn't even listening to the
conversation you killed her the toxicity
you killed her Kiara how dare you so I
so locked in it's okay I'll avenge you
rainy I'll avenge you wait does that me
confess to
me yeah she she wasn't listening she
wasn't
listening she wasn't
listening this therapy no no we were
just saying cuz um if you shoot in
Indonesian it's also another word like
if you confess to someone you know like
you shoot your confession oh really but
why do I no I I did shoot I didn't
confess because I already confessed to
you before me you shoot me you to
confess do it the second time not the
third
time not second
time they're all fighting after my life
you know what bra is mine ra you can't
have this oh okay
then I I think I cannot shoot you
and I I don't I don't I don't I don't
don't look at me like that why are you
looking at me like that no I didn't know
I didn't know your relationship I'm I'm
sorry anyna we need to prove to people
wrong you know that there's actually
some love between us a little bit at
least right I prove people wrong I I'll
prove it by shooting you cuz shooting
means shooting means haveu Ina Indonesia
Kiara that means I'm confessing my love
to
you feel very loved right now
A it's another meaning of me investing
my love to you bullshit you're just
you're just using your language to your
advantage
now
you no you fail well well
[Music]
well oh okay n hold oh ah why me I
didn't shoot
you it's more equal like that I shoot
[Music]
you let me think about this stop stop
smoking
kiaha oh not
healthy it's not healthy for your Longs
wait what
wait the phone said how on unfortunate
so it's only blanks left
right I mean only one way to find out
yeah only one way to find out only one
way to
find I don't but I thought there was
still one in there wait wait wait I
thought there was two left
to I I can't I can't invert anym did I
have an inverter anyway I did yeah you
have like you have like two inverters
but I'm saying
if if if it is a blank one and I shoot
myself will I won't I continue in the
next turn yeah you you're the first one
so I'm going to risk it unless the pH
has like a a minimum of like hey it has
to be minimum two rounds left if it's
only two then I will not tell you cuz
they want some M I don't know e I'm
pretty
short
no okay
got to believe I got to believe I got to
believe in myself
what say how unfortunate so why did the
phone say how unfortunate if that was
the case right it might really have a
minimum of like it has to have three
shells inside and and were only two
inside so it it was like I don't know I
think I understand the logic behind it I
think I understand I got to use my items
man
no I got
it none of you guys have
six
cigarettes no six what six cigarettes
yeah
cigarettes you you don't have one you
don't yeah you don't have fun what what
what did you think did you think of
something
else you should steal the
cigarettes okay um I steal
cigarettes none of you have one wait do
you have one no yeah no no one has no
one no one has Secrets oh no one has
yeah no one has
Secrets yeah how unfortunate wait did
you just turn the
order yeah cuz I need to use my
items thank
hey I want to
know share with me four four
right
[Music]
yeah so what I'm going to do is I'm
going to shoot myself
oh
okay okay
okay checking again using all your it to
see
[Music]
mhm what's what's there to see
come on Ana in the end Ana to shall
Prevail don't you think what happened
you can't have
this you can't have this it's too
dangerous for a cat like you so I'm
going to take it true you should not
weaponize a cat hey
what no it's you know it's too like
balance I stole from Raa and then you
know if I were to shoot Raa it's going
to be you know it's going to be too
Overkill so that's why I shot
you that's why I shot you you know my
stomach
[Laughter]
hurts oh no oh no oh no you jamed me did
you uh no I didn't maybe I should why
you J
me I haven't played a single time this
turn it's un I jammed you cuz you have
the most HP in here m
I'm just G to I have actually no way of
knowing now so I'm just going to
try damn it
oh damn it oh it's going to be my turn
oh yeah cuz she got
gemed I don't know to you you don't
really have any items huh you only have
the yeah I only have my my soul
interesting no I'm not going to risk it
it's all about luck now yeah it's all
about about luck
well
oh yeah very very luck
Bas very very luck
Bas wait what's the smartest thing to
do well well I guess I'll just
shoot come on it's got to
be wa
no what so many blanks in the row
that's that's freaking crazy crazy how
did that happen I'm going to waste them
so you guys don't use it you didn't have
to attack them you could have just shot
oh you are you just going to shoot one
time no I am just wasting them it why
cuz she doesn't want to get CU she don't
want you guys to use them no she has so
many
HP come on come on give me cigarettes
give me cigarettes or a steel got a
steel no you can wait it's going to be
my turn
right
42 okay please tell me it's my
turn yes
no you got to do what you got to do okay
okay ana ana ana ana ana what what what
no no no I wanted that I I need those I
need
those you were delayed you didn't finish
what you're saying you're not going to
need them
I need it's okay let's put the end my
addiction that I didn't know existed I'm
suffering okay I told you she to
quit no K smoking is bad for your lungs
you know I'm doing this cuz I care for
you yeah yeah she's doing for you yeah I
don't believe a single word you
say oh I'm surprised it didn't go for me
yeah cuz has full
HP that's going to be bad on the long
run you know
[Music]
yeah I see I see it
oh
[Music]
oh well well well I don't see myself
winning anymore but that's
call Wa
is I mean you can ask for
[Music]
Mercy I don't believe in Mercy
anymore oh that's
smart
uhhuh so who of you since I be dying
anyway who of you should take the shot m
let's eat it
out has four Ana has five no I'll help
you girls
out thank you so nice of
you
okay I'll win oh my God so much beers
yeah I got so much beers too but you
could also keep me alive as your
assistant K kiar since has so many HP I
I'm going to shoot her anyways you know
you can help
me I'm not going anybody's assistant
whoever keeps me alive I will assist
them cuz you can kill me easily I can't
heal up that much anymore anyway it's
okay let's put an end to your suffer
right so you're oh you don't want me as
your
assistant
no oh you're going to shoot
her not my magnifying
[Music]
glass no I want to work for you you want
to work for me oh wa how you doing is
just chilling know I'm enjoying I'm
enjoying the view I'm enjoying the drama
don't mind me I didn't hear you for a
while yeah she just chilling oh I I'm
always watching it un the whole time I'm
so invested
you on purpose again yeah you're
addicted to alcohol Sho
oh need
calculated oh it's time for a comeback
it's time for a comeback Wait does that
mean there's only blank he calculated I
think there's two um ammos still
inside wait I
I'm not keeping count and as your
assistant I can tell
you if you leave if you keep me alive oh
oh you you're kicking one out okay well
I can tell you what the last one
is do you want to know I was drunk yes
okay it's a life one but don't kill me
please well let's make it even then
we can make even oh okay I see I see I
see
[Laughter]
yeah you me that
you I knew it there only two blanks left
I knew it I was right I was my
calculation oh my she lied to me no that
was really not
purpose okay the least thing you could
do is to not shoot
me
um well okay I mean yeah you if you
shoot
me I'm jamming I'm jamming
Ana why but I will
shoot but you're going to skip my I'm
telling you if you show me you'll
die oh my God I will die any we got
everyone everyone's gone what the heck I
hope oh besides me
[Music]
oh yeah um everyone's gone for some
reason hello I'm still here Ana why do
you hate me so
much can you hear me though oh yeah oh
yeah you can hear I can hear
you's back
r h how do I be back I guess I'm going
to
try um Jo I am I am I am I am I am de
posing though oh I actually I do see
that oh there she is oh yeah she's
moving on my
side Anya can you make it room
again um I wait let me try let me try
myself again oh look at me
okay I am peing oh I'm oh my God oh look
at me everyone oh the two of them are te
posing look at me I'm like half here and
half there I was like they're moving on
my side so what does that mean what does
that tell us I guess um I guess I need
toing I guess okay you know what is
playing the
game I am playing the game you're
playing the game okay you can play taken
over
oh what's what's even happening okay
hold
on oh oh oh you shot me while I st shot
my
house okay I made a new one
girls all right all right all right all
right I'm coming I'm
coming wait why did I do that you caught
me off guard ra why won't you do that I
get another
turn wait
it doesn't make me die anymore oh there
you
go oh hello I think the game crashed oh
no you just didn't put out your items
okay no
pic no Panic no
Panic oh that's going to be a short
one this round is so long okay I'm going
to you know what I'm going
to okay okay
oh oh I'm I'm back again in the room oh
you're back whoa oh
no Ana
multitasking yeah I'm multitasking wait
is it my turn
no oh it's R's turn yeah chill all good
yeah we're all gone now in the in on
your
screen yeah um so
drinking beer no that's so busy I'm busy
oh my God you're drinking a lot okay you
know
what okay that one didn't work so I'm
making a new one again let's between me
and you
Ana oh no what happened while I was gone
I'm okay end can you guys can you guys
join again oh all right sure sure sure
oh wait I am in again
no I don't see you I made a new one I
made I made a new room oh yeah I I see
you now I see you now I see you okay
there we
go all right all
right hello I'm here let's so it's it's
43 right
chat I haven't checked I think it was
four 42 wait four leaves
I don't
remember two blanks for leave oh two
blanks
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay what do I have you
here
a it's okay okay you can be
[Music]
here okay there we go only missing
Kiara you
livei oh oh oh
well
orange stole the orange spot
K hey you don't have Kik privileges you
don't have the perms
that works cute that cute
cute okay that works all right good good
okay are we good we're back okay we're
so back let's
go
um no one has SEC oh I do what the heck
I do have one
nice
okay um and then
G use
this going to win place your bets now
Chad place your
bets most likely
Ana because she she has two extra turns
yeah so I guess she she
won GG in that
case I don't know I I don't I don't have
anymore I don't have any more you know I
don't have a glass I don't have anything
to let me know what what's
inside just trust your instin your gut
this is what the game is all about
oh I mean I will risk it I'm going to
use my knife cuz I don't want her to
steal it from me so even if this is a
blank it should be okay
Oh
yay we did
it I
won
Yi was that the
last oh was that the last
yeah
[Music]
nice oh
man oh you're the most resourceful
resourceful I have no idea what that
means
find never up to your
imagination yeah it was fun it was fun
thank you everyone for playing thank you
yeah thank you I was like when my chat
told me that this is coming out I was
like okay okay I got to plan a collab
but then you already were like planning
one I was like okay good perfect I'm
going to yeah yeah fine this is so much
fun it was fine thank you enjoy it in
the end after all of this we all still
love each other right except me and
onion of course of course
obious despite the toxicity and
tragedy friendship restored you know
only
[Music]
love that was so cool I like this game
it's even I think it's too it's very
different from when playing against just
the the computer yeah I think much
better yeah it has this like party game
feel you
know
yeah good job everybody GG so
much play a again next time of course
yeah let's play more yeah thank you girl
thank you thank you thank you thank you
does anyone have any announcement
uh no not me I don't think so not me to
I have an announcement tomorrow I
release a new new
[Music]
cover oh yeah the one
with NI I can't wait the cover looks so
cute already
thank I can't wait I put a lot of love
into it I love I love matasa it's one of
my favorite song so nostalgic It's So
based So based
thank you thank you so
much and then um
also just just o cut it it's fine it's
fine okay okay three two one o cut it
[Music]
every byee
he
[Music]