[Music]
This program is
brought to you by our sponsors
[Music]
Hello everyone
helloveryoneHoware
youdoingniceseekers
ONLOVEYOUFRIDAY
Morningevening
at to Noon Good evening
everyone. Well,
first of all, let me
explain Holtalk's E program.  So, as always,
please listen to me for a moment,
as I'm sure some of you are new to this.
[Music] This
is an interview talk show for English speakers.The purpose is to let
people overseas
learn more about Japan's most important talents while living there.It
is brought to you by the host Chara Takanashi.This
is the 24th time.I
did a little bit of the opening.
I'm sorry, everyone.
[Music]
Thank you, it
's perfect.
Tiara-chan, Sagome, I mean, I was
nervous even before the broadcast started. I
pulled the screen, right? You were watching it, but
yeah, I always do this. It's already been 24 times.  I'm
so nervous even though I'm doing it. Peco is really
nervous every time. Please watch talk shows like this.
[Music]
IwantliketoPointer
STREAM That's what makes me so nervous.
If I may say so, I also talk about Pecola-senpai.  Okay,
what are you talking about? Did you do something?
Well before the broadcast,
that's me,
Kira-chan,
Care-chan, this is this program. Why don't I appear on this program too
?  Wasn't
there something like that?I was reading Pico.And
actually, a few days ago, I asked her to wear some kind of holt, and when I
asked her to, she brought it up.I feel like she was holding it.Beh,
Tiara-chan, listener, let's
listen, everyone.  Sae Cola and
Tiara-chan's
stuff like this There was something like that on Tiara-chan's
channel, right? I
had a dream about this Pecola. Yeah,
no, I
had a memory of that because the decoding was serious.  I
thought you wouldn't call me for the second time,
but I wonder how many people there are. Thank you very much for your help
today. Please come and see me for the second time. I
don't even remember the CU shift.
By the way,
I
also always start the tweet.  I do, but
my opening tweet is really boring,
so could you please change it this time?
[Music]
This is the second time we've stored together. Are you
misunderstanding this study?
Pecoras Yuna is definitely an office type
Shaft Witches
Senpai
First of all, the story starts with One Support
Time OK
[Music] You
mean once upon a time, right? Once upon a time, we've never been this far.'' Hey, what did we do?
No, I don't care.
Next
dayisbird & Rabbit
Dream Collaboration
Talk Show
[Music] I
'm saying this on the Dream Talk Show, so
I wrote it.
Please, please don't wake me up from my dream.
"
Okay, here's RIP Tiara.
[Music]
Well,
normally I don't do this with that guest,
but if it was Pekla Wi-Fi, I
'd definitely want to write about it.
Okay, so you've already
introduced yourself, so let's get right to it.  You
can also ask questions.
[Music]
So, the first question is,
what kind of activities do you do
? It seems like it's a lot of streaming, but not just patient streaming.  I do
n't know what it is, but I guess it's mostly being streamed now. There's a lot of games being streamed, but what game are you playing right now? It's changed so much. I recommend it to you. I'm super addicted
to NGO. I know about FG.
NGO That My Dad  But it
's Illustrica. I'm really addicted
to that wonderful game, so
who's my favorite?
Pekona is currently watching a lot of that Fate anime.
Yeah, I'll wait and see, but I often use it in FGO.  The
character
is Mr. Morgan, I don't know. He's a
Berserker.
If he's a male of the opposite sex, he's
Gilgamesh. I wonder if he's
doing anything other
than streaming. He's doing some projects other than streaming,
but he'll mainly be streaming once he's active.
Addicted. Currently streaming.
That's exactly what the
investment teacher said.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I
do this almost every day, don't you get tired?
No, it's fun. It's a
fun break after all.
If you don't have feelings, you won't be able to continue for that long.
[Music]
Haru Ayase is the best.
OkOk.
Next
question.
This is going to be a big deal,
so I don't know how to say it.
[Music]
It's become popular on YouTube and various other
sites.  I
wonder if I want to go to a place that shines brightly like this.I
see, but that
audition was
like that.How did I become a third-year student?
Next, I
only know the back side of this place, but it's like this, is
n't it?And what happened in the past?  I
didn't say it, I
didn't say it. You don't have to say it, but
why don't you just say this? It's a
little bit.
Everyone already knows that, but I see. It said, ``What should I
say?'' Picola said it many times.
When I say I'm going to use it,
[laughter]
So that's about it, Pecola.
It's a little deeper. I don't
know how far this goes, Peko. So it
was that, but the starting lineup
was Muscato, Peko, but that's it.  That's
okay, okay, okay, okay.Ok,
other people have already
said this quite a lot, so I don't know how much of my
true stomach I can say about that.I'm a
pyoko, so I'll just say it.Please
stop.
By the way, what did you think when you were called out to me
?
[Music]
Senpai: After all, I didn't watch the seniors of Hololive after all.
No, I saw that. The seniors were idols,
etc., and had a lot of
unique personalities.  No, I thought, ``Is Coola okay?''
No, you didn't think so. No, you didn't. That's why
on the first broadcast,
senpai was so cute.
At that time, he was
also doing that erotic Hololive.
Well, it's not erotic, but I
don't think it's okay. Well, I guess I was a little confused
at first. No, I don't like it when I'm
confused, but I like the streaming itself,
so even if I don't like it,
I'm glad that I can stream it.  That's cute.
OkGoogle
[Music]
Senpai, you think so now, right?
Hmm, no, I'm glad I joined. I
also got to meet Kirara-chan,
so please don't stop.
By the way, if I hadn't been scouted, I wonder if I would have
gone to the normal audition on that 5th day and passed it.
Pekura-senpai was about to
pass, so I
thought I wanted to become a vtuber,
but since I'm a VTuber, I
probably would have gone somewhere else.
[Music] I
was already conscious of that vtube thing.
Yes, it's cute, so let's do it like this.
It's crazy, right now I'm living in Peco La Bayer,
" or something like, "I want to sleep."  I'm
saying this a lot, but I don't know what it's like. I
don't think it's a good idea to be able to broadcast something like how cute she is, how she can move, etc. I thought it was a bad idea to be able to really show myself. I
understand, I understand, OK.
[Music]
Next  I'd
like to ask you a question.
Is there anything you've been unable to say due to the language barrier that you'd like to convey to people overseas? Well, I
guess it's really difficult to put into words, but
thank you for watching and supporting me.
Plus
Yes, it's not Crazy Rabbit, but it
's also said to be quite intense.
I said, "I'm going to go ahead with this," and then I
'll go with that.
[Music]
Hey,
it's a cute rabbit, right?
32 It's
called Rabbit Cute Rabbit.  Thank you
everyone for saying that. I'm
glad you haven't
said it. It's still being said, but it's
crazy. It's not Cute Rabbit.
Get rid of the crazy. Maybe, maybe, um.
Don't you have something to say about Ao-chan? Your
senior has been
practicing English and is now
able to say what he wants to say on his own.
Pecola-san, I
can understand the letters, but I can understand the words,
but I can't help but listen and listen to
myself.  When I suddenly want to say something in a sentence,
my mind goes crazy and I can't seem
to come up with the words.That's why
Tiara-chan can't speak at all, and she can't even listen.  I
can understand a few words like Sekine's, but I ca
n't understand everything, so I
think I should study harder.However,
when I saw Pecola-senpai's recent opportunities to speak English, I
thought she had really improved.  Right?
[Music]
What's that about English
? It's like a message game, but it's not like that.
When I use English, Mom, here and there, here and there, I really get better at it.  That's what I
thought.
Oh, I'm so happy. I want you to teach me English next time. Are you
asking me to teach you English? Even though it's
not Korean.
[Laughs]
Just in case, if
someone who doesn't speak your native language is fluent.  I wonder
what it is about those people who don't understand English
that make them so easy to teach.It
's said that it's because they understand their positions well that they become such good teachers even if they're not pushy.Well,
just ask Kari-chan.
Because it's Kari-chan's teacher, I
can understand something about Calliope-chan.She
speaks in English that is easy to understand during the message game.It's
because she's
Peko.I thought it was really amazing.OkAnd
[Music]
Wood
[Music] [Music] [
Music]
[  [Music]
[Music]
Okay,
next question.
[Music]
What is Hekoma-senpai's favorite thing to stream?
Game karaoke, after all.
Well, that's what I do most of the time
.
Hmm, I can't stream anymore without a game.
How about
collaborations? I like collaborations, but I don't know
what it is, I'm nervous, I
wonder if I'll do it, or something. I'm
not used to collaborations, so I'm not used to collaborating with people.
Google
[Music] I
'm addicted to [Music], but is there
any other game that I love the most
?  I have
n't played it much, but I
like Minecraft because it has a sense of movement, and I'm looking forward to Pokemon,
which has been on sale since yesterday on the course next time.Oh, I
guess I'll
play it tomorrow, starting on Sunday.I see, I'm
really into the last part.
But
[Music]
But I guess it's over now.
okok
Senpai recently
started getting a new pet.  I
asked him to tell me about the pets he buys.Yes.What
made you start
?
[Music]I think I won a
Finding Monkey.I
want an explanation.I watched that hacking
monkey explanation video.I
didn't mean it in a bad way.
[Music]
When I saw the video of the solution, I
thought it wasn't really that way. It
's a
joke. It's completely a joke. It looks like a monkey, so
this guy looks like a monkey.
Wait a minute, I thought, ``I should buy a monkey.'' Wait, it
was meant in a
bad way. I thought it wasn't meant in a bad way, so I
started using it myself. But that
's a lie. The way people
choose pets has changed a bit.
[Music]
Everyone.  I'm
so confused that I've
become Migo. It's still meaningless. It's
become a meme. I
was fooled by the explanation video. It
seems like Nonono is bad. I
'll never say it.
But the
reason I started keeping a cat was because of my cat's diary,
but in reality, the
first thing that came to mind was this leopard-print Jill-
kun.Actually, yeah, it's
cute.I want to
buy one that's that cute.It's
not difficult,
but it becomes difficult once you become a family member.  No need. I
did my homework,
watched videos of people winning,
looked at the pros and cons, and
thought about whether or not I should go home on my own.
But first of all...
Monkey-chan is hard to come by.I
can't buy it, so yeah, I
've researched the pros and cons.The
pros and cons
are: It's soothing and cute, and then it comes with gravel, but the cons are that it poops and pees all over the place.  That's a lot of people, but she's so cute
that she makes up for it.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Cats, yes, yes.
NEC Broadcasting I
say it myself.
Poor
Pekko, it's a bad day right now. I feel sorry for Pekko. I'm just
translating for Senpai,
so it's
not my fault.
Bed Um
[Music]
By the way,
how old do these animals get? It's
said that monkeys and monkeys live about 134 years and 5 years, just like cats.
[Music]
No, I don't think it's going to be big,
but I think it'll fit in the palm of your hand. I
see.
[Music]
[Music] I'll take you
outside. There's a cat
outside that I haven't told you to catch yet.
But if I don't give him two doses, he'll get bone disease,
so I
'm putting the gauge in right away, so
please give me some
vitamin D. [Music] It would be nice if he got vitamin D every time I took him outside.
I'm sorry, you're making
fun of me. Don't make fun of monkeys. You're making fun of magnetism.
But it's
really
strange, because there are many countries in the world where you can't keep this animal
as a normal pet.
There was also a video of that guy, and he looked
like a bush baby,
and there were a lot of them on YouTube, so I
thought it was normal for people overseas,
even though there were probably not many people in Japan.  I
want to see it
Well, if you ever come to Pekoland,
please be sure to check out OkGoogle. Please
leave the pet talk for a moment.
Next
[Music]
Pecola-senpai's mother's reaction when I revealed to her that
I was a vtuber.
It was a pretty big topic, and it
was even broadcast on TV. I'm really curious about
how they kept it a
secret until then,
and I
'd like to know how their family members reacted, and how other family members reacted as well.  I
guess I should say it was
noisy because I was just playing around on the internet, so from my
mommy's point of view, I
think she always thought it was overtime.  I
think that's what
Peko-chan was
doing, and that's when I said it properly, and even
now, I'm
still getting a lot of support from you.I
don't think I should have said it sooner, Mom.  kana
Eh, I don't think that much, but after all, people
check my streams, and
if there's something I want to eat on a stream, they
make something for me the next day, or they
buy it for me.
I
don't know. That's cute. Do you know the reactions and opinions of other family members other than the mother? I
haven't told the other family members properly, so I'm sorry.  It's
not like I'm getting any kind of reaction through the do-throughs, I've never been told that I'm doing something like that,
and we just don't touch each other.
[Music] I
don't say it because it's awkward.
No, I don't even want to touch anything anymore.  I
think it's kind of like that, but even if Pecola
were to say something like, ``Oh, please try again,'' I
think it would be like we were just watching each other, and I think we
were both reading each other's atmosphere, so I guess it's me.  The
guy who gave me the lottery is just an
inefficient guy. Does
he watch Vtubers?
No, I don't know what he's watching, and he doesn't even talk about it,
so I
don't know if he watches or not.  I don't know if I watch it
or not, but I used to like anime, so
if I still like it, I'll still watch it.
VTubers are already quite popular and much more
common than overseas, so
there's a possibility that they're watching them.What do you think?  [
Music]
[Music]
That's helpful.That's right.That one at 9 o'clock was in
that case of Connect rather than Bar Brats.That's
quite a senior.He gave me my carrot.2It's
true that the carrot senior is popular.
I was about to give it to him.I was about to give it to
him.That's some big guy.Maybe
that carrot guy is coming.That's probably
mine.Well,
just to explain a little bit,
there was a project called Valkyr Connect, and
those four people, those
two members of Japan, and the house.  Two of our members
were participating, and Pekura-senpai and I
were also participating, but when we
tried to give each other presents, they asked me what I wanted to give them, and I was
like, ``I'm sure,
carrots.''  I
think I was writing something about delicious carrots and something like that, but a
guy came along quite a while ago.The one with the
compressed sweetness hasn't been released yet,
so it's kind of small, but the
one that looks like it's a huge carrot probably came.
Here it is.
Wow, I'm wearing that too. Well, I've
been wearing all sorts of presents,
but for example, a cat's robot toilet.
[Music] I
'm a cat owner, so you can probably tell.  It's a
pain to get rid of that poop when you go to the front, so
I asked for a robot that can do that automatically, so
that's a little bit of a
big help,
but besides that, we
also have that huge beam bag,
that orange color.  A huge bottle box arrived, and it
looked like a carrot, but it was something like that. I
don't remember, but
I'm sure Peko was trying to give his senior a
delicious
engine.
[Music]  I
wasn't about to give you anything amazing, but it
was strangely delicious. There was a carrot on the tortoiseshell egg.
Maybe it wasn't that. It's stuck in my hair right now. That's it. We have
n't had the same number of people since the day we debuted. We've been
changing this every day.  Maybe it's a hit
[Music] I
got it from Tiara-chan and tried it out.
[Music]
[Music] I'm
sorry, but this story is a bit long, but
uhm, it's
big.
[Music]
Okay, this
is a long question, but I've heard that
before,
from a full perspective, Hekora-
senpai is the
type of person who wears Uniqlo, which I
really like. I've heard people say that she doesn't have a very good fashion sense, and that she's
a little uncool.
But, you know, Mariseb
[laughter], Senpai.  I was
so inspired by your fashion class
that I
even drew an illustration that I didn't need.Has your
fashion sense improved since then?
Does Uniqlo still exist?
Epekoze this
Who is this before?
Pecola-senpai is not the type to wear Uniqlo, she
's a junior. I said she was a peko-senpai, but who
said that? Well, the one who calls herself senpai is that
one of mine.  But
UNIQLO hasn't come that far, but I
wonder what's going on.
[Music]
Bucket, that, T-shirt, etc. I
wonder if they wrote it for me or something. So I went home, right? I went home, right?
[Music]  If you
look good, this will make your butt look like that. Was there something like
that? Yeah, no, I was wearing some kind of lame clothes, but I don't know if it's okay or not, but this seems to be a surprisingly good outfit for that day.  It
seems like he drew that illustration,
so
maybe his sense of style has improved.I've
never seen him before, so there's
probably a lot of stuff on the internet,
like ZOZOTOWN,
I don't know.
Nikiyo may not understand, but yes,
there is a mail order site, and I
often buy songs like ZOZOTOWN and other songs when I'm out and about because I think they're cute, but I'm
not the type of person who likes Uniqlo that much.
It's the first time I've heard that Uniqlo exists, and I've
only just heard it before.Yes, Uniqlo is also fashionable.Well, the design is a bit simple,
but I wouldn't say it's lame.  I
think UNIQLO is very fashionable, so
now that I have UNIQLO, I'm going to master it. That's
good. Even with UNIQLO,
if you have a good fashion sense, I
think you can look cool with any brand.
Oh, Koala-chan, yes, Marine. Now,
send me that number.
This is what I sent to Kira-chan because she gave it to me. It
says that she had beautiful feet, so I gave it to her to represent that.
Eh, Mainichi Senpai, I'm listening to this right now.
[Music]
This is it.
This is definitely very cute.
If she was really wearing clothes like this, she would be
too cute. I
'd give her a perfect score of 100. I
want to come too.
[Music]
No, it doesn't have to be scary
[Laughs]
Hmm, ok, well.  During this episode, I
asked the listeners to ask me a question,
and this one came from Rika-san.  Some
people may have said it was weird. You're the one who
picks up snacks for those who hate it. I'm going to master
Uniqlo from now on.
questioncamefromon
Vinofunds
You
do a lot of special project distribution and videos,
but did you draw inspiration from somewhere?
First of all,  I'd like to know
how you both choose the games that are on the bill.I
don't think they do anything special in terms of planning and distribution.  I'd
say it's a planned distribution, or rather, that video from the other day. Recently, I've been doing things like ``Why and What, Peko-chan,'' Midnight Minecraft, and things like that, um, but somehow, that little mystery, that little bit of mystery, something that kids want to know.  I'd
like to do something like that, and
then I'd try something like that, and then I'd
try that joke, and then I'd try something
like that, and
I'd be a
courtroom painter.
Pecole is often used as a joke in overseas dramas
such as Crazy Rabbit
and Pecola and Arrested.It's a
song, so if you actually get arrested, what
will happen to you?  If there's something I've
wanted to try or
something that seems popular, I'll do a little research and
think about doing it.
[Music]
[Music] I
think this is fine, so next time
Before you listen to this,
there's a paulownia key tree, so I'd like you to take a look at it
let'sGO
[Music]
overy Let's
move Yes,
please prepare
[Music]
Disappear Well then, please
take a
look Please take a look
[Music]
So why?  Let's make a sword. The
strongest weapon. It's not
dangerous.
[Music]
Hey.
What's this? I didn't have a Holo subjet and was
able to upload it using my normal mackerel, so I tried
it.  It's
not too bad. It's so
nostalgic.
[Music]
There's a sheep over there. The
old man who really wants to use it is the
first
[Music]
[Applause]
Even if you drop it in magma, it won't disappear. You
[Music]  I
'm serious, oh, so I'm going to throw it, but I'm so
anxious, so cute. The
organization has already done this. How are we going to do this? Oh,
this is what we're
talking about. We've already gotten three episodes, but
wait a minute, it's scary. Wait a minute, wait a minute, seriously wait a minute.
Oh no. [Music] Ah,yo.
Now you're
gone. Are you gone now? You're gone now.
What? You're back? You
're back.
[Music]
Don't give up on your past Peko seniors.
[Laughter]
[Music]
But I'm
holding on
too much. I
don't have it. I'll flush it.
Hurry up.
[Music]
[Applause]
But it's still hard to get the
letters
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh, that's good.
[Laughs]
In other words, you
shouldn't be 100% intrusive on what the listener is saying. It's true,
listeners, that sometimes lies. It
wasn't a lie, but
[Music] You
should imitate it.  No, it's
dangerous.
[Music]
So let's go back. By the way,
from Pepero-senpai's place,
my voice has been coming back a little bit.
Sorry for the lie, okok.
Healed, healed, good morning. It's
not healed.
I can still hear it. Well, I can hear it, but
I don't care. [Music] I can hear it, but I don't care.
[Music]
Now, I
just saw a cutout of Minecraft. It looks
like Minecraft or Rush.  I
think you have to
play these games for a long time in order to get stronger. How long have you been playing those games?
Actually, I
played Minecraft for the first time after joining Hololive, and I was really hooked.  I've
really been doing a lot of streaming
[music], and I've
been doing it behind the scenes, too.In the beginning, I was
just doing [music], so how long have I been doing it?Well, it's
been a long time.If I didn't have a job, I'd do
it.  If it wasn't for streaming, it's almost time now.I don't know how much I'll be
addicted to something that I would have done if I had free time.I don't know how much I'll be able to do it.Hey, I
didn't even see the ending before I saw this.  I've
become so strong that I wonder what's going on,
and
how many hours a day I spend playing it.I got really
hooked.
Season 2 has already reached
the point where I'm really hooked,
so it's been as long as when I was hooked on Minecraft.  There was probably a
time when it was almost there, maybe it
was the same, maybe it was the same thing.  That's
interesting, I really like games like that.
[Music]
[Music] What I
wanted to hear was
Pecola-senpai's Minecraft distribution, including Fan Tiara.
What is the biggest or most extreme one? The
biggest one is TNT, attntt, or TT.
The biggest one is TTT, but the one that is extreme or slightly
dangerous is TNT.
Hmm, that's right.The
museum-like song that blew up the 3rd generation when I first started playing Minecraft was
probably the worst.I
remember the
[music] from that time when I was watching young people.There's
also some local Cannon music.  I was making it, I
was making it, I was making it
[Music] It
didn't stop at all, it was terrible,
the world was going to be destroyed, the world was going to be destroyed,
Picola-senpai Yeah
[laughter]
Something dangerous and terrible happened.By
the way, did you know that
last time,
Minecraft only makes mistakes?The server in that house
that Amelia made when I showed it to you.That's
right, that's the
inspiration for TTP.  I've been using it as 3 pieces throughout the whole time.
Yeah, yeah, Ame-chan. Even if I'm
sick, it's
pipi.
[Music]
Anyway, I
'm a rabbit who likes TNT.
[Music]
Explosion is an art group
Explosion Explosion, just everything explodes
OK, but this story about Minecraft is already
getting too long, so I'm going to
speed up the characters a little bit. I'm going to speed things up a little bit.
[Music]
On the final day, we'll
become everyone's enemy and we
'll have a player war.
But what did Pecola feel like in the beginning?
Pecola had made a huge amount of
bombs, bombs, etc.,
but they were taken away.
So, I thought, ``This is terrible, I won't be able to do anything,'' so I
joined Detsuichan's team and wondered if I could do that.Even if I
thought I could betray him, I betrayed him, and in reality, I lost
my family to him.  I
had no plans to protect the base at all, so at first I
thought it was okay to leave it as it was already solidified and there was no need to protect it, but I was wondering
if it would turn into a graveyard along with that thing?  I
thought I was going to go home, but everyone around me was already there, including the
vice principal
and Piccole, all
beaten up and beaten up, but it
was fun. It was
great. They were
all doing really well. They were all mixed in. I
was killed, though.
[Music] I
made a mistake.
[Music]
Senpai has killed enough people.
[Laughs] I
never expected Kiera-chan to betray me.  I
thought she wouldn't kill Pecola, but she
turned out to be an idiot.I don't understand.I was worried about Sakura-senpai's feelings about me, so I was
planning to watch her from a big tower in the next season, but no
one was there.
Oh, that's what happened. Hmm, there was no one there.
At the end of 3, there was almost no one. There
was a bed, but as
expected, it was a one-two, so I wish 3 had been like that.  Well, I
do
n't understand why you've already left the map in the middle of the map because it seems like there's a bug here too.
[Music]
[Music] The
usual
yes
speed  During the quiz, I'll speed up a bit and
ask a lot of questions, but are you
ready?
OK OK
[Music]
As for the weather, which one do you prefer?
Karl
:Ok,
rice, men, or Saizeria.  Are
you on
Instagram or
Twitter? Canned
apple or orange juice?
[Music]
Climb a mountain or run a marathon.
Hmm, what kind of clan black is this? OK, I wonder if it's
amazing. My
arms are my
computer, and my computer is a game key. That Playstation.
Which one do I like?
Putting pineapple on top of pizza.  Is it
spicy or sweet? 3
Hmm, tea or coffee can
Cheese
Welcome to the beach by the sea? If you
go to a famous big city university, it
says CT Should you sleep naked or with clothes on? Wear clothes.
Pajamas and pajamas are OK
Favorite events Halloween, Christmas, Tanabata
Instagram, etc.
[Music] It's
probably the Instagram I was thinking of watching Yay yay
7 cars Family Mart or Lawson
7 I probably
like it I
prefer phone calls that use messages
Text tone
Giving presents or receiving them  Which one is
better?
[Music]
OK
What is your blood type?
BB I see.
B What kind of person is B? I
don't know what type of person Tiara is.
But people overseas don't really know what their blood type is. They
don't have a hairdresser
or something like that. No, I don't know much about blood type fortune-telling,
so I
often hear in Japan that people have this kind of blood type.  I do
n't remember
[Music] She's
cute, she's a
genius, and she
's like that. She's
full of motherhood, she
's strong, she's like that. The more you remember, the more you learn, the more you
'll know.
Peeposit Don Breeze &
Pilot
Order
Yes, thank you.Actually, the question I
always put in is that the
person
has passed away, so everyone is
confused.It's a little bit in English.Secrets,
Maiden's SecretsAt
first, that's
not what I was talking about.
Let's get back to the question. So let's
hurry up and eat. OK
[Music]
Next time
[Music] Let's
watch it together.
Okay, jajan.
Why do I have to watch the first broadcast?
No.
[Music] I'll
probably never be able to come again. I'm making you watch this for the first time. It's
getting better here. It's
cute. You do
n't seem cute now. But you're
cute.
[Music] -
[Music]
[Laughter]  It's
not cute, it's
almond. I
can't hear it. It's
not strange. I can
hear almond right now, but it's probably not right. It's
probably just a coincidence. What the heck is it? It sounds like
almond. What on earth
is Mondo?  I
tried almonds too, and it felt like a campika. That's a
lie, it's Campika's 3rd generation live performance. It's
Pikola Pico Almond Almond
[Music]
Well,
once I heard it, it only sounded like almonds. The
3rd
generation's plate, Pekola Pyoko -
Oh no!
What's this seriously? Your
cute intonation is strange.
To be honest,
[Music]
Please stop playing almonds.
I'm absolutely sorry.
I
can't hear you.
[Music] I
can't really hear your name.
[Music]
Anyway,
I wanted to compile the cutout of the cat because it's usually Pecola-senpai's
greeting because it's cute.I
guess that's why it was strange in the fog.Today
too, I
was giving Konpeko Compact Greetings.
What happened to the old Don Don Don? I do
n't
use it anymore. I certainly haven't used it lately.
[Laughs] I
gave up on this one because it
sounded better than the original.
No, I don't think that's the case. I've
used it once for a project or something, but
even though I'm wondering how it's going to work, I'm like, oh, please
do it like this.
If you're doing well, then let's practice again.
[Music]
Okay, game.
What's this?  No more
[Music]
Now that you've finished cutting out the clips, let's
move on to the next question.
For me, I really admire Pecora Latin Pie as a streamer,
but for Pecora-senpai, are there any
idols or Vtubers who are an
inspiration to you?
For example, me.
Since I'm new to spring, I
wanted to say something, but
what about Yukari Tamura
? Oh yeah, the tortoiseshell hole Maamomochi is amazing. I
like her, but as a streamer
and as a reference for her activities, yeah, Momochi is
amazing.  Peko was
such an
amazing person that people even said that she was a professional when it came to learning the deaf.  I
guess when it comes to streaming, I look at various people's videos and other streams and see what's good about them, and what I find fun to watch.
]
[Music]
When I heard that Hello Polo liked Momochi, I was so happy
that I was at Baby Water
Berryz Kobo.  She's so
cute, she can't sing, and her face is so cute.I
loved her, but I've said that I've been to that concert many times.As a
child, I only went to the Pecola concert once,
and I'd rather take pictures of Momochi.  I
also liked Berry's, but I
also really liked Mochi, so I would
often go to places like Ikebukuro to see their photo books and CDs.When Nenan was on sale, there was always a place in the basement.  I've
said it over and over again about Venice and Nakano Sanfraza's Big Observation concert.If you
like [music], I've always wanted to talk about things like this.  I
want to talk to
you. Even if I say I almost like you because
of that song, I know quite a few of the songs.
By the way, I
know that song, ``Forgive me, I'm cute.''
[Music] I
'm at home
Thank you very much Yes
[Music] I
like it Tsujiji
Many people I
really love the balance and harmony of the 3rd generation, including the characters.
How would you describe the relationship between the members?
If
Pecola-senpai  I'll leave this part for later. Please
describe in words the
relationships you have with each of the 3rd generation members.  I think it
would be better to call them comrades-in-arms or occupiers of a cell, but
rather than rivals, they
are friends who are fighting alongside each other.I see.Well, they
may
not be family members, but they are
more than friends.  It feels like we're less than a family.
[Music]
What would happen if a senior lived with the 3rd generation members?
Who would he share the room with? How would you deal with that first?  I
wonder what will happen.If we are
going to share a room, I
don't want to see who I can live with.What
about Wani-senpai?
Marin goes to the big room with Flare, Noel, and the older sister group,
Majima-chan.
Pecola stays in a room by herself, so
that's not the case.Marie definitely likes Noel and
Flare, and you know that older sister who
likes to play dog in a group.
Pecola is Peko, so Pecola is rather one thing.The more we
are together, the more we use each other, so we
can't always live together.Okay, I see.
But if we were to live together,
if we had to live in the same room,
who would be better?
[Music] I'm
watching this
Streaming
[  [Applause] I don't know
who itis,
but Marie is a really nice person, so she's
willing to help me with things like counseling, so I can't help
it.  I'm
going to make it Mario Mari, so I'm
going to make Mario seriously, and I'm going to do something like that, and the distribution and
stuff, and it's going to be like Mae Corner,
but if we actually lived together,
Pecola would probably
understand that I'm not good at that kind of thing.
Pecola: I think it would be easy to live together. I see
.
[Music]
This is Marin-senpai.
[Music] What if
the four of us
lived in the same house instead of in the same room?  I
wonder who will do the cooking. I don't know. Is there anyone who will cook? I don't know, Noel or Flair, or I'll do the over-the-top cooking. I don't know, but I'll leave all the cooking to someone else. I see. So there's three of us, right? For now.  I do
n't think it's okay to be spoiled
by someone in the older sister group.Who's
going to let the other members clean up?
Who's going to tell the other members to clean up because it's so dirty?
[Music]  The
person who cleans is the person who
cleans, or the person who tells you to clean.
Well, what do you think? It's because she doesn't really like cleaning.
Pecole is the one who cooks the dishes, the older sister
group makes her clean, and the older sister makes her seem like she can't do it.
Well, numbers are boring and
troublesome. I hate them, so I looked at them.
Hmm, I'm worried about whether it'll work or not, but I'm sorry to
hear that.
[Music]
I brought you Religion.
Pecoland only has a MV for Brain's song yet. Are you
planning on making the first MV for other songs?
Well, to be honest, they haven't released it yet,
but they've been
steadily working on it, so I think they'll be able to do it this year.
Please wait.
[Applause]
[Music]
I'm looking forward to it. I've received some good information.
Thank you.
OK.
Next
Sorry, just one more.
Pecola-senpai is on the list of most popular female streamers.  to  Have you
been ranked several times?
Do you feel any pressure or stress from the large number of viewers or attention? I'm
serious.
Pressure.
Is it pressure or stress from the attention? Oh no.
If I say I don't feel it anymore, it
would be a lie about pressure.  I do
n't really feel like I'm being watched a lot, but
at first there
were times when I wondered why people were watching me so much, but I guess I've
gotten used to it now.  I've
gotten used to the pressure and stress so I don't feel it anymore, but I
guess it's still
there.npg
on
Healing It looks like it's disgusting
What was your reaction when you saw it on that list?
[Music]
Nationwide  So
when I first saw it, I wondered if it was being watched so much all over the world, and I was so happy,
but I can
only speak Chinese Japanese, so I
felt sorry for it, but I also didn't speak English either.  I
felt like I should have studied a little more, but actually, I
was happy and felt like I did it.
[Music]
[Music] A
female streamer, a
member of Waukyure, and
those two beautiful ladies.  We
were talking about wanting to collaborate with each other, but I don't know if we ever talked about that time or anything like that.To
be honest, there's a lot of things that happened to me,
like Horsepower, and all sorts of other things.  I
collaborated with streamers on games and things like that,
like Amon Grass.At
that time, it
was really popular and I'd
like to see a lot of different streamers doing it.See
this too.  Please invite me. I was joking
when I said that on the stream,
but I never expected it. I'd love to do a collaboration to draw Valkyrie. I
saw the clipping, and I didn't
see it. I
thought there was nothing there.  I
think I'll have to talk to someone.Also,
since Fecola still supports me and can't speak English, I
thought that even if I tried to do that, we wouldn't be able to win.Hmm, I see, I kind of
understand that.We can
have a proper
conversation.  It's difficult if you can't do it.
[Music]
If you'd like, I'll translate for you, so please feel free to
let me know. Of course, if you
really want to do it, where can I do it?
Thank you very much for following me.This
is my last question.What
is Hololive
?I
see.It's Hollow Knife, but what is the most important thing?
Hololive?But what is Hololive?Or
rather, thank you for this live.First
of all,
yes, it's a continuation of what I said earlier.  However, the reason why
Pecola has been seen by so many people is because
she
has worked hard to broadcast it, but first of all, if she
didn't get into Hololive, she would have made her debut.  I
didn't do that, I don't think anyone would have seen anything like this,
so I'm glad I
included it in Hololive. I
think the best thing to do is to be grateful.
[Music] [
Music]
Thank you [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you.
Thank you for telling me so much about this.Alright,
just in case, let me just promote a little bit of it.Um,
Sunday, UnSunday Asia Snow
[Music]
You and Restoration Eviction,
That Sunday, This
Since it's the 2nd anniversary of Talk, I'm
going to do an interview, and not only that, but I'm going to
use this studio, this cat's studio, and do it in 3D, so I'm going to do it in
3D on VRChat, so
please take a look, and I
'll also be announcing the first version.  So, what's that?
Tell me right now.
Well, that's something to look forward to on Sunday. Well, Holtalk on Sunday
will be on Monday morning in Japan time, but if you
have time, please come and see it.
Thank you everyone for watching today. Thank you
too, Tecora-senpai.
Raku: Do you
remember your final greeting? I
asked you to do it a long time ago.
[Music]
I remember, I remember.
No, no, no, no, no,
can I hear it?
[Music]
[Laughter]  ]
First greetings, okay, okay, that's okay, I'll forgive you. It's
okay,
Daundien Jendsen.
[Music] In German, ah, it's Bill. [Music]
There's a senior in Pokemon,
right? [Music] Ok, everyone.
Thank you for your hard work on your senior's daytime Pokemon.
[Music]