foreign
[Music]
looking
good
[Music]
foreign
little room
[Music]
foreign
uh hello hello
what the [\h__\h] is the matter with my game
capture card I see it on the screen and
I'll be us but not in the game captures
green why
[Music]
I mean Pokemon probably
isn't really uh
I think I wouldn't even matter if I
played an obvious
hmm oh
did you guys like the remix it's
actually pretty old it's a pretty old
heart Challenger remix there are not
many heart Challenger remixes out there
but
I was thinking about heart Challenger
before the Stream
uh where's my phone here okay I was
thinking about heart Challenger before
the stream and I was like hmm
maybe change the PGM into it scared you
a little why
why you were surprised that we had
something else on I wonder why yeah I
wonder why
it's almost Valentine's Day
[Music]
yeah yeah
uh what Christmas
oh
I guess yeah in time for Valentine's Day
probably should get rid of the Christmas
music
um
Valentine's celebration
that's right stream stream it stream it
stream it stream heart Challenger
meow chunkers
did you hear that
wow
huh now she stopped answering she was
meowing in the distance wow
wow
eh I'm not gonna use glue to make
chocolate come on I
got a glue
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no
uh yeah chunky singing a solo concert
for us we're gonna play Pokemon Legend
I'll kills
uh once again
um I suppose since my well capture card
leaves me no choice
um even though I restarted it okay so
I'm gonna play the nobs okay that's fine
with me
doesn't really make much of a difference
oh
um
[Music]
Pokemon wait is there a sound gonna work
though
wait a second
I'm supposed to hear a sound yet right
let me open it wait a second
well I did not hear that
oh it's feeling a pain in the ass
it's being a little bit weird
um Elgato game capture close that [\h__\h]
again
and uh
close this I suppose
do we have any other processes open no
hmm
okay Wawa and computers a Dream Team
like
shut the light to the weight sound yeah
do you you don't hear oh it's working
oh [\h__\h] we're like in the middle of
nowhere
uh
welcome everybody
okay I don't have to play for OBS
anymore
[Music]
so
I played a little bit on my vacation I
also changed my outfit doesn't look cute
look at my orange
I I am I combined some uh New pieces
into this fashionable beautiful
wonderful Majestic masterpiece
yes yes Orange it's the color of this
season it's a trend Trend color guys you
just don't know it yet but it's the
color of the season and what I did off
screen is I filled out the map uh of
this area and the other area as well uh
I went to places that I didn't go before
through the water uh mostly there wasn't
really much for me to do but anyway
there but I wanted to check it out
anyway
um
I was like
his dad
Psyduck dead
no just sleeping probably probably and I
also did some
visiting of uh you know those Rifts
those space Rift thingies
uh and I did some cyclists but yeah it's
not not that much
um I waited to continue the main quest
again and what am I doing with the main
quest anyway
Highlands Empire
uh 19 Pokemon yes uh and we see here
please take a look
um I have an alpha patches
and I caught a Flareon
because it wasn't that Rift but I
actually
um
I I don't need it because I have my
beautiful nine tails
uh I kind of messed up I was in a in a
space rift raft Rift
um before on my vacation and I saw I saw
a
um what's it called again I saw the the
night the night
um was it Umbreon the night Evie
but it disappeared so quickly
uh so I didn't even get a chance to try
to catch it Umbreon yeah that one I
would have considered putting into my
team so I kept on looking for Rifts to
find more Eevee evolutions but uh the
only one I could find was flarian I just
caught it because why the hell not but
um yeah it disappeared so quickly
ah
money
[Music]
all right
look at me with my money so much money
what an alpha polygon I was so excited
to support it gone
um
yeah I caught a lot of new Pokemon for
the first time polygon is so cute
polygon already researched level 10.
nice patches is also 10.
I was doing my best oh right horn level
10. Hunter 10.
oh oh yeah I did
um
I I I was like uh uh trying to get a
shiny Haunter because I saw that there
was a mass
um what's it called a mass event of
haunters
um I didn't do it too seriously though I
I wonder how people do it do they just
like save before they go there uh the
outbreak they saved before it and then
if they didn't see you shiny they'd come
back to it
I just killed everything and hoped for a
shiny one to spawn because I wasn't so
serious about it but I didn't find
anything of course not uh
uh-huh safe before yeah I did save it
but then I was like whatever I don't
really don't really want it that bad
anyway and I think I did also do a
different outbreak of something else
uh before that
um
[Music]
I see so many people okay not so many
but I see so a bunch of people randomly
finding shinies being lucky I want that
to tomato
why can I not find wait am I getting a
new rank already online wow I want a
Shiny randomly too I don't want to work
hard for it I just want to find it
randomly
is that too much to ask like oh my God
no shiny yet yeah
[Music]
now where is my phoenix look huh
um
foreign
I also did a lot of collecting
of
um everybody's lost [\h__\h] why do you guys
keep on dying
unbelievable and I realized I could buy
one of the
uh evolution stones
um to get a specific Eevee evolution but
I'm not sure which one
and I have a bunch of them on my own I
have like a I have
wait Shiny Stone
oh
what the [\h__\h]
that's misleading makes you think that
you can turn Pokemon into a [\h__\h]
shiny
um no I have like thunderstones I have
Leaf Stones I have I have water stones I
have fire stones but what I don't have
is like these these ones are the ones
for Umbreon and and the other one is it
oh which ones was it
is this one for Umbreon
it doesn't too bad it would be too easy
and too cheap
wait which one is for Umber
ah oh yeah right that was friendship and
uh evolve at night
that's right I forgot um
[Music]
should we do it because Umbreon looks so
cool
hmm
if we know
I'm eating Pokey
Mikado
um
[Music]
I feel like I'm too far ahead level wise
because I've been holding off on the
main story for you guys
see I got another ring
I can count this time this time I can
count six I was about to say five for
the six I think
correct me if I'm wrong
[Music]
um
my mom
okay
I think
um where's my Minecraft I am I think one
thing that I did off-screen
uh main quest was one thing that when I
opened my switch and my Pokemon game and
I tried to run out I realized that they
didn't let me out I had to talk to
the peeps that were standing over there
otherwise
um it wouldn't let me go uh so I talked
to them didn't nothing really so
important uh was said and then
and then I continued but that's all I
did just one tiny dialogue
yeah yeah it was a awkward spot to end
my stream at last time
mm-hmm
um
I have a question to you guys here
[Music]
this Quest
makes you catch I think a total of free
clumbies
each in a different location
I did the first and the second Super
annoying because you got to keep on
going back
now I was looking on reminisce Island
but there are no [\h__\h] colombies on
raminus Island
why
I need to hit a tree
oh what the [\h__\h]
okay
well
also
um is it just me that's having a problem
with like the them stating the locations
here like reminisce Island I'm like
where the [\h__\h] is reminisce Island and
you can't you can't look at any other
map besides the one that you're in right
now right so when I'm in the city I'm
like
I don't know where Romanus island is so
I tried out each area and go there and
check the set out
oh [\h__\h] well thank you well that problem
is solved then all right uh so Romulus
Island uh was
wait how do I go in then okay okay
Romulus island is here okay
well then let's quickly check for that
stupid Columbine
I didn't know that did the menu say that
I didn't see that in the in the
interface
[Laughter]
hey where does it say wait wait send oh
it doesn't say oh I mean okay I just
thought you could zoom
[Music]
I didn't realize you could zoom more I
don't know anyway
let me get that stupid combine
hmm
uh
stupid Columbia
who cares about Columbus man
wow
Alpha
here out of all places here
[Music]
Alpha catch it
I don't really see why I should catch
any Alphas that I don't want to use in
my team but I suppose
oh so why is the moving tree oh I caught
I caught that monkey over there
you see the monkey Fire Starter monkey I
caught it when I was last here when I
was looking for that stupid other thing
bro where's the combi
Columbia
and I feel like I feel like I I feel
like it's Evolution was here too yes yes
yes yes and I think I tried catching it
did I succeed
let me like look
uh hello
wait what
let me look at you
hi yeah
no I did not succeed wow
[Laughter]
Alpha Starly okay cool when you said
moving tree
this one's not moving
I have Ultra Balls yet maybe I could
catch it now because now I can catch up
to uh level 80 and with Ultra Balls
this one is not moving
this is moving it's not moving
or could it be in that stone I don't
think so this one's not moving either
okay
what about this one
I need some questions
what the [\h__\h]
hmm I have to reload need to restart
Matt by leaving what
[Applause]
one go there and be like bamboozled
it's not here like for real it's really
not here you're not just too stupid to
find it it's really not here
where was that Alpha Abra
where was that Alf Alpha Opera
isn't it over there
yeah my discoveries aren't you it's not
fair
okay
so I have
I have uh Ultra Balls now did she give
me some no she just give gave me the
recipe
[Music]
what level is that Alpha album or anyone
can I craft I can't craft it
can craft this one though
okay I'll try to catch it with uh
uh with a great ball
after checking out the level yeah but
you know what let me I like using smoke
bombs
with those stupid operas
they [\h__\h] disappear all the time
all right 24 only
little [\h__\h]
hey
No you little [\h__\h]
okay
haha
what was that
you [\h__\h] bastard
I [\h__\h] hate eyebrows
okay I don't care about this glass
anymore I'm just gonna pick up that
she's gonna pick up that bag
yeah I forgot that once you go into a
fight with an Abra it will usually be
like I'm out of here
I forgot about that
okay we'll do the main quest
forgot that you were there
where is the there it is
don't be intimidated by that huge ass
relaxer
there we go okay
ah well I didn't catch anything
I did try a smoke bomb I was hidden by a
smoke bomb why am I moving like this oh
my God what's happening why am I moving
like this
hello
why am I not moving
oh my God
has it been like this all this time
or just now
missing the outbreak I don't really care
about the outbreak but I guess we can
check it out
if there's a shiny if there is not then
I don't care
miracle
[Music]
shiny
no shiny
I found it yeah but
I don't care
[Laughter]
no it's shiny
oh I'm still lagging
[Music]
um
I know I know I know it will spawn more
if I defeat them I know
but ain't nobody got time for that
oh
[Music]
wait what I did catch it
huh
what
oh it was just encountering it
I like so I just teleport oh hooray
hooray
why am I so laggy
oh yeah
um
well at least you can
see how I'm munching on my Pocky so you
won't know that I'm snacking top secret
no one will know
was I ever here before
um
no I was not
now you hear nothing I'm not snacking no
no no you can't see my mouth move so I'm
not snagging
[Laughter]
why are you unstopping
um
okay
no you are my girl welcome to the
Coronet Highlands I expect you'll find
all sorts of rock type uh ground type
Pokemon wandering around here you
know blue I believe the great roof and
space time is The Pick of Mount Corona
itself the magnetism from it may well
accept some sort of influence on the
Pokemon throughout the area faster
up why the [\h__\h] am I not moving
okay
damn that's frightening is this area
small no holy [\h__\h] is pretty big
it looks so small from here I thought
this was it
[Music]
mama
heavenward look out is that a chicken
wait why is that oh
where's the
the [\h__\h] is that
what
happened
why does it
oh wait the chicken head
[Laughter]
oh no it's night time Ghost Pokemon
incoming already
probable pass oh
I see it does it have chicken heads on
its sides
that one fell off though
okay wait wait why am I what am I
supposed to do here make your way up the
mountain with Ingo where the [\h__\h] is
Ingo
Ingo oh hello
[Music]
what's this what's the best route to get
up there
do I need to go through
oh
when I need to go there
okay
I need to go through a
uh okay perhaps
hello hello hello
oh I can go
hello
uh the electrode known as the lord of
the hollow is somewhat different from
the electrode I recall but it's
electrical discharges at least are
familiar one false step around it could
put you in danger if you're going to
face it you might consider catching
Pokemon that can withstand electricity
ground Pokemon
and
what else
it must be difficult being a Pokemon
don't you think especially one is
irritable as electrodes
then become friends to boot
huh
true it's tough
it's a tougher life of Pokemon humans
alike who's talking oh
oh God
whoa whoa what an Ingo of the blue cloud
and oh my the Galaxy team Grand from
before
you're punching well above your weight
to seek out the great Electro lord of
the hollow
but by the sheer tenderness of my heart
I'll Grant you a trial to see if you're
worthy the greatest obstacle dude ever
faced awaits you right here battle me if
you dare
[Music]
oh wait did I say absolutely not
wait what wait the options were
absolutely not and maybe another time
a lot of fight though what the [\h__\h]
well then let me tell you the great
maly's take on this whole situation
[Music]
the plenty of our Nobles is nothing why
are we not fighting
why not
nothing other than a mark of Almighty
sino's favor and protection why because
it makes them stronger do I really need
to spell out that that's a good thing
we must let my Lord friends he hasn't
made to demonstrate the almighty Sino
that the diamond Clan lives as it's
right and good
this may even be there I say it's the
very reason I'm here on this Earth
what business is it of the Galaxy Chiefs
anyway if electrodelets lose a few
spikes
[Music]
the mountains
really you should do us all a favor and
slink back home to that Village of yours
rather than persist in this Folly and
with that both Voyage
baguette bucket what a selfie shot look
these friends is caused the Pokemon
themselves such suffering
but what is it you want to do kiawa
I want to fight that guy but yeah press
on I suppose
very well the tracks your head will be
perilous but I pride myself on safe
driving driving
to me sneeze look yeah well you must
pass through here wait word cave
here you'll find Pokemon like Golbat and
their ilk which are quite at home
navigating in the dark [\h__\h] golbats
don't want to see any more of those
quite dim inside so you'll need to watch
your step
thank you sir
um I will be careful
um
do I have any I guess my main Pokemon
will be chunk
does chunk not care about electricity
mm-hmm oh
darkness no full wet foul weather
Wednesday Road he's a weird guy isn't he
okay
oh we're walking slowly please don't
fall back yes yes I'm coming
I recall faintly that I had a partner
once a precious one
I'm kind of scared now
did you kill him its Name Escapes me but
I remember wait I saw I saw some lore
about that if only it were here because
he's uh in another Pokemon game but with
a guy that looks like him a twin brother
please forgive the unscheduled stuff
oh I detect an alpha crowbar to our
right under normal circumstances I
dubbed its presence would obstruct
someone so competent as you
but given the poor visibility I propose
a track change in the interest of safety
please follow me
oh he's from gen 5.
wait which one is Gen 5 I'm starting to
recall a man who looked like me with bad
lung disgust Pokemon I think
the words I like winning more than
anything else flashed through my mind
why is he remembering something and I'm
not remembering anything
we'll soon be arriving at waywards caves
exit
even if the memories themselves have
faded it appears much still lives on in
my heart please don't fall behind
black and white
[Music]
uh-huh Game Boy or is fine progress
we're nearly Home Free
wait could those be huh
ah
let me put those torches back where they
belong this Darkness could be perilous
for the next person to pass through here
so weird
my safety concerns have been addressed
ready for oh
this word I didn't take my medicine to
work before I forget again can I go I I
had to I should have taken it hours ago
we are big
[Music]
okay
I met this cute fat cat on my way
I wonder who that cat was cute cute
so cute and fluffy hmm
[Music]
yeah what is John Gray sleeping
sleeping in her cardboard box but
actually
um
[Music]
I actually heard boxes
falling apart like in the middle of the
night
um when we were sleeping
I was woken up by chonkers falling out
of the box and falling off of the bed
made a loud noise I was like what the
[\h__\h] what happened
she fell down together with her box and
cardboard boxes falling apart because of
her weight
yeah uh it's so usable though I put it
back into his spot now she's sleeping in
there again
yeah it's kind of like
um
one part uh like the sides are like
glued together I suppose and that kind
of came off
on one side so now it's like not
straight anymore and not so stable
anymore
chocolate is chunky yeah maybe she needs
a new cardboard box but this one has a
perfect size man it's a little bit
bigger than usual shoe boxes
[Music]
[Laughter]
Saturday
yeah
that's right I need to buy new shoes so
I can get new bucks for cat yeah they
have the shoe boxes have a good size for
for junkers and some are a little bit
too small but generally it's a perfect
size
anyway my safety construction is ready
for departure okay
we'll follow the track marked by torches
you'll reach the Terminus of this cave
Terminus do you mean the last station
the last the end of the station
where was I supposed to go I just said
it I think this way that one
oh
I've been ignoring these uh
diamonds and stuff too much
[Music]
okay
Leaf yes
that was not that scary I thought I
should have been more Pokemon in there
there's a you noun in there what
I need to go back Professor lavington
told me how you fell to this land from
the sky
for my part I simply found myself one
day here in history a region whose name
I'd never heard
oh so you didn't fall through the hole
all I could remember was my own name hmm
I was still standing there in bafflement
when the Pearl Clan came to my Aid
I showed a natural affinity for taming
Pokemon which is why I eventually became
a warden oh
but I still wonder what my true purpose
is here
oh
very interesting
but now I've sidetracked us with this
talk let's hurry onward a question
question is there a hint in in the
original game where he's in and uh in
the black and white game that he's gonna
eventually be time traveling or that he
did time travel before like
does he ever like say something like
that or is this very unconnected no
nothing oh okay
okay but cool I like uh how they uh
Implement characters from different
Generations different games in here I
also saw a video
um I saw a video with the title game
free game freak did this on purpose
maybe you guys saw it too wasn't my
recommendations uh where there's a side
quest where I don't know you make some
flowers bloom and then they flash back
to the original game where they talk
about how long long long time ago uh
someone made the flowers bloom and this
is long long time ago this game so
they're kind of recreated that pretty
cool oh nice nice detail you had a shame
in quest apparently
I like that they have stuff like that
that's like connected to previous games
yes uh make your way up the mountain
with Ingle oh
[Music]
I see something that caught my eye
let me go there oh
is it moving me no what if I'm here what
if I'm here
okay that would be
a bit more realistic of the if the water
would uh
swoosh me down there if I get too close
to it
all right
thank you Jacob's monkey for the pinky
what Bananas movie what the [\h__\h] are you
talking about but I love bananas and
banana smoothies and smoothies
what are you talking about
oh cause I'm a monkey
in my monkey form I would like to have a
proper solid banana dough
monkey don't need
in smoothie for him
monkey he still has teeth stop what the
[\h__\h] is the matter with me
I want to collect some [\h__\h]
stop running into me
okay no space again God damn it
oh you again
yo
Ananda what's the big idea putting back
all the Torches I spent ages Tiding away
ew do you get some sort of amusement
stomping around and ruining people's
Noble Deeds oh my god oh rendering okay
if impossible to people who read sure
inside hardly seems Noble to me
hmm
well this just goes to show that even
wee wardens don't always see eye to eye
I extinguish those lights for the sake
of the Pokemon in that cave who prefer
the dark
but now you allowed to have put my
efforts to waste if you think I'll
talk to her head to meet Lord electrode
you're solely mistaken
the only way you're getting past me is
if you defeat my partner Pokemon
how will you proceed Kiowa
of course I'll beat him finally let's go
oh ghost gun tank
oh he's allowed the true meaning of
Silence but deadly
scan tank lame
I've been using a fairy Pokemon
okay oh poison [\h__\h]
I don't have anything that's really
effective but anyway
let's go
[Music]
let's go let's go Aqua wow
full
China
ground this is only weakness holy [\h__\h]
well then we just gotta
we just gotta
um
we just have to
stand strong
[Music]
it doesn't matter it's almost dead
anyway I'll show you I'll show you the
strength of a bear book
[Music]
yeah thank you for the stream thank you
for watching
thank you
[Music]
oh
listen here neither I lose contact had
been defeat just yet our challenge to
you still stands
however I will withdraw to a forged
contact time to recover there's no shame
in tactical Retreat it's more of an
advance if you think about it keep your
guard up we'll be back
already
oh you're going that way and I don't
know well we're going that way too what
a lively character
[Music]
I cannot fathom watermelon's
interactions but for now let us press on
press and press and push and push
wow
oh I want that light
wait I want to go there oh well
I I suppose we're later Gonna Get Away
of going up those stones I want to climb
cool place in here
this is the ancient Quarry
the stones used to build the temple atop
this mountain were all cut from this
place
whether by humans and Pokemon working as
one or by the labor of Pokemon alone I
cannot say the stones that were left
behind should serve to cover us from the
gazes of wild Pokemon I did see some
wild Pokemon over there though
ah there you are angle who's willing and
ayank
yo Volo whoa what was it what is the
matter sir
I wanted to ask you about the memory
loss of yours have you considered that
it could have somehow been caused by the
space-time Rift
I have no cause to think that Rift is to
blame but then again I hardly remember
things so it's difficult to say with
certainty
if I what I can't remember my own home
nor my family if I had any
so you might do better to pose your
questions to kiaba I think if it's to do
with that Rift
unique well I do hope your memories
return wardeningo how about you then
kiawa do you remember what you saw
before you fell out of that Rift was
there anything else
um I'm such a dumb protagonist I know
absolutely nothing
sorry I wish I did interesting you see
personally I suspect that whatever is on
the other side of that Rift is causing
the strange lightning that plagues us
um
yeah makes sense so down there so this
net as Jago would say
indeed soda snare I did some digging and
Found Records indicating that the same
space-time Rift also appeared in history
in a distant past that's why we already
had a name for it as it appeared in fact
now what kind of world do you suppose
stretches out on the other side of the
rift
my guess is that is it is Almighty
signals around
but then that begs the question why has
the space-time Rift reopened when it
closed once so long ago and why would
kiavo have fallen through to us there's
just so much we don't know
however really hope you unravel on my
Alexa play unravel this mystery Volo
the protagonists don't know
anything at all
I'm sure it would ease people's fears
over the frenzies of our Nobles and
while you investigate sir I'll continue
to prioritize the safety of the people
living in this world
oh I'm a mere admirer of your ruins a
little more if something needs
investigating and I wouldn't trust that
task to Amelia Watson until next time
then bye-bye
once we're through here it will be just
a little further let us move with speed
but not haste thank you for renewing
your membership
all right oh it said that that uh
uh iron Pokemon
total weight to the weight to the weight
I need to revive my chunky boy
oh here you go
don't don't be sad you're back alive
everything's good
there we go
oh yeah bronze Pokemon
[Music]
do we do you want to find are they
aggressive they don't seem very
aggressive let's see what am I doing
can I can I make some more
yes those are the ones I wanted
only free damn it
oh wait I can make the great ones the
ultra ones whoa free
[Music]
um
now let's try oh
huh
[Music]
uh fire
I wanted to stealth it but I couldn't
I guess right I guess correct
one of the really really rare occasions
of me guessing correctly oh my God
okay the other one we're gonna catch
this so noisy
[\h__\h]
what a waste what a stupid ways ah
[Music]
ah
owl probably I'll probably get the
chance to catch a lot of them
sooner or later
so whatever maybe there's one here
is that the evolution I think it is
let's just try to catch it with a stinky
normal Pokeball
never [\h__\h] mind
well I'm not surprised they noticed me
that quickly because uh
it's [\h__\h] noisy the echo of my
footsteps
oh I can do that too but okay you know
what since you're still alive I'll take
that chance
um
dude yeah
[Music]
yeah we got him we got him we got the
Brown song
nice at least something caught in this
cave
all right what's on the other side
what's outside
it's daytime
oh wait
oh
Big Bear I already oh no I needed that
apricorn I already have
uh caught one of those or a couple of
those before I think
um damn it
um
I shouldn't have those in my inventory
right now damn it okay I'll throw
these two away and I'll throw this one
away
um
I guess I'll throw this away
apricorn more important
I don't want to fight it
catch it wow
maybe a normal ball is good enough oh
I'm sure it likes honey do you like
honey
foreign oh my God
aggressively Stomps away it was uh
he did not like the honey
but it made him fall asleep
damn the land runs so fast suddenly
it looks really funny especially with
the sounds
[Laughter]
I got the zombies
[Music]
can we catch this one too
I wonder what my research level is on
that one
six wait what does it want me to do
oh uh
the feet were fighting type oh I can do
that
and scare off of scatter Bank okay you
know what I will do both of those first
I'll defeat it with a fighting type
sorry I'm late no problem
I've been looking forward to
playing Pokemon again I hope you have
been looking forward to it too
[Music]
ouch
oh it dropped some poop
okay and over there I'll scare him off
with a scatter band gives me a reason to
use those normally I never use them just
for the sake of
those tasks
big surprise
okay that's that should be a good it's
good enough what about this little boy
he's so cute little teddy bear
whoa
oh it's so cute oh
yeah nice
that FBS practice is paying off
uh
[Music]
[\h__\h] what
okay
Teddy Ursa so cute yeah
guys do you have any Pokemon plushies
I think I mentioned it before but I have
uh
what's it what was it called again that
Pikachu with two two sides more pickle
more pickle
and I used to have a few more
but yeah as you guys know I'm not really
into plushies anymore
[Music]
we cut you in rowlets oh groky and chunk
Pikachu monsigno
popplio Cinder Club Pikachu a lot of
people have Pikachu
not surprised and alone Pikachu and the
Gengar oh
oh slow poke really
because
where do you guys get those
where did you get them like I got mine
at the Pokemon shop in Japan but do you
guys just buy that Anime conventions or
Amazon or
Pokemon
that's a nice one to have online
Etsy Magikarp
foreign
game toy store just ordered a line oh
you can order from the Pokemon Center
Online of course you can I guess yeah
that was that's pretty
obvious I suppose
maybe we should try catching the
evolution is that that's isn't it Alpha
no
is it no
oh
[Music]
it does have kind of red eyes but
for a different reasons just it's normal
state
I don't
know
wow okay I'm much more high level
I suppose that makes sense okay
all right hello
wait
okay
wait a second okay
you're not Volo I thought you were Volo
is that a girl looks like a girl huh no
part of the Galaxy team I've been
waiting I came here since I heard you
were planning to set up a camp I guess I
was was I but it seems not much progress
has been made since that bronzer is
getting in the way it's not belligerent
but it seems like it wants something so
we can't just ignore it either
it wants something do you think you
could find out what it wants
yeah
maybe it wants to be melted
by my own hands
okay oh I guess I'll ask nicely if I ask
politely you think it will tell me
hello uh what do you want uh you need to
kind of leave
I guess or I mean honestly you could
stay in my opinion but what does it say
talk to me
huh
you want to meet your friend
yeah I saw it I saw it
I talked to the other one then no
no
are you scared because of the answer
runs
it's all
oh now it came with me
so tall oh
okay
what in the that bronzer it's well
wanted this is no good at all here I
would fix it right up oh his friend was
injured
I see oh God
seems to bronzer at the new campsite was
looking for his friend this whole time
I'm glad you looked into it otherwise I
may have been too late to treat this
bronzer
this land is dangerous even for the
Pokemon that call it their home it may
be wise to be extra prepared as you
explore this area
what
tasks
all right nice
oh they're just gonna stay there another
hotel
and item storage
[Music]
putting this away
and uh this
uh this and this
I collected so many of those in the
space Rift
and not rip the Distortion I guess it's
cold
oh
well I'm gonna sell
oh wait what was that
Max Ah that's the max potion
I want to sell
these oh no no no no no no no no no
oh
I thought I thought I was selling huh
what was I just doing oh was I trying to
uh I'm confused
but okay
crafts what don't sell Stardust craft
them what
what
anyway we can make a lot of Max potions
look I need Citrus Berry and King sleeve
and then let's craft
those I guess or
yeah
and those many many bowls
all right
thank you for streaming thank you for
watching welcome welcome let's take a
rest while we're at it until morning
a recipe for Stardust what interesting
uh in any case give me a moment
my Pokemon are arrested and happy yay
that was my honey
exploding on me
what am I what is that sound
what is that sound
what's up
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
t on my keyboard t on my keyboard
t on my keyboard and my kiwawa
um keyboard match [\h__\h] I'll be RB
now man
yeah
[Music]
Chihuahua
no
[Music]
okay
damn it's hot water I don't know if my
keyboard liked that it's still working
though
hahaha it you know it's um I poured it
over those keys on the very right the
the numbers that no one uses I only use
the ones on the top
I never used the the numbers
uh on the very right side of the
keyboard you know which one's a main the
numpad yeah I never use those anyway
so even if it's broken now it doesn't
matter
yeah yeah
I don't use it I never got used to using
it like for example when I had like a
proper job
my my colleagues were using a numpad for
typing in numbers and I still I only
used the the the top row of the numbers
of the keyboard
and they were like yo why are you still
using that I'm like I don't know it
works better for me
um
anyway no this is not the marshmallow
tea yet
because I didn't feel like it
um uh yet to prepare it yesterday and
supposedly I have to prepare it
perfectly a day before
and then I was too tired yesterday
I was too tired
tired but but but
um I'll make it don't worry
oh this place is
this man okay we need to
we need to get up over there
let's go
if I find a phoenix bird Pokemon will
you release it are you hinting at
something specific
will will I find a phoenix bird Pokemon
Doppel bonnets
and come on jump give me those mushrooms
my dear is not made for those jumps
apparently
Moltres and Ho-Oh do you think I'll meet
them
it's in the lower right
should I set myself free
yeah
[Music]
ah what angle
huh
I was trying to get some mushrooms man
oh
you would never expect to be able to
climb such sheer Clips as these oh are
you gonna help me out with that now
but we're sneezler as an ally it becomes
the work of a moment she is so at home
on a cliff face one might think she knew
some Secrets some hidden move
oh what am I saying hidden moves there
are no such things in history surely
what what
yet I feel as though I was on the cusp
of remembering something just now
just who was I before I came to history
if you fell from the sky you come from
another world altogether most likely
perhaps a Pokemon battle with you would
jock this memory loose a logic sure sure
foreign
[Music]
conductor by any chance
if I notice it then you must notice it
too
much okay
foreign
um oh I realize it's strong against it
yeah
oh I don't think he remembers anything
because that one hit did not give him
much of a chance oh
Glitz score did he bring those balls oh
come on with him from another world on
the PO catch those here what the [\h__\h]
whoa whoa whoa whoa wow wow wow wow okay
oh [\h__\h] uh okay we can use chunkers uh
oh my God
down
I respect that
[Music]
down
I can do it one more time
[Music]
oh another one I didn't say he has so
many Pokemon
thank you
yo
oh yeah
um
oh my well
still posing yeah and he's very strong
oh my oh my oh my god
um wow
this is good
yeah he's not using all his Pokemon at
once like certain other people were
doing he's actually
uh fighting fairly
supposedly
yeah
let's go strong
[Music]
oh
okay I'm pretty pretty uh defensive you
are
[Music]
another one and
I see the top right but I didn't look at
it until now
[Music]
um you have strong Pokemon very strong
Bravo excellent
oh
yeah
[Music]
your talent has brought you to the
destination called victory victory
now allow me to call sneezler oh
gobble gobble and turkey maybe I should
make an M turkey oh Vermont write it
down kfb notes I think I can do a turkey
impression if I try write it down for
next time
oh
I have
I don't recall seeing the evolution
very often before so it looks very new
to me
finally oh
what is huge
honestly it looks a little bit like it
could be a character from Sanic
[Laughter]
allow me to introduce you Kiara this
King close Pokemon is sneezler I
wouldn't be surprised if it suddenly
started talking to me in a really cute
voice
would you be so kind as to play your
flute for her to hear
she gets it she gets it she needs to
open the heart and learned well the
sound of you playing
oh the toxic plate oh she's a gamer
I see looks like a gamer I'm afraid this
is my final stop are you gonna die don't
die please proceed up the cliffs
Prestige those Aid and quell the Lord up
in the mountains
cool I I was like spoiled that there are
that there's also a flying
ma but I did not know yet that there's
like a climbing Mound what the [\h__\h]
I was not aware of that did not see
anything about that
pleasant surprise that there's another
Mound
I will return to the Joby life Village
please convey my well wishes to Warden
Melly oh well wishes you sure about that
sir well then all aboard
well wait will I be in that box
it
will I be squeezed into that box
that's kind of uncomfortable
I don't know
[Music]
you can climb up and down Cliffs Ledges
and other sheer surfaces of sneasels and
cool took summon sneezler pressed the a
button
cool cool cool
does it also work ah
oh I'm in there
wait that's supposed to be my eyes
eh
I I don't think I
yeah my eyes don't look like that
[Music]
oh come on oh come on could have tried a
bit harder putting my eyes in there
she got it yeah
that's not my eyes it doesn't even blink
what the [\h__\h]
it doesn't even bling
oh my God
that's funny
[Music]
oh that's pretty cool
now I wonder in the other areas
which areas there are that we did not
check out yet but can now
with this climbing feature
[Music]
pink
let me try to
catch it from behind
I rarely use stealth balls
[Laughter]
I don't know why I was genuinely
surprised right now
oh wait my Pokemon
why am I the surprised one makes no
sense
I'm so stupid
oh man
okay
um you know what eat that remedy
oh
[Laughter]
it's a surprise that becomes the
surprise
ridiculous
absolutely ridiculous
okay well so we can just climb straight
up here
there's a shortcut oh my God we're like
so close to that raft now Rift not
wrapped
oh
Coolio
it's like I'm a different person now
what the [\h__\h]
um
by the way
uh I did I I did uh now I do now
um have the possibility of planning a
monopoly collab uh I actually originally
because I thought the trailer looked fun
I was gonna do Monopoly Madness but then
I looked at a gameplay and it didn't
look quite so fun anymore because
Monopoly Madness I mean eventually I
want to give it a try too but I actually
just want to play a Monopoly game and
watching the gameplay made me realize
Monopoly Madness is barely a Monopoly
game I don't know if you've guys seen it
but it's not much of a Monopoly game so
I decided to organize a collab that's uh
Monopoly Plus
um it's really really confusing there's
like so many
monopolies from Ubisoft
um but uh I can tell you
there's one from Nintendo switch
and that one is called Monopoly for
Nintendo switch and then there's
Monopoly
plus which you can also play on the
switch but you can also play everywhere
else I think thank you
so on PC for example I think I'm gonna
play it on PC because uh otherwise for
the other services you need to you need
a subscription as well as to
additionally to buying the game oh
oh it's that [\h__\h] Pokemon that
wrecked me
isn't it
uh yeah so now I'm looking for uh girls
to invite to it
um I think I'm gonna do like a four
person collab I think I've seen it can
be up to eight people
but
uh I think I wanted to be a four people
Club
and it should be
Monopoly is that one sleeping
Monopoly Plus
yeah which has been out for a while uh
but it looks pretty good
has been out for a couple years and
by akidoso senpai
has been playing it with her viewers I
saw like she played it a lot in the past
she plays it laying pretty regularly
with the Villas hmm
so we could also try that I suppose
playing it with viewers I don't know if
that's really I mean
it's a very long game each time then not
not that long actually I think she
should
I think she does it like usually [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] one hour or two
so
for [\h__\h] sake
it didn't notice me though surprisingly
oh
invite Aki for the lulls interesting I'm
sure she would be happy to play uh play
Monopoly with other girls for once I'm
surprised she didn't do like a whole
live Japan members collab with Monopoly
until now
she's only I only saw her playing it
with uh with her realers
hmm oh I was playing it I was planning
on having it as a en members only collab
but I could do uh later on I could do an
international version as well get
someone from Indonesia someone from Ian
I'm from someone from Japan
and maybe also hachama
because she belongs everywhere
oh this is cool being able to climb
around like that wait a second
wait I just realized realized
there isn't that where you cut you fight
the legendary at the end of Pokemon
Diamond and Pearl
oh
cool it's nice to recognize stuff like I
usually don't recognize stuff there's
probably a lot of things that I missed
but this one I recognize
foreign
[Music]
that's so cool
all right we got a gold uh there no we
don't have to go up there oh wow this is
where it ends though
we have to go over there
uh no
up here
we can Dash with our deer
oh
shut the light let me craft a little bit
I don't know I'm really I really am
excited about playing Monopoly I hope
some of the girls
uh that I'm trying to invite are excited
about it as well
for me Monopoly
was a game that I always
um played when I was younger with
um part of my family
uh
yeah I really liked it I haven't played
it since so
[Music]
it will be
it will be the first time in a long time
for me and then digitally
might feel kind of weird to play it
digitally but
we will see
it's a great family board game
indeed
and it has so many different versions
right I feel like I probably played like
Lord of the Rings
um Monopoly before pretty sure I've
played that one
let's see what
the [\h__\h]
when did you notice me I didn't notice
you noticing me
little 54.
defeated with ice type moves do I have
ice type moves in any Pokemon
to use mud bombs standing by about 54
what the [\h__\h] whoops oh no thank you
I should
I should probably go down
I wanted to switch to sneeza what the
[\h__\h] is that why is that
oh is that
is that a Pokemon whoa
ball
Let's Play Soccer guys
oh you're not a soccer ball oh I'm so
sorry
okay it's getting mad uh water is weak
to electricity
um
[Laughter]
the [\h__\h] is wrong with it
it's the matter with you
it's not even that high level
[Music]
oh my God
oh it's a history version oh
the texture on the bottom indeed looks
so different
interesting observation
water uh water is weak to
[Music]
electricity
yeah but electricity is weak to I don't
know what ground but I don't have I only
have chunk
[Music]
oh yeah oops
what's in there oh
there was a Pokemon on uh under that
what what
lots of cakes but oh
it's hiding I think it's trying to catch
me with its body because it's a Pokeball
but what if I catch you
it's like don't pull the belt on me I
don't wanna have a belt on me that's the
only thing you may single to become a
perfect Pokeball trust me
[\h__\h] no
no
[Music]
um
misunderstanding it's a misunderstanding
please don't kill my trunk again
please don't kill it again
oh what is this
oh you again
um
oops
do you want to fight again because I'm
coming real
welcome to the moon view Arena the seat
of Lord electrode
I know I've not exactly been supportive
of you reaching this place but a part of
me that hope you'd make it call me
contradiction or contradictory all you
like Galaxy Grand but such is live
embracing the complexity of both
ourselves that the world can only help
us grow
as a member of the diamond Clan my
highest calling is to please Almighty
Sinnoh and right now that means I must
protect my Lord by stopping you where
you stand
if you still wish to defeat me and gain
entry to Electro's seat you and you're
your little Pokemon are welcome to give
it your best shot you
let's go Scandal give them another whiff
of your silent deadliness
okay
boy
use diapers
you stinky oh now you're
foreign
[Music]
I might be a little bit [\h__\h] because I
have nothing that's a super effective
against any of these Pokemon apparently
or is this just telling me what I have
effective for the Pokemon that I'm
facing right now or does it say all
three of them let's go with obese Sparks
foreign
tank that I have nothing effective
against
[Music]
oh well 22 is really weak though so
thankfully that's something
okay and our obese Parts is pretty
chunky uh so it can take at least a
little bit of damage
but we are poisoned and they hit again
it's not [\h__\h]
he died
it's not fair
[Music]
man
I'm gonna throw you on the ground
[Music]
down
yeah killed yeah kill all of my Pokemon
is it fun
are you enjoying it
having a good time
[Music]
damn
ah
what should I do
those Hill
what you guys do
even if I do a strong one now it will by
far not be enough and I will die
[Music]
weekends defense before dying
oh Roost oh well
oh
hey sorry oh snow
well
[Music]
Bruce would have been a waste probably
yeah
[Music]
okay
I don't know what I'm doing
is it it's not it's enough it's
him
thanks slither.io
one of my favorite names man
[Music]
hmm
let's make one thing clear I didn't lose
you may have won but there's a
difference
wait
is that the snowy effect on the clothes
interesting you just look dirty though
yo you look very dusty thanks to the
snow I just like a time yes I'm afraid
there simply wasn't enough time for me
to raise my Pokemon nice and strong
ah could this be why adamant is always
going on and on about time being a
precious thing
my word of diamond Clan and Almighty
still truly are never-ending fount of
wisdom
yes yes I know what comes next you'll
want to know what places Lord I
electrode so you can make some bombs of
it
well I'm afraid I won't be able to help
you
because I have completely forgotten what
electrode likes
[Music]
[\h__\h] you gotta guess what's the other
upset too bad anger doesn't make bombs
man is really Melody's really giving you
a run around isn't it
my hero
um
wait the snow effect on my skin
makes me look like I have some uh
allergic reaction or some skin disease
or something
gotta look closely but I don't think
this is what snow looks like when it's
on your skin a little like it will
probably immediately melt and turn into
water
yeah I should probably go to the
dermatologist
unless this is not snow but ashes or
dust but I don't think so
I guess it's my fault we're not telling
you in advance what electroluxe so
here's the
oh
what now
I couldn't hear you just now you know oh
you're really going to tell this little
noodle
well she needs to find just like that no
no
if we kill him kill him
lest we all forget you're the leader of
the diamond Clan why do you bother with
these Galaxy louds
use your eyes Melly haven't you even
looked at your frenzied Lord don't you
feel even a twinge at How It suffers
fighting to control the energy that's
bursting out of it
you see nothing but a Pokemon overcome
of Joy being among Almighty Santa's just
once
anyway it's not like trials and
suffering are always cause for Doom and
Gloom these things exist to help us grow
he's stupid it's just plainly stupid
I'm sorry manly I can't ride off these
frenzies there's some trial from
Almighty said no that's why I'm doing
the best I can to help out here this is
bigger than what team Clan or the
teamwork clan we belong to blah blah
blah oh and by the way I wasn't just
going to tell her that she needs crunchy
salt I was going to go right ahead and
give it to her oh
okay we're making bombs now is this a
difficult frenzy fight guys because the
last one was pretty tough
is this one more difficult even
kaimo yeah
oh
the hardest one oh
wait hey
um
give me a moment
shut up
I need to
I can teleport back here so let me go um
to my camp
and heal myself
I'm gonna move a lot okay I'll Dodge
okay I'll go
uh-huh
nine tails
okay
I'm eating Pokey
Pokemon
okay
um
well
the first time we just gotta figure out
what's going on
and even if we fail that's okay we'll
try again
with the power of Punky I will defeat
electrode
mm-hmm
Pokemon
[Music]
where is it
oh
[Music]
yabby
let's go
this your face is turned around is it
supposed to be like them yeah
okay okay okay I can do this I can do
this
I didn't notice yes
what is that
[Music]
oh come on
[Laughter]
thank you
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
ing
come on
[Music]
foreign
oh my God
okay okay
send in a Pokemon okay you guys said
nine tails
nine tails is that really the right
choice
[Music]
oh get out of here I'm paralyzed oh well
I have plain wheel okay
[Music]
it's Grass Electric what
my finger my spaghetti sweaty spaghetti
hands
oh
my God
[Music]
okay going pretty damn good so far
yeah yeah
foreign
[Music]
you always start out the same way I
guess
foreign
[Music]
I couldn't keep up uh running
um I couldn't run far enough on it
could I not attack because I was
paralyzed [\h__\h] oh no oh no oh no yummy
uh
Chong could fight uh yeah
I guess
chunk bad I know because water is weak
to electricity but we'll we'll attack
first and we don't have a power
we'll be fine
[Music]
look
ah okay hmm
it was it was a it was a nice spot I
would say
it was a nice spot
[Music]
who should we bring in next
uh close it was close Mary
Mommy I beg you
[Music]
um
we only have to do a little bit more
damage
[Music]
okay Hallelujah uh wait a second before
we continue
let me revive my babies
okay
okay I I have played around a little bit
too much
oh it's so close to me
[Music]
I can't go anymore left
oh no
ah yeah
okay oh my God I got it sending the
Pokemon
foreign
[Music]
okay okay he didn't use paralyzed though
so this will be fine this will be just
fine
easy
[Music]
[Laughter]
we did it first try
[Music]
blue
ah
yellow ball
turns back into normal ball
you look pretty as a yellow ball though
are you
are you good you feel better now are you
gonna thank me
you're welcome it was my pleasure
exactly
you lost to the sky
well I am after all the gamer of whole
life English have you guys forgotten
that
you know whose stream you're watching
here's the blue guys
Tomatoes a cursed bombs yes but now that
Almighty say those precious blessing has
vanished forever it's just so unbearably
sad
is that how you see it electrode looks
relieved to me glad suffering ended
probably
oh come on Adam seriously that's just
your wishful thinking nothing more
all your preaching doesn't ruffle me one
bit but if Almighty still grows angry
with me because of this I don't know
what I'll do
I arrive right on schedule yeah
oh
what did you bother coming back for
only to say that I recalled some things
after Kiowa did me the honor of
traveling with me oh I'm curious tell me
tell me
things to do if a world where I believe
I lived before my memories were lost
[Music]
most people there caught Pokemon lived
with them formed supportive Partnerships
with them
and then there were the Pokemon trainers
the ones we called Pokemon trainers were
truly devoted to their craft they always
looked over at the next challenge and
had Pokemon battles every chance they
got all to help themselves and their
Pokemon grow
battle trainers forged bonds of
understanding with their Pokemon and
with their opponents and their Pokemon
too with everything I suppose
if Pokemon and people work together we
can forge New Paths forward we'll be
lost to history if we go on believing
only Pokemon can be strong or if we go
on fearing them instead of understanding
them
interesting was your word I can go
described to kiawa
uh
I don't think she remembers
so interesting that she can say it sure
was
hmm I guess we do remember now
if I want to or I can claim I remember
I never have thought such a world could
exist
oh once again the brilliant Warden
Mellie has realized something rather
clever it's not just Pokemon that need
to be strong it's me as well the greater
my Valor and might the more my Pokemon
can reach their potential potential
I wonder if Almighty channel will be
pleased once I've achieved exactly that
hey adaman share with me again the
wisdom of the almighty signal passed
down among our clan
all right all right open your ears shut
that big mouth and listen well my friend
give
give nothing to sorrow give not into
anger offer only friendship to those
around you give not in oh give not into
sorrow give not into anger bring not
Almighty Sinnoh to sorrow
for that is when times flow will cease
and there you have it
oh thank you you're welcome
Bravo excellent
please all of you do your best and run
toward the destination and even higher
state
of course your higher state is clear
kiawa it surely lies with the next Lord
whoa
now this time I really will make the
complete return trip to Jubilee Village
perhaps with someone like Yahweh to show
that Pokemon needs not to be feared the
people of History will find new tracks
forward
now begging your partner now Commando
come out on my report until next time
kiawa
dude you are a cool person very helpful
as well
can we find a way to honor our past
while also forging a better future maybe
that's what Almighty Sino really wants
from us after all it rules over all time
and it created everything there is be
ready to Shield your eyes Galaxy grunt
I'm going to polish up both myself an
electrode until our strength and
Brilliance are blinding
oh I can't believe we did the first try
when so many of you were like it's even
more difficult than the last one I think
I think what I found very difficult or
the last one was you know that the the
oh I can go up there
oh what
what uh was that the area that we were
fighting in
um was yeah
how to say
uh
oh
not very even like this is again just a
round Arena to fight in
and previously it was uh yeah pretty
spotty a lot of places where we weren't
allowed to step allowed to step into a
left allowed to step into yeah yeah
wow wow wow I've done it once again
uh we gotta go to kamado it seems all
right
we shall do exactly that
well I guess that depends on the person
because I did not think so
um
yeah but I guess I also
kind of expected or knew what was coming
but having to run all the time was until
now always always the case
so hmm
anyway
let's go lavington
I'm ready for some potatoes
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah let's be off to the Village
yeah the terrain yeah yeah for me that
terrain made it most difficult
yeah people only eat potato mochi
so weird we need to like the The Village
has been expanding a little bit but we
need to expand the Restaurant's menu
more than anything else
I am a Cuisine Bowl
I like to eat so I'll need more more
difficult kinds of food
restaurant menu
what do you think
sword and Melly believes that the
frenzies of these Pokemon are some sort
of Trials set by Almighty signal
we cannot know if that is the case or
not but it does beg the question why
ever with this Almighty signal Drive The
Nobles to Frenzy
is it angered by something or does it
seek to drive a wedge between people and
Pokemon
well far be it from us humans to Fathom
the thoughts of Pokemon
and what is that space-time Rift anyway
what caused it to open
but you must be tired go on then to the
Wallflower get some rest while you can
yes
find this potato I'm watching
huh
the finest only the finest
hmm
I wouldn't mind eating something else
but okay at least you know if you have
potatoes there's like so many other
dishes you don't even need different
ingredients just different dishes
different recipes
of course it is I'm not paying anything
here I'm doing everything to it for this
Village
like a robot my avatar just wait for the
roof
this is generous for the boss
well I've heard a talk that our progress
surveying Pokemon has made Gathering
ingredients are less onerous or at least
less dangerous task
well can we talk about how you've gone
from being some nobody from nowhere to
basically the hero of History
yeah let's talk about it ah praise me
praise me home again oh dude taking on
such perilous duties has earned you a
great deal of trust Kiara it's like I
always say behavior is a mirror that
reflects one's true nature oh
you let your actions do the speaking for
you King I want the message is clear as
day it doesn't matter
one wait where you came from your part
of uh the survey corpse a jubilize
village down
where's
that my third hand I'm afraid shut up
shut up but what was that
I moved something
scary
I don't have a third hand I don't have a
food hand
s
I only have two hands I promise I swear
I'm not some weirdo
oh my tea is ruined the tea bag opened
what the [\h__\h] did it open no
oh
man
I drink it anyway because usually kind
of like when you raise the cup it kind
of goes to the bottom anyway
I suppose and it's not that
it's not that uh probably it doesn't
doesn't hurt me to drink some tea leaves
right
yeah yeah
mom
whistle guys tomorrow
is coming out me and I'm a song cover
and then decide on the time yet
um
wait a second fdm's is that the finished
video music videos still uh in the works
nope actually it's not it but I think
we're getting there it should be
finished within today
a little bit Kitty Kitty uh
yeah music video is still in the works
but oh my God it's happening tomorrow
but
um yeah it's kind of a busy time
Valentine's Day so uh there won't be a
collab with Batman
um didn't really have the time to plan
that out and I think she's very busy
because she's streaming a lot before her
trip so
yeah maybe maybe when she comes back we
can do a collab
but I'm so excited for you guys to see
the new song cover whoo
we've all worked hard on it and I might
sound so cute
I almost sounds so cute in this song
cover
I I recorded
um I recorded like a guide vocal for her
uh I was like I mean do you think you
could like you you could use a gag vocal
from me rather than I'm just gonna say
it the original is a vocaloid song so it
was like maybe that's easier for you
than learning it from a Vocaloid Voice
and she was like yeah please please so I
recorded it and I feel like she a little
bit a little bit
um
imitated my way of singing it a little
bit because she sounds very very cute
it's like giving giving a baby
something and the baby adapts it and
learns from it very cute
yeah
but it's very fitting the cute way of
singing is very fitting to the song
um
foreign
does that mean you think your own
singing is cute yes I think so
yes I do
yes I do I like my singing voice I do
I I'm generally not a very confident
person I don't like many things about
myself but if there's one thing I can
say that I like about myself I can
confidently say that I am a good singer
and yeah
laughs
yes
yes I mean I have my I have some moments
where uh out of nervosity or whatever
sometimes I miss uh something up too and
I sing uh badly every now and then as
well but generally I I sing well yes
and praise my oshimar okay I'll praise
myself more
you just call me a twit
thanks for introducing me today
is a really great producer they make
really really cool songs really dope
songs
um
okay so what happened the next day
I am now just ahead
Isn't it nice getting up early
is it it's not as if getting up early
changes what you can do with it
[Music]
is she's someone who also wakes up
afternoon although I did I've recently
been waking up early but still still
generally this is such a mood
such a mode
yes
yes it does it opens up possibilities
such as responding to command to come
out of those invitation today in a
timely manner
well I got the same invitation and I had
to wake up even earlier than you to run
all the way here for it
come on no need to growl so much over a
nice little early wake up hey you it's
an early wake upper
are you coming too I'm sure we all can
guess what Commander wants with us
eh I actually don't know you'll still
come Galaxy Hall is quite close anyway
uh yeah okay I'm coming I I'll be
anywhere as long as Edina is there
I will gladly go there as well
you've now quilt a frenzy of four Nobles
when word of the Francis arrived from
all about history I feared what would
become of us but here we are already
preparing to clone the final final
is the final Noble
[Music]
yes
yeah who would have dreamed some
stranger who tumbled out of the sky
would be your salvation life never does
stop surprising you
the only Lord left to be quelled is
Avalon which lives in the alabaster
Island
he is also the largest of the Nobles
according to what Edina told me
hmm
laughs
[Laughter]
[Music]
unbelievable
[Laughter]
I can't
but those Dawns have been jump scaring
me quite a few times I think in previous
previous episodes
your mission is to quell I would love to
find the Lord and perhaps in doing so we
may trigger some change in the
space-time Rift as well
I don't know how you get that idea but
okay
it might be true
I have a look maybe the Pearl class
Noble but my clan and the Galaxy team
will have to step up to resolve those
two for the sake of a brighter future
the night is Halloween in the cold
reaches of the alabaster icelands until
then
yes
hmm
no matter how many of these frenzied
Pokemon you make well the fact remains
that you are a strange excuse me after
all this time
no small number of people still regard
you if suspicion and distrust the most
you can hope for is to gain the trust of
as many as possible and to do that you
must prove yourself for your actions
and the game still has quite some
content no after the last Lord
I'm not done so soon am I
[Music]
with the main story
a lot okay cool
[Music]
isn't it cute
teleport oh Opera can teleport other
objects too
not only himself
she has a gap
so you're too survey the alabaster
Iceland's next
this is the most treacherous climb
you'll face in all history it would not
be an X picture
egg to say that you might be the only
one among the survey corpse I can task
or surveying the alabaster icelands you
know your orders see your mission
through
egg
okay I don't know why we needed to have
that talk but sure what do you want
okay I've been looking for you my sister
one that went off the cobal the
coastline she never came back I've asked
her fellas
yes side quest okay
oh Ursa or Saloon Ursa let's get some
more
space
seven thousand oh guys
um how many more can we get
up
teach me
are you surprised I have so much money
well I've been working hard
nine thousand oh my God
Charlie
maybe two or three more ten thousand
oh you never had that much money
[Music]
yeah that's that's uh
what I get from playing off screen I
suppose and I did I did do a lot of side
quests
12 000.
okay I'll stop here
no thank you I think we're good now it's
just really annoying to always have a
full inventory so I want to make it as
big as possible
and yeah okay a few more spots should be
helpful let's empty out our inventory
you're already at 16k per slot what the
[\h__\h] are you kidding me
yeah I think that dude is definitely
scamming me because like how is it so
expensive just to make a bag bigger
yeah I'm not buying it dude
no no no no no
[Music]
um
let me go to the chest
such a scam yeah he's probably the one
who invented scams
we apparently found a Shiny Stone
who does that evolve who evolves is a
Shiny Stone
oh
[Music]
Tyler kissing Rosary oh Tonka kiss does
yeah
I think
now do hold on and I do hold up
[Music]
a hat
let's use that XL hmm
I'll use it on sofa wow that's a lot of
levels damn new idea for a move oh I
haven't looked at the moves for a while
shall we look at them
what is your new idea
uh
Amber
no it's not Amber flame flower flower
and fireblast oh
uh accuracy 85 though
I think we wanna
replace flame wheel with flamethrower
oh wait no it's a different is it's a
which one is better flamethrower yeah
[Music]
okay even though it's different
different style
okay
um the others I think we should keep
because we want that variety
your special is better is flame for a
special I don't know the signs like
which one is which but I guess this one
is special
and the other one was physical
let's see let's take a look at the other
ones
and leaf storm
uh or a sphere
no no I don't need shall we take Brave
Bird
um
shall we use it
where my final she is
yeah it hurts me to use it too
[Music]
and maybe she's fine as she is yeah or
he
uh and let's take a look at junk
oh Swords Dance I can't believe we still
have Chunk in my team
time to replace chunk even though it's
been pretty useful
um
double edge oh it's the same skill but
normal oh
I don't really want a normal skill
though
we're good we're good
uh we'll be spikes oops
what do you have to offer for me I want
to iron
wow
instead of we finally got a steel attack
instead of
um
Thunder Wave
[Music]
what do you think guys uh or Spark
or Swift
I guess Swift is fine too
okay
yes
and my snack
hurricane
[Music]
this usually attacks my rent but it's 75
accuracy oof you don't understand as if
it were vicious oh Aqua tail
do I want Uncle oh better than a lot of
pools
okay
looking good
physical attack
I don't know any of these things so I'm
very glad you guys are telling me that
and then we have oh oh play rough mimic
call mind
nothing really that speaks to me here
double edge no
no
[Music]
yes
okay but I do want to change my team a
little bit I think
I do have an Eevee
Dad I think already likes me pretty well
[Music]
shut up
oh that bear looks so cute
and so I was saying cute
have an Eevee here
doesn't mean does it like me
enough to evolve yet that is the
question
I would
probably replace chalk with it
foreign
wait did it work did I do it
yes
it can't evolve yet
we should run around a little bit with
it you can check the guy around the
corner I mean to ask if it likes me
enough
no I mean if it if it can't even evolve
during the day then I suppose you can it
doesn't like me enough
or or do you think it's better to evolve
into into someone else if we look at my
team we have fire we have electricity we
have water dragons steel uh fairy
psychic uh grass flying
[Music]
what would Umbreon bring to us that we
don't have yet
[Music]
dark yeah
don't we have any Dark Yet
I think we do have a dark
Type move on
you
yeah we do but
tagginess
crunch is dark
additional cuteness that is true
can learn ghost moves oh yeah because I
did drop my balloon it would be good to
have some ghost moves on it then
nasty plot is above true okay so you
think it's worth it to get Umbreon then
I'll keep uh our little
little Eevee in the team for a little
while
[Music]
um
foreign
Quest not now I am uh busy
okay
Amber is cute and cool yeah and then we
finally have a pretty tanky Pokemon
I need to remove the fair I forgot about
that
um
and change moves
[Music]
uh-huh
true true otherwise it will um turn into
a kusogaki point two
so we might want to make it uh for
Alabaster icelands oh
I suppose I mean I still wanna
uh I still haven't seen much of the
other area but I guess I'll do that for
side quests if if the story already
wants us to move on
wait did I say I'm going on did I say
I'm not going
um no it's really but who first to go
out of a way to subdue him hmm
if avalox has huge and strong as they
say there's a good chance he could start
an avalanche Avalanches don't require
any Pokemon's help they occur perfectly
well on their own you know
I'll come first I still have my doubts
whoever we should even be gotten
involved in this case no damage has been
done so far but if we sent Kiowa out
there we'll be putting her in danger out
for a harm
yeah what people say the friends is made
the noble suffer right
yeah so wouldn't it be a kindness for us
to quell the Lord
indeed
that's cool let's call him
there's simply so much we don't yet
understand when it comes to the noble
Pokemon we don't know whether the
friends is truly all causing them to
suffer nor do we know what they enter
the states in the first place or if this
is all connected some heart to the
space-time Rift
[Music]
what is it I wonder
that uh Commander hopes will come about
a book from Elk Wellington
or date from surveying any of the
Pokemon obvious land what is it he hopes
to achieve
[Music]
um
a little a little Canadian in him
I certainly hope so
the goal of my research is to help build
a future where everyone gets along with
the Pokemon
professional what the [\h__\h] is wrong with
you are you okay are you having a stroke
ah no no nothing to bother yourself
about a boot that list I'm just being a
silly sausage
you've got a mission to carry out
haven't you okay then we will support it
with it
how about I offer my support by giving
you another shot and holding your battle
skills
oh wait I hope I'm not sending out Evie
wait did I say no
okay
I did not say no
all right let's fight free Pokemon I see
so fast
open go [\h__\h]
Mr mime
a good opponent I must say
in Jamaica
oh
start wrapping y'all above
that does not hurt at all but oh
[Music]
[Applause]
interesting
I will change more Pokemon to whatever
the game tells me to use
I will not let her die right now right
here
okay
[Music]
beautiful
gorgeous Rachel
good time on that one oh oh
[Music]
but he got that Iron Tail
um this is not so good um not a good
match I will change for the sake of both
of us
um but I actually don't have anything
that's super effective
huh
um
bite-sized the snack for my obese Sparks
still got game
come on
or mermaid I think a lot of people say
moo may but let's bring in kusogaki
[Music]
[Applause]
come
we should feel a little bit sorry man
oh man
that hurts
poor question but okay that was
beautiful nice critical hit
[Music]
have the remains and feed them to my
obese box thank you
though
oh thank you for the red super chat very
kind of you oh
you're so sweet thank you
thank you thank you I'm also getting
enjoyment from it I'm so happy that I
have a place to be
a place where I feel like I belong to
um
thank you
oh
please evolve even into Umbra that's the
plan that's the plan right now so I'm
gonna try to make it like me
you know what let's let's speed it up by
fighting a little bit with it in
they'll still be low level right they're
not raising the level according to my
level right
they should be more level I think
you are however too low
level four
wait let's go
maybe here
any Pokemon you want to help me evolve
my Eevee
why is no one here
okay
are you guys up for a battle
hey what level are you 13 oh that's also
nothing
plans I knew you want some money to
fight me
higher level stuff need a wonderful act
true level three are you kidding me
level three
hey
uh I just needed to like me I guess so
using it in battle
I don't doesn't make a difference if I
use it
against high level opponents does that
give more friendship than using it
against low-level opponents
um
things I do not know about Pokemon games
doesn't matter if it's a 50 oh well done
okay
friendship points by using your most
powerful Pokemon to fight all battles on
Eevee stays in the background we still
get friendship coins I know I know but I
suppose this gives it more
oh
foreign
[Music]
will increase happiness I want to
increase happiness
I've been using it on Words and stuff
off screen but
it doesn't like me well enough yet but
okay
maybe we'll just Farm some stuff here
and maybe
Maybe
fight some moms here as well
seems like I have forgotten to get that
uh
to get me and that that you known
oh we could check out that Island again
because it's pretty close
also the sound is [\h__\h]
should be fixed now
Evie how's it going
Evie we wanna see you in a glorious new
form please
that one can evolve which one
which one what
you need to go to reminisce Island
it's a female oh
Phoenix comedy oh
I don't even know what the evolution
looks like
anyway let's see if I'm free moves for
once
again
[Music]
moshi moshi this one's not moving
is this one moving
this one's not moving
they're all not moving
oh come on
RNG I've been here several times now
oh what's this music
oh is that the noontime music
nice
to climb up that tree because now I can
climb trees cherry
[Music]
don't worry about it you guys are never
interrupting
always happy to talk to you guys at any
time
keeping up that tree
foreign
I can't go higher and what is what is it
even possible for for what
well what reason what purpose does it
have
ah
sorry
wonder what level that one is
online
it's too high level we'll switch oh
there's a new note on the bread what
what would I do about you guys man
okay
week
[Music]
I should I shouldn't use Swift
no it's okay it's okay it's okay
you know at kiwabo Channel back seating
is
[Music]
um
oh I see it it's it's uh quite common
and uh I would be lost without your
vaccine okay so how oh
[Music]
did you guys find this one oh wait I
ride I need to catch it oh
[\h__\h]
oh
dangerous
letter x
apparently
[Music]
oh we're going down
thanks for letting me know
[Music]
okay
Evie Evie come on
[Music]
I would recommend training Evie at night
but it doesn't evolve automatically
anyway so shouldn't it be fine
you know what now
I kind of wanna
catch a female uh
female Columbia I feel challenged
but I feel like I might have already
caught a female on a Combee before
though
um
oh he's sleeping
hmm
oh it's mail
[\h__\h]
yeah I know about the fair enough thingy
how can you run away when I caught you
off guard
I thought that's what you gotta do
to make them fight you
as male okay whatever
foreign
what else do we have
mail I don't know
hi I
[\h__\h] B language with me oh can you
teach me some so I can communicate
better with amen
oh he's so cute
I like those friendly Pokemon that don't
hurt me
bam bibs
foreign
definitely one of my favorite Pokemon in
that generation
from like the design but also the usage
I I enjoyed using it in my shining Pearl
and play through hmm
hi hi
oh by the way
I wanted to talk a little bit about some
things right
what was it again
what was it again that I want to talk
about
let me see
foreign
[Music]
ers
and just the idea of it I didn't find it
quite so interesting
but I have to say after watching the
trailer
I'm a little bit interested in at least
doing like one or two streams about it
because it does have story too doesn't
it these Wario games they come with a
little bit of extra story and that is
quite interesting to me
yeah
as far as I know Hyrule Warriors had
some
story to it as well
foreign
[Music]
back
and it was just so cool to see you know
by left again and it'll guard and by
left in the final form you know man it
made me so excited to see that oh that's
not this I can't destroy this one it
looks like I could destroy it
no okay well
yeah okay
[Music]
Kirby looks really adorable too I've
never played a Kirby game before
but I think I never opened wasn't there
something to open in this cave and I
never opened it before
um if it comes out I might
I might want to give it a try
I mean
[Music]
I always was interested in Kirby thanks
to Super Smash Brothers
that's the only place where I ever
played a Kirby
oh
I guess I'll catch you
could probably
catch you just like that
could also feed you beforehand you know
what let's do that
uh raspberry
oh God don't look at me
no
baby
[Music]
oh that was close that was close that
was close come on come on come on yeah
Alpha happiness
not that I'm gonna use it
but is that the one that turns into that
egg egg holding Pokemon
[Music]
fancy and they stay awful right when you
evolve them yeah they do they do we have
a alpha Raichu
of course they do
oh Einstein
foreign
okay
chance is a good team healer with soft
boil
there is one on top of the cave
a fake egg to imitate its Evolution
carrying I really like oh
cute am I going the wrong way
I think I'm going the right one
is
yes see I've never oh
where does that lead to
ah Evie can you do it
amazing holy [\h__\h] Evie
calm down I will never underestimate you
ever again
good job
but I was able to access this already I
think
yeah it's not not my first time I think
Hmm
oh wow
oh yeah so fine but actually there was a
lot in this Nintendo Direct that looked
good to me
um I think for RPG like jrpg players
this this Nintendo Direct was quite
something
foreign
[Music]
of course I suck Xenoblade free
announcement at the end of it I
I don't I don't know
man it looks so good like even though I
don't know the story of of fennel Blade
the trailer kind of gave me goosebumps
nonetheless
so good job on that I must say oh
what is that
oh oh God you scared me
is this one strong
and obtained two I have yet to obtain
this one
um
I don't know if it will let me catch it
because I already it already has seen me
was there something to make it to like
distract I can stun it I guess
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
yep so much for that
what is that cute
over there what the [\h__\h]
is that the one you told me about
oh
kind
Alpha boyfriend
oh
oh my God
that is terrifying oh
let's get it
oh my God
gigantic gigantic got gigantic eggs
don't look at me
62.
don't want to really find it but
how about we give it a berry and then
hope for the best don't get too close
please
come on come on
oh
holy [\h__\h]
seed of mastery
I did it if I put that in my team now I
will have a level 62 Pokemon holy [\h__\h]
yeah
it's gigantic gigantic all right she
doesn't can be given to the captain of
the security Corps to have a Pokemon
master and move
thank you for giving that to me yo
donkey shouldn't
all right
let's craft some things
[Music]
all right what's up there
what's up that hill
gamer of Ian
yes
I said before that I don't want to do a
whole Central blade playthrough because
it seems like a challenging game to
stream
um
Thunderstone if only I could like play
like a play like for one or two episodes
and then play the rest off screen but
you know me I will probably not have the
time to finish it off screen
I I don't know I wanna get into the into
the franchise I do want to get it
Waterstone
I want to get into the franchise
hmm
urray
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
when is it coming out again was it
September I think it was September I
mean that's enough time in theory to
finish it privately
in fearing
[Music]
it
it isn't that long
18 hours for torna what does that mean
oh yeah but doesn't mean that if I I
have to play Xenoblade 1 as well right
wait I have I already own Xenoblade The
Definitive Edition is that one or two or
both
I'm not sure what when I what I have
oh it's a DLC uh-huh
that's one oh okay
and give those to me
oh
okay whatever no more items then no more
anything else interesting up here
that is
pretty cool
oh
hold up
Center by 2 is closer to 50 hours it can
easily become longer because of the side
quests
honestly I don't want to rush it either
though you know I want to enjoy it like
[Music]
oh
my I want to try catching that
nice and he doesn't even notice
and it disappeared but I'll catch you
[\h__\h] and his tippy toes
and he doesn't wanna
okay
I'll game with my first play if it was
still 100
always one until aren't really connected
so you don't even need to play them in
order
[Music]
I feel like we can totally get through
get through the year by playing other
RPGs I don't think that will be lacking
um games
uh we can always play like Zelda games
and stuff
and and other older tales off games
but I do have a feeling that no one else
in whole life English will be touching
cenoblade free so
um it would be nice to have at least one
en member playing it right to represent
represent jrpgs and stuff
right
why not give Okami a shot well I was
thinking about it
actually that was one of the games
that always have been bought and
downloaded on my switch you guys might
may have seen it sometimes when I
squirrel for the games
and but yeah I didn't even know that we
can play it on stream but yeah recently
I've seen Ollie was playing it
I am aware of that
um
uh-huh
let's catch it
stop walking
I had 2175 playing into oh come on
all right you're gonna permanent
opponent for my Evie
Okami looks great yeah but um I want to
play it but I I'm not sure if I really
want to stream it not right now at least
it is one of the possibilities though so
yeah so anyway I like stuff
the
Fire Emblem uh tread
Mill
our friendship you Joker
you little [\h__\h]
no
I will I will catch you though
how much
how much does that set me back I wonder
[Music]
is there no item that raises friendship
I wonder
not much okay
hyper potion ah here's another portion
exp candy I don't have any with me right
now do I
hmm
probably time to go to a camp and sell
some [\h__\h] oh no no oh
oh yeah I'm out of here
go to
[Music]
for the discount
I would like to do some shopping what
else was in I forgot uh what else was in
there in the direct
what else did they have at the mario
kart tracks there's gonna be a lot more
have you seen that guys
I don't even need so many of those
stones so let me actually sell this one
let me sell this
Earthbound oh yeah I've never played
Earthbound before so that's pretty
interesting Splatoon 3 Splatoon free
I've also
not played yet so
don't have much to connect with oh yeah
Chrono cross
uh uh very interesting to me I've heard
about it before never played it before
but
it has caught my interest because it's
such a classic
uh it's uh it's a remaster
yeah it looks great
let me move no I don't want to sell them
uh I want to bring them
to the other inventory
oh I have a lot
okay
let's try this Evie
[Music]
another one 140. come on are we not
friends yet
please
like me
skinny not the goodness
ah live alive yeah yeah I've never heard
of that one before but they said it was
never released outside of Japan before
so that's the first
[Music]
um
Cali got a whole Wii U for Earthbound
and then they they just put on the
switch now oh what's she planning on
playing it with a Wii U
but who knows maybe it's a shitty Port
like Ocarina of Time was right
maybe it doesn't work so well maybe it
works better on the Wii U
H oh oh she already did oh
I guess so
oh well done I
if she doesn't need it anymore she's
welcome to give her Wii U to me but
there's like so many things that I want
to do with the Wii U
H we are very very very useful anyway so
it doesn't matter
hmm
are we sure some more tea
uh
honey
yeah I want to play The Wind Waker
[Music]
with wind wake up I really want to play
with oh I love Wind Waker I wanna be on
that boat on the ocean hear that music
see that water that cell shaded
beautiful I'm not I'm not making fun of
it I really like the style of the game
the self-shaded style and the the art
style
I really like it
it's my one one of my or the most
favorite art styles for Zelda games for
me personally
hmm
yeah look very cute
um
it says simplistic style but I think
it's beautiful people in 2003 hated it I
always loved it
okay
[Music]
um
should I just
I'll focus on the main story again maybe
Evie will do us the favor to evolve uh
on its own sometime sooner or later
um but for now
for now
I think
well do our own thing
I will buy a few of your pokeballs
though
I'm sick of not having so many
okay then we'll return once oh wait wait
wait a second where where do they want
us to go
Alabaster Iceland's okay
two Alphas look at those level 62.
should I put it in my team what type is
that
normal normal fairy
or something like that
most Illuminating I know right oh my God
blessing normal
only
[Music]
oh
it's so cute though and so round
return to a village
yeah well was that all I found
interesting the Nintendo Direct I was
just happy to see so many RPGs I think
jrpgs
uh
yeah would have been cool to see some
more about breath of the wild but
I guess they're keeping it until the
next Nintendo Direct hopefully hopefully
we'll see something
in the next Nintendo Direct Mario Kart
DLC yeah um I mean it's cool to have so
many
so many new
um
uh
Maps I don't know but
but
think about think about how many
uh tracks we will have to practice if
there's another Mario Kart tournament uh
we should limit uh the amount of usable
tracks in that case like holy [\h__\h] oh
that's what I was thinking about if we
ever do a Mario Kart tournament again
oh
[Laughter]
maybe maybe next tournament only those
48 new tracks
uh because like we've seen the old ones
often enough that would maybe be
interesting to only use the new tracks
um but I'm excited to see some that I
remember from GameCube times and so on
some some more
uh yeah
[Music]
I'll break
I do want to see that
William
Kiana
uh uh wait don't go
uh sorry
um
should I do this seriously
I don't know I never tried getting a
shiny uh so stupid
like this at least I have not tried to
do it before
it's just be there without me having to
try
just automatically be there
I won't appreciate it
oh dear
sneezle
go down go down what is that
what is that
isn't that it
why is it that color is that a shiny
that's not a shiniest and that's just
normal is that just normal
oh
I thought he saw it sneezle
I ain't got ten for you right now
[Music]
see if I don't kill it I'll try to catch
it
if it kills it then it kills it that's
fine okay
poison fighting okay let's see where is
that other whoa whoa wow wow so what did
we do we attacked him and and if one
once the outbreak is over and we didn't
see it shiny we'll reload or how do you
guys do it
or do you should I reload already
I saved at the wrong spot oh should I
have saved before coming to Coronet
Highlands
too late
ah
safe before you start and leave if
there's no shiny ah
all right that's okay then let's see
maybe we get lucky I doubt it but
wait you did notice me though didn't you
but you gave up already
hmm
it's a lot of saving resetting running
back and forth between outbreak camp and
Village
I would recommend watching a video yeah
I was thinking so too
um well oh well
it's a good good way to oops
well I used an ultra no that one's a
great ball okay okay good good it's a
good good way to
okay
good way to what I forgot what what I
was trying to say it wasn't fight me
let's fight like this then I'll just
fight all of you
I'll make a I'll make a soup a fish soup
out of here
all of you get into the battle all at
once six
simple
ah
[Music]
huh
oh dear oh dear oh oh I avoided thank
God
hyperbeam
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
um
oh avoid avoid avoid
magical
run away I can still run away and then
we'll come back so um
I'm sorry I hurt you
I didn't mean to
top cake that was unexpected I didn't
expect him to be so high level hi hi hi
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
oh dear [\h__\h]
chill would you
um mind killing for just a moment
stop following me stop following me stop
following me oh no
oh
[Music]
there's so many here
wrong Pokemon to go into this battle
with run
oh god oh no I just wanna I don't want
to be noticed why don't they all have to
notice me
I think now no one no one has noticed me
let's keep it like that
um
how about
we make a smoke bump
oh wait
oh come on
what's up
[Music]
no no hey
stop
I'm not here anymore
oh
that was the name
oh what the [\h__\h] where the [\h__\h] am I
um I'm coming back I'm coming back I'm
coming back oh
smart
it was here
it's probably not really worth my time
anyway I feel like we're not gonna get a
shiny out of this
but
we'll use scatter oh it's sleeping
in that case
are you sleeping is it I feel like the
eyes are open
[Music]
maybe it's just chilling then
[\h__\h]
I messed it up once again
yeah I got the Shiny Ponyta
[Music]
okay this side if we clean up nicely oh
mine
then
55.
come on please get into the ball
fried Berry
it doesn't deserve being fed with a
berry by me
okay beautiful
so
oh yeah I wanted to talk about something
and you guys might have seen me freak
out about it on Twitter
um but
so you guys may know because I talk
about it every now and then that I am a
fan of uh or I used to be now I still
like them but it's not like I really
follow them so
oh God two of you
follow them so actively oh you you want
to fight in the water
what if I don't want to fight in the
water
um Idol tangent time
foreign
[Music]
agency that I really like it's called
hello project
and they are uh pretty huge
in Japan
I feel like they're they're uh
popularity used to be a bit bigger back
in the day because they had this Idol
group called or they still have it but
it would have different members and all
that they had this idle group called
morning musume
which
um appeared around a time where oh my
God
[Music]
it appeared around a time where
um
what if I bring out the same Pokemon
what should I do
where Idol uh culture was just starting
to become popular and develop in Japan
that's the end of the sentence
um
I should have used Strong Style
okay
good good
uh
it's a Pokeball not good enough for this
one I wonder I don't want to use an
Ultra Ball on you
um
so yeah
morning Melissa has the system where
every time like they keep on like
bringing in new members
uh can I use
smoke bump on the water
it's so short though I gotta be quick
[\h__\h] bastard nah
why oh my why are we here just to suffer
what Fire in the Sky
what
what Smoke on the Water Fire in the Sky
is this what we're singing
what are we singing
did I say something stupid
what that was actually correct I think
the original lyrics are wrong though
foreign
[Music]
like this is not worth it
wait just chill for God's sake
bye
[Music]
give me one at least just one
foreign
I'm not gonna get anything out of this
but let me get that purple lines
it might be just passing through
[Applause]
some water
okay just I can't I can't I need to do
the main quest I've been wasting my time
I need to do the main questions
one Pokemon
it is a level 62. yeah this is better
than ours it has Hyper Beam
I want Hyper Beam
oh
ah no I wanna
return to the Village
gotta go to the move tutor
I have it
no I don't have it
I can learn Hyper Beam in the dojo what
I feel like that's actually worth it
lady my beautiful lady could you teach
me
my my snake needs a new move I've seen
it somewhere else and I was
fascinated by it
do you have what I need ice ice cream
Hyper Beam oh it's just normal
why was it so strong
you guys what do you think ice cream
or Hyper Beam outrage is great
you should we're going on a rampage let
me come fixate and using who is that
really good Outreach instead of my other
uh
Dragon Mill here we go here
[Music]
we have ice coverage already I think I
do I think I do
outbreak isn't really good is that so
I'll I'll get this one just in case
chunk his eyes yeah but chunk is not in
a team anymore
um
no I'm good
Evie when are you gonna evolve
Evie
please
[Music]
oh wait
um should I sell some or put some stuff
away maybe
this this
[Music]
okay
I'm on my way guys we're going uh
serious we're gonna be serious again
this oh there's another outbreak here
[Music]
but I
hmm
oh man we're not here to hunt hunt
shinies you know but we can just take a
look we can just take quick look
[Music]
this Pokemon is rare
that outbreak might be easy to do yeah I
think so too and here I saved before
before I go there so if there's no Mac
be there I'll go back right I reload
I got distracted okay Magby let's go
come on come on come on
quick peek
it's uh right here
uh and
okay
[Music]
don't jump into the lava
oh my God
hi guys is this the outbreak look
S
no shiny so
I really love
I want shiny monk be so bad oh
I'll get it for you that's not how it
works is it
or we can just clean up here and if if
we clean up everything and there's still
still no shiny
then we can reload
that might be an option too
nice frill
oh this is much easier right now
stay calm stay calm stay calm and get
into the ball
oh
it still worked that we're an already
noticed me though
they are really shy aren't they you know
what I'm gonna make a smoke bomb
oh
I'm gonna clean up quickly
[Applause]
nice
[Music]
so far away
oh sorry oh
wrong item oh you were eating that okay
foreign
I'm inviting you I'm training you for
dinner
[Applause]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh that worked as well hi
no shiny we're the shinies
[Applause]
[Music]
that one is the last one I think
is that does that still count as the
outbreak
up
what I'm I might as well fight you
no more respawn no shiny neither Hotel
true
so
let's let's set a maximum of how many
times I want to uh refresh this akina
let's say maximum three times refreshing
doesn't it tell you that it's over
though
foreign
[Music]
this is number one
let's go number two auto save his own
did it save
what
let's see where we can come out
did you guys see it saving
Auto Sales
it saves when I catch them
oh
[Applause]
yes now
okay I'll be hunting
um
Chinese in my free time
not sorry yeah
[Music]
okay well we are going to return
I want to go to where is the party why
is it happening without me
how dare you
what is are you showing her my stream
right now hi hello Kiana cosplayer
thank you for cosplaying me
really cool take a photo I want to see
yeah where are the pictures where are
the pictures where are the pictures
shiny kadabras
why
there's we're not we're not going there
we're not going there we're not going
there
we we're not we're not going there
I don't care about a shiny
at least maybe look
more outbreaks than acne on a team
and I don't know
[Music]
no not that oh man
oh is it is it set correctly okay
okay we're gonna look
[Music]
you think I can get a shiny Kadabra
oh it's all the way over there so far
away
okay
ah
done
I'll probably refresh anyway
no need to get that now
I'm on my way
shiny boy I did say your fiances did you
not see it I saved and then I turned off
all those same
or is this outbreak that you all are
talking about
it was stupid teleporting boys
we gotta be sneaking
I don't want them to teleport away from
me all the time
that really triggers me
we're close
[Music]
with their spoons
all right
show me how you can bend those spoons
I want to see
I have a lot of wing balls let's use
those
[Music]
I found
it
[Applause]
[Music]
go away
[Applause]
oh gosh
[Music]
yeah
ain't true don't spot it is over
cycle club
super effective did I choose the wrong
Pokemon to send into battle it seems so
but I'm stronger than you
mm-hmm
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay fight me
I think I think I think nine tails was a
good choice if I remember correctly yeah
okay
okay I'll just kill them it takes too
much time
to be stealthy
is
is there still a respawn let's see
not sure
yeah nine tails always good choice very
fluffy
now nowadays probably no respawn
just in case
catching is faster if you don't get
caught yeah
I did catch a bunch of them
so
at least something oh still respawning
sponge foreign
you're still not satisfied okay
spoony boy
where did you leave the fork for Keta
Where is the polketta
huh you can't eat everything with a
spoon it's so much easier to use the
other Cutler ow cutlerys as well
oh there's one over there too
wrong
well
you can play around a little bit Cadabra
but it's still your destiny to die
let me eat some chocolate
are you guys snacking on something too
there's a lot of
respawns here hmm
banana
Stephen you're just flexing
um
my dog
ah
thank you iron Vader I was far from
finishing my story
thank you for reminding me
now I have
more space in my brain to tell you the
story
[Laughter]
so yeah
so there's this Idol agency
no respawn
there is this Idol agency hello project
actually I I I was a fan but I also kind
of dreamed and hoped to join the agency
myself
I actually also applied when I was
younger but I think I applied when I
lived outside of Japan so
chances were really low
um
and I was I was really young and yeah I
I I understand why they didn't take me
they only they had them
they had uh foreigners before uh I think
only two though and they were called I
think
and uh
if I remember correctly those were I
think the only non-japanese people that
they ever had in their agency hello
project everyone else was Japanese so
it's pretty difficult to get in
if you're not Japanese
um
yeah but I was fine with supporting them
as a fan anyway
um
I wonder what would have happened if I
would have made it in that would have
been crazy
um
yeah yeah
uh but yeah they're they're just like
the perfect Idols the reason why I like
Hello projects so much uh compared to
other idols
um is because hello project it also is
very well known for this but I'm just
proud to be a Helen project fan because
they
are trained so well uh to to perform
um live sing and dance like really
really tough choreographies
for hours
for hours of concerts uh and then and
sing life to it
really in in the best quality ever
they're great singers great dancers
great entertainers they're cute they
know how
to behave
and stuff
um so yeah being a hello project fan it
just makes you really proud they they
really like are amazing like I've seen
so many Idols in Japan outside of
outside of um
outside of hello project as well and a
lot of them
they just
they just don't have it all
don't have it what it what it takes you
know
there's just so [\h__\h] good at being
Idols they're trained so well
it's fascinating it's inspiring and
they're they're just so amazing
yeah
so uh
where was that
my point was
I don't want to be found
that uh my Oshi Idol group was called
Betty's Coble
uh berries Kobo
and they already don't exist anymore the
group was kind of I'm not here
how can
you the group was kind of disbanded not
really like not officially but yeah a
lot of the members just are living their
lives now normally like my ocean
she is now married and has two kids by
now I think
two babies
yeah
uh go away go away
you gonna attack me really
ah okay let's take care of you oh oh
you're done okay
I think I just wanted to
have me go to sleep okay
yeah Betty's cool boy it was so fun
supporting them but all good things must
come to an end
and then there was this other Idol Group
which was created damn it
after Betty's Global was active quite a
few years later so this was like a
[\h__\h] cool High group called smilage
oh damn it
a concur
oh
foreign
made up of the cutest most
did girls that they had in their agency
the [\h__\h] party let's go
did they get any mileage the name was a
huge pun
um yeah Smiles mileage uh and ages of
smiles or whatever I don't know they
they were very funny
[Music]
um does not matter what I do
and my
[Music]
my originally a girl called sakiti
not not Canyon at first but then
Saturday graduated and Canyon was my
second most favorite and so then she was
my Oshi
uh yeah that is the girl that followed
me back on Twitter
uh oh I don't know when it happened but
yeah I don't think it was that recently
but she followed me at some point on
Twitter because I was following her now
she's using a different artist name
though
um she changed her name because she left
the agency she left the group the group
kind of
not this Bandit but it changed so much
with with so many members graduating
that they ended up changing the name
adding more members changing the name
and it's just a completely different
group it's under the names
it's a French word written as anger me
yeah
and none of the original members are in
this group anymore all four of them are
gone now
yeah
um but they were legendary they were
amazing
they were so cute
yes
and actually when when I uh was in Japan
I went to a bunch of their concerts and
handshake events and stuff and there was
oh I should have healed my my Pokemon
um I remember this one oh
I remember this one event
uh there's one concert that they had
and where I showed up
and they had a concert and then
afterwards they had a handshake event
so I lined up with a handshake event it
was I was really excited it was a lovely
day it was a concert outside actually
I think we're done here
oh it's over
and yeah yeah and and I've never told
this before but like so they line up the
girls they line up and like uh like next
to another and and then the the the the
the the fans they line up to and you go
from one member to another you guys
shake the hands and then the staff
behind you will move you if you don't go
on your own after a few seconds uh and
then you shake the next person's hand
and and and and and then uh and then I
think it was uh before or after my
handshake I'm not sure but like I think
it was before yeah when I was walking
past and about to line up I think that's
when it was
both of my ooshies sakti and Canyon
because back then it was still all for
all the original members they both were
like uh
did I accidentally say it
pencil face palm incoming
no why
I did turn it off
Monday
I am 100 sure that it was disabled
I'm so mad
oh
[Music]
no whatever [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
I I turned it off after saving oh Dad
the settings the settings need to be
saved like that I thought
is
it's ridiculous why do why does that get
reset
ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] ways to time okay whatever
uh
whatever I didn't care about that
Pokemon anyway just thought it would
have been cool just fine it would have
been legendary to have a shiny appear on
my stream but no it's just not gonna
happen and I wasted all my foreign
not all of them still have a lot okay
anyway I'm back to the I don't talk so
okay I do not give a [\h__\h] about getting
a shadow Geo dude
um
well we have to look at the Ice Area
first we'll get there we'll get to the
point of my story I just want to explain
everything oh
mama
no no Hokkaido
oh is this not at the top of the
mountain because is that the same
building that we saw from the other area
it must be
oh my word is right or chili here in in
it glad to say you make a cell phone
salt or any curse very few venture to
this hour Alabaster Islands
apart from tauhua leading the supply
Corps Excursion together
but a Chevy corpse of course must go
anywhere that Pokemon are found
from what I gather I speak Arena where
you'll find Apple is rather far off I'm
afraid I don't know what the [\h__\h] I'm
doing
I don't like this mission
to try to keep yourself safe
[Laughter]
out here isn't it
my angel
how aren't you freezing
freezing I'm practically sweating you
know she's like so hot oh my God
if you think this is bad just wait
there's nothing compared to Larry headed
you know I'm beginning to think the
problem between us isn't a diamond Clan
thing or a broken thing it's just a you
want me thing
we'll never see eye to eye on anything
come on be nice to each other
I don't see how we could as long as you
and your clan cling to your vision of An
Almighty signal that Reigns over time
forgive my bloodness but if such a being
even does exist it's certainly not
Almighty Sinnoh
yeah yeah believe what you want just
tell us where we have to go
we're headed to see my teacher and he's
only ever found in one place
thank you Optimus stankison which is
you're talking about the Garrick fellow
right where did we find him
and Emma looks let's see of course where
else but a great mass of ice could I
have meant when I said would be headed
somewhere even call her
where else indeed where'd you go Kiowa
of course I am
[Music]
as long as I don't have to put on my ski
shoes sure stomp up without me this is
why I can't stand people who only care
about wherever time is passing done by
see what envelope's lunch is thinking I
want to take care on your way well bye
bye I'll miss you don't go
don't go I love you
I love you
oh
cute I know this no there's Pokemon it
do be so hacking cute it did not notice
me really
apparently not
thank you
[\h__\h] are you gonna run away of course
you are
oh it's so so cute
come on come on wait how the hell do we
get over there do we have to climb that
way
it did not work it didn't work okay wow
oh
oh we're going this way
more monkeys okay
story story story story
so yeah yeah they uh those two members
that I liked the most
they were like oh you're talking that's
Kiana of course they said what what else
would they say um but yeah uh
recognized me because I was uh very
often at their uh concerts and stuff and
mm-hmm
I was so happy like I they're so popular
out of all the all the fans they wait I
could just go down there huh
what I love all the fans
they remember me
I was so so excited when they said my
name I'm like oh my God that must mean
that they stalked me on social media
maybe have seen me tweet or something
you know how I stalk you guys I wonder
how are you guys freaking out about that
I would be so happy if my favorite Idol
looked at my Twitter it would be such an
honor to me
cute
Hawaiian
if that ain't cute then I don't know
what is
[\h__\h]
move so quickly
damn it
[Music]
swing up Swinub
oh
wrong thing
it doesn't seem interested in eating it
either
oh that's it I'm out of bowls
[Music]
and I need apricorns Folk
is there an apricorn tree here
is that is that an apricorn tree
I think it is
no I didn't want to fight you
damn it iPhone
no I I am not gonna let that happen I
don't care
a monkey
I just I just want to get the tree
nice
add more please is that an apricorn
three over there too I think so
ow oh that hurts you okay hmm
so so so
back back to my Chit Chat uh sorry I
keep on uh distracting myself
um
that was just the beginning of my story
to introduce you and and have you guys
understand the situation why this is so
special
anyway that happened years ago
there's a cave down there it happened a
long long time ago
um
yeah eventually unfortunately
um both my old shoes graduated sakuchi
was the first to graduate and then
kanyeon very very sad what is that
what is that oh wait can I destroy that
and yeah I'm smilage just at some point
wasn't anymore what it used to be
and
um and uh
disappeared completely but Canyon joined
a different Idol group
a while ago
it's called zoc zoc
joke
don't know if I'm pronouncing correctly
I think I think I am
I don't care about all these Pokemon
right now but okay I'll catch them
and snowball I guess it's like a mud
ball
water is weak to electricity
[Music]
and yeah said that OC
and
they also
uh they they already existed before
adding uh Canyon who is now a model they
already existed before that but
um
they added her for some reason and then
she started her idle activities again
yeah which is pretty exciting I have yet
to see a concert or anything of that
group
um
in reality
but yeah she's doing fine
and I'm glad she's still like
um on on social media and stuff and
actually she is
not only on social media like Twitter
also but she's also been doing like
YouTube stuff she's been making uh
YouTube videos
about all kinds of things on her own hmm
it's really interesting she's doing her
best at
um you know
doing some stuff on the internet they
originally like when she was in hello
project everyone in hello project they
they kind of it felt very distant the
idols didn't interact with their fans so
directly and the the content it felt
very controlled
um
like it was kind of Unthinkable that
they would create videos like that for
YouTube on their own and really decide
the content on their own like hello
project was a pretty controlled company
I would say
um
you would not see much of them besides
uh their concerts and their DVDs and
their music videos and their their daily
Vlog entry uh blog entries
yeah yeah yeah but I think in in this
current Idol group she probably has more
more freedom uh more creative creative
freedom and all that that's why I think
she's possible she's she's able to do
all of that yeah I am anyway uh
um I follow her I've been following her
and some other hello project idols on
Twitter
and during my vacation I actually I was
thinking
what if one of those hello project Idols
followed me back and I just haven't
noticed it yet I should check it every
once in a while that was literally the
thought that I had
and then
I checked the first one
which was her model
and she was
fun
and I my heart stopped I was freaking
out I was like am I seeing this
correctly what the [\h__\h] is happening
oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my God
oh my God she's following me oh my God
oh my God I was alone at that moment rmt
was not there uh I told her later
explained everything to her
yeah it's gonna kill me no magic dance
oh RM team was just smiling and nodding
listening to me
um
what does this mean what does this mean
because like I understand like maybe she
just followed me because she saw someone
with a lot of followers follows her so
for networking purposes I don't know I
can't imagine that she actually checked
out my content or anything and I don't
think she knows that I'm that girl that
went to the handshake event I don't
think she knows I'm not sure
oh
foreign
so I'm so excited and um
I was like [\h__\h] how can I deal with this
I need to
I wanted her to know that I was excited
about it and then that I'm a fan of her
because the other way around I would
have been happy too if I was her in that
situation but I know that it's not the
same for everybody I can totally see how
some other people maybe just want you
know to have their privacy and they
don't really want to deal with fans
becoming friends like that's not really
in everybody's realm of a possibility if
you know what I mean not everybody would
would do that and generally I understand
I I have some deep trust issues as well
I wouldn't just let any fan become my
friend obviously but I think if it's
someone who I know that they've been
supporting me
even like in a different Idol group for
so many years and and and yeah just it
just seems like I can trust that person
and they seem
just like there they don't want to do
any harm
and maybe maybe you know as since we're
also the same gender maybe there maybe
uh maybe you know having a girly
friendship is a possibility like I don't
know go becoming actual friends going
shopping and stuff I don't know
you know
I I feel like that's that makes it
somewhat
acceptable to
um let a person like that into your
friend circle of course with much
caution I totally get that
[Music]
with much caution and and
yeah
um
I really really respect her
yeah I'm not here
I really respect her and and like though
the things that she's done until now her
experience her as an idol
she she inspired me when I was younger
um so yeah
the thing is
um
I don't I don't wanna I don't wanna be
too
uh what is this I don't want to be too
how to say
clingy or anything or pushy
so I was hoping that if I noticed
if I if I tweet about me noticing it
then maybe she would DM me first because
because I feel like
I I shouldn't really be dming her first
uh
so I was kind of hoping that she would
DM me
and then on the same day
she tweeted out something
about
um
streaming a game streaming a switch game
the Animal Crossing DLC and she was like
how does that work how do I do that guys
she was asking her fans openly
and I replied to it like I was like this
is my chance holy [\h__\h]
I was like this this is it this is it I
need to appeal
need to appeal to her and now or never I
ain't gonna live forever no I am gonna
live forever but you know gotta live
every day like it's my last one
my time has come but I still I still
felt like it would be better if she dm'd
me first so I just did a public reply I
said yo if it's streaming if it's about
streaming games I think I might just be
able to help you
uh yeah
I should have front a banana oh well you
like this one too
oh how the [\h__\h] did you see me
no no no no no no no no
so I waited a little bit yeah I'm doing
mental gymnastics yeah yeah I wear it a
little bit but nothing came out of it so
this all happened on the same day
I ended up actually
directly messaging her
and I was like yo
yo
um streaming games is my job I'm the
gamer of love English that I didn't say
that I did say that it's my job and I
was like if you want I can help you out
and explain to you
um yeah I don't want to share any
details of course but let's just say she
was happy about me offering to help and
yeah she she ended up like
um following my advice and stuff
so it was a success
but it's not like we're BFFs or anything
yet it's still very much
um
on a professional level or so I think
but I'm so happy that I was able to help
my idol
yeah
and if she starts streaming then I'll
know that I helped her I made that
possible partially
professional Zone that's okay I
understand it I mean it's made myself
change one time but
[Music]
to know
I think if someone really supported me
that much and liked me that much I think
I think I would want to know
I'm just gonna I'm just gonna act away
that I would
oh hi
that I would like it
I think
um
uh yeah I don't as I said though I don't
want to be too pushy so I'm not dming
her anymore
um for now unless she has a question for
me again
I don't want to be too [\h__\h]
I I want to give her her space you know
if she wants to be friends I think I
made it obvious that I would like to be
friends too so
[Music]
so yeah I I respect her boundaries if
there are boundaries
I respect them and I will read the room
yeah yeah
well behaved behind yes
I'm an honorable fan exactly
exactly
I don't want her to regret following me
back on Twitter
yeah but I was so so happy I was um
I was like in between massages and [\h__\h]
while all of that was happening but I
was I tried my best to like reply as
soon as possible as soon as my massage
was over I was like I took out my phone
I was like I gotta reply I gotta reply I
gotta reply
yeah
I was so
so focused
uh we're going this way
um
it's just I always had this image of
hello project Idols being like so
untouchable and I still I still have
that image
um
and not not it's not for no reason they
really are pretty untouchable
unless you are in the same agency or you
are also like a
damn it uh a successful Idol or singer
or whatever in the same
a job genre you know
him damn it you want to fight what type
are you are you normal or ice I'm gonna
try with nine tails
yeah I am I am an a virtual Idol I
suppose
I really do wonder if she saw a little
bit of my content like if if I would be
curious if I was in her situation I
would at least I think check out what
that person is doing
I think I would
pretty sure I would
so
she must have seen
but she doesn't speak English so
I don't think she really understands
what I'm saying or when I'm writing on
Twitter
um
yeah yeah
good morning
[Music]
um
foreign
guys I mean it was always worth it
joining whole life but this just makes
it once again
worth it on a whole novel level
joining whole life
brought me even a tiny bit closer
to an idol that I've always looked up to
so much
I suppose you guys guys The Ghost and
Ice ghost eyes eyes guys
[Music]
do you need a strong style let's try
for utensil thank you don't let your
dreams be dreams exactly
up your eyes oh okay
[Music]
the German word for ghost is Geist which
would now be a funny combination of the
English words ghost and ice
Geist
wow that's huge
how did you already respawn or did you
follow me from the from behind huh
oh my God I never thought
this would happen
I'm so happy
about about
model her nickname now is model I don't
know if she still likes to be called her
old things then that's also something
I've been wondering because like I'm so
used to referring to her in my brain as
Canyon
which was her nickname in the other Idol
group
but now she only uses
uh her new nickname but I'm not used to
it
well I I I'm trying like uh when I wrote
with her I I addressed her with the new
nickname just in case you know I didn't
I don't want to I don't want her to feel
weird if I use her [\h__\h] old name why do
I keep on missing you guys
you're freezing aren't you let me put
you into this warm cozy Pokeball
it's cool there's hot chocolate inside
trust me
finally
would you mind being caught as well
oh really where'd you see that oh my God
it's not nighttime right now is it we
should go to uh camp kyampuchi
or we just wait for a little while
let's just wait for a little while
[Music]
maybe they'll let us open a camp here
oh my God
terrifying screams here I want to go
down
of that Pokemon over there is sleeping
let's get it with a heavy ball
safe before evolving you mean if it
evolves into something I don't want it
to evolve into
wakey wakey
it's time to stream heart Challenger
wake up
[Music]
are we are we running a race
whatever I don't want you then
[Music]
heart Challenger one year anniversary
coming up in two days guys
OMG
you said that's not awful
can I catch you
okay let's fight
just a big boy about marshmallow
okay I'll I'll try to not kill you
sorry I wanted to keep you alive but I'm
just too powerful
my last Pokeball
that little
snow cone
when they got
thank you
another one for the Pokedex
oh
interesting
too scared to go in there right now but
I suppose I suppose since I can climb I
can always climb back up
there's something really good in there
should I check it out now
go down there nice rare Pokemon
okay
oh wait we should climb
sneeze left oh well okay never mind
is that rare but wait I'm lacking some
balls
uh I can make a couple of those
and football does
okay
let's try to use more heavy balls that's
a bergmite back it's German for uh
Mountain
in case you didn't know we got it
yeah yeah
you seem pretty ballsy to me yeah I
think uh the fact that I dm'd my idol
dad took some balls to do I was very
nervous that she would not like me dming
her
it took some balls
what I like that Pokemon
I like the design of it
pretty damn cute
let's see
can we catch it without without it
noticing me oh
ah
I I always aim a little bit higher but
it's really not necessary with this ball
is it am I too far away
are you leaving
you not coming back
guys I saw another one over there
cool place here though very icy very
cold
[Music]
imagine telling past Kiana that soon you
could DM her
[Music]
she would have freaked out looking
forward to the Past God damn it
man don't Aim so
far
in life you can aim high but in Pokemon
don't Aim so high
let me start with this Pokeball God damn
it what's this
oh what's this
ice rock do I have to evolve some
Pokemon here
I think it could make you freeze
oh maybe I should freeze myself so that
I'm that my character still is alive
by the time Pokemon
Glaston oh
I could turn it into a glass down here
I was gonna say by the time the Pokemon
Diamond pearl is happening
I could turn my Eevee right now into a
glass in
but we want an Umbreon right
I think we want an Umbreon we're so
close to getting it we just need it to
be night time
[Music]
I scared
of the ones
uh
oh
at least we're getting these ones
ghosts spun only at night
oh in caves don't they also spawn even
when it's not nighttime I don't know
[Music]
I don't want to do it if I'm not too
sure what is that
what is that
what is that it looks cute
wait wait we don't want to scare it away
what is that what the [\h__\h] is that
why it's running away I think boys
attacking me
oh okay
uh uh okay wait what
I seen it before now remember the the
color looks weird though is it because
of the cape I think so because my nine
tails also looks really weird
Kawaii
uh let's first take care of
you
oops
[Music]
oh my God it's normal girls ah it's a
historian form
[Music]
oh oh
yes slash me slice me up
I will just try to catch you with and oh
is it worth an Ultra Ball or are they
gonna be everywhere later
normal ghost OG is dark
normal is okay here's Ultra it's rare
okay
Google
who's a fluffy cutie
you're a fluffy cutie your rebellious
fluffy cutie oh what is that bitter
malice
oh no
I don't want to hurt it
don't worry Ark you already had in your
party
total Arc
oh it looks prettier in actual proper
light wait let me look at my
Pokedex
uh
Alabaster Highland Iceland
where is it where is it
I want to see it in color
you don't know I caught it
oh it's so cute
normal normal what normal ghost yeah but
we don't need it do we if we get Umbreon
and give Amber and a ghost skill
oh yeah I gotta report to the professor
[Music]
meeting
and welcome I think it's night time
because uh some time has passed
but we still aren't done uh going
through this camp
let's get this over with oh is that the
evolution over there
of that other monster
thank you for renewing your membership
only a week to dark
oh wait yeah that's genius isn't it
because a ghost ghost a ghost Pokemon is
always weak against ghosts but if it's a
normal ghost
then it's not weak against ghosts
oh
um
[Music]
oh
that is pretty interesting
I don't want both of them I think I
think they Clash a little bit
what if we get
um the day type Eevee
or did I stop since we're here
we could
it will be an ovulator oh okay I like it
when it's small though it's cute the
psychic one yeah go ice or psychic
we could do glossy on and so our glasses
one could be fun
you think so you think so
why did it not offer me to evolve it
though when I was at the stone what do I
have to do
[Music]
um
ice ice you guys like glass and why did
it not let me evolve it
stand next to get very close okay okay
first okay
I need to sneeze ah
ah from the menu okay hot
okay oh God I'm nervous
my second evolution
can't evolve right now oh because she's
out here
foreign
welcome to the team I hope you will be
useful
uh we were always planning on Umbreon
but now you are here because I did not
expect to find such a cute other Pokemon
um I think eventually we're gonna kick
out sliver.io because flying is covered
by mumei and I think glacion can learn
water moves I am assuming so
um
uh so that would kind of mean that we
don't need glassy on that much uh that
we don't need sliver.io anymore that
much powder Snow Ice Ice Baby damn
she already knows I spam
probably the snow attack may also leave
the target of frost but like no no
should I use this one too did glass and
get water moves yeah I'm sure I could
teach her somehow
Gladstone cannot learn water
really can I teach anyone else water
not a tank that's okay
don't make me regret it now everyone was
like classroom glass and glass soon
she can learn water polls okay
yeah from the move tutor maybe should I
learn this one too
I feel like
yeah why not
call mine we'll teach her some proper
texts
eventually
there we go
Ice Beam powder snow
I need some name now hmm
help me out help me out guys
ah
small she does look like smoothie a
little bit
and since she kind of replaces chunk
it's oops it's kind of fitting we will
call her smoke chunk and smooth
not chunkers and smoothies
she's just smooth
yeah she looks very smooth too so
um
uh oh wait I need to heal oh
I hope I'm not gonna regret this but I
mean can always get another Evolution if
I'm unhappy right
can always change my mind
movie where are you at good question I
missed her and actually
it's been four and a half hours that's
the main story
quickly
I will catch you this time
where is it going
foreign
it's gonna run away now isn't it
well
okay that that worked please
there
Mysteries that's your name I need to I
need that one for a quest
ah I was like what the [\h__\h] is a
mysterious
aha which one is the layout is this the
layout
yeah okay
there will be Evie outbreaks there
sometimes oh here
is that so
now that catches my interest
hello everybody oh there's a new person
is that the warden here
well that was a real slog fighting
through those miserable icy wins to
reach his desolate bit of nowhere well
done as
this gentleman is avalox Warden and my
most honorable teacher gay Eric
let's begin with some proper
introductions I am great Wick I serve as
one of the Peru class Wardens
and you must be Kiama writer of the
Galaxy team
answer me this
would you on what grounds do you come
here seeking to quell Lord Avila I've
been told to no he's in the frenzy
don't lose me to my next question what
is wrong
you could have the same discussion with
me again as the other one it could
travel others
foreign
then I have another question setting
aside any orders what is it you are
tells you to do
to quell is frenzy what is this stupid
quiz
alrighty lord of the tundra avalook has
done nothing to trouble any another one
like that
okay thank you
sir please try to keep your cool
for now indeed analog's causing no
trouble but aren't we also Duty bound to
free our people from living in fear that
such a colossal Pokemon might begin to
wreak havoc at any moment
we are there's certainly some logic to
death but if that is what you hope to
accomplish then we must judge whether
this child is up to the task
battling
is she gonna use a nice Pokemon my
musculature is hard and as unyielding as
ours think you can break through
yes
where are his pants
oh
damn it starting with the wrong Pokemon
uh oh oh you have two of them out of
course
of course you have two out
now
um
[Music]
yeah this is a that's a cool Pokemon
yeah that ghost ghosty boy
um nah
burn
and burn to ashes
[Music]
Now Phoenix has arrived we must let them
know
number 24
okay so what do you say what do you say
huh
hahaha are you done being a stubborn
child now
[Music]
outstanding I'm tough as an iceberg but
you smashed me through and through like
the Titanic
I suppose you all can get on with it
though oh that was easy
and he should put on the shirt oh does
he have nipples
it doesn't does it
frenzy you'll want to claim some of that
Eternal ice she likes and bring it to my
I have to do it myself this time
[Music]
um
I'll have to fly oh okay wait what the
hell now you
know you gave it to me but okay I guess
I'm getting a flying Mound for that
okay
turn the light stuff can't be found on
the top of Apple's Legacy here but to
get there you'll need my Clan's help
I'll even sneeze looking Clap the
surface
okay
Galax one Garrett once managed to climb
nearly to the top of avalock's legacy
and I'll have you know he says he made
it to within six feet of the top
might makes might makes right or at
least height huh
and uh about Tabby how do I put this
even when she's not flying with bravieri
she's got her head in the clouds well
you'll understand once you meet her head
towards the Snowpoint Temple and you'll
probably come across her Studio later oh
huh
oh my God she is cute
oh I love her
oh I love those fluffy braids the green
hair
oh I'm not even I don't care about the
mount I want Sabby
um
can I have her she's so cute I want to
adopt her
no I don't care about the bub
ba she's like a Green version of pecora
senpai
with those fake braids she's green
pickled out
green Cora
Kai I think I need to go to the idle
meeting though uh oh
I'll be right back okay
a great cook
uh
I'll be back in one minute BRB
foreign
one sec
yo
I think we really need to ban pants
you know why
I don't know what exactly it is but I
think I'm allergic to something
some fabric in pants
um ever since ever since Christmas
uh
I've noticed every time I wear pants
like jeans or now now it's pajama pants
I
um I'm getting like uh
uh like a rash on the like behind my
knees on the inside of the like the
calves I think no calves is it cows
and it's a little bit itchy it's not
like crazy but it is kind of itchy can I
downtown
but I didn't always have that it's weird
dry skin no I don't think so
change washing powder
[Music]
um
now I think we just need to ban pants
that would solve the problem Oh but I
also had the same thing when I was
wearing tights I think
I think Tides had the same effect as
well
uh yeah well I was wearing tights and
pants all my [\h__\h] life and now
suddenly suddenly now I'm getting uh
some kind of rash
on a very specific area though in like a
circular a circle circle rash it looks
funny looks very funny
um
it doesn't look very dry though
no
but yeah I should probably I need to go
to so many doctors man I mean I need to
go to the dermatologist have have that
rash checked out
now I can suddenly develop
it sucks circles has come for a wrenches
no need to come for
rub
and
ah
you guys are worrying too much it's just
a rash
circles forgive me
[Music]
hmm all right anyway
s told me that I've lead you on a chase
I think you can reach me
I will reach you cause you're too
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] home I say what you meant about
Sabi but why would she be up there
seems you better focus on pursuing word
and sobby and let me focus on my workout
while I still can okay do those push-ups
or sit-ups or whatever it is happy
it's not that difficult
[Music]
what is that
salt
I have some crunchy salt for you
savvy
[Music]
I will I will I will make you my Oshi oh
my God look at her being killed
hello my name is savvy
nice to meet you
oh I like those Circle cheeks cute
the pleasure is all mine
wasabi
I've heard about you you're super
talented right I bet you're gonna be fun
to play with huh
I know I hear here too you want Barbie
Iris help so you can quote I'm Alex
friends you don't do
let's kidnap her yeah well you'll get it
if you can catch me first
kiss
[Music]
her name in Japanese is really Wasabi
apparently why did they take the the
water away where'd she go
why did they remove the Y it's not like
we don't have Wasabi overseas
some weird name choices but okay
happy zombies zombies
[Music]
wait for me oops please
damn she went far away ow oh I ran into
an alpha God damn it
to climb up there
ordinal
oregano Sabi that's the only Wasabi I'll
ever get close to
I don't care for real wasabi
this is the only masabi I wanna get to
know closer
what's happening
here I climbed the [\h__\h] Mountain for
you
I'll do anything for you
I'm your simp yeah
so happy to see me you made it all the
way up here in this cold but the
question is did you catch me or did I
let myself go caught
following one more thing am I even
really clairvoyant
um
you might be
no one but me couldn't really know
around anyone the challenge continues
the next stop of our merry Chase is snow
Point Temple
but the real question here is am I
really having fun playing with you or am
I bored no don't
be more fun I could teach you how to ski
you guys don't have an invented skiing
yet here have you let's go bring
me out you like the snow area there's
this cool thing where you you stand on
two sticks of wood or whatever iron if
you have I don't know and then you slide
down the mountains it's fun trust me
trust me bro
[Music]
come on man how can I make her like me
skinny nothing more nighttime
[Music]
why skiing when you have Pokemon well
you maybe can ski on a Pokemon I don't
know
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm gonna adopt her I don't want to do
anything else
she's cute I want to I want to be her
mommy
can I not be her mommy
actually I don't know I I want to be her
big sister not her mommy
why do I need to go here
um
oh because I don't have to yeah okay
I'll go get wait there's something here
something's sparkling oh there's a
little little village thingy over there
you guys are everywhere aren't you it
was monkeys too
oh
hello
[Music]
oh
I like this we was like
do these tents look inside
um the same way the others did
they're kind of do yeah
[Music]
those are some cute wait those are maybe
not carrots I think they could be a
uh what's it called again
paprika
[Music]
and the pixel team I actually haven't
been doing it uh for for this game
uh I don't know
starting it now would kind of be late
wouldn't it
um
bell peppers yeah we call it Paprika in
German
I always thought oh I always thought it
was kind of weird that
oh cute
[Music]
oh they're just chilling there
oh that is so cute what investigate no
yeah I found it weird how
um in English they're called bell
peppers but still
you call the Powder made out of bell
peppers paprika paprika powder don't you
oh what is that [\h__\h] I want it
huh oh well
yeah why do you call powdered bell
pepper paprika but uh when it's not
powdered it's called bell pepper well we
call it all it's just paprika
yes you didn't know see this is why this
this makes confusion
they should just call it paprika so that
people know it's the same thing
didn't know that either a lot of people
don't know
that's where paprika comes from
wow wow I taught you guys something for
once amazing
laughs
huh
uh uh oh so sometimes I forget I am a
Pokemon in that moment okay
apricorn
let me craft a little beat
[Music]
so many of those bowls now hmm
I have arrived happy shopping time if
you want we can have a Pokemon battle
maybe that's more fun for you
[Music]
hi again Kiara she likes me don't you
think
she's so excited that we're done it's
nice having someone new out here to play
with safety and numbers or something
like that
anyway here's no point Temple I've
opened the front door for you just a
little more tasting left for you to do
but the real question is here am I
really having fun playing with VR am I
but you already said that before
I heard what word and Sabi said if you
have warden's office approval to enter
then by all means do so but be warn
those who cannot solve the Temple's
puzzle won't get far within so if I went
here before the story wants me to come
here I would have uh not been let in
honestly what the hell is that
texture on my clothes
I look like I've been in the Attic
alone for five years and someone just
found me
I look so dusty
that is not how snow works
out
that's that's just not what how it works
snow snow of the past it just looks
different yeah
come to think of it I believe the
statues have some sort of patterns on
their chest too huh
so we're gonna have a riddle now
riddle time maybe like a Zelda dungeon
I wouldn't mind it
oh oh
I mean if if we change the character I'm
moving with this does look like a Zelda
dungeon maybe with some fantasy like
those look like those those thingies
that bounce and bounce and bounce and
jump on top of me
the ones that eat the bomb and then they
go
there are faint traces of a rock pattern
on the status chest uh-huh
ice pattern
there's Pokemon here too though
steel pattern
okay get that one out of the way
am I supposed to remember this
oh yeah probably yeah oh
cool
the order of it maybe
oh
come on don't make it so difficult
oh no oh no
wow
foreign
each puzzle is its own room
okay
I need to heal my Pokemon
damn
okay so this is
still okay so it's uh the same as over
there
is it
still ice
Rock steel ice rock okay do you want me
to put a rock Pokemon in front of it I
don't know
um
do I just don't know nothing here
is that not a riddle
oh we already talked about Xenoblade
free today
um
I'm not quite sure like
I'm interested but I'm not sure if it's
good as a streaming game that was my
conclusion
[Music]
and if I were to play it I kind of have
to play the previous games so
I don't know if I have time for that
privately you know
but I am interested
keep advancing okay about which way I
hope this was the right way
is this a maze Auto
free no blade
oh
Rock pattern am I gonna fight a rock
Pokemon
steel pattern
oh
ice pattern
and
Roxy lies each panel has a pattern
carved into it there are fan choices of
words carved on the door as well River
The statue's Gaze which panel you press
first oh [\h__\h]
Rock
still
ice
was it correct it was correct
oh she I wasn't sure I was not sure
[Music]
okay
you did not think I would be able to
remember this huh without your help or
without going back to check
whoa very cool first try
so
wait is it are these the same eyes
frog
still ice rock still ice rocks too
I smoke still
am I going it
I spoke Steel
ice
Rock
there's only
but that's fine why am I hearing an
alpha or so
ah
maybe combined with that one
because okay this one is ice
this one is
Rock and this one is that steel
I think it is
follow the way they face
oh
so
am I go am I starting from here
Steel
Rock
am I even seeing those correctly still
Rock eyes
let's try Still Rock eyes
still
showing me now
[Music]
Rock
eyes
you're going to the Navy no why is
everyone why is everyone leaving to go
to the military what the [\h__\h]
never mind wait wait now it's moved
what what what more than three it is
longer than three oh that's why there's
five oh my God
okay now we're gonna go back to the
beginning
uh so so are we starting here
ice
Rock
Rock ice rock
but what about the way they're facing
well if this one's facing that one then
I suppose that's one and two ice rock
this one is looking at that one ice rock
still but this one is looking at
that one where the [\h__\h] is that one
eh wait I forgot the other ones ice
Rock
Steel
can I look at this one if I go around
the corner ice rock still oh yeah ice
rock steel Rock
and ice ice work steel Rock ice ice rock
Still Rock ice ice work steel Rock ice
ice
Rock
steel Rock
ice
I figured it out didn't I yeah
yes
beautiful
is there another one that's even longer
oh no
where do we start
where do I start
maybe you oh maybe we're done but that
one looks just straight
where do I start
here maybe
because that one stands all alone
steel steel looks at
uh eyes stay on ice rock
Still Still Rock ice
wait single Rock ice rock
yeah stay on Rock ice is Rock
ice steel Rock ice rock ice
did I add one accidentally steel Rock
ice rock ice
oh God Still Still Rock ice rock ice
Steel
Rock
Still Rock ice rock ice steel Rock
why am I stealing rocks Still Rock
still
Rock ice
Steel
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
something was wrong
still
ice
steel ice rock still ice rock still iced
Rock
still as rock eyes still eyes Rock eyes
still eyes Rock eyes
still eyes Rock steel still ice
no
still a ice rock ice Steel
still ice rock ice steel Rock steel ice
rock I Still Rock
still
eyes Rock eyes
steel Rock come on
come on
that's a tough one why is the tough one
yeah no I did not miss anything
I hear an alpha hello
yeah
uh why is that here
excuse me
oh my God
uh
do you want the raspberry I think I have
one
huh yeah one
but the other one might eat it
uh-huh yeah
um [\h__\h] oh maybe the other one comes I
disappeared
that's too stupid that was just too
stupid I wanna redo that
[Laughter]
ah I did save just before I um fruit a
raspberry so
I'm it's funny how you guys always ask
did you say when I literally saved in
front of everyone's eyes a moment ago
hitboxes be like nope
okay
you make me question myself too
I don't like that
foreign
I don't think it quite saw me
but it's panicking
damn
it
foreign
I should just use the air ball after all
can't throw that oh really is that the
problem
man
uh I just want to get once we have the
mount I think we'll end the stream or
the the gaming heart at least
oh
I think
didn't do anything
oh man
and
ah
finally
[Music]
okay
the way it runs oh my God
what that was a close boy come on please
please
oh
[Music]
level 70 is tough
does the raspberry still count after I
failed catching it once
don't look at me
oh God oh God it's zooming holy [\h__\h]
oh no wasted
I don't want to fight you
can we like make a deal or something
no
[Music]
um
I don't I don't I'm too scared at all
whatever that was that was very scary
hello
um your mom down there is [\h__\h]
aggressive can you do about something
about it maybe she is like that because
you ran away
and there it goes again go back to your
mommy so she can chill the [\h__\h] out
whatever I don't need it oh
on the way here
you tried to kill me
what the hell
I guess I've been caught so we're nearly
done that's no fun hey remember my
Clairvoyance it showed me something else
I saw you flying off bravery do you
think that we can come to pass
I'll make sure it does
well however the future turns out flying
with bravieri isn't easy
if you really want to be able to fly
high in the sky prove to me you're
strong enough
okay I'm gonna take us on of course
now get ready because here I come right
here Mark mortar
and Electro buyer all three of them go
yummy
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
they look strong
fire
oh
okay that's okay
um
oh
[Music]
oh maybe I'll have a chance with mermaid
okay let's give it a try is that what is
that type
what is that time yo
oh my God
I'm still not enough
and not anymore
let's water this week to electricity
[\h__\h]
what about uh the other one uh I was
like electricity I have nothing
I have nothing
that's strong
against that so
I have no ground moves
um where's my best bet then I don't want
to bring out sliver right now
uh smooth is not gonna happen
Revival me
Kamikaze around your sliver well
I hope I don't regret this
so fetch oh well see I will attack first
anyway
[Music]
so once we get uh
uh Mark more tower out of the way then
it doesn't matter sliver dies
okay just in case we're gonna do Strong
Style
[Music]
wait it's level 30.
I didn't need to do Strong Style this
one's level 32. and it just wants to
paralyze me okay you know what
I'm still alive thank God
then
[Music]
should I should I fetch so fetch no
or twister
oh I wonder if I could maybe kill it
anyway with something here maybe with
crunch
maybe with strong style crunch
because power 100
and I was repaired oh you have to
believe guys
hey yeah it was maximal power
why you caught us and your penis you won
our game so far but Braviary still wants
to get to know you even better up to the
roof we go
I think it's very fitting that this last
um
Mount is very hard to get like you need
to go for all these tests because flying
ain't a joke
you can't just give someone that power
that easily
that would be boring right
now
uh I will say
uh-huh
and never fight
who am I fighting
I'm out of Porky battling I'm gonna have
snacks oh
whoa
wait put your channel
that looks like fujisan
[Music]
oh
the shape is just so beautiful and
perfect
this is it this is it this is where you
catch the legendary
I think or maybe below I'm not sure I
think I might have been below
senpai
I go mango mango man I'm sorry Savvy I'm
sorry I'm sorry you're the only thing
that I'm interested in of course
all right baby why not test up your
strength for yourself
I'm gonna find them
of course I am
okay what is it I uh flying only or ice
flying
something that electricity is apparently
very effective too thank you for letting
me know flying psychic ah
well I'm gonna go strong style because
level 54 ain't a joke
yeah I'm still alive wow
impress him
Roost okay
[Music]
but that's just enough if I do the same
damage is just enough to kill you
destroy him yay
how to stream Sparks why did oh
what the [\h__\h] is happening
maybe I should use a different one no
wait what why is it not effective
[Music]
Ruth removes the flying type what the
[\h__\h] you know what
it that's ridiculous for how long for
the rest of the match
so I should go ghost or dark
side
just set your only dad turns
why should I switch
is it worth it because I feel like if I
stay in it's gonna continue doing the
same move until it runs out of it how
much
does roost have 10.
uh maybe agile style yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah so it won't get to use Roost
and now it's back to flying
no apparently not yet oh oh wait did I
use spark why did I do that oh well
[Music]
this is ridiculous it's gonna use roast
again unless unless
a Dodge
oh
and
and Bruce
why but
I didn't heal that much what if I do
iron Gail
I want to see what happens
come on come on come on
come on okay
that is a interesting strategy though I
thought I only thought about Rose to
heal myself I didn't realize that you
could you can do a 100 IQ move big brain
move
to remove
flying and then they would just have
nothing super effective against you
anymore it was very interesting wow this
this this bird has a big brain we need
to hire it for kfp
damn I know movie can do it too but I
never thought about it that way
100 IQ is average
maybe not for a verb okay
maybe with a verb that is
extraordinary
can't believe we're very very lost but
that's not thanks for playing with me
guess I'll head home now bye don't jump
wait the [\h__\h] give me the boob
I was kidding
playing along with me on your hunt
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Laughter]
okay Sky Play Let's Go
thanks happy oh other one
because you kill the alpha for me
because it freaks the hell out of me
sure having Kiara to fly around with it
with
uh ah should be fun for Barbie
yeah I'm glad a world where people and
Pokemon live and work together huh
um tell me why do you think the
lightning that comes from the rift would
cause these Frenchies
do you think there's all all my this is
all Almighty Sinners anger or do you
think this is a trial it's putting on us
if it is a trial if we prove ourselves
worthy and we quell the last Noble calm
Avalon and then the rift really ought to
close right
even if the one who seems to be clearing
this trial is a newcomer like you not
one of us who've been living here in
history for ages now
how come you're playing all wise I
thought you big finger Adam on
watch zombie I can feel a story on the
move
called him stupid
cheeky brat girl like her
cute
she's hiding her kusogaki Tendencies
perfectly
holding your cat
oh meow
and as far as I can see the one ushering
in Disney World Is You So if I stick
with you someday I might get to meet
Almighty signal myself
the question is does listening to
listening to other man Fascinate You or
boy you to tears
bore me a little bit
but also fat no I'm not fascinates it
doesn't fascinate me I wouldn't go as
far as fascination
um I'm interested but also bored because
I want to listen to the cute girl
anyway yeah well it's time for you to go
somewhere with bravery
if you jump from way up here baby I can
take you gliding just about
just about where
gliding only or flying
does it Glide only
but don't forget to get the Eternal
lights that's why you need a braver in
the first place right
that is correct oh it's only colliding
so I have to like climb up mountains and
then fly
aha
Ava looks like this thing is down there
I see now go get a feel for flying with
bravery when you're done sawing disguise
and want to land just ask him to dive
honestly that burp definitely has the
skill to fly properly
they are nerfing him as a mount to only
Glide it doesn't quite make sense
it will fly up a bit and take off not a
hotel
every other Mound will be 100 useless if
he could fly I guess so yeah
[Music]
I can now call bravery
I guess that makes sense so maybe it
means that I'm just too happy maybe
you're implying that I'm too heavy to be
lifted up by this bird so it could only
Glide
maybe maybe that's one explanation
okay so do I just oh do I just do I just
jump
oh okay
whoa
wow oh I can stay on the same spot
without losing altitude
it seems so
oh
what is that stone over there
well that's magical
that is magical
oh
it's like paragliding
[Music]
you know
well how do I dive again
so I just press plus again
why or this one B to speed
[Music]
why to this month okay but it was just
gonna drop me and I'm gonna die
oh okay okay
well wait the view is kind of bad
oh
let's let's uh
and smash into that rock
boom I wanted it to explode
I feel like I feel like my Pokemon just
exploded popped like a balloon
you good ground are you still alive
Joe investigate
let's take that ice
hmm money my arc phone is bleep beeping
what is it I obtained a piece okay why
did my arc phone beep though
Eternal ice
we got it we got the question
oh wait how the [\h__\h] did you get up here
elastic summer is conquered
and I see you made it too oh man oh my
flew down to this place and obtained her
to the lights did you what drives that
burning Zeal of yours I wonder
now we can climb up I thought you
couldn't
thought that was that was the reason why
I got that stupid bird
ah well here's the ice I do have to
respect the effort you put in
I may still have my own jobs Weighing on
my mind but I won't make the necessary
preparations so that you can face my
Lord Avalon meet me at the Ice Park
arena
okay well that will be for the next time
now don't try to repeat the wondrous
feat you're about to see me perform
a tall lead like this can only be
managed by highly tuned bodies like mine
till next we meet it's gonna jump
oh
I was I was actually for once expecting
an animation for that but okay
okay
I guess it was not possible
not at all though
[Music]
wow
okay well that was interesting we're
we're getting the last Lord next time
uh
so
wait is my question Okay Ice Park arena
which is oh it's right there
hell we could do the last Lord right now
you guys think I can do it right away
I mean while we're here
foreign
well I first tried the other one
I think I'll be fine
can I catch Pokemon while I'm in the air
I must be able to right
it's a bit tough let's just try it let's
try it
then Sean tension
[Music]
I'm Not Gonna Leave This episode at a
half-assed spot
hello
hello I have arrived let me save one
more time
Save Me Baby One More Time
I can't catch Pokemon while I'm flying
oh
so you do have to catch those flying
Pokemon while you're on the ground after
all huh well I did it before already but
I thought maybe there would be an easier
way later on hmm
what a pleasure finding a familiar face
or any face in this far corner of the
alabaster icelands
I came to bring Gary in order of Sword
cups and he was more than willing to
have a chat with uh about Avalon
what do you say interested in a bit of
gossip
yes always tell me why won't you be
so I will guess the fifth of History's
Nobles
yeah that is and you know what he's an
absolute Beast
yeah quite quiet I'm scared
well yes according to what I was told
not only does he burage you with chunks
of ice he also first fires off masterful
icicles and he can cause sharp ice
crystals to erupt from the ground below
you
doesn't that seem a bit too powerful to
take on or it's more apparently that
look of old could be up to a hundred
feet tall doesn't that seem a bit too
big to take on
and
me takanashi kiwawa the legendary
phoenix I'm a legendary Pokemon myself
I can take it on
I'll be fine
you'll be all right you just have to eat
some sword caps and then give your
training you're all
nothing better for building muscle than
I can't waste my time like that
I have enough muscles thanks to my
skiing vacation
that's that's all all the help I'll get
when it comes to muscles
maybe that Macho cat can help me a
little bit huh
foreign
ER please
oh thank you mother Orchid thank you
very sweet of you
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay did I
save I think I saved
like at least a little bit before
[Music]
he's making the snacks
okay
um
wait a second I'll save one more time
okay
and I suppose having nine tails out
would be the best choice so we're good
okay I'm ready
I strong
am I still effective then
with nine tails
PP
ah good question
I feel like they're gonna heal me again
though I won't just go in I think they
usually heal you before you go into a
whoa
nice scene
oh
can I like go underneath it
do I have to maybe
enormous gigantic gaijan oh yeah
[Music]
oh oh I have to stay up here
oh
oh I have to stay up here
honey
okay I see I see what we're doing
oh God oh God
oh okay I shouldn't I oh okay oh okay
okay
what is that what is that
the Dodge for that okay sending a
Pokemon yeah yeah if I can't get up I
can't get up
oh my God
wait that was too late
oh God
okay okay [\h__\h] I think we'll have to
redo this
is
oh
my God
yeah that ain't happening I don't think
I'll be able to make a perfect Dodge
oh
oh oh oh oh
holy [\h__\h] yeah okay
why are we doing again yeah let me do it
again
I would like a second chance
concentrate on dodging and wait for your
chance to strike back
aha a powerful being that avalog
launches from his mom can be evaded with
the line but anyway
mm-hmm
a recite
restart from the beginning we ain't
babies here
thank you
full Focus focus on this
gamer of Ian
uh okay
uh-huh
oh
that comes so fast okay you start from
that side
oh God uh
okay
I don't lose
oh okay
it's just effective do I not have
anything else that's more effective
[Music]
kind of want to check that out
water and steel would be better
fighting as well oh well interesting
okay and we'll switch afterwards
um
oh dear oh dear oh dear
oh man
come on but look we almost had him down
almost had him down okay we'll swap to
Mommy
[Music]
we have the fighting type as well so I
don't think he can hurt as much but I
mean he's pretty much dead now anyway
there we go
[Music]
huh
okay
round two
oh
I mean once you know the attacks it's no
problem I guess you just gotta be really
patient with throwing the bombs
and mostly there is no real time to
throw much
it's really just you need to wait until
you can fight
and then throw it afterwards
a little bit of time there
and here
yeah
uh uh uh uh
all right
yeah this is the Run
[Music]
our mommy Mommy I know this one we don't
even probably need a strong let's just
do normal
huh
[Music]
oh I'm surprised I
what
Isis effect
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
but I want to even move Strong Style I
don't think it would have killed him
looking at the damage that it did now oh
wow okay let's go we'll be Sparks come
on
it's laughing good yeah
oh man
by the way let's heal my Pokemon
what I only have four revivals left
cheese
oh my God
that's not very convenient but will be
final design
um okay
holy [\h__\h]
come at me bro
oh what both
well that was unexpected okay is he
gonna combine some other moves as well
um
oh oh spikes spikes spikes not Sparks
yeah yeah
I'm not gonna do anything cocky now it's
gonna chill
oh God
are you gonna do the thing the bean
okay
oh
damn I thought I had a little bit more
time ah
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
one more hand and I'm down I think
oh God
these are different
[Music]
I wish that I [\h__\h] up man
oh
a laser laser laser tag laser 10 from
that side okay
okay can I do it can I fight you now
okay
sorry for being cocky before
oh God oh God
nice fight though
okay
we should not be standing in the lay on
that
so let's see how much damage
yeah
super effective and only half
courteous
wow is this the last battle I'll be
getting or is there one more I wonder
well
um obese spikes should not die
not should not be even uh touched
um
[Music]
should be fine yeah yeah
okay oh my God
oh please be kind to me okay no more no
more no more no more no more oh it's
just a little bit just a little bit dull
[Music]
ah this is risky I could just throw like
two more but this is almost more risky
than throwing the bombs
not throwing them is almost right scared
am I am I one hit away or two
oh God
okay never mind never mind never mind
never mind never mind never mind never
mind never mind doll
oh oh wow
foreign
what do you think guys what do you think
do I deserve to
um
I think I do
you know we could totally do it in one
go uh but I don't want to end the stream
soon uh so
yeah
oh reset the gosh
isn't that just starting from the
beginning
you know baby mode baby mode baby mode
you know we all know I could do it
without baby mode
oh here he did reset a little bit
a little bit
uh
uh you
do
okay
thank you
[Music]
oh
wow now laser
foreign
[Music]
do you think this would make do more
damage
I kind of want to see we're gonna die
anyway one hit so I want to see how much
damage it doesn't in
in comparison
okay it's also just how
I guess fighting fighting is four times
effective but it does have less
power in that attack
[Music]
well lumay was what I had on on default
so whatever you [\h__\h] avoid it
now you make me mad
no one can avoid my chunky Raichu
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
I will not do another round with you I'm
done playing
no more playing
[Music]
oh oh hello
Big Mountain spider
wow wow wow
challenging I like it
um
yeah yeah icicle plate that was the last
Lord that we had to frenzy the last one
but
as you guys said the story does not end
there there's still quite a bit to go
apparently
oh yeah so the question now is since we
since we uh
calmed all of them down the question was
if the rift will if something will
change about it
uh
Eric sir you need to look quite so
downcast
was seeing Mike Diablo quelled and by
such a slight child a child that fell
from the very sky
is this kiawa girl some kind of monster
in the sky what
I'm a God
that's why I fell from the sky
I'm an angel Maybe
Angel's powerful too
she is no monster
she's the one who risked her life
without a second thought in order to
quell our friends eat suffering Nobles
yes
kiawa Gary cares for the program with
all his heart and believes in Almighty
signal just as deeply so he has feared
more than any of us that getting
involved with a diamond Clan and your
Galaxy team could cause her people to
flag in their Devotion to Almighty
sinner
but that will change
here we go
you know your fears will change once you
see what you've what I've seen Yahweh
has much to teach us she's shown us how
we can overcome all manner of strife so
long as our Pokemon are with us
she's made me want to help Glaceon
realize greater strength as well and to
see my whole world grow broader
it seems you've already changed Siri
though
I knew you could pull that off key one
way
you quote every last friend's Noble so
is that space timer going to start
closing up no what
doesn't look like it's doing anything
at least not for now there's a little
way of knowing for sure though the rift
does seem perhaps a little smaller some
yeah
[Music]
let's hope so anyway
well with any luck things will settle
down now although even if the rift does
start spitting out more of that strange
lightning we should still be alright as
long as we've got Kiowa
indeed we should be it's good to have
her at our sign
you know something here we go we may
never agree on who's got it right about
Almighty say no but you Brooklyn folk
aren't all bad in my book
even
anyway now I will call the last notebook
say we pay grimald command to come and
do a visit and see if he'll finally
crack a smile for his hand
oh
oh yeah I think we need to
report
um or I wonder if they let me out out to
the area without reporting
um but hey oh my God we should take a
picture how do you turn off the
but even if I do then
oh I guess I'll stand here
how do you turn off the the thing again
there was a button for it I think
the overlay
that is now
uh first let me take a selfie exactly
right stick
well
right click stick I'm doing it
HUD
it doesn't doesn't work
ah it's disabled
there it is all right
I feel like I'm
shouldn't the camera always be centered
I feel like there's more space to the
right side
my OCD I didn't know I had it
but I feel it strongly now
how is this possible am I not standing
straight in the middle apparently not
what I really I'm not in the middle of
the screen am I
why am I not in the
L trigger just sent it no
ah well okay
no it still doesn't
do I stand
there's still more space on the right
side
why but okay okay well it's okay it's
okay it's okay
let's take a screenshot
they're looking at me
look to the front
nice
[Music]
oh she's freezing
you good kiwawa fine though well I want
if I stand there
wait
I don't mind the cold I'm a phoenix
maybe I can cover her up nicely ah
can you go somewhere Chihuahua
oh
I'm I'm there I'm probably should be a
bit smaller
look here
I'm in the
let me I made it I made it so far oh my
god well if that doesn't mean success
then I don't know what it is
[Music]
you know what I feel like with my
standard outfit I kind of fit in nicely
too
wait a second
I feel like it might have low-key
Pokemon trainer than vibes
actually my casual one too a little bit
[Music]
um
how does it look
am I fitting in
I'm too slender my body type is a little
bit too sexy
duh
yay I'm a Pokemon trainer
DLC when my curves are too much that is
impossible too much for them maybe
hmm
let me let me pick up my child
okay Savvy let's go
wait somebody take my hand
take my hand take my hand One Clap
zombie you're so small let me make
myself smaller I can't hold your hand
Savvy come with me
I'm going to I'm going to show my yummy
food at home and cats cats can I show
you my cats I'll show you my cats I have
lovely cats come with me come with me
hahaha
I'll take her home then maybe I'll take
you to me
irida would you also like to come join
us we can have a little party I don't
know watch some Netflix
while cuddling Miami cats
yeah the other two get lost get out of
here okay
let's go girls
foreign
[Music]
uh wait I need to save the game though
wow it's a snowstorm right now suddenly
stay small chocolate Super Chat should I
stay small
initial
well that was a fun
hello I'm your boss
I might be small but you still have to
respect me okay
now
hello Chad hello
how are you
hey what's today's uh business that we
have to finish
[Music]
um
chickens have become too fluffy to
handle understandable I think that's
good though no need to rip out any
feathers keep them fluffy that will make
them look cuter oh what do you mean oh
and we have to make the sizes of the
uniforms bigger in that case okay
that's fine let's make the sizes bigger
whatever it takes to make them look
chunkier and cuter and yeah it's my
preference so it has to be what else
what else the chickens and chickens want
to eat something else besides uh fried
chicken before for lunch
well we have salad so just eat salad
then I mean what what else you want corn
is that what chickens eat corn
I can get you guys some corn
understandable I love corns too corns
yeah yeah I get that I get that I get
that
[Music]
what else oh chat chat you is do you try
now
would you be okay with sharing your
current well mine would be the superior
core and your your guys's corn would be
uh
average corn yeah
[Music]
any other issues to discuss today before
we go into the Super Chat reading
I can't believe you're actually asking
that if you can get a raise you know
what the answer is
ah
you should know
I've said it many many times
if only I had my denied button right now
can I get an extra hat
um you can have
and
as many hats as you want as long as
they're not more hats than I am wearing
at the time if I wear two hats you can
wear maximum two hats if I wear one hat
you can wear a maximum of one hand
yeah don't wear more hats than me that
is the rule
because I feel like other ones you're
challenging me in my existence can I
wear your hat no that is not an option
you can wear a hat that looks like my
hat you can make yourself one now my hat
is not an option no
the union you mean the onions man you
guys need to turn off your Auto auto
correct what about the onions there's
one in Inna smile for you if you want an
onion ring then I guess steal it from
Ina
Ina is eating the onion rings I think
she uh she might be monopolizing all the
onion rings on this world
it's not fair I think that is actually
something we might have to discuss with
her
because onions are quite important in
Burgers Some people prefer them without
onions and that's okay but we do have to
have onions just in case but recently
there has been a lack of onions because
they're all going to Taco Bell
an inacceptable
[Music]
so let's steal some onions and once
again a good reason for war with Taco
Bell
yeah as if we didn't already have enough
reasons
more onions
feather calming
oh is there no one in charge of that
right now
I thought you guys were grooming
yourselves
well then is there anyone up for the job
anyone who wants to become kfb feather
Comber
you might you may take the title now if
anyone's looking for a specific job
foreign
[Music]
you were the first one
you were the funniest one Chris guac is
now the feather Comber uh
[Music]
we could also have a
uh
what's what's it called uh
I forgot
[Music]
a big box Waxman that's interesting
no you can't that's not that's not
hygienic hygienic
[Music]
you must clean your beaks yourself guys
yeah I feel like that's just asking for
accidents like ax
accidentally
picking out each other's Eyes by
accident I don't want that to happen too
often so
um
Talon trimmer what's the talent is that
the tail or the red uh weird thing
that you guys have
a claws oh Talon trimmer
Who Wants To Be A Talon trimmer the claw
trimmer I guess we can have someone like
that it's like a shoe polisher it's for
chickens
Tony okay
tone is the first one I saw Tommy you
may be the actually I think it sounds
good in your name Tony the Talon trimmer
that sounds beautiful it has a nice ring
to it
[Music]
many new jobs there and you'll get a job
and you'll get a job and you get a job
and you get a job
mm-hmm
[Music]
okay you guys are always welcome to pick
your own job titles so I'll leave the
rest to you guys
but you already the gaming pair sure you
can change it to lurking piano if you
want to
so thank you everybody for watching the
Pokemon stream today
next Pokemon will be next week I think
I'm currently planning it for Wednesday
or Thursday
and uh yeah
I
I will
read some pictures now
oh
are you guys gonna go crazy if I leave
this music long
[Music]
last Pokemon next Pokemon could be the
last before the critters oh am I that
far
it would be good to know
uh but
even if we like finished kind of early
there's so much to do like side quests
you can still do like side quests and
stuff afterwards right
is there also something like the what
was it called
uh
the victory Street no what is it called
again
for the post game like like in Pearl and
Diamond
or was that not even post game
the victory round was Victory Road post
game well not pre-pre-post game
yeah I mean obviously it doesn't exist
yet that makes sense but I mean like
anything like that
in like similar
it was before all
my Elite Four yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
um
okay super chats from this stream I will
stay small I'll make myself a tiny bit
bigger for the phone users is anyone on
the phone right now you guys see me
where the phone uses
you guys good how is Kiana today I'm
doing fine thank you for asking me me me
yes hi I'm on phone hello I'm small
using my phone at the moment oh so many
phone users should I be should I make
myself bigger for you
so
[Music]
actually oh I was thinking I really need
to get a new phone man
I've had um the same phone for a while
and um I'm kind of
um maybe not that clumsy but I've
dropped my phone several times and it
was fine it didn't break for a long time
but a while ago it started cracking and
there's not like a huge crack on it but
it started cracking from the bottom uh
corner and
after some days passed it like continued
uh spreading
it's not that bad it's it doesn't stand
out that much but it gives me a good
reason to get a new phone because I
wanted to get a new one anyway
um
yeah I don't have any case on it so
honestly I'm surprised it survived so
long it's pretty pretty
um sturdy
birthday my giraffe yeah
congrats I'll give you a number later
yeah yeah it's totally usable but I
think why wasn't my brother I think when
I was talking about getting a new phone
my brother was like can I have yours
then
I think it was my my brother or my
mother probably also
wanted it not sure I think they both
they both want my old phone
yeah yeah
[Music]
you used to take that photo of the plane
yes that one yeah yeah it has an insane
zoom function
um my phone is sold after em it's it's a
still a fairly new generation I would
say but damn the cameras and phones keep
on getting better and better
yeah I only use Android I only like
Android I don't want to use the iPhone
privately
ah yeah I wanted I want to get like a
new Samsung
but now not one of those foldable ones
did you guys see the new foldable
Samsung phone is there not even that
phone they knew they have been doing
that for a while apparently but I don't
want the foldable one new Samsung just
came out this week is it is it a
foldable one because I don't care about
the foldable one
huh
I just that's just kind of weird it's
like why not get a tablet then
I I liked you know back in the day when
there were those
like OG foldable phones
that was cute and uh I had one when I
lived in Japan for a while when I was
younger because Japanese people still to
this day use the typical older folder
phones still they really like those I
don't know why but they're really
popular in Japan yeah the flip phones
um
I know
[Music]
it's a flip phone again in Japanese I
forgot the word
the term gagake
[Music]
[Laughter]
I know
[Music]
that it is
foreign
[Music]
you can get Samsung S21 or s22 is that
your your current
uh suggestion
recommendation is that the newest one
Samsung Galaxy I never had the Samsung
before I think
[Music]
oh is that the newest one the newest one
is s32
does it have a cute color it comes in
pink
it comes in pink and I love in there as
well
no wait that's S21
oh it came out of the 9th of February
yeah that's so recent holy [\h__\h] I could
get the most recent one yeah
oh
it has one two three four five cameras
and one on the front I suppose is that
is that so
Wait no that's not no it has four camera
no wait there is a bottle with three and
one with five
interesting
oh the one with the five is the ultra
there's s22 s22 plus and s22 Ultra
wow
cool I think I'm gonna look at them in
the store
and I want to have them in my I want to
hold them in my hand and see if the size
is okay I don't want a too big one I
don't like when the phones get too big
I also don't like them too small they
have to be
like something in between
yeah they have to fit into Pockets
nicely into average Pockets at least
like from jackets
it doesn't have to fit perfectly into a
pants uh pocket because we're Banning
them anyway
but it should fit into a jacket pocket
yeah
s22 might be best for you for most but I
also want the cameras though I might
just get the big one for the sake of the
cameras I wanna be able to take photos
that look insane
you know I need to take those pictures
for you guys
cheers
gonna test it out and look at some
review videos
[Music]
okay okay okay enough enough to chat
super chattel
no more chit chat now Super Chat
why not just get a real camera yeah
cause I'm not gonna carry around a real
camera all the time
it's just way more convenient to have a
phone with a great camera now
um
what a question think
grass Mo think
[Music]
rasmal Fink are you thinking think
told you to think
[Music]
okay
when it's too cold oh I'm sure the new
ones are fine
foreign
[Music]
I'm not bullying you I'm just telling
you to think
think
oh let's bring a camera everywhere oh
well I mean if you do like photography
as like a pretty serious hobby then I
totally get it
then your camera is your baby
so understandable
obviously nothing will ever top a proper
uh camera
[Music]
but the phones these days are pretty
insane too
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is this
Pakistan is that some kind of tongue
twister in a different language
probably mispronounced why are you
laughing at me
what
a tongue twister in Spanish oh oh
[Music]
I ain't saying that one's pretty short
though you might explain your Danish for
the pinky oh lovely gorgeous Phoenix I
finally took that Loop of fave and
jumped into the hot oil here on okay huh
it's been a wonderful year with you
Kiana you've kept my spirit up and got
me for some rough moments I'm glad to
have you as my OC I also received my
birthday merch with a friend that my dog
would make the slippers her chewy toys
so I ended up displaying them along with
my stuff toys ah
yeah I can see how a dog would want to
do that
yeah that's probably for the better to
be careful about that and display them
uh somewhere where the dog won't try to
eat it
[Music]
good idea
thank you for one year of support and
maybe even longer than one year
depending on how long you were watching
me before your membership but yeah I'm
so glad you're still here and hopefully
you'll stay here long enough to be
revived into an orange chicken
yeah
so thank you so much for all the love
and support you give me thank you soon
decibel package in for one two three
four five pinkies
yo are you good oh but it's my Crusader
I haven't heard anything from you in a
while
[Music]
okay let's see two her Reverend Chiara
DV your vassal and Hubble servant
greetings with Antioch Concord
represented into Syria stormed Bara and
Mara cities of the bamboozles and
captured fortresses in that country as
we delayed there there was so great of a
mean among kfb that we found chicken
edible finally your Phoenix fire lit our
way and we entered further into the
interior of Syria and the most Bountiful
merciful and Victorious hand of our
Phoenix model was with us for within the
desert as prophecy
decided by the mother of chickens there
was a great stable containing a galleon
Gallant horse whose name could only be
circles and the cities and fortresses of
the country through which we proceeded
with circles surrendered to us
but as we still recovered from our
tribulations at Antioch and it was the
unanimous wish to hasten to fix and we
accepted their pledges and made them
tributaries
tributaries our conquests continue to
feed into the number of the hosts of kfb
and windows at nikaya and Antioch heard
of heard how the hand of our hot wings
was with us many from the Army who had
remained in those cities followed us to
tire
therefore with Kiana's companionship and
Aid we proceed thus as far as Phoenix
didn't
[Music]
sounds like quite the adventure
I might have said this before but you
need to put all this together into a
collection
[Music]
yeah a lot happened that's what I got
from them
you need to make a book out of it a
collection maybe even an audio book
maybe just yeah with my voice reading it
out loud
for these streams worth of a super
chance to look back on or was it that
much holy [\h__\h] it's been going on for
some time yo
that is dedication
thank you there's a vault you deserve
many a kisses for that
[Music]
I I wish you a luck and success in your
quest uh onwards uh and uh make kfp
proud
yes don't die
whatever it is don't die
give him your handkerchief I don't have
a handkerchief
I'll have a handkerchief I'll give you
I'll give you uh I'll give you my sh my
hat
bring it back bring it back safely
don't wait
so now everyone who's wearing two hats
must take off one because I'm also only
wearing one
there you go
it's it's
close
okay I'm counting on you to stay alive
to bring back that hat to me and I don't
want too much blood on it okay
keep it white
[Music]
support thank you so much
damage ready for a rainbow I think
that's a rainbow thank you savage
[Music]
oh wait I mean yeah that's right today
wait are you hinting that you were
watching movie or so and what's your
profile picture now
there there is indeed a movie
I was thinking when I was looking at the
small one that kind of that brown thing
looks like Mommy
uh-huh let's see you changed one of your
oceans again I see I see
I missed quinoa I'm still there
[Music]
come back to Kansas before watching you
stream I'm still in busy works you mean
busy watching movie
but I will try to keep watching Kiana
every day I went to the owl cave on my
way here and Mumbai also told me to use
kfb salt and pepper forever oh
oh really
by the way Kiana's best chicken most
cute best funny I'm not a chicken though
[Music]
there's a Korean sentence that says
apparently according to Savage translate
Kiana I always love you but we of course
don't trust Savage
so we will translate it ourselves
because we're not gonna get fooled by
Savage
foreign
it's a secret that I joined the owl
membership
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
Jessica
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah it's okay
okay of course you can join other
memberships as long as you stay in this
one make sure that you're always in this
one
[Music]
you little
Savage
Savage I knew it I knew you were should
not be trusted
uh what humans want to give your regards
[Music]
I don't know what to do with those
regards
[Music]
thank you savage I guess
Jessica is
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
is that is that really uh does it really
have the same meaning as the OG I wonder
or is it more like me saying you are
poop or yourself I wanted to have the
same kind of ring to it you little [\h__\h]
you can just go
I hope it has the same meaning we don't
want any misunderstandings here
[Music]
I'm gonna get some more water
such a son of a bee really
oh but at least uh the insulting tone of
it is there thankfully
[Music]
and motion thank you
oh you finished it today
did you like it I feel like I really
like it so honestly I was thinking about
it today while I was playing this this
is probably going to be my most favorite
Pokemon game there's definitely some
things that could be better but there's
also so many things that are better than
other Pokemon games and it's very
special and uh the story is I feel like
way more
detailed and then other Pokemon games in
my opinion and and
there's so many lovely characters
I like all the NPCs I mean okay like the
personality of that who what was his
name Melly or so the blue guy is
questionable but still like everyone has
a very unique personality and I like the
character designs from everybody too
[Music]
um
yeah
so I'm very very satisfied and the
fights are challenging the
um I've heard from other people before
that they think in Pokemon games the the
level uh curve is not very good like all
the Pokemon are too low level all the
trainers are too low level
even if you don't grind but in this game
I don't think it is the case like they
did a good job there
and and the the Lord fights are
challenging as well they get more and
more challenging
yeah the wild Pokemon hit much harder
it's quite difficult
and yeah
and even even being stealthy is
difficult
yeah it's a lot of difficulty increase
and I've I suppose you know because
Pokemon's main fan base is still or main
goal is still pleasing the younger
audience the children audience so they
have to keep the games a little bit easy
but this time they did not care about it
that much maybe yeah their main
demographic about keeping it too easy
for them
it's probably still manageable but I
don't know about a 60 year old playing
this game
how how young are people usually when
they play Pokemon is six years realistic
or seven years
I can't really I think they would have
some travel play in this game
sometimes
at least for the Lord fights the frenzy
ones
six seven years is that realistic
not sure if they will do so well in this
game all the time I think they would
have some troubles it might get a bit
frustrating for them sometimes
hmm
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
growing up with original NES difficulty
was possible so this should be fine
[Music]
um
next Pokemon game will probably be
probably go back to the old style see
that is the question that is the
question how much will they keep
and how much will they go back to their
OG Style
I can see that they don't want to have
every Pokemon game be as open and free
as this one is
I can see that they would go like paddle
back a little bit
but I hope they keep a lot of things
that they made uh for this game
um
there are a lot of improvements
that would make sense to keep until the
next gen
foreign
I think yeah if they see a success in
the game then they might consider
keeping it
it's a very interesting question we will
have to wait and see yeah
[Music]
this game is selling better than sword
and shield so far is that so is that so
well that's a good sign but it is it's
definitely kind of a revolutionary
Pokemon I think just the fact that it's
so different made a lot of people wanna
maybe give it another try uh maybe they
skipped some Pokemon games but are like
yo yo yo might give this a try and I've
seen some people who are usually
critical
um of Pokemon games actually praise it
so
they're definitely doing a lot of things
correctly and that's really cool to see
[Music]
burnt out at this rate yeah I I think so
too I mean there's always gonna be new
comments to the genre to the series
so
the the same formula could always work
on them but you gotta think about the
old Pokemon fans that still that have
been supporting it for so many years for
centuries perhaps
gonna think about how to keep them
um
right
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
anyway
sound thank you for the red so much
oh my God some sick beats for intro just
gonna keep working here don't mind me oh
yeah yeah I felt like changing it up a
little bit and I'm actually gonna be
getting an
um a new outro soon a new outro video
about the music I don't know what yet
what to do yet but I do want to change
it
so
um
[Music]
gotta look around maybe there's a
maybe there's another cool remix that
would be suitable
hey but the outro is pretty special
it's very very um
yeah the last one the one that we're
using right now
um was just made without my request and
I just asked if I can use it uh but this
time the new outro will actually be
commissioned so
and
yeah
there's a
um and it's it's according to my wishes
you will see soon I think
um it should be ready soon
yeah
but I won't say by who it is no no no no
now I'm thinking like what do I do about
the music hmm
hmm
yeah but please look forward to it
foreign
[Music]
no it needs to be something more calm
because
um it has to fit the ending
graphic
yeah anyway thank you Felix for the red
super chat
yeah yeah I I kind of would like to see
more remixes from my songs so if musical
people are listening then please feel
free to make remixes
actually that reminds me I wanted to
send the Sparks stems to someone
guys can you remind me if I forget
after the stream in the ending tweet
can you guys reply to me just one person
is enough someone asked me
if they could remix Sparks and I was
like yo yeah you know what I'm gonna try
to get you the stems for it so it can be
even higher quality
God I'm getting so hungry I need to read
super jets
[Music]
down
down down down
[Music]
soon
it is
[Music]
but man you make one heck of a cute
monkey yeah so hey if you're not busy
later how about we go get a Bananas
movie from the Banana Bar wink wink just
joking of course or am I also welcome
back from your trip yo I would love to
go to um to the banana stand there's
always money in the banana stand but
there's also yummy looking
bananas chocolate covered with nuts on
top
I would love to try a George Michael
served
banana
[Music]
[Applause]
you can't not have me make a reference
when I'm watching Arrested Development
right now
just one banana how much can it cost
yeah probably not much
George Milo yeah that's one of the
characters one of the people in the in
the show hey it's so funny money
Arrested Development humor might be my
favorite humor
[Music]
Stephen Gardner Duncan
on Google Translate
Google Translate son
I think that's Russian could be wrong
though
Ukrainian
[Music]
thank you thank you soon images
greetings are the best bird and I want
to share so much with you but my the
lost four words all I can say is that
your streams bring me much enjoyment
really proud to be under kfb's
employment again I get much enjoyment
from you thanks for the content thank
you for watching I would be nothing
without you guys if you weren't watching
my if you weren't watching my streams so
it's uh how to say one hit one hand
shakes the other
at least we say that in German
do you guys say that in English
I need you guys to exist otherwise I
have no reason to exist
[Music]
oh One hand washes the other not shakes
theater
that's the saying well do you say that
one in English
you scratch my back I scratch yours I
guess so it's the same sentiment yeah
so thank you Super Saiyan mommy I'm so
glad you're enjoying my stream please
continue doing so I will do my best to
provide content
continuously thank you so much mwah
everyday
[Music]
I'm a newbie who joined kfb for two
weeks it's all two weeks so new how did
you find me
it's finally time to say hello
managera sorry for using a translator
because my English is weak no problem
I'm sorry if I interrupt the Flow by any
chance thank you for always making the
stream enjoyable so polite what a polite
chicken
well welcome to kfb everybody say
welcome Sherry welcome Sherry oh yeah
chocolates a smoothie hi I thought you
were talking nice movie
says welcome to
well did you hear that well
she entered the room to say hello
[Music]
you did hear her
it was a very aggressive mama why are
you still streaming meow
meow meow meow
oh
[Music]
she's so cute so soft
oh okay well
and once again thank you very much
Sherry for the support I'm glad you're
here now I hope that you will continue
watching me and have lots of fun here I
don't speak Korean and you seem to use a
translator for English so it's a it's a
miracle that we have found one another
but it's meant to be perhaps don't you
think
[Music]
soon
I have not tried it yet though I think
no
[Music]
thank you
Stephen Gardner
[Music]
um
for the pinky I always play Pokemon
while watching your stream and I just
called a shiny Alpha carnivore what are
you looking for it just there what the
[\h__\h] to step on me oh I mean to battle
for me sorry I'm drinking right now so
this message might be weird but I'm just
happy and felt like giving you a Super
Chat
[Music]
what a shiny Alpha Gardevoir well that's
pretty cool
and I want that too send it to me as a
caffeine chicken you're you are
obligated to give me anything that I
asked for so
um send it to me
[Music]
just kidding you can keep it I'll find
my own
[Music]
I wanna see a shiny too I want to see
that Spike oh
[Music]
zero seven
wonders
I'm gonna skip those those are a lot
that's a lot of flushing we go to
English
Frank closer thank you no I did not
change any of my fabric of washing
detergent or anything yeah it's weird it
just came out of nowhere I don't know
why
[Music]
I'm a clerk at campus Korean brand yeah
it's my first Super Chat I don't think
I'll be able to watch Kiana for a while
because from the 14th Valentine's Day
I'll be called by the state and join the
Navy I hope you're enjoying the
streaming until I come back always be
healthy how long are you going are you
still here
[Music]
how long how long
meows moving meow
you still here now
sorry my cat is talking to me now
[Music]
it's not here you already left man
foreign
let me know on Twitter
Ice movie she's getting impatient
yeah once more I'm playing the
sailor's wife waving goodbye oh I don't
like it he said to come back November
2020 no way
two years
no let's wait too long but wait can you
watch like in between if you're in the
Korean Navy are you able to do some
stuff and I mean no way that for two
years you won't be able to watch any any
YouTube at all
no way
foreign
[Music]
minimum required what the [\h__\h]
YouTube is watchable uh-huh so we get
some private time
man
and why why you guys gotta do that to me
and say goodbye like that when you just
arrived
[Music]
I mean now you're leaving it breaks my
heart
under your panda
no no no no no
did you write it incorrectly on purpose
I'm a high pair the way you wrote that
I'm a high pair and the who would be a
neck
no
no no goodbye
I'm hungry I'm gonna start eating some
chicken soon
yeah the kanji was wrong
yeah no you wrote the wrong candy
anyway
[Music]
well watch me every weekend please
please please
right so freedom because
Sherry for 757 thank you for the pinky
boss I'm leaving work first it was a
happy five hours it's three a.m here
it's Infinity that I can't watch
streaming at dawn based on jst good
night hope to see you again no problem
don't worry about it I totally
understand
uh yeah my streaming times are kind of
awkward for a lot of viewers
yeah but yeah if you can try to catch my
stream sometimes I would be very very
honored thank you for your support
[Music]
yeah it turns out that this game is
almost impossible to play while holding
a cat oh I misread it I thought it was
impossible to play it without holding a
cat on your lap maybe okay
up and then maybe even uh like uh lean
your hands and your switch against the
cat so I'm sure the cat will like it
cats like to be like close to warm
monitors and stuff
it can be your your support
[Music]
try them
cats need to be included in the gaming
session doesn't like to sit on my lap he
wants to be held on when that what the
[\h__\h]
huh mine don't want to be held or be on
my lap they just want to be as close as
possible to me
without being on my lap or being held
although smoothie likes
um being carried over my shoulder
[Music]
um for a certain amount of time
chonkers doesn't like being carried much
at all not not for very long if it's
just for a moments she's fine with it
but yes movie actually has accepted
being carried around I think as mostly
As Long As I don't just stand still if I
walk around the apartment I think she
kind of sees it as a tour
[Music]
as the tour and me lifting her higher
gives her a new perspective she enjoys
that
have a place where it's sweetheart
beautiful Phoenix but I love Amelia
Watson I should always be carefully
employed
understandable I respect that
I respect that you can be both you can
like both
but that's a struggle that a lot of you
us have to deal with I think
liking more than one YouTuber
laughs
oh Spanky hand here's a kiss from
lavanger
[Music]
oh yeah by the way I think second time
you should always prioritize cat hmm
thank you mad arcade very sweet of you
Patrick
oh just relax
[Music]
ing excuse me Jacob 47 aldakashan calls
me kind donkey
[Music]
birthday merch finally arrived let's go
because I have a employee ID yes it's
number 86 and a job title for whatever
job you may need done perfectly willing
to get my hands dirty I'm a loyal
chicken after I love you tangible
hmm
uh
[Music]
a job
how about
he doesn't mind getting his hands dirty
how about tomato squeezer that's you
you squeeze the tomatoes to make them
into ketchup to make them into sauce
we need someone to squeeze tomatoes for
that purpose
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes
I think if you do it for a while you
will have very very strong Wings because
you don't have hands but I'm sure you
can squeeze them with your wings
you'll be a really buff chicken but only
in the front part of your wings
[Music]
then we need to slice them as and of
course for the burgers but for the sauce
we need tomato as an ingredient
we have a lot of sauces we have to make
all of them possible
oh yeah also my two month sentence of
the usual uh room is always a February
9th wow the sentence was a little
excessive just for saying you'd make a
great goofy in Disneyland
perhaps
I was saying I'm I'm not
just but I'm just happy to finally be
out and away from that Pop-Tart die
[Music]
yeah you better be be careful now
squeeze those Tomatoes make me proud
don't make me angry again
sometimes sometimes go got a tiptoe
around me you know
sorry about your falling phone oh wait
wait wait dakuma wants a number
um
[Music]
bakuma
I'm wondering if there's a
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
eight nine zero because big brain we
tried to uh go by
[Music]
um Japanese
um I can't explain I I don't know how to
explain it but maybe you kind of
understood what we were doing
[Music]
890 sick
you can feed your chicken family now
cute oh man
and
can kfp donkey
oh thank you oh
yeah she's [\h__\h] cute man I saw her in
the trailer cute dancing celebrities
beats thank you for the pinky am older
to celebrate my birthday I made a cafe
chicken pinata me Elena I asked you to
decide it's Fate The Glorious but brief
life of most pinatas or shall it live to
see the future birthdays as an aside
your Spanish always makes me send oh oh
really
[Music]
thank you
um
well first of all happy birthday
you're so sweet so please stay the way
you are your perfect the way you are I'm
always happy to see your comments
and you have you're so sweet you're so
kind you have a great personality thank
you for the love and support I wish you
all the best
stay healthy
yeah no need to change anything uh the
pinata
ask it to
to
poop out the candy kindly ask it
politely
and an offer that if it does that then
you don't have to kill it but if it
refuses to do so then smash it
smash it
or ground pound it even or throw it on
the ground
foreign
[Music]
's working hours are kind of weird but I
shall overcome that with loyalty
oh you guys are the best can you point
me as a specific position for KFC oh
[Music]
what should we do what should we do
loyalty Council huh
ah ah uh how about
[Music]
damn
loyalty card
Stamper is there a better word for that
loyalty card stamp
or you become the stamp how about you
become the standard
loyalty card
well now we do now we have a line with
the card
for customers
approval loyalty card
[Music]
stamp
ink on the feet oh that's cute stamping
with your feet
oh okay you are the stamp loyal you are
kfp loyalty card stamp
[Music]
ah
that is so cute
customer comes by with their loyalty
card buys their fifth Burger this week
pulls out loyalty card you come by
you're like okay leave it to me you tip
your little feet into that ink I know
stop cut Softly on the loyalty card and
say thank you so much for being loyal
we value your loyalty dear customer yes
cute very cute
[Music]
or or I just grabbed you yeah like a
stamp
put your foot into ink and do it myself
no no no I'm sure you can delete
yourself
[Music]
I'm sure you can do it yourself I I
can't be in every store at the same time
you have to be able to do it yourself
okay be welcome thank you for your
support
thank you
another man that's thank you for the
pinky so to go back to the phone thing
but if you want examples I have photos
from my vacation that I can post on
Twitter they're just star and nature
shots my phone is a Samsung Galaxy Note
21 Ultra the camera is the only reason I
upgrade it
oh yes I would like to see it I would
like to see please share it with me I'm
curious to see the quality but if I'm
gonna buy one I'm gonna buy the newest
one
but I suppose the 21 the 22 Ultra will
be even better so
[Music]
and now we're done guys thank you for
today I'm gonna go now make food and
I'll see you tomorrow I'm not sure yet
what we're streaming tomorrow
um I'll think about it a little bit and
then put up the reservation yes
movie is already waiting oh waiting my
cuddles she's waiting on the floor
think she fell asleep on the floor
[Music]
isn't the new song tomorrow yeah but I
want to stream anyway
[Music]
um
you know you know you know yeah there
will be a stream and there will be a new
music video a new song cover
I have yet to see the final version so
yeah bye again
[Music]
all the teammates shall also be informed
yes I'm a Tony song cover
it will be exceptionally cute trust me
on that one
um
[Music]
yes yes
it's it's gonna be tasty yeah
so that I said good night everybody and
enjoy what we say
and thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
I [\h__\h] hurt I got brown palette by a
chicken oh no
[Music]
foreign
good night hope you feel better soon
[Music]
good night everybody
good night good night I will try to
become bigger again until tomorrow I
will eat my veggies
[Music]
Ohio
foreign