[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
all right
now
[Music]
foreign
there we go
hello
wow you guys here are you here often
it's been a day too for years
it was really just
let me cleaned up my OBS no no no not I
mean I'm not not really
uh yeah you come here often usually
every day oh I see
uh I I've I've been here like 84 years
ago
so you guys come here
either like once every 84 years or every
day even with Windows 84 years
interesting interesting
oh your first time
whoa your first time here incredible
that sounds like a big fat lie to me
I don't I don't think so I think you're
lying to me
it's been so long hasn't it
uh do I sound different to you
okay
[Music]
um
I do
okay
I'm going that that I cannot explain
that's just uh my room I hear a
high-pitched people yeah that's like
you know I was recording something the
past couple days
um trying to record several things but
um then I noticed this
like sound right like I'm a bee
um but I'm not a b but you know actually
like you know now now you probably hear
it very loudly do you do you now now
even louder do you hear this
yeah so I was like I noticed that and I
was like what the [\h__\h] is this
so
I turned down do you hear the difference
the high frequencies which does not get
completely rid of it and also feels like
it takes a lot of the radio oomph out of
my voice so I don't I don't know man has
it always been like
that was there always this like this
this in my uh
background when you don't hear BJ I
think when there's bgm you barely notice
it but
it hasn't
because I don't know what it is man I
think if it was there then it was there
for a while recently and I just noticed
because I had to record myself
um and listen to the no bgm version
and then I hear this [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
yeah yeah I was fiddling with it and
this is the result uh I tuned down the
high frequencies but I feel like it
takes away a lot else than just dubs
I even tweeted a little some time ago oh
really oh yeah yeah with bgm in the
background is not noticeable it's not
not a problem to be honest
[Music]
um
uh well you know what so I will I will
turn it a little bit back up because
once I play the music you won't really
know what's you know
um
uh-huh uh-huh
uh-huh noise noise from the usual room
I don't know
it's time to shoot the Trump bomb yay
electrical interference in veterans
interference
I wonder
um oh you think YouTube audio
encoding helps me anyway with that
well guys it really hurts my ears well
how loud do you have me
like my own voice is very loud in my
ears and it does not hurt me so much all
right
yeah turned it back down again but like
yeah this is weird too it feels really
weird to me Max
yep you guys listen to speakers all with
headphones
I'm curious
headphones oh so many headphones wow
that's actually uh surprising
I wouldn't assume that the headphone
gang is all on PC or yeah traveling at
the moment
am I right
yeah
I thought so
um
never use you never use speakers when
watching me oh is there a reason for
that
do I make weird noises that you feel too
embarrassed about and don't want anyone
else to hear that you're hearing it
[Laughter]
clouds listen to me with speakers
Set Me Free I want the whole world to
hear me
hey
anyway let's see if I turned on the
trombone
the people who are suffering through
this really tiny and Noise
won't suffer anyway I feel like you guys
are not even human because you guys if
you suffer so much by that
then I feel like you hear frequencies
that a normal human can't even really
be bothered much by
what are you
are you a chicken
perhaps are you a chicken
a hill
let's this game mouth flashing really
whoa okay so I've heard about this game
where you can play it from bone and it's
kind of like a rhythm game but
you use your your mouse which I think I
will do so much of a better job than
with uh you know what maybe I even you
think it would be even better if I use
my my tablet
foreign
[Music]
let me try that I'm actually curious
that might be like next level
oh
maybe maybe
I feel like with the mouse I'll get
across the screen faster but with the
pen I might be able to
um I don't know like
we'll test both out perhaps but I feel
like I'll be more accurate with the
penalty but my my pen tablet is huge
cheese stretch hmm
but yeah the thing is I suck at Riven
games
we all know that I'm really bad
[Music]
yeah okay so I know this game is kind of
funny because like it's too dude and
there's some baboons apparently I don't
even know what that is is that a real
name for a sort of
animal
because it more sounds like an insult to
people
to me like oh you're such a baboon
[Laughter]
monkey
okay okay
but is it also an insult
I feel like I've heard people say that
before
[Applause]
yes and yes both yes ah
I'm serious wow music music
are you hearing this
ages after the
I knew are we starting an RPG game or
what
Brave so one day you will stay this is
so like
deployed wow
one day you will win the very fabric
that binds this land huh
oh
but until that day
you must stop
judge your trombone Brave
oh my God
trombone
wow wow this is so motivating and
inspired
why did they put him in like that that's
like not his Charming chocolate side I
gotta be honest
Mozart my man
welcome to
play to play the main game afterwards
many Secrets await the
what
so like I don't know it's funny
it's already funny I thought the funny
part was just to do dudes but the lore
is funny too okay I don't know is there
like do they teach me how to do it when
I play the first one
choose your tromboner do I have a choice
oh
pink hair
there's not enough Choice here huh oh
wait there's more
which one's no one looks like me no one
has orange hair wait let's let's go by
the names
Appaloosa Beasley okay zile II Trixie
Bell Mel door
milder sounds like kind of like a
Lord of the Rings name germa jesty horn
Lord and soda
which one's the best for me
[Music]
why germa
why
so that was before soda senpai
[Laughter]
wait why is there
why is it even like one and two like I
don't get this part do they have a
different like wait there's different
instruments did what is this what what
is that difference
[Music]
what is this what are these two things
oh the difference here is male and
female
what no they look the same
[Music]
I understand I'm gonna go for the horn
lord
lord of the horns and I guess we'll just
go like this now and I don't know what
this Tunis means oh
well it will make awaits you but first
let's start with a warm-up oh yeah oh
yeah oh warm up your trombone with this
simple warm up perfect for first time
it's okay okay okay okay scroll speed
tears dudes uh-huh interesting let's do
this
don't you don't you say don't you feel
the same
move the mouse forward and back to move
the slide line up the dot with the note
lines okay easy press the left Mouse but
no any letter key to do toot
uh okay
using the keyboard maybe easy on your
wrist oh
if you play well you build Combos and
increase your champ meter
wow this is how you get big points once
you breathe meter if you hold a note for
too long you'll run out of breath
I see interesting so realistic most of
all have fun and enjoy the beautiful
succulent music you you will soon create
okay so hmm I wonder if it really will
be that easy with this
with the pen I'm doing the pen now
why am I why is it inverted what
is this because of the pen or oh God
what is it supposed to be about it no
inverted
um
[Music]
there's settings for that I'm not gonna
do this on my tablet after all I thought
this was Big Brain but no pain
problems oh [\h__\h] but there
was genius well I'm being manipulated
change the setting
where
things
uh
[Music]
controls
foreign
[Music]
why is it inverted by default is that
just
why okay I'll do this then
okay
horn Lord
let's do some horny dudes
this time this time you'll see on the
first second already
that I was born for this
let's go
do to you dude you
[Music]
made
oh yeah let's go I'm warming up my
trombone let's [\h__\h] go go here we go
baby let's go okay let's be in the house
and keep one one is here too let's go
my trombone is sick as hell do you hear
it is
and every other instrument trombone is
the best in the house
[Music]
let's go
oh yeah what what
[Music]
I told you I told you you will see from
the first moment on that was fun for
this baby oh
hmm
wonderful
um I I knew it like why the [\h__\h] would
you doubt me hello I'm like the
descendant of Mozart
pouring some water because I'm too
fat in my throat because I'm on fire
is Mozart German it's
take away the few things we austrians
have
Mozart is so obviously Austrian like
dude
the real deal so like everybody goes
like for all these songs right
where do we even start what is what is
Sugar Plum Fairy that sounds cute this
piece oh oh damn already wait we should
sort this by difficulty
and start with the like oh oh oh
the easiest one there we go like
somewhere
ah okay this is the next one I would say
Sarah
the first part of this piece titled
Sunrise became famous after being used
in the film 2001 the Space Odyssey oh
have you guys watched it is that a good
movie I don't know that one yeah
Strauss
uh huh
yeah I know him I know him why would I
not know him of course I know him
[Music]
good
that's this oh I am junk wow what a
legendary sound
get it ready
get ready now
awkward pause
[Music]
oh my God so fast my eyes hurt
happens
[Music]
one more
eh
oh okay
[Music]
[Applause]
wow that was
absolutely amazing you're telling me a
German wrote this
wow
damn read all strands and Germans are
just like [\h__\h] geniuses
but also I didn't know this was like an
actual song
for me it was just a sound
[Laughter]
eh what do you mean I'm too good at this
that was easy what just started that's
that's just it how could I not be uh
good at that that was literally like a
one star difficulty
don't give me confidence that it will be
hard to follow up on later on man how am
I supposed to like impress you later on
when the difficulty is higher
all right
next
oh oh Beethoven
my beloved
lyrics
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
together this is
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Laughter]
I could have done like so much better at
that I was just distracted by the Angels
because it felt like they were kind of
manipulating me because the real angel
here can only be me
yeah
B football
uh
yeah that was by the way 100 accurate
lyrics of course you know it
I was kind of like waiting for the song
um because we all know that this is my
my national anthem no my European anthem
it's a beautiful song though okay next
the king oh I feel like I probably have
heard this before the Royal Anthem in
most Commonwealth Rams and there are
territories this also known as our
country country tis of tea what
in the United States why is it uh what
why
if you place all of the hormones on the
earth and the end they well oh oh can't
even erase that oh
God save our Grace she is King long live
our Noble King God Save the King
this is the first time I'm hearing the
lyrics
but ah it's hard to read them when
they're down there
[Music]
beautiful beautiful
what was that sound
it was such a disappointed sound man
[Music]
ah
oh
wow wow wow
absolutely killing it God saved the
beans
the beans don't need something the beans
are fine
I'm gonna speedrun this how many songs
are there what was it 20 50
April Austrian
yeah I did I did quite good at that huh
compared to old to Joy foreign
[Music]
this has become the theme song of North
American baseball although neither of
the songs offer has had attended a game
at the time of its writing
oh I I don't I probably understand when
I hear it but right now I don't know
what this is
ball game
ball again
Take Me Out to the Ball what
no it doesn't sound familiar at all do
you guys really play this when you're at
a baseball game
it's kind of like a circus music
oh quite beautiful though oh the balls
are coming
Dodge the balls
[Music]
take me to the
Ballgame take me to the crowd buy me
some peanuts and Cracker Jack what is
that
[Music]
I'm sweating
[Applause]
so answer my question is this actually
something you guys play over there
I love caramel corn
oh I want to have something of that what
did I just say I wouldn't have something
I wouldn't mind having something of that
some of that I don't know how to speak
yes I have a little little
oopsie in my brain
every game
it's a well-known Baseball Song I don't
know [\h__\h] about baseball I'm so sorry
[Music]
originally commissioned for the Saint
John Baptiste buncat in 1880 this didn't
become the de facto until Anthem until
1949.
[Music]
where are you at
where am I
where am I I'm playing this for you this
one's for you
Oh Canada
[Music]
this is the first time I'm ever hearing
this how come oh
I have to I have to do better I need I
need the Canadians to like me
it can only help having the most polite
people on Earth on my side right it can
only help okay
down
[Music]
Oh Canada
oh it's quite a beautiful Anthem I'll
give you guys that wow wow
Oh Canada We Stand our ground party
what's up kill
so cute
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah I was like not even doing that well
and I still get a how do you get
you get Beaver oh how
hands hi how you doing it's what time is
it over there like afternoon early
afternoon or so
it's from being here
turn down the scroll oh okay I'll try
that do you think it'll be easier what
if we make it even easier and oh my God
I'll have like
so so much better rankings won't I
we cannot allow such a thing I'll blow
everyone away
between noon and 4pm
Central Grand almost by the ladies and
the real ones
what do they actually sing
oh where am I where am I where am I
where am I where's where's Canada oh
this this menu is so weird
huh huh
foreign
like when I scroll I don't know why how
how it's
how is it scrolling ah here we go
finally okay I'm back okay
try your theme song soon what's my theme
song I have a theme song in here is it
not Ode to Joy
look at the stars oh does it just like
skip certain songs
no no this is sorted by stars anyway so
what about if I do like half scroll
space that doesn't make the song uh
slower right gladiators
why is that my my theme song
what
okay we'll get there I have no idea what
you're talking about though
why is my theme song oh
oh
trombones
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
um
trombone take me to the sky take me to
the sky
I'm so happy I finally learned an
instrument
[Music]
in the sky
this is beautiful
I love the melody
[Music]
oh it's not Albert
who's one apply so high oh yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
wow almost 1 million baby eh only B for
over one million points you for real
rigged
I mean I could do better but I was
really trying to read the lyrics and the
lyrics and the melody was really busy
wow wow wow wow
so it is difficult yeah why is this like
on the same level I don't get it
marching kill box was that Martin's
attack in the remaster of a track from
an old holy wow album
title Choose Your Own Adventure
I did not understand
anything this is from 2008.
okay okay okay
ah
there's a song this is the famous One
have I heard this before
we're in fans
[Music]
no lyrics
okay okay
[Music]
up here
[Applause]
[Music]
what was bad
[Applause]
[Music]
he always
Chucky
[Music]
[Applause]
laughs
oh my God
absolutely destroyed it holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I
was like damn it doesn't stop going and
going and going
oh I feel like that was a really like
I don't know it got us into the mood
right
whoa whoa whoa you guys some of you guys
say a Blue Danube uh is my theme song
and I feel I understand because I am
from Austria and the new be goes through
Austria so if anything it should be this
one you guys are
confused did you not know about the
Danube have you guys heard of it before
and this is Austrian Waltz baby
which I I totally know how to
and you guys don't think ladies what the
[\h__\h]
anyway I totally know how to do a waltz
totally hundred percent
also this is uh by never Stroud's man
you'll hung Strauss
Johan
yeah I hope them gets good
[Music]
foreign
da da
a
[Music]
yeah
I feel like I'm having a fever dream
foreign
[Music]
but at the same time this was home
let's have a problem oh
you [\h__\h] this game you are a [\h__\h] no I'm
redoing that I don't deserve such
treatment like what the [\h__\h] I was doing
so well like I was feeling it they don't
account for the soul that I was having
oh right
as an Austrian I cannot let this stand
every Austrian that listens to this will
understand that this is a fellow
Austrian playing
[Music]
my eyes I feel like I'm my eyes turned
around and I'm seeing through the back
of my eyes this is how you guys feel
when you play Rhythm games
[Music]
no no no no no no
no oh my God I feel like I'm doing twice
my eyes hurt so much
I feel like my eyes are gonna throw up
[Music]
everyone they're gonna pop out and
explode any second now oh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
oh
that was a bit better than before wow
longest combo too what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
what
what the [\h__\h] man what what I get it why
why why why
yeah
no also why does it hurt so much to play
these games are you present correctly it
increasing oh [\h__\h]
am I too late or too early
maybe I was too late
[Music]
they hate austrians this is
discrimination what the axle
if my mom sees this she's gonna like
she's gonna write these developers a
very strongly worded letter
and she's gonna be like my child
is the best Bluetooth player on the
whole wide world whatever like if you if
you don't give her an SSS
at the least
then this [\h__\h] is [\h__\h] rigged
okay I'm not I'm not I'm not perfect but
that's just because this game is making
me go crazy the more I play it my eyes
hurt I'm gonna lose my eyesight
[Music]
ale
ciate that but I got even better oh my
God
I tried so hard I tried so hard but hard
but what
it does not send me sick
it doesn't understand
retarget no it does not understand the
sophisticated soul that I have it just
cannot keep up with it
foreign
I want this
song to be removed from the game because
I feel insulted
ah anyway okay next one was this one of
the first modern folk songs in the
Hebrew
language sorry I don't know how to
pronounce that oh
okay I'm gonna I don't know if it makes
better but I'm gonna make it even slower
I didn't really see a difference
Hebrew ish
Hebrew
Hebrew okay there you go
oh
[Music]
no no no no no no
no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
[Music]
no
oh my God
[Music]
just smash the buttons just smash the
buttons
down with a heavy metal remix
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
oh my God my eyes hurt
foreign
[Laughter]
taking retry I don't want to retry
please save me
oh it's just um the famous
the one and only
the very very well-known one that we all
know
trombone
laughs
oh say can you sing
[Music]
twilight's last gleaming who's been blue
yes we want
[Music]
oh my God the explosions
of that
I'm in
[Laughter]
[Applause]
my burger
oh
[Music]
that was wait it wasn't so bad look at
the beer beef a burger I guess so I mean
we all love Burgers right Burger is good
I'm gonna cook a burger tomorrow but
today I'm still eating leftover from my
Autumn stew did you see on Twitter like
I'm like cooking so much I'm like
totally wife wife material I would say
did you see
yeah like my food actually looks so good
and it's really good like it tastes good
it looks good I mean normally before I
like uploaded my cooking photos on
Twitter I would just throw things
together like whatever but for you guys
I'm trying to make it look good as well
like aesthetically pleasing and I think
every time I post a picture of my food
on Twitter you guys are like no not at
this time I'm so hungry kiwawa why you
do this to me planning is a skill too
yeah I mean but honestly you guys are
um
praising me for my plating but I'm
really just trying to recreate what's on
the example picture of the recipe yeah
but I have to say food that I have been
making has been very very very good what
is this Skip to My Lou
possibly the ride from a crow folk song
This Dance was popular during Abraham
Lincoln's youth in southern Indiana
oh Abraham Lincoln
have I heard this before
[Music]
whoa what what what what what what what
what
wait a [\h__\h] second now
[Music]
what is that oh my God banjo trombone
and banjo collab OTP I ship it
[Music]
I'm I'm not I don't know what it is
but she's cute oh is that a high-waisted
skirt and those puppies sleep looking
hella cute girl oh
yeah
I don't want to go home with the
trombone player tonight on a girl with a
Bento player
I don't think I'm the only one
[Music]
thank you for ending this soon yeah
that's [\h__\h] I know that was [\h__\h]
wow I'm I'm honestly surprised
[Laughter]
yeah well I mean
the horn Lord you know
he does not deserve the banjo lady okay
went long-tailing but is that the
what is this an original electronic
piece written by 2020
by the legendary maximalist Max Tundra
that sounds like a big joke to me the
meme name the maximalist max Tundra
[Music]
what
oh the devil sorry for roasting girl
oh let's see what you got I got some
sick beats yeah
egg
sandwich
funky bumpy junky music what the [\h__\h]
was that
[Applause]
oh
I like that
I got me going like
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
nasty he
you're nasty
or ranking is going up again it's
looking sunny
that's actually a decent song I'll give
you that
much
can you read this it's from The
Nutcracker
oh Pummel and those nuts
what scientists don't know how the
trombone makes is that how could you not
know
come on
[Music]
oh
I can imagine her dancing to this
[Music]
does not do this song any favors
gonna be honest
there's some songs that are like
screaming play me play me
[Music]
but this is not one of them
but I guess I just picked whatever was
in the copyright free uh audio library
oh [\h__\h] I didn't get this collab
approved
gonna be scolded
[Music]
so cute
[Applause]
[Music]
did I give good support for Poma
how is it how's it looking oh we're
looking decent okay okay okay
she dances so gracefully like a fairy
yeah
ah the cutest fairy ever
is it anyone's birthday today foreign
anyone anyone
thank you
really
mine was yesterday okay then it's yours
today too
pretends there was one oh
[Music]
my okay for everyone okay okay okay for
everyone everyone here who has a
birthday in the year 2022
I think there might be a couple of you
guys
this is
from my heart
to your heart with much love oh my God
I knew it would be a couple of you only
a couple of you
happy birthday to you all happy birthday
to you happy birth to you and you and
you happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birth in your pants too happy
birth to you oh yeah happy birthday
wait the song actually is more than that
don't recall this
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
how many times can I possibly miss these
notes let's hear it girl happy birth to
you happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday in your pants too and those
nuts two yeah happy birth to you happy
birth in your glue don't eat too much
to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
[Music]
happy birthday
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
I think that was the most beautiful
Happy Birthday song that anyone has ever
ever conceived and and yes
as it should be
[Laughter]
it's one of me
let's go
you know what this means it means a
small
hey small what is this about huh
what is this about chat
hey small what a small what
a small wood
Mozart
wrote this
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
um a small small little bird my bestie
wrote this down I co-wrote this
[Music]
oh trap music
[Applause]
[Music]
what the actual [\h__\h] man you you just
throw trolling us
what is that what the [\h__\h] is that
Melody what what Mozart this is this you
should have been fired you are you
should be thankful that you didn't have
an employer
if I came out with a song like this I
would have been fired
from Whole Life yeah yeah because they
would be like oh my God she's having a
[\h__\h] stroke constantly that's her
life State
and yet I'm Austrian and your bestie so
I have to like pretend that this is okay
but is that okay it's only a little bit
okay here because we're putting some
trap music behind it
oh my God
[Music]
almost a million
I gotta see for
let's see for
a c for a seal failure oh wait it's not
only called a little a small it's called
a little
night music but why did they write
the S with what's that I'm pretty sure
that is not originally live with that
because that's a typo
if we're taking
it all right that's kind of cool
what's next
old gray mare written by the seven time
mayor of Baltimore Maryland some believe
this song is about the horse lady
snuffle
why
when did he write a song about his Force
um
care to explain
loving your
horse a bit huh
oh my God it's cute though
it's a children's song
[Music]
Oh my God it's so cute
what is it with the popping popping up
horses
they're so cute
play this game before I think she did
right
she must have loved this this is for her
music and horses
[Music]
[Applause]
mama mama
[Music]
oh I was gonna like go and ad-lib now
what the hell
[Music]
what do you mean what is Circle I I I
rescued circles properly okay it's on
stream after you guys
with me for at least a year into saving
circles I did it and what did we get
from it nothing
we wasted our time
but circles is Happy okay
so this is the the theme song is it
is this the theme song
oh
monkeys
[Music]
Donkey Kong best friend is a baboon yeah
monkeys monkeys monkeys monkeys oh
shaking
I want to wear like a skirt with like
you know like all kinds of like little
shaking things on it and then
[Applause]
shake my hips to this
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
what was that oh
those are the rules of the funny faces
oh
[Music]
bye
what
bubbles that was so Random
in the afternoon
I love them in the afternoon
lies lies I didn't see any punks I only
saw baboons we love them in the
afternoon yeah only only in the
afternoon
not
an evening but maybe maybe you can start
loving them in the noon as long as you
don't go over afternoon
why is this not my theme song why are
you guys don't say this is my theme song
It's a bird song a skating bird song I I
know how to skate
why are you asking about my shoulder my
shoulder is always doing bad but thank
you for asking
so random but thank you
that's amazed oh yeah I guess like Skye
is kind of her thing
oh
no
too fast
[Music]
I see something in the corner of my eye
thank you
[Music]
I think that this is easier if you
already know the song
I don't really know this one
but then you can anticipate where to go
next like low-key
[Music]
my arm hurts oh my God this is a workout
for my arm I'm gonna get bumped get
bumped
and then I'll finally be able to lift my
own shopping bags
[Music]
so stop calling me grandma
oh my God I'm so bad
this is because you guys praised me too
much in the beginning of the Stream
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm losing my arm
[Music]
foreign
balls overdose
[Music]
the trombone
is
killing my bone
my arm bone
I need a fruit candy
see
I'll take it
ah
[Music]
I like the description
apparently they really want to discuss
on
[Music]
understandable I I will let everyone
else play this cardboard from now on
this is not for me
maybe something like calmer hey this one
seems to be calmer
originally written by the tech musicians
who have the world in popularity around
World War II
Beer Barrel polka
I think I hope this will be
calmer uh
have hair in my
mouth
[Music]
please be nice to me be gentle oh
god
wow it doesn't get easier does it when
it's like
but difficulty
wait why is there like uh that that
pattern in the background
I thought that was like kind of like
um a Bayern thing
[Music]
can I do that is that forgiven if I just
go with a long one over the small ones
like that
[Music]
[\h__\h] I can't read the comments is it
what about my other question yeah isn't
it wait the beer and the pretzels
[Music]
I thought it was supposed to be
something I don't know check
[Music]
oh my God
I'm dressed for the occasion what about
you guys where's the lederhosen
oh
I want to see you kill champions in your
most beautiful little ocean
I have the perfect outfit yeah so
appropriate hey what the [\h__\h] we almost
said B for beer now it's just C4
so close yeah
God damn it
what is this
foreign
on New Years with lyrics from a Scottish
poem and music based on traditional
Scots folk Melody
oh that sounds exciting
I'm all in for that let's go
not related to friends when they're just
friends oh
[Music]
what is this
I know this
wait is this being sampled in like
modern songs
[Music]
what do I notice from
oh is there like a famous song that
samples this like a famous pop song
[Music]
Tell Me Later
remember this question
[Music]
before
oh my God
we're partying real good now
[Music]
la la
la la la
[Music]
la
pretty well with this one
foreign
not fair Happy New Year
you made me question the date for a
moment
why
is this a happy New Year song I don't
think I I hear this in connection with
that most of the time
but maybe I did and I just never noticed
Japanese store
oh maybe that's what I heard it before
Japanese store closing music
maybe I did when I lived in Japan
wow this song
went to a lot of places didn't it in a
lot of countries
foreign
Electronics track are you ready to take
on these clutch baits
[Music]
what Gladiators soon
clutch beats all right
show me what you got
oh
um yeah yeah sick beats it's k f b oh my
God they are dropping their jaws because
they can't believe these sick [\h__\h]
beats baby
[Music]
and her trombone
this absolutely sucks
the worst thing I've ever heard in my
life
my ears
is that liking these
oh God I thought this game was about
good music
[Music]
he did
but hey I think my chest meter is not
doing so bad
[Music]
it's this I no no no no no no no no no
no no no make it please
[Music]
oh God
I don't want the bee for this [\h__\h]
I don't want it what a [\h__\h] terrible
song number one
number two what a [\h__\h] terrible beat
number three what a [\h__\h] terrible
speed why I have it all the way down
here why is the scroll speed still
so unbearable I just can't my eyes are
not trained for rainbow games I need a
six-pack on my eyes
gouda probably has one right
slower is not easier it should be back
up
what's better
slower is harder
what the [\h__\h] it didn't really feel slow
though
fast is better okay
I'll Beethoven we're back to you bunny
one of the most famous classical pieces
of all time Beethoven really killed this
one
all right
finally something that will heal my
heart and soul from the damage that has
been done to me up until now
some good [\h__\h] [\h__\h] music
was about time
[Music]
oh my God
what is a trombone make so many farting
sounds
[Music]
I'll buy you a beer
you like beer
I need to stop like uh even trying to
hit every finger every finger every
single thing
when they're so close together
[Music]
oh
that wasn't so bad
my new standards be like the basic [\h__\h]
that I am we all know that
how many please tell me how many
YouTubers
who have played this game
when they come to this point have asked
you if you are not entertained
I have a feeling
everyone
[Laughter]
[Music]
like two zero oh I'm surprised if it's
really not everyone and I'm honestly
surprised wow what is this this piece
performed Solo or sold as roles for
automated player pianos sounds much
better with the addition of a trombone
what
from Scott
Joplin
a fun piano stand I love the piano
I love piano what is this
huh
oh no oh
no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
no no no no no
no no perfect
[Music]
um I think this is a really entertaining
song
this is not false advertisement it gives
you literally
what it tells you it's Gonna Give You
entertainment baby
[Music]
do I lose my score when I do that
it sounds nice
[Music]
yay
what's hundred percent false what I said
what
I lose my combo when I do that whatever
whatever I'm happy with that
[Music]
and here comes the Gladiators
why
[Music]
named because of food chic's personal
interest in a Roman Empire this has
become one of the most widely known
pieces of circus music why why why
what
is
why why
will I agree after I hear this
well if it's my favorite song I better
do well at this
[Music]
what what
[Applause]
oh
my God
[Music]
theme song Let Me download
this theme song
I don't agree
why because everything's orange here
[Music]
you think I'm funny am I a joke to you
what
[Music]
I feel like you guys are making fun of
me by saying that this is my theme song
fan the use of circus yeah I guess
that's why I don't go to zoos because I
don't care about those animals being
held captive
it's always the same anyway
all the zoo animals are the same
I only care about the animals in my
apartment
chunky one Pants movie
so kfb you got some explained to do why
are you saying that this is my song
I feel absolutely no connection
whatsoever to this never to the
non-existent lyrics
nor to the title nor to the composer no
to the melody
you guys
are you saying I'm a clown
it's every bit wow
what
better than us
you guys think you're oh so so smart
so much smarter than we are huh
uh-huh I see kfb I thought you missed me
so much after those
two days without me
or three days before you missed me what
what about that
surprise
surprise you just missed to make fun of
me
you little shits
[Music]
so that is not my theme song I would
just like to tell you that very strongly
if anything it was one of the Mozart
songs
really really really disappointed in you
guys I was looking for
before yes and then I was gonna hear the
song and I would be like yeah
yeah this is toy is totally me and I
listen to it and I'm like [\h__\h]
for making me look forward to this
Mama Mia
Mommy I was born to be disappointed
[Music]
thank you
what the [\h__\h] is coming down here hello
guys
[Music]
okay I hear it now
this is my theme song
[Music]
I feel like the horses are tickling my
eyes
stop tickling my eyes
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God
this game
is the worst possible
way of enjoying music
oh yeah
that was I I forgot to use a key instead
of clicking yeah yeah that's why my arm
hurts so much now why am I doing this to
myself
it did say that it's better if you use a
key for some reason I was in the past
songs just using my finger clicking
everything
that that makes so much sense now when
did I start doing that
hmm
yeah let's Kiana play
what is this size and stress whatever is
it another American song oh yeah after
1987 Act of the US Congress this became
the official national March of the
United States of America you guys have a
national March what about a national
April
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
wait wait this is the national March so
that's different from the national
anthem huh
[Music]
oh my God
are you guys marching yet
[Music]
much more blocks to five for this case
bills let's go
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
oh beautiful
[Music]
oh my God
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
standing there beautiful
[Music]
I got so happy every time there's a
fireworks
[Music]
I don't know something about the timing
of the fireworks really didn't put me
there oh it's really enjoyable
hell yeah and also using the key again
to activate the dude was way better than
using the left click
I'm an American now
no thank you oh
we're almost there
to your game finisher kiwawa strikes
again our son attempt at composing a
meringue song
a fast-paced Latin American dance
originating in the Dominican Republic
fast-paced
Pace I don't know how much more I can
take of this
okay
fast-paced I'm far from finished now I
see that as finishing okay
I did all songs once that's good for me
[Music]
makes me wanna throw take off and throw
my shoes up in the air
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
mama
[Music]
party [\h__\h] party
thank you that really deserved that
[\h__\h] bad
[Music]
that was fun
that was terrifying as a trombone player
but fun as a dancer
last star Mexican Hat Dance I love hats
I love dance
I guess I love Mexico
ah performed by Mariachi beds is a
national dance of the national dance of
dance represents a courtship Bridge
[Music]
of course some ritual I think and
absolutely slaps my butt
oh
la la
by Sam vamos
[Music]
that came out of nowhere how is that
supposed to get that give me those
points
I'm ready I wasn't ready
[Music]
come on come on
getting points even though that was
perfect anyway
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
Mexico
people of Mexico
[Music]
Mexico
how far how much only
no no
no no no
[\h__\h] you
and any of that
I'm still getting sick okay
all right what can I do with all my
toots
what where is my unlocks
what do you mean
where would let me use my tools
Fletch
welcome to your collection play the main
game to earn choose
I have 10 000. well
holy crap you can afford 20 packs how
many would you like to buy
uh 10 for now
oh is this gotcha
oh
my God and then I have to choose the
right one or do I get all of them
who is that
Bill watch Rose a popular Jazz from
Bonus Oh I thought I was getting boom
booms
Tommy Dorsey another Trump bonus
huh
oh
Austrian oh
stop cute Gustav Mala your glasses are
freaking fencing my beautiful beautiful
Austrian friend
Tchaikovsky all right I think I got the
jackpots with good stuff
bye
look what a cute name oh my God
he's old
that was in one sitting no way
no way
oh what's this glissando is a slide from
One Tone to another the trombone is one
of the few instruments capable of
performing a true smooth glissando oh
yes it does
smoother than anything else
look at that mustache twirl oh
amazing he's walking and also he's
sharing the same glasses as good stuff
where they're like like roommates or
what
um
never heard of them
John Phillips
wait what is this about hot dogs again
he only ate hot dogs in private well
this is about arthas where do they get
this information
mouth a beautiful beautiful gesture
bonus was the first woman trombonist to
play in big bands
she could eat ten thousand
what
wait oh everyone gets the hot dog info
did they ask them
what
did you call him up and you were like
how many hotels can you eat or did you
actually test them what's going on
sack boot
did you know the early trombones from
the Renaissance and Baroque eras are
sometimes called suck boots
sure look it up now you know that's cute
cute look at those two dudes they're
like snakes
they're like brass snakes oh my God so
true
JJ Johnson what a name
are you again
Trump
bone without the trombone none of us
would be here so true so true
it is the glue that binders together the
voice that keeps us moving forwards
often called the baboon of instruments
hey what insult it is the Alpha and the
Omega
what about the delta
my love
listen listen guys
and remember this
prodigious Austrian composer of more
than 600 pieces one of the most
well-known classical composers of all
time he could eat up to 30 hot dogs in
one sitting and when he's standing he
can eat a hundred I know it I've seen
him I've seen him do it
look look at him look at that marvelous
face
that is
a face
that you couldn't could proudly call
your Oshi face
yeah
no one cares about the others it's only
Mozart that counts and matters brass oh
scientists have no idea where brass
comes from [\h__\h] no way what what do
you mean with that
foreign
[Music]
that is obviously a Yu-Gi-Oh reference
even I know that
blue eyes white baboon one of the most
powerful trumpona cards the blue eyes
white baboon is a representation of the
troubled Club as it relates to Bobby the
Egyptian deification of the Sacred old
world hamadriyas baboon
surprise
eggs and the reference why are you
surprised that one I mean that's the
least I could understand
anything beyond that I do not understand
indeed
[Music]
you beautiful beautiful
man with those curls that are absolutely
charming and flattering for your
beautiful face
look at that double chin gorgeous
Flawless only a real
composer can have a beautiful Flawless
double chin like that Johan Sebastian
Bach this is how you say his name Johann
Sebastian Bach is widely considered one
of the most influential composers uh
influencers yeah he's an Instagram
influencer like
way better than those others influences
out there posing in their [\h__\h]
leggings where I can see the whole shape
of
everything surrounding their butt
but anyway he imagine he invent hot dog
let's go let's go genius genius what the
uh
oh
I understand
now
he lives forever yes in my heart
trust them Immortal Guardian Spirit
tasked with preserving the order of the
bass and the trouble eclipse what does
that mean as a guardian Spirit unable to
eat hot dogs but imbuild of the power of
at least 10. oh so depending on how many
hot dogs they eat the stronger the card
is
now I finally understand what Bales was
going on about the whole time with
transom tresum
did you guys watch the snack Box review
on vale's Channel
[Applause]
oh I want a hot dog now oh my God
why why do you show this to me wait it's
14 21 when it was invented what no way
this hot dogs are so old
are these beef between sandwiches or
something else entirely no one knows for
sure but one thing is certain they're
every composer's favorite treat
how the [\h__\h] do you know that
wait where'd you get this [\h__\h] info
even if not Eden simply holding these
infused on power is this like their
favorite food of the developer
oh my
ah
I do have to say baboons might be the
ugliest animal on the planet
I'm looking at this and I just ask
myself
why baboon why
like why would you
the part like all of the nose
it looks like you know when
um the photos or like I don't know if
you can call it a photo of like muscles
of humans
sometimes look like this
with the like I don't know
the lines of the muscles
so this looks like someone opened up the
human body ripped out the muscles and
put it on top of the cute face of a
monkey
and then this happened
[Laughter]
it tells us that that baboons were the
ones that ripped open the humans
and just had the muscles stuck on their
face ever since and just did not know
and just left it like this
[Laughter]
what why is this so controversial in my
chat ah
wow slide
well well
Glenn Miller Hello nice to meet you
oh
Don Drummond he has like the name of a
drummer but he plays the trombone
what happened did he maybe have like a
little bit of a
of a misunderstanding with the drums
what yo his face is so Austrian and his
hair is so fluffy it's going like
upwards what's going on with that it's
like this side of his hair is like he's
aiming to be a crazy professor and then
he is mostly normal
so cute look at that dude
in his chin this Offspring composer with
an immense
body of work is considered one of the
best of the 19th century although he
wasn't widely appreciated until after
his death is always this [\h__\h] always the
same [\h__\h] man his one up one down
College style allowed him to more easily
consumer
[Applause]
but that doesn't only reflect in his
color it also reflects in his hair I
wonder if that's like on purpose like
this side is his crazy side yeah his
crazy bedroom side and this side is his
composer chill side
oh my God
but I hope for this game you guys are
learning that Austria is the country of
the classical music and I want you guys
to respect Austria for that thank you
on the right faces on the left exactly
oh
Mama wow look at that oh I wonder if
there's more austrians
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's get all the austrians
maybe there will be a card of me
[Music]
suck boot
hmm
hot dog hot dogs
the red leather sale books
Claude
Debussy
[Laughter]
I'm trying to wing and sound more
friends but it's like you can't escape
from it
oh shiny
um
[Music]
oh
can I put my face on there then
what kind of name is that what
hey I want to put my face on that and
then there will be a kiwama card oh oh
oh oh oh oh I think he's new Roswell Rod
legendary tromboner and composer who
worked in free and avant-garde jazz
yeah like guys
red eyes black baboon
oh we got the the other side of the
other Dragon baboon card
wow
well austrians more brass and more salsa
yeah
Beethoven we already had Beethoven did
we
wait maybe we didn't
I think we actually we didn't this
influential composer and pianist best
known for his Symphony Number Five lost
his hearing late in life possibly as a
side effect of eating 50 hot dogs and
one sitting and he probably pushed them
for his falling down his ears you
shouldn't be doing that oh my God
trombono cards in the card in the card
in the card in the card cards conception
collectible cards featuring famous from
Bonus legendary composed and all sorts
of incredible things everybody loves
these cards collect them all or stop the
tragic consequences okay I hear you
offer Missouri born trombones
oh the misery
everybody wants to be their anime he's
new I think sagboot Glenn Miller you
again
Glenn Miller looks like a talk show host
to me
uh-huh Tom Tommy Dorsey
looks a little bit new
laughs
your hunched house the second
you look at his
beard and all I see is arrows one
pointing that way and one point in that
way obviously telling himself to breathe
strongly
with confidence in all directions
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that fear I'm So Far
East house this Austin phone composer
wrote over 500 piece and is credited
with popularizing the Watts in 90th
Century Vienna sadly his baboon like
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
that is such a terrible
Faith to suffer fate that is probably
why I was making so much fun of you
because you're like a baboon no no
no they slather no he's one of my
country people I must protect and
praise him you have a beautiful beard
you do not look like a baboon at all
anyone who says so doesn't know what a
baboon is
Tchaikovsky I think that was a new one
too and a very famous one at that
Mozart wow look at my hands look at my
hand
oh Hungary
that one's new Elle gray I think is new
too
I've heard of owl Gray
what a book on plunger techniques what
Luigi must have co-written that book
[Music]
I'll be
ancient Egyptian deification of the
hamadriyas baboon whose name translates
to Bull of the baboons
or chief of the baboons was a deity of
the underworld and is very relevant to
this trombone game
oh my God I just saw something in this
statue I was gonna say it's a cute
statue but then I saw something and I
want to be wrong
I want to be wrong
um you guys are probably
having a hard time seeing it
no [\h__\h] way
I I cannot look at that any longer no no
no give me give me no no we're done one
two three four five six seven eight nine
ten eleven twelve thirteen freaking
cards I'm missing apparently I'm going
to mention
surely this is from both
I will not comment on that
what is this
oh no I'm so close I almost prayed the
baboon
thank you
I need four one more as Frank wow
I feel like I can do that
I feel like I can one more
wait so I had uh you can give me an easy
one
this one is as this one is as which one
is the other one that's on us
um which one could I oh I killed this
one literally
[Music]
I wanna ask
the [\h__\h] out of blue the new B but we
should probably go for something that's
closer to us
So like
um either this one or this one let's try
God Save the King
or Oh Canada I'll try both let's see
let's see
I need one more I need this now
foreclosure
[Music]
oh that's so slow
compared to what we played before
beautiful
I feel like I'm playing in slow motion
now
[Music]
I think this is an easy S rank
[\h__\h]
[Music]
is
come on come on I can't get much better
than this
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
it's literally on the dot
come on you just give me the benefit of
the doubt and give me a [\h__\h] s what
the [\h__\h]
no okay okay okay okay okay okay
this time this time
okay
[Music]
super Focus mode
that rainbow was beautiful holy [\h__\h]
rainbow in the champ
[Music]
I wanna go visit England again
[\h__\h] it's been a while since my last
trip to London wait did I do better or
worse
ah
[Music]
is it just not meant to be am I not
British enough for you what the actual
[\h__\h] all right let's fix this [\h__\h]
your [\h__\h] bastard
bloody hell
send him
Victorious
happy and Glory as long I should not be
looking at the lyrics
I'm holding it I'm
Hotel
[Music]
wow
still I'm gonna assume that just by
holding that a little bit longer
[Music]
I got some extra points
yes look at that
I know we were just meant to be after
all I have this blood in my body we're
connected yeah yeah yeah wherever you
want it or not
This Is Love
are you
yeah I might be in the previous life
so what's this about
done
free the bubble bubble
oh
where did that go
I wasn't done I should knock off
Oh I thought it was done
hello
and how much do I knock on it
gosh you're ugly
on my little heart
yes
[Music]
are for after all
I say get that from bone champ is it
fine wish to become the jump
yes
[Music]
oh that is good news I love me too
introduce myself I am
allow me to show you something
faced Divine eyes upon the tooth vessel
this what is it for how does this affect
my life personally
these are questions of for which I have
long since forgotten the answers my bad
the tooth vessels
feed its truths and clips oh my God
ah that's why it's called the tooth
vessel
German that's like
[Laughter]
[Music]
it is literally a vessel for totes
anyways
so with the tooth so that treble clef I
still don't know what that means may I
like it
ah
no I don't have enough
now
that's why something no
no
I thought this was giving me the
conclusion that I needed
no way eh
what with the gacha I couldn't I could
have used that here no [\h__\h] way
hey that was the same thing the same oh
but I got that from playing that one
song on S rank like three times
no I mean I mean
I mean I mean
it doesn't sound too difficult
we shall just toot a bit more than
expected
all right Canadians you listening still
still or did you get sick of me already
[Music]
I will learn this by heart
and then I'll be Canadian after that
[Music]
oh my God that was shitty
[\h__\h] this is way more difficult than the
other ones
oh I didn't lose my combo let's go
[Music]
Oh Canada please be nice to me
what the [\h__\h] did I do to you
what the [\h__\h] did I do yeah
am I not Canadian enough for you how do
I speak like a Canadian I really don't
know
what how did he collect a Canadian how
to do Canadian accent
why is it on a daughter Anna
ah a boat
I bought the boots the boots
speak like chronic I don't know how to
speak like crony
I'm like I don't know like her English
sounds just absolutely normal to me
her voice is you know very special but
her English sounds so like normal to me
it's beautiful sorry
a
said Z instead of Z and I do that
already
because in German we say that
okay
Oh Oh Canada I'm so sorry eh please
forgive me a so about the S rank please
be kind a
come on
okay
[Music]
I'm hoping that I get extra points for
singing
but I don't think so
[\h__\h]
[Music]
thing in the background I forgot when it
was cold
[Music]
I got over a million
what color is yeah
how was it better like I was looking at
the lyrics so I think like my my mouse
was not always on point
it felt worse but yay only 401 tooths
from that
I guess I mean no I want to play
something else if we keep on trying here
what else could we maybe where else do I
have an AM
ah nothing else
it's just downwards from there
um
well maybe something with a low BPM like
oh God no this has a low BPM but this is
still a difficult song wasn't that
yeah I don't need points but still I I
mean I don't need S rank but still
it would be nice to do good
[Music]
oh my God this is so much easier
like before I definitely
this is the mouse
[Music]
oh I'm doing so much better
what
holy [\h__\h]
this is because I'm Austrian
that part is difficult
[Music]
on point
holy [\h__\h] that looks like a million
times better than before Oh my
[Music]
oh my
um excuse [\h__\h] me why does this
happen everybody
this is not fair what the actual [\h__\h]
I take this as an s
because I deserve that but wow
and I could get like s or a rank for all
of these [\h__\h] songs I have the
confidence now what do I want to try
again maybe happy birthday
[Music]
happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you and you actually meant happy
birth yeah that was bad happy birth to
you happy birthday
happy birthday in your pants too yeah I
know that's weird but happy birth Happy
Birthday Happy Birthday Happy Birthday
Happy Birthday older celebrate celebrate
you're getting older every day yay
21 is cool 23 is cool 27 is school 29 is
bad now you're in your midlife crisis
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday
[Music]
I bet you'll need some new shoes because
those look real in [\h__\h] man
what
how did that one do so much worse than
the other song I just did I'm like what
the [\h__\h] you're killing my magic
[Music]
should we do
I get this one that's my favorite song
ever
[Music]
I present to you
oh the European anthem
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
Europe
is amazing okay
[Music]
oh my God my eyes hurt so much but I'm
doing so well
[Music]
fashion this is
I am
[Applause]
wow
incredible
you can just literally feel it in my
veins
wow when I donate blood
all that comes out of it is
hot dog juice apparently because all
musicians eat hot dogs how many
people can I get it
what no no
hi this time you say hello so much
faster
I mean I feel like I'm there
oh oh
easy the tooth vessel awakens
what will happen
[Music]
that's so aggressive so aggressive wait
what
[Music]
what is this the end so can I really say
I I ended this game hmm you played this
video game a lot and unlocked a thing
character polygons
oh there's more this is not the end oh
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
[\h__\h] you kind of moment
I hate you
um
take my money
I don't want it anymore
I don't know if I like or dislike this
game
but it's definitely the best experience
I've ever had with a rhythm game ever
before
[Music]
songs yeah that's I think for me
that is
just all it takes to finish this game in
in my books I don't know about your
books
well I feel like I played plenty hmm
oh I can sell my duplicate cards all but
well if only if the only thing I get is
the new character then I'm good I'm good
I'm good
um my throat really hurts from all the
singing but I'm gonna go ahead and read
some super chats
from singing and screaming man [\h__\h]
painful
that was fun it was fun yeah I don't
ever play Rhythm games I mean you know
if I if I was like a little bit better
at staying at them I I would like to
play rebel games on my channel but like
uh I don't know how people like gonna do
it honestly like my eyes
that is the most exhausting thing ever
for my eyes and also I would not be able
to talk while playing these games much
at least if I want to do well
and I I'm in my streams I want to be
able to talk a good amount of you guys
so yeah
go go it's so intense right for the eyes
like trying to keep up with those fast
moving things on the screen
and in some games it gets worse than
this so holy [\h__\h]
I don't know man
so I respect the six pack that Kura has
on her eyes dear Lord
um
I mean I guess like if you're really
good you know the songs by heart that
you're playing and you know the dude by
heart I guess like for other games other
ribbon games
oh my God my throat hurts so much why
why doesn't hurt so much
like actually yesterday when I was
trying to record something
my my after singing like one time I
noticed holy [\h__\h] my throat is not doing
well
even though I didn't stream or so
um
no no no no I'll read some super chats
yeah yeah
we got time and I already have food
because I'll just eat what I have left
over for the first day in a row
um
I thought it would be finished yesterday
but I still have leftover
yesterday I added rice to my
um Autumn stew which basically
gave me more to eat than it would have
been
I was really good with the rice
works really well so today I'm gonna add
yeah more rice again and then then I'm
finished with the Autumn still and then
tomorrow I'll make some burgers
um
the stew was so easy
so one pot recipes
it's so easy and it's pretty good I was
cooking it while play while watching Bae
play a little nightmares too
um
are we allowed to share the recipe
um I mean it's just a basic stew
or basically
first you
um
you uh what's what's the you know when
you appeal first you peel one carrot
then you peel two big oven potatoes
um
then
oh then you cut the chicken in some of
course you cut the the other vegetables
in some like pieces and then you cut the
chicken meat fillet in some pieces
okay then then you
um take a big pot and you put the
sunflower seeds in the pot and with no
extra oil or whatever nothing just the
sunflower seeds you
um kind of roast them until they start
popping and smelling good
um
[Music]
so yeah and then you you um take out the
sunflower seeds and put them on the side
because they'll just be like sprinkled
over the finished meal at the end and
next you'll um put like two two spoons
of oil into the pot and then you throw
the chicken in there and you grill the
chicken
um quite a bit okay and then you put uh
while you're doing that you put some of
the seasoning that was provided by
oh
shh
um
not sponsored so I'm not gonna say their
name
yeah put the seasoning and then once
you're like done with grilling the meat
a good amount you'll um take it out of
the pot again
and then and then I put some oil back in
oh wait there was also leak leak was
also one of the uh vegetable ingredients
so then you throw all of the cuts leak
and all of the cut on not onions no
onions surprisingly all of the cut other
vegetables inside the pot and you just
um lightly
um you know
not really like Grill it but you just
just put it in there and it fills up the
big pot quite a bit
um
so you do that for a while and then
and then oh yeah and then you
um pour I think it was like
400 milliliters I think of water hot
water into the pot then some good music
um that's like the the vegetable broth
yeah I think it was vegetable or was it
chicken it was probably vegetable broth
and another seasoning that came with the
recipe uh yes and then mix it you know
mix it mix it and the water will cool
down then the temperature for a little
moment but then yeah you let it simmer
and
um
yeah let it simmer let it simmer and
then you add the
cream fresh we call it cream fresh it's
not sour cream it's different from sour
cream it's some kind of creamy stuff you
put you put that in and turn it around
no first at first I think you put the
chicken back in and then the cream fresh
maybe I don't think it really matters
that much
heavy cream maybe it was a heavy cream I
don't know we call it cream fresh here
kind of weird
it's similar to sour cream but it's not
the same
yeah
um
it's not whipped cream even
not either
it's just some kind of cream whatever so
yeah and you pour that in uh after the
chicken after bringing the chicken back
in and then
oh yeah just salt and pepper try to
season it I added some extra
um garlic seasoning and oh one of the
seasonings that came with uh the order
uh was like a mix of
moose cut nuts with something else
Muscat
what is
um but I felt like it wasn't strong
nutmeg there we go those nuts mix
so I felt like that seasoning was kind
of weak and I wanted to add some more
seasoning and I I still had some uh
grinded nutmeg so I added some more
nutmeg and the garlic and so on yeah and
then just let it simmer for a while and
I think that was pretty much it that was
so simple
hmm
yeah just let it simmer and then and
then
you put it on the plate and then you top
it with some of the leftover cream fresh
that was the white stuff on top just for
the sake of looking good and then top it
with
um The Roasted and cut chopped
sunflower seeds
on top
you have a wonderful
from Autumn potato carrot chicken stew
to enjoy
if you want with some rice it was really
really really really good
hmm
[\h__\h] you said it was a simple recipe it
the fact that I was able to just say
everything from the top of my head from
remembering what I did
uh proves I think that was really simple
it's a one pot recipe it took like maybe
yeah 30 minutes maximum most of the
other recipes take like they say they
take like 45 to 50 minutes but normally
for me it always takes like a little bit
more than an hour because I'm like
really slow with preparing everything
and I wash my hands a million times in
between to make sure I know you guys
probably think that there's cat hair in
my food but I make sure
every step after every step I wash my
[\h__\h] hands I I over wash them yeah
because I need to make sure I don't want
cat hair in my in my food so like I I
don't even uh dry my hands after washing
them I just air dry them because I know
there will be cat hair on the [\h__\h]
um not blanket you know the thing it
doesn't add flavor no I don't want cat
hair in my food
the thing is you know my mom
she's like you know she she has cooked
so much in her life that when she cooks
she's just like
so oh
last time when she cooked something at
my place
I was like looking at her and I'm like
see her like using the the towel the
kitchen towel where I know there's cat
hairs and like I see her just never
never washing her hands in between the
steps
so I like have to tell her mommy no
offense but I know from experience that
just by touching literally anything or
even when you think you didn't touch
anything you will always have cat hairs
on your hands if you are in my apartment
even for five seconds
so please please please please please
please please please wash your hands
like at least like a bit more in between
um
and then preferably air dry them I have
to tell her because she she does not she
underestimates the amount of cat hairs
that will surely end up in the food
after all that
hahaha
yeah
yeah yeah but so so you must understand
that my food does not come with cat
hairs most of the time I try so hard
like it's really hard to see but I have
a good eye for them like even if you
first look at your hands and you think
oh there's this looks they look fine
they probably don't have Cutters on them
you look closer and you find like a tiny
tiny tiny tiny tiny one somewhere that
you only see from a very specific angle
and even after washing hands sometimes
they still stick to your hands so I have
I have um built up a certain technique
and skill to
sense the cat hairs and get rid of them
when I'm cooking
don't let me cook for
eign
[Music]
your food always looks really pretty
thank you
every time you know I try to make the
food look really nice just so that I can
take a nice picture for you guys
which always like ends up in making my
food a little bit colder than it should
be
but for the sake of a good Twitter
picture I have to do what I gotta do
yeah I'm quite proud honestly like I've
been cooking so much I'm so proud
um
thank you guys
okay let's go to my office
[Music]
here we go
oh
she is
now let me fix up the chat
I'll turn off that music by the way
it's too repetitive
no no no no
close again
I was playing in full screen by the way
I never do that normally
so how you doing chat how you doing how
you doing yo I got so much to talk about
but we have a long stream tomorrow so
hopefully tomorrow I'll remember
everything that
I had to tell you
um
doing good
to hear he
yeah my throat is sore but I'm I'm I'm
licking the throat candy right now
desperately this is my fourth one today
I think holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] I wonder if it's like the
the air
or if it's just
maybe my throat is forever [\h__\h]
Harvest Stella is that another like
Farming Simulator game
yes I did turn my heating on oh that's
probably not helping yeah
yeah I need to
um turn on my humidifiers again yeah
Actually I don't even like really
desperately need the heating to be on
I just don't I don't know last night I
felt like oh I would like me some coffee
warm air please
but I do like the currently quite
Pleasant so somewhat chill
late Autumn air outside it's really nice
it's really nice really nice
it is getting cold though yeah okay so
super chatos I have to read from doko I
think there's a member stream that I did
not read right the the Batman stream was
fun but what about slate aspired did I
read until the end of slay the spire
[Music]
I don't know
um yes yes no
did I
I'm reading that I'm trying to remember
them I feel like I probably looking at
those
um
no I did because I remember this one
from their Yoma Converse fun celebrities
beats around a wonderful kfp fan panel I
did read this one I think
no wait that was just the only one that
slipped in between those other super
chats that I was reading
hey what is that one doing here weren't
we
that's why the other ones don't look
familiar to me but just this one yeah
okay okay
I'll rate the slay the spice pictures
let me get out some audio stuff
audio stuck
stuck
[Music]
stuck in the audio stuck
um
what do we want to listen to I've got so
much
in my audio stock folder
[Music]
I have a good idea
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
because we were hearing a lot of classic
music so far
[Music]
you know
marvelous wow
[Music]
so fire
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
nothing tops a nice jamming session to
Mozart
it's not just the best thing ever
divide
Divine we've only wanted more than you
he'd be so famous one day he'd be
providing me this BTM for the legendary
attack with Super Chat remix
he would cry from happiness
he would be so honored
he would have written a single for me an
original singer
yeah it feels so classy now me too you
can hear the hot dogs oh yeah he's
consuming them he's breathing them
[Music]
oh I'm head banging I'm headbanding
so headbang blue not workable but hat
bangable
[Music]
oh my hair's gonna get messy I am dizzy
jackets
that looks like a rainbow to me thank
you
hi lady Chihuahua even though streaming
long hours is nothing new for you
streaming over seven hours
and Luigi's Mansion streams alongside
sports fans compels me just
set you oh yeah maybe help pay for the
next massage oh thank you thank you for
all the Fantastic kiwawa content I felt
bad about your vision not working out
that broke my eye ceiling because we all
know you're an amazing singer dancer
Entertainer oh don't worry about it
I also think
it's a bit unfortunate
um
let me turn this down a little bit
I really did think
that it would be a good idea
[Music]
yeah but
uh
yeah as far as I know it's too late now
for 2020 free I just did not have the
means to contact the right people
apparently
um well who knows maybe if I'm still
around at that point then we can try out
for 2024.
but I just feel like it would have been
something that I really needed like now
like not now but like I feel like bye
that time next year it would have been
really helpful
the bus oh man well well well
can't have everything it's all right
[Music]
you just need a chance to show the world
I will keep not I keep hoping you get
that chance I'll have to watch the
stream again I've tried twice this year
to get a job with fewer hours to watch
more live
and how many hours you have now
I'll keep trying please dedicate my kids
chunkers and smoothie thinking of fauna
I keep praying to the merch Gods to ship
my Kiana birthday marriage oh
is it like being shipped Maybe nowish
soonish
yeah because it's like because like uh
birthday merge like usually takes like
half a year right so maybe in December
Maybe
[Music]
that sounds pretty close
December January
well time passes by so fast guys it will
be in an instant
job
[Music]
well depending on where you live
obviously it might take a little bit
longer
I need my toes to get a blanket oh yeah
arm as the temperature drops yeah me too
me too I want the oven mitt and the
blanket
[Music]
[Laughter]
stop
[Music]
it
damn I have to say this is like
foreign
[Music]
for this
I can never reach the heights of Mozart
never
and when I think about that
[Music]
it does make me wonder
is it even worth it
I I know I will never reach that level
I can't ever become like Mozart
[Music]
is why life even worth living then
I mean
I wish I was more tired
[\h__\h]
anyway thank you so much.com for the
beautiful rainbow and the sweet messages
Duncan kitchen I hope you find a job
that you know helps you want more
Chihuahua but first and foremost it
should be a job that you enjoy and I I
assume that jobs in general are hard to
get out there at any point of time so
don't waste or throw away an opportunity
that would have been great just because
you wanted Less hours oh my God I'm so
selfless
foreign
of course I want you to ideally
just watch me 24 7.
but yeah I need to
I need to State it clearly don't throw
away good opportunities yeah
[Music]
thank you so much for your support
I know you're there I know you out there
working hard to support Chihuahua and
yourself
and all the babies that you sit because
you're the babysitter
thank you so much
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
I feel so sophisticated
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
just enjoying it
just trying to enjoy it
did you imagine the season really
they'll imagine like a classic music
concert like this and then somebody just
had had banging
that would be me
laughs
absolutely [\h__\h] losing it
[Music]
like that like that
go
what's happening we're just appreciating
classic music
[Music]
extra unhinged
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
okay if I listen to this the whole time
I will not get very far with my super
chance
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
what's wrong about enjoying classic
music like that because like honestly if
you just
sit there so stiff and tight
[Music]
just staring at the musicians
are you really appreciating the music
and enjoying it and feeling it as much
as you
pretend you are hmm
[Music]
I don't know about that
oh
wow
[Music]
I can't
I can't play this any longer
all right guys
but wait
[Music]
this brings me joy
I wonder if Kira can write me a classic
song a classical original
this is a genre you can do
[Music]
this is not even Mozart I think but
it gives me the same happiness
[Music]
you know when something makes you so
happy that
it makes you unhappy
me right now
I'm sad
good to know yes
as a mood
[Music]
I'm so nice
yeah the clarinet is so pretty can we
have a clarinet to Champ instead of
trombone champ
why this make you sad it's so good
exactly that's the problem
Atelier oh I see what you mean yeah
it does give off some Atelier Vibes so
yeah like just I don't know Village
Vibes and like happy happy Pokemon
Village drops I don't know
um jpg Farm Village yeah
ah
I had um [\h__\h]
makes me so happy oh man speaking of RPG
Village maybe this will be
yeah
maybe with this I can actually read
super chats
U
perfect night
for the red super chattel and the pink
one too let me put this one very random
message
huh
[Music]
love you
me my
own one and
only
oh
what only oh oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah yeah there was a encoded message
with like uppercase letters
contained a message
so do I even have to read the the
fake message
let me put this one very random message
here I want you to know how much you
mean to us there's only wow and nothing
else that can make a chimpkin so damn
happy every day okay this actually still
works and makes sense
okay now it's getting already difficult
for me to leave you this hidden message
because in other words it's not hidden
you tell me
because it really terrible at this
you're bad at keeping secrets aren't you
that's like immediately without reading
to that part like in the first sentence
I already noticed something was going on
here
yes
no thank you
thank you you're so sweet thank you soon
but next time let's try a little bit
harder to keep the secret okay
so that it will stay between us
our little secret
he isn't that exciting
[Music]
um
thank you
so much
ex-legendary hero dangashun
[Music]
wow interesting some mods for slightest
fire
check out 47 out thank you
Monster Hunter
again thank you Daddy look daddy
Hearts back to you all the hearts back
to you
thank you
um
I don't think you could have asked for a
better first run that was incredible one
turn and the run back on the boss and
ended you first ever run you are too
powerful and physically cannot be
stopped saber at kiwawa thank you it's
so sweet but like you guys did all the
work you guys chose all the cards and
taught me how to play with the character
I cannot really even take credit for
that
sometimes I tried doing my own moves but
as much as I would like to be praised I
don't think I deserve it
[Music]
um maybe next time
yeah but I definitely needed like one
session where you guys babysit me
because uh I just had to learn the
character every character has like
really different mechanics and ways of
fighting so
um different cards and all that and so I
needed that yeah I did learn from it I
did I did
yeah
apparently my steam deck arrived at my
friend's place I just have to pick it up
[Music]
um
I bought I ended up buying the middle
option
I don't know if I told you yet
but yeah I have to pick it up I'm just
like too lazy
[Music]
is
you know
yes team deck
yeah oh wait same
[Music]
place
fire works really well in the deck
that's literally why I bought it
that was my inspiration
yeah I'm gonna take it to all my
vacations from now on wait
no wait why would I do that
for a moment I was like oh I wonder if I
take this bean bag to like Japan if I
connect it to my laptop if I could
stream what I'm playing on this theme
deck this is theme deck I could just
play the game on Steam on the laptop so
whatever I was thinking doesn't make
sense but I do wonder if you could
um capture a steam deck just like you
can capture a switch probably yes right
[Music]
yeah but then at least that's true it
would mean that I don't need a gamer
laptop if I plan on streaming some Steam
games
uh if I can
um stream it like that then if I can
capture it like that then I just need to
steam deck so if I want to save on like
PC power
that would be a solution
[Music]
but I don't know it's not really
necessary
I think I guess
yeah good reasons to do that
hmm
[Music]
I don't know
maybe a bit unnecessary
[Music]
um
USBC to HDMI
hmm
[Music]
why didn't you think the steam deck
would be so successful actually I guess
when I first saw it I also
didn't quite see the
necessity for it
I did not plan on buying it when I first
heard about it
I I guess I was just like way well the
steam games I just play on my PC like I
don't need a a console to play it like
what
but then recently I've been playing
games and I'm like oh I wish I could
also just play this in my bed I guess or
when I travel yeah
some games like I have so many Steam
games at this point
thanks to streaming
my steam Library
compared to oh damn compared to day one
before starting streaming I think I had
like
free
free games in my steam Library
and now I can't even count them
damn
and that's just my steam Library
because obviously I have a lot of like
switch and Playstation games and so on
too
yeah damn
hi shinsuke
um
it grows fast yeah because there's also
so many games that just play for one
stream
like just one-off quickie games
almost feels like a waste to buy them
but thank God I'm a streamer and I make
um money from it so
yeah hopefully
hopefully it makes sense to buy so many
games
I just really wanted to get my money
back from playing rust because that was
so expensive
[Music]
it's a business expense it really is but
my tax person will not let me write it
off although it really is like I would
not be buying
95 of these games if it wasn't for my
work
literally
[Music]
yeah well
it is what it is
[Music]
equipment yes but I basically my tax
person said this too that I have this
problem that I basically have little to
none write-offs
which is very unfortunate
because I have to pay so much to my
country
I have little to none write-ups because
like my my technical things like you
know my microphone my PC those are all
pretty much one-time purchases
and then a few ongoing ones like a part
of my apartment I'm writing off
uh internet
uh yeah
that's like you know most of it and then
in the beginning when I moved I had some
things like cables that I could write
off that I bought
stuff like that but yeah it's really way
less than someone some other like
independent people Freelancers and so on
right off
yeah like similar supposedly similar
people to me but not really similar
[Music]
um
nothing will beat Kelly paying tax to
both Japan and the U.S well yeah but
also I think
um
uh Austria
has higher
taxes compared to for example Japan or
America so I do pay more than those
girls do
when I told
Japanese colleagues how much I pay
to the country they were like holy [\h__\h]
damn
and then and then I pay so much for
um
for my health insurance and I don't even
like really make use of it which makes
me so mad too just thinking about it but
I'm forced to have that
ideally I would like to have no health
insurance and just go to private doctors
whenever because I don't go that often
now
and even when I do with the health
insurance I still choose to go to
private doctors for a certain
um
like things like I go to a private uh
gynecologist
is that what you call the theme the like
women's doctors
and I went to a private uh dentist
um
yeah yeah
for the sake of
being treated like a better human
because if you don't go to a private
doctor you are not worth paying
attention to
um
[Music]
and you do want to have health insurance
I don't wanna
ha
in the U.S even the private doctors
don't like us oh man
that's a nice solo visits I can tell
it's all from unreasonably unreasonably
expensive
and uh in the past couple of years I
just barely had use for going to the
doctor and when I went standard was
useless so far
anyway
my doctor called me a good boy oh
[Music]
sweet cute
my whole life in Austria without private
doctors and have had absolutely no
problem so I do not understand what you
are talking about
hmm
well I think our
situations and bodies are very different
and we just have different problems
[Music]
I know I've had good experiences too
like my my private dentist and my
private
gynecologist they're very nice and they
do their job very well
yeah
so no problem with them
and I remember in the city I grew up in
I had a really really really nice
um
like we call them house doctors because
those are the doctors the general
doctors that you go to that bring you to
the other doctors that you need to go to
or they just handle all the basic things
like if you have a cold you go there and
they you know prescribe you whatever
the medicine you need
that guy was very nice it was a really
old
old guy very sweet
my mom loves him too even until this day
um a general practitioner yeah yeah
exactly
[Music]
across the austrianism that's because
less than 100 euro per month yo me too
most likely
less than 50 euro per month and yes I
and yet I pay thousands of Euros for
them
[Music]
I don't want to say numbers and [\h__\h] but
let's just say a thousands
thousands
I want to
this is why I want to break my leg or so
because Santa
I want to break my whole [\h__\h] body to
make it worth it
um
[Music]
what
parachuting off collab it doesn't have
to be an off collab I'll just go alone
I'll just parachute myself off a
mountain
[Music]
my mind it seems dumb I feel like it
makes perfect sense
[Music]
without the parachute yeah probably
to make sure that my body is broken
after that it's already broken like
makes no difference
has done parachuting before are you
[\h__\h] kidding me really
like in Japan
[Music]
how how long ago is this a recent thing
for a show
oh my God
oh
[Music]
yo I need to launch that
oh
damn is she a frill Seeker oh my God oh
my God oh my God frill Seekers I I I I
watched this video about the I I really
don't know why I'm wasting my time with
these
useless YouTube videos but there was
this video about uh someone
investigating maybe you guys saw it
about where that clip came from from the
Malcolm in the Middle opening
um the the clip from the skier who's on
fire and someone went on a search where
this club came from and then it was
thought to be from frill Seekers and
then surprise it wasn't even real
Secrets but anyway like so unnecessary
I'm like why am I wanting this I think I
only watched it because of the thumbnail
that was showing it was kind of Click
fade because it the the thumbnail was
showing dewy
and it kind of looked like a memorial
picture
as if Dewey is no more
and and next to that was the picture of
the burning skier so my brain was
thinking oh my god did dewy
like Lewis's Life by skiing on fire a
what
I mean the title wasn't really implying
that but
that's when I saw with the thumbnail and
I'm sure I'm not the only one
so
that's why I watched the video
[Music]
we burst into flame
skinks this is top-notch Click painting
top nuts hahaha
like they could have used like a I don't
know a different picture then it doesn't
even have to be doing because this video
was not about Dewey at all it was just
about the opening scene of Malcolm in
the Middle it was not doing specifically
so it was so weird
so weird
[Music]
so baited cruise I have not read a super
chat in like 30 minutes I think Slavic
fellow dungeon decided by dangerous
44 thank you
happy hour thank you for the pinky it is
fun watching and learn this game getting
better every time also if you want to
play Magic you can play Magic Arena
is that on Steam
I just I don't know I
I it's probably because that's how I
started but I want to play it with real
cards in my real hands you know but I
don't have anyone to play with so I
guess I'm guessing magic Arena would be
online with people
and then at least I have someone to play
with you know what
will request perms Magic
wait it's not
[Music]
it's not MTG Arena
no magic the Gathering what's it what's
it called on Steam is it not on Steam
it's on Epic Games Magic
Marina it doesn't show up that's weird
huh
am I looking what
I get like magic spell slingers
Iron Gate Arena
Toho sky Arena Matsuri climax
Aquarius magic together right
[Music]
ah they're on their own launcher oh
wait what did you say which uh
uh publisher
epic epic games
don't I
can't we play every epic let me see let
me see let me see
I don't feel like getting back into the
Nostalgia of magic would be a lot of fun
[Music]
and this time I'll actually like
hopefully learn how to be good at it
that would be amazing
epic games Epic Games camps
epic games
uh
big games
[Music]
I think I need to get perms separately
all right all right all right all right
who here has played Magic the Gathering
before
huh Wizards of the Coast oh ah okay
[Music]
meet me
only tiny bit oh my God
well then you guys can definitely help
me build a really sick deck
oh oh let's go play today oh online or
in person
oh my God that reminds me like damn
as a child like going to
[Music]
like there was this this place where
there were a lot of games
like a game house for children
sometimes I would go there and there
were some some people playing cards
like magic and Pokemon and Yu-Gi-Oh oh
man I never partake partook in that
though unfortunately I always only
played magic with my family
[Music]
hmm
would you play Hearthstone oh I've
played it before
not on stream though I think actually I
did play it privately before
surprisingly because it's free
huh
can you do oh
[Music]
my mom was listening to the stream I
don't know if she's listening now which
I just saw her message to me
oh I don't care about Yu-Gi-Oh don't
worry I'm not even Desiring to play that
I'm not a Yu-Gi-Oh kind of person
I'm so sorry but Yu-Gi-Oh always was
kind of cringe to me I'm so
I was a magic kind of person you know
they call me weeb but when people were
playing Yu-Gi-Oh I was playing Magic the
Gathering so can you really call me a
weeaboo huh
huh
she was eating Magic the Gathering over
Yu-Gi-Oh I think tells you everything
you need to know
uh-huh uh-huh you think so you think you
I actually took a test the other day I
was sent a test I was told to take it
um and I was going to Tweet about it but
I wasn't sure if I should
I took a test
yes
and it said that I'm a normie
[Laughter]
it was not a buzzfeed this
[Music]
but it told me I was a normie
it had like I don't know 40 50 questions
and I am a certified perfect Normie
I did not cheat no no no I feel like a
lot of my questions were very
um like hinting towards
not much of a normie
result
[Music]
see even then you guys don't believe me
[\h__\h] it
I'm gonna Read Super chats and ignore
you guys
question
Jester Cosmic Duncan
rpwnkt Danke Schoen James mcfeen thank
you for the red super chat great job
attention that was a beastly kill on the
geometry boss yeah
it even though it was like
um
thanks to you guys building up
everything for me
that was just too epic not even letting
the boss attack
holy [\h__\h] that's like next level
Pro Gamer skills
I felt so overpowered felt good felt so
good thank you very much James for
helping mwah
rank you I read this one before so thank
you again thank you for the pinky
another clear in STS and another game
beat yesterday you're on the wrong
pencil speaking of Pokemon travel
tomorrow oh which one was that though
maybe it's better to be surprised next
week can't wait to see what you can pull
off of the thing the company sent thank
you so for Pokemon I don't know the
trailers I've been seeing recently
they're not really like special
groundbreaking like there's still no
info about at least no official info
about
um the starter evolution so I'm like
what the [\h__\h] do they I guess they
always do this I've never paid so much
attention previously
[Music]
do they always just wait until
less than a week
before they show what the starters look
like in the evolutions
foreign
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] what are they waiting for
they've been holding back lately
style Evolutions always get revealed
latest yeah but apparently not this late
hmm
this is unusual
damn
maybe they're not ready maybe they're
not already
maybe they're in such a Time clutch
you mean
[Music]
maybe there is such a Time clutch that
I mean honestly Pokemon throws out so
many games so fast
they're obviously in a Time clutch all
the time as a constant state so maybe
it's so bad that they still have not
finished all evolutions
but I'm just saying the truth
it's the truth
time crunch not clutch oopsie
crunch crunch crunch
Pokemon
um
[Music]
oh I can say nothing about that
um but I just due to
how my next week is looking
even if I were allowed to play Pokemon
it doesn't look like I have the time to
play Pokemon next week
which is probably fine because
I assume that if we are allowed to play
it that everyone will be
playing it at the same time so maybe
it's good if I started like a couple
days later
Maybe
a couple days later than everyone else
like
maybe like a week or two later
a week a week
one and a half weeks at the most
[Music]
that's because
um the game released as well on the 17th
and uh that's exactly when I have the
whole talk
crunch
[Music]
two episodes
on one weekend
oh it's like more the 18th well then
yeah see that weekend I can't I can't
squeeze it in unfortunately I want to
um
I mean I could try to squeeze it like
into Saturday
but
who knows if I can even play
and then I I kind of want to prepare
for whole talk properly
yeah I think I will need the time
[Music]
mommy said she doesn't know in German
learning it
or she can watch my German lessons on my
channel
anyway
uh Martin ain't thank you so much for
the pinky I'll talk a little bit more
about the thing that the company sent uh
tomorrow
[Music]
taking a lot of time off of work and
I've been able to watch most of every
stream for the past week wow
and though I'm not getting as much done
around the house as I planned same same
same same
I'm surprised I was able to vacuum clean
my apartment today
so happy I get to spend time with you
again thank you good afternoon are you
here now go
girl there you are hi I'm glad you have
more time for me
thank you for being here
did you take time off just for me or was
there different reasons
[Music]
um
the one is for me was it for me
was it slowly for me
say yes
what you're like literally took up time
of work for me oh my God
[Music]
I want a small chill I'm gonna give you
like a really wet Grandma smooch
[Music]
[Laughter]
ew
um
thank you soon
[Music]
was it moist that's how it's supposed to
be
hmm
keep up our love
want some other cookies my cookies oh I
have yet to get into cookie baking
properly
last year
I tried right I made some vanilla
um vanilla coupon I think on stream
right I want to make other cookies but
then vanilla people were already so much
work I think you know with how much I've
been cooking this year
especially the past two months or so
I think I'll try my best to get my
Christmas cookie repertoire
my variety going
hmm
a gingerbread house now I don't really
want to repeat things I did last year
you know that's why I didn't do the
pumpkin carving
[Music]
um I will try to think something else
though with a Christmas theme
you guys are welcome to give me some
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] are you talking about
mirror Myron
[Music]
gingerbread without glue
nah that's impossible like that's like
literally not possible
although this time I could be so smart
to plan ahead and already now order a
kit because back then
um I wasn't able to find a kid and had
to make the dough myself
um
yeah if I if I find a pre-made kit
I might consider trying it again but
has no charm like a pre-made kid nah
it's so easy it has no charm has no no
soul to it
they look too perfect and all look the
same nah
[Music]
do you have a frozen break this
gingerbread house in the bathtub no but
I did have it decorating my shelf for a
long long long long long long time and
it never it never like was getting moldy
or anything
they hold up so well
[Music]
and honestly it was a really cute
decoration
oh my God
Advanced can spending on the Korean
about this is so any good idea
oh damn German fellow had a really good
idea what's Advanced guns in English
oh I don't know if you guys do that in
America or so or wherever you are
but even if you're not like religious
even I buy this
and no not an advent calendar but like a
yeah an advent wrap breath with like
four big candles on top do you guys buy
this every I think every Sunday
uh for four Sundays until Christmas you
light a candle
hmm
reap
wreath
I think they're just so pretty and and
yeah
um I buy them even when I'm even though
like I'm not very religious at all but I
still buy them because they're so pretty
you can make it in so many different
colors and I don't know it's just nice
to light a candle once a week
[Music]
so someone was saying I can make one
myself and that's actually a really good
idea I've never tried it before
[Music]
but it's totally possible
oh fry I did think about that just
yesterday
I was thinking like about it but I was
like what should I do every day until
Christmas one short video what would I
even be doing I need a lot of ideas for
that
but it would be nice
[Music]
um
yeah it's a hand cam stream yeah yeah
yeah
I feel like it would be quite messy but
I would have liked the idea I'll keep
that one in mind
[Music]
a little Christmas series
yeah daily ones are
I don't know what to do for 24 videos
[Music]
anyway I'm getting really hungry and I'm
done with this latest buyer superchats
pretty much thank you grabbed it in once
again Caroline Oh Caroline Sherman Danke
Schoen you've made soon
I'm gonna leave it at that because I'm
so [\h__\h] hungry I only had
like two two small chocolate bars and
one um like small sandwich
today I think that's literally all I've
had and it's like midnight now oh my God
[Music]
I'm gonna go make some rice
and yeah warm up my food I hope it's
still good
I only had two super chats
yeah and members only super chats too
though
but yeah it's not so so much it's okay
thank you for this fun stream thank you
guys
you should do more streams in this time
zone I I stream like until midnight all
the time bro
like all the time
you're just missing it
subscribe
I missed having my quinoa content thank
you thank you very much Happy you are
happy I'm happy you're happy about me
being happy
[Music]
yeah this is usually my time
at least like
I guess I like ever since you know has
been on a break I guess I did
more often go longer
because
yeah no one I'm not overlapping anyone
[Music]
supposedly I might be without knowing
how far did you get in turn bone from
I finished it
and I think for the
um Chihuahua game finisher books I think
it should be added to the list but I am
aware that there's more content to it I
guess but I put all the songs so for me
it's done I'm not putting in them oh
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you to the list then
motion you're not in charge anymore I
didn't know you were in charge but
you're not in charge anymore
whoever will add trombone champ to the
list will be in charge of the list from
now on
[Music]
yes you allowed yes you have to
you have to
me
I know that I leave you thank you for
the fun stream guys
and in German we say
[Music]
bye-bye
tomorrow we have a longer stream
[Music]
gonna be puzzling
entropy Center
[Music]
foreign