spee
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
hello
everyone hello welcome to mahova channel
I am mahova from whole live Indonesia
generation one and today I
join the whole hardcore
um I didn't know that I
will I will have time to join this I I
actually thought that I I could in but
hey I got a few days enough of
time I have no idea what I'm I'm going
to do because um
this
is p Sao server let's say she make like
even every day but I still I still don't
know about the rules kind of thing about
that because all of them is mostly in
Japanese
and and I don't know which which one
should I should I should I
check like there is a lot of mission and
wait where is the mission kind of thing
like that I I don't
[Music]
know they didn't they didn't translate
it how I don't understand but at least
the rule is don't
die so let's join the
[Music]
server okay
who's
that um what should I do hold on on I'm
I'm going to lower my game what's
[Music]
this oh yeah
Anna put the take the what's
that put
diary take
diary only
J I have no
idea what's happening in here
take
free yeah everything is free but well a
Siege
board the C
board
hi
um trying to read something that I
cannot read
uh-huh ah
nice nice
wait
yeah
for
for Fore
[Laughter]
[Music]
audio
output
Minecraft Minecraft
voice I
[Music]
remember h
if you go to my locker um you can find
some iron armors and stuff you can take
it oh okay wait my how how how to
setting the fe uh the
ah v v v yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
I'm I'm going I have to go going okay
yeah
[Music]
for what should I
do what's
this take pleas hat
diamond oh that's
mine my blind oh it's in my
house ma ma where where I have I
have I it I
it what hold on hold on is this how we
do it wait wait I I just put my oh thank
you yeah you just put your head on it
you just put your head
on what's this why why there so many
diamond in
here I have no
[Laughter]
idea where's so many diamond in here am
I am I allowed take
that oh this is for people who
discovered the piglin thing the
pig so so so so so um what should I do
first
come with me come with
me I S like there's a diary or
[Music]
something
okay okay
emal
[Music]
yeah
armor ohe
[Music]
[Laughter]
spee
for
[Music]
M my God
wake
Up's h
up wake
up power wine wake up silk touch ooh
nice um loting tree and Flame
s
by um
spare
Diamond wait is there's a r about
Diamond rules what
[Music]
rules I'm doing great I'm a little sick
though
uhhuh that's
F yes
you have to go to the main server and
give seven diamonds to seven diamonds
yeah but in the main server not this
server so in the main Holo Holo life
server oh oh okay that's cheap okay
yeah so if you die once you just go to
the main Holo and seven
diamonds
so seven
right diamond
though seven diamond
blocks seven diamond blocks it seems I
don't know oh yeah yeah was it seven
diamonds or seven diamond blocks I have
no idea but um it's on you have to give
it to her at the main server okay pretty
much hey y I mean I mean she'll tell you
if that
happens
so wait I have a
um picka
I have no idea if seven diamonds or
diamond
blocks am I training
h i could get armor myself I could make
them
myself question is should
I I do I do think I do I I need another
diamond
sword there no
unbreakable why
not oh hi hi
there is no
unbreakable it's okay it's okay
[Music]
I um I'm going to go to NE after this oh
good
Lu
for
okay wait where is oie oie
[Music]
okay okay
we have to help each other
[Music]
Unbreaking okay thank
you
okay fre siou
efficienc
Unbreaking like
orang uh
okay
uh okay okay let's
go up up up
[Laughter]
[Music]
Sen
for
step by step
[Music]
it's I'll take them all
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh okay
you
dri
senp thank you for the
gift yay I hope you stay all healthy Ali
thank you m
ding Miss
over
[Music]
and Quest they bring with a skeleton hat
ooh First Hat 100 diamond per hat 100
diamond per hat
okay
yeah uh
[Music]
for
punch punch
protection I want to buy
I want to buy
a oh yeah sword I'm breaking
two efficiency two I'm just buying
efficiency
two
which I'm breaking
tree okay at least the base I have the
base now and base
s real quick I don't have the
bad wait what's that oh that's item of
someone who just lost it I guess
[Music]
oh this is is is is
fore
[Music]
so disne
how to
make
emerald oh yeah
[Music]
sorry efficiency for efficiency I'm
working
[Music]
what are you waiting
oh okay
okay hot tourist o hot tourist
wow yeah
[Music]
yeah
boots oh yeah
[Music]
h
I don't have
enough why should
we from this side
I'm going to take this
[Music]
one oh
nice there's a spider
a don't you can get anything
expensive o
o I need I need bed and and food where
can I get food okay okay follow me
follow me
okay
yes oh there is so
many and we need to cook it need to cook
it
okay nice
[Music]
so
many free torch yes thank you free bed I
I'll I'll take I'll take
two take the bed I'll take the one free
Farm
take fre
Gohan
Gohan oh okay
[Laughter]
oh nice
okay okay okay okay uh okay okay okay
okay we can take this one
right all right what whoo oh what
[Music]
B more
I cannot hear you I can't hear you
you're too far away
far away but I can let's
go
Kyla Kyla
Mart Kyla
Mart
K Unbreaking Unbreaking okay diamond
sword need Unbreaking two BS do Bow need
Unbreaking wait do Bow have Unbreaking
do we need Unbreaking for B
I'm not sure
yeah remember don't really you
know
K it is square K Square
K Minecraft Square infity
K
Infinity yeah infity
we are going to
Kyla's place to get stuffs so see you
[Music]
soon
hi sorry
is that head
[Music]
[Laughter]
cups ending infinity infinity
yeah uh let's let's let's make
[Music]
paper we need we need we need to make
paper we don't have enough
Emerald silk torch book it's just
something just
something me
enchanting
book protection
plant let's see
everything let's see
everything wow
[Music]
um
infinity infinity
di
infinity
flame clim Li diamond
di Emerald Emerald Emerald
emeraldo Emerald
C iron
IR m-
sticky
yeah wait wait wait how can I forgot how
how can I forgot
[Music]
you
yeah
okay I also need like tree
mending tree Ming
okay
oh okay
what is
that yeah that that's
okay so one
okay 36
I'm going try
first I'm try
[Music]
first let's see how much Emerald we can
get hello
be only like
22 only
22 yeah maybe we got Infinity first
Infinity all right book the book the
book the book we need a
[Music]
bookity iy
girlies
yes
okay o thank
you
I are you going to go to the and try
[Music]
yes we're preparing for
it R
now
okay Dingle one
Arrow one
Arrow do you happen
maybe pant pant pant P
pant p
me wear my bodies I'm
everywhere where is go to
[Music]
[Laughter]
theen
nah C stick F now uh
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
nice I'm
ready okay
[Music]
oh yes shield shield shield
shield shield okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay thank you you're
welcome
by-bye byby let's go fire
[Music]
protection
oh G gas
[Music]
okay
sque let's go
F got
[Music]
itk God what let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go good what
wither wither
the
head the last the last one the last
[Music]
one
a a
[Music]
what
what's that are there so many
hat I have no idea
[Music]
F re
cushion ah nice fire resistant OE fire
resistant free
oh for eight minutes
only
once
Kiara sorry for the long wait oh don't
worry it's okay I'm not really waiting I
just started anyway but uh so they just
found the Wither head which was the
biggest mission for today
but I think MAA it's your first day
right is it yeah it's my first day you
know we can do all the other missions in
the never for you and I wonder because I
most of these missions are the same as
yesterday I wonder if I do them again if
I still get the diamonds probably
probably probably yeah yeah chat saying
that there's a Bastion Quest oh Bastion
is
hard really was it Bastion
the missions together
actually yeah okay we can go if you
don't oh don't worry we have gold both
of you weren't there yesterday so we can
do all those missions and hopefully I'll
also get a reward again second time
y yay was it here no
here uh yeah oh oh this ah one gu guess
okay that's that's pretty easy that's
pretty easy wait how do we get how how
do we
sand yeah so sand easy like I got all of
these like yesterday the only new ones
is this getting the Wither head uh but
this is over now because it was only for
the first three people who found it and
the other new mission is this one that's
not translated it says we have to get uh
what's it called again uh you know in
the Never that really rare material to
build never I think never right yeah
ancient debris so if we can find free
ancient debris together uh then will all
all of us I think will get each 20
diamonds 20 20 why is it so cheap deis
yeah ancient debris is pretty difficult
cuz we need bombs
probably wait we just need one ancient
debris one for each person yeah if if we
want 20 diamonds per person then we need
one ancient debris per person
oh I see maybe we can do it without uh
do you think Kyla is going to join us
she said she'll be here
at yeah yeah so like four more hours
she'll be online four more hours oh you
you mean she will be another former
hours online or what yeah yeah okay do
you think she wants to go with us she
would love to okay then we get four
ancient
[Laughter]
debris yeah or you know um joining other
than maybe she can give us some some
bombs yeah we don't we don't need the
bombs we just need beds
right oh yeah beds oh right wait what
okay I think cuz I did this like a long
time ago and beds in the never for me
just translated to bombs
cuz they blow
up okay okay let's do that together and
all the other smaller things we can do
everything except for the Wither head
mhm looks all right let me screenshot
this real quick oh there's no wo
F but there's no wool
farm sheep make B easier yeah we have we
have sheeps from paas and
oh you just have to share them yeah and
we need cut
wood if you die in hard yeah uh we won't
die I mean it's it's mine you haven't
died right I haven't yeah not yet my
first survive is free is what I heard
right wink wink get Soul free for
survive you have to go to the solo
server and get seven diamonds oh okay
and then second revive does not happen
normally oh oh oh I see well I mean we
can do this we got this we can we can
see like maybe Kyla you know Kyla is
very very calm in the never so we just
let her explode
everything and we take everything from
her she must have she has so much
experience I think with uh finding
ancient debris so we just leave it to
her and we'll stay in the safe backside
that's a good idea okay I'm going to go
get some food and when we're all ready
to go maybe we meet in front of the
portal yeah sure all right then all we
need is maybe some beds though I'll
check out paa Farm yeah I'll go to BU
senpai's Farm as well okay what do you
want to do MAA
Senpai uh I don't
know you want to come
along yeah sure
you put it in
here
okay all
right all
[Music]
right are there so many people making
another w
what are we going to
do we're going to bul us in by place to
get some food and some
beds yeah
yeah hi
hi so I'm going to share I took like
like 20 beds already you guys can take
the rest maybe okay okay
okay I take the bed
oh now wait it would be so good if we
had a Ender
Chest how you make end chest
again all right we need
the do any of you guys have
axes do what kind of
Axe uh I I want to cut down some trees
oh here thank you oh I'll just take the
oh oh oh oh I'll just take the iron one
thank you okay
oh yeah I guess one of us will oh yeah I
guess I guess we do need some trees to
as well I'm going to going to help
environment
thank you for the gift
[Music]
KY there's no
Kyla huh
huh G are you
okay I don't think that's
Kyla Kira that is not Kyla Kira
[Music]
okay
like put
[Music]
oh no we don't have one more
left
okay okay
where should
put put in
here okay
[Music]
what what you want me to do
she cannot talk right
now why does she give me bone
no it's not muted
sh what wait why she want me to
[Music]
actually uh this kind of even is really
ni a four for
more
got
[Music]
I don't oh
yeah where's where's oen car went to
when did you want me to
eat yes
[Music]
Modern Art
yes
[Music]
guess
where wait
where and IR I I um anything I need a
bone
meal I'm in front of the diary
[Music]
okay what happened if if I die and
then how can I join again can I just
rejoin immediately
h m
for
double
caramel okay okay hey yo hey y I brought
a few building blocks and I brought
brought a chest so we can put in all the
beds and some fire potions here one for
you
oh I still I have one already okay now
take it though because I also have two
okay okay and I brought some torches and
weapon and stuff and food okay okay my
inventory is pretty full do you guys
have like some more mining blocks maybe
we'll need more um I have three three
stack of planks okay planks maybe PL May
planks wait wait hold on
need to put things
first put things
first put things second put thing Church
let's
go if we need more uh blocks we can
always mine the
neck we good good oh yeah so we can go I
think yes let's go all right MAA did you
ever do this before with the ancient
debris although we're doing the other
things first but have you ever done the
ancient debris well not on
Hardcore oh wow he's exper I least we
need to go to minus 19 kind of thing
okay know that wow by by the y or by the
X's wait why why I think it's why yeah
yeah need to get low
o
oh
ooh oh there's another blocks in here
yeah oh there's another another bed yeah
I took three more beds out of here but I
guess they belong to someone
probably okay
um where we go wait what is there's
another Titi in here Titi oh well okay
so we M yeah
yesterday we just went through one of
the paths randomly to find all the
mushrooms and the other stuff and the
the gas so we can go anywhere really oh
okay so what was it again the Soul Sand
one gasand one gas kill three skeletons
skeleton a potion make a potion we are
make a potion how do make that later
outside the potion
okay where are we
going which path did we go yesterday was
it this
one was it this
one um I need Pap fine though wait hold
on just in
case okay just in case okay
all
right okay let's go okay let's go yay
left or
right any
anywhere okay
left
okay why coordinates
why why would I need to ride it
down oh H are those div vines that we
needed to
get um the war FY is that it no so yeah
the mushroom that's the mushroom the
green mushroom but it's not here
oh uh we should find stuff like oh I
hear some
Gast yeah wait H H How would could I
know that we defeated a
gas oh us what I just run it down oh no
nothing nothing
nothing gas can gas WR it right on the
on the diary right ah here's the Bastion
ha oh so this is the Bastion but we
don't get points for this anymore not
only
yesterday
unfortunate okay okay this place low key
kind of
scary actually no I take that back it's
highkey very
scary okay
um there's also mushro Mushroom in there
the red
one are they the ones that we need to
get oh no no we need the green one the
yeah it looks like oh I hear you but
where are you where are you I hear you
but I can't see you how did you almost
die we're just walking on the edge to
death don't
worry we only got
in h oh the path continues here I think
over there
oh oh I hear Gastly can they regrow the
the ones we took yesterday and do they
regrow there should be some green
mushrooms somewhere in this biom but be
careful of the
pigs but I can't see it yeah I hear it
but I can't see
it somewhere somewhere maybe I should go
[Music]
further should go further
there's a
pig a damn that's a big
pig uh-oh
careful
ouchy oh I got the green
one
okay maybe I need to go up do I need to
go up
[Music]
oh yeah there she
is I got I got the
thing what
thing the
fungus wait really where down there just
one though
I want to look for more oh there's
another one there yeah oh yeah I've I've
already got one oh there it is yeah
behind the lava be
[Music]
careful oh all right I
forgot sorry I'm trying to hit the pig
sorry sorry sorry sorry I saved do
y I see is she okay I save you you
good should we go
down yeah maybe there's
more let me
search let me search
oh oh there's Bunch guys
Bunch come on come on come on come on
here oh wait wait here here here Ollie
Ollie Ollie Ollie Ollie
Ollie Ollie K come on come on come on oh
you another one yeah lots of it come on
lots of it yes okay
here oh my God that's so much
nice wait should we take them all
complete oh just one per person just one
right okay okay nice okay okay now we
got to look for Soul Sand yeah Soul Sand
and gas and skeletons okay wait are the
skeletons like the upper skeletons or
like the nether skeleton
ah just normal skeletons are fine the
white one oh oh okay okay guess we're
going to go back up where is the best
way to get
up oh it's so nice being able to walk on
top of
magmas oh God there's a lot of pigs
around I just want to go look I'm
burning and I'm not dying
okay scared
scared there is a pig over
there over there
oh I'm Not Afraid no don't
worry wow nice aim but needs one more
hit or
so nice
nice where should we going again we go
back the the whole time do we go back oh
just continue somewhere we'll find okay
oh oh all this PA is made by me Miki and
Ana and the rest of our group by the way
we made all of this path you guys paved
away yeah we did yo we were so scared
the whole time
nice gas skeleton Soul s oh that's it
under the ancient debris okay okay okay
yeah let's go let's
[Music]
go I hear yipp gas loud and
yeah come at me yes chicken why is the
chicken
here
chicken oh my god really weird how is
the chicken the only normal animal you
can find in the nether I don't
understand it's because they are
actually evil around there there's a lot
more because they're
dinosaurs ooh now where do you guys want
to
[Music]
go yeah this way oh did we stop building
here oh no we just oh God is is this I
think there's a path that leads nowhere
we made another
path you want to save
one oh yeah this way
okay oh
interesting Super Chat thank you uh uh
it could be anywhere really like
everything looks the same but yeah I
died on our trip while we were going
through here
ma F coming don't worry we got
you we got
you oh God oh
God the corner all
right see
oh
God we're fine sorry sorry sorry sorry
it's
okay oh look have
kids ow stop it stop it stop
it oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
yeah
Warrior oh God
oh
nice get the
child almost
died
okay a good job
y almost died y
yay uh let's see um we need to
find Soul Sand Soul Sand right I mean I
mean we can we can do by going down
there like is there a soul sand down
there randomly you know on our this I
know that this path eventually will lead
to Soul Sand cuz we just got all the
items yesterday mhm while making this
path So eventually we'll get there is
this the path yeah I think so or is this
where we came from no this is A New Path
okay
[Music]
yeah yeah there was a lot of soul
somewhere
w we here before did we go the wrong way
no no no yeah I think it's
new It's
s too only
yeah my legac not this one I got the
same as you oh my god let's
[Music]
go oh my and oh
no I got
crickets and
Applause
ooh you have a
lot and I got some Chimes and The Rim
Shop when something's
funny
buts I don't have
any that's okay we'll be your soundboard
you don't need one anyway this path uh
it where does it where does it go it's
dead end does it end here or yeah there
there's another path over here but I
don't know where this leads ah oh this
leads back to the portal actually we
eventually realized we were going in a
circle um which was quite funny oh my
God
you're
oh yeah but I think this way will lead
to another different area a little bit
different in the end it's all connected
but somewhere there are is some Soul
Sand I'm
sure
okay mhm is everywhere Soul Sand
everywhere yeah oh are we going we're
going home if we go this way are we yeah
yeah be because the torches are on the
right take a
different circles
[Music]
you can just go directly to the Bas if
you want I hope this is so sad I
a
probably okay let's follow
them yeah it's not worth it yeah not
worth it where was this
again this way
right this torch is not good only
oh not good at all
nope put the bed away from your hot
bar okay where are we going G I see
Ender we need
you come on I think that's a regular
sand is
close there you
go oh oh sh
what hi you
miss oh it went down it went
down come back
right come
back there is one down there
[Music]
you can if you want careful though be
careful
[Music]
what
huh H I can't find
it I I saw it like stocking down there
platform
I think it will come back hopefully it
comes
back oh she oh it's time for me to
eat my medicines wait hold on but I'm
not in a safe place right
now
A oh is it coming
again I feel like sounds so loud why is
it
oh no no no
[Music]
no I think I'm going to
wait
oh somewhere in
range huh I heard it
shooting are you sure yeah yeah but it
would usually go
not
oh
miss where is it so it's pretty far
pretty
far it's not r
ing yeah come out you
coward oh my
God dang it D it D oh that's not good
this is not good this is not good at
[Music]
all I got Zombie f
well well
well now what should I
do what should I do with
that what should I do with
that I think it's
over spit
LML how can I go
there
wait
the where's the
[Music]
to hold on guys
first day
damn
why that's tough
[Music]
buddy we can't we need we need
her yeah
[Laughter]
wait where's her other
[Music]
armor please put it on
myam can I put the D
oh why can't I put
it you just need to post a
screenshot of the diamonds in your
inventory in
the we're fine
we're okay okay guys hold on what why
can't I hit it oh
okay I I need to disconnect for a
[Music]
while what is different different Ser
different paper different paper so I
need to
check can I put a screenshot
though Wonder
seven block of
diamond seven
[Music]
block where did I put
um Super Chat thank you the whole server
right
now oh it's seven block of Nite is it
really is it really really
really really wait
wait
I'm I need to go back I need to chck it
[Music]
first I need to chcken
First wait oh oh it's not
showing is it showing now oh okay okay
it's showing now okay
um
what wait what did they say
it okay
okay wait wait
what wait wait uh on the solo server
St oh oh not holos saage oh oh okay so
not not on the H
SAA ship okay
okay I need to change
[Music]
the 30 minutes
time dang
but before that hold on guys need I need
to take my medicine
first I need to take my medicine first
hold on hold on I havek for a while
[Music]
Super Chat thank you
okay sorry sorry
sorry
sorry so I just I just got uh
information from P that just take three
just take SE seven diamonds from zero no
time limit
gotcha okay 15
minutes Super Chat thank you
timer timer
timer
okay all
right New
World let make a new world
is it hardcore
more creative world
okay
okay no I I'm not asking to you guys I'm
literally asking to
P I'm not trusting you guys so many
misinformation so I asked directly to
her
instead thank
[Music]
you smart move my choice
yes
yeah directly
[Music]
okay in for now
how long do you think it's going to take
for seven Diamond I don't know depends
on loock I
guess actually she should make this even
more
often or maybe make it like um not just
for
weeks yeah should she she should make it
like more
often even for
uh these kind kind of games where
there's a mission it's really
interesting
where if if we got a missions every
day
mhm pretty interesting
I need to Green
Some Coal after
this I need to Some Coal after
[Music]
this yes
why there is
[Music]
no no animals
around what why there is no animals
surrounding
me no animals at all where's the
animals this is an unlucky
spawn there something f
[Music]
fire my Lu is so low right now
let's just
go let's just
go so my diary for today is going to be
like I got the mushroom I found gas and
I
died you didn't even have
time say
hi Oh yeah I di because zombie
pigling remind me again thank you remind
me again oh
hello but you're not the one that I'm
looking for
though but it was
[Music]
okay I'm searching for
sheep why there's no shape
oh it's
really I need to find some
sheep sheep sheep sheep sheep sheep
sheep sheep Super Chat thank you
there's a there's a fish
though Al some super chat
me what did what did you say what did
they say what did they
say you can do it
speed running
iPod all
right I need some sheep
[Music]
where can I find
sheep I got super
chat seven Diamond I one forgot
you seven
Diamond don't worry we can we can find
seven
Diamond I
just I need sheep
all all the
animals that Mojang give
us but they only give
me cow and pig but there's no sheep
where can I find
sheep I need to I need to find at least
something to eat you you
know okay there's a coal in
there but I don't
even have
any I guess I am really really in a very
very bad position right now
[Music]
really really bad position right now
diam
fore spee
all
right I just know that
oh
sh
[Music]
okay oh
okay
okay fore
[Music]
let's going here
okay
bye CH couple CH couple
yo ho yo
ho yo ho yo
ho I'm
searching for
something yo yo
[Music]
right
hold okay time to eat
that was the bur Ni
No mhm
[Music]
hey we need a lot
Salah Salah
okay we have the kn
got two though it's not
enough we can dig
here super chat thank you
good thank you
[Music]
ran out of
it wait why we do why we not okay we
have a lnch
[Music]
Shield to as
well
three okay can
wait still
night we need
food how can I survive without food
okay
D they almost comes
may I
should
back again
[Music]
May me one
more goo
[Music]
oh yeah maybe I can just go with
fish take those so one
and cook the salmon
okay
[Music]
and code
also why is it so hard
okay
[Music]
okay no why is so hard for them
okay no fish
anymore
okay there you go
then we just need to go
up see if the is
free and easy
[Music]
way to get
iron I still don't get the bed though
do you think we need to get the
bed get hun for
ship donations thank you
[Music]
chy bed chy bed chy bed
she you need to find the
bed where did I put my we need to go
Village to find
Village where it take
my an from
here just in
case just find another
place that's
fine let's move there's no time limit
don't worry about
that yeah
if there
is that there might be like probably
near the village probably
near if we have this
one probably near
somewhere
oh oh
oh uh
wait we cannot take gold because right
now hold on
H eat
more we need more
just to screens this
one we don't need gold though and not
going into the uh knit
[Music]
more iring
we're just
waiting just
waiting waiting for the
fish
y waiting for the fish
[Music]
Diamond uh start from
zero yep
okay I need I need to AR hold
on I do
it hold on wait a minute
[Music]
okay back back B
spee
[Music]
oh
no this s again
so good
night where should we
go looks like this place this is an
open there's a
village there's a
village looks like a
village looks like a village to
me let's go just go
there go to the Village
and there's a
sheep bunch of
sheep okay
[Music]
okay all right
make my own bed
fore
[Music]
for
speech fore
[Music]
okay for spee
all
right
no no other things that I can
find Lee we have
much we can we can actually mining
now should we should we go mining
directly from this
side
hey
hello oh
okay I
mean let's exchange this
one yep
[Music]
I take the
gold because we don't have any iron
wait can we take it no it's missing
okay
understandable need
iron all
right I guess this is my house now
[Music]
this is my house now
okay okay
[Music]
nice first of all we don't need this we
don't need this we don't need
that okay
okay how to make a
chest why cannot make a
chest
there just two two is
fine two two is fine
[Music]
okay
nice got
enough uh STI
what is it
again
torch you're useless
[Music]
where is it
bring
more oh
hi you're the one I'm looking
for not really
[Music]
okay don't have enough of iron
what
else uh
steak that's enough
[Music]
okay we're set
okay we're
going how deep we need to
go how deep it's going to be
yes minus
ouch sorry
guys that's actually Qui for me to sleep
but
hey what's sleep in Minecraft
MH
okay
[Music]
still far the coordin is still far
it's not that
far accidentally
[Music]
yeah not even D SL
yet really hope there's no cave around
[Music]
well well well
we don't need this
[Music]
okay yeah we just change direction
easy easy
pey okay minus
now DP slate now
[Music]
nice I don't like
whenever I have to go
to not
yet I hear
lava nearby on the on the right
left 16
this
one -
right H oh m is
54 okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay
I had it so
[Music]
much that's a big
cave
huge
keave down
there I need I need to I need to close
it okay we can go that way way
down instant minus
indeed no but I don't like it I'm just
go strike mining for
now get a believe that we have to start
from zero
again
[Music]
kind I'm going to this
safely instead
[Music]
I'm still I'm still hearing the
noise yeah
keep hearing the
noises wait hold
on okay
[Music]
think we can dig down now
how close are we right now I don't
know are
we I don't like
cave not at
all 54 - 54
right around 30
blocks still way 54
yep yep
yep yep yeah
[Music]
20s one
two
[Music]
four
five lava up there
oh
okay why
10 well
[Music]
1 14
17 18
[Music]
oh
oh okay
now we go
further
ah hello
there my
love didn't mean to find
you fancy to see you
[Music]
okay
because we're just aiming
for diamond we don't need
anything
[Music]
for where's this old we just waiting for
now just waiting for
[Music]
now not giving it friend
now to stke
mining so I will not be lost
nothing interesting in my life you know
my life is so plain right now
[Music]
let's
go
so spee for
speech foreign
[Music]
commentary comment
oh thank you one two
three
one 2 want how many more
zero I I still need seven seven seven
one two
three
four
six
7 all right so
[Music]
one two
three
four
five
six
seven like
Nana
S one two three four
five Super Chat thank you
six
[Music]
s at
it keep at it
yes one
two three
four
five
six
seven this place is so
shitty
look one
two
three
five six
seven not even
cold
one
6 7
two
[Music]
6 7
three
5 sixe
[Music]
damn still zero
after Bu The Diamond will show up yes
wait wait wait
[Music]
sorry thank you for waiting sorry
sorry I have other things to do I'm good
now all okay
fore okay
[Music]
do go
what that's what that's what
put
[Music]
okay foreign
speech
fore fore
but
but okay
two
yeah so
one two three
[Music]
four
6 it looks like it's still bad somehow
I know
right
one
tender how can we hear thunder and the
grin I know right how
how can we hear
it on the
[Music]
ground I'm just going to
Che right we don't have enough of iron
for
now I want to save it
no we we we don't need
Redstone
three four
we should go further
[Music]
I just go further for
now we don't
[Music]
have it's time to do a
mining
mining mining
time to do a
mining
Min mining
[Music]
mining still no luck for now
my luck machine got broke
mining
mining mining
[Music]
I'm still uploading my
luck what did you do actually to do your
Lu it should
be moang probably
[Music]
mad to me because it's been a while I
haven't played their
games so they like I take your luck away
MOA I've been waiting for
decades yeah prob like that
[Music]
or they fix Diamond spawn right
diamond
[Music]
okay hold
on I
have really
I want to make
sure everything's safe
[Laughter]
I love you
moang
okay there's enough there
[Music]
screenshot got it
got
it
lucky
[Music]
lucky got
lucky Lucky
Seven
nice
now turn run quick
can I join again
though let's
try wait I don't know if they're in or
not is Almost Do hours yeah there's
unlimited
time
wait screenshot this
yeah but I'm still we got
your yes sh
how to teleport
again Super Chat thank you how to
teleport
again
one
one there might not be any anient debris
here cuz I feel like we already got the
the the two de Bree yeah the the luck in
this area is already out maybe but I'll
check no we need like we need to ask
waiting
for I mean uh I already sent it on
Discord but
per she's not only right now de oh she's
watching us thank
you right know bring her over here maybe
oh we got to show her I can send her the
oh she's still spectating now okay I can
send her the
coordinates for where her stuff is oh oh
oh no ol ol oh no I'm on fire are you
okay but maybe P already went to sleep
yeah prob went to sleep
already feels like there she's not
replying oh no she try to again
okay let's go never mind never mind
never mind chill never
mind never
mind
okay too much too
much no more lava oh what are you doing
here buddy
wait work
neighborhood
oh
okay come
where
ah how can I say what can I say
huh
huh what a
spectat
I'm
near
you miny
[Music]
it
ah thank
you thank
you yeah thank you thank you thank you
now I have to go back I'm going to die
if I go back
now yay thank
you thank you thank you
now
ah take
free for
the item power of strange oh this is for
the Ender leer I believe
I
think hold
on if I'm going
to I'm going
to press two again I forgot where did I
put
my oh hey it's
MAA
hello hi hi how's you
doing yeah I want to go back to the
nether to get all my stuff want but I
don't have any gold armor right now oh
yeah I don't I don't have any any spare
ones yeah
unfortunately yeah so I don't have any
spare
ones maybe maybe K and the others have
some yeah guess so you can try you can
try asking
them oh the gold chip yeah I do have
gold nuggets can you can you make stuffs
with
this I think how much do you need here
you go here you go oh that's a lot
that's a lot thank you so much that's a
lot okay yeah that's actually a lot
thank you so much okay y thank you make
some gold armors with it yeah
ah
okay oh wait
wait it's not
enough we need more
need one
more why do why do I hear a static
[Music]
noise
D the static noise
where is the iron farm
again yeah I hear the static noise from
my
microphone I don't know where's oh oh
it's gone now oh it's back
again I always got the static
noise still got it it's random the
static noise is so
Random where is it what where is it
what's this
my
there
ah w
we can prepare
again
oh thank you
okay that's nice screenshot
it I'm going to sell all the
[Music]
items nice
thank you nice com
16 by hi
hi did you get my stuff or or or should
we go get together we can get it
together Sona only full done
weap infity ball okay that's
enough yeah that's fine Infinity B is
fine
see no it's not
okay you can use
mine why does why does this sell it
so thank you
self
touch okay where can I get the
armor here H armor
okay yeah we do need thats
ooh that's that might be
help that might be help
[Music]
gold oh yeah thank
you okay
wait more we can hel them
hey
nice to get another iron
we just need
more
armor yes
[Music]
another
one what are you on
[Music]
Dron Kitty
inflation this stone stone col oh my
gosh stop pushing me stop pushing me
what the heck
[Music]
hii need
blacksmith need
blacksmith to SM see and what what do
I new weapon SM the freaking the
freaking Golem new weapon Smith
okay the PIR and is ancient
what um diamond sword
netherite it
[Music]
drag
yeah
okay okay
uh uh
Ming unbreakable unbreakable
unbreakable
yeah Unbreaking
Unbreaking
protection protection and Unbreaking do
I search for the for the book
do I search for the
book yeah
yeah do you have a bed so no
stor thank
you thank you
yeah wow bad
[Laughter]
[Music]
Sur thank you
present thank you thank you
present she gave she gave you her
bed wow so bad Serv bad service B
service oh you're going to take it okay
yes
[Music]
okayer
it's in here
D what using
back bro it's over it's like
J is there no way to like
exchange
no
[Music]
there I don't know
which are the chest all in
here but just in
case I change
it I will put on my items
here it should be
enough oh static please
stop the
static how can I stop the static
sound it's really bad right now the
static sounds
[Music]
so they will grow more
hey
hey Daddy
Daddy weapon
[Music]
I want it to
yeah
weon SW yeah just one
sword
okay okay let's
what gave us a
attack
coming
take
Co okay
grave oh
okay this
way
oh can we have one piece of neate armor
for each of us
what guess
wait it's not this
way now you lost oh
[Music]
mil look at
Port huh
for
Fore okay
she need help
Kira
here is it really this way though
uh
honestly I mean I did screens shoot the
coordinates
but I trust
you wait but it's supposed to be this
way not this
way was it this way
[Music]
oh
sorry
uhhuh m
[Music]
yeah
really uhuh
hold on
I don't know where ho right
[Music]
now I don't know where she is right
now should I just follow my
God I like at thing that she lost or
something
oh
hi where are you
on I don't know where this is going
to I
there pun
it isn't it
this
yep blindly ding the BL oh sure oh sure
I'm never looking at Chad ever again
what she hates
it right now
a
[Music]
sh oh
yeah oh sh
oh
okay
hello I least to got my bow
back my Ines don't want to hit the Fig
L same
same I don't have Arrow
yet okay
I'm so hungry right
now I mean it was a good
start
where I might I might not help a lot for
this serer but at least um on the
probably
when they SL the Ender I can help a
little
bit but than not help at all
right was very
unlucky yes thank you for
waiting you're welcome I'm going to take
you to Kiara and then I really have to
go okay RK
now
oh just realized that I don't have
enough
of K Senpai I'm going I'm going I'm
going to off to as well because um it's
really took like a long time for me like
around then then you just want to end it
yeah but I need to write some
diary oh
okay
okay let's Road some
diary Deary
[Music]
Deary I lost my stuff but that's
fine oh pleas don't leave
yet she
Sav we need some food
though
need I need some food right
now is this a
place dear diary
o has a chest everyone has a
chest
right
everyone everyone has a
chest I'm going to put torch
back um this also
that
um good
fine
good yes yes please
[Music]
what's this someone
house
yeah ah
at the portal she
sayfe she's already at the
portal where do we ride the again oh I
know
it just
wait we need to wait
I'm going to become a farmer in this
place okay
[Music]
it's not working
not working
[Music]
anymore there was St does in
here I think need to it on
something hi are you already
ending not yet not yet well I'll give
you four four pieces of never right so
you can make one piece of never Rite
armor and you fulfilled the uh the
Mission with this oh thank
you thank you so much right wait is this
that's all you need for one right guys
one four blocks of ancient debris for
one part one armor right yes for one
armor okay
okay I'll continue mining but
yeah I don't know what are you planning
to do for the rest of your stream now
well I think I'm just be safe because I
just died once
so I don't know if I'm going to the
nether I'm just waiting for for yeah I
need to be careful so right now maybe
I'm just gring uh in this place maybe to
upgrade my my weapon my armor kind of
thing like that okay now maybe Kyla um
will go online later and join me or so I
don't know yeah all right then I wish
you the best thanks for hanging out
today with me thank you k
oh and MAA tomorrow probably around 7 8
or 900 p.m. is probably when they're
going to do the Wither
fight
jst
7even 78 n they didn't give a proper
time yet but I think it's just like a
gold golden hour like the usual prime
time for jst oh
okay okay maybe I'll see you guys there
yeah you have fun with the ancient
debris yeah you too
too so Ollie Ollie yeah uh do you need
to write diary for today yeah mhm okay
what what what you plan to
write uh I'm planning on writing uh the
things that we did and tell them that we
fulfilled all of the missions ah yeah
okay oh
yeah
oh
okay
w why are all of these
Fus and
Nite I need to fix a potion it's kind of
tingling like about why it's
not is it is it another water
bottle it's tingling me
about do they do they don't have
any I don't know maybe
it's stuck in awkward potion
look
[Music]
h
okay it's upward potion now
[Music]
oh
no
[Music]
okay okay this one
work why this one not
[Music]
working oh
okay
okay should be okay now
[Music]
nice
for speech foreign speech speech
[Music]
okay just Ste like that see
diary ah
is
this
okay looks like they're got a template
or
something look like they got a template
something yeah
I think like
that they want
Mana
[Music]
yeah
e okay
[Music]
does it need to be Japanese
uh what
o o a
[Music]
we
oh why is not changing to
s
is that how is it
[Music]
what did see
for
Fore we
[Music]
um
this a what this
[Music]
now she made
she for speech foreign
speech shinda
[Music]
wait wait
wait we
not more now
sh
this
this oh
[Music]
wait how how can I say three people
more fore spee
[Music]
uh
more there more
foreign foreign
fore speech
[Music]
how to write
n how to write n
go
there there a
[Music]
na
e
n going to Nether I want to see going
through there and then
[Music]
foreign foreign
or
[Music]
yeah
okay what is what
is mushroom uh green mushroom the green
mushroom name
no me to
be
no
no okay
[Music]
do you need
help writing yeah I'm writing right
now you can write it in English probably
oh I mean Japanese seems
fun I can just learn at the same
time okay yeah yeah what is
uh what is the the
nether you mean the never rides that
yeah
yeah uh just write wait I I can send it
to you in Discord and you can copy paste
it oh yeah please thank
you I don't really know what they call
it in Japanese either but if you if we
just write not ancient debris in
Japanese but just never ride they should
they should know what we're talking
about
yeah yeah just think
katak
okay all right it's just an evolved form
of ancient
de copy the one on the mission I don't
know how to copy it can you like copy
paste
that already
done okay you got all the others too I
guess you did you ever end up uh killing
a ghast
no I guess
oh but the potion did you make the
potion ah
ana ana the
[Music]
chat wait I I'm writing you sending you
the fixed one in Discord that's that's
how ancient debris is in okay
nongo what should I write
potion wow I feel so cool writing in
kanji even though it just C pass pull
pull my
keyboard
ption
potion
okay
okay I forgot why just I just
write potion okay okay those free than
or did you do anything
else oh wait are you writing this into
the diary yeah I thought we have to
write it into the mission
book huh we have we have our own book
right yeah but uh the diary is just for
writing like General things like what
you did today and then there's the
mission book but you can copy paste what
you wrote in the diary and then put it
into the mission book
oh yeah this is just for you know no
today I went out with this person and I
did this and that cuz peka will read it
in the beginning of her
stream okay okay okay so so
basically wait where
where um no not here it's outside oh
outside around the
[Music]
corner in in the right side book first
uh you can see that they write the date
and then they write their name so you go
to the very last page and then write the
date and the name and everything you did
Ol wrote it in English
so you can also write it in English
probably okay
okay in order you know how to take you
going write it
first oh I'm not done yet for today so
okay yeah take the book and then take
the book yeah just copy paste what you
wrote in the
diary or write it in
English ah did you get the Soul Sand too
from
Ollie no no
no I think you
yeah yeah yeah we got that on our own
kind of so yeah maybe it doesn't count
okay m not
are you going to be I can copy from this
from from my own place oh oh oh I just
copy from Discord or so
again
yeah always is say found un the be like
from
20s yeah I found I found the a lot a lot
of ancient
debris yeah I just
wored she wrote it ancient debris in
English yeah that's fine that's fine I'm
sure it's fine yeah 28 diamonds we
yeah okay going to go back in I cannot
see I cannot
just MAA just
MAA and when you're done you put it back
onto the table with right click and then
your diary you have to put it back into
the box where it says put book
here oh
okay if you need something you can just
write in the
chat come back there U good night okay U
bye-bye
byebye
now for me so literally all I say
this uh
yeah do we have to add another one
[Music]
potion ption potion is potion potion
okay I think it's good at it is
I'll just say thank
you thank you
for for realive
me thank you for uh how going is it real
life re alive me
Reviving
rirt MAA reir
Arigato
rice AR
maybe I say like
that
uh
[Music]
rebirt
rebirt uh is it K is it k
[Music]
Mo
n you say k
[Laughter]
yes okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay I'm I'm trying my best I'm
trying well that's
it that's it again now we need to
rest need to take a rest
um tomorrow will we have to stream again
as well
right I will make sure to to join the
Wither I will make sure to join the
Wither
D Moon thank you so much everyone for
coming to my
stream bye-bye thank you thank
you yay e
[Music]
the