[Music]
do
oh my goodness
[Laughter]
i've been jamming to this for how long
you know um 30 minutes i don't know
no not that much we only got together 10
minutes ago
but um
i couldn't feel my sanity points dropped
in quite a bit
i can't help you when that music plays i
ain't going
the guitar is still good
it's the sex one it's not the guitar
it's the saxophone when the sex one
[Music]
oh yes definitely oh where's my
microphone there's my microphone hello
hello
[Music]
yeah it's another
a taco totty collab that's right
we didn't let you wait for too long
that's right we're driving safely today
no no no no
safe drivers
following traffic you can
teach me something today teach you want
teach me how to be good
get good oh i'm not very good
oh don't lie don't laugh
people people say that i'm good but i'm
always like
i'm almost so bad whenever play with
viewers
how
you you put the mario kart in your
schedule quite a lot in the coming days
i saw that yeah you know
serious are you about this
i'm
aiming for fourth place in the group
y4
um it's not too high not too low you
know just just the right place and kind
of in the middle top ish is my it's my
goal
um it's interesting because i'm also not
aiming for
the top or
[Music]
and also not for the bottom i'm
aiming for something average because
you know you guys know my strategy is to
not move on to the next round
i'll see you at the zocco cup kiara
we're in the same group so you know
we're fighting for the middle place
we're fighting for the middle place both
of us
not many people can get the middle uh so
it's actually um kind of a problem
though
you
you don't want to win
well everybody we will start out by
playing uh only with me and ina and some
mpsteens and then later after the first
second round or so whatever we'll have
you guys join in and challenge us and we
will crash you like little bugs and ants
yeah
you sure about that
yes we have to we have to like you know
we have to feel it and believe in it
[Laughter]
yeah you should uh join my room
get my room
oh oh sorry forgot oh forgot to wear
doko ah do i have to go multiplayer
no oh i'm playing online yeah online
play is it a or b it's been too long
yes
i'm actually a bit worried um
that the tournament will go well in
terms of internet connection oh yeah
that's true
yeah
we just got it because like even
even with uh
uh like you know with with overseas
viewers when we go in the tournament
often the
room will just break and fall apart
right
yeah we will have a lot of ping too
maybe depending but you know that's just
how it is with the online games you
gotta you gotta become one with the
latency be welcome one with the ping oh
hello kiara
welcome ah i see you see me already yeah
oh wait i'm still choosing my cart uh
which one was the one
ah damn it which one was it again
i have it but no i think there was a
cart that i wanted to use oh which one
oh
i think this one
this one right yet
uh and then the rest doesn't matter are
you going for speed or for control
i don't know
that is i just chose a cute card that
people said was
good really yeah
oh but but people said it was good okay
yeah not only cute but also
okay
gosh this doesn't
matter but
um weight accelerations
speed
acceleration
i'll go i'll stick this okay
here i am okay
okay um 150 cc no teams normal out of no
calm
all vehicles four races right
sounds good to me baby yes
whoa whoa
you haven't gotten to warm up normal
items no calm oh all vehicles
four feet she looks so serious
all right shoot the random oh yeah okay
yeah random is good yeah
random random random one
did you put in empty steve
oh wait i forgot oh well but then we'll
just do against one another first okay
japan versus austria
oh boy i'm scared i haven't played the
game in a while
uh me too
i'm already slower than you ah
why luigi's so popular among the whole
life japan girls
apparently it's like the meta again
uh
how do i use an item again okay oh there
we go okay
[Music]
yeah
you stole my item no that wasn't me that
wasn't you
that was not me sure
i don't have any items
are you sure you disappeared from the
map hmm
[Laughter]
no
suspicious
nothing is suspicious here in yeah
[Laughter]
wait that's the wrong song
[Music]
okay
we're good we're good it's okay once
once the viewers start coming in
that's what i'll be uh
okay
[Music]
yeah yeah now life is too easy on
yalinha
no i've been probably losing a little
bit off stream too
me not yet i wanted to but i haven't
gotten to it yet uh i actually played oh
do you play my car with your family
sometimes but you know
i don't have a family i live alone yeah
i mean when you like gather for like a
family
like it ends immediately
i mean mama mama totally play mario kart
no she plays many games but she doesn't
really play con console games i guess oh
yeah should we go back and let people in
and let's npcs in maybe first oh wait
wait hold on
no
is this it
should i do i need to go out for that no
i might have to leave the group and
a communication error has occurred let's
go
i'll join you go oh i never mind
okay i'll remake the room
oh google yes
yes yeah mama told you once he plays pc
games yeah
okay i remake the room wait if you play
against friends then you can't put mpcs
in is that it or
not
did it say that
no it's just uh hold on i wonder if it's
in here
oh there you go
uh normal come easycom com is computer
right
yeah yeah
[Music]
will also be
hard okay
start race because off
how hard is that
i'm sure i'm sure it's like the 150 to
200cc type
uh npc okay
random let's go
l1 l2 i'm just like
yeah i press buttons
sometimes i can't play
rhythm games well i don't know where the
buttons are
especially the ones on the controller
i'm just like what
[Music]
oh wait i just realized i'm playing on
obs
[Laughter]
oh no
the show but i mean even even i'll be
playing not in obs wouldn't help me much
here right now
i'm getting myself a little bit of a
handicap so
are you oh
stupid baby daisy i'm the only days in
here
how did i how do i keep on missing you
stupid mario
oh maybe i shouldn't use the item there
not too strong
it's just npcs
yes yes of course they did yeah
yeah oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah i've been listening to it too
like this
oh i missed all the coins that's great i
think a lot of people got addicted to it
why did i say i like this uh road i'm
doing pretty bad right now
oh man
this course is hot
first get a feeling again for the
for the
roads and then once i have that down
i can think about other things you
always do bad on this map
when they come here
[Laughter]
[Music]
i was trying to stay on the side because
of that
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
not fair okay if you see zombie you get
the get the the the audience in here so
that you go more to the bottom as well
okay okay
you shouldn't be up that high i'm sorry
i don't speak phoenix
[Laughter]
all right i'll make a tournament hold on
okay i'll make a new one since uh okay
some people already used the ones from
before oh where's my switch there we go
create a tournament um
[Music]
no
oh wait but i can enter my friends and
rivals too can i now probably not i have
to do tournament training uh search
using it
there it is
i shot them
better there was a time the last time we
did the we did the en id tournament i
was at least decent i was better than i
am now and i can get there again
probably
yeah i'm sorry
a little bit you'll be fine
enter
i will have to go into a second round
after all because i'll end up being 11
for 12. um
or screen time
exactly
yeah
did you make it i'm naming it right now
taco toni
okay 150 cc no teams normal items no
calm
all vehicles smart steering not okay
oh
no smart steering okay um
oh yeah i'm still playing yes
give you the code first
yeah
i will not show them the code yet okay
[Music]
guys don't worry i'm an experienced uh
streamer and yet i have two yappies in a
row um that that doesn't mean that i am
not an experienced streamer who knows
when to hide the screen
zero
and the zero and an eight and no
one little one
okay
and now
and now let me enter too
oh where's there we go um we shall write
it
on the
on the screen
okay i can turn this back on
are you guys ready to challenge taco
today
i'm not ready
jay are you gonna show it soon
yeah i'm gonna write it i'm writing it
down now
okay
because you're both already in
okay there you go
welcome everybody there's a number
have you noticed that uh whenever
you or me or anyone plays mario kart
no matter what time it is there's always
the japanese bros who hear of them yeah
somewhere
and they come at any given time this is
free a.m doesn't matter especially
pickled us in places yeah they're scary
those are so scary
yeah they're so famous ones they almost
show up
they're like in the like it's like
they're like so yeah and then they hear
mario kart and just like
yeah
okay where are you guys where are you
they're joining you joining us
um
i would oh i like the cheap cheap pizza
i want to do chip chip beach oh i'm so
bad
i'm gonna
but you have to learn any all of them
you have to be able to deal with them
code oh the code is on the bottom left
guys under the
uh new song covered with inna out now so
uh promotion
in the middle
is there a communication there that's
not
[Music]
no this is the this is the npc like
communication error
when that happens what
are these npcs that we're driving again
i think so
oh my god you see that we're closing
will i even be driving
there is gonna be a it's gonna be an
[Music]
otherwise they'll take over the world
taco over in the world mysterious
business
oh it's really mario's
so are they which difficulty are they
they better be easy probably not easy
i didn't set
anything
why you keep on blocking them why not
i was feel so slow
yeah me too
there you said the
speed to one two
get out of here
i need revenge on the clones
we're going star wars here
[Music]
i lost control
ah why does this feel so slow
i don't see anything okay i'm back to
second
oh nice
oh sure is this really 150cc it doesn't
feel like it doesn't it
i must have forgotten to uh switch it i
was like why is this so slow like
or a hundred it feels a little faster
than 50.
but to be honest um
you know when i learn
songs that have like really fast uh
lyrics like raps
i sometimes um i turn it down like i
slow him down
easier
and then i go back into the actual song
speech and then it's it really works
like that's how i learn revs
so maybe
uh
are you already through no
[\h__\h] here beat the marios beat the
marios
anyway yeah maybe we're driving maybe
it's the same you started slower than
you can
150 right
yeah
i'm pretty sure
racist mario i believe you i believe you
did maybe something good f'd up
real people how exciting uh okay
all right real people now
can't go easy on them my kiara
remove your limiters
oh
sure
show them what
[Music]
at all
that gets me in the
[Music]
some mood
games
i haven't played a zelda game in so long
oh i forgot i'm gonna show you guys my
skills now
[Music]
no
i missed the jump oh no
i got it
see now it's 750cc you didn't change
anything did you no
look at me being decent
wow kiara
see maybe you're just strong against
real people never mind
either you're behind me look i was using
huh
it's the ping
wait why am i 12
10. i'm 11.
that's what i wanted to see but if it
means that you can be brought all the
way to oops oh where did that ramp go
all the way to the bottom
then uh that means uh what i was i lost
my point
yeah i think both of us being at the
bottom is not exactly a good thing
[Music]
[Applause]
the other whole life members she will
also not do that well probably
yeah
not only me we're gonna be exactly high
together
i just wanna rest
me too but
it looks bad for us at the moment
[Music]
i just wanna rest
and now the ramp is back hey what a
bamboozle
so in the second uh lap it left it's
gone and it comes back in the third oh
no
oh
yeah
i was stuck in a wall at the end
but what do you mean you didn't give me
a hug
i need to
activate what
you know you did that yourself you did
that yourself
oh
you can't blame me i don't mind you
giving me a hug but i didn't feel
anything
[Music]
thanks for the game
following the rules without us even
saying that yeah please watch the game
after one round everybody thank you
what was i saying uh
what was i saying what are they saying
she said
[Laughter]
who is that weird small guy with the
green eyebrows
the plankton
that's the villager
[Music]
so it's no fun to see everybody's
creations here
[Laughter]
come to
come to brazilian
come to brazilia i don't want to visit
one day
i won't travel the world one day but
then going outside is troubling
come to brazil you're not even in brazil
know even if you say like me uh i have
already been to brazil they still
continue saying come to brazil
i don't know if they're even serious at
this point
[Music]
well sure but yeah
i want to go back to brazil is there
like the army convention in britain
and maybe visit yeah
two two times actually
i went to sao paulo
was a very nice oh my god what is this
irish the crap though so good oh no the
shell please no no
my coins
i hate this
oh gingerbread man
did a ginger really bread this man
what his name is
also i saw no
nice timing it didn't get me because i
had to start on since
it's okay oh time to catch up
i saw a bomb walk by me it was scary
a bump yeah a bomb like the the walking
bomb i forgot do they even have a name
oh
that was close
what
oh that was just planned
hi
oh one more round one more round
that shell just hit me
well i like the music change oh that
kite is so
did that just cute again can i predict
thunder i am once again activated are
you the god of thunder here
before the founder
[Music]
nice to get the stars
see you later suckers
nice nice skipping all the difficult
parts oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
no i should have been i should have been
above you guys
thunder twice i saw you i saw you in
front of you for a split second what did
your face
[Music]
the race isn't over until it's over
you know
what does that
mean the race isn't over until it's over
you can't let your guard down until the
very end
oh is this spider-man what does it mean
that is a
a very simplified spiderman
oh never know let's go oh no i'm scared
you're not
it is currently uh 6 a.m in japan
no did you see the mario kart and
everyone's schedules they're just like
i'll be there
yeah i guess at least for en members we
have this uh just uh
tradition to put up uh
the schedules well japanese members
usually don't do that so
i guess they can plan ahead for us to
wake up early for hours three years yeah
maybe they just do a few matches of
mario kart before they like go to work
and stuff i guess it's the new year so
they might have time off but oh yeah
yeah also
sunday tomorrow or now in japan
it is spiderman
i am going to beat ina's ass
oh
okay
did that not hit anyone why did i do
that
hello
do you want me to beat your ass with my
bare hands or with oh
my items
i lost seven items
oh unfortunate isn't it
unfortunate isn't it
oh coins
nicer
oh
[Music]
how can i beat her ass when she's behind
me
yeah it dropped my heart
if someone didn't take it
[Music]
[Applause]
uh guys remember the last collab of me
and ina did
where
i
said something in the lines of
oh
it would be nice if
we would finally do ocha makino someday
huh i see you had an hour
when you said that i was like sweating i
was like
[Music]
this is over
well who knows what i'll be teasing at
uh today that you guys will find out
about in
a month
what would it be
[Music]
when i tease things i do it in a manner
that
it's it's you can't you couldn't know
it's not obvious so i won't get in
trouble for it
but yeah finally we got ocha makino
you sang the first line yeah yeah it's
only because uh
i only i used to only sing the first
verse
so i was only confident the first first
of the year
a lot like the second verse i'm just
like uh
i don't know
especially the wrap part near like the
like bay and cronies line it like i
cause we had to record like it through
all once right all of them man
that that little part took so long all
of a sudden they were like oh by the way
you're only seeing the first one
[Laughter]
for all the trouble to learn that second
verse and then it didn't get used
but i thought i did a pretty good job in
my recording maybe
maybe one day
oh [\h__\h] so i had no not a big trouble
singing it but i also i remember
i think
the
the uh council members they
were saying like
wow that second verse is so difficult
and then it turns out council members
have to sing it
well it's a way to approve your japanese
council members exactly oh yeah i think
singing in like japanese songs is a good
way to practice
yes yeah yeah yes the pronunciation yes
yes
yes yes yes yes indeed
oh there's a trick there
[Music]
oh you get slow even as a ghost okay
okay ooh animal crossing
oh i wanted to play an emerald crosstalk
animal crossing marathon i wasn't able
to i was sleeping but yeah i wasn't able
to
i was uh i was i was busy beating my
family in mario kart
oh
i guess uh in animal crossing they also
have like a countdown every hour
yeah they do
we just created our um countdown on
animal crossing as well actually oh you
like doing that
because like last year we did it for the
first time because mama needs played a
lot of animal crosses i was like you
know why don't we do the
countdown in
um animal crossing because it's really
cute
and then we did it again this year
i once again stopped playing animal
crossing it's so sad well again it is a
big time thing to be honest
um
games like that they only catch my
attention for like a short amount of
time and then i never get back into it
same with since
but at least for sims like when i was
playing privately it was like that but
now that i play it kind of for for
streams
uh i i played way more often than i used
to
and i actually get back to the same
family i used to continuously make new
families
when i was younger and playing it
privately like every time i would open
the game again i would make a new family
oh
yeah 11.
got your number one explanation sorry
i'm bringing cursed language to your
childhood i don't know this time the sun
there wasn't that many attacks on me for
some reason i don't i don't understand
why but wow and i was even driving
pretty well for my standards i would say
but okay you're number one but i am two
times number one exactly
double number one
oh my god
[Music]
a little bit
on purpose no not on purpose there was a
driving mishap look there's a chicken
that is
that
you know the rubber chicken that goes
on your present
never have seen it actually i think one
time we went to like uh like a retreat
with like my my uh music class
we were creating each other yeah
continue and then um someone brought the
chicken i was like my best friend for
the entire like
entire retreat and she got so annoyed
because i kept like pressing the chicken
randomly
oh freaking gym
[Applause]
he got us both food
that is an insider for everybody who
doesn't get it
you're not in on it i guess
[Laughter]
that's because of the phone conversation
we had right
jim is already free
i don't know you said something about
jim being still in the counting when i
was like
where the hell is jim
whoa it was a lunch break back then you
know
boy
you you know
maybe
what the hell is going on oh my god
oh my god i'm getting good items
must be nice
oh [\h__\h] now i've fallen behind again
because of one little mistake
it happens
it's so easy in mario kart one mistake
and you're out
what i just got
comboed
and bullet oh this is great
like great i mean not so great
okay but i'm driving well while you say
kfp come on oh there's no snow it's not
my fault
she's getting better
michelle
i'm driving alone
everyone they're nice items
oh hello
oh wait the next item is amazing
oh my god it's so crazy over here
[Music]
[Laughter]
there
[Music]
jim is forever free
free
of his mortal body that is
i need some practice the subway
what happened there kiara explain what
happened
i had a lucky streak
oh it always comes to my mouth
in the posture
for a moment i'm always like oh
no
look at me i look so dirt
oh my god do your face turn around what
happened another chicken as well
[Laughter]
are you sabotaging the race are you
trying to make clones of yourself so
that i can but that's the cooler you
know or something
together
they don't have an inner name though
i don't know they have they're from
germany they have something called
inna versus your evil twins
it's okay that means if they win then i
technically win too because they're me
right
that's how it works work
yeah
i think so
no
yeah yeah yeah okay let's rock this
[Music]
but this makes me dizzy
this race this road is really a little
bit like what
like tilted everything's yeah
oh no
he took my idle chiara
i almost ran off course
hey
vulcans
that happens that happens
take care of your kfb they're bumping
into people on the road
bump into inna with all you've got oh
my god
oh look he's doing that
how come they get lightning all the time
i never get lightning
i didn't predict those
oh as if i wasn't already fast enough
man
oh come on oh no
oh no
oh it's looking bad for us huh
yeah i think we might have never
but this time i wasn't so far away from
you yeah yeah yeah
let me try to fix my chat quickly
boop
last one the hill
yeah
welcome welcome
good night thank you guys thank you
joining i hope it's fun for you guys
this is always nice to be able to play
with the audience yeah getting better
don't lie to me
you are you are you are
you know they say they say luck is a
skill you're getting better
lucky skills
oh you know oh you know this is our
first collab in 2022.
i guess it was my first stream in 2022.
oh really is it oh yeah
oh you had the yeah at the clip stream
earlier but this is my first with you
yeah
in theory because now the clip stream is
private this is my first stream yes so
although i popped i made the sims 4
stream public again that was before 2021
but now it's public in 2022 so no you
streamed it originally in 2021 yeah
it looks like both too good to have on
that one yeah i was like i was wondering
if it was b-max but it is phoenix
you know what game are you looking
forward to the most in 2022 yeah what's
coming out
uh the new zelda breath of the wild and
coming this month and end of this month
is um
the new pokemon oh
pokemon problem what else what else are
people looking forward to ah elden ring
haha
i guess
i'm
guessing um
some side game of tales off will come
out nothing big though probably yeah
they bring out a new game every year
i think something small
uh when you rise a game well no not
probably it's a fact
no but what would i stream no no
wait
hey
splatoon 3. but isn't that 2023 though
really chad is saying 2022
by another three star field what's star
field
i may have seen something
i felt like connecting with you by
falling down oh
i'm definitely lost in this race
no no
it's garfield but space
what really are you kidding
chad are you joking is that why it's
called star no that's you guys are
joking right you guys are messing with
me now oh but item i want to use that
oh i'm gonna get another one
go away you know hi
go away
no
i wanna be with you kiara
we're going
yeah don't leave me
go away
oh i don't keep doing that
wait
okay i guess this works
yeah i told you this is like my worst
worst uh
map
what happened now
this is actually i'm feeling better at
this one than many others because i
never go left but people tell me it's
it's better to go left right really
doesn't really matter i go every i go a
different direction every time i play
this map
oh
[Laughter]
it's not crony it's it's like a imposter
it's like a crow me you have finished
your chosen ah you i think you did some
some
wrong settings
otherwise i'll wait one one round that's
okay but if i if i like join i'll be in
a random room
oh i didn't know the setting is that
we're like that should we change the
room then so we can get rid of the
setting
or yeah i'm probably not gonna get into
this round yeah
no i didn't join yet so
oh you got kicked out too yeah yeah yeah
oh oh i'm joining already you could join
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go i don't know if we'll
be in the same room though
because there's like 400 people
yeah but i'm spectating right now oh
you'll make it in make way for the
priestess everybody move lay down the
red carpet i don't think it's in control
yeah if it's spectating oh are we in the
same one okay
yeah
um a link
there's two links
and isabelle an inkling girl craig mcgee
from canada no
canada we're we're in different races
there's like 480 people at least trying
to play so
how would you what does it say that
somewhere like when i went out to see
the um
see the room it said yeah
what 400 people like to make
like a new room
okay
we could uh we could go into one of my
tournaments okay
wait how do i get out of here ah
quit okay sorry guys
i'm not very good at making tournament
rooms
into one of mine
um
for a moment
[Music]
search by code
okay
uh-huh
sorry guys new quote coming up right
away
sorry the first part is different
there it is
okay i joined
the new the code is updated guys on the
bottom yes
i need to update my code mine's not
updated okay
are you but did you already press enter
yeah
okay good
new code to this are you and you go to
this
uh yes uh almost
almost
oh i like i like the
tradition in japan
there's a cali too
oh no i'm scared that is you right
that is you right what is
[Music]
i have only been to like like public
pools but like something
dope like that
no
with like
with with with fancy stuff like that
this is like
99 kfp people participating in
they've been here before
yeah they probably had the tournament
saved yeah
and we're guessing that i was gonna go
into that one woohoo
kfp you know what to do help me they
never do
they only helped me in sliver dot io
which is pretty nice too oh yeah those
are
nice know before the stream i was
watching
um while quickly eating i was watching a
video i was watching some cooking videos
um
and one of them was how to make
blueberry cheesecake and made me think
of you
want to try it you should
you made cheesecake right was it easy
yeah it was really easy
did you crash the cookies
cookies
yeah
and for the ground of the cheesecake oh
yeah yeah the crown crackers
yeah yeah yeah yeah i did
i actually have a box left over i've
been munching
also actually when i went to buy food i
bought a fortune cookie cool did you
read your fortune
i'm not yet i wanted to open it up on
stream oh
and i i don't know if i should see it as
a fortune towards my mario kart uh
winning chances or
not towards my whole year
i mean 20 things depends
food
[Music]
oh my god oh my god
i need an item
someone just directly throw banana
[Music]
[Applause]
they saw
anyway let me open my fortune cookie i
love the taste of pork and cookies no
okay
so
buy a fortune cookie says okay probably
something in german
oh there's something in italian and oh
here oh
what does
the most
should i read it i'll read it in german
i read it i heard it in english at the
end so that you get extra confused
that's
oh
yes
the most dangerous heart diseases
continue to be envy hatred and evil rice
or every soul
what ever [\h__\h] is that supposed to tell
me
the most dangerous heart diseases uh-huh
continue to be envy hatred and
ever ever rise to restoration
i guess it's just saying that you know
those negative emotions are bad for your
heart
yeah then i shouldn't be uh en envious
or
or feel hatred towards people whatever
and or greedy
i
see
another one of the
from the i'm ever sad
who hurt you
hold that crunch
that crunch is next level
what is that microphone setting for that
crown
[Laughter]
it's yes
[Music]
okay i got a new power
i've had a revelation uh-huh
it's powerful
[Music]
i haven't played that many
so we can't really give you a good
answer
but the one that i i remember playing
was on the ds 3dsd
that wasn't the uh the train one
the what there was like a spirit train
or something
oh
you have to ride like a train track
spirit drive speed checks yeah
that is one of the worst um oh is it
i wouldn't know i still enjoyed it
oh i'm sure i'm sure it was a fun in its
own way
but you missed out on so much quality
games
i did enjoy watching a playthrough of it
though um i watched someone play it this
that one and phantom hourglass favorite
tracks
both the s games both not very uh
not very um
not not that good as as other games
but cute definitely cute
[Music]
were you like into a different franchise
at the time where it's okay i played so
many games when i was little
hmm
she was not a gamer
[Music]
busy with other things huh what are you
doing
playing with girls just kidding
busy drawing already back then
as a child
yeah i mean my parents didn't want me to
be oh come on
i mean i was when i was younger i was
also more watching oh you know we were
so close again
i was [\h__\h] and then people just
bumped into me at the end
yes sure sure you seen that after you're
in front of me kiara
i love that
oh the crunch is so good
it's like it's a discord
oh said on me i was right behind that
army and then i i got
i got distracted by a
distracted by
life
you're stunning good looks
even though i was behind you how could
you be distracted by that
okay i can look in many directions oh
look it's a small is that the scratch
[Music]
it's so cute that's so cute
the little
flaps is that behind me though what is
that supposed to be
[Music]
i don't know when is that
i guess you're seeing a different uh is
that is that a saplings what does that
mean
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
do you also love fauna
fighting
fighting fighting
you know now people now that i spoil so
many things people think that i spoilers
en holostars
but i know nothing you know you can you
can confirm that right
yeah we don't know anything about [\h__\h]
like the
if you're talking about the audition
it's basically just open to be the same
as like the id and
japanese japanese editions yeah because
they always have their auditions open
uh-huh yeah
i told you guys you don't believe me
anymore
i left i love this road oh come on
no
where does that go oh
oh my god i don't love it anymore i was
playing around too much
become serious
siri
i missed the coin oh no
oh neil
you know what was your meal on christmas
uh on new year's i mean new year's
lobster
some lobster tail
holy [\h__\h] lobster this lobster tail so
fancy just lobster tail after they're on
the grill simon
like they just saw the lobster's tail
you know what i had what do you have
leftovers from my freezer the last ones
that i had
from christmas
no no new year's oh
no i got leftovers from christmas meal
i don't know leftovers from even before
christmas that i made when i cooked the
pasta bolognese was it frozen
no like like did it not go bad
no you know oh you i guess you don't
understand that because you don't
usually cook for yourself
but when you cook something you can put
it in the freezer and it will be good i
know that
that's why i said it wasn't frozen
like like did you freeze it after you
cooked it
oh yeah yeah but then i made it warm
again okay
[Music]
where are you all the way to the top
again
i think our talk was kind of appropriate
because the map was like icy
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah true
hmm
but yeah of course i thought i know to
freeze my food when i make too much okay
okay okay okay okay okay
okay
i was wondering like sometimes sometimes
like uh my sister used to like meal prep
for like the week right but sometimes
she would make too much and then she'd
be like oh you can eat this like like a
couple days after she made it but
sometimes i would go badly
oh
but the other one oh
i see i can see you see it
i haven't watched that show but i i know
i don't like that much either people say
i sound like one of the characters from
i think oh be really like which one
there's like a what's it like a game
console character [\h__\h] oh
demo [\h__\h] like [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
oh
from brazil is is the caller
oh it's
did i just see two garfield am i going
crazy
yeah i think i'm going crazy
seeing garfield everywhere
create creative what happened to those
food
i keep on forgetting to do this oh my
god
the boosted pasta
oh
you snowed up and you were really
excited for north and cro cross oh yeah
that was that's my one
i think that is my favorite song
[Music]
song or your favorite ever song from
that show
ah
then you are welcome me lady ooh triple
i learned that song just for the relay
yeah i learned a couple songs just for
the really
but i didn't do too well because
my lyrics learning skills are not up
there
i see you aiming at me behind you
oh thank goodness they took that
banana i raised your little [\h__\h]
oh no the wall
i reset the fire
sorry i don't i don't even know if
humans exist anymore at this point i'm
so far behind everyone
it's like the humanity was wiped out
i don't know why i'm like these curves
i'm scared of falling off
changing the aristocrats
[Music]
oh man where is everybody
you know what placement i am
nine okay
where'd you catch up in this one
what are those crabs man
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
i was so into the bullet that i forgot
to speed so that's why i fell behind
but then i had to start and i could
quickly re-speed thank you
nice
nicer
i think i think at least that the whole
life members
will be generally
besides aqua senpai and money senpai
maybe not as good as these people like
keep on playing with us
so
yeah i'm pretty sure
they get both these guys their audience
too
i mean
they do get like first place against
them from time to time so
i don't know
not often no no no no
you've been practicing
at least we're not in group uh c was it
was it baby
i mean d is pretty tough too like
is and we're both in d
so
we'll see
first take a screenshot take a
screenshot
take a screenshot everybody
oh my god i'm so first it's record time
you know is that you no huh
[Applause]
it was a nice memory it didn't last long
but thanks for the memory
i love that song sam
oh
they saw them throw that bomb
oh [\h__\h] i'll use two at once
move everybody out of the way
oh that did nothing
oh i forgot how to
steer
oh man oh man that curve
[Music]
video
it feels good to
be painted on oh
i feel good it's kind of nice i mean
like when you were when you were a child
have you ever
like had someone do face paint on you
yeah it was tickling stuff yeah i like
that tickly sound
okay
coming for number one
that blue shell was mine
oh
i'm getting lost
no no i am i'm still way more behind
here
that was just okay
[Music]
i sang i must say an absolutely perfect
rendition of that during my kyogre relay
um
yours is uh our card right there yes
mine is our guys
did not you know
go catch her alive you can always go
and
watch the archive of her perfect
thank you i was always top top butter
butter butter butter a butt b-u-t-t-e-r
but butter
yeah
that was tough batter batter batter
butter butter butter butter up i keep
very kicked it off
a new word that i have invented
i cannot kicked it up just like hickory
kicked off 2022.
and then the kicker we kicked off all
these people off of the planet i see you
you carry kicked
yes
exactly
it's gonna be in one of those words
because
it looks like peter i love it
peter i love it it looks like peter from
family guy oh
thank god for a moment i was like oh my
god did i sorry just flirt with someone
else you recovered fast from that uh
shell inya i did not get hit by a show
oh okay
i totally didn't want to hit you anyway
so
paul
come on do better kiana oh come on
okay
here we go
i feel like the blue shell
you get it like only when you're like
pretty low right uh-huh but
it doesn't really even
do much for you being at the very bottom
right the one who first
messed up the first the one on number
one you're so far away from getting
there in the first place so
how does that help you in the bottom
hmm
the only thing that happens with that is
you can make the whoever uh
is gonna get hit salty but yeah doesn't
help you with the placement no
it's just an act out of spite exactly
exactly
just like this
and everyone has a star in front of me
literally everyone in front of me except
that person
hi
oh no
oh my goodness
i'm getting comboed
i was doing so well what happened
what the [\h__\h]
i think i'm being bullied
oh
let's start once again i'm being bullied
i'm bullying myself
i'm being bullied
where are you
[Music]
the reason why i'm not so happy every
time i'm
above you is because i know that you're
good and it makes me feel like i
actually give something for once
you can do it i believe in you
you see did you see the the kimono
reveals uh from the
new gen and and energy i was sleeping
but i lost it like afterwards i saw them
afterwards
they're so cute which one's your
favorite
oh my favorite
i would say either
uh coyote or idoha personally oh
yeah you know
[Music]
ears are so cute that is so cute what
the hell and their inner tamaki and then
yummy
hers fits her really well i thought and
then and then
oh the one from purasu made me oh yeah
and when i first saw it i was like
where's this photoshop
yeah
this is the screen
oh it's photoshopped
yeah
oh no not again the clones oh no the
clowns
um
i did read into it and apparently what
she was trying to do is uh you know
those itasha the car
yeah yeah
she said that you wanted an ita kimono
and i was like is that actually a thing
or did she make it up
i mean like it's like
like you know like fashion stuff you
know like when they
when you go to like where's the place
like harajuku or something and they have
like really like
out of the world fashion kind of
maybe it's that it's like
oh i forgot the boost because i was
talking about the kimono
number one screenshot time
frame it kfb
yep it's over
[Laughter]
[Music]
at least we're not all alone there's
still a ghost yeah
who
apparently is not an npc
and it's kind of some person i think
oopsie
oh
thanks for the boost
[Music]
wait who was your favorite then
um i really designed i really liked oh
you don't want to see how definitely
yeah yeah it's so soft
and clear yeah
and clothes too and we have we like the
same ones i think they have similar
tastes when it comes to like clothes and
stuff
maybe yeah
oh my bananas
[Music]
and they threw it to the ground did you
watch my video my rap video i did not
yet not yet oh my god it's it's not on
my channel um but it's going around on
twitter and on kana udder's channel i've
been making some videos
little like previews of it but i didn't
like fully listen to it yet
the christmas one yeah
oh you missed both of them i'll send
them to you afterwards
yes please
yeah i've been kind of out of the loop
lately
for not listening to them
although maybe that didn't hit you i did
not
and then i fell behind
i did not she did not hit me she did not
oh hi am i
oh i see the blue shell
that wasn't my world
[Music]
anymore if it's a clown party or a clone
party
[Music]
what's going on
thank you
now can we get back to the normal people
yeah there's real people now
there's another me
oh cute that inna looks cuter than you
again
how do they all manage to oh sorry
[Music]
the one that i see
here on my screen that one looks
beautiful more beautiful than anyone
could ever be in this whole wide world
when i asked the mirror mirror on the
wall who is the most beautiful of them
all day saying you know my inner niece
yeah okay
and i i confirm it with them several
times a day okay
i'm pretty sure about it it's you
see you
thank you
let's go let's go now that we have put
some butter or some honey on her mouth
and we cannot destroy her
oh nico puddings one
hey honey
hi hello
honey
is your cute puppy no the content that
you have i think is the one that i
wanted
oh well
whatever the one this one works fine too
the cards that the
the card that you are riding on the
the bug one
yeah i want that one
i think i still don't own it do i oh
time to play more maya cart
i've already played quite a bit i feel
not enough apparently
everyone has the fire
you think thank you
okay
am i you're doing great thank you thank
you
why you say that now
i'm gonna sing
and i'll say that you're doing great
oh my god you just passed me
you know wait though me i miss you
[Music]
i can't live without you
i know i can't wait to help you
where are you
you're in front of me
like
hi
[Music]
that that was a good race for me that
was good you're doing pretty well
awesome i wish i was doing pretty well
[Laughter]
[Music]
you're so crazy you're doing great
you're doing great
yeah
i need to teach myself you know how do i
get better i want to keep going
you're doing great you just gotta you
know be really lucky
can can you keep the ghost she has been
not leaving
i have to do it
how do i do it uh
can you do it
i don't think you can do it on
tournaments
oh
[Music]
you know i'm gonna go skiing in like uh
february at this point you know how to
ski
i'm not uh
do i know how to ski
yes every austrian knows how to ski
australia
austrians yeah austrian australian diary
in australia
now i kind of stopped saying that
because too many people really really
really believe that i am australian and
have been like talking to other people
like oh
she's australian tried yeah yeah yeah
she's australian yeah so i kind of
recently like stopped saying it one more
okay
everyone over at inani's
audience i am
not australian austrian in case you
didn't know
that's why my english is so bad
oh sure yeah but um
me and my old roommate who i used to
live with
we are
gonna go
skiing for probably like two nights
three days or so
yeah i was looking forward to that she
goes skiing so much and i mean when i
was a child
um
i i learned how to ski in like one day
and i was really good at it that i was
immediately um brought from the
beginner's group to the
medium group uh-huh but then
when i went skiing with kelly a certain
famous incident happened
and i
i almost broke something
a body part
yeah oh yeah
it was horrible i thought i legit when i
was like sliding down
that mountain
um and then sliding straight into a
fence and losing everything all over
uh-huh
i really thought my life was like fading
away but i mean it would have been fine
because i'm a phoenix so of course it
doesn't matter but i think cali is there
too so she could probably you know talk
to the person who comes to people
after herself then oh my god
i mean she's on vacation herself so
you know she probably didn't want to
work
you know
oh my god
wait the ghost is still here
okay next round i'm gonna make sure that
the ghost disappears right why is
everything so
what
[Music]
the balance is so weird right now
i didn't get any items
i just felt like extremely weird as if i
have changed something
or something else
i was saying i was saying that the snow
in japan was honestly really really
horrible and i feel like that definitely
uh had some parts to play in oh truth
yeah so you are oh
number two i see
[Laughter]
yeah yeah i think the snow like type um
like really changes how you react to
some stuff too so
understandable
you're back how am i doing
okay everyone in the room right now say
something so we check your name
i don't see that name i should be gone
okay
isn't that name were you
no i mean
it's my sashimi not of me it's my
sashimi like i bought it right now that
is after interpretation i would say yeah
it's the sashimi i got from the store
not the same as before yeah different
i think it looks
[Music]
that was a glitch
uh yeah we're missing people
[Laughter]
[Music]
has he been here before his face looks
so familiar to me
maybe but their their score is zero so
they haven't played
yet ah this time right
okay
it's a goal
[Music]
um a little bit i probably forgot i
learned once before
you can probably learn again yeah it's a
lot of wait no wait my my controls are
really weird what the hell did you
accidentally press like smart steering
or something
i don't i don't do that do something
weird guys
because they feel so wobbly or so like
huh
oh come on
you try to get me
is that what it was you know i fell down
and then they brought me backwards
instead of to the front and
uh
tilt controls wait i'm testing no no
probably not
milk controls
playing chill control
oh my god
oh well okay let's draw someone off the
map i'm so sorry
oh no
[Music]
oh no the karma okay hold on i can drive
i can drive i can drive
it's the pain oh
that was lucky
ah that was my fun day it didn't hit you
i predicted it
did you learn that from me
uh
although i slipped off no no are you
watching any tv shows right now in yeah
not that many
i don't really watch tv
oh yeah
i mean like netflix and someone never i
haven't watched netflix either sadly
oh my god
what about disney plus
oh i watched hawkeye recently
oh yeah
one of the marvel movies yeah the marvel
disney plush show
[Music]
oh my god
i don't like this
oh finally it's over
you know sashimi is too strong
[Music]
they could be fake
i wanted to pronounce it uh german first
fe tuba and that would have meant uh
uh fairy tuber oh
she is kind of like a fairy she's small
oh wait now i get his feet tuber yeah
oh that took me a while
and feet you know
got that internet explorer thinking el
congratulations
you shouldn't drive so fast in the rain
you're gonna sleep
oh i i drifted the wrong way it's just
funny
um
was that
[Music]
car noise
here we go
oh yeah
[Music]
i'm wondering right now why i am
planning on waking up at 4 00 am for in
order to play this game
suffering is part of the fun right
yeah no but just kidding it's it's gonna
be fun
just like the minecraft thing
yeah it will be worth it it will be
worth it it's just ironic because i i'm
bad at this for minecraft at least i
i i think minecraft is fairer and then
yeah you can practice better
it's not so difficult
to get good
oh no
fine
[Music]
[Applause]
no they pushed me off
it's okay
i did well in my heart
okay
hi
nice i wasn't even trying anymore again
i was just driving off the cliff again
and again and again on purpose are you
okay
do you need a break oh the i think the
choices of maps in the next round i
don't need to break enough i need a win
thank you for the round
i have a feeling the next one is gonna
be rainbow road maybe
let's choose grumble volcano
yeah
choose that one everybody
let's read the room and not go for
rainbow round volcano whoa
[Music]
children for next christmas oh oh you're
not going to get gifts guys
no no
[Music]
you did so well during en and id what
happened question mark
hey mario kart is a mario kart is a luck
game you know sometimes you get just
you just get really nice items yeah
no
well
a big part of if you're only an average
client and the big part relies on the
items yes
yes
of course you could get really good like
aqua senpai and then you don't need to
care about the items but i mean she uses
her items well you know
not for long
[Music]
nice nice to leave those
ow
was that you yeah
oh nice
finally
oh that
oh oh
that never hit me before man
[Music]
i lose
i have a feeling at least for this one i
could
be
above the placement 11.
i want let's do our best yeah
oh god
i see you so close to me all the time
makes me feel
more more happy and confident and safe
that's good
that is good i'm not going to nothing
too well here
i'm doing pretty well but what the hell
was that how did i have a chance for
that hmm
oh no
isn't there only 10 people in this round
i don't i don't even know
oh
is that so i don't know
it's over it's oh it's over
it's over
yeah that was that was that that was
that
[Music]
i've never gotten this item before
oh
[Applause]
thanks for your power taco touches
we are on staff
[Music]
with your with your power i was able to
get the the lucky eight item
[Music]
are you okay
i will say
that when i if my placement here is 10
then
in my actual
d group i would probably be 5.
and potential thank you i'm dizzy
you need to have your pet
um i already have two pets but i don't
mind more i meant pat not pet
i want both
i want ina as my pet to pet me
huh
um i mean i want to see the terms and
conditions of this contract
is there going to be
three meals per day
um is my is my lodging
included there's going to be another
breakfast
oh all day perfect oh oh okay okay
and there's going to be obviously
lodging in my bed with my other two cats
okay okay okay
and you will be um cuddled
at any given time i see you every any
time
another what if i don't want
no is it
you do want them believe me are you sure
oh no we're invaded by the mario crowd
again
the mario army
we got some real people though but
they're just a lot of
a lot of uh
a lot of marios
i like eyebrows though
it's like it's like rock lee
from naruto
no he looks a little bit like
that guy from
me
i don't want to say anything
oh do you see him
oh wait who am i thinking of no no i'm
thinking of uh
that actor from handmaid's tale
i didn't want anywhere
you shouldn't it's true
the red cape
everyone yeah
extremely traumatizing
but it's also extremely well made
oh
michelle
i'm not doing the great okay there you
go oh oh what where'd you go
[Music]
really
match here that we got going on
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
wow
[Music]
yeah that was
[Applause]
[Music]
is
foreign
yes
you
[Music]
are you okay did you make it
[Applause]
god has forsaken me
that was the cry of phoenix
look at now
you think i know how to aim items
[Music]
kyra
hi famous
kaira kaya
[Music]
oh
what do you call a rooster that likes
eggs
and
that was so bad it made me fail uh my
boost
[Laughter]
i was hoping for something up there
uh well
henderson
is oh that's weird in japanese
but hen sounds like
hen so you know because roosters don't
like eggs hens do
you know
yeah
huh exactly
ah
i'm at the end of my wits
same
mario kart does that to people you know
like when you're doing well and then you
get shelled and five people pass you
[Music]
i guess we should stop walking on
eggshells
to not get shelled or
excellent idea oops
oh come on
oh nettie is your second time did you
not were you not able to leave the round
i guess sometimes people are like two
cents yeah
is really weird
your sound yeah like i hear the music
but i don't like hear
like drifting sound and stuff
it's really weird
[Music]
this stream was like really low at the
beginning and then it went up in the
middle and then now it's going down
again oh sam
i guess that's just mario kart
just when you think you got
just when you think that you got a hang
of it it's just like
[Music]
stop
with my europeans
you're like you're like second and third
[Music]
yeah
you're doing very well you're two and
three and the one and two
oh
beautiful
pretty impressive isn't it impressive
[Music]
thank you guys
thanks for the race
unfortunately the power of potentials
didn't help me
as i thought it would you still you
still did pretty good
thank you
[Music]
wait what place were you
uh i forgot
i was too busy looking at the other
kiaras i was somewhere in the middle
i think nero needs to leave haven't you
been there before and there's another
kia
another camera
i'm winning
or someone else's power
our friendship
[Music]
oh rainbow road no no i want it damn it
rainbow room i went
to the other one rainbow road kiara
no no that was not me no one's not me
i don't want to but this time both of
you look so similar i can't i can't tell
which one is which
we look similar we look the same
kia no kara again
wait we have colonel here too kfc
oh did you see that i didn't see it but
there's also macaroni these people are
too funny
macaroni
yeah
have you ever tried making macarons
before
no
but i also didn't like macarons before
now like they weren't my
choice of sweets but
i got i had some good ones the other day
and now i kind of like them yes
i never really took a close look but now
i kind of see the world be below that
rainbow road is beautiful can we go
there instead
i don't want to happen here we have
rainbow road at home
i'm lost right now anyone
oh
hi now i am
out there
[Music]
okay
i rewatched that clip of me teaching
good at japanese today it was so cute
[Music]
did you win
are you winning
i i oh you got four
i could have gone even further but i
didn't see it already ending i couldn't
use my speed it hasn't been like further
i'm so proud of you
you did it
that that bullet kind of saved me though
like
i love people yeah yeah
okay
wow that that cheered me up a little bit
now i'm confident again do you want to
end it on the high note or do you want
to go for one more
one more ok
no more
mario no more mario
all the other times you're gonna play
mario kart until the uh until the
tournament are you always gonna be
playing against the audience um i wanna
have one where i just sit in the voice
call and whoever you know wants to play
can just join in i guess uh
i do want to join our practice against
ghost too just to see where the
shortcuts and stuff was i did that last
time in the enid tournament and i did
yeah i practiced big blue there actually
i should do the same did that help you a
lot it did actually it kind of like i
didn't i was really bad at my car but
they kind of like clicked like when to
start drifting and stuff so
it has occurred
not for me
oh man
it's already starting for me but you're
still there no
not without shoes
hey
oh i got
[Music]
not all races either a couple that i
remember
but the one that i remember was
big blue i did rainbow road too actually
one of the rainbow roads
and so until i beat the um
yeah oh unable to connect to other
consoles oh i guess that's it for me
i think that's it for me you're gonna
spectate me now look at me
i'm always like no more rivals i'm
number one
i'm always looking at you
let me let me get the water actually let
me just watch your chair
i wish i could just spectate like you
i wanted the last one to be with you you
got to come back for one more right
then we might have to like choose a
different tournament or or we can do 1v1
at the end you know just to end it
me and you do get it out
okay okay
okay should we do that i'm doing really
bad right now
okay oh you're racing though
you're driving how do you do that
like even when you're not there you're
good and above me i'll do one race with
this group and then let's do 1v1 so wait
for me when you're done okay
okay okay okay okay now i'm in front of
india
all right
i'm gonna be speed guys we got 1v1 kr
she's speaking the language of the
phoenix again
[Music]
i'm guessing that she got a star you got
a star right didn't you
oh what was that
[Music]
not skateboarding here i don't want to
be on the rail
come on
that was such a beautiful drift
oh i got a coin they got a shell of
course of course
maybe the trick is to just not be
starting first
oh i saw i saw aku sen by doing that in
the yoshi island thingy like she stayed
behind 312th
and then she went all the way to the top
with a bullet
item
that was pretty cool
once you catch up to like fifth like
fourth
and like if you have the bullet in your
in your inventory then you can easily
get first so yeah
you know
maybe that's what she was waiting for
i think that is a strat
but like it has to be done like
when you know like people you can catch
up otherwise you're going to be at the
back for
hey i am not
[Music]
kids admiring
okay so how are we going to do this now
uh just wait for me
i'm on the second uh second
or should i leave minecraft yeah leave
the ground we can just 1v1
even though those stands just entered
sad class
thank you guys for joining we're gonna
do one more with me and enya yeah
after after i uh
get out of here
okay
i can join your tournament
oh no just wait for me you can 1v1
1v1 me bro
only one without npcs
no that that's like two obvious of an
outcome
i know what's gonna happen if it's only
one v1
i mean i'll use a different car i'll use
a different car
no that's lame too okay well then we can
do it with nbc stand here
[Laughter]
okay sticks not bad right in the uh
right in the middle
oh
right in the middle not that congrats
thank you
i won against saitama one punch
but yeah gigi thanks for joining
everyone
thank you everybody
you guys had some fun racing against
these
super cute top idols
oh yeah
okay i made the room
[Music]
yeah
that sang that color of
the
[Music]
privately more i'm not going to do as
many
mario kart streams as you're going to do
okay one race or four races
oh actually four is the least we can do
we can do 48 but
four
five okay hard calm items normal items
race count okay hold on let me let me
double check 150 no teams normal items
all vehicles first okay you got it
yes
oh look at us dancing
hello
oh my god
[Music]
no
we gotta be ready for everything
something in the kitchen that's really
loud
[Music]
oh big blue
oh no that one is the one that's so
crazy
yeah there's a lot of twists and turns
like look at it
no it was not my stomach
i'm focusing now
wow wait that gives money
what gives money
oh
i like the music here though
yeah the music is still good i remember
when i was practicing with the ghosts
the music was so bopping i didn't mind
it
oh come on get up
what i hit something was that me
i don't know
the green shell
ah no it wasn't red i think
okay did that was that my fire
uh no i just i just fell off the map
did you fall from it shooting into the
void and i'm like
does that maybe hit someone
maybe you never know
right good luck
[Music]
so far better than the last time i was
on this map it's good
as long as you're you know improving
yeah
can't be why are your chairs
don't take that away from me
oh oh my nose is itchy why not
you gotta hold on kiara
i didn't
i scratched it while holding the
controller that's good
honk
wait
[Music]
that's
yeah yeah yeah
it's stupid it's a hard npc a hard npc
when we started out i i lost by far
against the npc's right yeah i wasn't
that you were like the middle of the
pack but you're improving you're
improving
okay
what
oh this map
no no that one is fun
hanukki mario
i once um
when i lived in japan i uh saw a real
tanooki oh was it cute
it was uh
it was cute and weird what do you mean
this guy's as a human
no but it did something it was kind of
cute like i i lived in a neighborhood
that was pretty um
wow
central uh-huh so
it was like a lot of houses and and
narrow
alleys
uh-huh ellie's airlines oh ellie's
alleyway
yeah
uh how do you keep on blocking my
shelves oh my gosh i have another idea
anyway i was saying um
and then i was coming home one night
from something i don't know what i was
doing uh-huh and it was dark and i
i walked through
this one path and then i noticed
something
drinking water out of uh like a
like a planter uh-huh
and i was like is that a cat is that a
dog what is that it wasn't so dark i
could barely see
and then oh my god yes it wasn't it
wasn't
it looked at me and i looked at it
and we looked together and i was like
legit scared for a moment because i
didn't really know if like
i don't know would it attack me tanuki's
attack
do they endanger oh i don't think they
do okay good
so i stood there for a moment i didn't
continue walking i was too scared
and then
i took a few photos and then oh i think
i think it ran away maybe
yeah we did i ran away everything i
don't know i
i i think i run away
you're scared
i wasn't a little bit intimidated i must
say ugh
[Music]
i used to live in a place that's kind of
like near a park
and like in the winter i would just
randomly see
like
dear family
coming to eat our grass
our cousin
yeah
it's definitely interesting like like i
would be like getting ready to go to
school like in the morning when
like it's like dark outside and now it's
nice to use like sets of glowing eyes
in the dark and they just all be staring
at me and i'll stare at her back and
they're just slowly munching away at the
grass
it's okay you're still fifth you're
still fifth overall ranking that's what
matters right to my defense i was very
focused on telling my story yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
saying happy new year's kiara i'll drink
until you win
you're gonna be drinking for a long time
i think i think okay they don't really
stay behind
no i just i just i just accelerated too
fast oh okay really didn't you really i
didn't actually try to
stop
that's because you would call me lame
[Music]
and the fortune cookie told me to not to
be too greedy well here i am exactly
being greedy
oh i like this music
oh this is still the clockwork map i
like i like the one i always miss that
shortcut
[Music]
employee
for
i will fight hard for you so you don't
have to get a a
alcohol poisoning
is that a thing that you get when you
drink too much or like how do you get an
alcohol poisoning
that's that's how you get it right
is it
yeah apparently yes
well i haven't i've never even been
drunk before so i wouldn't come
[Music]
no no no no that one's so stupid
says yes
the alarm is ringing again
ain't not time to wake up from your
dream
i'm dreaming
from your slumber on the ground oh
i thought it was just cause you're uh
your very dream
[Laughter]
i don't want to be above five come on i
see that as a win
uh-huh
oh come on
that was not necessary
it really was not
ghost
and stuff
come on cara you can do it
beat the inkling boy you can do it
[Music]
okay all right all right um
i i i think uh
wait do i have one more uh i don't i
don't know do we it's not the fourth
yeah we have one more we have one more
okay i can do it one more chance to get
first this is the last
come on
i can't do it believe in my hands that's
how the drive is doing right
just kidding i didn't spit into my hands
somewhere for some reason it's
disgusting but i don't know
that's unsanitary
there is no tomorrow
oh my god
jeff like there is no tomorrow
oh whoops oh no
yeah go back
[Music]
where are you
behind right behind you okay good job
no easy mode
you can do it i'll get you i'll get you
this is a fairly easy map i have a lot
of control over this man you do
believe in yourself believe in me who
believes in you
oh
wow
[Music]
what npc is in front of you how did that
happen in you i wonder too they got
lucky with the items that's what it was
one of us has to be number one in yeah
to defend our honor oh
it's over for me
[Music]
[Laughter]
you'll defend what
wait there is still one one more in
front of us though
wait
oh wait never mind they're no longer
dammit
oh no please she doesn't want to get
trapped
[Music]
i tried i tried kiara i tried breaking i
did i see that as a win yeah i see that
as a win
you can stop drinking now look closely
yeah stop drinking
you can stop drinking
what's his name again what's that name
against that dude
it says nice try for me what does it say
for you oh i didn't see congratulations
maybe
yeah
[Laughter]
are you okay
that was fun i should probably remove
the code from
yeah oh yeah
but thank you everyone for those of you
who joined us or just came to watch us
have fun
thanks for uh thanks for joining us
thanks kiara for uh suggesting that we
collab instead of doing two solo about
your course training
[Music]
you still have so many more chances to
drive so low yeah this time you're able
to drive together yeah and if you if you
feel like joining when i'm just just
randomly racing against schools let me
know
yeah yeah well
thank you for giving me um some
no no
yeah my job here is done
[Laughter]
my job here is
but it done fun and i i wanna i'm glad
that we're doing more collabs right now
let's play together more
yeah some other games perhaps yeah we
started the minecraft too
huh splatoon
indeed i have suggested uh
and i just told it in the clip thingy uh
already that i invited kuda i also
invited ina so good at ina and me will
be going to disney and then one more
number yeah yeah yeah
one more member that's
secret secret but
yeah we'll be going to the disneyland in
minecraft as you have seen there's a
minecraft world
before
and i wanted to try that one out and go
there with some friends
so i figured enough because of milky
mouse
you mean
michael move
oh
my name is michael
what's up
but it's so hard
you got to do something in your mouth
but i don't know
are you from kingdom hearts
does that server have kingdom is that a
meme
because mickey mouse is in kingdom
hearts you know
once one time gura prank called me and i
uh
[Music]
since then everyone's been asking are
they in kingdom hearts
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know about our lord and savior
lightning mcqueen
know um
i'm actually really surprised that we're
even able to play that disneyland world
because in disney like super hard with
the with the copyright like everywhere
like mentioning even even men i noticed
that the japanese members are even
scared of mentioning disneyland but i
just do it all those times
you remember
i always say that it's true that's true
just saying disney is dangerous
yeah i mean they're playing a safe life
but then we talk about michael moos
and mike who's who's michael moos ronald
ruck
and
what yeah michael moos we're on
michael moos
[Laughter]
all right all right
why do i feel so stupid right now
i think you're right brittany needs a
little beer break he had a pretty long
clip stream and then this sheep
go get some brown sugar
be i'll be doing a um
stream tomorrow i hope i can
get i hope some of you rub off rubbed
off on me today through this stream so
that i have some more feel free to pat
my head you know for extra luck okay
okay okay but that's after stream okay
we gotta we gotta say a good place
no no no no no no
come here
okay
you were to my left mm-hmm oh left pink
pepper right
all right good luck
thank you
and
i will see you guys
uh soon
uh
and in german we still have venus
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
you'll be fine
okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
you