[Music]
la
squeaky W
chicken did you hear that Kik that was
me just that was actually not the
chicken that was just me saying Kik did
it sound weird must have been the
unusual streaming
environment well let me try again I I'll
say it again
[Music]
okay yeah eh doesn't sound
weird squeaker riy
I
already pretty pry really and pretty pry
mhm uh
unexpectedly
unexpectedly got the merch samples
everything except the fan I was just
asking if I can see it in person um
yesterday I asked it if I can see it in
person one of these days and JMA brought
it to me today so quick to
act
n
pry good word I
think oh my God it squeaks like so
loudly the impact IRL is stronger I
think than what it sounds like uh on
through my
headphones it's it's it's quite the
impact is pretty loud and um I think it
is dangerous
because this sound will only
motivate dogs in this world even
more to
destroy and chew the [\h__\h] out of this
chicken so to all the dog owners who
have purchased one of these uh please
protect the chicken
please this is danger danger dog's
favorite
meal it woke up your dog are you playing
me on speakers well of course he's going
to wake up your dog and and now he has
awakened now he heard the sound and he
will never forget it until he he gets
what he thinks and dreams of every night
now thank you for the membership
come yeah yeah I also got
the uh everything except the fan right
so also the The Happy The Happy the howy
um and I didn't realize this from the
pictures but the and in German we say Al
Z part is embroidered really nicely like
really thickly
that's quite
nice maybe tomorrow I'll show you the
happy on
Twitter so speaking of Twitter uh since
another week has begun let me show you
the schedule really quickly
um
T now we are going to play whole life
Treasure Mountain it's kind of you know
a little oneoff fun game a fan game uh
looks pretty cute it's kind of like the
sua game but in frd and with whole life
members whole life Japan members so
going to I'm going to play that for a
little bit Yeah and then tomorrow I know
I said yesterday which spring are but I
said either or because of Friday being
either or um but I decided tomorrow L's
mansion and a little bit earlier than I
thought because like uh my
brain is like you know it's hard to
think
and while while I generally prefer to
stream later in the day and that's just
how I'm used to doing things um the more
I think about like time zones and what
time it is for you
guys uh when I stream in the evening
jst at like 7 600 p.m. I realize oh
that's so [\h__\h] for most of you
guys uh at least for like no
America uh uh yeah well on the other
hand Europe of course but Europe always
when I'm in Europe Europe always gets
plenty of normal time streams so I want
to take this opportunity while I'm here
to do decently timed streams for na you
know cuz I normally I don't have this
opportunity I'm not going to wake up at
6:00 a.m. in Austria to stream for and
or at 4:00 a.m. I guess to stream for
any a prime time I'm not going to do
that in Austria so while we're in Japan
I'm going to you know try to do that a
few
times here and there and that's why
we're going to do Lu just Mansion also
because I want to have dinner with a
cute girl
tomorrow yeah yeah yeah and then
Wednesday first day I'm busy with work
so I won't be and able to stream and
then Friday I really hope we can do
Olympics watch along I quested it I just
said um sorry there's nothing particular
that I want to watch I just want to
watch everything over the course of
several
hours can I do that please so we'll
see if they say yes I hope they
do um and then if not then we're going
to we're going to finish witch spring r
on that day
otherwise uh yeah but I'm looking
TimeWise I'm looking at uh like starting
at like 5:00
pm jst I think and then just watch for
like six hours or
so
yeah and then Saturday we have uh ID cup
they have you know the Minecraft thing
again and I'm invited again so I'm
teamed up with Wayne and so we're going
to practice on that day and then the
following day uh is going to be the
actual event
so
yippe yippe that's the schedule y let's
have fun probably the last uh schedule
for now where I have so many streams up
there like a normal amount of
streams so enjoy while we have this
moment in time and
[Laughter]
amazing it's
amazing I have to look at
him he's he's a marvelous
creature
marvelous very very marvelous
fascinating now they'll take a proper
video for me um official looking one so
I don't have to do it yippee okay now
let's play okay and tomorrow I'm also
like my plan for tomorrow is to do way
more progress than we did yesterday okay
for L's Mansion like tomorrow I'm going
to I'm going to like do at least two
Mansions yeah nobody can stop me nobody
can stop
me okay opening the game oh my God is it
going to be loud please don't be loud
please don't be loud please don't be
loud please don't be loud please don't
be loud
okay that's
[Music]
fine H life Treasure
Mountain
um I was kind of like I opened the game
to like look for any way to get like a
clean high quality high resolution
graphic uh and logo because nothing
online
nothing and then I stumbled
upon uh where no I not it I stumbled
upon the opening it's pretty long I'm
not going to watch it again
but that was a surprise just a wink won
recommend to anybody who hasn't seen it
go watch it it's funny like what she's
just rambling and rambling m
just rambling and rambling and
rambling it feels like it was like 5
minutes or six seven minutes long that's
about it felt leg she's just endlessly
rambling I was just looking for like a
clean graphic to screenshot or so I
ended up just screenshotting like
um
um no
no like this quickly screenshot and then
put it in the thumbnail and then I cut
out the
logo yeah cuz it wasn't anywhere with
big
size pot calling the kettle
black
huh why would the pot call the kettle
anyway HH why are you black why are you
gay
sh Shark in the
Water continue in my favorite meme from
yesterday well let's play Let's Have
Some Fun okay I want to I want to Stack
some friend shaped whole life
members uh oh I used the the keyboard a
or controller uhu space or enter to
shoot oh okay I thought it was just all
Mouse
another all right
a set sail
all right is there there's no time
pressure right because the music makes
me feel like there's time pressure but
no okay but what's the is the is the
order from left to right up
there and P sea is the greatest thing
you can get or
what oh wait
ah I prefer to aim with the
mouse okay
okay well I don't know it's probably
going to end up in the middle anyway
whoa okay that that has quite a quite
the momentum to it
wait Did she
always did she
have TW half twin half up twintails in
her a default outfit
[Music]
looks so
cute yeah oh my God okay so that's
that's uh if if I get two of that I make
oh they stick together cute it feels
like they stuck together oh yeah they're
kind of sticking
together why why was
she why was she why was the hearts what
does that
mean if I get two Ramy I get one
n but I don't even see my my arrow so I
guess just got to oh
oh why does it get Hearts is it because
it's happy that it's like getting very
close to the
others I like this
[Music]
music C wow we need to let
T they they all Yap I need to listen
can I make can I make man sena's voice
[Laughter]
[Music]
louder she's
shaking she's
trembling
oh yeah that's okay thank you thank you
thank you money
Senpai okay now I can hear her louder
and clear
uh when do we throw
thisai doesn't really matter does
[Music]
it oh maybe close
tunami what's what's itchy there's so
many funny voice lines of her in
this I like it it's cute she's just
yapping um uh okay ban already turned
into something else so let's put her
here and then oh how about maybe on this
side yeah oh touch touch C touch no
don't don't don't get too touchy and
feeling with K you want to touch your
other
self push her over there oh now you
[Music]
could so far this is easier than the s
calm down M I guess you could probably
if you if you're unlucky they will start
like tumbling down the edge right
probably
eventually um two lamies is
one they so far from each other now
that's not
gooda is already pretty
big wait let's throw that over here and
we have oh another canatan wow the
map checks
out this is
cute yeah it's like free d sua kind
of where throw this
no uh close to Canan would make sense
[Music]
oh this looks good doesn't it oh we got
to
do they look so cute they look so friend
shed oh okay what then this zy goes
close to
nura
oh nice oh nice oh nice
it's been a while since
there
okay
n we love
n okay so this one finally we can
finally I'm bring things further away
because I want this to go to B wo okay
[Music]
nice drink she said she's the energy
drink of everybody's heart
a that's a cute thing to say it's not
right wrong I don't know why I'm
throwing that there I have absolutely no
thoughts about it head empty U but this
one maybe close to
Pon and then maybe we can combine
later
W let's
go this easy this easy oh there we go
combination happening
[Music]
skill a little bit tired in that voice
line so not much of an energy drink or
maybe because she's the energy drink she
doesn't have much energy herself
[Music]
there oh let's
[\h__\h] another Genius of ASMR something
I do not understand really something I
do not have a talent or a skill for
sometimes you know I think about like
trying it at least once as like a
gimmick
stream okay okay chill out everybody
just as a gimmick stream I'm thinking
doesn't that doesn't Studio have ASMR
[Music]
microphones to borrow like could I set
up a stream at the studio with a as SMR
microphone from them while I'm here you
know make use
it I don't know what the is would be
about I know I know I didn't want to
know but that was like with her you know
feel feel like you know nervous around
her
so who knows what I could do if I'm on
my own who knows
really maybe I can unleash
[Music]
So Random these phrases she just said oh
it's not like I'm horny suddenly now
I've always been horny from the GetGo
okay man by I mean I didn't doubt that
ever I had no
[Music]
doubts
cute that's a secret it's not a secret
doesn't seem like a secret
yeah it makes a lot of sense in freedie
I like
[Music]
it I saw like SAA game merchandise
recently like you know just the fruits
turned
into um plushies and it's so
cute actually I have
one I have the
pineapple okay now it's getting kind of
tight in here
[Music]
it's not doing mucho yet to be honest M
Senai stream
pineapple yeah they're just fruit
plushes but it's really
cute and somehow I don't know makes me
feel like I want a full collection of
them just because not I wouldn't want
any kind of fruit plushes just because
it's SOA game plushes that's why I want
them that's the whole
reason um maybe close to N
right another one we need another
there and
here
yummy
yummy okay now it's tight but I can
still stack them on top of each
other I could start doing that probably
but I don't know I don't want to cover
anything up
here well I'll do it oh God oh God it if
something falls down
is that game
over is there no pora at
all okay
squeeze oh that's G oh dear then then
this is good for our first try already
isn't it okay we get Lamy over here we
get wa this this will be good because
she will immediately she will turn into
CL down and then she will touch the
other kind of down in the middle will
this cause a big
explosion no it's relatively
calm
here nice what's What's
after I'll throw it on top I was okay
another one wait can you please land on
top
[Music]
physics not as crazy as SU game yeah
yeah
yeah yeah oh guys by the
way do you guys like spam spam the
food I haven't done like a Japanese food
review short in a while but I saw that
in the convenience store like everything
seems to be about Hawaii not just the
quas there's like no it's
okay M they there's like a Hawaii theme
going on in in the in Family Mart right
now and um they have some things with
Spam and I was wondering should I buy
this and review
it
yeah is that
good and that would fulfill my challenge
of having eaten something for the first
time cuz I've never had spam before and
I trust Japan or Japanese convenience
stores to make something good out of
spam is salty
meat very high salt content oh dear I
think it's like with uh Teryaki sauce
and mayonnaise and then you know on on
Rice it's like a only gidy with
Spam super processed H I don't really
like such super processed things but if
it's good then I I want to try it for a
video you
know can I squeeze it in here don't fall
down
okay
[Music]
wow isn't all the com food high process
I would say like this is from the Fresh
So to say food and banto section I feel
like those things are not that processed
like the bantos and all that and the
only maybe the snacks but not that right
don't break my don't destroy my dreams
right
now make sure to wash it or bright it oh
but I'm not going to get it like
straight out of the can no no no I would
get it like in the version that is the
[Music]
musui use
challenging just eat out of the can no
ew I'm too scared especially now after I
hear your
reviews let no no no no no let's throw
wait the next one is also dumy okay okay
let's throw her on
[Music]
top NOA
why no it was going so well hi
what was my first try how you
that 7, almost
400 that's not bad hey I got
pick icon does everybody get that retry
retry ret
try good first try I would say okay I
need to still you know get to know the
physics like where can you really risk
it and where should you not risk it for
the biscuit you know it's it's it's
something you have to get feeling for it
it doesn't come so
[Music]
naturally you go here we don't have much
to worry about
yet nice nice
oo can you guys like turn around and
kiss each
[Music]
other love yourself some there we go oh
that's so
cute I I saw the child of V Senai and
found
[Music]
today what does she mean with
that what did she just say what does she
mean with
that uh uh I think it's Japanese Indie
vtubers new outfit and it's like the
same Artist as FAA but this so by being
the same from the same artist it already
looks like you know similar you know and
then she's blonde though and she got a
new outfit and the new hair really made
me think of V Senai and it looked like
like vat Senai drawn in like faa's
Mama's art
style I I I I
couldn't unsee it
yeah it's as if found and what M I had a
child I really like seeing um like these
like artists other children so to
say I don't have such a delight you know
I'm the only I'm an only
child so I can't really you know see
that kind of like similarity in others
but it's interesting when I see it for
others yeah I have no savings I have an
only child unlike IRL I am not an only
child
IRL who is that in the middle is
that what are you going to do about
[Music]
that oh w
w nice clean
up nice clean up
[Music]
it's good if you can keep your whole
Battlefield clean early
on nice nice nice
nice you're related to Black sh kind of
but I don't really look like them at all
I don't look like cook is others like so
to say children or characters I don't
look like them he drew me in a very
different art style that's also the
thing
[Music]
I'm adopted yeah I might just be
adopted adopted and an only child how
sad is
[Laughter]
that he wants to
all right all right then so be it do it
do it just do it wo waa three big ones
in
here maybe closer to Altera that is that
the the the like white gray silver
haired um fate character right she's
really pretty she really
beautiful I really like that character
design m
yeah out of all like fate characters
that's actually I don't play fate but
that's actually one of my um favorite
character designs from fate
coincidentally even without Hook's
influence like without the fact that
it's from Hook
[Music]
Papa yeah just the the default outfit
already I really like it
[Music]
no no no no no no no we Lo and
Pie let's
go wow wow W okay I didn't get that far
last time and it's such a clean field
would you look at that I wonder if
there's a meta like in CGA game you
wanted everything to be in certain
positions if you want to really like go
hard um I wonder if there's a good
position to have your big ones in at all
I don't know though I'm just going to do
whatever do
[Music]
whatever another big chunk
of it's staying so clean is this the run
is this the Run
to get P Senai I guess is kind of the
goal like it was the goal to
get two
melons no what was the golden s game
kind of like the the best you could
do
one not watermelons what what what no
yeah watermelons two watermelons was I
uh really difficult and the the greatest
thing you could do I think you can't
really do free although I think i' have
I seen people do free I feel like maybe
maybe I did see people do free and that
was like the crazi thing ever could that
be did that happen or was that in my
dreams in my
[Music]
dreams free must be ah two pckers will
make each other a kiss will make each
other disappear really and then what
they just they're just gone two
combining vanish oh like in sua game so
they mirrored what happens in sua
Game
oh was only ever able to get one I don't
think I did I ever get two suas Two
waterm
Moons I feel like maybe I
didn't
[Music]
sad I really like the game but I was
like traveling and busy while it was
really
popular so I kind of you know missed out
on all this CH game
hype I still got a little bit from
[Music]
itce
nice let's
go why are they making out there they're
like
flirting should I put my face on over
here probably
because then you can see M by
[Music]
properly and push push her out of the
way yeah yeah yeah when I when I had to
like Ci was streaming I was over at her
place she was playing sua games she was
so addicted to it Mama Mia and and I was
just staying over for a night and I
couldn't stop watching her even though I
needed to sleep cuz I had to get up like
really early in the night liter like it
wasn't even bright
outside it wasn't even bright outside I
really had to go early because I was
going home the next day like on that day
after I stayed
over give me the can I squeeze in n in
the front yes okay don't ruin my run
please this is going so well
I have high hopes for
this oh my God as I'm
saying holy [\h__\h] is this normal that
things go so well this is my second
[Laughter]
try oh my
God what what's going on is it this easy
wow wow wow wow wow
wow show I'm I'm not even thinking much
in s game I had to think so much
more careful there don't push so hard
don't push your
sandai oh wow Kam uh
amazing it's like they're I feel like
they're more bouncy now maybe because
there's barely anything on the
[Music]
field okay okay go in the
middle why is she so bouncy we need to
fill it up more so that they like stick
together and hold hands and
be
um let's put her
here let me let oh let me no problem
okay
did you see that uh H
cure Kai is working on the thir
gen so they already posted screenshots
so maybe within this year right we'll
get a new nice Holo cure Arc whoa whoa
whoa
who yeah oh three and four they're doing
both let's go let's go let's
go
nice and auki R
uhhuh
interesting yeah I'm so excited I'm
going to play the hell out of
it really interested in what new stuff
there's
coming really all these Whole Life indie
games are really a
blessing for us too because obviously we
got perms for them and and it's
a little bit surprising to me how well
whole life fan games tend to do in terms
of
like okay this is you know you know like
you guys seem to enjoy watching them
like a lot of people show up for whole
life fan games especially for holo cure
of
course
yeah it's nice like it's it's like
promoting
whole life within whole life and I don't
know how to say this it's so smart it's
like actually such a genius
business thing too like we're just like
it's an endless cycle
of supporting and
promoting
so I don't know it's just
genius it's just genius
fans like to see more
[Music]
content even if it's just like simple
small fan games like these they're cute
and the fans appreciate that it's really
nice really cool yeah positive feedback
loop exactly and it promotes yeah yeah
it promotes whole life to the outside
too and it's like cool to have you know
whole life games in the first place like
when when there's random people
stumbling across the stream and they're
like oh what is this game that this
person is playing oh it's like their own
game hey yo what cool interesting wow
are they that famous they have their own
games or they have they have like
literally fans making games for them
like so many for free what what what's
going on with that I need to get into
that I need to look into
that why what is this
culture is this a cult actually wait
wait it might just be a
cult
actually now that I say it like that
what is this culture it it's made like
ding ding ding sound in my brain like oh
I think what it actually is is a
cult seems like a very cult cultish
thing doesn't
it okay we got to throw her on top of
your a
oh dangerous dangerous we need some
cleanup soon come
on is there a bon somewhere in there I
think
not yeah B running out of space ah pka's
coming up next and the pka's stuck in
there but we got to squeeze her in when
we can let's let's throw B on here there
space Oh this this could this could
maybe touch but okay well I have another
one and another one
okay this will touch with
Canada right hello touch please final
touch okay okay okay
some some
development still deep in
there but throwing this P there maybe
not the best idea oh no everything think
will be harder to reach but okay I'll do
it
this can go here oh this this might help
no this is difficult now feel like we're
getting closer
to ending it
all now the N need to touch the vamas
need to touch the lamies need to touch
the canas everything I have like
everything double except P obviously now
we're mixing n into the bunch there's
free how are they not touching how are
they not
[Music]
touching oh okay two bons makes one
energy then I'll throw this one on top
of
energy this one
[Music]
too okay okay okay here F to the middle
then the two lamies turn into Nan the
Nan turn into canatan then the canat
might touch the new canatan might touch
of the old
canatan oh okay okay nice what why
not I know oh wait if I thr this here it
will turn into ly and the the two lamies
will touch it's all clearing up
okay oh oh
oh but other is really
far
h well it is what it
is one day one day you meet you meet
your your other
self cannot uh n Touch
N become ly ly if I put n here maybe
they will touch with Lamy too
yeah I love this it's such a great
feeling this is such a great
feeling okay
nice good
position
oh we got a new TOA
Senpai that's pretty good there's still
what is ah B Senpai stuck in there I
don't know if she should be released I
get I I get a new Buton
zai so I should not cover her up now I
should try to bring this
Nan somewhere else
where would be the best maybe next to
Katan here can you can we squeeze it in
what do you think like in between water
and
K N is relatively
small
scary okay come on okay that that
brought her a little bit more towards
the inside I feel
like uh or another Buton after that and
then nity in the
middle let me put protocol here that's
not too
bad put on here because it can turn
it yeah
indeed this is this is difficult because
Lami is pretty big compared to the
others and we'll cover up stuff but as
long if I throw it here uh as long as I
get the button to turn into n in that
moment she will touch the N that's is
below her so even if I cover n up a
little bit from this side it shouldn't
be too bad
I would
say oh God oh God okay she did not stay
where I wanted her to
stay and por is not about to touch the
other P okay okay but here we have some
something will happen here with the nan
thean oh and then she might even touch V
if we're lucky because the N turn into
Canan the Katan turn into V the V will
be next to a
water wait that looked to me like she
was falling off holy [\h__\h] I feel like
she was about to fall
off oh oh my god let's go okay let's
throw this higher for safety okay
good um oh ah wait this just the bounce
made to poras touch I think okay okay
but I'll throw her over
there and here here and one over here
please new Lami order coming
up oh newa
order oh oh nice nice
combination getting rid of the small
ones without
like getting all and covered up in the
in the middle
nice now new let turn so should stay
close to a nanora maybe maybe this one
here though cuz I feel like I can land
it here nicely and then soon there's
another one and they
[Music]
tou this this uh it's a little bit hard
to say like if I throw it like this will
it bounce off the n and fall backwards
towards me again you know what I mean so
I might want to throw it higher but when
I throw higher will it have more bounce
and also be dangerous I don't know
usually usually it seems like they like
catching them almost and keeping them at
Bay literally see it's not so bad
actually not so
dangerous but yeah higher higher is
generally better okay new nity nity
should just stay there then I
guess and Nan turn into k
okay kind of done this
far can't help it oh god oh careful
there make yourself comfortable
please all right two
nanas okay if I place him here in the
middle we can have good chain
reactions probably would be better to
have them here next to this canatan but
the problem is
that it doesn't look as safe over here
as it does over here I don't even
necessarily want to cover up B on Senai
though I don't want to cover her up yet
to be
honest KY has
12K holy
moly why' she do
that damn she cleared cleaned up nicely
I I just noticed like when you're like
going around you're literally like
touching them if they're a little bit
too too far outside huh they collide
with each
other because it's KY period yeah yeah
because KY there needs no other
explanation ah okay I'm I'm really
indecisive about this one
but it would probably fit here I just
don't want to cover up Bon Senai forever
so I'd rather put her
[Music]
here maybe they will but then might as
well just go for this one
[Music]
already but this this one feels
dangerous I know I get another one right
away but I'm trying to think like which
can ofans I want to become vame if I get
this can ofan to become V they can
combine immediately if I make this one
then they're probably not going to
combine
m in front
here that's a bit too dangerous in my
opinion I feel like Nei might push her
off might not happen but I'm too
inexperienced with this game at this
point to see that far
ahead
two I don't know I for whereever
[Music]
okay it's good that I didn't cover up
ban because Ban's
next wait the to are going to touch the
to are going to
[Music]
touch very nice very
nice uh
[Music]
I don't know where to put her
now cuz n I'm obviously throwing over
here so I don't want to cover up n too
much but if I just throw her like over
her that it shouldn't be too
bad oh nice she just she just stays
there and chills
[Music]
they're not too energetic I like that um
this
[Music]
lety let's for her
here the can combin
[Music]
into that to be closer to flare well I
don't know I can't do much about that it
will just happen
when when time and fate Collide when
the oceans and the sky meets each other
at the closest point when the Moon
Rises
uh and the sun rises at the same time
when the stars shine
brighter than the lights of
[Music]
Tokyo you know you know it's just
eventually going to happen I cannot do
anything about it I would say I I
wouldn't want to risk
it maybe I should have done that over
here
actually
well want to squeeze her in there so she
stays close to por but as long as
paa's there she might just get like
covered I should keep that open still
until I wait I'm getting a paa next okay
okay then maybe
higher and over here please okay nice
and touch and touch n
please I'll force you
then throw her here throw her
[Music]
there there and over there wow and here
and
tou no B on left right but there's still
the last pora in there doesn't feel good
doesn't feel good at all
here's a lot of space Here's a decent
amount of
[Music]
space n coming
next N I would just maybe throw on top
to meet
lammie I'll put her
here oh there's another Lamie ah in that
case right here or L me there no I
didn't touch [\h__\h] I should have thrown
higher from the other
side okay well everything will sort
itself
out you don't see it she's there there
there there there there there there
there there you need to look
closer for the hidden ones in between
read between the
lines see between the whole life members
[Music]
nice okay a lot of lamies here Lami
becomes nanora there's no nanora right
now but we got two lamies okay we can
make two
Nanas and the nanas will become canatan
so we want to keep them close to the
canatan so first of
all one here and then one
here I thought she was safe she waited a
moment to fall down no
[Music]
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] 5,700
[Music]
okay why is one say 5,700 but this says
free what what's that other
score it's a good
round she's trolling me
why did she decide why did she change
her
mind okay I'll do my best to
live keep on
living oh nice
nice nice push I was hoping for that I
didn't think it would go that strongly
do you understand do you understand
I
[Music]
understand going fast
now I'm on the
highway I'm on the highway
to SC keeps on showing
up the shark can
see I should have done the other one oh
well that's okay
that's
nice okay by the way guys I'm not going
to spoil it but I did see the newest and
the last house of the Dragon episode of
the
season I thought something completely
different was going to happen because I
I kind of saw like something that I
thought was a spoiler like a screenshot
that I thought was a spoiler
and so when I was watching I was hoping
it it was wrong or I saw it differently
I saw it wrong or so and I was but I was
thinking something was going to happen
that did not happen at all so then I was
kind of relieved but the whole the whole
episode long I was so anxious and like
awaiting the thing that I thought I
saw and just yeah I was so
scared so scared that was going to
happen
[Music]
like every scene I was like oh is it
going to happen now is it going to
happen now is is it what about now hey
it's not happening now okay maybe
[Music]
now
yeah yeah I see a lot of complaints
that like it should have had two more
episodes or so the whole season if
they're going to leave it at
that I mean I I would always whoop
appreciate more episodes of
course
um and I would have also of course
appreciated more progress on the
story yeah like I can't even really I
couldn't even spoiler much from this
episode because what really actually
happened the one thing I'll say
though the one thing I was talking about
like what yesterday or the day before
yesterday did kind of happen when I was
like hey guys do you think this will
happen and you guys were like No And I
was like H sad but it did kind of
[Music]
happen or certain someone showed up I
kind of called it yeah I'm so happy I
was
like I'm going to tell everybody that
somehow what I was hoping for kind of
happened my intuition just something
gave me the feeling you know that she
that's definitely what she's
kind of planning to do but um not in the
same way as I was hoping for a little
bit different but it kind of happened
anyway everything I'm saying is so
vag people don't watch House of the
Dragon are probably like what the [\h__\h]
talking
about what is she talking
[Music]
about but then I was really surprised
guys I
saw girls calm down I saw that uh
there's like what is it a spin-off uh
Game of Thrones spin-off uh like a
trailer a teaser teaser was released
some teasing footage was released for
what was it called again uh some some
big tall Knight dude the Hedge Knight
oh it's a
spin-off and the fact that they already
have footage to show a teaser makes me
think M middle or early 2025
maybe Duncan the tall I've never heard
about that part of story before
never yeah they're working on several
things but the fact that they have
footage for that makes me makes me
hopeful that it's not going to be too
long to see that
[Music]
don't bounce so much
nice indeed I'm going to get this pora
stuck forever in the void
again the dunk and egg novels which are
fun and short dunk and egg what a weird
name are those stories finished
when did he write
those yeah yeah they're working on so
many let's let's
go I'm happy because like if that comes
out 2025 then the way to 2026 for hotd
season 3 won't be
too you know unbearable I
think egg is a nickname for
eggon makes sense
but egg eggun doesn't show up in it does
he bask what basketball what the [\h__\h]
are you talking
about it didn't look like basketball in
that
teaser it better not be about [\h__\h]
basketball I don't want to see a Game of
Thrones basketball
show
h
Huh what are you talking talk about the
show PL six episode season okay that's
short but at least that's something
new to get over the time I hope it's not
too late in
[Music]
2025 talking to each other I what they
talking about
nity nity can you stay on top of Bon
somehow or Dare that's fine
thanks
[Music]
nice sh I need to focus what
becomes I don't know oh nice I didn't
even think
[Music]
House of the Dragon Ball that becomes
another different
[Music]
show
here what's of all these smaller ones
huh too many of
them okay
[Music]
this is not a good run but I'm hoping it
will it will become better if I just
keep on keep on
hoping okay she just
said something controversial oops are
better the bigger they
are Mone zai I mean I like boobs too but
don't we like them in all sizes
H come on
no no why' you go
there this so quick
[Music]
don't oppress the
chest medium is premium flat is Justice
beautiful words beautiful
[Music]
phrases I don't I don't really hear such
beautiful poetic phrases about the
male
genitalia I feel a bit sorry for
that double
standard of
C why why not why not
[Music]
why I mean it's not I'm not going to
come up with them for you guys you got
to come up with
them you got to come up with them I'm
not going to do it for you but I I'm
just saying like would be nice if you
guys had that kind of you know poetic
phrase too thank you thank you for your
sake
there I wish those NES would have
touched I really wish they would have
touched but they don't so now I don't
know where to put the N maybe here
[Music]
trade offer I give you two canas you
give me one right next to a and then you
give me a to point how about that so I
push let me push
him let me push him again yes
[Music]
me and shiy no no no no maybe shiy and
bails I don't know baited the pee
stream I don't want to be involved in
that
[Music]
um w w
where should we go that maybe
[Music]
here I watch a little bit of mum's live
birthday live it was so pretty
especially like at the
end that song
Alice when she sang it first when I just
saw the tile I wasn't sure what what
what that song was but then I heard her
sing it I was like ah this song
was so nice with the acoustic
guitar very very
beautiful she sings
like like no
other such
a talented talented
[Music]
individual God
Marine is going to pee herself good to
know I can't put that there n is going
to fall
off is holding on so strongly I don't
know how to help her oh okay okay yeah
we got to make her fall tumble backwards
somehow is there something there no
behind um now transforming her now might
be
safe relatively
safe what just happened it optical
illusion of her Falling Towards me
because I got another one okay okay okay
okay okay go over there
[Music]
oh wait interesting things about to
happen nanora become kanatan kanatan is
over there
oh say by so close to each
other it's not over yet it's not over
yet ah addicting
game if I put over there that's just
going to separate the bamas for a while
longer but I
don't I should have thr higher what is
that thing inside the island
[Music]
anyway one more one
more let's go let's go no time to
waste that was not a good run General
from the
beginning so I had no hopes for that
anyway this is for example good this is
a good start this is how a good run
begins you know
it you know looking
nice do you understand
[Music]
yeah 2K still a good score thank
you now we're going to get to see
oi don't ask
me okay okay this is a this is a good
run this very different from previously
don't you
think like what was the what was all
these like combinations I had before
just getting too crowded
[Music]
but yeah that that Thro from me that
ended everything that was that was my
fault the frow was my fault but it was
kind of doomed anyway
[Music]
thank you thank you just change your
ranking
and yeah I could do that I know I can
change it around I know I know but I
don't want to I don't want to I'm fine
with
[Music]
this she's like b b faster what
what what she what are these phrases
from I need I need references I need
links just like in the Wikipedia article
I need you to link to every single
phrase where you pick that up from from
which
stream I need
context no context is not
[Music]
acceptable you want to know the context
I want to know the context yes I want to
know the birthing
[Music]
context maybe she did a birth child
birth simulator stream you know that
would explain
everything oh why is she so close to the
edge I don't like that I don't like that
do you think it will kill us if I throw
it on
her maybe it kind of looks like
[Music]
probably
YOLO YOLO
[Music]
oh it's all
still oh and now okay if I make n into
canatan I don't think she will fall down
I think she will combine with the other
one that was close that was close she
was tipping over
okay okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
is very
very those to us why don't they
touch oh they touch we got sire again
[Music]
cleaning up this is like my second run
again
y I can push them I can
[Music]
p me like it
likey
likey okay careful
[Music]
higher wom on woman action
hot oh my God there's so much yapping
cuz I'm so
fast twice mentioned
[Music]
yes me lucky me lucky lucky lucky me
lucky lucky
[Music]
lucky I don't want to cover those up
maybe on top is okay because she'll turn
into
lummy oh oh oh okay interesting not what
I expected
[Music]
close but now I'm going to separate them
kind of
unless because if I'm don't P her here
like I don't know but if I if I I don't
think necessarily they will ever
touch even if I put but on somewhere
else now there's still like two
separated from P andan lying
here I'm just going to go for it I'm
just going to make another Bai somewhere
[Music]
else careful there careful
there
careful what rid can't really get rid of
her unless I get a PKA now I want the
pka you know but they don't give me the
pka when I want the
pka I'm going to try to throw n really
far where is where is
that this weird kind of hard to
understand I would like the angle to be
a little bit more from above like a tiny
bit it's like
this looks like it goes closer to me
than this even though this should be
further out you know what I mean this
looks like it might go behind
protocol but this should be
closer this should be further away this
should be even even further
away it's confusing
[Music]
me is it is it on purpose
M oh
well can we get her in there I think
[Music]
so I think I forever
covered that b up in
[Music]
there oh God oh God oh God it's over
I know but I kind of had to do it I kind
of had to try
it
Ah that's a good run
man
[Music]
can't go next go next let me drink my PO
sweat
that was a good run it was a lucky run
good
[Music]
combinations too
energetic much yapping in the
[Music]
beginning okay this looks good again I
think generally it's harder to have a
shitty run than it is to have a good run
I only had one like shitty run I would
say so
far how far do you get if you just Spam
it and spin it around oh I want to try
that kind of maybe I'll try
afterwards but then if we get to like a
good point I don't know if I cannot like
if I can resist stopping and just like
properly continuing it in the proper way
if I can really pull
through who
whoa
hello
you so beautifully purple
[Music]
today oh my God so much so much juming
I'm going to turn a little bit after
all I've heard enough I've heard enough
now 20% makes not much difference
[Music]
anyway now that I've been playing it for
a while though I think I'm fine with the
controls I don't have a problem with it
not being
Mouse I think I'm fine with it
okay I got used to
it wasn't there I guess not thought
there was another P but this is
[Music]
fine I'm on a
roow w
w by so
[Music]
early she was eager to come back to
me and cheer me up
[Music]
why is she so
nice
W
Speedy
Gonzalez
that what what am I doing sorry what am
I doing I don't know what I'm doing why
is she
there that was a misro
kind
ofor will maybe [\h__\h] us up I I should
maybe push her in I don't know I don't
know if I
can I I don't know
y sorry how do I get I can kind of yeah
yeah yeah this pushes her doesn't it is
she further inom before maybe
okay maybe we're
fine I'll save you
eventually woohoo okay why don't you
don't you want to roll further inside
there's more space
[Music]
now oh if I follow her here maybe they
combine more towards the
left nice okay
problem
Sol this should be a phone
game I actually like more Hall life fan
games to um be made for phone game um
not to be played on the phone but just
like uh play to be uh for vertical
streams so that I can do vertical
streams with them
[Music]
please game developer this shouldn't be
too hard to rearrange into
vertical shouldn't be too hard I think
there's not too much going on on the
screen no no no please di please Di
please
dibs does that have a is that
vertical
[Music]
heyy no listen to me this I st like you
know I I I I have to like you know think
of the growth of the
channel and it's like one vertical
stream every once in a while will not
kill
you let's do it let's do it guys you
have to think like me like a business
woman you always like praise me for my
business lady like merchandise and
sponsorship selling skills I get so
why don't you why don't you like you
know want to learn from my vertical
stream thoughts huh at least I'm I'm not
spamming
them but I'm looking for good
opportunities to use it to utilize
it thanks for the
raid I did not know where to put that
that's fine no why don't you fall down
this way to meet the other
one
what that was not according to Kaku
before there there was
[Laughter]
[Music]
no okay one of the poras which one do
you want choose your
poison
[Music]
okay it turns
into just like how XX X XX turns into
something else too
[Music]
wow
amazing fascinating is there a word for
that uh
phenomenon
[Music]
careful don't no go wherever
oh it's getting so
crowded this
[Music]
bad okay okay okay more of that please
okay touch touch nice
nice oh nice okay okay we we're getting
good choices we're getting good
ones is there
yes okay
uh what do you think will happen if I
throw the nanola towards a
nanola yeah it's it's generous of
snapping back mhm I feel like I can also
like if I'm right there I can kind of
like hold it I I I I'm like a
wall I think it will be fine
yeah because it will fuse of can down
huh
a but like for a moment it's really like
about to fall off it's so
scary hey you're supposed to fall down I
thre her too far maybe I can push
her yeah
woohoo they're about to touch and we get
and we get
full now I don't really want to
transform the Bon because that feels
like it might keep them from
transforming actually let me throw her
here I'm getting another one anyway and
push and push
and push and push and push and push
harder push harder
push pushing
successful nice push okay all right all
right
[Music]
talking really yippy moments there we're
getting a lot of smaller ones again
okay congratulations on the bir thank
you is that yeah is that what she
means no because like that you know if
she recorded the phrases for this then
that would make sense but I think
they're just taking from streams which
makes it funnier
anyway no let me why why you always are
the death of me why
I got a new
one he
y
okay but it went so well I had
a okay wait so what instead of ban
Senpai we have Aki Senpai there now oh
okay okay that's going to have to get
used to that
wait I thought this was all all the
choices I had no I guess not actually I
looked before the stream I looked into
like the unlockable characters I saw
that they were unlockable characters why
didn't I
realize let's
go that's
[Music]
exciting I didn't really like
realize
consciously what my options will be
[Music]
voice lines
yay I
know friend
shaped is it all Japan yeah yeah there's
no English or ID members as far as I
know but maybe maybe they all them think
there is
potential
[Music]
po where you going
do you want to
[Music]
touch don't you want to
touch that phras so funny like very
politely and properly she says yes we're
thinking about uh starting to date yes
indeed what is she saying that about is
she saying that about
but Shon or
or who could she be saying that about
who did she say that
about seems like a famous phrase that
maybe we've heard in the clip before
wooo saying it about me uh-huh yeah sure
she's saying it about you yeah totally
totally
totally I think maybe she
oh she said it again she said it again
kind of no that was a different one
actually but similar
[Music]
topic we have an En
no oh
God they're more bouncy than
just my
[Music]
imagination where you going
now
careful
[Music]
okay why these Braes are
she now she said yes M will try her best
to not flash or like let her her boobs
fall
[Music]
out see don't you also want the context
for this and then listen to
more from where that came
from me personally
yes but I want to get it like in there
yeah
[Music]
kind of crowded kind of not the best run
kind of a messy
one okay wait so let's combine
here
[Music]
ohai might be
touching and then the TOs can
touch I should push him what I want to
push him
[Music]
you think she's too big to be squeezed
in
there think she will fall off she's
always a downfall to
me don't trust the L
me Luna is just bigger but look at the
Luna size it's not that big maybe we can
maybe we can fit oh okay it didn't
really push it didn't necessarily
push okay let me do let me combine
these okay even more choice
to to find a mating mating
[Music]
sheep speaking of sheep sheep stealer
I'm so excited for that I'm so excited
for sheep stealer
but I guess we don't get to see that huh
not yet got to wa two [\h__\h]
years but from the from the one scene we
saw like sheep Stiller on the ground
sorry a little bit of spoiler but I mean
sheep sealer has been around all the
time I like the looks of sheep sealer
somehow the the like tips the inside
tips of the the wings the Cur the the
claws or what I'm not really claws I
don't know what how to describe it but
it looks kind of curled and
cute I don't think sheep steel is
necessarily supposed to look cute but
someh look pretty cute to
me over here is good
wow wow wow
[Music]
no let's
go nice there was a a toora creation
there a double one it happened really
fast could barely witness
it
no whatever is that that's a pora down
there I think not a a Senai I'm pretty
sure the hair color P's hair color is a
little bit more ashy than akis senpai's
blonde yeah sheep is a wild one but I
think I think they will pair
up I think they will because like what
else would all that build up be
for like for her to just get eaten or
what I don't think
so that would be such a weird story to
write
they even parachute no I think that
would make no sense like as a writer as
a story riter like I I don't know man
that's just a boring and they're heavily
implying it I don't think so I think
they will pair up because like he will
he will like see how she has a lot of
pass he will feel the passion and
the the ambition she has to get this
particular Dragon like I think the
dragon will feel that you
know
yes rather than seeing it you know as
thank you thank you something to eat
okay I need the pora in there though oh
nice oh I didn't think that would go
that
well this should be okay this should be
okay this should be okay okay
[Music]
ni difficult if we bounce against n
okay worth it stks they seem to have C
actually the show I heard about it
nettle Nettles right but like how long
was that person sheeps as actual writer
in the
books what happened I need to maybe
maybe alt shift has a video on that one
[\h__\h] I have a cramp in my left foot in
in the foot part not in the leg part
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] it'll go away well I just have to
keep on stretching
stretching she stays right until they
both disappear
oh a no I I I think yeah alchi also
talked about I mentioned Nettles a few
times but it seems like they're kind of
combining
the existence of nettles and what was
her name
Raina I think they're kind of combining
them into one person more or less which
is I think fine because it seems like
nettles on her own was not very
significant to the story but then does
Raina in the books ever get a
dragon a different one or is she just
never writing
anything please tell me book readers
please tell me
[Music]
and if she never gets a dragon does that
mean that Nettles with sheep saaler
joints when you signed braa gets morning
who's a baby
ah okay so she never does she never end
up writing a dragon properly in the
books and does nles join rira after the
war her egges
ah damn I see
mhm yeah she's taking of the care of the
so yes is that yes for N J F yeah no
actually I think I like it better than
this way I I know people generally want
to go with how the book is but uh is
this like an unpopular change I wouldn't
say so right I haven't heard much
outrage about it from like the AL shift
[Music]
Community n's team black is re okay
oh no okay don't spoil too much
guys don't spoil too much now has a
weird thinging with Damon the CL
attention but they seem to scra them oh
don't worry there's attention from
different reasons anyway so they make
they create tension anyway no one can
prove she's a Taran so she frows into
question who can actually come Nal for
Nal it's like not known if she's tarian
or like DED or like said that she's not
Taran interesting no Taran and also no
Valyrian blood because like there's like
these thoughts that maybe valerium blood
is fine too
right sh
cool if you never seen the show then I
don't think these spoilers I don't think
you would even remember them at the
point where you start watching the show
in the future if you plan on doing
[Music]
that that's how it is for me usually
like I don't even remember any I've ever
been spoed about if I watch such a thing
like two or three years
later she's T she tamed sheepa by giving
him sheep that's cute that's so easy
that's so simple and I mean as I said
previously I feel like sheep are just a
general choice of food for any dragon
really why
not she wasn't she just offered sheep
pap
what that's so
funny maybe it's like
the wait how
does maybe the wild dragons can be
ridden by
any nonar valan blood kind of
person maybe that's how it works maybe
they don't give a [\h__\h] about that and
then the ones who are kind of like breed
breeded within you know the or already
existing cycle of taryan
dragons those are being raised there and
you
know I don't know who knows really right
nobody really [\h__\h] knows
anything
but interesting
[Music]
interesting no need to get there too
bad ah I don't like this ah I don't like
I don't like this I don't like this ah
you going you going you
going not much
space not much space at
all
okay okay
okay cleaned up a little bit I'm afraid
that blood has nothing to do with it and
they just serve whoever they sense is
wor um I think it has be both someone
who's worthy and blood but it could also
be just worthiness and it just being a
coincidence that often the wory people
are to garans but that's just because
how who they're usually offered to like
of course not many other people are
going to get a chance to get a dragon
and show that they're worthy of usually
until that point dragons were usually
just offered to full-blooded
tarians there's just no other like
examples that could be made right
[Music]
we've reached the chill uh Zam part of
the stream where we just come up with
random Game of Thrones theories I was
really surprised that they showed so
many like Game of Thrones related things
in this last
episode and it felt so it almost felt
like a filler but it was also cool like
an out shift I heard the part where he
mentioned that a lot of tarians have
visions of the far future like the White
Walker stuff so it's not we super weird
for that to be
seen but still felt like they just like
took an opportunity to fill the episode
with something that already exists and
doesn't really progress the story at
all they just they just don't want to I
just it just felt like a big filler
episode didn't
it I kind of
[Music]
did um where from here maybe okay ah Dy
dangerous push
push such a
mess yeah that
much not good what if I throw her in
there is it going to be
bad
okay that was
good okay
nice she F over because I like it's
really good to stay where you just threw
it so so you can kind of protect
it they just skip to the wall whatever
right away people would still be
complaining I don't know I guess the war
would have been too long to squeeze it
in there they really should have just
made two more episodes then maybe they
could have squeeze it in there well I
don't really know the story so I can't
really say
that they could have done it confidently
maybe they really couldn't have done it
I don't think this a good idea to put uh
the Lamy there is it probably not feel
like it's dangerous and Nami is always a
downfall of me
could have also because I see
[Music]
W thank
you well yeah I I
think it it's all right like I could
have seen it coming that the the war
will not happen in the season could have
seen it
[Music]
coming can I put her there
what do you
think become
n maybe on
top like very but this is too that'll be
too far kind of want to put it right on
top of her so she will become a non
where she is let's see okay protection
activat oh let's go oh y okay oh y
woohoo
yum she flipped again is there is there
AK down
there has to
[Music]
be not going to
merge it's too crowded I need to throw
them on
top but like wait no turns into nanora
so close to this nanola would be
good is is the downfall of me like
literally holy [\h__\h] but kind of yeah I
saw that coming I for too Loosely
again my gu oh well that was my that was
my fourth highest score
[Music]
okay why
L she hates me
[Music]
freaking yapping man we need a whole
English and ID version of
this so that non Japanese speakers can
enjoy all these like
yappers all these phrases all these
random stream
phrases but it should probably be
someone who speaks English who chooses
the phrases so they should like team up
with someone who speaks fluent English
[Music]
insane she's so
crazy my partical attention no that's
never ending no we can't put that in
there it has to be shorter
qu on knak as we like to say in
German short and um crunchy not quite
crunchy Kake is more like you know like
a sausage when when a sausage is like it
has like like not a crunch to it but how
do you say that in English Snappy yeah
short and
snappy snappy
[Music]
M I want a nice Like Remix like this I
could work as a endless bgm for my own
songs need to
[Music]
commission I want something like this
cuz they're so addicting all these like
H remix is
true
[Music]
so by the way you remember my recent
member stream where I was like yapping
about these new
[Music]
hires both of those hires ended up
watching the
stream both of them watched it
embarrassing I did not take them
seriously when one of them was like oh
I'm going to watch it then if if you
talk about it in the member stream I
will become a member I'm like you're not
going to really do that are you no way
underestimated that's
[Music]
completely welcome to
kfp the land where
you're frying fast food dreams come true
[Music]
this is not too bad it's a bit messy
looking but it's not too bad I'm like
building
up building up guys trust the
process
like
trust this process oh okay
a
stay no n n yes yes
[Music]
n trust the
process I'm hungry I'm
hungry today I had for breakfast my
cereal and and I only have one serving
left and I had a salad a tuna egg
uh uh lettuce
carrot and corn
salad with g s sesame
dressing favorite
dressing and then I had some apple this
is before the
stream but at least you know I had
something resembling of a
lunch salad just a small one but that's
[Music]
fine
nice lack of protein that's okay I'll
get the protein maybe for my dinner
you guys remember that tweet I did about
the sesame dressing the GMA
dressing some of you a lot of you guys
were really confused about the about me
saying that it's a common phrase to say
Curry is a drink it's like a
joke it's not really like that people
really see it as a drink and drink it
out of a glass it's just a joke that
people say because they love curry so
much so also me saying sesame dressing
should be a drink it's a joke but
actually I'm lowkey serious about it but
actually it's a
joke no a lot of people were confused
about it they also say that about Mayon
yeah but I hear it more often from Curry
and then it became such a phrase meme
phrase that there's a there is a
restaurant chain I think that has that
name cures a drink in
Japanese so really really proves you
they love curry but like Japanese Curry
particularly usually Japanese
Curry I wouldn't drink it I would
personally not drink
[Music]
it okay okay no no we're talking
andno being placed in the middle is
actually really good once it is mating
season it will happen
immediately easily she has access to
every direction
what
what mate the mates they're all her
mates gen mates and uh other gen
mates you know it's the season of the
mates
[Music]
careful
care okay nice
ah oh no
[Music]
ah here is good ni
all push push
push push
harder B will be lost in there
forever sacrifices have to be made
[Music]
aming season
baby ni St made it's
true can we get this one in there too
cuz now there's an a sire lost in there
H she'll get there she'll get there she
a she's getting
we leave no one
behind oh I don't know what just
happened but it's
nice nice there's so much space
[Music]
now they made it they have made it
both self says yeah you know I'm I'm a
big supporter of self and loving
yourself so I really hope there's an end
version of this someday so I can mate
myself with
myself that would be
ideal you got to love yourself you got
to show yourself some love if you don't
love yourself how can anybody love you
you know you
know you know how it is okay this is not
nice because I don't want to cover up
these girls at the top even n or AK sire
I think I can squeeze n in
here dangerous dangerous she she went
somewhere
unexpected but it all worked out
[Music]
okay that's like comparable with all
those crazy like random
asss from the S game all those
incidents that never happened before
holy [\h__\h] she went to the complete
opposite side she went way too far she
just like she did she felt like she was
uh competing in the Olympics doing those
million flips and diving into the water
but she made a big [\h__\h]
Splash so not getting uh not getting any
medals from
that holy moly she went so far oh my
God holy moly why why would you do that
it was I was so
farun now it's impressive that my second
try was my high score so far why was my
second try so good was that my a
different try I think the second try was
the best so
[Music]
far I like this game
I like these kind of
cute cute mindless
games I welcome
more especially if they were whole life
girls better
[Music]
friend shaped to life girls
yeah second the first try and a lot of
things ends up being the
best yeah it's not like I had some any
any kind of technique figured out or
something
just random
getting
lucky didn't do anything in a special
[Music]
way this is this is going okay so
far wow
H where are you going how you sticking
up there and she goes
down stay there it's safer
[Laughter]
[Music]
beginner's
luck yeah that do be a thing it's
real real yo
[Music]
today I finally decided what I want for
my 2024 outfit and it's not what we
originally decided on I think but it was
one of the options I think one of the
things I talked about at least I
think yeah just had like a a realization
a moment of Enlightenment and it's
definitely something I will probably
make a lot of use out of and something
that will be
very use you
know and perhaps
overused if if it turns
out like drawn in a way that I
like you know
everything comes together nicely then
I'll probably even overuse it like this
outfit like this one
[Music]
and I've also set the things in motion
now properly with the fish nut ties and
stuff uh for the fite outfit but I don't
think it will make it for the
anniversary no no no no it will need
longer than that
probably but that's okay there's already
a lot of stuff going on if think during
anniversary uh during September at least
I
mean fishnet yeah that was the original
plan I wanted
fishnet tight as an
option to change into because yeah
that's the thing like once I reveal
those accessories I'm also finally going
to reveal the the skirt version because
the skirt already exists I have it in my
accessory options for the f outf it but
I I originally planned to have that with
fish tights and I didn't like it at all
it doesn't look good in my own opinion
with
the normal
leggings so I never showed it it just
doesn't look right to me I need to wait
until I have something that looks nice
and they didn't want to give me the fish
ties backck down because they said that
doesn't fit the feur so I do not agree
with that at
all and somehow apparently it has to
like fit within the bee unless it's an
accessory that's added later on then
it's forgiven well well well okay then
you know then I'm not ring the skirt
yet careful
there it is what it is but um I think it
will almost feel like a a second outfit
reveal because I'll have a skirt like
different different uh bottom
different
tights and possibly very possibly also a
new hairstyle to go with
it that's like basically a new
outfit it won't look like a new outfit I
think the only thing that pretty much
stays the same is the the blue sweater
but I'm also requesting to be able to
take off the blue sweater and have only
the the tatas out okay not only the
tatas there's still the leotard covering
it but you know what I mean right
this is also uh you know something that
has been
[Music]
requested this is dangerous PA what are
we going to do about this risk it for
the biscuit oh
wow I don't like the situation we're
finding ourselves
in not going to put another a there no
[Music]
no can you guys like get closer over to
the other side pleas this outfit gets
better and better yeah yeah yeah like
built
upon what I have just like with this
outfit like it has
really um have to
say it has
evolved into un unimaginable levels
[Music]
just go wherever I'm kind
of lost here I need some kind of big
Kaboom let me let me
careful I need some miracle
[Music]
now okay well we didn't get that far so
it's it doesn't hurt as
[Music]
much hey
laminator laminator
funny should be
[Music]
merchandised there so nois in the
beginning Mama Mia oh oh B bf b it's the
BF
[Music]
a birth
canal I think that is a problem word
right am I combining German and
English
maybe push
[Music]
push maybe the trick is to away when you
throw
[Music]
it for a part of the female anatomy is
cor okay so there's a birth canal
right it's a real word it's just Y no
it's not what is your B about birth
you've been
birthed it's just natural
nothing you bu about birth bth should be
wholesome and beautiful and emotional
and
moving and a
miracle nothing a buy about that thought
that
[Music]
was difference you hatching but hatching
is also wholesome and and a beautiful
moment to be treasured
forever
definitely so same thing basically you
should feel the same way about
it just because that's not how you birth
doesn't mean that that it's different
it's the same any kind of birth of a new
creature living
thing is
something to be crying about
[Music]
you know how I wanted to do whole talk
um with Justice Just like how I did it
for Advent I wanted to do it like right
away but then the schedules didn't
align and
uh it's so it hasn't been happening and
and then now it's like know I was too
busy to do it
and yeah and then time passing so I feel
like now it's like weird like if I do it
now not no of course not for you you
guys are always going to be like do it
anyway it's not weird it's not weird but
it it should be like right away you
know just like with
Advent and it bothers me that it's not
right away it's not that's not how it's
how I Envision it you know and so I'm
like not sure I also don't want to not
do it because I did it for ad have to do
it is true but the timing is just wrong
now but
then when I met laa again
recently she was
like please can I stand F please can I
stand fine please I really I love H talk
please let's do it let's do it let's do
it and she's like so motivated and so
eager and she really wants it to
happen and I love her so I feel like I
have to do it for
her and she said she watched every holot
talk episode until now and I'm like
what
okay I I I'll do it for
her what
she watched every Holo talk
episode that changes
everything she actually loves the show
she really loves it and really
appreciates it and really wants to be in
it I can't break her
dreams I have to make it happen
now I appreciate that because like you
know
watching someone else's streams like
that's not a
given and then she says she wanted
everything and that's a project that's
really important to
me so you
know that was like a special moment for
me when she said that I was
like
what no way every
episode so if you watch every episode
I'm I'm sure like when
she when she found out that she was
joining whole life for sure she was
probably like already envisioning the
day when she gets interviewed in whole
talk I would be doing that if I was
her
so I have to make that a
[Music]
reality H talk merory around at some
point
[Music]
H yeah probably not this this year
because I think it would be too late to
plan
that wa wa what happened I don't
[Music]
know
nice thank you thank you this is a good
run I would like to announce that this
is a good run
everybody we got to be careful with the
lumies always got to be careful with the
lumies thank God as long as it turns
into a nan everything is cool
everything's
[Music]
safe don't announce while holding L yeah
for real could have ended poorly yep I
know felt like very risky
[Music]
Endeavor maybe in here
I have no
space okay I have plenty of space should
be
fine thank you thank
you phes are
worrying okay this combines disco bins
disco
binds would you be down to share yeah
okay I've been asked this uh before also
by uh ston
directly I didn't answer because I
didn't know what I
wanted then I don't know then I forgot
about it
um I don't
know I guess it's
fine just I don't know because like I
don't know sure I guess
this sure
sure I I just had to think about it
because it's different from other models
because I I other models that are like
fan-made or even publicly H not public
uh official official
model
like you guys you guys I don't know how
to explain this
like cuz I paid for this but you guys
going to get them get it for free it
feels a little bit weird to
me but it's okay like I want to see what
you guys would create with
it shouldn't be missing out on
that on the great things you guys can do
with the model don't do anything weird
with
it what do you want us to pay you for it
no no I mean that makes no sense
either that makes no sense
either just make some cute stuff
[Music]
it
crack no there was just no other case
like this that I could compare it
to like like a case for me where this
happened before
like not
sure what's the best thing
here Shing
[Music]
this can drop it in membership oh
well I don't know about that either
because
that's that that is isn't that like
ethically wrong for me to
do cuz then I would make even more money
from it like it's kind of like offering
it I don't know it's like you guys are
paying for it but you shouldn't be
paying for
it no no it's fine it's fine just take
it just take
it take it
before I changed my
mind
no this is a good run we have a in the
middle this is like big potential
but you bought it to make more money not
directly but I guess
so but you know I don't I don't know it
can be
public it can't be
public people who love me so much to be
using the model like
that are often members
[Music]
anyway I don't think I can get anybody
to join the membership to get the model
anyway like you're probably already a
member
or or you don't want it
[Music]
thatly she looks so happy
there so ly let me tell you if you fall
down you're not going to be happy
anymore you're going to be eaten so if
you want to keep your happiness the way
it is
now then you should stay where you
[Music]
are oh my second highest
score man like with f in the middle it
was so good she's still there she's
still there and annoy her too oh my
God is that
a who's that over
there not a pic right there didn't there
wasn't a pic creation there right
[Music]
no like everybody fell down there just
like
busted that was two times man
unfortunately that was a good score
though good
score I think I see now what's like a a
pretty common score to get is probably
around 3,000 and all that is it's like a
good run already so I shouldn't take KY
as my reference at
all right have you guys played this what
are you best
[Music]
scores the Lamy on your hands to stop
the Lamy on the edge
H I don't know I can't think anymore how
the situation
was not yet but I'm considering do it do
it do it do it do it do it do it do
it 5,800 4,200 wow how long have you
been trying though longer than me
right 5,000 6 oh my God he got 16 nah no
way but then that then Kyla wouldn't be
the high
score
uh way did she do it off screen or on
screen sh off stream
[Music]
that would have been an epic run like
the moment you're over like 12K or so
start the
stream you have to stream dad you can't
just do that off stream if you're
already that far in start the freaking
stream why are you hiding that
[Music]
what if being on stream maker do worse
doesn't nah I don't think that's she's
so used to streaming it's her job I
don't think for her doesn't seem like
streaming makes her worse at games for
me I feel like uh it is the case part
oh [\h__\h]
sorry I feel like for me that that can
be
said you guys just don't know you
wouldn't believe me but it's true I
think but I thinka is just so good at
like multitasking and handling all of
that at the same time that it doesn't
affect her I
think not as bad as me at least I think
I think
wait was that a there Dam it I should
have thrown it
there no no
[Music]
no just
sneeze
me okay like it's possibly my fault too
of course but like she's just so
unpredictable she's just so
unpredictable look at all these
[Music]
comos careful careful careful push push
push push
care I want to
more she scares
me what if I no I can't I can't you're
[Music]
risky a she's she's
relatively safe there I think relatively
it's not too bad
byebye where are you
going wait it put it instead of AK no no
no no no put it like instead of somebody
else super
super um here oh yeah these are
Treasures okay uh then let's switch like
these yeah I want more of the new
[Music]
ones okay I'm not going to switch to
position of P Senpai it has to be Pea in
the end it has to
be the the feeling of achievement you
know could you turn down the voices a B
sure
funny Fon yeah no I like pora in there
but I wonder if akis Senpai with her
twin tails is actually like kind of
um a
[Music]
problem like if they tend to be in the
way in certain situations where if she
didn't have twin Tails
if some things would go better I don't
know
could that
be somebody needs to test that out for
[Music]
science yeah I wonder if it has a a hit
box if it doesn't then no problem I
would hope it doesn't because she her
twins are way longer than for example
picas but picas is bigger as a whole
like
[Music]
looks so cute in this
form so
cute I love it
yes yes yes you got you got P oh my
God the coll doesn't have to match the
object can just be a perfect
Spar yeah if that is
so then my question is
answered sufficiently
[Music]
SE oh no in the middle let's keep her in
the middle because she can eventually
turn
into
there that's
good I'm going to surround her
purposefully
[Music]
now so that she doesn't flip to the side
I think midle is always like
ideal it's coming
needs to be cleaned up oh nice nice nice
nice
[Music]
nice I need more sa voice lines
more say
something
impression but that would be really
painful on my Thro I
think but I can
do kind of right but a whole
stream's but now that I think about it
so there's a few ones where I could
potentially usually do just like short
phrases so I don't have to do a full
stream of the same
person just do a to where you choose who
you're
calling but even that is kind of like
high level of skill necessary to perform
properly cuz I need to be able to like
spit out random phrases as that person
and not just like
but it would be a funny
idea actually herb should do that she
she should do a to a call-in stream
where the caller will choose who they're
talking
to I hope she does that sometime maybe I
should plant that idea in her head maybe
it's already in her head who knows
[Music]
push push H this will turn nice nice
nice nice relatively nicely
aligned a challenge was made for
[Music]
I gotta go for full P stream I think so
too but what else will I be doing what's
what's going to be like do I play a
game do
I do a
[Music]
PO do I
do what do I do you
know there should be more like oh God oh
God
[Music]
that should be more of a concept
there D it why' you go
there dangerous dangerous dangerous
dangerous dangerous
[Applause]
[Music]
dangerous there's an enti there oh in
there too
I don't know I don't know I don't
[Music]
know
Minecraft I need like a proper reason to
be like something that makes sense to be
impersonating
her sorry man no why did I do that why
was I so
careless why was I so
careless need to be more careful careful
K careful
K too much
carelessness I was too confident in my
AC
can who
Reckless when will I learn my lesson
guys am I doomed forever to be this
[Music]
Reckless it's okay I will I will redeem
myself this is redemption
Arc I will earn myself a p
Senpai I'll will earn it for hard work
and not just moving her around and
making her the smallest
blob that I can get no I will earn
it there's easy ways to get her but this
this is not what I
want she was destined to
be the final bunny
final happiness to
achieve I will not change her Destiny
who am I to change someone's destiny
that is impossible one cannot change
other people's
[Music]
Destiny
nice beautiful
[Music]
beautiful she looks like a [\h__\h] egg
there perfectly placed in the middle
round and nicely as if she's laying in a
nest she made squeaky sound like my duck
that's not a duck they make squeaky
sounds woohoo
woohoo it's like I'm
amazed I'm so good at keeping it
clean
wow okay it's going to get dirty again
or is it or is
[Applause]
it it it get it is this the Run guys is
this the
run now I know what it means to be to
have a run the run in this game having
the Run means to get to
[Music]
by I'm trying to go in the circular
motion if you know what I mean but
actually the circular motion of birthing
bir Canal I'm trying to create a birth
canal but I think I already failed I'm I
I'm abandoning the plan
[Music]
try not to fro
challenge I never tried to
Fro I'm always doing the try not to Pro
challenge
oh what's in
[Music]
there stand by I'm coming for
you uh
[Music]
L is my my cursed
one eventually if we if we exchange her
maybe someone else will take over the
curse and it will still
[Music]
happen do you
understand push push I have to hold her
I have to hold the baby I have to hold
the baby don't drop the baby
don't drop the
baby
is just
a maybe I'll throw a over there
[Music]
then this should be fine yep yep
nice what do you mean it doesn't look
good this looks amazing
if only no was in the middle that would
be
nicer but this for now is okay too I can
still get her into the middle maybe when
she turns into
fora that will be the
[Music]
moment thank you for waiting for meire
not immediately jumping into the water I
know you don't like it when your thick
sheep coat gets wet that's not ideal we
don't want that oh
God in the
[Music]
middle
perfect perfect outcome I'm telling you
wow so clean again this is a good run
but I should stop rushing I should go
slowly wow
[Music]
wow wow
wow it's not really in the middle
anymore because there's nothing much to
[Music]
surround throw that
here
doesn't close enough to the midle
them before
right should we push for out to the
middle of
[Music]
ly I love
dangerous feeling
[Music]
oh
okay could push her let's try to push
her
yep and now can we push Lami back inside
or should I try to go from this
[Music]
side yeah there are some voice lines
where the microphone is a little bit
crispier but I think I can push her a
little bit towards the inside when I
transform
her see okay all is
well we're good we're good we're
good so many princesses
[Music]
here said oh this is one of my
central um you know spots that you know
she she reacts to you know what I
mean what are these voice lands and why
did I throw lamitan there do I do I like
to feel the
[Music]
frill seems like it I am
testing me myself and
I get get further inside please
[Music]
going to touch her under too
soon
[Music]
okay oh why did I could push her without
even throwing anything there we have no
I that oh my
God wait I'm so close to
pekora if I get an she will turn into FL
and touch the other flare I already have
a
[Music]
flare I was never so close to it before
I think especially with such a decent
field oh why won't you touch let me put
that here
there's a
there uh she will drop
eventually want to
[Music]
drop when two P tou you win I for me
it's already wi if I get one p us
point I don't think I can never get two
pck us at least not day I don't know I'm
not very positive thinking about that
we'll see we'll see if anything then
this is the
run if this is not the run then there is
no
[Music]
run let me throw
that
here there was here too
I got to cover her a little bit
[Music]
unfortunately don't you want to
touch but ideally they should move
towards the right
to I could try squeezing subu in there
but too dangerous to be honest it could
work but I'm too scared to do it I'm
just going to continue working on this
side oh this I
like this I like Okay okay then we can
make another
[Music]
here just got to leave it up to fate I
think one pick was bar not too hard for
me it's hard
okay well KY also had troubles with
getting two peas
if you get two pekas you're like I guess
around 12,000
[Music]
then okay maybe here L I always got to
be careful but I don't want to cover up
the small ones too much this works this
works this
works this works
[Music]
here is
[Applause]
[Music]
best put on top I don't want to I want
them to
comeb go somewhere else
no you should roll down to the
left wait Lami Lami that's okay Lami
turns into nanora but there's no nanora
close by is it better if I do it here or
there if I do it here I might push K
down off
accidentally almost feels like here
might be safer
[Music]
which side
this or the
[Music]
other
this who what just happened
there next is n okay Nan can be combined
with
n
oh why why why so that
was that was not so predictable but new
high score I couldn't have seen her
coming she rolled too
[Music]
stupid I didn't expect her to roll over
there what do you mean old Fuki it's
Fuki
right huh
it's just
because ah
cute wait okay goodbye n it's
over oh cute she looks so
smug oh shut up terra one mom fual
room so
smug so smug I don't like your smugness
[Music]
to smug well is bigger than before now I
made him
bigger I made her
bigger having a Al moment
there that's she gets for ending us true
I guess it was her was it was it her I
don't even remember anymore
I want to hear
lines she didn't say anything this
time she didn't say
anything she said a little bit there
took a while to start the
line I don't think I can I have to
believe I have to believe I have to
believe I can't say but I don't think
I'll get there again oh see maybe maybe
I can maybe I have to
believe who's I didn't I didn't replace
Lami yet
huh is Lamy still going to be the danger
of my life
[Music]
it's hard to hear
her she's so
cute why is she so
smug what happened to make her so
[Music]
smug no she's not talking she's so
shy shy focuses she still I got a double
of her and she still didn't talk how
about
now
nothing is it only when they combine
wait is it only when they no it's not
just when they combine
[Music]
right what what I already
got n
[Music]
fast SM maybe because she's bringing me
luck of course all of this all of those
combinations were according to Kaku
every little placement I did there was
very thoughtfully placed because I knew
that this is exactly what was going to
happen and I would get that nowhere to
stand by exactly for that reason it was
all well F out yes yes yes yes
she sounds like she's in
pain let's release her from her pain by
turning her into Namy
Senpai push push push push push push
push
push who's saying that is that F sounds
like a new voice l so it should be heard
but it sounded like NY a little bit to
me thanks for membership
welcome yeah this week no membership
stream even though I do them weekly I
just felt like I can't really squeeze it
in this time unless I give up one of
those public streams but I wanted to do
all of these streams so for once you
know I think I think no members are
going to complain about
one time the member
stream um
being
canell for one
week
yeah you're getting so many
[Music]
anyway um
go
[Music]
there okay
okay no you like sub Senai so much right
so if I
push right here will that push that will
will that push you over there yeah wow
trick shot trick shot absolute trick
shot
could have gone really wrong though
could have
didn't all according to
[Music]
Kaku
who my Kaku is
[Music]
unfolding but
dangerous oh okay she moved a little bit
back nice there's so many
can maybe if I'm squeeze
here still know soon soon soon soon soon
soon
TM oh
[Music]
nice those phrases will be in my dreams
tonight certain ones are just going to
stick with me
forever my nightmares no no no no
nightmares
[Music]
[Laughter]
probably should be landing more on top
that's what you guys want I know but
it's so tempting to just go in between
and right in front of me but now I'll
put this one on
[Music]
top this one careful of this one I
know I know but maybe now's the time to
transform into
rumy maybe from
here oh her whole chin is up in the air
her whole chin is right
[Applause]
there her whole chin is like I don't
care wa poetry slam oh uh no no no no
no oh wao Dr shots Dr shot
baby yeah don't worry guys that's what I
was uh what I knew it was going to
[Music]
happen Please Release Senpai from the
suffering is that all ever says like
different versions
of
okay oh how about here perfect oh yeah
that's just
[Music]
hot will be hot too watch watch and
learn wow hot
hot see another
one wait I
can't but I'm preparing for it
[Music]
sexy do you
understand I didn't see that there was
something down there
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
okay I think she really only has aim
Mario voice lines
[Music]
don't scare me like that there still a
Noy in the middle this whole time I
didn't
realize um you know there's going to be
uh three Noels in a moment which is
pretty yeah cuz I have four [\h__\h]
toyss and they're next to each
other h
dang oh danger
danger but
amazing okay what's that in the
middle must be Fuki okay okay okay it's
got to be
Fuki whoa this is the run you think so
I'll I'll try I I'll I'll try my best
I'll try to be
careful want to get noil closer to Fuki
there but
[Music]
get in there get in
there get in there
deeper Infiltrate The System be part of
it
is there anything else there
no thr her here and another one there
and I'm still waiting for a single Fuki
to throw in the middle there I'm impress
this run is still going why this is
going to be one of my best on to it's
already
3,400 noce but I don't know where to put
the
N maybe close to L so that they can team
up
soon but like this goes too far it's got
to be like kind of here probably but
that feels like it's going to fall down
towards me don't like it can I put it
here no difficult I don't want to put I
don't want to cover up fubuki
[Music]
yet I already could have built it with
the two AIS but I didn't know there was
going to be two
no here could also fit but it just won't
transform anytime
soon I
could don't trust the arrow too much are
you saying what are you saying with that
that's not as bad as I think or not as
good as I think I think this is I have
the highest chances of Landing it where
I want here but also the lowest
chances oh uh what do you think is this
[Music]
bad I want to land it kind of on top of
subu rip need to aim higher but like
here it goes over
[Music]
probably we risk it
what
oh
no that was one of my best
friends I'm still learning okay I'm
still a baby I'm still learning how high
I need to aim to get it to where I want
it it's okay I can recreate this magical
moment
[Music]
I going do it I going do it going do it
I going do
it
[Music]
I I'm already on it I'm fixing
everything okay
I'm fixing
[Music]
it now a winning
run
[Music]
okay okay I'm I'm soad very much in a
good mood hey look at
that oh all right she says she too not
just a
Maru she has more than just that
[Music]
like I feel like her she's my spirit
animal I feel it it's just
like this feeling
of so relatable
Europe is
lagging SAS Europe with their shitty
internet connection
L with those shitty ass WiFi
things my internet here is like already
a million times better it's just a
random place like it's not even an
expensive place like a $5 million
mansion or anything no it's just a
random place in the middle of middle of
Japan I don't like this
run okay I like
it change my mind I like it it's
fine it's fine yeah I changed my
mind cries in Australia you guys don't
really have good connections either
huh Australia I hear about
[Music]
it kind of crazy cuz Sydney is like huge
at least in Sydney there should be good
internet such a famous
Capital should have better internet
[Music]
cool wait syy wasn't Melbourne Melbourne
I was thinking about it too the moment
after I said it I was like wait was wait
wait what i n for sure I no should
be wait but
what
Melbourne and EV them wait
what what the [\h__\h] is
cber I've never heard of I've never
heard of cber what are you talking about
don't Gaslight me I've never heard about
this city before I think the world is
gaslighting people that it's either
Sydney or Melbourne cuz I've never heard
about camberra
before both of TR end the world
everybody is gaslighting each other
then
what where is that
even is it close what's to Sydney or
Melbourne because Melbourne and Sydney
couldn't
choose I've heard about perf before but
what the [\h__\h] is
Cam between them as a compromise that's
so dumb do people even live there more
people live in Sydney and Melbourne for
sure than they do in
camar that must be one of the like like
what usually like the capital of a
country is always the most inhabited one
right that's
insane what other countries are there
where the capital is not as inhabited as
many other cities like probably per
probably has also more
inhabitants what USA well okay USA has
is too big and has too many cities now
that's not a good example I mean more
like normalized
countries you guys have too many big
cities because you have too many like
you just have too
much that's not a good
example like in Europe I don't think
there
is like the same
situation I don't think there would be a
comparable situation where the
capital is smaller than other cities
[Music]
is that tell me if I'm
wrong yeah I don't know about this run I
don't know it's already [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay natural super came out of
me
screams okay I didn't expect know
[Music]
suddenly have time to change the places
of
power oh doesn't matter
it's in any case it's a rare
[Music]
thing there's still help in this room
you're so
sweet you're so
sweet okay Switzerland but Switzerland
maybe you know Europe but it's not EU
okay so I could change my argument and
say h it's not in in in the EU that's
not a thing
[Music]
it's a rare thing it's a [\h__\h] rare
thing it's a rare thing okay and aren't
you also shook like there's surely uh
besides Australians there's surely a lot
of people who or most people who haven't
heard about what was it cber sounds like
Cambridge but it's
not like the fact that I'm so shook
about it and never heard about it before
that's concerning
that tells you
all that tells you
[Music]
everything
yes oh never heard of C thank
[Music]
you we forget about camera to let's go
what do you mean having a hard time
finding example where it isn't the case
that's that no no no no no
Austria
check France Paris biggest
check Italy prob I would assume although
I can also Imagine maybe not many people
have space to live in Rome cuz too many
tourists I
know care
[Music]
Japan easy easily unfortunately one
could only dream that more people would
choose to live elsewhere in Tokyo in
Japan than in Tokyo yes yes yes because
there's just no freaking space here how
do they squeeze so many people live here
but like there's this this just this
thing of like there seem to be this like
feeling of you have to go to Tokyo if
you want to
succeed or get like a good job or
whatever like you got to go to Tokyo
everybody's going to go to Tokyo like
you
[Music]
know there are apparently 27 countries
with capital not being the biggest city
interesting is there like a like a you
know some some someone else who figured
that out and like looked at everything
how many countries in the world are
there 27 out of how many right it's not
much 27 can't be that much there's many
more countries in the world so so as I
said my argument still stands it's a
rare
thing it's a rare ass
[Music]
thing 200 is okay there you go that's
like 10% that's
10% wow map's good
amazing
[Music]
math thank you thank you guys finally
finally we've reached the agreement
Point feel nice I don't want to fight
you guys I don't want to fight you guys
[Music]
I will win the fight T I don't want you
to
suffer I mean when it's a physical fight
you guys are chickens what are you going
to do huh what are you going to what are
you going to freaking
do
oh facing the inside oh I think she
wants to
hug hot
[Music]
I can peack knees like nobody's misses I
don't think you can reach my knees can
you
[Music]
close
close it might be
close you can Peck my
toes you probably probably tickle
me make yourself comfortable
please
um where do I put you n here's
space right in front of to
but I'm going to put you
[Applause]
there and then I'm going to put you here
cuz you turn into oh
wait well
[Music]
[Laughter]
you guys are all bring of Legend of
Zelda
huh I wouldn't say they're really
dangerous
[Music]
now that I'm done with House of the
Dragon now I can finish Vikings and shun
I still didn't finish Shogun I forgot
about
Shogun have to finish Shogun I'm like so
close to it and I think somebody is kind
of somebody kind of spoiled me about it
even they assume that
[Music]
Finning thank you thank you yeah I know
they're both good they're all
good close but I knew what I was doing I
knew what I was doing there oh I don't
know about this
one if I move is she going to actually
fall down am I actually holding her
right
now okay okay
okay
see but now I can put I think I can put
Lami
there
nice help B this is like a whole mess oh
oh
God yes yes yes oh God I can squeeze her
in the air probably
oh there's let me throw that here maybe
she will go
[Music]
there thank
you purposefully pushing on each side
thank you for the memberships guys don't
move
where to put Let me let me needs to be
close to
N I could put her
[Music]
Lam is my
scapegoat oh was a good
[Music]
run do I still get nothing
new damn it okay last one I
[Music]
think cuz tomorrow my stream is
relatively
early 11 a.m. tomorrow wa
time but I am ready to
play pretty
[Music]
long
tomorrow I have like nine plus TMS
what's going on oh oh what's this
okay what's
this
huh oh
okay what
this
huh one Manion no two manions
tool what
[Music]
bro okay
whatever that was something I
saw in
[Music]
mys not you guys two Mansions
yeah got to do two
to make up for whatever that was
yesterday I will blame it on the
controller
partially different difficult to control
you
[Music]
know no not 12 hours I do have dinner
plans there's no time set yet but
I can probably make it relatively
late which is good I need dinner plants
cuz I'm eating alone too
much I need to eat with
people who what was that Bo taunting me
[Music]
I want to
see
roundness I want to see see how round
she is how big she
is please let me see
[Music]
it I'm
focused I'm
determined I am
Tak and I know that looks dangerous but
it's okay
push push push P she's not far enough
outside for me to push her which maybe
is a good thing
[Music]
um if I had dinner
Lamy no no no no no
no that would be funny but
no it's not a Japanese
[Music]
do anywhere is okay but I would have
liked you to not go directly on top
of all
right wa
yipp ypp
no soon they just got a
touch how
about
here why don't you go so far she's right
[Music]
there why what what's wrong with you
guys what's wrong why do you hate each
other why why are you doing
[Music]
that they go different places when I
throw them to
far okay okay we got the no we got the
no climbing for an aan metal chance
woman's breakdowns and maybe
synchronized
swimming ooh okay so there's a few
things where Austria is there I'm not
really betting on them winning anything
though
to be
[Music]
honest there's a in there we got to save
her from impending
doom there it
is no wrong direction
[Music]
where are you
going where are you going your crown is
going to fall off girl how is it staying
there
actually how is it
[Music]
staying I don't know I wanted to reach
a no I
have hard to get her where I want her to
go
well we'll see where it goes ah went the
wrong way
[Music]
again this part of my body has like
grown
[Music]
in yeah she can never take it off no but
she definitely doesn't have it on for
all of her outfits so that can't be true
now I covered up the AI
Senpai this is not good this is a big
mess
[Music]
sucks this is not the
run this is not the
run so much I can tell
you oh it's look what will
happen this might
explode
[Music]
H thank you for having
Mercy should I get this close one or
should I not no maybe not not
[Music]
yet okay but maybe no got another one I
could build them elsewhere I could build
them
[Music]
here not over
yet I need my whole life volcano
yes it
should red anytime
[Music]
soon
okay lau
lau
lauu you're safe
there now want do do I want that lumy
there do I want to try yes where will
this
go okay
[Music]
oh
God precious my
precious big now I can save all the ah
they're saving
themselves oh wonderful wow it it hasn't
been this clean for a
while oh my
it feels so
[Music]
refreshing
ah okay I still want to get those small
ones out of the way before I bury them
again burying them alive
okay hello
hello okay here we go
the Sharks the sharks are so close by
the rabbit is on the horizon I see
sharks on the
[Music]
horizon
res wait we're close there's basically a
norai right there don't you see her
don't you see her I see her I see her
very clearly it's it's not me going
insane I see
her B why are you so shy there you go
oh I told you I told
you okay
[Music]
there there that's fine that's a good
spot that's a very good spot that's a
good
[Music]
spot go
there
there why wouldn't you you were right
there you had one
job safe Zone
if
only if only if
only this should be safe if I combine
she will M merge with canadan right away
she should she should she has no
[Music]
choice okay no right is there one no
that's her ears
okay
um
[Music]
here we basically have one to
Senai but they just don't touch for now
[Music]
what do you think about this run guys
Rabbit
Run yeah futan is not
amused is this like Frey is this just
Frey G basically but with whole life
MERS make everything
life all Life Is Life what life becomes
life
[Music]
no
lu I got to be careful now I can't mess
oh I can't mess this up I can't mess
this up
now oh
[Music]
this won't be the run but cl to high
school why why why
why should be close to there's a gap
here
[Music]
okay okay okay now hold on everybody's
surrounding the princess and protecting
her from
danger because it's jinxing it and you
guys don't want to jinx it okay okay
that's sweet of you guys you guys are so
considerate wow what was down there
there's there's there's a puki sampai
and an Aki sfai and now we're
adding I would say we're adding I don't
know about add the small on in the
middle but it is what it is okay okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay wait this
is this is basically a p i have a p I
just got to make it happen because
twoam three watas just two of them have
to touch to get me a TOA then the toas
touch I get a n the N touch with the
N it's right there in my reach but all
the is are separated so I don't know
maybe I'll make another one
even
come
[Music]
for she I can already hear her she's
right
there she's right there
[Music]
guys where to put this
anywhere I don't
care why you touching her what do you
mean you're not touching look this is
touching evidence the lines are like
melting
huh okay they will touch now
[Music]
probably I'm so scared
oh my high score is over
4,000
bur get this small onside I don't know
man I usually would do that but I don't
want to like separate all the bottoms
more you know what I mean now I'm kind
of
[\h__\h] how am I going to put that on top
of anything I don't think I I mean here
maybe uh
what do you think here or squeeze it
like in here do you think it could fit
here between
to or should I put it on top
of between
between top next
toi yeah on to on top
between okay but like where do I
[Music]
aim I'm I don't know where to aim should
I aim really
high what what angle is this angle fine
or more over
here higher is better this could end
everything I know like this is also good
is there a better
option it looks like there's space Maybe
behind what is ire here
honestly that should fit
[Music]
too it might be saf for there
but a coming up
[Music]
yeah yeah let's I'll put it here I think
it's kind of safer
there the other is could work
too m
just shoot it straight there and I can
still hold
it okay oh she's so she's so
far holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
you were supposed to stay there so I can
make you into a
[Music]
Lumi the is basically there
guys she's
there why doesn't she want to show
up I don't care about the op preferences
M and by run all right
now this this could be
good
let let
[Music]
M me m
me
[Music]
whammy wh
me but that is a sick high score I got a
new
one I need to take mmy out to eat ask
her to remove the
curse I Cur any chance of AI
wa for now maybe maybe next
year I can't recover from this pain and
this
feeling mmy why M me m me why I didn't
even get rewarded for getting over
4K but she was there I even heard it
didn't you all hear Pai she was just
buried inside she was there
she she was I mean where else was that
voice coming
from
no she she was there she was there I
heard her I had everything necessary she
just transformed without us seeing it
and she was then covered by all the
others that's what happened is this is
this my last situation
here thank you for reminding me of my
trauma you could also just like you know
put wamy some somewhere there in the
ocean floating to to at least show off
who was at
fault ah but I think I handled that
pretty well for as long as I could
[Music]
I really think I
did I want to play this
again I don't know when I guess next
week then
but I don't have much time to stream
next week
so you will have to replace one of the
longer games like Luigi or witch spring
we'll see
you ah damn
it I need to
[Music]
maybe played with the V person oh it
could be a challenge oh the challenge
could be these kind of things sound
better in
Japanese have to do p Senai impression
until I get P Senai can't end game until
get peka Senai while doing P Senai
voice that could be chenge one next time
oh that's an
idea that's an
idea rip
no no that sounds actually interesting
that sounds
[Music]
fun I might do
that that that rings a bell in my
brain but it's kind of difficult for me
to do her in English to be honest it
just doesn't work it does it doesn't
sound sound like her
eh now I'm speaking English if I
transition like that from Japanese to
English that's what she would sound
like but I don't think it will even
sound like if I just continuously speak
English like that to you guys it doesn't
sound it doesn't sound like her unless
it's [\h__\h]
now I'm speaking
English oh no what do I
do [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you oh kind of
work I just have to probably reel myself
back in by speaking Japanese every once
in a while
[Music]
oh my
god let's
go
oh think I'll do that that's
funny dying pick she's just constantly
dying when I voiced her
put on what if I put on some bunny ear
acid that would be
cute and oh is blue listening or or
somebody else who can make aets like
with this swimsuit maybe on top of that
we could draw her bunny suit but in my
colors and then um the bunny ears wow
that's high effort yo that's high effort
for one of those for just doing a bingo
challenge you're
here can you do it
or she can also do it I don't mind who
does it whoever's here listens to this
right
now sounds fun I'm motivated oh this
music is nice what the
hell this sounds like an original
soundtrack not like a
remix correct me if I'm
wrong I love it
[Music]
we'll do it together
okay
really does she don't
know does sheo
know yeah sounds Mario
sunshiny yeah my voice will be fine
it'll be fine it'll be fine it'll be
[Music]
fine what you get it in the first round
of the challenge and then the stream is
well that would be
amazing cuz even one round can take a
long time it wouldn't even be that short
probably that would be amazing I
wouldn't mind
that that would be like me getting the
first Trident in Minecraft without
trying on first
try same thing short stream let's
go okay guys you may have expected it
but super chats
are next time
[Music]
uh should should should have time
tomorrow yeah uh got to figure out what
time we go
[Music]
each so
4 a.m. W time next stream what oh ah you
mean yeah yeah W time right now it's
Japan time
though I again what you mean yeah I'm
going to set up the stream now make a a
thumbnail quickly and then I'm going to
set it
up yeah it's it's early for Europe or
like ungodly for Europe
[Music]
Unholy okay and I'm going to figure out
what to eat for dinner now en me S thank
you for watching I had
fun it's small small small game small
small game but even then it's almost 4
hours guys this feels like I only played
for 2 hours or
less doesn't it feels like that to
[Music]
me time flies when you're having fun
true enjoy the house of the Dragon
tangents thank you oh you enjoyed them
you say yeah I'm a little bit mad
because I was like I watched the episode
a little bit later and then um I I
wanted to like watch the alt shift live
stream that he did right away after but
it's like 4 hours long it's his longest
uh so far on the season and I was in the
middle of watching it I was only like 30
minutes in or so and then it got
copyright struck and taken down while I
was watching
it and he says that there's a Audio Only
version like on Spotify and old patreon
and never place but I want it with
video like he puts up a lot of like nice
reference pictures of the the family
tree and the dragons and everything so
it's like way easier to understand when
there's something to visualize man he
always like does another like follow-up
video at the end of the week that's like
shorter just a 20 minute like um recap
on the on the episode but I like the
long live stream
Recaps that happened immediately after
the episode so like everything's still
fresh and everyone's hyped and asking
many questions and all that I want to
see both you know I always watch both
the long Recaps and the short Recaps I
didn't do this for the first season I
only really started doing this like
immediate review of Al shift uh after
the episodes that I watched for the
second season I didn't do this
[Music]
before I knew the channel but I didn't
like follow it like this previously it
is one of her songs
really what which one what the
hell it
is I'm watching him since College okay
that's just I can't even really think oh
that's a long time cuz I don't know when
you were in
college Al is in
Tangent you sound more excited for the
stream than you do for the show no both
both both I like
both it's nice to follow the
analis okay fake
out don't forget to get the
merchandise shall I squeak for you
[Music]
[Laughter]
cute so
[Music]
cute oh the air inside smells different
when it comes
out like some kind of plas not don't
worry okay it's like I'm smelling this
chicken's farts or something God damn
it okay bye-bye bye-bye don't help the
chicken fumes I can't help it I can't
help it byebye bye-bye see you tomorrow
Luigi's Mansion bye-bye
[Music]