Hey, hey,
hey, hey, Aqua-chan is cute. I
really like her waiting voice. She's a genius whose singing voice is not good. She
makes me feel glad to be alive. This is the reason for world peace. You
know, I
want to thank Minato and Aqua.  I want to thank you too,
but Aqua-chan is the one I love the most,
right?
Love, love, love. There's one quiet person in all of this, but who is that? Ah, she
looks like a fairy, or something like a demon. I'm troubled.
What's so good about looking like a fairy? Then,
as a person, as a person, you're like a
fairy. Well, the fairy incident happened, and at a live gathering, I dressed up as a fairy.  On LINE,
I kept saying things like ``I'm a fairy today'' and I
thought I was acting strange, so I thought it would be a good idea to get together for the first time in a while, so I
tried to cheer myself up and ended up looking like a fairy.  Shio was the one who sent it to me and
poked me in.
What kind of fairy is this? Laugh, it's a fairy. I don't think it's funny. It's like a fairy. It's like a fairy. What are you talking about? It's like this guy.  I do
n't know if Aa-senpai is the most idol-conscious of Hololive, but idols do
n't go to the toilet after all, so I
think everyone shouldn't either.  I see,
that's right. I'm stubborn because I can't go out. That's how it is.
Senpai is in a
diaper. Hey, Akutan. Hey, Akutan. What's that? Hey, Akutan. Hey, Akutan. What's that? Hey, Akutan, the bathroom is long. He
doesn't go to the bathroom. He's an idol. Hey, he
doesn't go to the bathroom either.  I'm going to
go and do it properly,
so when I'm not streaming, I'll
tell you that I'm not streaming.
What were you doing? Go back to dreamland. We were
eating biscuits and having a tea party.
[Music] I
might have written something like this.  It
's begun,
it's begun, yesterday I saw Mr. Ho yesterday, and
before I knew it, he was sitting next to me and it was
really interesting.
This is a 1-hour broadcast, and
this person has been around for a long time.
What's going on? I'll let him go home for a while.
He's really crazy in the best sense of the word. He's a really good
singer. He's
really good at acting.  So why are you
here? Shiso-sensei is quick-witted and
good at games, so it's
okay. I'll stand in two rows,
watching the uncle working hard.
Acho Adakaze-sensei-sensei-sensei-sensei The teacher is crazy because he
has a stuffed animal as a friend.Some
screw is blown off,
so he thinks I'm a stuffed animal.Acho, I'm going to go to the bathroom.Oh yeah.
Nice toilet It's fun, right? Nee-san, E-yea-san.
Cute little girl. Cute little sister.
[Music] I
love you. I don't want to imitate my
stuffed toy anymore
. Now, Toa is going to the bathroom. Toa
is going to the bathroom.  I'm alone with you. I'm
alone with Tan. We're making out. We're not making
out. It's a bad channel. It
's not a channel. Ah, then I guess it's over for today. Is it the
water channel? The
timing is right. It's good. The two of us are making out. The
channel is amazing.  I think it suits
you well. I wonder if he was a nuisance to Hakusui Channel. We
had a choreography lesson that day and night,
but after the lesson, we
said let's go out for dinner, and we got together at the dot, and today,
when we were supposed to be choreographing, that guy was there.  But, we
chatted like we weren't going to eat today or anything, and
sent it to us. Yeah, I want to
go. That's what I want to go. Well, I said let's go, and I heard that Sei-chan was going too.
After this, there was a payment for
me and To-chan.  After we finished, we
lined up outside. It was really cold. It was
night and I was feeling a little thin. I
was touching Maji Buru Buru, and Towa-chan
said it was really cold, and Towa-chan said, "
It's okay to be cold.  Gyutto-chan loves me. I was so sleepy
after the Endurance race, so I
played golf and I told Akter and Su-chan that I
slept, but they said no, they didn't sleep, they didn't take a nap, so I
thought that after the golf was
over.  Toa said oh, I'm sleepy, so I'm going to sleep, and Aku
was okay, and after that, the two of them
played Minecraft. To be honest, I'm not going to write anything like that,
but they're not in that dimension anymore.
Everyone I know is in the same dimension as you.
That's not true, Toa is already in another dimension.
Please don't mix it up. I know because you're behind me with your arms folded. You're an
adult.
[Music]
Ask Aku-tan, it's true.
Atan, I'm going to play with you.
Why are you playing with me? Why are you playing
with me? Why are you trying to play with me? What's wrong with you? It
doesn't matter if you're good or bad. I
won't forgive you. It's
not good.  I'm going to catch it inside you. That
kind of crazy love isn't good. I've
never done that with those balls before. I don't need them. It's none of your business.
[Music]
It's up to you.  A
of