[Music]
[
Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
After
this The D block will start After this, the
limbs are crazy.  Nona
[Music] I'm not the type of person who is
sensitive to any type of race, so my fingers are shaking
If I'm going to tremble, I can
run without being nervous at all, but now I'm really nervous.Art
By the way, do
n't look at the comments during the race.Run
at full speed.
So I hope everyone will cheer us on with all their might. Hahaha I get
nervous at tournaments like this, right?
[Music]
My heart is pounding, my heart is pounding. It's
going to start in a little while. Oh, it's so
bad, I don't know what to do.  What should I
do? I
had some time, so I
went for a run, and
then I made a new Me. I
changed my name a little, and so on. I'm
acting like I bought new sneakers on the day of the sports day. Is
this okay?  Will
this actually make me feel better?
[Music] Is it
okay if I change it on the day? Is it okay? I
just changed my mood. Her
face is different, right? She's changed. Her
name is also different. Oh, that's a terrible doll. I'm going to turn on the air conditioner. It's so
hot. It's so
hot.
[Music] I wonder
if this is because I'm so nervous. It's so
hot and tense and I have a hot runny nose. My
breath is getting worse. Should I
drink some water? I'm the
type of person who gets nervous and has a stomach ache, but no matter what.
Just now,
my stomach hurts a little.  It's showing in my body that I'm
nervous, pounding, pounding, pounding, pounding,
pounding, pounding. I'm not nervous because I'm a sister. No, no, I'll do my best. I'll do my best. I have to do my best.
When it starts,
everyone's comments don't seem like money at first.
Cold Reiki.  I'm floating, but it's a little
too cold.
Maybe it'll start soon. It
might start like that. I'll do
my best.
After I see the name of the princess, I'll
let you all comment first. Goodbye, I'm off to go. No, I
'm going to
take off my clothes myself. It's a
lie.  I'm waiting for you to drink it yourself.
What's your favorite course? Yeah,
isn't this random? Oh,
wait a second, it should be no
random. I'm sure you said it wasn't random,
but it's happened so many times.
Baby
bar. I'm
going.  It's
too much of a luck game here.
[Music] I
want it. I
can't get the coin. I
guessed Shimane, and the
first place was bad.
You also used the wrong guy. The
puppy won't stop.
[Music]
Ah, third place, that's it.  Oh no,
I can't talk even if I can't talk. Do
n't be serious. If you're not serious, you'll be reckless. It's
dangerous. Yesterday, it wasn't mushrooms
anymore
. My mouth gets dry when I pick up coins. I don't have any coins left.
[Music]
[Music] I ca
n't come with this.
Oh wait, I had this. I didn't see it.
[Music] I
haven't gotten any coins. Oh, I'm
going to hit a banana.  I'm having
fun with this. That's how much I
showed it.
[Music] It's
here. I'm glad the
mushrooms appeared. My heart is pounding. Let's try to make the pulsing
vibrations. I
wonder what I'm good at. My
long hands are getting numb. It
's F. What kind of course is this here?
That's the same guy.
This is the only one with shortcuts.
[Music] I'm
panicking because it's a secret.
not good at drifting. I
want to open it. [
Music] I didn't expect a
mushroom to come here.
[Music]
Something strange.  So I pressed the erotic button
How many years have I progressed so far? I think it's about
3. I'm pounding, pounding, I got it for 3 days.  -
Oh, I saw it!
[Music]
Congratulations
[Music] I was
able to do it when I practiced earlier, but
now I'm in the
actual performance.
[Music] I
did it, but I'm done. But I can do my best.
[Music]
Couple  But it's too bad. I
couldn't get the item.
[Music]
Ah, it's decided. It
can't be too far-fetched. It's a real hit.
This
tension, this tension keeps the bow from becoming squishy. Hahaha,
this is
probably the last time. Let's have a
quick toast.
[Music]
[Applause]
Everyone's at the temple
[Music] The
grind dash failed
[Music]
[Music] It's too much to
do
[Music] Mushroom
quickly I was nervous and couldn't do it -
Everyone
gave me a
break - I'm excited for the groom  I was so excited that I had a lot of water. I
failed again, but I did my best
. Now it's getting hot.
[Music]
Thank you for your hard
work. We had a practice session,
but it's
time
for the actual performance. We were so evenly balanced that my bow was shaking, but I was still practicing.
[Music] Now that things
have changed, I don't know what to say.
Good, I'm glad I
did it. Thank you everyone for your support.
[Music]
[Applause]
Now, I'll
close the frame and end the broadcast.
Thank you everyone for the highlights and places.
[Music]  I'll see
you all when I come to stream tonight. See you all.
[Music]