[Music]
would you still love me if I was no
longer
Phoenix but a
worm would you still love would you
still love would you still
love
really thank you oh byebye chy Wy I told
you you didn't want to be here
now ah she never listens she never
listens she just she's just really into
chilling and hanging at my in front of
my right side monitor right now cute
patootie sorry baby sorry it's streaming
time yeah yeah we want to eat the worm
of course you would love me as a worm
because you would want to eat
me your little shits cuz then you feel
you're just saying yeah I love you
because only because you know that if I
become a worm then finally you will have
more power than I currently have over
you and you you could potentially eat me
and be free of
the what's the
word not
terrifying not
horrific what what do you call this
leadership that I have been T yeah t
tyranny yes my I'm a tyrant show I just
I I remember you guys called me tyranto
before
no but I am I am the best leader you
could possibly imagine okay oh my God oh
my God my M wow schedule
crazy mama mia Mama
Mia
[Music]
uh
H jenma JMA just sent me a an overview
of of the things I put together so far
for for my Japan time de
me I don't even want to look at it it
looks uh
terrifying I thought I'd have more free
time but who needs free time right who
needs free
time ah we're going to play this funny
game I I it looks cute but I heard it's
a rage
game
I just want to oh let me resize this yay
I love I love when you can resize
however you want
it and not like you know like it doesn't
even have to be the the as aspect of 16
to9 you could do whatever you want no
actually no I guess it creates a a black
bar but yeah do you hear this beautiful
sound of
worms
I don't know I'm usually oh not good at
these games I think also wouldn't this
be better to play with a controller I
feel like but okay is it normal does
everybody play it like
this it does work with W ASD and the the
arrow
keys your brain's already
melting oh it's
difficult
wait wait I'm already
struggling I hope you're good at
momentum oh no wait I'm already
struggling how do
I wait it can't be so difficult maybe
turn around here no
ah
[Music]
I'm okay so you like kind of like roll
off of that side okay
a apple can I eat yum yum yum yum no no
eats the
Apple also some I heard that uh you can
fall down like super far really when I
watched like M's stream it didn't
really seem like that to
me oh does it matter if I press the up
button when I jump does does it make me
higher
I love these
sounds I wonder is it more difficult
than jump King I don't care because at
least the visuals are hella cute
[Music]
[Applause]
[\h__\h] oh the way it bounces off [\h__\h] why
do I even jump over those can I not just
somehow do a profan here oh almost
can I bounce
off no of course not not with my gamer
skills but in jumping there's a babe at
the top us well who knows what do you
get at the end of this
game maybe you become a beautiful
butterfly I
[Music]
mean wait what m is still the beginning
pretty much oh oh how long is this like
I I skipped a little bit through her
stream to get an
impression she seemed delighted by
it
no so bad move the cursor you you mean
for you guys or does it help me is the
is the cursor something that works in
the game I don't think so
wa I like how it can just like stand
like so still upwards I don't think any
worm can do that
[Music]
[\h__\h] ah for viewer experience okay no
problem okay I'm warming did you notice
the warm on my head oh [\h__\h] what I'm so
bad at
[Music]
[Applause]
this how could I
not yeah blue made me a little warm and
was so smart to make it a transparent gi
[Music]
gi why did I panic
jump going to eat that worm no nobody's
eating that worm it's my brain
worm if you eat it then how can I think
actually I guess I would be thinking
better if
I if I had no brain worms actually you
probably should eat them from for my
wellbeing I'm never going to make it
guys I'm I'm never going to make it past
this point let's be
honest H they're confusing the physics
yeah I think so too will I get better
will I
really W I don't know how I did that I
really don't
[Music]
know oh okay okay the banana that's
doll no don't make me do the apples
again no no no no no no no
no honestly you should probably just
land on the tip of the banana once and
immediately jump
off
[Music]
but
yeah and then I got to go back here but
I'll get see I'm ah I'm getting better
at this
part it's okay it's okay it's
[Music]
okay what then you jump in the direction
you're facing so if you're angled
downward you'll jump more down
oh
okay oh
oh oh yay nice nice okay hey
Improvement actual Improvement
[Music]
guys but I'm I'm angled upwards now at
least
so oh yeah let's just stay here
[Music]
no oh do I have super chats off still oh
my God I'm a Susy bucka let me turn him
on pea pea I forgot didn't realize there
is no need to have them off they're on
now
enjoy love it where did this game come
from like it's so sudden and out of
[Music]
nowhere suddenly new flavor of the month
or the week or the half month
game that did I not say kikiki oh my God
who am I
[Music]
Kik hi
Scooby oh she's so noisy what I'm
streaming do you want to eat the
[Applause]
[Music]
worm here look there's a worm I don't
think you like
worms finally the stream can start
K oh you want on my
table go away go away
bye-bye
no
no I
apologize for sucking so bad at this
[Music]
game you will have to suffer with this
for me through this with me actually
both works I feel
[Music]
like what come
on okay okay ah
ah why why can life not be easy I guess
there an emo it's just not that
easy nice no Yahoo
[Music]
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah like
that it looks so funny it looks so funny
okay no no no
no I'm a worm and I shall no I shall
warm like a
storm I am the worm that is
approaching I don't even know how the
song goes I'll just pretend I
[Music]
do I am the worm that is approaching
nobody came up with that yet did they
[Music]
huh I'm so
hip uh how do I do
[Music]
[Applause]
this
yo okay lucky
[Music]
jump can I oh wait actually not on the
tip is easier okay okay okay okay
okay yay but why are we going to left
why why if I fall down in that Gap I'd
probably land at the
bottom look at this
girl oh a look at all these worms that I
could be eating why is
this why is this key sign there is does
it just tell me to go to the right
side
no the time slows
down is that
me the time slowed down and the music
slowed
down it begins
it surely
does wait how did I do this
ah a oh my God Ah that's
fine oh my God I'm ah I'm getting better
though look at me look at me go look at
past me going
like
nice guys I've been really stressed out
by the way I have lots of things to do I
had one recording today in the early
morning and then um but that was like a
program recording you'll see it later on
when it is uh actually being released uh
as a you know as a stream like not
really a stream but like a an almost
stream it's like a pre-recorded
[Music]
stream come on latch on to it you should
be a pretty sticky
worm and then uh I had to record two
songs to be honest I have to record a
couple more of my
vocals before I go to Japan and yeah
that's that's pretty difficult no
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
uh-huh yeah cool story bro ah that was
close oh my
God yeah
by what a
[Music]
setback oh [\h__\h] why am I doing
that
[Music]
damn yay free Years thank
you thank
[Music]
you h what n
why
[Music]
no I I am surely now already regretting
my life
choices
oh my gaming choices that part is quick
though but having to return to the
beginning kind of
sucks oh my God oh my God would be so
much easier as a controller game I think
no no no no no I forgot how to do this
jump I forgot how to do it
[Music]
okay
okay worm worm worm worm you give me 1
hour before rage quit I mean it's not
like I have much more
time to play this
game today anyway okay so no wo
dangerous I thought I could do the same
thing as with the bananas uh before like
look in the other direction but jump in
the other
direction this
jump ho ho ho how how how how how it's
like way too close like
what
[Music]
no I I play this game for 45 hours holy
[\h__\h] oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] at least I didn't bounce
off the edge of the
watermelon okay okay okay okay
okay
okay uh uh maybe yeah yeah yeah oh no
it's the
beginning wait wait
[Music]
wait
um
oh yeah yeah so yeah uh fine everything
is
[Music]
fine everything is fine I'm scaring your
cat I scare my cats too probably nah
maybe not anymore at this point your cat
should get used to it like why is your
cat not used to it yet like do you not
watch my streams
enough ah speaking of cats I brought my
Kito C to the oh one one of them chunky
wonky to the
vet couple of days last week actually
right and everything is
okay ah it's it's probably just allergic
reactions it's what I thought
anyway um but the vet was like actually
kind of like what do you call it when
you guys are like super worried and like
thinking it's way more dramatic than it
really
[Music]
is honestly I I like the vet but she
seemed like yeah Doom posting
exaggerating yeah I don't know Doom post
I feel like Doom posting kind of fits it
quite well um cuz like I told her that
junky wonky is like you know pretty lazy
and calm and like I mean you know a
little she will play around a little bit
but then maybe she gets a little bit
intimidated too by by smoothie when she
joins in on the
playing and oh my God she's Tangen thing
and tanging makes her powerful let's
go but then she was like no that's not
normal like she was basically saying
cats can't be
lazy if they're healthy they can't be
lazy I'm like what
surely there are lazy cats that are
healthy she says that like there might
be
something that is the reason for her
being lazy like that but like no like I
really I have this feeling like of
course I don't have scientific proof yet
uh but I just have this feeling like she
may have allergic reactions but besides
that she's healthy and I think uh she's
just a lazy cat she enjoys being lazy
that's her lifestyle you know
[Music]
okay nice
recovery yeah so she was like Doom
posting that it could be this or it
could be that maybe I have to go scan my
cat
uh under a Canon printer scanner
combination I said no mine's broken but
I guess it can still
scan that's not how it went down um
um oh oh interesting
interesting
mhm um but yeah she did like uh blood
tests and chuny wonky throughout this
whole process chunky wonky was just like
so patient she didn't even meow a single
time from I took public transport right
and it actually like it wasn't so fast
like she she was outside for a while
while and but I was like carrying her in
the carrier but you know we took public
transport and everything and she didn't
meow a single time during the transport
and then also she didn't Meow in the
waiting room and she didn't Meow in in
the
actual left or right I guess right
procedure
room so she was like the goodest of the
good
babies and was praised so much by the
vet for her being so well behaved like
she said oh um I told her
the she wanted to know what the what the
breed was of chunky wonky and I told her
to breed and she was like oh and I said
I said I don't even really believe it
anymore that it's really that I feel
like I got scammed because like more and
more I noticed that she's not very much
like the breed that she's supposed to be
which is okay like I it's not okay
because I paid a price for a certain
breed right um but it's okay cuz I still
love her you know she's fine that's a
tiny platform
[Music]
man yeah [\h__\h] you yeah [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
you fine fine I keep on Tangen thing do
I look like I care no I don't care this
doesn't affect
me okay so far it really doesn't
[Music]
um yeah so she said that cats of
that oh so
[Music]
funny really really really really that's
how you want to play it uhhuh okay okay
cool she said breeds that of cats of
that breed they're normally never that
well behaved for
her and I don't know my cats are
generally well behaved maybe those cats
are not well
raised by their
owners I don't I haven't heard of that
breed specifically being uh like
a like a like a not not well behaved cat
[Music]
generally
what Garfield also La he's also orange
well Garfield may actually have health
problems cuz Garfield is
fat and he's not real anyway
so that might have something to do with
it
with him being the way he
[Music]
is lots of lasagna yeah uh yeah so she
did she she she first she weighed junky
wonky a healthy 4 kilogram by the way
she looks much he heavier and she she
feels much heavier to me cuz I struggled
carrying her especially in the pet carer
though because like it's
just it's just not easy you know
balancing a cat in a pet carrier arm
weak
spaghetti what is this sound I keep on
hearing this wind sound but I I guess
it's in
game part of the
bgm makes me feel like it's really
[\h__\h] windy but it doesn't look windy
in this
[Music]
game
okay uh yeah so she weighed her then she
heard her her heartbeat but the
heartbeat was
fine no irregularities she said that
sometimes like there might be cases
where there's something wrong with it
but you don't hear it
nice generally should be fine and and
then uh she looked she looked at her
teeth and she said by the way chunky won
they're now smoothie and chuny won they
becoming I think 5 years in
January ret turning uh 5 years um but uh
she said her teeth are beautiful like
wow amazing
teeth I was so proud but like um I don't
even you know for dogs you maybe some
people brush their dog's teeth right I
think that's kind of you kind of have to
do it with dogs for cats not really I
mean I still know some people do it
[Music]
what
a yeah there's like treats that are
supposed to help with it for dogs and I
guess they exist for cats but I don't
know I don't think my cats would eat
that stuff uh or make use of it I've
tried it
before yeah
um
oh yeah maybe it's because chunky wonky
only eats dry food and dry food is I
guess good for
teeth no I tried it for my
cats wet fot is bad for cats Ste oh
really yeah I guess if you only give
them wet food
[Music]
huh
I I'm I'm I'm a little bit of disbelief
excuse me
[Music]
um
so yeah back to my K that I'm so proud
of because she was praised about
everything her well behaved
nature her beautiful teeth her beautiful
fur
yeah she was not overweight okay people
like to think she's overweight but no
she is not healthy
weight uh everything was fine yeah yeah
she said she's really cute like she sees
a lot of cats right a lot of cats and
dogs and this and that each day but she
seemed genuinely Enchanted by my
cat and I was so proud everybody who
sees my cat even
vets love my cats my
God yeah so she's well she looks I I
never said she's fat I believe in her
being healthy
wait so where was I uh yeah and
[Music]
uh uh yeah she like you know I would
tell her because like we were so F
trying to figure out if
[Music]
um if it's more than just an allergy
know um cuz she was like first not
really she said the the the things that
she the reason why I went in the first
place is because she froze up a lot
these
days and I was worried because if she I
she's like I always I've been trying to
figure out if she has an l and if yes
what for like over a year now I think
switching Foods you
know and like there were times where it
was a bit worse but it was like mostly
scratching you know when when your cat
scratches it's usually you know fleas or
allergy it obviously doesn't have fleas
[Music]
um but H then at some point the the
scratching got better not completely
gone but like she wouldn't scratch that
often anymore that would be
concerning but then everyone the last
she would throw up but that's pretty
normal cuz like hair balls right but her
throwing up made me concerned because
her throwing up is like what comes out
is not hair balls how I know them I had
to I had a cat back in the day a family
cat who which would throw up a lot but
you would literally see the hair balls
and and and my my Kato chunky wony for
her I always just saw like uh the food
the the Kibbles coming back
[Music]
out and
I I she doesn't seem to have issues with
hair balls but um even then like I even
brought a sample in a bag uh but even
then the vet
said uh that that might not I mean
that's still that's still hair ball she
says I don't know is this
me how long was I waiting here ah
oh that's going to happen again the past
repeats
itself does she eat to fast no I don't
think so but interesting thought um
there was just
one vomit thing recently where it did
look like a hair ball but mostly it's
like the Kibbles you know so I don't
[Music]
know
oh
wow she doing it how B how bad can you
fall down here is there ever like a
point where you get to at least like a
new level of falling down like like a
middle level or so you know that would
be
[Applause]
[Music]
nice
n
[Music]
mhm okay
um yeah uh for the blood test she put
chunky wonky in like
a like a Insanity vest
basically like
like a a wrap she basically wrapped her
in some
something like a
bag and only made her her head and her
paw peek
out and told me to like maybe pet her
head a little bit to like keep her calm
she was going to take yeah like a
straight
jacket cuz she was going
to uh she was going to take her blood so
it looked really funny
cuz like it was really tight
so only her head um okay cool no problem
only her head showing out was like
really cute with her fluffy fluffy
fluffy
head and then they took the blood and I
actually
started I started feeling sick because
she was taking so much blood and and I
don't know like if it was just a moment
moment I would have been fine but
somehow I felt really
hot cuz like you know it's kind of
winter now and oh and then you go in
with a with a winter jacket and then
yeah I don't know I haven't oh it was
morning and I haven't had breakfast yet
by the way so that might have affected
it too and I was kind of dehydrated and
I was exhausted from carrying chunky
wonky you know all these things getting
together and then I don't know that that
tiny amount of blood in Fe it's tiny
because it's a cat right even if it's a
lot for the cat for me it should be
nothing but I don't know I don't know I
started getting sick and I was like yumy
I need to support my cat I need to pet
her but also I need to sit the [\h__\h] down
we get some fresh air I Tred Holding
Out for as long as I
could
but yeah then I have had to sit down a
little bit and watch chunky wony from
the distance but even then she was doing
so
well even then she was doing so well
even when Mommy wasn't petting her ah
she's such a good baby I'm so proud I'm
so proud she's also not as like [\h__\h]
about going into the um transportation
cage as smoothie like I I last time when
I was bringing smoothie to the vet uh it
was like I had to bring her again and
again cuz the vet was that kind of vet I
switched already who wants all your
money so he makes
you he makes you come back several
times
yeah oh my
God oh my God this
game so like I had to bring her like
twice tce a
week a few times and and and and she
like getting her into the Vet was like a
a real fight between me and my cat into
the into the
cage which is why then I I bought
something else right I bought like a
backpack but I haven't used it since cuz
then when I bought the backpack it was
already like I was done with smoothie
with bringing her to the
[Music]
bed
okay
finally yeah smoothie is just really
annoying so I'm glad I have to do this
right now not with smoothie but with
chunky wonky smoothie would not be so
well behaved for
sure yeah um but yeah blood test and
then and then and then ah and then she
got a little uh Spritz
uh what do you call it again can I not
go left by the way you wouldn't want
that
maybe a shot no not a shot an injection
yeah of like something that she said
should help her with at least for that
day with throwing up not throwing up I
[Music]
guess yeah and she was so well behaved
during that
too
everything like it just didn't seem to
bother her she was just
[Music]
chilling so
cute I'm so proud thank you chunky
wonky for your sweetness you're the best
she's so cute and then I brought her
home and then even even you know the
whole way of bringing her home she was
well behaved like she did seem like
maybe now she would want to get out like
she was really calm in the cage before
that but now she was like looking around
a bit more on the way home probably
losing her
[Music]
patience just like me just like
me just like
[Music]
me
I need to save my voice you know I have
lots of recordings to
do and and it's just like normally I
rage a lot of games but this is actually
like a really
unbelievable situation for me like I
can't believe the audacity of this game
right
now it's honestly baffling to me so I I
can't even
scream I can't even scream
[Music]
but it's okay even in the on the way
back you know normally I was like when I
when I would walk around with her I I
don't carry her like hanging her down I
carry her like like close to my chest
because I need the the strength of my
both of my arms ideally to carry
her and so I would the opening where you
would see her face I would usually like
try to hold it so that
people don't can't peek inside cuz I
don't want I don't want chunky wony to
feel uncomfortable and I don't want
people to be like okay no actually I
don't mind because then it happened when
I was sitting in the trans public
transport some older lady and an older
guy they were really curiously peeking
in and and they were like oh my God
she's so beautiful she's so
cute what kind of cat is she I and and I
I I was
uh I I was again flattered I feel so
happy when people praise my
[Music]
[Applause]
cat
[Music]
do you guys understand
this do you guys have you guys tried
this game it's really cheap you should
try it it's fun it's so
fun also I want Amy to play
it please
Amy
please just because I feel like it fits
her
style and and she likes platformer and
raging games
right like we all
do you play different rage games this
game doesn't look fun what it's
fun of course it is I know she played
Mario Wonder yesterday I love her her I
love her I love
M and she DMD me and
she uh all of nowhere
[Music]
today showing me my Archive of my VR
dance
school I don't know how she was why she
was thinking about it but she said we
should do this
again I'm like yeah sure but like maybe
after my Japan
trip I said maybe we we can do a a
Christmas
special I just I I I'll be honest like I
don't really like doing stuff in VR
because the thing is super heavy and
it's like exhausting and mine especially
feels like hella scuffed compared to the
other girls's
uh [\h__\h] other girls's uh devices cuz
they have they all have a different one
than me I think maybe there's like one
member who has the same one as me I
don't
[Music]
know that one time I got that jump I was
so lucky and I knew it I knew I was
really wait where am
I where is
this ah here okay okay okay I knew I was
so
[Music]
lucky it's a tiny ass
platform
so [\h__\h]
tiny also the one problem during that VR
stream also was audio like really we
have to figure out a better solution for
that I guess because I think GAA and
Amma were hearing it delayed and we
tried to fix that but wasn't
really
possible delay was
bad and then me having to go back and
forth to like control maybe next time we
can have someone else control the audio
the video and
stuff so that I don't have to keep on
taking my goggles off and on blah blah
blah yeah I know the VR streams were
always like really Charming I know I
know and you know I know I know am
talked a little bit about it like you
know why she didn't do anything for
Halloween this time and I don't think
you know I don't think it always should
be her you know like just to take the
pressure off of her I don't think it's
fair to always rely on her to do these
things that's also why I tried to plan
at least something else like not VR but
at least something you know Family
[Applause]
Feud I don't really have
the the
brain and the knowledge to plan like a
VR
stream um I mean I could I mean I've
done it before I guess with the dance
school but even then I had a of help of
but yeah like
okay I don't think I can I'll bounce
off um I think it's fine that it'll like
now it's not I'm doing something every
freaking time especially now that we
have a new gen maybe the new genen can
try planning and bigger things too you
know I just I I personally
I don't want to always rely on Amy I
love her but I I feel like it's not fair
to her but the things she does plan are
always genius and I always enjoy them
and if she does plan something that I
always want to join you know I I always
want to support her projects you
know um so I know she said something
like maybe maybe the girls aren
like maybe they're like a little bit
burnt out on VR or something and I'll be
honest yeah like I hate I hate it
um cuz it's just exhausting man maybe I
would maybe it wouldn't be so exhausting
for me if I had the other device or if I
tried one of these new ones cuz like
this year they
released like a lot of new stuff in
terms of
VR like less weight no
cable uh goggles for example
[Music]
right
and I'm falling
[Music]
down a
banana
ha
ha who would have seen that
[Music]
coming
eh I don't need to jump oh can what do
you mean it doesn't didn't look like the
bee really touched the
edge that I could just walk
[Music]
over oh yeah but yeah I'll see what I
can do with the dance school I don't
know which dance I would teach it would
be nice to have something Christmas be
but wait is there is there is there an
anime song that has a CH on
existing that's like kind of
christmase or like a vocalize
song oh I don't know
snow it looks I I feel like that one
might be difficult Padu is there a real
dance for
padoru I guess I should come up with one
but N I feel I liked that one that we
did before those because they're
everybody knows them
and they're
[Music]
legendary wait do we have a Christmas
song no right we don't have a Christmas
song does whole L have a Christmas song
why have we not released a Christmas
song so far
no I don't okay I don't consider the 12
Days of Christmas no no no no
no but no why don't we like everybody
needs a like one Christmas song in the
repertoire [\h__\h]
[Music]
hell
it's like you can't even control your
jumps it just does like
whatever I it's just
[Music]
like straight jumps are still somewhat
okay like
straightforward but these upwards
bouncing off jumps they can go [\h__\h]
[Music]
themselves nice fine I'm fine I'm fine
I'm not angry
[Music]
I'm fine my recovery is going pretty
well
nowadays now now a minutes now a now an
[Music]
hours yeah I'm good at the great
part can't make
me crumble there
anymore [\h__\h]
your
okay I know that was that was premature
um just like your birth no
[Music]
um where are we where are we in my
tangents
[Music]
huh uh VR so maybe maybe I could do
something but it wouldn't be like I
don't know dance school with like 15 or
10 to 15 members I can't really imagine
that's too chaotic
that's too [\h__\h] chaotic oh it does
touch
okay it's too chaotic so I I I would
rather do it with a small amount of
people
[Music]
no
please be
taxi thank you oh
[Music]
cute why do you I have to go down like
this it's like it's mocking
me it's mocking me when it's bouncing
off its
[Music]
tail be taxi represents am
carrying then I love the be
taxi a myth M event what
no I don't know if I want
to I don't I don't want to plan like
something that's
like that big it scares me it scares me
I don't want
the
responsibility also you know these
things are expensive too like planning
like uh ordering 3D worlds like Amma
usually
does I don't even want to imagine what
her bills looked
[Music]
like now we have a lot of world uh that
we can choose though also our winter
World from like yeah not not was it last
year like last last year when we first
used that one I always feel like you
though we should reuse those because
they're beautiful and and obviously it's
a waste to not reuse
them now
nice hey wait for
me hey nice jump off early for
safety we could reuse it and just
redecorate it or so
but where are we going where are we
going Yahoo
wow look at these tiny ass jumps now
[\h__\h]
that n no
way no [\h__\h] way no
no nah I'm going to fall down 100% And
you know where this is this leads back
to the
bananas unless you
land somehow luckily on the
bee
n
[Music]
yeah sure yeah yeah how the [\h__\h] am I
supposed to do this kind of
jump
[Music]
go oh danger danger danger noodle oh oh
I could go to the middle one oh ah maybe
I can maybe I
can thank you for the red CH oh
oh don't [\h__\h] it up don't [\h__\h] it up I'm
going to [\h__\h] it up I'm going to [\h__\h] it
up I'm going to [\h__\h] it up I'm going to
[\h__\h] it up I'm going to [\h__\h] it up don't
[\h__\h] it up don't [\h__\h] it up though
[Music]
[Applause]
ideally oh my God but I'm going to I'm
going to die soon you know that guys
right uh
uh have to do it
again but that skipping the first one is
pretty
[Music]
smart totally
manageable oh nice you see me just
likeing maybe I can jump from
here no what
[Music]
no d d d
noodle
oh oh Mama
Mia Mama
Mia okay I'm a taxi I love these I love
these [\h__\h]
worms
oh
[Music]
oh better jump off
early so other otherwise if you bounce
off then you
[\h__\h] no
no back to work
okay
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
w
[Applause]
[Music]
I hate this part why is this my most
hated
[Music]
part why can I not do this
one damn these jumps are
crazy
oh my I didn't even think about that
one gosh I'm getting like really good at
it but like is it actually worth it huh
is it worth the [\h__\h]
anger this is so cute though like this
is this this might be worth everything
looking at the the war being carried by
the Bee makes it worth
it
oh my
God oh my
God just don't
[Music]
think yeah any if anyway anyway any
anyway if we want to do something
special for Christmas we should probably
like start
[Music]
planning
no
[Music]
ah it's
okay I wonder how we could use that
world but still do something different
not like completely the same I think
like certain things we could maybe
repeat like the Christmas like Christmas
tree section with the balls cuz I want
to see I want to see Advent creating
their own balls what am I doing what am
I doing what am I
[Music]
doing yeah and like always could
Implement uh uh a secret santa kind of
thing
[Music]
oh yeah right Advent perfect uh we are
working on the Advent calendar by the
way now with the support of
management and the the wallet of
management not my
wallet oh [\h__\h] that reminds me I have
to I have to transfer the domain
before
before the
deadline you're
bear you're bear I don't even know how
to do
it let
me remind
myself by reminding them to remind
me um reminds me to tr
to have you guys tell
me how to transfer
the
domain cuz we want to use the same
one
yeah I remind you to remind me actually
that's what that is that's a reminder
for you not you guys
them the team of the Advent
calendar and we're basically going to
just work with the same people as last
year
um and I'm still like kind of organizing
it I'm like the I'm the Puppet
Master somewhat at least when it comes
to um puppeteering the
talents getting them to submit
videos yeah [\h__\h]
hell but hopefully this time like the
plan is because it's you know in
corporation with management my nose is
so itchy the whole
time cuz if if in cooporation of
management we want to have everything
done way earlier this time like not a
day or hours before uh the video should
go up no this time also for the sake of
the
artist we're going to have it earlier
although I don't know if I really like
the
way uh I feel like I want to suggest uh
an improvement of our ways
[Music]
now still it's still my product it's
still my baby and I I get I get a good
say in how we're doing
things so many ghost rounds yeah they're
all
me it's I don't know it's nice that you
know it
can
[Music]
yeah of course that's going to happen of
course that's going to happen because
how the [\h__\h] can I recover from
there it's too close to the
ceiling no I don't want to talk to them
off because they do possibly they could
show
me how I can do things right and how I
can do things
wrong but at the same time they're
mocking
me and just showing me
how meaningless all of this
is look at all these stupid ass
worms just wasting your
[Music]
time they only show
mistakes what
purposefully that's so
rude well then at least I can show you
how to not do things I guess but damn
show me when I'm doing it right
[Music]
man at least I didn't fall down in the
middle I know what the I I know where to
jump in theur it's like earlier earlier
than you
think I know
that like here instead of here kind of
[Music]
see
well that was not
good look at the other one fell down to
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
w
o
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't like going silent in my streams
but in moments like
[Music]
these how can I not
be
[Music]
[Applause]
o that's in the
way thank
[Music]
you it's different cuz when you silent
we know it's really messed up mhm
mhm
is this how I would have been if I would
have played Jump King I
wonder we should just talk about
something you know we just got to talk
about
something
no I'm so good at that first jump
[Music]
now so
good
what do you think maybe jumping is I
don't I've seen some pretty big Falls if
you're unlucky then you can fall so far
in Jump
King it's
actually
[Music]
disgusting which one is
worse oh [\h__\h] hell I hate this jump
you did so good on H up thank you I
talked about it in detail in my member
stream but yeah I had a I had a great
experience I felt very proud of myself
and I I feel like
I I kind
of I don't know overcame a a a big big
invisible wall inside
my
inside my brain that I put up
[Music]
myself now so I really I really
practiced very hard but like the thing
is my biggest problem is performing
Under
Pressure
um I mean I don't know there's been
there's times where I do well on
pressure and times where I do badly but
I think mostly in situations like those
like a tournament stream I mostly do
[Music]
badly at least when it's like when
there's like all eyes on me if it's like
games tournaments where there's way more
participants like the other games that I
participated in like the the the Kus and
the the horse the horse
one that was totally fine
[Music]
fine oh timer timer is also pretty bad
although the timer was extremely
[Music]
generous we all were able to do it
within the timer normally
with most of us with a lot of extra
time so oh [\h__\h] wait I missed the time
let me do it
[Music]
again that was plenty plenty of
time okay okay I'm back I'm back
Y and soon I will fall down
again hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey oh [\h__\h] W I can't believe I just did
that oh my God okay I feel like we have
to use the small platforms otherwise
they wouldn't be there and I failed I
failed I think last time I tried this
jump from here but I'm bad with these
tiny
[Music]
jumps oh my God rude rude rude rude rude
rude rude rude
rude rude as
[\h__\h] I don't know like it does it just
does it you can't control it it just
goes wherever it [\h__\h]
[Music]
wants I can't slow it down can only jump
like I'm on
edge that one is good though that's a
good
jump oh I wonder if I could do
[Music]
like
[Applause]
[Music]
should we just play like
this
[Music]
look at this ugly ass Worm look at you
[\h__\h] you you suck stupid stupid [\h__\h]
ugly worm I love you you're cute you're
cute as [\h__\h] but I hate
you it dust I shall insult
you
he's got three hairs yeah oh my God I
just noticed the hairs thank you for
pointing the hairs
out should we pluck them
[Music]
out of
[Applause]
[Music]
pliers make it
suffer no not
acceptable we will not fall down down
here
no
no no no no
[Music]
no I'm good at that part but the first
jump is a bit iffy sometimes okay yeah
[\h__\h] you yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
well what [\h__\h] do you worm I love worms
though I love especially hairy
caterpillars
I'm sending so many mixed signal signals
like within 5 seconds I'm telling the
worm and the game that I love it and
then I hate
it it must be really confused I'm also
[Music]
confused complicated
relationship well yeah I I saw some
mentions about sua
game it does seem like this is where all
the fruit
goes and the worms are like maybe maybe
the worms have to take care of it and
clean
it but they don't get paid well so
instead they just like chilling hanging
messing
around but so far it seems fine because
there's not that much
fruit laying around here [\h__\h] you
[Music]
[Applause]
no they look like spatler these
[Music]
worms remember my first cooking stream I
think it was my first my first hand cam
cooking stream where I made SP
myself the cheese pasta it's not cheese
pasta that's that's
like how can you call it that
K it's not just cheese it's not macaroni
and
[Music]
cheese lasagna was oh right my first one
was lasagna and then was K ah the good
old the good old
times ah yeah yeah
yeah you can't pronounce it well what's
so hard about pronouncing it SP repeat
after me
sp sp
sp
[Music]
sp the chocolate one oh that's that's
not really a cooking stream I didn't
[Music]
cook
my w warm Jo not H warm Joo oh nice so
cute oh so
[Music]
cute
a I'm back
[\h__\h] my nose is so
[Music]
itchy some cat hairs somewhere on my
nose but there's also cat hairs on my
fingers I guess so I can't really like
you
[Music]
know just doesn't want
to let us enjoy the air up here while
we're
[Music]
here
M nice
nice fresh very fresh are you feeling
it
okay worm worm I have an idea I have a
proposal how about you get the [\h__\h] out
of here you help me play this game by
not being so
stupid and then I will reward you by
adding more hairs to your very hairless
sculpt they can be from my kitty cats I
have more more hairs that I could ever
make use
of what do you
think you look so
gorgeous
yeah a nice head of hair yeah maybe your
whole body if you want body hair I can
make that all of that possible for
you for
[Music]
free no
I mean
it just have to be nice to me you know
I'm going to [\h__\h] up this jump it's been
too
[Music]
long oh
my oh my oh I'm doing it no no no no
[Music]
no ah ah
how
how how do I do
this I don't want to fall down I don't
want to fall down he's like
automatically falling down be careful
got to be
careful I know like here if I jump from
here I bounce off if I jump from here
it's like so
dangerous that's okay that's
[Music]
[Applause]
okay why is there no cover we from up
there to the above of the
bananas so
[Music]
[Applause]
mean
[Music]
no the shadows are some of my previous
attempts but not the successful ones
apparently although some of these are
successful but I guess only up to a
certain
[Music]
point
[Applause]
I'm okay I
mean honestly a rage game might just be
exactly what I need these
days can someone like tell me if it has
been scientifically proven if anybody
has done like a study if rage games are
like a good Outlet
of Rage that has been pent up inside
you
[Music]
I would like to know if I'm actually
helping myself then then I will play
rage games more
[Music]
often got to ask Callie if during her
dump King Arc did you feel generally on
the scale of 1 to
five
one extremely relieved of
stress to
[Music]
[Applause]
to severely less stressed
free kind of less
stressed
four stressed or five more
stressed please please take the the box
that applies the most to
you swollen with
stress
[Music]
my
my that one is like such a
toughy and you can't really practice it
properly cuz if you fail you fall down a
[Music]
lot
woo it's actually bad if you do it
frequently Studies have shown that
releasing anger in Hobbies is a good to
mod
[Music]
don't breathe while jumping wa don't
breathe while
jumping I was
lucky don't war and read
that they must have they must have hoped
for this to
[Music]
happen wow wow w wow no
wa too late for my
taxi hey don't jump to death worm I look
at go look at it look at it
[Music]
[Applause]
go let's
go they see me rolling they see me
[Music]
hating I know the angle this and that
like but what am I supposed to do on
like here like there's only two angles I
can possibly be
[Music]
at
[Applause]
[Music]
y
[Applause]
[Music]
f
but I do find it fascinating how these
sections that first seems so difficult
and so impossible you do get better at
it and it does feel good like getting
through it
quickly but like what the [\h__\h] man like
why what what what
[Music]
why oh you know what I heard
yesterday
I I I messaged I messaged
um I messaged
RT and and RT is like really close to um
someone that uh I used to work with like
my the I I may have told you about her
before like the lady the superior at
work that's okay that's okay the
superior at work that is like super cute
and I love her
and kind
[Music]
of kind
of Dream Woman um but anyway
um
um so she told me oh did you know she's
playing now for a while
already I'm like oh my
God like she's going to Bear the best
human ever like anything that comes out
of
her is like going to be a blessing to
this
world not
[Applause]
there
honestly
[Music]
amazing makes me happy to hear that but
it's crazy to imagine like cuz I only
know her
not and she's like small and and pretty
thin you know imagining like a big belly
attached to that it's like kind of
crazy kind of crazy
woo and she's a freaking extreme
workaholic so I think this is really
good cuz it forces her to not
work maybe I
should maybe
maybe should I say this is [\h__\h]
cursed what I'm thinking about right now
is [\h__\h]
cursed I'm not thinking about myself no
no
no what what what do you think where I'm
going what do you think where I'm
going say it you say
it what what what do you
think no
no no no
no I was yeah it it was I was yeah it
was going to be about
JMA
[Music]
you know it's it's it's Goodwill what
I'm trying to say is it's just Goodwill
but it's so cursed I understand I
understand I completely
[Music]
understand
I don't know I don't
know what I oh my
god
[Music]
oh oh my God orang right oh it's bouncy
oh I love the
bounce it's a I think it's
[Music]
a
it's man mean but hey we were we're
bound to fall down at least a few times
you
know you can't I can't not fall down
there at least once when I I've never
been there
before this is what the game is
about it's okay it's okay we accept a
few Falls
let's see if we get good at this
part nice oh I could have almost jumped
up there now how the [\h__\h] did I do
this I said in Japanese I said I don't
[\h__\h] know maybe I say that
again yeah
okay seems to be the way to
go
[Music]
okay okay okay
okay
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah that's that's
cool I got two DMS are there for from
JMA
yes I didn't think Jemma would be
watching I thought she would be
sleeping ah yeah yeah whatever
[Music]
whatever she was
like what's this part how what where am
I
am
oh red
apples so at the very [\h__\h] beginning
almost okay cool cool cool cool cool
cool cool cool cool cool
cool no no cool
[Music]
fun you
know jenma is very busy so you know I am
also very busy we are very busy so much
to
do so much to
prepare I'm actually losing my mind over
[Music]
it there's so many things I'm forgetting
too that need to be
done and now now I even have even more
unnecessary [\h__\h] that I really don't
need right now like handling
FedEx oh
[Music]
so like uh cover sent me some merch
right samples from my own merch like
just so that I could get like one piece
of my merch okay cool that was bad I
know it was way too early to
jump
um
and
I didn't get like any notification from
them and the tracking also doesn't say
like please contact us but I noticed
it's like stuck you
know so I gave him a call AI talked to
me I was like [\h__\h] that well they
couldn't even help me they the AI even
said uh I can't help you unless you have
an account with us so please chat to the
to the other AI on the
website and I go to the website but
thankfully if you say I don't I want to
talk to a human if you type that into
the chat
they do um connect you to a
human so I talk to the human in the
chat
and they told me oh my god well your
packet should have actually already been
sent back
today but since you just replied to us
please
contact FedEx email this email
and sent
them confirmation of order and payment
and this and that and I say oh but it's
not dad and they're like oh okay I can't
help you please contact this place is
your is this phone number correct and I
say yeah so then when I was about to
write an email I get a call actually hey
I don't even have an account but if they
call you I guess that's
fine so I get a call from
FedEx which I wel
come and I explained that thank you I
don't
have uh any of these things they're
asking of
[Music]
me and then they're like oh so you are G
and I say I don't know if I would say
I'm
Gish I just uh I'm I'm a freelancer but
I I just got some stuff from the company
I work
for so I would like to receive that
please I didn't pay for it cuz it's not
something I pay for and then but they
say yeah okay so this is g g is
commercial
so I need something else from you now I
need I need this crazy
number that you don't normally Happ you
have to sign up for it and in order to
get that number you need another
number to sign up for that and this
there's lots of paperwork this and that
BL blah
[Music]
blue
yeah oh my
God and I
said [\h__\h] that the thing I remember um
for
the may I think it was for the
PlayStation
5 I had to do that back then as well
oh maybe maybe it was for the
PlayStation 5 or
[Music]
something
else but I got that stupid number and
then I don't didn't need it anymore so
we basically like shut it down my tax
lady was like helping me with that but
anyway I call my tax lady cuz like the
moment I opened
the the like the sign up page for those
stupid ass numbers registration
numbers I I was like what the [\h__\h]
man complicated as [\h__\h] I don't know
complicated
words let's let my tax lady do it again
at least one good thing she can
[Music]
do so I called my tax lady and I
explained it to her and
she told old me while in order to get
that number you first need that number
and now you don't have that
number so you know it's just all [\h__\h]
annoying and oh
man
but now I I'm even considering just
letting it be sent back picking it up in
Japan could make it in
time just pick it up in Japan and then
bring it home bring a second suitcase I
don't
know and then you know I was thinking
for the for the accent
suit they also want an also a stupid
number they want the vat number right
and I don't I I don't have it I mean you
could make it
now
but my tax lady said that's also kind of
complicated um like there's so much
complicated [\h__\h] okay so maybe I'll try
to get them to send it to Japan after
all and pick it up cuz I didn't want to
do that because I it was kind of like
time pressured but now it doesn't matter
cuz like I changed my plans and there's
not really time pressure anymore and I'm
going to Japan soon so I might as well
pick it up if they would send it to
Japan and then to me then that would be
annoying again cuz probably I would run
into stupid stupid issues with the
Customs again and and yeah but if I can
pick it up then maybe it's
fine so trying to figure out all that
kind of stuff too that
now it would be easier if I can just
pick it up but my trip is pretty short
so if I just miss it you know that's
going to
be anger
inducing not as anger inducing as this
game
but imagine they're sending the suit and
and the stuff that is now in Europe
already at the Customs imagine they sent
that back to Japan now
in theory it should arrive like pretty
quickly but you never know also it
really amazes me sending things to Japan
is like no problem what do they not have
Customs I mean they do but they don't
seem to care much unless you're like
sending meat or or fruit or something
like that's they really care about that
stuff
but if you're sending just
like
can I get up
there not worth the [\h__\h]
trouble I was just warming
[Music]
around I was just warming around man
[Applause]
innocently recently had issues with
customs with merch I bought you mean two
Europe
up but I think sending stuff to Japan
like I I don't think there's ever any
[Music]
problems Europe hates Imports yeah
Europe especially like I think last year
or this year beginning of this year I
don't know they um they changed their
laws I think it was especially Austria
too like Austria changed its uh laws a
little bit on its own independently from
Europe to be even more
strict so
that a lot of my friends you know they
order a lot of stuff from from China my
my German and my Austrian
friends and my Austrian friends like
it's not so easy for them anymore a lot
of these Chinese sellers don't want to
send to Austria anymore cuz like it's
really difficult you it's still possible
but they made it really difficult so a
lot of my friends like let these things
be sent to Germany instead and then have
their friends in Germany send it to
[Music]
Austria it's ridiculous and it's more
expensive now too than in the past the
[Music]
Customs what
what I'm so
good actually I I may have potential for
these kind of games what do you
think is Austrian Customs even wor than
German
yeah yeah it
is definitely I don't want to brag
but I do have
potential jumping no no reason I picked
this up is because the visuals are so
[Music]
cute no okay okay okay
okay okay the only times I ever made
that jump is when I scream
[Music]
vak
wow
[Music]
Bounce no no no
[Applause]
no okay it's after the the bananas I
mean there's another banana here but
it's a different one okay can you just
stand normally like lie down not
stand it's
over it's okay it's okay I I figured it
out I figured it all out
first tried that part too
nice oh sh that's risky of me to go
through so
[Music]
fast how big is no idea I have like
absolutely no idea how much I got ahead
of
me and I I can promise
you I'm not going to try to
even find the end of
[Applause]
it I don't think I passed m m played it
for like 3 hours couldn't
[Music]
imagine
oh yum almost there
m almost
[Music]
where [\h__\h] be can you wait a moment
for
[Music]
me she got about as far as you only a
bit forever not speaking of far of far
how far in a game um I'm planning to
play Final Fantasy
tomorrow um I know we said that I
probably can't finish it in the Stream
and that's fine but you guys like does
anybody know like how far did we think I
have left so that just I can like um
figure out what to prepare for and how
much free time I'll have to do other
work behind the
scenes 12 hour with no side quest okay
so like 6 hours maybe per
[Music]
stream
like seven being generous maybe
seven okay I can do
that I can do
that
[Music]
get
oh wait wait wait
[Music]
wait what can I
say too far no yes
[Music]
fore
so
[Music]
warm can't hear
it say it say
[Music]
[Applause]
it
[Music]
going out side uhhuh yeah yeah are you
really sorry are you are you guys worms
why are you saying sorry I asked the
worm to say
[Applause]
[Music]
sorry
would you still love me if I was a war H
never mind I I don't
[Music]
know what was that jump you little
[\h__\h] what was
[Music]
that
where are the secret shortcuts
guys tell
me I know there are none at least I
don't know maybe there are but it was a
joke it was a joke from my
[Music]
side this isn't only up only up has
secret
shortcuts if you love froggy wa why
would we love warm chill worm Cho has no
arms worm Cho has no
feet worm Cho has nothing to
offer I would just be a
[Music]
worm all I can do is
warm and honestly warm CH should only
exist as an offering to froggy waa
[Music]
M Mia
M woo sick flip though man I could
perform in cir the solay as a worm
that's
something
you need a lot of confidence for that
jump but if you have confidence it's
pretty
easy
[Music]
jum maybe this whole game just it's
about
confidence I love this I just love being
a worm on a be
[Music]
Taxi
no not back don't go
[Music]
back okay hi I'm back I'm back here in
this area that we don't see so
[Music]
often
yay
yay just YOLO roll on the oranges all
the way no could work but not going to
risk it that was dangerous by the
way okay never seen this part so this is
new um looks
difficult I'm going to it
up but just just got a YOLO like what do
I even do I don't even want to think
about it I I don't I don't know I'm just
going to jump and see what
[Music]
happens the oranges eat your jump do
they yeah I'm just I I hope hope I just
turn into Sanic and then
just roll off of everything I don't know
we're just going to we're just going
to what I've been here before
really we're just going to jump but just
not going to think too much but where
where do I start jumping like on the
edge here down here or like up here what
do you think is the way to
[Music]
go I failed this before and why don't I
see my past worm here maybe cuz there
was only one and it's already gone ah
there it is what did you do what did you
do
oh I I jumped like around here and I did
land but I just warmed off off the
cliff not a hold
[Music]
on
don't don't be so rude to my head warm
my brain
[Music]
warms nailed
it oh that's fine
like a few fails are certainly
necessary and the The Landing there
isn't so
bad like how far you set back there
isn't too bad like here here I could be
set back all the way to the ban bananas
yeah that's pretty
bad so but what happened like my jump
was not long enough this time I think I
just
didn't didn't land a landing at
[Music]
all
I just want to see what's on the other
side of the
oranges I just want to see what's
[Music]
there oh
man oh man
[Music]
[Applause]
y
[Music]
that's
fine I'm so good at
coping
man three years of H life have taught
[Music]
me I don't know
I don't know what that means I don't
know what that
[Music]
implies oh [\h__\h]
man
[Music]
yeah yeah I just I mean yeah yeah yeah I
at the accept in stage like in many ways
not not just this
game just in terms of
[Music]
life just
generally it's just not worth
oh worth
getting so upset about
[Music]
right oh wait wait way too way too late
I it didn't
look could have made it still
though
yeah cul is an important life
skill cul or
[Music]
die
banana no be it's a be takasi Kiara
it is what it is yeah I am in the it is
what it is Arc the like the Hopeless
[Music]
Arc no cope no
hope yes cope but no
hope it's okay like you know I'll I'll
probably get out of
[Music]
it wait I wasn't
ready no hey hey I made it up but I fall
[Music]
down it's the vakai
jump what am I doing here what I usually
do here I
forgot do I just get
lucky backwards flips
[Music]
[Applause]
my biggest enemy
during physical education
[Music]
class but not like flips just backwards
rolls they didn't make us do flips but
uh you
know just back
rolls
what's going on it's like I'm in a slump
[Music]
slump
no B
twice this
bee loves me must be
[Music]
am what am I
doing I can't can't do it what I don't
even
okay
[Music]
okay oh you I don't think
to it's really difficult like maybe it's
possible to get up to the second one but
night um seems really iffy
[Music]
wait yeah okay just got to go to where
it goes
straight then the jump
Works
[Music]
hey okay I can do it without back on
night
now
hey
well can
[Music]
I what is this
section
nice look at me look at
me no that's mean those are my past runs
yeah not there not
[Music]
online
[Applause]
[Music]
oh anyway I keep on warming
I just keep on
warming stand back she's
[Music]
warming H one
wait I'm losing it I'm losing it I'm
losing it I'm losing
it I'm losing it I'm losing it I'm
losing
[Music]
[Applause]
it
I wish I had teeth like
Amy then I could show
you my copious
[Music]
[Applause]
smile
[Music]
but look at me this is what happens if
you don't have health
care if your job doesn't bring you what
what do people always dental care ask
for in America when they get a job do
you guys have dental
[Music]
care
H you have teeth too I'm so jealous
[Music]
this jump really
sucks no teeth
W no
teeth I have no
teeth but I got sick ass jumps look I'm
even like timed with my old self of Mama
Mia but it took an earlier
[Music]
taxi can I have your
teeth
[Music]
[Applause]
Ora
[Music]
huh
f
[Music]
woo
w
[Music]
oh
amusing amusing are you amused guys
[Applause]
[Music]
H you can do it you can do it you can do
it you can do
[Music]
it
[Applause]
[Music]
War ghost Army yeah with so many worms
we can clean up all the sua
[Music]
trash
this is like the Gondor
battle so true this is exactly play a
one to
one
remake
rebuild of what
[Music]
happened what do the jump WWA you can do
it that's what I'm talking about that's
what I'm talk not talking about what the
hell
our our
worm Lego
[Music]
worm sunwise
warm hey
hey
warm
do sour
[Music]
warm sorry I was watching I was looking
at War air that one's good too
cuz it sounds still like the OG
name you know what this makes me want to
do this makes me want to organize
another worms
[Music]
collab ideally with ideally including am
and gura cuz they're just
like the perfect kind of people for that
kind of
game hey hey
[Music]
hey what you doing what you doing you
little
[Music]
[\h__\h] we should have flal play worms but
like against each
other moku can let out her
rage her
frustration I really support Moco
finding Outlets
[Music]
I love the dynamic that they
have FL back seating and me just
imagining in my
brain all the things that
M would like to say to for
[Music]
while she could if she could
no of course not they there they are
like if they if they weren't
like twins that get along extremely
well they would not be doing this you
know this job together and I know I
know out of personal experience how
close they are
and how how to say how you can literally
not separate them no matter what I think
they'll they'll spend their whole life
[Music]
together and all the rage and whatever
you know
that's just you know
fun banter
entertainment but I love it I love just
the idea
of M absolutely losing
it yeah anyway this makes me thinking
about them being so
freaking like well together makes me
calm down makes me happy this does not
this does not
[Music]
however
the one I
[Music]
retreated
yeah I meant obviously I meant smoovie
is the one that goes bow bow bow but
like with meow meow meow and then the
way the way F was screeched oh my
God we have never been so far back for a
long
time this is a difficult jump
how do you how do you give this to
beginners this jump
huh how do you think this is
justifiable
welcome well
[Music]
thanks you SC
sometimes sometimes i' the thing is it
doesn't work she doesn't give a [\h__\h]
even if I bring out the big biggest rage
screams of my
life way worse than my rage screams on
[Music]
stream like pure anger you know she
doesn't care like she doesn't think
anything's
wrong so I gave up and then for some
time I would um try to close the door
right but my cats are used to a
lifestyle where the doors are always
open
so when they are closed and I am not
with them in the closed room if I am
behind the closed
doors Dave will not tolerate
it which I think is in some way
cute but like it it worked
maybe one night I'm not not faced by
this it worked maybe one night um and
then the second night I would try that
was already impossible like cuz like and
it she made me worry because like she
would start scratching so hard on the
door like it was two layers of doors
okay and what the thing is one door is a
normal door and the other door is a
sliding door the normal door she can
open but thankfully there's a first
layer of a sliding door
[Music]
and the sliding door she can't open she
she could attempt to open normal doors
she has the skill for
it um but even when I have that door
closed I still kind of hear her
scratching and trying to get in between
the the the sliding
door and it makes me worry that she's
going to hurt herself cuz she just does
it endlessly
and I hear her
scratching trying not scratching like
normal scratching but like more like
um let me see this this is normal
scratching right but what she does is
like you know like trying
to get through the the like a tiny
opening or
whatever and and that makes me worry
like uh I don't want her to
like destroy her nails completely her
claws so I don't when I hear that I'm
I'm like okay I can't I can't do this
can't I can't let her she won't stop
like there was one time where she would
stop but then when I would do this more
often she would not
stop I haven't done it in a while though
like closing
her off in another
[Music]
room hi B I know it's been a while thank
you for still working so hard
hardworking
[Music]
bee oh was that a suicide warm
huh solution is to cover your or with
soft stuff no the solution is just
to just to give in to your cats cuz they
are the
[Music]
[Applause]
overlords
[Music]
night
that wasn't confident enough I need to
be
[Music]
confident don't go
back
[Music]
H how can I how can I I can't do it
[Applause]
anymore Lally my wingman
holy
moly what a
bee what a be what a be what a be what a
freaking good
be what a be what a be what a be what a
lovely
be my beloved
[Music]
be
ah
[Music]
back to my
cat so mostly these days it's not as bad
anymore as during that one face where I
I was just going insane cuz smoothie was
going at it every night no it's not that
bad
[Music]
anymore you can skip that part if you
keep pressing space you mean which part
this
part I don't need to skip this part I'm
good at this what what do you mean what
am I
doing she did not wait for the be
Taxi
why did she not wait for the be
taxi why did she not wait for the the
the orange okay next time I at the
oranges I'm just going to jump forever
forever does that actually work I was
wondering if that might actually work if
you don't know where think it just jump
forever endless
[Music]
jumping
he do you mean even even over the last
orange like uh over the the green
[Music]
part I was wondering about
that she K does it there are you guys
seen her do
it how did C get the
idea hey hey hey
hey hey hey you
you I don't like your stupid
[Music]
face your worm friend hey hey you you I
don't like your worm friend no no you
you think you need a new one a new
worm hey hey you you I don't like your
worm
[Music]
friends
da meow meow meow meow meow
[Music]
meow okay I don't know how much more I
will tolerate this game wasting my
time
not much
[Music]
longer today is just supposed to
be a little fun evening with
[Music]
kfp so all that matters to
me is that this worm will be set
[Music]
free
AKA did I kill it with
fire burn it melt
it setting its Soul
free from all the crimes it has
[Music]
committed I am a saint and this worm is
a
sinner
and that is clear also to the eyes of a
beginner but even more to those who you
call a
[Music]
[Applause]
winner and in the end I will get warm
warm chicken
[Music]
dinner
po I hate this
jump certain jumps are
[Applause]
[Music]
just ha my ghost
failed okay hi be this time I will wait
for you I don't know what got into me
that at that
point I like how the worm always like
turns around when it tries to board the
taxi the Shakespeare of our
time thus I shall be
[Applause]
named shakes
[Music]
Jo
I do get to shake sometimes when I'm
nervous
[Music]
yeah this B is
MVP I think we
all sh KN in front of D
be time it didn't save
me but it's okay you can choose
freely of when you want
to be the bee that saves
me this is a poetry slam stream welcome
[Applause]
everybody
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
I will make
it this
time I'm going to get up there to the
oranges I'm not going to fall
anymore do you understand
[Music]
guys that doesn't count cuz I fell to a
place that was relatively
close
[Music]
that also doesn't
count cuz I haven't really begun yet
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
sick jumps sick
jumps this section
[Music]
can suck this war I don't
know oh my my my my ring finger is
starting to hurt cuz my ring finger is
on one of the arrow
[Music]
buttons welcome to the
membership oh thank
God again
again I can't do this jumps anymore much
longer
hyy wait wait yes I'm here I'm
here
[Music]
who the lady's ghosts even even they
have to take a minute to think about
what just happened before they can move
[Applause]
[Music]
on where was The
Bee I'm worried about you sanity me too
Oro I am
concerned
[Music]
no actually I'm
fine keep on saying that if you say it
often enough it will become
[Applause]
[Music]
true like we're Bloody Mary right I
don't
[Music]
know
what are you talking about
[Music]
makaku
vamos what's warm in
[Music]
Spanish or caterpillar I think it's a
caterpillar
[Music]
fuckingo how do I say like how do I
insult
el el
squiggle yeah yeah yeah I'll
squiggle I
SLE oh
I'm Amia Watson in my brain
[Music]
[Applause]
forever I'm his Spanish
being not as much as I expected
[Music]
El diabo that's what that is this is the
most accurate description El
Diablo
[Music]
diabo diabo
Gano Diablo
[Music]
Gano I think I hear babies
in the bgm now like screeching warm
babies
[Music]
nice so you say I should just
roll I wonder if it should start from
here I don't know man I feel like it's
not going to work for me not on the
first
[Music]
try
no I should have rolled a bit more that
looks like I can't make it normally I
don't
[Music]
know okay okay okay okay I wasn't sure
when to stop I thought it was time to
[Music]
stop oh
no got pretty far
[Music]
though yeah yeah yeah yeah no the
oranges weren't really the issue it was
a just a small platform after that but
obviously there were more issues to
arise soon after
wait why did I jump like that why did I
jump so late why why why why why why why
why
[Music]
why is the level like over soon after
that or
[Music]
what that's worm rise
up you can't just put worm in every
word
and call the
day usually one just one Long Level
oh warm
not what the
[\h__\h] watch
me you mean warmed
you I'm 25% well okay then this is not
this is not worth my attention
[Music]
it's not warm for my
attention I do not want to admit the
feet
[Music]
not yet not
yet not
[Music]
yet why are you
dancing why are you playing this game
with
me do the game I can't complain I do the
same
oh do you do you
say do you feel the
[Music]
same my jump was
wrong I don't know
why this worm has a personal V against
me I
[Music]
think this banana is banana blocking
me and
[Music]
squinkle
my finger okay genuinely we really can't
do it much longer but I'm thinking like
maximum to the fre hour
mark because my finger is not
functioning well
anymore and you know I do need my
fingers tomorrow for Final
[Music]
Fantasy
of course we're reading super
[Music]
chats who do you think I
[Applause]
am you didn't save me but it's okay
because this time the
land has saved me oh my God
forsaken Amelia worson
wait wait for
[Music]
me I wish there were more sections where
you just roll through I mean maybe there
are and just nobody has ever
dared to attempt it yeah [\h__\h]
you
yeah
[Music]
sourkraut I don't I don't I only like
sauerkraut in combination with very
certain
foods
um let me try to what do I normally use
Sauer CR eat SAU CR with oh no you
[Music]
didn't
I
think like
[Music]
wouse
uh I guess like normally yeah it's it's
an okay combination to eat
sausages with Sauer Cloud yeah and I
know you see that a lot probably in
Germany but not something I normally
ever
[Music]
eat yeah there's a like I don't have any
problems with S Cloud but the most of
the foods that you classically serve
with it in Austria they're just
not what I really like is Road Crouch
not s
couch it's the purple the purple
[Music]
stuff those are like it's amazing with
apples in it like you cook it with
apples and then you serve it with like
Duck or
something some
game yes amazing wa knows how to call
that uh for
[Music]
Christmas red shredded cabbage yeah I
guess the way we make it here is
absolutely delicious oh my God I I I
wish it was more common to serve this
kind of whole dinner outside of
Christmas
too
sheh
M and even the Frozen one is so
delicious like don't even have to make
it yourself the one in the frozen
section is
like so [\h__\h]
good why angry face cuz I'm
[Music]
angry nothing can
like nothing nothing
nothing can make this
[Music]
better com
sweet com
[Music]
s
shoe
[Music]
cream okay here we
go it's time to
[Applause]
[Music]
warm oh this feels bad oh come on no no
no absolute
[Music]
betrayal
a
nah I'm done I am done I am done I'm
done I'm done I'm
done I'm
done
thank you
for suffering with me it's I like it I
like it I like it
but there's so many things wrong with
it silence is relaxing
right silence is
golden oh my God man man man
man oh Risa is playing baller skate
right
now oh I know where to where to
uh where to warm you guys through
later warming with the warming I think
it's an appropriate way of using this
word and what what what where do we
stream where where do we where I'm out
from I think like possibly Minecraft
white team Practice Day the first one
maybe or yeah probably somewhere
there that's what I thought that's what
I
thought do we have a lot of worms to
read shouldn't be too many
worms
oh what H is this it is this not loading
or
huh does this stream really have eight
super chats okay not this one but the
that one worm speak it was after the the
Polaroid action so you guys are broke
thanks to
me I broke you like this game broke
me
was fun and it's cute and I I liked uh
the sections that I did well at but it's
enough now okay it's enough all good
things must come to an
end let me put in some equally infurious
ating
bgm on
[Music]
here maybe not
equally and take 47 D
um now I can't read the
rat Joda Super Chat properly because
there's a [\h__\h] ridiculous ad in the
middle of my screen and I can't get rid
of it
wait never mind now it's gone
okay okay M I wish you have a great day
as always I've been enjoying many good
things since I came back to Austria
feeling European Wilderness eating nice
foods and wines and other else and
today's my birthday oh happy belated
birthday wait European Wilderness he
went to my mom's
Garden where did you get the
address
I hope you are having fun although I
feel like by now you're probably not in
Austria anymore right or do you mean you
came back from Austria not to Austria
probably
[Music]
probably thank you for all the updates I
hope you're having a lovely time and I
wish you a beautiful birthday it's
already over but I'm so sorry but you
know let's just act as if it's
[Music]
today
congratulations to you
R yes yes Korean currency so I sing in
Korean h
thank you for being part of kfp
hopefully in the following years I can
continue counting on
you ziply D 3,000 ER CED tanks of soup D
lean 7 dun and Valk dun and Sky
dun that was
that and the one right after is the
sponsored one um for uh Star
Ocean start ocean I saw you guys a few
of you guys got yourself the
game are you guys enjoying
it is it
good about the game after you stream
have you been playing it too been
enjoying it good so far playing right
now oh oh
oh oh so many
enjoyers pick up recently it's good
nice not sure yet going to play it on
Thursday oh okay
okay oh I'm curious too but like I don't
have time to
[Music]
play I want to play it though as long as
long as like this stream is not too far
away time wise I would like to play it
while it's still in my
memory but yeah we can kill GTA but no
no no no I'm not going to do a a
playthrough on it
mm- no no no no uh Tales of AR rise has
special treatment in terms of that me
doing full playthrough of a jrpg for
free doesn't work for each single
one but you
know there's um too many other games
right now it's like impossible you
[Music]
know too many also yeah we're like
waiting for other games like um the DLC
and Yakuza and the Mario RPG
thing still got to finish GTA still got
to finish fantasy but I'm hoping to
finish it this
[Music]
week you know lots of my plate Jacob 47
D morally immoral than soon three times
thank
you
oh
was free ms was only a fan to you but
the whole Sports made me a fan of all of
whole life especially Calli and Sor
early in that first month was dealing
with Ching car changing jobs and moving
watching you made that month better feel
like everything would be okay so thanks
oh you're welcome I'm glad that I could
help by Sheely
existing
than I wish you all the best F fight
screw
py Adam
J I leave it R when I get home it's on
whist now it's back to W never ending
cycle
and Daisy thank you for the pinky I
still have vivid memories you mean like
Vivid Cruise memories or what of getting
into an argument with a friend when this
game first came out on PS1 over whether
or not this game was a sequel since we
never got the first one in the US until
the PSP remake
oh
well wow that's something I feel like
you could just look
up but maybe you guys were like too
young to think about that option
the internet has all the answers but how
long is that ago did the internet have
the answers back
then that's a different
time too long
ago there was no in surely there was
internet but not just like that not that
much right like not that accessible and
not that useful
yet
M but like wouldn't that if it was a
sequel I feel like they would you know
make it really clear that it is like on
the on the box of the game or so I don't
know but I see so you also have
Nostalgia for this game I love I love
hearing you guys have experience with
the games that I play especially if it's
like a childhood or teenagehood memory
for you guys that's really nice
H Professor
King arti I find it crazy you guys say
like there's 80 endings for
it or about if not more
[Music]
sheesh Dan while next is
dun Bob K dun thank you wish you did
voice for this one oh I wish too like
I'm waiting for those kind of jobs
forever ever since I joined GD d space
wonderful danash M A Dan and ziply Dan
thank you I mean I guess I did voice
like myself in other games you know but
the cool thing would be to voice a
character that's not myself you know in
like a legit game not just not just some
you
know some you
know you
know you know what I
mean
next
uh next Super
CH so this was apparently the only
stream for the pre- party for the white
team so there was a lot of Japanese
talking going
on sorry about that
guys
but but let's see oh not many super
chats either nice nice nice I guess
Jacob 47
monkey is
[Music]
this
to there's like a [\h__\h] ton of Kes next
to each other it might be Chinese so I
don't know I don't know how to read this
I mean this person will probably never
listen to the Super Chat reading cuz it
seems like they're like a one of those
onetime listeners just because they
there were other people in the Stream so
so it's probably it's probably fine
d
pillar next
is Sport ball
D I don't have anything really in terms
of outfits that's like
winterish
do I noticed this with late too but like
wearing our casual
clothes maybe it's
generally what council went for
the not necessary no not all them but
like um mum went for quite the winter
theme right like a warm warm outfit and
my clothes are ah my Kimo yeah
true yeah maybe like currently I have
planned you know what
outfit I'll be getting
for 2023 which will end up being 2024
but you know it's a 2023 outfit maybe
for the 2024 outfit I could think about
something that will be wintry but I
don't know maybe I'll just like you know
request eventually like uh like a
wintery Cape like M has like the like
the promised girl have like a like a
fluffy wintery Cape so I just I don't
have to like sacrifice a whole outfit
for
it and just put it on top of this
or so
H kiy
cloak D with the jacket looks somewhat
warm yeah yeah
[Music]
somewhat I feel like I had some ideas of
what to do for the next next outfit but
now I forgot
them well still long to go to think
about
it a poncho Poncho's
[Music]
Poncho pajama pajamas oh pajamas would
be cute too yeah they might have a lot
of usage oh yeah there's a lot of play
easy themes like school uniform would be
cool
too but I I don't know some
something
that goes in the direction of a like a
CEO kind of
suit could also be
[Music]
cool I don't see you in the school
uniform well but I want to match with
[Music]
G I just want to
match I can look cute have you not seen
like for the Singapore Cafe
Cafe how cute I look in that g kind of
look high school
uniform I look so cute in
that M
yes with a sweater but like wrapped
around my
hips
cute m m g but not too much just like
really slightly G you know there like
crazy crazy levels of
G picture of
telephone I
[Music]
am
slightly G best
G yeah I would personally agree with
that yeah
[Music]
yeah
oh oh oh cuz I had it off yeah I was
like not a single Super Chat for the mai
stream kind of sad not going to lie but
I had it off they did ask me to turn it
off so
okay then we're at
today's
real wait how do I get to my today's
Super
Chat you didn't let us I'm
sorry I'm
sorry tomorrow 400 p.m. starting time by
the way for Final Fantasy
I want to go long but before before
that I need to record a bit more and I I
said I was going to like do dance
practice recently but I didn't do it
much at all these past days I really
should be doing it
actually
no it's
okay it's okay shouldn't be too bad uh
let me I need to put some things on my
calendar like I need to send
um need to sign
[Music]
documents text lady and
FedEx just don't forget it I'm putting
everything in my Google Calendar cuz
that's the only thing that I actually
look at these
days uh then practice that
song Wreck two songs
Maybe
[Music]
and
mukashi you sure you want to stream yeah
I want to finish it before the Japan
trip and I think I can like if it's
really not not much longer than what you
guys are saying I mean some of you guys
are saying conflicting things but most
of you guys were like 12 hours so that
sounds like I can do
it I'm just wondering just wondering how
to balance it with other
[Music]
things Holo talk soon no not anytime
soon
would be nice if I could squeeze in one
more before the year
ends I'll try you guys going to remind
me
[Music]
though who would be the next guest vame
oruna Senai vame would actually like I
guess be interesting because like
because of the timing like now would be
interesting
cuz like she's planning another concert
now or afterwards I
guess her second
[Music]
concert yeah uh so let's read super
chats from the stream uh
uh
uh do
here you know I dug out a really really
old fan out for this one because I just
wanted something kind of derpy cute
nothing too
serious this one's really old this one's
so old that the person who drew this
they changed their username since but I
I still found
them I still found them I wonder if they
reacted to me using a super old fan art
like oh they retweeted it well sometimes
when I use these super old fan arts I I
wonder they must be thinking like oh
[\h__\h] damn I didn't think she was going
to use it cuz it's been so
long well I have a folder with so many
fan arts that I can like dig through so
that that I find the fitting fan art but
I feel like you know like I have to go
back to older ones recently much more
cuz
like uh recently I don't get much fan
art it's a bit
sad
like
yeah there's still like a good amount of
fan art but like it's not a lot of
sketches and stuff as I said before
M yeah and also like I've been
struggling to find alter kada fan art
but now now there's a I got a couple new
ones I
saw that's all you needed to
say
please
[Music]
please I only meme sorry no problem
don't worry about
it
yeah yeah I'm thinking like maybe I just
got to get good at Art myself so I can
draw my own
[Music]
art don't have to rely on
others so do in
there yeah okay let's read these Brandon
dun Jacob dun GD dun Nathan thank you
for the
pinky Hi D could I get a something to
help me kick this cold I caught a
something I don't want to miss any more
work you mean like your actual job you
don't want to miss it you don't want to
miss it
really do you have like not paid sick
days that's [\h__\h] up if you if that's
the case but I feel like most people
have paid sick days cough cough
no hey you should if it's like a throat
thing like
cold it doesn't help with cold but cold
but with with coughs you could you could
use that that that magical mystical
medicine from the Asian market that I
got you know you know which
one
[Music]
yeah papa
yeah that one I'm utilizing my surprise
time off very good yeah I see you
utilizing it you're here like I honestly
have no problem with you being
sick but I don't know how painful it is
for you right now I totally wouldn't
wish for you to stay sick I
mean I mean you know tomorrow long
stream so it would be great if you could
stay in bed all
day but I wouldn't wish you to stay sick
like of course not so I hope you get
well
soon
yeah good luck with
[Music]
that
yeah fingers
crossed yeah crossed because I'm
[Music]
[Laughter]
lying and Roa Dear Santa thanks for the
pinky K let's say that oh here we go
that a Bay from another world appears
and turns smoovie into a
serval that's a like
a danger cat
right danger
fluff will you continue life as normal
or will you have chunk or stay with your
mom until smooy is her usual self
again uh no I might have chunky wonky
stay with my
bro cuz he just you you know is closer
um but yeah that's kind of
crazy Bae what the
[\h__\h] ba no what what if I ask Bae to
turn smovie back like what what would
Bae ask for this Bay from another world
in return to turn smovie back to normal
cat like we have to clear that one first
okay Bale no it's not bailes because
this one is ba from another
world it's a different person from Bales
no those two people are different you
know I would call her Bales if it was
bailes yeah yeah yeah don't don't
confuse
it AB C thanks for the pinky can't
believe my Oshi has
worms my best friend used to give her
dogs garlic and onions to get rid of
them holy [\h__\h] hope that helps no I
didn't mean I I have worms no that's not
what that was implying me playing this
game oh my
[Music]
God yeah just brain warms oh yeah those
I have plenty the one on my head yeah
that's not in me that's on
me I can just flick it off if I wanted
to
flick but I like
it I like it on my
head he cute so don't worry about me Eby
it's sweet that you are concerned and
giving me tips that you used on your dog
I mean your friend used on your dogs
thinking that would work on me uh thank
[Music]
you moving
on
I mean I eat garlic and onions all the
time so I should be constantly free of
[Music]
worms morally immoral Dan
seanan thank you Dan I saw you reached
three years
[Music]
congratulations finally it's about time
yeah every every chicken here hopefully
will reach the freear milestone one
day most of you are getting really close
or are already there looking fabulous
you got more one more week oo oh
memberships it's raining memberships
hallelu you know you know what guys like
I found something
funny
um no don't sing she we don't think in
the in the description in the comment
section where was
it oh yeah I
found under like an English comment like
really
hidden really hidden I found like a
pretty
decent uh transcribed and amended
English
version and it
actually flows so
[Music]
well do you want to hear a little
bit lonely LLY ly got the sense for you
when I rain the spell there's nothing
you can do this is the
Salvation
recre let's go touch me get arrested
kiss me he you busted 1 2 3 three four
I'm so sorry oh you say you're sorry but
can't really hear you get perched Dolly
gots
R in the future yeah I don't want to be
liked by the lik of you just go and wash
your dirty mouth with mud now we have a
date in court
hey not then officers on the way to come
take you away
delusional you are a horrible guy why
don't you just go and
die please wait n what would your
parents say if they found you sing like
this n you're so damn cute ah thank you
good
job LLY ly got the sense for you creepy
guys are on the loose what do you do B
if you're not a normal person just
please go away way for me lovely Lolly
LLY got the sense for you when I ring
this Bell there's nothing you can do all
of My Kind of
Wonderful my amazing
only please go rest in peace now your
new
Paradise these s like pretty good I
really love the part that goes like
touch me get arrested kiss me and you're
busted 1 two 3 before I'm so sorry H you
say you're sorry but can't really hear
you get perched Lolli guts
R so
good so
good this was this was in a comment
section like it's it's like kind of a
waste they just like put it in under the
comments of a comment but like you have
to scroll really
far time to cover it in English sounds a
lot better in Japanese yeah but like
this person you know they just like
these people in the comments they were
just talking about the lyrics and what
do they mean and then suddenly this
person shows up and like posts perfectly
translated and transcribed so that it
even like flows well automatically with
the Melody lyrics like not just
translated but like you can't just if
you want to translate lyrics to fit The
Melody of a song you can't just
translate it you have to think about how
it flows with the the melody you know
yeah and he just does that and then just
leaves it like that just just like here
take this I just did this like in five
minutes or
whatever it's so good it's so
good should he should like put it like
somewhere where people more people see
it but just in case you know
here's the credit it's from someone
called blacker screen Productions
1368 just a random comment under the
comments
yeah yeah yeah anyway back
to
this it's funny yeah the LCS are so
funny nissa's
alt nissa's alt account could be could
Phil weasel D moral immoral D oh thank
you I don't know if I'm getting in but
uh if I get
in I I would try everything I can yeah
in my
power but it
would it would be crazier pressure than
the Trident well who knows who knows
maybe I maybe I would be less nervous
who knows
no definitely
nervous I don't see how this is how imom
Mushi was anything like Hollow up for me
no not at all donate blood and watch me
to his D oh another free year badge
person
nice the Great Ghost Dan morally imoral
Dan Che Chan Dan boohoo 723 Dan DK Ed
thank you thank you thank you for the
pinky wait I feel like I haven't seen a
super chat from you in a while and now
I'm actually like wait you're Australian
see I didn't remember that you
[Music]
Australian
mate wow w w you did so good guard in
Hollow up I have no doubt you can clear
this game effortlessly
[Music]
too
PS I managed I managed to get Cutting
Edge in world of
WFT eh what's Cutting Edge a week before
it becomes unavailable putting me in the
worst 1% of the top
1% please call me a good video good
video game boy what what's that
[Music]
what's Cutting Edge in World of
Warcraft who knows who knows
this a week before it becomes
unavailable I killed the last boss in
the hardest
difficulty and why does that make you
the worst 1% of the one top 1% why this
seems like
a
hello
hello hello
hello hello hello hello oh
oh are you back I'm just been saying
hello to myself for a
while hello
M oh I was having a
conversation
and what class do you play like did you
you didn't kill the boss alone right did
you what role did you play in this fight
was it a raid or was it like a a
dungeon tell me more so that I can I can
praise you a warrior Warrior ooh so is
that a tank I think 20 man raate oh
that's a pretty small raid oh that's
comfortable cuz like I just imagine like
Final Fantasy rates with like 100 people
I don't
know a warm rear I'm a war myself oh
yeah me too that kind of
warrier a con concern
warer you doing me a
concern Final Fantasy raids are eight
people eh and what have I
seen whatever anyway you DPS your tanks
are smart than me DPS is like brain
empty kind of job I I imagine like I
feel like yeah I feel DPS is pretty
brain
empty
roll just hit it just hit it endlessly
let the Healer heal you let the Tank
tank for you you just endlessly Smash
and
[Music]
mash but good job good job though good
job that
sounds challeng like a challenge yeah I
want to I was actually just thinking
like more and more recently I've been
thinking about wanting to play World of
Warcraft again a little bit for a
stream I want
to I want
to I don't know I just need to I feel
like I need to feel the Nostalgia again
that one time it wasn't enough enough it
was not enough we need more
Nostalgia I just want to play classic
though but even classic has already like
proceeded too far in my
opinion they should let you
choose they should make like several
servers and they all stop in a different
expansion they're putting out a new
Classic Plus are they going back again
like I don't I don't want it to go past
or at least not very far past burning
Crusade yeah it should stop like there
cuz that's where I
stopped so it's just me being very very
um
[Music]
selfish I I started playing when there
were no expansions and I think I ended I
stopped
playing
yeah around burn burning Crusade I
think were those blue
people part of burning Crusade or did
they come after words it's in another
[Music]
expansion yeah I hear good things about
the Lich King but N I don't know not the
night elves I mean the yeah I think I
mean
[Music]
aenai eh TBC what's TBC the burning in
Crusade okay yeah then I I think that's
really where I stopped cuz that's all I
really
remember
seeing so I wish it would just end
there the burning
[Music]
qule I want to see I want somebody like
a high level person to take take me on
the r is there like double mounts that I
can join
[Music]
riding yeah I want someone to take me
through all the areas that I remember
and I just want to see them again but I
can't take the time to level up to like
40 50 60 I mean the highest I ever was I
think was
42 I kept on making new characters my
highest was only ever 42 I think
I didn't get that far in World of
Warcraft I just I I didn't actively play
much I I hung out a lot just chilling
and enjoying the scenery taking it all
in I didn't want to do all the serious
stuff like Dungeons and little
whatever PVP
blah
[Music]
hey
hey we back okay I just wanted to
mention I think I remember like um that
little village uh that you go to right
after you you leave um or like let's say
right before you go to storm wind the
little village you know where there's
like all these paths in different
directions
what was it gold CH I think I think
sometimes doesn't it have like little
seasonal like festivals or like
something like that those were so
cute
[Music]
YouTu yeah the Dark Moon Fair I remember
the Dark Moon
Fair okay
okay yeah wait yeah does the Dark Moon
Fair still
happen does that still
happen I
wonder it does wait what what what did
that entail again I don't remember even
I just remember something being there
and it being kind of cute every month
oh it's pretty big now many new things
to do
wo woo it changed a lot oh yeah tickets
tickets tickets yeah
tickets yeah there were
tickets oh yeah there was a cannon
yeah oh now there's a roller coaster and
the merry go run oh my god oh my god
let's
[Music]
go
oh yeah I want to see I want I want
somebody to take me on the tour because
like I don't have the time to level up
to see all these places again I just
want to have someone princess carry me
in a carriage through
everything cuz otherwise it would be too
slow everything would be too
slow leveling is really quick now I'm
I'm
like I don't know what it is cuz like
every freaking mmpg offers it but I'm so
against
boosting
I don't like the idea of boosting at
all I don't like it like it makes no
sense to me like why play the game if
you're just going to you know okay maybe
if you already made a million characters
and you already have seen all of that
like a million times but especially then
like don't you like the TR I know it
takes a lot of time but like you know
okay at least in my case like if it's
the first time in a million years
I feel like you shouldn't boost yourself
you should experience everything again
cuz it's nostalgic and and and you
know why why why Zoom through half of
the
game without looking at
it I don't know man just doesn't yeah we
should be mindlessly grinding for
hundreds of hours no that is the best
part of the
game that is exactly the best part of
the game grinding I love
grinding it's not even I feel like it's
worse than other games
like I I don't know I mean obviously I
didn't never get that far in World of
Warcraft but there's some grinding like
Fly for Fun grinding was [\h__\h] but I
loved
it I remember man I was
um in a high level high level area like
max level
when people were getting to their max
level the last few levels I was always a
Healer so I was always like tagging
along in one-on-one teams you know and
and and for each mob you would get like
0.00002 exp or
so and so we were trying our best to
like be as efficient as possible not
like it was not acceptable to
take like even two seconds of a break
between an enemy no no it has to be so
efficient just go from one to another to
the next to the next to the next there's
no break in between you have to grind
the [\h__\h] out of
it of course with all possible exp Buffs
and and attack Buffs and
whatever and faster healing faster
healing
[Music]
how many levels would you get a day
Zero Zero at that point
zero it's a long long
journey but
somehow I really enjoyed those grinding
times
man good
memories yeah good memories I want to go
go back to the life of fun and eat an
eternal times you
[Music]
know I wish they would still put out
games like that
man my anime
MMOs my cash shop bling
bling and I wish like I wish I ever
really understood how to play trickster
online
properly I genely am considering
starting to play on a private server now
cuz the game hasn't been like officially
existing for a long
time and I really liked the visuals and
everything of it but maybe it was my
lack of English understanding at the
time I don't know and and me not knowing
a single other player but I really
didn't understand uh how to play it like
it was just another MMO but I don't know
the anybody ever play trickster online
cuz like I really did not understand
anything about
it yeah blue
protocol that will be exciting let's
play Blue protocol 2024 time is going by
fast it's already been like what half a
year almost since it released in Japan I
think just got to wait another half a
year
probably [\h__\h] yeah
[\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah you forgot most about
trickster and me too
but I just never understood it in the
first
place if you're playing I'll play let's
go let's play
together a yeah yeah yeah bio I think
bioo was going to join me right maybe
Ena will join me I feel like she
would she loves
[Music]
MMOs going to get
addicted
yeah [\h__\h]
yeah
yeah get some ID Girls to join me
too oh who having KY on my side in an
MMO would be insanely
powerful
oh oh yeah the time zones no it would be
more like like join whatever you know
like a
free kind of
thing but it would be nice to have
someone to like be somewhat in my time
zone or like something that's yeah
easy eh I don't know does she play MMOs
maybe not now but maybe in the
future yeah Kyla would play with me
anytime I got to I got
to I got
to you know get her into blue
protocol I feel like I could get her
into it just got to ask
nicely Ka do you want to play a game
with me
please
[Music]
anyway anyway anyway anyway let's move
on the Great Ghost D Flappy boy two red
super
chats
nan oh NE supers are back again finally
I can pay you my birthday tith
oh been sitting on that since Saturday
oh okay okay okay it's not that long ago
thanks for being such a positive source
of inspiration and making the burden of
aging more
bearable no song needed by the way my
only birthday wish was to see you during
the festival Conquering the sky so
fearlessly I was I was almost as Flappy
as
you wow in the distance smoothie is
wishing you a happy birthday Conquering
the sky so fearlessly Majestic
majestically and flawlessly smoking the
competition like a true Phoenix and it
came true
already it did thank you I appreciate it
cuz my throat kind of weak right now but
thank you so much I'm so happy to have
you happy birthday MW mwah mwah MW mwah
MW I do think I said this I think
already but I do think I would have not
been so good if I was up against beu and
suicide just the sheer thought of being
up against them would have destroyed me
mentally
so I remember we were like in the VC um
ana
sui and a couple of
[Music]
others
maybe maybe Chloe was there too I'm not
sure but like the moment that we all
understood who's going up against
who I was like cuz this whole time I
thought I was going against beu and
suici but I was when I heard it I was
like yo let's
go than God I was screaming so loud out
of joy
and it was so funny I was so hyped up so
relieved it took so much so much
pressure from me you have no idea and
the others were just like oh
no ana ana is so chill you know like I I
I love her actually man like obviously
she would have put the oneon-one
together and would understand that I'm
relieved to go against
her because we all know how cracked the
others are you know we all know how
cracked s
be
so Ana was taking it very um how to
[Music]
say she was taking it
well I love
[Music]
her oh Chad not Vis yeah whatever we
don't need it I see you in my
heart don't need to show you to anyone
else
[Music]
anyway thank you Flappy boy I will
continue flapping maybe we should have
taught the emo Mushi how to Flap this
emo Mushi will never turn into a flappy
boy like you you're the only one you're
my unique Flappy
boy thank you and happy birthday happy
flap
day M
congratulations cisal clips than Evans L
than uh M eight thanks little
pinky good job in Hell T did you hear
Kata and I am praising you yeah as for
the VR thing you can just simplify it in
that AM wants to do stuff with you
another dance would be nice since she
won't be in the countdown life oh yeah
yeah yeah
yeah n m i want to do I would do
anything with Amy yeah I do want to do
more parties of Amy I also like I know
that she a while ago she asked like hey
who wants to play okus together and then
you know times got busy and it didn't
happen but I just I told her the other
day like hey Amed we should just do it
together we should just plan it
together amus I want to help her with
Pro projects hi Cat
hello
like I can do the the organizing on the
talent side and she can do the
organizing behind the scenes we we would
be or we are a Dream
[Music]
Team
Unstoppable
[Music]
yeah new mushroom map yeah yeah yeah I
know I know that's why we wanted to play
amus that's exactly
why Lord dun picture of a phone dun
Dominic K dun mp15 fre garlic dun star
Creator dun free no D
Danos
muchos crusty
crusty another Australian oh so many
Australians oh so many Australians thank
you for the pinky just want to say
congrats in the sports sport Sports F I
was
really rooting hard for white and
although red won you killed it
personally your ability to go above and
beyond for your timkin is something I
really admire never changed
T okay okay okay okay okay I I made
through most of it without
fing it's not difficult for me it's not
not not an issue it's I I don't have
to force myself to hold back
no it's easy for me yeah it sounds like
a [\h__\h] pirate I can't I want to get
back
[Music]
I don't have a problem I don't I don't
have a
problem oh thank you so much crusty I'm
happy to hear for your your support
thank you so much I wa I March
March I wish I could
speak more like
[Music]
your
how how how how to speak
Australian like why can't I just like I
hear so many accents why does my brain
not just copy paste why am I so hard so
difficult eh why am I so bad I can't
speak why is it so hard why is it so
difficult
to to uh do that for me
just
like burn it into my brain and
then
yeah ah I'm
exhausted Nathan caught down thanks with
pinky since I had the day off from work
I just finished baking some profit
rolles despite being sick damn okay wow
hey how do you bake those I've never
made those but you are a baker but damn
now I've just got to wait for them in
the custard to cool more baking are you
going to top them with chocolate did you
top them did you did
[Music]
you I'm at ice skating
promise what did we did we promise to
ice skate in real life or in a game you
will oh please share sharing is caring
for the
WWA
please I made my banana pink CES today
again pretty proud of myself irel well I
mean I'm going to have a hard time
skating with Amy if she not
here I might go ice skating with uh waya
I don't
[Music]
know waya and
wha way
[Music]
waa that is such a good question I don't
know where is
she hi smoothie smoothie why are you
like so busy running around and
terrorizing me
huh no did you hear
[Music]
that I love like running her tail for
my fingers when I like pet her back but
then I continue going through her tail
it's so
[Music]
soft you just put a banana pudding into
the oven wow you put pudding into the OV
I guess when it's so liquid
huh you bake it in the
oven
yeah I love you and I hate you but both
when are we going to say goodbye
[Music]
soon
Zachary you're not you're serious
right
[\h__\h] how old was
do how old was do
[Music]
10 a yeah I think you know could have
been older but still lived a long and
plentiful happy
[Music]
life
but that is terrible I can
[Music]
imagine I hope you
can you know I don't know even what to
say like man such I can't even imagine
you know I would be
devastated oh golden retrievers don't
get much older oh really oh golden
retriever oh I'm sure she or he was so
happy to be with
you
yeah W like thinking about your own pet
someday not being there anymore is like
so Unthinkable you don't you really
don't want to think about it I feel like
it's something even harder to think
about than your own
death Rosie Rosy Rosie Rosie is going to
look down down from the heaven the dog
of Heaven on you and Rosy wants to see
you happy Rosy Rosy probably wants to
see you go to
the to the place where they keep all the
Stray doos and adopt a new Babu Babu Doo
to save another
do and if you get a puppy I think I mean
you don't have to do it immediately like
just happened today but I think a puppy
could help
you and you're helping the
puppy help each other help each
other continue the cycle of helping
dogos give them the life that they
deserve a life of happiness every dogle
every CLE they all deserve so much
happiness they only deserve
happiness nothing else yeah
you're welcome go make another DOA happy
like all all the all the love and
happiness to you and to
Rosie but you know what to do in the
future take your time to get over it
now but in the future just keep the
cycle going I think Rosie would
appreciate
that make more Doos happy give them a
home that's your mission Rosie gave you
this mission
[Music]
yeah you gave one dog a happy home so
far as much as you could for a long time
as long as you
could your mission has been fulfilled
once now starts a new
Mission yes yes but yeah I I couldn't I
I can't can't think
about my cats ever be being gone that's
like I I would I
would not know how to handle that
[Music]
ever I'll need you guys to help me when
that
happens anyway Nathan I'm waiting for
those PES I don't know how to say that
in
English but I'm waiting for them D star
thank you for the red super chat hi Tel
didn't you do something to your
feathers you're looking exra beautiful
today ah you
just also I streamed your new album
multiple times on YouTube and Spotify
and of course to remind you you're my
favorite YouTuber of all time I'm a
pretty say so and innocent chicken
uh-huh well you know you're lucky again
I
again I again forgot what you are in the
usual room
for I don't remember but you in there
for a good reason I
think all I know is you're in there for
a good
reason they're not done yet do they take
that long to bake they seem like they
don't take long to
bake I always forget yeah I don't even
put that many people into the usual room
anymore these days and I still forget so
I don't know D but this ain't working I
will take the compliments but I will not
be giving anything back to you besides a
kiss you stay where you are game 891 oh
dff and D simplon thank you for the
pinky hey T though I'm sure it's been
said this is my first chance to say
sports V waa gaming thank you yeah I
didn't I didn't make it possible for you
guys cuz I had no stream and then yeah
no super chats such a clutch gamer in
amazing teammate I agree with kanada
that you were an MVP kfp loves when you
have fun and do so well thank you I
would agree with that
too I I I after after you know all the
feedback I've received and all the
information I've received uh it does
seem like I was quite the MVP which is
uh quite Unthinkable I think you guys
you guys let's be honest who you didn't
expect me to do so well
overall I didn't expect myself to do so
well overall no none of us expected me
to do so well overall let's be real yep
no no no yeah you want to say I believed
in you that's so sweet but let's be
real
oh yeah I always I always choke normally
that's what I do it's my job I
choke
yeah and then someone tries to save me
with the what's it called Hinrich
maneuver a he not
hrich Hinrich is quite the German name
but he is also German why is it called
he maneuver do you know h means
secretly in
German oh oh the guy oh it's his name
too I guess it could be a last name it's
not really
common but I guess it was his last name
H okay okay okay so a German or it could
have been something else too
Hess what is it
American that such a German name
it's freaking America a German
[Music]
American American for
foras sick surgeon and medical
researcher widely credited for the
discovery of the hake
maneuver H I feel like that was like
pretty
obvious like anyone could have
discovered that probably people in the
Stone Age already discovered dad Mr
[Music]
hey oh something stuck in their throat
uh squeeze
them I don't want to I don't want to
give him the
credit but they never copyrighted it
well because back then they didn't need
to copyright
[Music]
everything
shambles but it might break their rib
yeah well I might break your
ribs if if I attempted on you um not
just for any reason just
[Music]
uh anyway uh thank you simpleton I am
very
proud about for myself and I'm also
happy that I could make you guys a
little bit proud
y
[Music]
looking for the top d delar d I am a t
beep D Max first D J Monkey D Cruz D
Alita oh hi thank you for the red chat
hi W two things finally watched the
sports festival and was so excited
amazing job ah thank you was super proud
of you and two
recent recently adopted two kittens
they're super precious and absolutely
love them oh my
God pictures or it didn't
[Music]
happen pic or it didn't
happen waiting for it you're welcome to
add
Wawa or even no actually put it in the
kfp tag yeah and tag me both maybe I am
awaiting the cat tags
yeah I need to see the babies show me
the babies
I need the babies
now maybe a video too a video would be
much
appreciated two kittens good choice good
number I don't know if you already have
cats or animals in general but if you
don't have any then good choice to get
at least
two they can be there for each other I
have I have some name suggestions how
about
smoothie and
chalkers or
Cheeto
and whatever the [\h__\h] that other thing
is Radio Action Cheeto and burrito oh
that's actually [\h__\h] cute oh Cheeto
and Dorito burrito oh that's actually
adorable
m
that's so cute I found uh a YouTube cat
um like an account that makes like
YouTube shorts of their cat and they
call their cat valto and it's so cute
that cat is actually so cute what the
hell found a treasure of a
cat
yeah so
cute Pepito a
Pepito has Pepito come home just
now
Pepito
[Music]
no no Pepito hasn't been out for 21
hours
apparently
no which is good I guess but sometimes
it only says like twice in a row it's
back for example instead of like it left
so here even here it's like three times
in a row no four five okay five times in
a row Pito came back instead of leaving
even
once so like how are there more pitos
than
one maybe there's maybe there's five
pipitos and they all look the same they
have five black cats and they call them
all
pipito and at some point five of them
left and now five of them came back it's
like this this kind of bus situation
when you know five go in two leave to
get back on a bus one leaves free get
back on the bus and so on but now we
have a situation where finally all pitos
are back home so it's kind of a reset
and you can start the calculations again
from here on
out I don't know what I'm talking
about there's just uh a theory a game
theory a
fairy
yes shinger Pepito no no it's just bus
Pepito my kiaha
Fury kiaha Fury takashi's Fury we shall
officially call it
that
[Music]
pitoo so Alita many name suggestions for
you let me know when you name them they
better be satisfactory to
me maybe I can help you a bit more uh
after judging the pictures I might find
more applicable names mhm yeah thank you
so
much space wonderful d zly d space
wonderful oh again D you know you stream
oh cuz you're playing DND
D I think a safe thing to plan anyway
would be um playing it during the
nighttime jst where I would be
sleeping if you want to plan cuz I'm not
going to give you concrete plans cuz I
can't make concrete plans right
now
H just play during Japanese nighttime
how about
that a phoenix Fury thanks for
watching
Crystal
Clips mafin eight thanks for the uh R of
chat perhaps one day you if when you're
free of the stress of all this you can
experience
no
no as for 16 don't stress if you can't
finish it this week uh you can finish it
in GTA when you come back also it's been
3 years since the I'm my ice SK oh yeah
uh H I guess I could
but it it would be nicer to finish it
now cuz then there's not a big break I
mean even then it's not going to be a
big break cuz I'm not gone for that long
but still you know let's see how far we
get
tomorrow and how stressed out I
am mhm how many things I have
done at that
point
I'm already stressed out I'm so
stressed I'm scared like it's actually
I'm
terrified I'm kind of terrified
W still need to sign IRL polar Awards
and your guys is polar Awards
too but the IRL polar Awards and
bringing them to Japan
Japan um I don't know when the deadline
is don't remember but sometime during my
Japan trip
maybe don't feel bad about canceling
streams well I don't because I haven't
even officially told you when I'm
planning to stream this week
guys I've got some some plans you know
but I'm not going to guarantee anything
now so that you can't use it against me
in court later
on k i
Channel
funny sounds so much like kizuna
I oh yeah my pajama oh my God I'm going
to forget it can you guys like keep on
reminding me of that in the coming
days until I tell you to
stop just randomly
randomly
yeah I need to bring my
pajama
yeah shall we scheduled tweets no just
like whenever whenever like any anytime
doesn't have to be a you know just like
by the way
pajama at the end of your other
[Music]
tweets my lips are so [\h__\h] right now
now holy [\h__\h] I need to stop ripping
them
apart they just get
worse they're so
chipped oh my
[Music]
God
mood uh
ow no lip balm I swear it makes it worse
for me
[Music]
it bothers
me okay [\h__\h] I got it
okay I will not touch it
anymore oh will
[Music]
I
um nah not on top of that anyway mafin I
I I 100% reject your raid suggestion
because I don't like raids I have told
you have I
not are you not
listening I don't like raids
no you with your hearts you what you're
saying is you know it and you still
suggested
it ah you just want me to experience it
because of the near I guess
yeah yeah thought so thought so ah we
know each other too
well thank you Zachary erand again Danon
and I wish you the best hug hug virtual
hug downstar Dan Alin
D
oh hey what's with these sad Super
Chat
what my marriage has been put to the
test my partner feels that I am not
worthy of spending my life with him it
is so
sad Google
[Music]
translate that sounds [\h__\h] up saying
you're not worthy of spending my life
you're not worthy of me spending my life
with you or something like that that
that's just that's
rough but then if that person thinks
that that way about you then they're
also not
worth it to you I don't know I don't
know how to form sentences anymore you
know what I mean if that's how they
think well same same thing yeah back to
you they're
loss but I I mean marriage sounds like
you you've come so far in life if you're
at the point of being married to someone
so I hope you can figure it out
somehow maybe counseling I don't
[Music]
know carpet absum thank you for the
pinky incredibly proud of your
performance at Fest you mean Sports Fest
next challenge would be to carry your
clutch je Jean while streaming your pewy
huh yeah well good thing there is no
Sports Fest next
year is that
good you've been clean for 18 months oh
my God like an addiction don't worry I'm
not planning on it not not now mm- not
ever for
now but
yeah ID one
[Music]
H for the ID one I didn't feel so
pressured you know that's the thing but
maybe if they as I said as I suggested
if they make it
bigger then I might feel more
pressured cuz it was really chill but
we'll see we'll see how I feel in the
future depends depends we'll see k i and
now the last one was vus D I'm done I'm
going to throw some fish sticks into the
oven make myself some dinner just simple
fish
sticks feeling like a child
today M you know there's like in the
frozen section there's like all kinds of
like like more mature versions in my
opinion of the fish sticks just like uh
fried fish filets and whatever you know
higher quality stuff I guess but I still
go for the fish sticks the like childish
ones that you serve your kids that I've
been served I still go for
those
because [\h__\h]
yeah that's why M than pretty casual
compared to what you think they are H
but then first I would have to get to
the level and I'm for sure not boosting
my
character although for Final Fantasy I I
I might even like for Final Fantasy I
would do it
maybe wait what wait wait I didn't
really register
it what what
what forget everything every everything
up to this
point
what is there a
[Music]
trailer those little shits remember when
people were like you know after the
Mario
movie Zelda
Zelda and they were like no we're not
doing it like not with that company that
made
the mar
Mario Mario movie
[Music]
oh life action if they if they I mean I
would trust Nintendo to bring it at
least to the quality of One Piece life
action Zelda live
action four minut
just
h
[Music]
uh we we we we
we we we we
[Music]
we breaking
news
breaking
[Music]
news breaking
news okay which one are we reading
everything The Verge following the huge
success of the Mario movie Nintendo is
now planning to make a film based on the
Legend of Zelda Nintendo Nintendo's 4 a
into movies isn't stopping anytime soon
the company has confirmed that it's
working on a liveaction adaption of The
Legend of Zelda the movie will be
directed by Wes ball best known for The
Maze Runner Trilogy and the upcoming
Kingdom of Planet of the Apes
uh-huh Zelda Creator shikaru Miyamoto
will serve as a
producer much as he did on this year's
animated Super Mario Bros
movie while there aren't any details on
the movie itself Nintendo says that it
will be co-financed by itself and Sony
with Nintendo footing more than 50% of
the bill the announcement comes at a
pivotal time for Nintendo as the company
has made its Ambitions to become a
broader Entertainment Company
clear yes that includes not not only the
Super Mario movie but also a line of
Theme Park attractions this year uh also
saw the release of the latest major
entry in the Zelda series of Tears of
the
Kingdom it's officially started on the
waa News Network
[Music]
yeah oh my God
more
more I've been working on live action
film of the legend of zala for many
years now really with ABI aratan who has
produced many mega hit films shik
Miyamoto says in a statement on Twitter
I have asked avisan to produce this film
with me and we have now officially
started our relation our development of
the film with Nintendo itself heavily
involved in the production it will take
until it's completion but I hope you
look forward to seeing
it my God are the movies of this guy
good I've never heard I've never watched
those movies that were mentioned
here is track record is not so
good kind of mid
M lots of
trash ma not
good oh
oh why did I choose
them got so much money got so much like
choices
[Music]
why
I I you guys and I know you guys like to
be like pessimistic about these kind of
things but for me personally I loved the
Mario movie and I'm sure that the Zelda
franchise is so important to them that
they wouldn't like dare to [\h__\h] it up
and I I know life action is worrying but
hey look at one piece that turn turned
out great and it was
Netflix
so now we have Nintendo
okay pouring their love and money
into a movie for their biggest hit
besides
Mario give it time give it a chance
let's wait I mean yeah it's concerning
that it's so someone involved who has
not so good movies but give it time give
it a
[Music]
chance
sorry I was writing an
essay hi
[Music]
smoothie now back to you thank you yeah
oh F Oh I thought it was I thought we
were on the weather what did they not
switch to weather oh [\h__\h] sake fired
fired Mama
Mia okay I'm going to go now did any any
new super chats come in that I have to
read still oh oh now it
did JB thank you D can't believe Neil
interrupted K Super Chat reading for
this special it was done anyway it was
basically
done but holy moly I can't believe this
news just dropped my
God oh my God
I don't know I think you know I was
originally thinking they were going to
do it animated just like Mario but I
think you know they can go like the Lord
of the Rings
[Music]
route or like uh a bit more magical than
that obviously but in terms of visuals I
think they can go be inspired by Lord of
the
Rings you
know I think that's what they're
thinking too I would think so too yeah
yeah visually not kitchy just more
natural looking you
[Music]
know I I would think so I will put all
my horses on
[Music]
that exciting exciting e how long
ago before the movie came out was it
that they announced the Mario movie
do you guys
know a year or two two years before the
first
trailer a year or two H why AR some
people saying five
years year two yeah I think it was
something like
that huh so it will be within my
lifetime
let's
go Ah that's exciting [\h__\h] yeah [\h__\h]
yeah [\h__\h] yeah you know what they should
do
oh wait I was just going to say they
should release a game to go with it but
they probably won't and it might even be
their replacement of a new Zelda game
their excuse to not work on a new Zelda
game for a
while did you think about that
movie the
game no but no but I mean for Mario they
didn't release a game to go with the
movie but I guess they did release Mario
Wonder just recently so they they can if
they want to work on two things at the
same
time surely they have different
departments but I I don't know I don't
like the the idea that maybe they won't
work on the game cuz they're working on
the
movie
oh
well okay
whatever
well
Pajamas not
now okay guys I'm going to go I'm going
to
go and enjoy
byebye hope you had fun I had fun see
you tomorrow for Final
Fantasy the not quite the finale of
Final Fantasy but it will be a final
fantasy one of the final
fantasies Final
Fantasy see you tomorrow 4M wa
time is the it's the wa time it's a Taki
wa time Taki wa
time no it's the end of the wa time for
today oh yeah wait
weisa let's do it let's do it let's do
it let's return also py dun just saw
[Music]
it
she won't know she won't know what's
coming she won't
know huh wait it doesn't show up what
[Music]
n is she done she's streaming
me let me type in h
[Music]
live
uh there's no way she has writing off
now
do you have ring
off oh no I see it never
mind now I see it but I couldn't find it
when I typed in Nissa and Raven C that's
so
weird oh
[Music]
byebye