[Music]
so
oh god
here let's see let's go to the the room
where we hang
it it's the room where we hang out we're
going to it now
we're in it now you cut off the sentence
of the little shorts i was a little
worried
we're here in the room where we hang out
where we hang out
we hang out we hang out hold on hold on
a minute wait
it's the place where we hey hearing
going from uh
you know
please don't take my head please i want
to keep it oh my gosh
no that's that's up to me to decide
sorry you don't get any say in that
drink huh oh it's juice what do you
think it was
it's mud huh did you give me coffee
no it's whatever you want it to be dog
use your imagination
can you have the thing behind you huh oh
the the spiritist are you are you sure
you want to
are you sure you want it it's just water
right
it looks like water yeah yeah you could
say that
maybe it smells funny
no no it's delicious i i promise you'll
you'll love it that's like a sharpie
i mean how's your pregnancy going i'm in
yeah i heard about that i heard the word
on the street
yeah i think i might give birth in like
30 minutes
oh that's pretty horrifying
are you feeling okay right now is it
painful
no no no it's fine we're all here for
you amelia we're here to support you
no matter what what
what we're here to support you you know
oh
oh is it a placebo never mind no a
placebo
that's like a pill that doesn't actually
work right
but yeah that's what a placebo is and a
placenta is an organ
i would i would know wow okay
yeah i mean it's kind of an or it
doesn't really do anything though you
don't you don't quite need it to survive
little known fact isn't it okay yeah
anyway we didn't even introduce this
hello everyone wow today i'm hosting the
street gosh am i nervous because
wow i'm hosting a stream oh goodness
gracious i don't know whose house this
is actually we just kind of showed up
here um
i really hope the owners don't come back
i'm a little worried about
exactly what we're hanging out so you
know do you like you wait what do you
like the smell
must be yeah it's kind of nice what
that's just your nose
hmm
[Laughter]
i think you'll probably end up going
under the table in the early side of
your stethoscope watson how's that
ladies hold it all set
no fights please we're gonna play games
today i i think that's what we're doing
yeah we're playing games on this day
it's a day
april the april the first the it's it's
just a normal day
really any other day with the every any
other day with the holo ian girls
like any other day like any other any
other day
with us on a date totally normal day
we haven't prepared anything at all
nothing prepared no
yeah nothing yep oh we prepared one
thing
what was that no disappointment
[Laughter]
yeah like a master almost as good as me
no expectations it's good yeah exactly
that's how you don't let get down
gosh that's depressing we're gonna play
games today um
i have a million things running on my
computer right now so let's let's see
um if we survive or not or if i explode
this house
with my pc blowing up we'll see what
happens gosh
uh we're gonna go to the room where we
play games now we're playing jack box
games
i don't know anything about uh this game
these games
plural well but if people are patient a
little patient then the thing that we
definitely didn't prepare we might want
to
show it to you halfway through right
yeah definitely that's a nice idea
yes but there's nothing that we want to
show you yeah nothing like that
not at all not at all
what are you even i feel like you're
implying something when there's nothing
to be implied actually
there's nothing nothing yeah you have to
join too
i do how do i okay yeah i got it um
how do i join do i have to go on the
internet
i have to go on the internet what the
you got to be kidding me dog all right
hold up it's gone now come back
thank you oh it's gonna go away probably
hold on
oh my god all right jet hold on
i have a dead pixel on my monitor that's
the worst that's really aggravating
how big is your monitor
[Music]
31.5 inches times two
you could come so nice to me we can
watch the movie we can each have it on
one side of the screen
me yes okay
i got it i think about it why did the
game make inna the vip
did she join first cousins gonna win
as always wins
the funniest person will win i'm not
gonna get double audio
i don't even know what all these jackpot
schemes are about i have no idea
testing your wits kiara my wings
click wait yes oh i have those oh
yeah all right now it's not not in my
library
all right click everybody's i'm clicking
everybody's in uh on the screen
okay oh my gosh where is the everybody i
think you know has oh
everyone's in okay thank you oh you're
the vip i get it that's it
i pressed it but nothing's happening
oh what is everyone ready up is there a
ready button
no i don't see one sit back and relax
baby okay i'm gonna rejoin maybe someone
else will be vip
okay i think it'll just it'll keep you
there
like if you refresh
oh it's going okay where do i play the
game do i play it on the internet
yes whatever you join the uh thingamajig
with all right well the
the code is now in the corner i think
everyone can see it
but it flashed but i i went away it went
away
i mean if people if people i mean they
can come join i don't care if they join
like watching okay do you guys care i
think they just
they just vote they can't like actually
write anything all right
in the game for this game code and join
them and i don't care
come join
and everybody else will decide which one
they like better oh yeah yes
points you score points based on the
problem
clear enough sure hope so let's go so
right now i'm badly
xd okay yeah uh-huh
it's like writing your answers in your
device what
okay oh let's see oh do the others
wait they don't get to see it wait do i
have to
they don't get to see on the screen what
oh the worst no no they
they'll see the answers like that
because it's like i
oh my god but i think my
way mine isn't wow
[Music]
all right i think i like this one
oh there are a lot like two questions
right not 45 questions
only yeah only two so you have some time
to think about it okay
i'm stuck in the character select screen
refresh you're refreshing and then just
press press select
just enter the code again and you'll be
back in 30 seconds
was i supposed to answer funny things um
i mean if you want
if you're i think so somewhat i mean
yes
eleven ten nine
eight seven six five
four three two
one did i not finish your answer
okay it's dough let's see what we got
baby the scariest thing that could pop
out of your boobs
[Laughter]
i love that
who's picking
oh
[Laughter]
gee i wonder who wrote these is
[Music]
this is didn't think of anything no you
did great you did great enough
to write inside a get well soon card
don't just don't simple and clean
what are these votes are these for real
oh
hey whose hand was that
not mine
watson did you hear it oh kiara okay
oh come on i know what you're thinking
you could have given me that one
what would it be waffles
is that even something that you can buy
in bulk
i don't know can you i don't know maybe
i mean you get a life insurance
you'll get a life insurance i have a
ton of live insurance because i'm
insured forever and my life i guess so
huh you really do have nothing about
that
[Applause]
spider memories can't believe it in
memory
it's not a weird number that's not a
weird number there's nothing wrong with
a number
nothing wrong with the num it's a
what
this is hard oh
um
i can't be funny i suck at being funny
i know me too this is rough
oh god i can't think of anything
okay okay okay i'm done
oh no while we're waiting let me ask you
how do chickens get strong
hello hello hello
huh what did you say i hear you i
well at least the chat is laughing i
love you
so i was entering an answer i'm sorry no
you're you're fine because it's
i just listened
all right well i tried we all know how
that's gonna go
oh come on
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's like you must have seen many a
whiteboard
[Laughter]
what's that what's safety cute it's
cheating
as because my brain wasn't working i was
gonna write uh next one up
never mind um
who's euclid um a place
yeah shapes are important
when do you use shapes after you leave
after you after you leave school
when do you use them put
[Music]
[Laughter]
i like fishing i forgot to vote oh wait
never mind
oh don't get me started on this
that's pretty clever actually that's
pretty clever i gotta say that's a
clever one
[Laughter]
it was good kiara it was good the most
important
lesson in a social media class for
senior citizens
oh man what would it be seeing your
citizens
it's not good
google.com i just did a google
it's not google
the facebook status status bar is not
google
[Music]
yeah one more round of brown yeah
i like this this is fun this is a fun
game
is so good i'm right behind you
driplash on your
what some of us don't have this level of
comedic ability no i'm competing
against the npc oh no
it's gonna be easy
what
the most recent generation
who is jen said um
is that after zoomers
oh um oh god my brain
oh no my brain is totally a blank
um oh god
this request requires some multi-level
comedic skills
help help help oh god okay
um i can't i can't
oh my god 15 seconds
time's almost up hurry
[Laughter]
um
i wonder who got this one
[Laughter]
[Music]
the what what the
chili sauce the the corn on the cob
no no the the roanoke the cool
my crony oh oh no i didn't
wait who
you're funny
fast
right vote for the one you like best
the problem is being faster than life is
that from calling
i get it every time it's not us
competing against each other it's we're
competing against the game
i get it oh it's competing with the the
computer thing okay
i couldn't think of anything
oh just kidding no it wasn't clown
no i'm not that edgy
[Laughter]
but i feel the second one very much
because i'm also not funny it seems
i feel the second one
i can't go wrong with cat videos
[Music]
can all collabs we ever do always
jackpots games from now on
i gave up immediately i tried to be
funny for like
10 seconds and i was like nah forget
this i think i'd rather die i'd rather
accept the feet
you have over a minute
same player no not play again we'll play
again please something different please
i'm different okay
same one what do you guys want to do
same different thing different
what what about um what does chat think
maybe they want to see it again they
might want to see a different something
else
yeah why do you want to get i'm
predicting chat will say a different
game but maybe i could be wrong
the same oh yeah same different more
same
differences i want to think about
different different different different
different differences
same same same
this is a nightmare what do you guys
want to do what do you guys want to do
were you ladies feeling this game if you
were we can play it one more time but
it's up to you
yeah let's play it one more time and
then and then do our thing you know
our field okay okay okay
okay same players let's do it yeah wow
i gotta be funny yeah let's be let's be
real funny you guys
it's so good
just to warm up for houses
don't challenge me
i wonder
[Music]
how can we go
you guys have 60 seconds and you only
have two so you know take your time
oh i already answered it sit back and
relax
tasty clip safety clip oh you didn't
is
wait oh only one oh if i take a safety
quick
yeah sure if you're feeling like yeah if
you must then
28 seconds you have 20 seconds yeah
[Music]
nice smitty got bars
is to dress like oh
chocolate
don't dry oh come on it's obvious
[Laughter]
god i wish i'd thought of shrek
god i wish i had thought of shrek
what the
[Music]
um i i think i have to go with the
second one
i feel fortunate
[Music]
i mean the slang is up to date michael
bay oh
god
can you imagine if michael bay tried to
make a movie about like books
just exploding books add
i don't hate it see i don't even know
who michael bay is
oh
[Laughter]
where could it be oh
what
[Laughter]
oh the audience i'm glad you guys
stopped
differently
i think i know exactly who both of them
are easily
there
but actually some chicken or chicks
mixes tell her no
it was a tough one it was a really tough
one
but it's what's in my tummy you know oh
yeah
what wait what nothing huh
so the points are doubled oh please
don't do this to me
double or nothing all right what you got
here
okay
oh
my english brain isn't anyway
i feel like it'd be easy to put points
if i just make it hollow live related
right
as it seems to be that's gonna be funny
just say holla stuff
[Music]
hmm
ah you guys have 20 seconds
no no no no no no
[Laughter]
16. okay 14.
can i skip this round
oh
bears of course it was ena oh my god
that one is good too their ropes are
good
that was tough
[Laughter]
that's clever oh god i don't want him
you guys are clever oh wait wait it's so
little
wait wait did not vote everyone i was
thinking
sorry my brain isn't that high output
right now
oh my god both are crazy
why not gotta be honest
that was hard but they're both good
[Laughter]
[Music]
one friends episode titled the one where
i love friends though i love that show
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
then it doesn't mean anything she ran
out of time
i ran out of time thanks girl
thanks girl i was the start of a great
idea i just know it
i appreciate that
okay i'm going to try this time i'm
going to try i promise
i'll stop making the game not fun
starkey
were the last two ones last time now
we're the top ones
i'm gonna pull out the big the big guns
for this one
she rolled up her sleeves here we go
oh my god you've got this are you
pitying me schmidty
is that what this is
oh my god
i got a good one
oh my god what am i right i hate myself
oh my god no oh this is horrible
i love it that's horrible
[Music]
oh
oh i was the first one you girls are
still thinking
think think hide
time's almost up stop game
in you're late with me on your birthday
didn't you say 30 minutes that's over
now
where's your baby oh
um it's coming you feeling oh
i didn't finish it in time
oh
i see i say i see okay
photographers everyone finds us what the
outline's still invisible pretty
funny schmidty
why is
11 herbs and spice
yeah it depends it depends i guess on
the relationship
is kiara um a friend or food
i guess we'll find out right now i mean
both make me seem like a food but okay
i mean i don't want to eat something
with squishy
season with herbs and spices
i think this
[Music]
wait no replace my eyes with nuts excuse
me
oh it was me
oh
answers
[Laughter]
all right i guess all right are we going
to take a little break
because it's time okay i think we're all
getting children right now
what we need to do for a baby
we're gonna go help uh i mean uh uh yeah
with a child
that's what we're gonna do a doula
yeah all right so we're gonna have to do
a little standbys is that cool you guys
we'll be back shortly wait wait wait we
have a yeah i think yeah
yeah we're gonna go stand by and we're
gonna we're gonna mute ourselves uh and
you're gonna listen to the jack box
games music
chat you're gonna like it you're gonna
listen you're gonna like it
we're gonna be right back okay here we
go
zoom goodbye be back in a minute we're
leaving now excuse me sorry excuse
the me
[Music]
instead of one came down
is
so
[Music]
do
me
[Music]
give it your best shots
the quickest
for me
[Music]
when is now
wow
[Music]
me
give it your best shot
[Music]
it's time
for me
[Music]
three
quickly
[Music]
so
me
give it your best shot
[Music]
it's time
for me
[Music]
now
here
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
me
god
[Music]
we're fine
it worked we're fine thank you everyone
who waited so patiently
um we're ready to share something
special with you
are you ready are you ready
[Music]
here we go and three
two one
this is so awesome
[Music]
do you guys like the new outfits
[Applause]
everybody boings now it's awesome
[Music]
yeah you guys want to zoom spine
[Applause]
no it's okay it's special kiara it's
special
it's enchanted
oh man i could play with this forever
oh no bring your back
bring your body down bring your back
you know what's funny
hey amelia i think you rendered us
[Music]
[Applause]
nah it's fine it's part of the charm
you're ended up well they won't notice
well at least kiara is fine
uh i'm scared you're just gonna hit me
my fight
here's time i can i can do a little a
little mechanical adjustment
believe it leave it to me
unless you guys can see where you are
you can move
yourself oh okay okay i'm traveling
between portals
quick flash three
[Music]
you're stuck do you need me to help you
amelia all right
no i i got it you guys oh i think i'm
overlapping
a little bit hold on i'll make you a
little smaller
yeah because i'm the god of this world
hold on a sec drink ray
and then extend okay wait oh but i can
see grass trident there we go
quick lash through perfect
equipment perfect
is so sad i want to pull down my glasses
okay do you want to go all right let's
switch to stand by real quick and put on
we put on your glasses
put them on hold on one second
i'm gonna bring out my size while i'm at
it done
all right let me grab myself
you guys know i can take off my crown
but i'm not gonna i'm not gonna do that
in this stream
why would you take up your crown no
right naked
huh
i wish i could whistle
for you
[Music]
all right and we're going back
hey
yeah check it out we got sunglass well
kind of yes
here we go now the curtain now the whole
squad now the whole squad and the place
to be
wait
are we looking cool
there we go
[Music]
ah what can you do by the way number oh
whoa whoa you're
whoa there whoa there buddy
oh my gosh it's all right it's part of
the it's part of the april fool
the chaos is part of the april fool
i think we'll get a chance to show these
to you guys as well uh in our own
individual streams yeah that i have to
go
on wait wait
wait i might go mustache
who's
do you know no matter what angry or sad
expression i put on i can't frown
i can only smile dabbing attack
you can only smile i know right trapped
in true hell you can only smile
[Music]
[Laughter]
like it we sure do yeah yeah
why are you gonna grab them from my
house you want to find a car okay
look at the monsters that we draw yeah
hold on a second
yeah we're going to do that we're going
to do that i need to go rearrange this
real quick though so quickly we're going
to head back to those stones
and now we're going to oh my gosh you
guys are really jumping okay thankfully
everything looks pretty much okay kind
of possibly potentially
doubling boing boing
bubbling blindfold
[Music]
yeah i guess so huh we do kind of look
pretty goomy
like gummies oh yeah yeah oh i'm hungry
now
buddy
[Music]
we're playing the other game now right
yeah what do you guys want to play
the jaw oh the drawing one okay cool
what's uh what's the game
called so i may i may find it we can get
the out of this whiplash nightmare
hold on a second
this is music oh it's gonna haunt my
freaking nightmare
is it in seven or is it in six it's it's
it's in this one okay the one with the
fish
hold up lather round
oh man you're going in are you ready to
rumble
are you ready
[Music]
all right let me put my little sense
can you smell what the eyes cooking
uh do i want to
is that a do i want all right hold on i
think we're good
i think we're good okay i joined oh you
guys were able to join oh okay i guess
you can see yeah
yeah i feel like i have to choose all
right specific character
i feel like forced to use it
uh-oh i can't read it all right
let me oh my destiny
you know i'm spinning that's perfect
[Music]
perfect let me join too hold on i want
to join
wait i'm being i'm being put in the box
i like that giraffe
now will be this one oh
um
[Music]
all right i think we're good to go
yes i shall oh press everybody's in to
start
who is the vr it would be crucial
to see who's the best decree oh man nice
with unusual skills okay
underdogs take down the heavy
oh man
[Laughter]
nice jumped up
he's ready to draw all right i have my
mouse ready
i'm gonna use my mouse too oh my god did
i just did you skip the tutorial like
uh oh does that mean we're drawing
just follow what it says on the prompt
and try to come up with something
according to what it says
okay on your screen yeah what does the
word a front
mean a front like uh to confront
somebody or like aggressively
okay
okay um
oh boy this is going to be interesting
you guys can't see what we're drawing
yet but you'll be able to see it
soon
why does brain go blank at the worst
time brain
did everyone like the new outfits by the
way did some i think a lot of people
like
did people take it seriously and think
we're really gonna bring out on the
outfit because i saw a lot of people not
believing it and then a lot of people
also kind of
maybe expected something but weren't
sure what
oh oh no oh no
yeah you guys have 30 30 seconds oh
no
oh i have to name my champion oh
[Music]
um new outfits 10 to 10. yay
we didn't give a shout out by the way oh
yeah yeah i think they are gosh this is
really bad
it's a warm up
[Music]
i
to create what they hope is a worthy
challenger
let's see the drama unfold sorry destin
say get off the screen we don't need you
there anymore
you can't save us yeah you just see
somebody else's drawing and try to match
it
i see what happened to the one i just
drew though
oh no i don't know how to draw of my
heart
oh drawing with the mouse is so hard
i have no idea what i'm doing is there
no eraser draw
something to challenge the picture that
you saw
yeah yeah i get it i get that i get done
don't know what to draw
oh eraser would be i guess the back
button
if on the top
wait how much time one minute oh oh my
god okay
everyone's so focused what the hell oh
my god it's
serious business yeah
you know there's no red color what the
hell give me some
yeah there's there's like orange and
pink it's like a paint bucket tool
so you can if you use the bigger marker
it goes underneath the thin lines
oh i see okay okay
it's time to name it wait
what
i tried i couldn't color
i don't
come on come on i can do this i can do
this okay
all right well i got the main colors
the main color oh
gosh i tried for the main event
our first opponent
[Applause]
oh
are they going to fight oh they're not
actually fighting okay
oh they're floating oh
a piece of wood it's not blank
it's not blank it's my original
character piece of wood
[Laughter]
is
cult later
oh
67 percent
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh that's a
oh she did her best
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
your
[Music]
me and i back you battled me or you
battled yourself
and i'm i'm somehow i won you're not
even wrong
oh
i see i see there's so many blue tones
why the hell
are there so many blue tones huh
against each other
[Music]
i don't know why i need the blue color i
don't know
i know i don't i don't know
and why don't they have a red they have
all blue exactly why no red
there it is red ah
it's orange it's the it's the top like
top right one that's red
that's orange maybe it's just your
monitor color
i don't know it looks red on my screen i
don't know why
oh man i'm ready for this battle i was
born for this
ah
okay whatever none no nobody needs to be
out no
no wait what happens
yeah okay
oh wow i wonder who drew this one
[Music]
okay
hmm
oh my god i don't know how to draw what
i want to draw let's google
you can do it kiara thank you
thank you i'll try
i wonder if people will understand what
that is supposed to be
this is really putting my speed drawing
skills to the test
this music is banger
okay i have
my thing ready
i think i know i'm better
this is so good can we do um jack focus
games
do another one sometime yeah
okay
i put all of my effort into mine
surprise contest hi include a
players can surprise out their
characters
and votes for both contests will be
curious
what's going on
[Laughter]
i'm being
i voted for the underdog and the perry
says
my gosh
[Music]
at least
oh
so powerful
what wait what does that mean like like
the tv stuff
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
oh no what's next
[Laughter]
hold on
it
oh my god oh my god
oh he got a load
it's pretty rude can we call a draw
i know that we'll call it raw
[Laughter]
of the century
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
i mean i think it's probably the same
right we stayed with the same person
that's really good i feel like it
[Applause]
nice very powerful
this is the final match the judges are
trying wow
final scores and uh
[Music]
that was fun that was a really fun game
yeah that was great
oh my gosh
[Laughter]
whatever yeah
that was really fun it's time for more
do you guys want to string but
just a bit longer please thank you
definitely peek the mic sorry about that
i really don't mean to hurt you i'm
gonna
go move it so we can play this game
again
do i okay would you like to one more
okay cool i have a stream too but it's
only in half an hour okay
i will be done before then for sure
right
drawing time
to see who's the best decreeding
champion characters
i think we can skip this tutorial
oh i can't i can skip it at the moment
it doesn't give me an option but next
time it gives me an option i'll skip it
okay yeah hmm
the trainer nice
i don't understand this one what's that
word let me tell you google
my english knowledge is being tested
here
i have no idea what to draw
oh no the laughter oh god
oh god one minute
i don't like mine i don't like my either
yes yes yes
oh
hey hey i'm in the zone now oh
hey
all right here we
[Music]
copyright
what is this supposed to be
this oh god
did you get mine because i don't know
what mine's supposed to be i think
i know
oh
everyone place your boots you still have
money
to place your bed guys this is a good
i'm talking to the audience this is a
good kind of gambling
you place your bets on us who's gonna
win the fight
online this is really bad
this is really bad
oh no oh no
they work swift
how much time
oh god
oh god well probably no one's gonna know
what i drew anyway okay
i'm sure
[Laughter]
someone right over your head
we're seeing something weird okay now
it's normal
don't worry about it
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
a day
yes
can you
[Music]
that future has seen better days oh
oh boy um
yeah i mean you see a better day you
seem better today
the people question mark
lucy
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh i mean i think it's pretty obvious
[Music]
this isn't the battle that i thought we
were going to have hold on
this isn't the best this isn't the
battle i thought we were thank you
i'm not chosen
with my butt we're not worthy oh
that's sweet at least there's redemption
in the end maybe the tentacle went
somewhere
no it sounds pretty good
wanna talk about it you want to talk
about it
[Laughter]
it's getting drawn out
i get i wait ha ha yeah
[Laughter]
i like it made it really
[Music]
to squishy up a woman who just gave
birth though
yeah still have to clean up the
afterbirths
no poland
where's my creativity today
never had it
it's okay you just gotta awaken it ah
this is hard okay i'm ready to roast
someone
[Music]
okay
huh
[Music]
uh right right
oh god okay
how much time not enough
40 seconds
40 seconds oh god
i think i finished
ah
name those characters
say my name say my name if no one is
around you
say baby i love you i love you
no god why does this model make me smile
excuse i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm
sorry
oh no
that's rough oh what is this
what what what
what who is that
but
[Laughter]
oh
i don't
um
oh boy
40 seconds out ah
i have no idea what i'm doing
let's go
whatever
okay i got it eight
[Music]
that was rough i don't know that was
rough that was a rough one
for the tag teams each matchup you ready
not ready
oh god this is rough
you're both good
yeah moving those furniture you know
oh you can swap out
you can swap it come on you can do it
[Applause]
this is a tough one
[Music]
oh gosh choices choices
[Laughter]
friends
which one is better at hacking the
mainframe
scandal
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh man pikachu come on
[Laughter]
see some stuff you know
oh what's this oh
man this is a tough one um
is
oh
the people who are dying in the
emergency room that's true
that's true
[Music]
let's go with the other boys put them up
put them up i'm the original boy come on
[Laughter]
yay
saturday night it's okay i would have
voted for glue eater tom too it's fine
i'm so happy the champion of saturday
night and the purge
nice
oh man
beautiful that was fun it was beautiful
that was really fun i had a good time
that was a really good time though
thanks for games everybody yeah that was
cool
that was a lot of fun
[Music]
oh
that was fun hey uh yeah
i want to bounce and is that a crowbar
okay there you go you know
yeah nice you want a bunk yeah yeah yeah
yeah
i'm coming over all right all right i'm
coming over
here i come fun hold on
all right i'm here i'm here i'm here for
you to bonk me
thank you i'm going back
um so yeah this is fun thanks for coming
guys
i hope that you enjoyed our very serious
outfit reveal
thank you it's very serious happy first
of april
happy yeah that's the one
um i think a lot of us are doing streams
on our individual channels uh with these
so we can share more of them with you if
you're interested
and check them out i haven't worn it in
five minutes
yeah it is my birthday on on april the
4th 4
4 which is the best day yeah and i have
a lot of announcements to make during
that birthday stream and i'm releasing
an mv right before the stream
uh you can see the times on my twitter
please come check it out you may be
really happy yay
yay
thanks guys oh by the way by the way i
wanted to mention this to you guys here
but um i am going to be uh accepting
collins
uh from from everyone in my discord if
you want to don't feel like you have to
but if you're available
uh give me your ring all right yeah yeah
yeah
this goes to jp senpai as well yeah so
anyway that's all i have
uh okay home talk is also on the weekend
time i might do it with the well
with this wealthy livestream that's my
gosh don't be amazing
this time with uh akiro tao from the
first generation so if you want to learn
more about her
yeah come to holocaust this weekend
yay cute
yeah yes very good i'm excited
[Music]
today oh nice oh enjoy
yeah enjoy that sounds like a ride i'm
gonna celebrate together yes yes
yeah oh yeah and gura and i have a watch
along together
oh my gosh so tomorrow tomorrow
uh my shades uh let me take them off
do you want to uh kiara do you want to
do you want to
take your shades off uh we can wink
yeah all right i i hit you you're hidden
away if you want to
take off your glasses okay
[Music]
come to my next stream if you want to
see the wig
i'm about to do another one it's really
hot in my home so i need to go turn on
the air conditioning anyway
i'm everywhere i hope you remember me
and we are hello live english
what's good homemade hashtag uru mess i
guess use that
is that one yes hey what is that
what does that mean you do
like yeah that's a cute comfy healthy
comfy
that's cute i like that and a huge the
biggest ups
ever to wealthy for making these by the
way for us
thank you thank you so much well if we
go give waffy some love
um for all the incredible
hold on a sec i want to bounce
the attention just go give waffy all the
love huh he's shopping off the stream
yeah yeah sorry i'm sorry i don't wait i
get weird
i i got it i'm really hot right now
i can't believe it went right
what the f word maybe i shouldn't be
surprised
someone ring them in my doorbell so i'm
just gonna say bye bye bye
bye bye everyone we're gonna leave now
bye guys we're zooming yeah bye
is spinning too in our hearts we'll
always be spinning
um in our hearts forever and ever
there's there she goes
[Music]
your challenger
soon when the battle starts
will you have what it takes