[Music]
oh good
morning
oh y y y y
y finally here
okay everybody does everything sound
okay
yes welcome to
B
[Applause]
welcome wow thank you for the green
blocks and as you can see I think all of
us have already uh seen the inside of
the borodor and this is the outside
right now oo it's it's
massive wow the massive
yeah you know what else very massive
very very everybody is wearing school
uniforms what else is
M my tail
W wait you don't you don't have your
tail though I don't see
it so yeah I would like to say thank you
guys for joining and uh we're still kind
of
in the beginning so first thing first
please group with your team I have my
[Music]
[Applause]
teammate we
have hello I'm
in hello
yay please say
something are you ready for
[Applause]
today you guys are practicing so I bet I
bet you guys are
ready yeah are you guys ready are you
guys positive that you can yeah we feel
good yeah we're
good we're going to do it what is what
is your team name what is your team name
oh we got to come up with a team name we
have
one
[Music]
okay and next team the dead p
iist all right so how how are you uh how
is your preparation for this for today
event we are preparing so much right oh
so
much
poon oh are you guys are guys positive
that you guys can uh win today so
positive no idea oh yeah we're so
positive
yeah and uh what is your team name do
you guys have team name KY what do you
think no hope team no hope why so good I
tried to call you say we need to do the
reaper psychology IED to okay I wish you
good luck everybody thank you so much
godam
it come back thank
you over here please
away from everyone because it's really
loud okay
hello
hello attention please attention
KY attention Ricky attention attention
Ricky we are the P nice Synergy between
the two so what is your team
namei we didn't even have to think of
one because we were p n all along we
were a team for years now
real oh no sticky ke I hope you enjoy
today will even if we don't win we will
be the winners anyway because we are the
ones who love each other the most
exactly yes good
Lu free lunch for
everybody totally not a bribe during
Simon Says can you please speak
slowly okay's job I can do that I can
slowly slowly slowly speak slow slow
motion
[Music]
okay okay thank you
Pap thank
you thank
you
next let's TR
yeah yeah yo we are ready for this no I
mean I'm much better now so I can do the
coughing why' you collect it third
36 what you mean 360 coughing Co please
you were dying last night I was so
worried for you I will see the doctor
again today so no worries okay
[Music]
where is your
teammate ASMR I tried to call
her her manager should try to call
[Music]
her manager
go what what is she doing um digging
what are you
doing will you be burying me in this
that's not my te what you
want what is your teammate doing there
oh are you having a fight she's
narrating she's make coron louder so I
can hear her beautiful voice yeah she
does this often what she's sking
toil oh yeah you can adjust my volum so
stupid sticky keiss how to turn off
sticky keiss on this
computer no idea keyboard shortcut for
stick is off stupid I'm laughing because
I feel bad okay off now I can do this as
much as I want y can I do it too oh
yeah it's
it's
j that's a okay my that's a little too
much guys that's a little too much if
you're if you're at home it should be
off when you when you go to V and then
to setting things and then to select
microphone yes do you really have the
mic that you should be using there yes
really people what mic is it I already
to that her that that this is her voice
like the real I'm going to go ride the
tweet I don't think I even have my
waiting room because I can't log on so
sad on Twitter I mean I don't know bless
you bless you bless you who is it
oh bless you don't you recognize my
sneezes yet no because you never sneeze
in front of my
face every minutes I'm
like place I
never okay yeah I was going to write a
tweet and then I forgot about it too
busy hunting hi cron hello are you guys
practicing you guys like the thumbnail
you want to see something really nice
that Me Andy found still kind of waiting
for that's not
nice I don't
know they should they should ask your
manager so I don't know man how dare you
I don't know okay my tweet is written
hey what the [\h__\h] killed the cow I was
traing how you going to how are you
going to compete without your teammate
huh I will rescue you don't
worry look at this such a
home wow I would prefer to live in the
temple over there
[Music]
ATT attention
please
oh three three okay
okay okay guys
uh so the first uh game will be treasure
hunts they uh there will be around 10
spots of treasure it can be in a chest
it can be in a shelter it can be in a
dble it can be in anywhere um so your
uh your mission is to find it and chest
have around three emeralds o that you
can use for The Maze later also also uh
there is hint around the area that you
can check
[Music]
[Applause]
okay so before we started let's sleep
first
again
okay okay they enough beds I think
so who's next to me is it
enough my bed everyone it's okay I can I
canle oh
[Music]
one more one more thing
everybody the time the time for uh
hunting the treasure will
be uh 10 minutes so after 10 minutes We
Gather here again we will uh we will ask
you
here uh by
chat wait where's the
treasure it's on the it's on the first
floor okay it's on the very first floor
with the mini mini grass Alo
outside it's not
inside outside it's on the lower part
with the many trees and grass we don't
need to break anything right we don't
bre
no you don't need
anything my RPG senses are
tingling who wants dirt who's hungry is
everybody
[Music]
ready I'm ready I'm ready I'm
ready I'm going to count the timer so
are you guys
[Music]
ready wait so if we don't if we don't
have to H okay it's fine
everyone stand
by yes what are we stand by for what are
we stand
by and then we find one go find your
treasure try like around here I'm not
sure probably aint here is
this how do you even find hints like I
have paper or hey Stone reveals chest
addess Stone a take I don't understand
English a
stone a stone oh it's just decoration I
think what kind of stone wait but what
if Ana what if it's like a button
there's
buttons yeah there is your M brick cool
stone plate
TI
M how what does don't look like in this
game
[Music]
like no we're
um what
is
no
F no
hum you can break Moss blocks I don't
know they said no need to break anything
so there's so many buttons so I assume
it'll be a button
[Music]
flowers flowers
to the hints are kind of I don't
know oh my God I'm like am I going to
find
[Music]
zero oops sorry
zaa yeah have you been
lucky
no I literally don't know
like where's my teammate my beloved
teammate doco
yo what's
up maybe they did find it I don't know
among the flowers the flowers I'm I'm
trying I'm also trying like I read the
clues and I'm like why why did you find
something
no I see buttons though I know we we
don't have to break anything
right how far would it be from the chest
should we break it from I'm going to
destroy public property no I don't think
we're supposed to break it that's not it
we should just break property
right uh you guys can like keep on
pressing stuff and whatnot or just look
for them yeah so like it's not a
breaking thing right
there's another one
yeah
oh no
it's like a dispenser sound
but come to
[Music]
me I think we need like a voice chat you
know we need like a group voice chat
H back oh hi n oh wait wait the book the
book read the book I need you for that
on Stones you stand both far near and
far to find the chest where Treasures
are press the stones to make the way
only teamwork will save the day I guess
it's okay there's this button right oh
this button here so I guess this is the
near button and there's another far
button that if we press it at the same
time I guess maybe uh
it will activate something but like but
like where do you want like a group
voice chat stand both near and far to
fun on Stones you stand oh yeah do you
think we should be on group voice chat
yeah I think so you guys probably need
we we need to each make
a one I'll make
one um I'm going to make I'm going to
make I'm going to do that now actually
wait no keep on pressing it keep on
pressing it wait no no no I'm going to
make a group chat for us and just can we
do
that yeah like a normal group chat maybe
can you hear me oh okay ah this is the
teamwork okay that way you can hear me
even when I'm far away yeah okay so can
you keep on pressing the button I'll
just press buttons that I find close by
far away then but like I guess I don't
know if they're
related cuz we have to press them at the
same time right but Ana and are also
pressing the button right now but
[Music]
yeah look around
dresses I'm going to go to the next one
where K is
coughing this is the hardest one
actually really hardest
but this one this one the chest is
waiting to inside search to gra around
the chest is the
branches B bushes hide
Branch Branch tree
branches how can how can choc chest
coulage I don't think I've ever seen
that before maybe maybe hidden in
like up here's nothing right prob I have
no
idea in the forest deep and old but this
one's like you need a key for it and I'm
like key we can't even find something
that's like not
keyed has anyone found
anything um what's this
to yeah see this is like something but
the dispenser doesn't do anything
that's sus that's that's sus or I see
people what another another another
weird button that's doing something but
no book
here yo have you found anything just out
of curiosity
no oh wait so I guess the people outside
our voice chat can't hear me huh or I
don't know okay what was this one H the
book is gone for one the book is gone
are they allowed to just take it maybe
it's because the treasure is taken
oops oh I'm going to replace this be
taken away there was
something this one's
missing yeah one book is
missing They're laughing at
me Mo that's like it what what the No No
that's I found a books that's uh empty
just so they already found it and I
guess that's why maybe why they took the
book but they weren't necessarily
supposed to take
[Music]
it okay the shers don't look hard to
find I want to find one maybe it's in
the tree somewhere in the trees look at
the trees why is there like a destroyed
Moss cool and old uh I destroyed one m I
think before
ouchies who made The
Riddles like there's like weird wool Bo
wools too and like I don't know which
one's like part of the thing and not
this could be a gray Sher
right what's the highest Moss block but
I feel like why is it why is it not
standing out to
me why don't I see it if it's a gray
Shuler it shouldn't have the pattern of
the
blocks yeah I'm just like so confused
cuz like there's like wuls I don't
know yeah baby I don't have time I know
we don't have time I don't think
so I don't I didn't find anything I
finish I'm going
to come GA around the beds please I have
no
idea because um we didn't practice this
either or at least we didn't practice
this on the um 10th so it's like I have
no idea what's like part of the
decoration and what's like actually part
of the you
know tricks or something because I don't
want to oh I accidentally took oh never
mind don't even don't even I can't even
go get wait wait I have nothing wait how
do
[Music]
I I love you I still love you I got a
poot
Emerald I got four em nice
everyone wait who found who found what
Kobo Kobo found four and I just don't
know how what I want to check C POV
after this yeah I don't even know so you
guys did you guys find any no I don't
know what to search for no no did you
guys know that there's actually one
really close by no probably right
here what the
hell Al so that's what it's supposed to
look
like yeah we said that they in chokers
and chest and hoppers
bln that I I didn't go down because I I
only checked like this this
area come here anyway come
here let's go I'll make you another
stage three emeralds but it's already
time out who got the emal who's got the
emerald we did many
have um in total
nine
it's U maybe moreable with shaders I
don't know but I think like honestly
um when they said first floor I didn't
know that the bottom ones were counted
as well so I don't know I just felt like
I was looking at the wrong places did
you
guys
any I know they were like in boxes but I
don't know why oh I guess I guess it's
fine it's like
and in a hole like
[Music]
right yo yo
yo y what happened what
happened she found time finished oh
you're just salty you don't have any
Emerald
huh that's [\h__\h]
Fair
of
no I think it's a joke
everyone everyone hello
hi attention
please hi okay thank you thank you for
the attention since we already done the
treasure H so we have to go back and the
baburu to continue the Simon say the
next game so
shall we sleep
firstep sleep
[Applause]
[Music]
first what if we share a bit together in
Minecraft the game what if there was
only one
bed be crazy that would be crazy wink W
everyone please go in let's go all right
let's
go in summary we came empty-handed but
we will recover it also feels up I'm up
we could also Rob the other members but
don't tell anyone I'm catching up I'm
catching I'm catching
run it's okay
it's okay you do pretty well what Simon
says so yeah that's true you're going to
make it up
here I have a I have a feeling that I'm
the one who's going to mess up Simon
says not because I don't understand
Indonesian but because I just have bad
memory fud I'm so
scared it's okay we'll probably mess up
before we get to five or soow
we are here Pabi is
ready who's Simon are we ready Simon am
I
ever oh thought one of those dragons
only one way to find out that's what
they say we'll do our best why don't we
listen to what Simon
says why does it matter to us
[Music]
yeah oh I I hope attention
please I wish I
like who's
ready no I'll let someone go first okay
okay okay let somebody go first yeah you
guys you guys looks like you're
ready RNG please rou r
draw a raffle I based
on no no whoever found the emerald first
uh whoever found the most Emerald should
go first right
[Music]
true we have more time to practice this
thing like by
watching like we we have like
demonstration we have an example ahead
of
us because I is at the top go
[Music]
first yeah that's why guys you don't
name yourself with
a you will always go first in
[Music]
school
a we watch
see how fast it
[Music]
goes I was like I was like oh we should
stand
[Music]
here the okay nothing
happen basically because
it's one Emerald per level that
go
okay a place we got
this we can watch
here to test my memory
[Music]
what the heck
is
there's okay okay okay if you want to
practice no we don't want to practice is
English and
[Music]
wait
hold like the I was like okay
face you're you're
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
giving I mean you're not wrong
wait so um when is it going to be
our we'll
see where's my oh she's
there ah it sounds so peaceful
here oh my God I now I know the onion
look the the like inhaling wiper laugh
but the high pitch now I know what you
guys are talking
about you
know that is so funny
okay the sound of lovely
silence ah
yes ah sorry I was like just staring in
silence they all went into group
Rees oh
okay so we can't even hear the
dialogue are we not supposed to I don't
know I think it's so nobody so I don't
know I don't think well if everybody's
in a group we don't need to be in a
group I think they hear us though when
we're not uh in a group they still hear
us I think they hear us but we don't
hear them no hope right CR turn around
if you hear us
yeah blink yeah yeah yeah yeah she SK
toilet toilet SK toilet SK SK
toilet okay wait should we go into group
okay okay okay I'm going to I'm going to
name it P
Papi no I'm going to name it mass
destruction what's wrong with you I
don't know I just we we needed a
catching name cuz they were all like no
hope and stuff like that come she's
catching it it is I guess like they do
any of them have like a I can't I can't
check Che
now I think are we the only ones maybe
iOS sorta is like a common uh name also
yeah they're like time Smith or
something I don't know yeah yeah yeah
time Smith but they're not using it
they're calling it no hope it's fine and
Kobo and Canada is canibu you know what
canibu
is is it a word in Indonesian yeah it's
kind of like um like a
like rubbery
um like a handkerchief not handkerchief
it's kind of like to wipe um surfaces
off cars after you wash a car or like
clean the bathroom like a rag like a
wiping cloth oh and that's like the
Famous Brand in
Indonesia wow like a sponge rag exactly
uhhuh yeah that's it wait wait to test
me test me and give me like give me like
uh five in a row okay
um wait are you allowed to do that or
you you start after everything is
done uh oh yeah okay okay right okay
okay
L mm um l
you said back once I think then look
left and then okay I already forgot but
I think like in in the actual thing like
we start with one and then it builds up
so I feel like it's easier to remember I
guess so cuz I I'll have it done okay
let's do it one by one and then add up
like one and then two and then three and
four you know Mund sat yeah Mund sat and
back okay up kid
L how many times
L just one
Lampa look to the left uh H up kitty and
jump twice and then what she say uh
throw
once yeah something like that go back
and I don't I don't even remember what I
just told
you
sh is okay
Mund um twice throw once but I don't
want to lose my potato so I'm not going
to throw now and then she said I don't
know what I said something three times
um oh yeah I remember what' she say what
did she say three times p p pul three
times right yeah I think so something
like that Wow Let's Go five
Emerald oh okay five rounds I did okay I
think the way we just did it now is how
they'll do it so I think I can do it
okay cuz I I remember the words and yeah
okay we're done okay no need
practice
next I can't hear
[Music]
her why you leave me I don't know cuz I
thought we were not practicing anymore
no yeah we are oh sh everybody I don't
want to make my brain
tired you have to make my brain tired
mass destruction
V2 there you go
sorry there you go okay okay can you
continue the previous one [\h__\h]
umly what was
that
J J sorry I just picked up my potato
okay okay okay wait okay let me do it uh
uh uh okay start one step back look to
the left uh jump twice uh uh throw once
and uh punch three times
and did you say jonok yeah I think so
jonok I don't remember how many times it
was damn it once once whatever yeah I
think you're good my brain's so tired I
can't remember all this at least four
emeralds should be
manageable
yeah yeah cuz if we practice too much
now my brain will be so tired because
it's like for you it's easier you
already know Indonesian yeah yeah I know
but my memory is so bad we have to think
twice because I have to translate in my
brain well good luck
[Music]
okay are they how are they doing I don't
know are they all out of the
now no I'm only
hearing
no I'm only
hearing she's out
too so that's why we're hearing the
good good sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry I didn't think I would go past
wings I can't I can't stay quiet I can't
stand still not in Minecraft not in real
[Music]
life I'm not teaching her Kali or
whatever because like honestly you don't
need to care about that I already know
yeah
matter yeah it's just like times you
know even if you if I say and without CI
it's the same
thing it's just saying it's just having
to remember even though the only thing
you have to remember
is yeah and Mera somehow I think of
c and then I think of red yeah it's easy
[Music]
why is my chat not showing on the screen
I want to
watch why why should
last what the well okay I don't mind
yeah I don't mind
whatever
uh please come to the okay Jo the group
VC
that uh group
ofc Simon
[Music]
Says everyone stand by in the red area I
want to Mee J L
L it's okay it's
okay on the red area please am I on the
red stand on the red oh stand not on the
red
area stand in the red
area thank you okay are you ready are
you ready yeah okay it will be super
easy
ID in Minecraft not not in real life
okay Ry ready K ready yeah yeah okay I
will give you the first one guys pray
for
us
lamp threee 2 one
go okay okay you can take your item I
was so scared you're starting off of a
difficult one wait so so that's like so
that's lampar three stuff or is it just
lampar and then you're like counting
down just one stuff actually one okay
okay okay
okay ah okay okay I thought they were
telling me to throw okay so next is
lampar
J three two one wa I have a question I
have a question okay no question just do
it wait but okay if they don't say it
maybe it's only one time I don't know
okay just one time
okay just do it one time okay okay and
if you want to stay jok that's also fine
don't worry you got it you got it ah
okay but you know uh yeah next next is
getting
harder lamp mhm J mhm
Lum mm l l two I already did it okay
Lampa
J yeah
let's go yes let's go let's go go go
let's go okay next next next
lamp
J okay three 2
[Applause]
one that was four times already right
yeah next next next four emeralds okay
okay okay next
L
J
[Music]
L hi wa I see your
okay next okay
next uh
L
J
ma three two one m l m m
was it Jun cook
uh uh wait uh L and then right and then
here and then here and then AB I forget
one IET one I forgot and then if I turn
and then if I turn right do I turn like
45 Dees right so to the front oh well I
mean yeah as long as you turn right
that's what I'm confused about no as
long as you turn right I think so I
guess that's correct okay yeah you can
you hear the ding ding ding no what who
was wrong me right oh what did I do
wrong no what you do you should you
should end it with fting means that I'm
fing the other
way so kitty yeah first you're facing to
R and then facing to me huh but I what I
faced right did you don't say how many
degrees right yeah no no that's
90 oh you didn't say how many
deges yeah so I think it's just like
okay well it's a misunderstanding oh
well it's had
up had up means yeah so it's kind of
like we we're facing here and then
because this is Kitty and then had up
Canan is like to the right of this
position so you have to face here
yeah so that means four emeralds five
was it five right five five five five
emeralds yeah five emeralds
[Applause]
yay I'm not going to lie we did not
deserve that there you go thank you
thank you that's fine you you guys
actually did great don't
worry okay still the highest so far no
no I think Yoda got five right but
anyways I'm going to exit yeah still the
same
[Music]
exit who get the emerald oh [\h__\h] it's me
situation I thought as long as is this
right right yeah I
mean that's the right
[Music]
five high
five
Suffering From
Success we going to VC or
[Laughter]
what
is
what do I say Canada did you know
cupcake do
I do I say Canada do you know cupcake or
is it
y for
[Music]
what the
hell
what that's very not Sigma of you
[Music]
well it's right it's correct that kiar
is wrong I want see do you want to do
VC okay okay I want to also explain
something to the chat so we can do it in
VC as well
okay hi so it is very unfortunate but I
guess after some thought I guess we were
wrong because technically had up is um
the real meaning is to basically turn
turn as in so like if you turn you turn
45 5 but at I I guess um but there we
weren't told that there's like for
example a back if if there was a word
turn back then no no there there wasn't
right there wasn't a turn back so then
facing right to me is just any right as
long as I turn right yeah I think it's
kind of like they were strict because um
they were because IO Sola had the same
issue yeah they can't say it's okay for
us they say it's not okay for them yeah
if they I feel like honestly to be if
they let iosa move forward then they
could go 10 easily because I feel like
five was like so easy you know no I mean
it's like a little bit oh kind of hon I
don't know I don't think it's that easy
cuz the nervosity really made me forget
everything I just heard I guess yeah me
too but it's kind of like if I heard it
five times yeah as long as I repeat it
in my head it's like better but I feel
like I I hope I hope they do the the
exact same thing to them though
otherwise it's not fair like had up can
on after up kitty and see how what they
do if they do it right then it's fine
but I hope they do it because we all
receive the same
treatment yeah yeah if they got the same
so I get that we would get the same too
yeah yeah they get the same gestures
everybody so you stand here watching
them you can remember it okay okay
that's awesome well okay well let's just
um view then I feel like if everybody
makes the same mistake then it's it's
whatever and if they don't then they're
lucky it's
fine that's why it's private I don't
even know
degrees you don't know the
GRE I can't count but I know mean 360 is
is a 360 like 360 is a full circle yeah
and 180 is half of
it not really
sure is Amy doing it
oh she's she seems to slow be in it yeah
how far are they right
now let's see when they start moving
again or they discussing something maybe
probably same thing
maybe ding
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah they just went yeah they past they're
like they're oh I they're at eight or
nine or
something yeah yeah yeah cuz they're P
the oh they did yeah they did the
jumping now we didn't even see
this did crony K
already get their turn I don't no not
yet no right turning and facing is
different but there is no turning and
facing
commands uh at this point I'm just like
as long as um everybody gets the same
instructions then I'm fine with
it
oh Kyla panicking
really why
no Panic no Panic calm with
K K's gamer she doesn't need to worry
it's all
right but even you know no matter how
much we get we are still tied with iOS
so it's okay oh tied in this game but
not overall right yeah I don't know they
got Treasures they got Treasures well
it's fine we can probably we can
probably catch up in other stuff it
doesn't matter cuz like I said in the
beginning even if we don't win the game
I'm winning because we love each other
I'm winning you yeah we win each other
at the end of the day we're the only
ones who went to the
males nine they got nine nine e that's
so
good you should you should show off your
Indonesian
um my IND you should say you should say
uh you should say in the Minecraft chat
an an yeah a n j a y you you always say
that when we meet an Oh I thought I was
saying
an it's so
over you got a face
need to be in a group chat right do we
the title is It's so over not I think
it's fine okay I don't get it we're not
communicating I don't know
cuz VC
is but I kind want to hear now they can
hear us too it's so
over hi Bluetooth
restrict we
were is crony KY the last ones I wonder
Canada acci press shift instead I did
the same thing yeah yeah I did the same
thing that's a Minecraft issue
yeah
have help help there's Vines maybe you
can climb up the vines okay okay yeah
yeah yeah yeah
nice only okay they're going that was
one I think same I got right two steps
okay yeah yeah that's what I mean okay
so in total we have we got
14 yeah we have 14 I wonder how
expensive the equipment will be I love
that they included Vines um so I have it
if you if you want three
steps the item price three steps we had
two okay no is there the third stage
third stage
oh my
God they're throwing the same thing what
the
[Music]
heck good oh they're still there oh
they're still there I guess they don't
need to turn yet free I wonder
iford probably has more reach but
there's only a wooden
sword axe breaks
[Music]
Shield let's see maybe
more four that's that's four I
guess okay okay let's see what the
question now the big the big moment the
big
moment I mean they may have already
heard it because we were in public VC
when we talked about that in the back
[Music]
yeah maybe they maybe uh you know I
don't really care it's
fine N I think it's okay yeah it's fine
come on come on do it do it
come
two three how
she did my mistake she did my
mistake oh no I they I think they should
say that's okay that's my personal
opinion but whatever oh I know I do
agree I wanted to go further like I am I
I knew what I was supposed to
do like I could go further if I
definitely everybody definitely could
even iOS could for sure they got the E
sort
connection
yes like everybody's making the same
mistake almost everybody mhm
damn well I wouldn't I wouldn't call it
a mistake though yeah maybe my way of
thinking is wrong but it seems like
several people's way of thinking is
wrong we're we're having a different
brain moments I think it's just like bu
differently it's just like I think um
the schedule of
Holo ID cup is so tough you know and a
lot of things happening so I feel like
even during practice we were still like
um testing stuff so I think it's very I
me when I was practicing and they were
like kitty Kanan I was also turning like
quite drastically but nothing and uh
nobody and then we didn't do any like
right turn right right after turning
left you know so it was less
noticeable yeah possibly yeah yeah
you're right build and get k also did
the same I wasn't just crony I I just
watched uh crony but I did it correctly
because oh wait sure oh okay yeah you
made it you made
it okay okay I'll do my best let me you
are are outside okay I'm going to
KY oh yeah you're not the only ones who
did that how many rounds we have yeah
because I was pretty confused right
because the that one and then I was like
stopping here and then I was like yeah
so like if you turn right which is it
reset position right yeah because it's
like a reset position so is this front
or is this right to them okay maybe the
default here and then so I turn turn
right one more yeah I just thought it
doesn't matter as long as I turn right
toing there a bit yeah also did the same
mistake too wait wait what was
it they made they made us turn right
after turning left right you need to
turn right so you have to so the correct
answer is apparently to turn 45 instead
of when you turn 180 or 90 90 90 0 but a
lot of people turned 90 which is
technically it's supposed to be fine but
apparently it wasn't you know yeah we
turned the same my group and you we did
the all we both we the three of us did
the same thing but it's fine oh okay cuz
like we we think we're turning right so
we were doing in our head we were doing
the same the right thing but we went too
far and that's oh I'm just I'm just
relieved that you know like I I didn't
mess us up cuz I was like I thought did
they explain it 25 no it didn't no you
did good good job sorry oh yeah sorry
like uh 45 sorry I got it confused but
anyways yeah good job turn 180 or turn
90 sorry 90 is correct we did sorry
sorry yeah my mistake my mistake confus
confused about
it okay how's it going over there with K
last right okay let's let's watch them
let's go yeah yeah let's go watch them
let's see if they get if they but they
hear us when we're in outside here so
maybe yeah we Hush
Hush yeah I'm I'm not going to lie it
did feel a little bit like a trick
question thing but I don't really care
here
because uh three groups got the same
mistake so I feel like it's not an um
it's nothing to be worried about or I
need I don't need to think about it so
hard going to
VC hi hi now we can talk okay now we can
talk yeah she probably needed something
to throw
mhm I don't know what's going on
they're
Whispering was training Canada really
hard like they're in the military so oh
nice what why Ena why Ena of the
mountain why what's Ena doing she pushed
me down hey that's evil or was it Ana
because she hates me you never know you
don't have eyes in your back ha each
other guys no we love each other but we
hate each other love hate all the same
if you know play oh Kitty oh she looked
left and she oh can it look
90 180 instead
90 I saw it I saw it so another group
who made another another group falling
victim to the
90 yeah
ah at at least we're not the only ones
that makes me feel better yeah yeah that
makes me feel much
better okay maybe leave uh VC again I
guess okay okay hi hi Jo VC
B it's so over it's so over it's so
over it's so over we hate angles we only
love angels I know I hate angles angles
I could be your angle or your devil
yeah no can you be my angel not my angle
no I would need to die to do that man
I'm just a
Burber man oh man SK wasn't for that ski
man five so many so many fives in this
house salmon games is finished yay yay
wo
building guest building guest oh my God
I am I am going to be I am so ready to
be a
[Music]
disappointment should we just build
should we just build from um don't
confuse me with your mask what the hell
oh sorry oh [\h__\h] I
forgot downstairs like wa is talking to
me but I see Ana's face follow me please
hi
come on come
on downstairs come on let's go
downstairs let's go downstairs
downstairs if you said that with Ana
voice then I would have really Fallen
downstairs why is
everyone I wasn't trying to cop here
[Music]
yeah no pushing pushing
pushing pushing push is um my
atama pussing yeah it's kind of like
you're dizzy pussing pussing yeah
pussing you know in in German in German
booy is like a
little yeah a little a little CH a
little little um like kiss on your cheek
oh okay I love
buoy pussing from too much booy yeah
pussing from too much booy really
too busy getting the booy
[Music]
one I can't see you too
short yes we
area here what
[Music]
we have to write it
down
yeah so people don't scream and they're
like o but like well you will probably
explain this anyway but like does that
mean that everybody gets the same amount
time how how do you write this yeah
everybody gets 1 minute I'm so stupid I
thought you needed a we're doing it at
the same time it doesn't matter if we
get it after 10 seconds or after 1
minute have anything right yeah because
we'll wait for 1 minute anyway okay okay
guys how do you write this without uh
without the
book you just open it right
click yeah I changed it I
guess I think we have to decide on one
guess we can't write sever yeah you have
to but then you can't that's that's
quite different from yesterday though
because like yesterday I knew that if
you if there was no ding ding ding ding
that my answer was wrong and I could
continue you answering answering
answering now I have to think of one
answer and decide on it and it could be
wrong though it could be
wrong ask you right you can I mean in
the practice I mean obviously you can't
ask
me one by one please go to all VC go
to
Hello what is
up be explain the rules now okay
okay so everybody has uh 1 minute each
and we will be starting at the same
time how how do you say it
inese oh sorry sorry sorry
[Music]
so for the builders you guys will go to
the corner over
here and you guys will see the theme for
yourselves so we made a room over here
and then you guys will come in and see
it
at the very Corner yeah don't don't come
in yet don't come in yet okay so this is
like secret room
I so these are all to prevent anyone
from cheating M
okay so when you know the answer do not
scream it
out please write it books okay okay now
for the builders please um come to the
uh
corner
[Music]
I'm do not turn the page okay p uh
turn oh and chat please don't spoil the
like what you see in the
[Music]
builders
only only only only only press like the
right okay there you go go ahead okay
and I guess when we're building it's
best to mute
right
okay round one one yeah
okay maybe the guessers shouldn't look
at
[Music]
chat yeah
that's can I build
or um um also I it's a better
I got the book wait did you guys both
already saw
I answering
right
no do you how to the ansers in the book
have a
question okay
okay sorry guys I think we'll have to
change the theme because they both
look I accidentally signed it it was
looking we have to
[Music]
decide okay attention
please build no no
no
build okay
I cannot build okay
Builder is this all of the builders for
the non-b builders please stay in your
lanes yeah please stay in your spaces so
that we can um monitor you guys yeah
[Music]
yeah monkey
not's voice just overlaps and I really
can't like listen to it I get so like
sick medically like feeling SI
answer I thought the proximity was good
so I feel like people should just like
Gather in an actual place rather
than getting so scattered you
[Music]
like every BS right wait SOA do I have
to sign the book and then put it over
it's obviously just one
guess this
[Music]
is okay just want to in the book okay
okay um okay so yeah so the thing is um
I think like person personally an all
group chat is good but only like please
um it's kind of like during like the
past Discord stuff like everybody mutes
them and the all chat is only to explain
the rules otherwise it's better to use
like the whole proximity chat and just
like Hey Hey listen up go here so that
it's not so everything's not in your
ears you
know because that's kind of like lowkey
the point of proximity I feel like Oli
should have like told everyone to like
shut up and listen to the rules and then
okay afterwards kaan you know and people
can reply I think that would be like way
[Music]
nicer
okay run
one it's it's the time but also like um
it's you know it's like our first time
doing something like this so I think
there's uh a lot of things to learn and
I feel like next year um we will be much
more like experienced with this because
like honestly during
practice it wasn't like it was just like
few people few people right and then
people were like not talking at the same
time so I feel like um nobody really
expected it so yeah I feel like next
time you know it could be nice a okay
okay
okay okay
[Music]
the prom not
yet theom is here round one
okay already
see okay okay
okay okay okay
okay okay
Z okay yeah okay getting
[Music]
K okay okay you
can I couldn't hear your
voice um I'll I'll I'll face this way
then okay yeah I
[Music]
guess bu over
there is that I don't know
they're doing it they they
have I appreciate it
R okay is everybody
[Music]
ready group chat I'm going to have a
voice group chat so we cannot watch so
from thec group chat okay
okay
Ka proximity only or should we have a
group uh but we're not super is fine I
guess let's just a
group oh okay that works too I'm going
to build from on the floor because it's
like more surface area and it's F too
okay I'm make a
group why do I call it papi know okay
it's supposed to be mass destruction but
you know what I okay I'll I'll build
from here so there's like more
surface so you should look from here I
it's okay I'm uh I'm looking from up
here from The Vines I have a good view
okay but basically I can also see what
the others are building so I guess
everybody has the same prompt so I'm
going
to I'm guessing cuz I mean I'll probably
oh well I guess I can do it like this
too be able to
tell count
it okay well I I think text is better
definitely everybody can see it take
your time with building by the way I
think you should build like uh as much
as you can in that one minute don't
don't just like try to build fast
because it's not about time anyway
anymore okay okay you goody you
goody go
[Music]
oh they're all very these ones are all
similar oh
aha well I mean that could be anything
so far
[Music]
I mean could be anything any kind of
anal
animal
[Music]
yeah how much time do we have what
already it's
over one minute everybody did the same
thing that's so [\h__\h] funny
what what
what wait she they're still building
wait there's wait somebody still
building yeah so Z is still changing
things and Ena is still changing
things
answer Yoda then I'll change stuff too
if people are changing stuff yeah it's
fair that
way yeah Z also changing more yeah Z if
are they getting rid of it oh they're
getting rid of it never mind well I
don't know it's some
animal
awesome okay yeah just write the answer
I I can't say yes I can't say no put it
[Music]
here oh I don't
know that could be any animal first I
thought it was a
alligator she so un help me okay okay
okay okay but there's like no way there
would make an alligator it's got to be
simple
[Music]
words what did she
write oh my God take I me it could be
anything why are you laughing no it's
okay I like
[Music]
it well all answer checked anyway so
it's not changing anything did you
happen to see the other the other people
build yeah they're drawing the exact
same thing right I kind of saw yeah the
ones next to you pretty much built the
same thing
well since they check the answer I think
it's I it's fine to tell you it's a car
Kiara oh no a
car not all voice yet I thought there
was a tail and eyes the the holes look
like eyes you're just animal brain then
it's fine sometimes it be like that I'm
also animal brain so and also some parts
looked like ears but then like for the
others too and then they got rid of it
and you also I feel like you also got
rid of it but I think there were ears
first it's like the you know some like
SUV
car damn it but I now that I know it I
feel like I get it yeah right but get
rid of the book that's what building
gets
wow
wow what how do I get a take book
okay
[Music]
wow damn next
round maybe should I change my strategy
maybe I shouldn't build no no it's okay
it's okay don't worry I think you're
doing well okay okay but think of what I
what else I could think of and how you
could prevent me of thinking of those
things that's um that's a little
bit especially cuz oo is k i you know
yeah okay like like if you give it
Windows you know it looks like ice to me
but it's probably not going to be a car
again so we'll see we'll see yeah
because there's not enough block to a
different shape okay I'll do this I I'll
read
again ah now I see they were building
like upwards maybe because they wanted
to do three dimensional like an actual
car but that would that one minute one
minute as we now know is way too little
not as long as we thought
so Shear shears okay well I'm going to I
might try building three di yeah but but
but you know how how short the one
minute just was I don't know if you can
build three dimensional like at least
you can build flat dimens F on round
Wheels if there's not even enough pixel
to draw round wheels on what the
[\h__\h] we can't have shears cuz like I
don't yeah e you can you
can you can change colors and color
shouldn't affect so it's tough do you
mean do you mean you want to build yeah
I think I want to build upwards yeah
upwards should be fine but like 3D like
having it be you know friend shaped
that's difficult I'm going to give it a
try I don't
know but just be you know wary of the
time because not as long as I thought I
don't know how I'm even going to build
this on the ground that's the problem
okay don't worry you can do it it's all
about my brain I'm going to getting a
migraine ping
ping sorry sorry sorry
okay don't fall down
okay all right oh no
well they
start mhm
[Music]
mhm that looks like the thing from
before not what you're doing R the other
ones oh every oh oh they all want to oh
ah there is no way there is no
way they wouldn't do that right I don't
know okay let's see
hard it's so tough I can't no there's no
way I can't this is the only thing I can
do I I I I'm thinking of something but I
can't believe they would build something
this looks like a
Bora another Temple it seems
wow it looks like B to
me I don't know I can't say anything
what the
[\h__\h] but wouldn't they go for easier
wordss that looks I don't know did it
have I feel like it have one
top okay or it's um a plug
could be n that doesn't look like a plug
over
there wait wait wait wait wait
wait but see the way I know if I'm doing
right if I'm doing good or not is like
I'm seeing everybody built and they're
building something pretty similar to I
don't know how to write it
but cuz there's no other way
honestly I feel like it had only one
thing sticking up I don't [\h__\h] know
for the answer what is wait wait I know
you guys no I want to change I want to
change no what what if it's a cake no n
it doesn't look
[Music]
like okay okay she didn't laugh this
time re didn't laugh laugh at my answer
re didn't laugh at my answer okay
but I can't believe that it would be
such a difficult word but that's all I
can think of yeah like there's no way
it's that maybe they do it because ID
you
know oh only
K but there looks very different
[Music]
too I did F cake at the end but your
candles look like you know they make no
sense to me why wouldn't they be more
aligned like but that one over there
looked like a cake after you know I
thought about didn't I say it out loud
for a moment when I wanted to change it
oh my God yeah the cake makes so much
more
sense cuz it's a simple word yeah
they're always simple words and it's
like ah but why was it separated
over damn damn it obviously it's not but
I you know I thought maybe you know ID
respect you know ID
respect oh my God you're you're thinking
so much you're overthinking because you
love the ID B so much right yeah we're
in here you know we're celebrating ID
you know can you clean up for me um
please thank
you cuz they're making me no or and
[Music]
then the cake in
the believe in
yourself okay something difficult
sounding maybe simple word but difficult
to build plus 1,000 aura awesome believe
in me oh yeah M I feel like there's like
also a lot of bias with the color even
though they said like the color k but it
helps the people think if it's like the
same color can I change colors nope I
can't I'm we're stuck with blue this
thing is definitely not going to
help okay hi right hey what's
up she can't hear you oh yeah I think
she just wants to know if you saw the
theme yes
I what is
that shears oh
okay
hope there you
go start
in Kiara I'm probably going to find it
up it's okay I'm going to uh I'm
building
um oh freak I don't
know I don't know how I'm how I should
do this
oh I mean that looks like
[Music]
this looks like an
egg this also looks like an
egg this is a 3D
[Music]
attempted please I'm I'm hoping I know I
know I think I know but when I look at
the others it makes me doubt myself like
what are day
making please
this is the best I can
do no I can't no don't say over what the
hell what are they building do trust me
trust me this is the best what are they
this is the best I can do really this is
the best I can do what is that what that
confuses
me because there's no other way to build
this in one minute I
mean I'm sorry Raina that looks like a
Christmas tree to me an egg look at the
Symmetry though but you know I I'm not
supposed to say this but it's I mean
it's just too hard I
[Music]
think stop dissing our art it's a
Christmas tree that one too that's the
decorations here same as there and it's
like well there theirs are symmetrical
mine isn't
there's a symmetrical use
isn't why I mean trees are not always
super symmetrical I guess so I'm going
to I'm going to I'm going to look at the
others oh is it we we are
struggling everybody is
struggling cheese wait is it cheese I
don't know but then why do they look
such [\h__\h] Christmas tree I think is
pretty simple cheese as Fair cheese is a
fair guess cheese is fair yeah cheese is
a fair guess because I get where and
pizza what about pizza is a fair guess
also but I can't change it anymore right
well I'm just I'm not saying it's right
I'm saying it's a fair guess oh yeah
they already checked
it I was fing pizza too yeah watermelon
oh my God that's
why but
like I wish we could choose our colors I
wish we could choose our colors honestly
because even even though color doesn't
make sense it kind of gives you the bias
yeah melon
watermelon and probably did a good job
too but their blocks were
red uh so I think like it's just a brain
thing you know nobody's cheating or
anything but it's a brain thing even
though they say EO night
M yeah yeah yeah cuz if someone's
building with yellow I would 100% think
of cheese like swiss cheese even though
they say color doesn't
matter
yeah everyone should build with
gray fair right yeah it's okay it's okay
like I'm sorry way I'm so useless right
now it's okay it's not your fault I'll
I'll think of but watermelon watermelon
isn't simple isn't that simple it's not
even a simple
word it's okay it's not your fault it's
it's really hard I would find difficulty
guessing I'm so sorry like every like
you know everybody's building the same
thing and not everybody able to guess
either ready
yeah oh no I don't know how to do this
I'll try my best though I'm going to
build
horizontally did you already see it yeah
I did okay
it's not that I mean pixel art is tough
yes
but the conditions are hard it's fun
though I like
building come
back no after this is there a oh sh sh
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry I
always accidentally press okay don't
don't stress let's go
[Music]
what
ah why is theirs
roundish and yours is like flat on the
bottom
like that's red so it makes me think of
a cherry over there
but this doesn't look like a
cherry there's probably there's probably
a reason for that if one and tree looks
like a cherry and the others
don't yeah because it's not a cherry
that looks
like that looks like an Al sorry sorry
sorry actually that looks awesome
ah is this just making it pretty
but is it but that could be a lot of
things it could be potion it could be
bottle maybe more but it could be a lot
of things so even if you get it wrong
it's not your fault maybe bottle because
like that is square and that's if if it
was a
potion I'm I'm going to mute
myself um um um uh wait um
what um I'm not giving up on 3D builds
it's like um some stuff are better
with thing that could be
more way the the only oh my God the only
way she should have
overthought the only way she should have
overthought oh my God I don't know I
don't know I don't know I don't know I
don't know I mean the potions are in a
bottle
so over think harder both there's Potion
bottles there's bottles yeah yeah put
both put both sh I muted by the way I
put M there bottles where there's potion
in and there's potions that are in
bottles but there's no WR both WR both
WR both there's not always a potion in a
bottle WR both like like just write
potion bottle or whatever please please
please please I beg you she's still
laughing what I've been M I've been
muted by the way so it's fair I I'm
talking to chat [\h__\h]
oh my God oh my God I beg you clutch
this no
[Music]
no is that
wrong wrong we were so close we were so
close to
Greatness bro she would she would be so
pissed once she hears the answer she
would be so
pissed hi what is up wa
oh no oh
[Music]
no was it po no no you know but it's the
same thing told you she would lose her
[\h__\h] it's okay because we love each
other Lena what we switch yeah oh oh no
I thought I was I thought that was
choice no here here here I'm going to
give you the the thing
oh no I'm going to do worse than now oh
shoot I'm going to do so bad because
especially cuz from this angle I can't
really see how the others are building
it that way see kind I I I I didn't see
at all I I was just tting my gut it was
just that apparently they're building
the same thing as me once I
finished one minute is too short I I
have the book no I don't have it oh
shoot um well wait can I just use this
book
you delete what what I wrote oh no oh
there can canot sorry can you take it
can you can you take this please wow wow
so I can put my book ah
okay I can't write how do I write take
book oh oh take book and then write and
then put in the lecture okay I wait I
didn't see that wait I didn't see the
wait I didn't see the pr
I didn't see I didn't [\h__\h] see the
pro what the
[\h__\h] that was too fast I was dealing
with your
book uh you know what I don't know it's
okay we can do the same
prompt just give me one minute can I
start I don't
know oh go on okay but then how
much okay did she even see I don't you
know what I don't know it's
fine you can wait
okay this one is Rally kind of like
impossible did I say it out loud by
accident I didn't right no you didn't
you didn't say anything okay maybe
I think it's like switching you know
once it's
ah a little
bit can't reach it I think I'm going to
mute myself so it's
fair honestly I think I'm going to do a
Kiara move and say this is an
animal maybe
let's like so like this like it's a
lizard or it's a crocodile how that look
guys I don't know
man if it's a crocodile she should make
it uh the Tails and everything longer
but I think like there's no much
building
space that's I okay that's I me I mean
wait consider what the others are
building too right oh Oh that's oh
that's
good we should say something outrageous
but that looks like I have no idea what
that thing is over there on the left
side the right side is
good what is
that what is that I don't know how do I
I think that's okay this is that part no
hold on this is that part mhm okay we
put
it oh did you ride it already waa I did
I don't know though let's
see m
I I think since you already wrote it and
they already saw it I can already talk
about it I guess so yeah yeah so as long
as alligator and crocodile is the same
then should be fine okay okay okay I was
going to I was going to be I was going
to like I forgot the tick tac that's a
good idea from Orange side I was going
to I was going to troll you and say oh
that's a really nice shopping bag or
something could honestly while I was
building it I was thinking of a dolphin
because like the the
the blue makes me think of dolphins blue
yeah but I just try really hard not to
let it affect me you know yeah yeah uh
it's like when you I thought it was like
some sort of car and then you added the
four legs yeah yeah the legs were cute
right yeah they stuck out to the side
because they have like side out sticking
legs kind of the blue made me think like
a think of a dolphin at first yeah it's
probably not a dolphin yeah because you
didn't draw the fins or something yeah
yeah it's never the first thing you
think of maybe I don't know no I
actually thought of a lizard first and I
was like actually look again do they
have a new one uh I don't think so they
haven't they haven't announced it yet
okay okay oh
okay we should we should just destroy
everything before Ru passes by so she
doesn't diss our
builds rnie how did you know by that d
damn yeah that thing that was funny but
it's the it's the head it was the head
you just have to look at it that way but
I feel like this this one if you look
look at that then and after uh and after
the answer is announced just go straight
to see the next prompt so you don't
forget got you got you thank
you could have also been a dinosaur
skull yeah but I just thought I don't
know I I wanted to write house gecko or
chichak but I house Geo but it I F
remember the house gecko we saw when we
had dinner we saw many geckos I love
geckos
Geck but that's also too simple too
difficult I mean gecko gecko is is like
more Niche I
guess still no no score no score yet
apparently
they haven't announced it no wor wait
there's green here were we supposed to
build with
green what do you mean there's green
wool in our hello maybe we're supposed
to build a
green I am was there someone else
building with green
I'm
hungry Zeta looks like me I'm not going
to lie a little bit it's the the gray
hair yeah and you wearing the same
clothes
yeah y y yeah finally sorry Raina that
we didn't get anything
until I'm sorry it's fine take book and
then I'm going to erase oh [\h__\h] take
book again also I wasn't laughing at
their answer like but like for what they
had I think bug would have maybe been my
answer too is that the last round I
don't
know I only Built one I've only Built
once one more round one more
round oh what I I don't know I don't
know where
my where's my box oh there we
go yeah see the promp see the promp
don't forget don't forget
okay I think I know how to do it okay
okay W one p I think I know how to do it
w what you're okay I'm I'm building
right no I'm building huh why I only
Built once you we four times or
something oh sorry I oh my God I forgot
go block so oh never mind okay never
mind oh my god oh yeah
yeah my head that's why I didn't have
any wool you didn't you didn't look at
The Prompt right no no no I didn't okay
I was just like yeah never mind never
mind never
mind okay I I know it's so confusing has
anybody seen the book not me has
everybody seen the book not W you see
the prom
right uh well why you should see the
prompt right wait did I
take bro what is going on that's what
you meant
Chad I took it like all
atically I thought you meant you have
the book as and I have Way's
book
oh
okay I thought you meant to have Way's
book bro
OHA is everybody ready ready I hope you
guys are ready we are ready are ready
I'm ready I am fing once again oh my God
I am hunger
[Music]
copyight I have a
goodidea wait wait stop okay focus
[Music]
focus should I not
sing I'm so
hungry 3D
what is
that middle
finger in my brain it's like what the
[\h__\h] in my
[\h__\h] wait wait wait it look like
snail yeah look like look like snail
wait wait wait um
[\h__\h] um I forgot to put it what the [\h__\h]
bro
Mar ignore the thing
[Music]
obiously I can actually kind of see
it this is not a thumbs up this is not a
thumbs up like that
what the
huh looks like a snail but I it's
probably not a snail I
mean I mean you know and you know no I
don't you know no I
don't what is
this you
know you know no I don't you
know you know
you know I'm like I'm like looking at
the I'm going to look at the others I'm
looking at the others and uh it's very
hard to understand too so I think it's
fine but I don't think it's a I don't
think it's a snail she would draw it
differently if it was a snail what could
it be thumbs
up like to
go you know what it's I'm going to I'm
going to oh I'm going to okay I'm going
no it's not a
oh wait what are you thinking I'm going
to I know it's not a snail but what you
I know I know it's not a
snail I know it's not a snail but camel
why are there so many camels I know it's
not a snail but God
damn I don't
know oh my God there's no hints
okay I S even that I will
write
[Laughter]
um up
I mean you always see it like
differently I I I I know that's not the
answer but I really don't know what to
WR
so I'm just not
seeing
it I said is that like is it
like is it like
you know what Kobo did did they spell it
out they spell it out they spelled the
SP hint word but is that the
r the whole thing wait you already put
it in right I already put it
in wa uh what oh H sorry sorry
hello I put it in I put the answer in Ru
already checked my answer what is that
thumbs up yeah I know that's not it but
I just uh I know that's not it but I I
just wrote whatever yeah and if you see
cobos and if you see coobo Team well
there's no rules against it but they
just straight she just straight up
that's why they got points in every
round I don't no I don't know I didn't
see but uh it's just for this round I
looked over
there isn't
using isn't using words cheating Butch
they doing over there look so weird
cheating because there's no rules
against it technically I was wondering
in between though if we were if we would
be allowed to do that and then I thought
ah no way we should well yeah I don't
know whatever I don't think I don't
think we should it kind of it doesn't
make it fun you know cuz like cat you
can just ride c a pretty easily on the
small field yeah whatever it's fine
let's
[Music]
go cool I think I need to uh punish her
you need to you need to SP punish my
child for that kind of
play please get your emeralds in the
chest so we got what
one why
five eh why there five so I just take
five I think it's the total so far from
also the the game um from before maybe h
I got
mine oh I don't have
mine oh I don't know well then I'll just
take mine oh so you have five have okay
okay join all please I don't know it's
probably fine I'll yeah it's whatever if
they put five then m
[Music]
m okay everyone
de mute mute okay yeah yeah mute mute
everyone mute
uh that D okay okay everyone thank you
so much uh for playing this game we move
to the next game yay yeah I think it's a
wrong wo so we have three minutes it's
the top bottom game to play with teams
and every each round got five Emerald
there will be like three rounds so let's
go to the to the wrong together shall we
come on come here come here follow us
let's
go let's go
[Music]
we can't even talk to our teammates I
think first uh you guys need to
uh you know click the the bed just in
case so you won't spawning outside
again but like
[Music]
we're not going to do this yet not yet
not
yet is Ax better than sword why is it
expensive come on up
here everyone
come
on so is for for me I'm an experienced
right Crouch not
[Music]
for
so uh can we explain okay okay there
will be three rounds in total it three
round and there will be no
[Music]
switching it's a battle royale
basically we're not going by groups
we're not going uh solo everybody's
going at the same time no switch and for
the wool Cutters you are
um you are to press F1 when you want to
play the game yeah okay and for the
foreman you cannot Crouch
[Music]
okay wait wait wait wait if if if
hitting is allowed then is eating also
allowed or like what if you die and not
fall I guess you're also hitting is only
for like you know make people fall don't
don't kill people you're not allowed to
kill you can hit but you don't
kill but what if like you've been hit so
many times you're about to die from uh
just not eating I think I I there is
food there there is food outside uh in
the upper there in the middle so you can
put in here too I think you won't die
person in here like unless like you get
we're going to distribute the
color what do you
[Music]
please can join I have another uh event
I will change kobo's place for this
round okay oh yeah okay I will take my
leaf now thank you okay thank
you okay
byebye
bye-bye sh sh and the purple box cheers
here cheers here Che here you can take
right okay
that
[Music]
time I took three
hi hi hi okay
[Music]
okay um for all the foreman can I can I
see what your color is okay crony is
yellow is green wait are we a sign color
is
pink yeah
where's the others is no
one okay which color
[Music]
not
wait what color is not taken there is no
orange do you take two or three
shears can only Brown pink
green yellow blue and red because that
is the obvious color
okay uh yeah it's so that you guys
requested you guys didn't want like uh
colors that are to close to each other
we won even like use one fully I think
so yeah they said I think they took my
you know wa was thingy because some
colors are for the foran for the foran
who already has their color should we
have a green can
we go
upstairs for the foreman who has taken
their colors please go upstairs because
it'll be easier for us to
monitor Brown yeah I'm Brown cuz Okay
Okay Okay blue is not okay okay gotcha
gotcha you guys can go
inside right here so green pink and
yellow is out green pink yellow and red
okay let's go with orange again I have
brown there is no Orange has
brown has yellow red green and pink is
already out so the left one is brown
brown okay Ena Brown I'm in
blue okay now go up please wait how many
stacks can we take sorry two please two
oh oh only two two should be enough two
or three is okay okay I brought a lot
I'll bring some
down okay but I think that's
everyone
okay I'm going to say it again
okay uh is everyone here one two three
are we are we just going to use all VC
or what putting my stacks of will Ka VC
V
Ka VC Ka going to stop using the all VC
so proximity
proximity
okay okay okay
proximity wait hold on do we do we
create a group no no right no no just no
need to create no need to create a gr
yeah don't forget to F1 for the lower L
good luck okay I'm
won proximity right
God
speed if you fall please let me know
that yeah if if fall immediately please
[Music]
report I think like even if I fall down
you can still keep using the shears
I okay okay
okay F1
F1 focus on not falling
down Gladiator
match I don't even know where my friend
is peacefully guys up here how that
there's no option for
[Music]
full Focus H go where are the
holes what
[Music]
the who fell who fell
go who
fell please say your name
[Music]
it's okay we did our best we
try two more
[Music]
minutes out out
[Laughter]
don't
know still continuing still
[Applause]
continu no what happened
what
okay is it the color counted though or
is it last one last one standing
standing if if everybody died then the
last one standing doesn't matter if you
place
BL but if everybody survives then we'll
[Applause]
[Music]
the I stop placing only two
people I believe in
you should I do that
hi that's rough
unless there's a time limit
right minutes slurp slurp it's quite
Cal it's okay I'll be more careful next
time on
rounds of this yeah you need to take
more oh so many blocks okay um I took
two is that not enough Al perspective
colors pleas howal is
this should be like 10
[Music]
we
not
[Music]
go don't forget to take more stacks
okay okay
nice oh okay okay going try a bit faster
yeah um yeah cuz otherwise K has
something after this okay
has something like this something after
that is very
important everyone already in and
they're on a time crunch
everyone yeah uh you're so
[Music]
ready I have
take it down okay oh I checked DMs I
have replied
okay three two one
go yeah the thing is the four men they
cannot they cannot
see oh my God oh my God oh my God okay
oh my God they cannot see oh my God oh
my God wait what color are brown
[Music]
one more
minute no not
[Music]
yet
no wait Who's down I don't even know
who's
down I think cuz I was
like I'm not going to focus on making
people fall because it might um a
[\h__\h] oops shoot I sorry I destroyed my
own team's
block you still up you weren't the
[Music]
only lot of
brown yeah that's
not there's a lot of brown
yeah I don't know I'm bad
at I destroy a lot of their
colors the thing is I don't know who's
down like I feel like most did they
mention
this green is 24 don't touch staff I I'm
not oh maybe somebody hit staff 24 pink
brown
right yeah two three I'm counting Brown
four five six
seven bro I got punched so many times I
was like a
volleyball so many
yellow we're looking
good 32
34 35 36 37 38 39 40 41 42 4 44
44 there's so many yellows
[Music]
though so what what does it say what did
they
say brown win a lot of blocks so Brown
wins okay let yeah I think it's it's
just better for me to mute myself I
absolutely have nothing to say put them
back one more
round
okay okay I'm going to take oh maybe
wait I can take I
[Music]
have to leave for the final game so I I
would tell you if I fell okay okay okay
right T why why yellow it's not it's
okay it's okay what why yellow what it
was
fun
what I didn't fall why are
yellow oh I think it's because they're
trying to get through fast
soed about the people who have like
schedule after
[Music]
this and I think um the game is going
longer than the supposedly expected
time thank you but um I hope it will
turn out well because I think we also
have like schedule after this
right ah
[Music]
no explanation
necessary and also I'm uh I'm I'm just
muting because I feel like if I really
have nothing useful to say and I unmute
it's just like adding noise to the you
know I think like we're pro using
proximity which is like not that big of
a deal but also people are like around
and it's just like I'm hearing noise and
it's just like it has nothing to do with
with the actual thing and it gets a
little bit overwhelming for me so I'm
just going to you know myself so I don't
the I got to the
corner oh F1 oops oh yeah F1
please1 please guys I'm sorry but if we
f one and you only say 3 2 1 go in the
chat we can't see it okay count
down 5 four three 2
1 I'm going to harass the other
[Applause]
te
was oh shoot oh T fell fell fell
no need to be so
violent just my crony already fell or
what 1
minute huh she shouldn't worry about
where I am so hard
Mouse oop sorry [\h__\h] I did it again
number one
fire no it's okay it's
okay
myle I kind of I kind of
expected
nice nice nice nice n nice nice I think
people should really like say their name
when they fall
because did k
I think honestly like people should
really really say their name because I
can't just nobody people can't recognize
my voice alone in like such a group
[Music]
setting survivors
are this one is
Fun the foreman has no idea who falls
they have to keep looking up
and it would be such a waste if um you
know somebody already fell and they
destroy the blocks of the Fallen person
anyway it's like so much
wasted there's a lot of ways to like um
improve the game play like the the base
game is really really solid I think we
can definitely use this next year too
but next year because we already tried
it it will definitely be like better in
you know the organization and rules
aspects
was did you kill me
again this is such a big project and
like such a huge
time
wow game G
[Music]
here wa so we only have 10 or something
it's okay it's okay no I'm just saying
we should uh strategically shop sorry
what were you about to say I was just
going to say sorry I didn't win I really
tried and I
think yeah I think I stayed pretty long
in each match but at the end yeah you
know it's it's like a different rule so
it's not not your fault you did very
[Music]
well it's fine it's fine okay 27 so
should we do should we do group uh
should we do group chat uh wait you can
take my emeralds right to buy stuff yeah
that's why I want to budget
our okay it's hard because
[Music]
because you like are you are you good at
shooting because it's kind of like we
only have 10 and B one bow and 10 arrows
is already nine I'm just like I thought
was free I thought that was free
everyone you have a free time everyone
is shopping right
now yeah I'm just like what should I
do we can only really
for one of
us how much is
aord um I could use 20 arrows I feel
like The
Arrow we have then my RO is actually
kind of meaningless I'm not going to let
way go out there it's so
expensive okay you buy your weapons and
I only navigate and I try to not get hit
by the other receiver
I only and try to tell you where Premier
wasn't oh my
God okay so we can rather
do and
then we have to get a
no was free I thought so too like I I
thought so too like I'm going to be
honest because the Navigator's job is
like to shoot people and like they can't
even pass they can't even see past like
I don't know but to be honest me
shooting people could go wrong like I
shot Ollie in the practice when she was
with me in a team so I could
accidentally shoot you too and then you
know oh [\h__\h] am I on yet you should be
at least able to protect
yourself I
guess yeah you should have something to
like fight because even if the Navigator
dies I think the fighter if if the
fighter is still alive the battle
continues so it's more important that
you stay alive okay well you're just
going to watch I guess
you need the weapons you need the
weapons more get whatever you want baby
I'm your sugar mama all
[Laughter]
[Music]
right stone
stone so should I just get the stone axe
cuz there's I can't get a Shield either
I can't get a
shield no armor by the way is just
Shield so take a while to buy for
everyone
[Music]
to is it somebody took the shield here
here somebody took the shield what do
you mean
[Music]
a shield which one is better a shield
and no wouldn't S no it doesn't fit it
doesn't fit it's not enough you guys
math isad worse than
[Laughter]
mine
just is this the first round
ERS hopefully
this yeah so
um I
want how do
iow like
[Music]
groupone
please
okay Stone a on
much
okay thank
you to have more time
hopefully not you get rather
get as your
[Music]
partner myf
yeah yeah yeah okay show we uh
okay um helloa
here helloa wait what go to
the
okay FEC the shopping FEC oh the
I wonder if anyone bought like bows
and oh yeah for you guys right like easy
have money
toy okay okay okay
don't what about
food are they going to give us food
[Music]
is there is there a
St
hello ah wait wait wait our strategy
should be you hide I tell you where you
can go to hide and then you let them
destroy each other yeah we have to be
cowards today yeah you hide until
there's maybe just one person left on
the field I tell you where they are and
I'll tell you if they're coming for you
or
so are you aware of the colors and the
arrangement of the colors of the field
like can you tell me I know first is red
first is red yeah pink is next to Red
besides that I don't know ah next to
Pink is purple oh sorry so next to is
like right or left I can't well try to
get on the tower and like hold on give
me give me a second I I need to
eat they said they're going to give us
food but so we don't need Oh you mean
real
food Minecraft food
but um
oopsie I'm going to see is this our can
we be in this Tower I think so we're
just going to clim it so red and then
clockwise red pink purple pink purple
don't know what there is but then
there's gray next to Red on the right
side know and
then afterward is oh me look over there
let me check what's next to gray we
don't have OptiFine I hope nobody here
has OptiFine or else they have like a oh
that's like red that's like kylo red
after
gray order is the order is um Ali and
then like Aria 15 on the left and then
Holo is like in the middle-ish and but I
don't know those H blue there's like a
nice blue next to Kyla red like blue
that's uh that's Kobo blue I know Kobo
blue is probably on the right I'm just
guessing and then besides Kobo blue I
think it's definitely mine ah yeah
there's another blue yeah and then I
know I know the order yes I know the
order and then there's lime green right
is that GRE lime green that's E's color
so it's basically uh on the left it's
ARA 15 on the middle is Holo when on the
right if you go over there I I won't
even be able to see you so I shouldn't
go to green right depending on where our
Tower is though but yeah where they put
us okay but I
know I know
yeah which to should we all go I
I I can probably only really navigate
you in the colors that are closest to
the tower yeah it's
fine
yeah but if I see someone in in pink and
you're in pink I say run run to purple
if purple is empty but yeah let's see
what chat what's what's next
to do you know the arrow I know I know
by heart but it's it's um it's confusing
if I if you if I tell you like what's
next to something next to something so
it's like a 3X3 and like left center
right from left from left top to bottom
is GRE lime green and then what we
should yeah when whenever I say left or
right we should decide at least that
it's like left when you look at the
center of the field right um you know if
I say left I mean left to the like no
that's confusing because I we'll turn
around just say um go closer to purple
or something and then if I go the wrong
way you can just say no the other way
okay okay it's going to be chaotic but
um otherwise it doesn't
[Music]
work the blue Tower because there's blue
Towers I don't know if the field is blue
in front of
it I think so where's the blue Tower oh
in it okay blue are we blue you mean
blue
flags not blue
floor right yes I assume that's what it
is I think so too
yeah all right let's
go
okay okay so we start at Area 15 area we
start at MAA we start at Moon green to
the left pink to the right I think red
red is next to Pink right I know I know
uh I remember it by heart I'm just
asking for myself also okay
cool food in everyone touch bed but
touched is here I think I touched it
like when I was over
there doesn't matter if we die once it's
open I mean if we die once we will get
somewhere yeah it's round one team ready
for round one team we we we cuz I have
to run afterwards I have to go wait so
do I wait wait wait so do I just go down
if yeah just go to the door yeah
[Music]
okay yeah we really don't have much time
is there a timer for this no right it's
just like last person standing last
person
standing okay let's
go ah yeah I hope you guys make it like
you have to but yeah I think we can be a
little bit late but not too much
hopefully I mean it's just not nice if
you're late you know ah we see all first
for every okay oh no no don't trol
hello hello thank you everyone for
coming I want to check it first oh okay
okay perfect
perfect and thank you so much the first
one the medle will
be flag anaa in yellow flag and rain in
blue flag your you know whenever you
want everyone is already on the temples
hi okay good so
um I'm just going to the
rules all right hold on wait a minut in
the Hol life official Channel I think so
uh as you guys can see there will be
three round but this time you guys in
the round one team mhm mhm uh there will
be a fighter and Navigator if the
fighter
dead what
oh
okay the H ID cup went longer than the
rown okay thank
you he so um if fighter dead that means
game over for your team if navigator
that that mean the game still must go on
but Navigator cannot help at all yeah
cannot shoot cannot navigate okay so all
you can um all you can do is depends on
your Fighters
team um and
wait if navigator navigator cannot be
outside of the of the temples M but can
uh fight with bow and arrow so if you
have a bow and arrow you can you can use
it if you kill the the
enemy and the items fall you can take
[Music]
it the bed is outside as you guys as you
guys can see the outside um that's
promising if you guys date then you're
dead that's me game over H should I
translate really quickly the the items
thing I think yeah thank
[Music]
you you not giving me the weapon yeah
come here okay okay okay is there
supposed to be a bed it can snowball so
I if
I uh so I should keep ey even if you die
once you can't do anything either as a
navigator or as a fighter real so the
bed doesn't have to be close right yeah
oh it's
okay are we are we good to go guys guys
okay ready cuz of the time yeah do we go
back into our own BCS
yes okay
bye-bye I'm more nervous about Eno's
time than my own
time y y y y y y y okay I was supposed
to okay okay okay I was yeah oh [\h__\h] I
was supposed to I was supposed to do
something with oh with uh with Ina
manager oh so remember I forgot to pay
you
money so so I think I'll have to like
send it through in a manager uhhuh but
yeah that would take some time I guess
but maybe I'll Rush after this in oh
it's okay we can talk about that later
later yes yeah
guys can we can
we yes
[Music]
ready no bow waha let's go Pachi only
existing by should I go left right which
one who I don't I don't know who's on
which side right
now you should oh wait wait I think uh
they haven't begun yet oh sorry
[Music]
Sor is that on the right side is
that and oh no it doesn't matter I'll
just tell you when somebody
comes 3 2 1 go
I'm yeah go out then walk out then can
you see me in the green uh yeah oh my
god oh they're shooting
me just ignore see you in the green
there's no one around you as far as I
can
tell there's no one in purple yet NE
which is next to us next to Green I
really don't want there
uh there's someone over at the red Tower
but you're you're pretty safe over there
I'm stuck I don't know where I am I
don't know where I should go would I see
a name if there was one I don't know
where I should go I'm stuck you see
names too right I do I do so you can
kind of tell if somebody comes closer to
you oh there's someone in the
middle not going not going I don't know
where to ex stay stay in purple for now
maybe although maybe they're all stal
mating maybe yeah pink is staying in
pink okay so far they just like walking
I think they're all ah they're they're
relying on The Navigators right now H oh
who's on the walls oh somebody shooting
somebody's trying to shoot yeah they're
trying to shoot you red is trying to
shoot you which is I think Sola
sire yeah I I think uh they're they're
aiming somewhere else now oh this is
scary I can
tell oh it's it's pretty slow
everybody's so careful this
time s there
yeah she's aiming she's aiming rain stay
close to the walls because that's really
hard to get
you I know from
experience H I want this to
open is just staying in her territory I
want this to
open I want what the oh my God
I think everybody's playing super
defensive I'm lost I'm I'm just lost
honestly let just stay stay there
there's no one there no one there we got
to wait for them to kill each other come
on come on guys wa where are you going
wa I'm
bored I see Y is going to the middle uh
but I think she's looking for the door
oh
I'm at Blue right now why why because I
feel like because I'm bored honestly
it's okay it's okay have fun don't take
it so seriously anyway I think you know
we don't have much
chances Yi is in the middle in the free
middle
oh
Bo I'm at Cobo blue I'm so far away from
you I'm so bored okay I cannot see you
oh my God it's so crowded it's so
crowded oh
[\h__\h] I can't see anyone everybody's gone
oh oh okay one down Ana was a fighter so
their team is out Ana Ina anaa team is
out
nice okay wa there's two other teams
left but who's the other team
there's sort e who's the other
team uh how do
I oh there's someone in the middle Y is
in the middle e is in the middle but I
would not bait her she has she has a
shield and who knows what weapon
anding oh you why are you walking to
Pink careful soda is sod SAA is uh
aiming for you I see
her she's she's she's oh oh she took a
shot she's totally going for you I she's
aing only three teams oh okay now it's
vers you versus Yi so actually we
probably should not um
yeah you will have to fight her I guess
I I don't want to stop but try to fight
her where at least s Senai can't like
shoot you that easily you're both in the
middle have fun have fun oh so if I
could accidentally shoot you'll be that
would be
fun oh yeah oh yeah I don't know oh yeah
okay you're surviving
wow damn how are your hearts
doing oh what wait a
what how the [\h__\h] did you take her
weapons take her weapons you can take
them I did I did who oops sorry Underdog
Underdog wait I I ruined something sorry
with one weapon and no functioning
Navigator
[Laughter]
five more minutes what do you mean oh
yeah we win yay five more minutes I
don't know how where to put the sh I
think I got to go too now so if you move
on to the next round you got to get
someone else to navigate you pick me
up pick me
up pick me up me no I don't someone else
navigate I'm
lost good luck wa good job so far damn
girl you did it you did it you were
underpowered in terms of armor but you
did it so let's go have fun in the next
round I got to go so thanks way for
working with
me I had fun than way see you again some
time okay bye-bye bye-bye come bye can I
should I go outside
[Music]
okay okay
so okay so how find our Temple where I
so I don't do anything right okay I'm
out
okay I'm out
to so I'm not fighting
today we I should have put my elytra I
forgot don't take my elytra
[Music]
please if I die no
more I am alone can we loot the Kill
player
yes they said it
so where do we watch here yeah where do
we
watch where's the Anon
[Music]
space a w right yo hey
there I don't know where to watch is
there like a VC where we can
[Music]
watch I'm
lonely since Wawa is gone who's going to
navigate for me I can navigate you
unless you
want can from one of us
yeah
um okay thank you
okay I'm okay though uh so I guess oh is
there like a space where we can
watch oh yeah you can watch in the
bridge oh there H I don't know how I get
there okay thank you I'll try to get
there okay
okay I'll try to get there I don't know
how but I will
try raids were alsoo manual raid
okay yo I have no idea how to get there
you know what I'm going to watch from
here because I don't know
how oh that's how you okay let's
go you know in such a big place like
this for like big concert venue they
should put like Signs like this way to
so and so I feel like it's a very nice
addition that I don't know I wasn't
joking when I said um hold on oh hi Taco
dases
oh I wasn't oh [\h__\h] hello I am I am
joking in in the Ana Zone I was joking
when I said oh yeah she is she's in the
middle need to Mark the exit you know
but not just
she doesn't have any bows and arrows
[Music]
well I'm safe
here oh my
God
Arrow oh my God
[Laughter]
[Music]
help hold space I know but then I'll be
like in the
Maze oh my god
look I'll be in the Maze and they would
there's a chance they would kill me wait
let's practice using the shield
now how do you use the shield
oh I hear
arrows are you
okay um I think I should wait until it's
all
over so I you want to go up together
yeah sure
oh a closeup battle
yeah yeah that's why I'm scared I'll
just wait until it's
over
okay there's people that's
why oh looking at them from up closest
one yeah
rain it off the pit what is your
wisdom oh my God looks like a fierce
battle something intense going on
above
[Music]
wi
wi it's so peaceful here I love it so
much it's so nice la la la looking oh my
my gosh with the music
of it's power of the
lights you think it's safe to take a pig
nuh I hear so much I'm hearing so much I
don't think oh my goodness who is it are
you
ooh what slid by Ru so canu wi ah
[Music]
finally
sorry there you
go here there you go okay this is so
dangerous I'm sorry I keep
falling it's fine so can we how do I go
outside we can just go from here okay
thank you I'm I'm very bad with
directions you will be my navigator I
don't have a bow and arrow anyway so oh
that's okay then I'll just tell you
where everyone is at yeah how does Cara
navigate you
um telling people's positions and then
[Music]
I think it's just like that like who's
around and then Sora Senai was actively
aiming at me and then she was like she's
aiming at you be
careful
okay uh I'mma make the group
y sorry sorry the green green Green okay
yeah
GRE lower your gaze
lower your
gaze where's the
Enderman oh
grou you lower your
gaze my eyes are up here my eyes are up
[Music]
here okay so we're here
Temple green green
Temple oh yeah because it's across from
each
other okay H okay so normally if uh
you're in uh Zeta area oi area or um
risu area you can't see
me okay J I'll stay away from those okay
who's the fighter for this
team
uh buy one buy one do you know if their
Navi have um SJ they have a bow and
arrow yeah [\h__\h] so I think it's better
if you uh give
app oh she's already in the middle by
the way oh
she's
waiting middle a oh she's coming towards
you from the left be
careful ooh yeah she is thirsty she's
jumping and looking for
you I think you can see her too
y she's just waiting at this
point I I want I want to I want I want
her to be like where the arrow can't
reach
me okay now she's you guys are close to
each other just separated by walls I
think she's trying to bait you in to the
like I'm not going to be
baited I think you won't get hit by the
arrows as long as you stay behind like
the circle walls in the middle oh Circle
walls what a circle wall
um it's kind of like surrounded by walls
right stay behind yeah that's kind of is
shooting she's pretty good be careful
did he just move a lot yeah
[Music]
okay why is she shooting from
behind she's across from us oh okay yeah
yeah but she's a really good Shooter
wait how many arrows does she have why
is she not running
I think they bought a lot I think they
have like 40 oh B I'm lost I'm like
legit lost oh then don't worry she's
coming for you by the way I think it's
going to be your chance uh getting close
okay you guys are separated by one walls
there she is good
luck yeah oh m
you did
great Shield is useless just Spam but
anyways it is what it is it is what it
is sh
yay
wow I'll join VC okay okay
[Music]
there
hello this is I will give you a
hold
on Wow we got the trophy guys what the
thank you thank
[Music]
you we got a
silver I feel
like I feel like I kind of
[Applause]
have what happened
no I think
well okay everyone thank you so much for
joining the Hol ID cup for this
year I really I really appreciate it
that you you uh spend your time to play
with us uh to trying the games um and
also thank you for the the ID for
helping me to building finishing the Bor
Until the End
y it was an honor for me to to to making
this uh
um being one of your mandor
and and well um after this after this
for the I there's another another stream
I believe oh yes yes yeah yeah and for
the participant who who
been lower your G lower your G
uh thank you so much and enjoy enjoy the
the game enjoy the food enjoy everything
uh please don't forget to uh Play the
medle song that just arriv
there's thank you so much let's take a
picture together let's take a picture
together
[Music]
in front of or inside let's let's go
outside you guys work so hard for such a
long time we appreciate you so much
oh it's s already oh my goodness what
the
[Music]
f
[Laughter]
OMG oh my
god
[Music]
oh
forever slip
slip okay
[Music]
scolding scaffolding
so hi
everyone wait we still
inside
[Music]
okay what are you
doing someone going to fall
[Music]
they
waiting K and am please go up okay okay
guys
guys the on the way
okay I'm going to take a
picture we
Crouch
okay okay
okay okay okay
okay three two one
[Music]
[Applause]
F thank you than
[Music]
than
okay okay three two one
[Applause]
[Music]
go thank you everyone thank you so thank
you so much
[Music]
is it
okay to shake your hands
[Music]
[Applause]
as I'm going to I'm going to talk to
myself so I'm gonna
byebye thank you so much thank you so
much excuse me hello what the hell oh my
God thank you for picking me as your
part
thank
[Music]
you byebye bye guys oh my God yay so
guys uh before I end the stream I just
want to you know have a little talk it's
well yeah if you guys guys didn't know
um after this uh in like um a little bit
more than 1 hour so at 5:00 p.m GMT plus
7 there is going to be um an
official uh an official get together
with the Hol ID it's kind of like an oty
so otai is kind of like uh you know like
well OT and then we just talk about it
and stuff you know uh so yeah if you
guys can come please do and yes very
nice nice um I'm very very happy that we
could get two and it was even because
you know it was even when waa was still
there like Wawa could Wawa needed to go
for a while and not for a while
sooner she had to go but yes we won we
wanton silver with with Wawa
too yes yes we can live the midle until
next stream yeah please I think it's
super Banger even me myself I haven't
even seen the final result but but we
can uh I I'm going to watch it after
this
parent yeah I think it's a really nice
uh you know progression we had zero luck
in this one and then uh everybody you
know we didn't have much luck either in
the like the other stuff but yeah the
maze I got kind of lucky I guess uh and
Wawa was being such a good job na uh
navigating and yes even though we had
limited resources we somehow did it
question mark in the way yeah so very
very happy for me Holo ID cup is like um
as an ID who didn't get to uh as an ID
who wasn't part of the staff or
Committee Member but also helped with a
little bit of building um I thought that
this was a very very nice project we did
start this project from like a very very
very very long time ago but uh sadly I
think um there were just like some stuff
uh in the way that kind of uh made the
building schedule kind of um shift and
as a result like we even we have to like
super rush on building it like just look
at this like building this from the
outside and um in the inside is also
super intricate you know I feel like
everybody you know did a super super
super great job and not to mention the
uh lomba too the competitions well of
course like it's our first time doing
something like this in a very minimum um
place to minimum time or
minimum chance to test uh the base of
the game was very solid of course
there's um I think we could um uh polish
some stuff in the future but I really
really really had fun and I can't
believe that we made something like this
you know so I'm very very happy to next
year is definitely going to be even
better or even you know honestly this is
just my opinion but I feel like even if
we kind of like set up the prog uh
different programs or whatever shouldn't
we just do next year in the same
building you know I feel like this
building is so iconic you know and we
put so much effort into it and it's Boro
buur is like kind of ID you know it's
like an ID identity it's not like it's
some random building so I feel like it
would be really nice if we were even to
reuse this next year I haven't even
talked about um this to the comedy yet
and stuff but yes
committee has been working so hard and
stuff preparing all the assets for us
and everything so I really really
appreciate their hard work sometimes you
know when a lot of people see a lot of
people see something like this like they
only see like the D-Day you know when
something goes wrong it's like oh it's
because there's blah blah blah they
weren't careful blah blah blah but
there's just like so many things
happening behind the scenes so I uh
despite you know uh things happen and
stuff you know stuff go wrong all the
time anyways and uh well the you know
the staff works so hard and I can't
imagine to just spare so spare their
time to think of games to think of stuff
I'm hunger I'm going to die soon unless
I go back inside and grab my food but
yes don't forget your elyton more rather
than that what about my food I can't eat
these
beds I can't eat these beds so I'm going
to try um to just get something to eat
uh and yeah so I hope you guys also
remember that and don't forget to uh
thank them for their hard work because a
lot of people watch this and see the
sports people a lot you know like ooh
maybe I did this I did this in this
match I did this in that match and
that's kind of like mostly the highlight
of the um these cups sometimes but
behind all this you know uh it wouldn't
we wouldn't be able to do all of this or
such things would be impossible without
the existence of you know the Committee
Member and the staff of the
[Music]
event and where do we go down
next I feel like we can oh we have Vines
let's
go and yeah as for like the switch UPS I
have no idea I feel like it's O
ambitious it's really ambitious to do
stuff on like the um within like a time
schedule especially because um it's hard
to manage things online and there are so
many people and we really really tried
our best to make everybody able to show
up but yeah unfortunately like some
switch UPS had to happen and it is what
it is uh but it's fine um it do be like
that sometimes we're just busy busy
Idols you know but yeah I hope you if
you guys have time please come to our OT
guy which is um very soon in like um 1
hour more than one hour sort of but yes
I'm sorry I can't I couldn't really
um uh read much because
my because my my chat looks like that
now if you guys don't know um this is
not rolled to everybody yet but some
people have their chat CSS not
working for some reason and there's
currently I
think I'm not sure of a way to like it's
like a YouTube thing so um right now
you're just going to see me like this
hopefully um we get it fixed soon sort
of um it's not really it's it's already
like this at home it's not a set it's
not a setup thing unless YouTube uh sort
of fixes it on their side we're going to
somehow see this so I'm just giving you
guys a heads up you know it's not like a
Rainer your CSS is not working like yes
it's not working but uh I think this is
I think this is pretty
funny yes yes yes yes Kono has a
temporary fix yes uh yes he does
actually but um it's still not the
official way kind of um I I know and I
can cook it up as soon as I'm back but
at least it will make it look better
hope you have 10 for a SN before the
next stream I know I guess um I'm just
going to log off now thank you so much
guys for viewing Holo ID cup 2024 this
was a very very ambitious project and
I'm very very happy to be able to be a
part of it and yay we got silver that's
so awesome and so I hope you know next
year in our future projects we will be
able to do something even greater I feel
like a lot of the games can be rehashed
or can be you know we can even do the
same thing just with like more polished
rules and stuff like that I am very very
happy the trap doors are very scary
but yes we love it so yeah thank you so
much guys and see you at the ukar kai
and while we are while you are waiting
for the ukara don't forget to stream our
new Premiere thank you so much guys
Salat everybody and I'll see you guys oh
hopefully next week like as in tomorrow
woohoo
bye bye-bye