[Music]
and don't you have a pro controller no i
don't actually
i've held off on buying a pro controller
all this time and i've still never what
i like
i should buy the small ones at least in
the in the thing where you like put it
into that it looks like a controller no
i don't even use that i don't even have
the safety straps i'm just have the
loose joycons
yeah but that feels like so small and i
don't know when i when i when i try to
use that it just feels like i'm not
holding on control i'm just holding a
stick or something i don't like the
feeling of agile max agility
how come you didn't get a pro controller
for like mario kart purpose for example
wait is it good for mario kart
supposedly yes oh well it's because it's
like they're quite expensive aren't they
aren't they like seventy dollars
and the us that's about you know the
price of a game but you can use it like
for so much and it's also wireless you
can have drivers and you should buy a
pro controller you should okay maybe
i'll buy one there's been so many times
where i've gone to the website and added
it to my cart but then i'm like oh it's
expensive
i'll just use the joycons
oh you need it though
trust me
okay okay
look at my huge apron
i was like i forgot to put on my apron
and when when you came out with your um
with your new outfit i was like
everybody apron buddies i know
and yours are mine i feel like bird
wings no mine are like so in your face
look look at my my beautiful red apron
wings
well today we're playing clubhouse games
51 worldwide classics
yes
and then we can play 51 games because
i noticed that online like already
they're like no you can't play these
ones so yeah
don't worry that is still enough i would
say i think so we can just play
an hour of
dots and boxes
um
[Music]
before the stream uh
i was like you know resting my finger on
on this one
and then fauna was like oh aren't you
like super good at this one didn't you
like dominate a few people with this
game and and the moment she said that i
knew that i can't use this to dominate
her because she seems to know what she's
doing when it comes to dots and boxes i
don't know it's been a while since i
played but i have played this game
before i think we have to try it we have
to see
what happens i feel this is the one the
one and only game that if i play it with
someone who didn't play it before i feel
so smart when i play it even though it's
it's so simple but this is the only game
that i always get a guaranteed win out
of if i play it with un unknown
with the people who don't have the
knowledge you know
you seem to have more experience in
hydrox you mentioned that there's like
actual strategies more than just you
know knowing the system i don't know
about exercises it just seems like you
could employ math or something
like there would be some mathematically
optimal solution but i don't know by the
way
do you uh do you know how to play chess
um
well i know how the pieces move but i
don't know
the strategies or anything well that's
good because i'm like pretty yeah i'm
pretty bad at chess as well
the last time i played i played with
rayne and i think we both didn't know we
were doing and it went on for like 20
minutes it felt beautiful it's a perfect
combination when both people don't know
what they're doing that's what where you
get the most out of chess really
but now let's start with something quick
maybe let's start and warm up with dots
and boxes where i'm probably not gonna
get my guaranteed win i
i don't wanna
come off as if i know exactly what i'm
doing because i definitely don't
okay
um played this one before
oh i think so
do i remember that's it
what the trick was
i should be fine
um
what's uh
i wonder if in this game the first move
is actually important because like with
um
what do you call that game where you
have x's and o's oh and like you play
plateau
yeah take that tell well that is like
pretty important right who who gets the
first move i don't know tic-tac-toe if
you know what you're doing it's
impossible for anyone to win it's
impossible for it to be anything but a
draw unless someone and if both people
if both people know what they're doing
then it's just
you never no no one ever gets a win
exactly it goes on forever
yeah
i don't know it feels like if both
people know how to play it'll come down
to like luck
okay we're just there please give you
the first um move
okay
let's see uh dodge and boxes first game
yeah oh it does feel like there like i
don't know this right like do you want
to take a corner piece or a middle p i
have no idea i'll just go
i'm sure there's oh like a good choice
there but i'm also not trying you know
what you took the middle i'll take uh
i'll take
i'll take a corner i'll go ahead and
take a corner we can make a corner
no don't take my cord no
no no corner
no
no we're gonna continue
oh no you're staying close to me i was
trying to keep a safe distance and you
just stay close to playing a game it's
like a dance right
i feel like i can
ah see i feel like we're going to go on
like this forever and eventually
someone's going to be forced to move and
then start
closing up the boxes eventually and then
i feel like that person is going to
get the whole board
or half the board yeah if we could you
know what i'm going to switch it up i'm
not playing games with you anymore fauna
no games
yeah
yeah no games this is not a game collab
no games no no no fun
no games allowed
no no
oh by the way i want to apologize to
your audience ahead of time because
you're kind of
more or less say so at least when it
comes to the choice of words
sorry if i swear it's like so automatic
for me like english is not my first
language and that's why i just don't
have a filter in english so i'm sorry
but i'll try to hold back and be safe so
just start today feel free to swear i'm
sure that they
they like it
i i'll try to use it instead of
is that the typical f word i'll try to
say
fauna every time i'm mad i want to say
[\h__\h] fun
way
mother fauna
wonderful oh
cause you're mother nature it kind of
makes sense
that is i'm what i never said that's the
thing i always say f the f word a lot
but i never said uh the mf word mm-hmm
that's like one step too far for me
[Laughter]
the [\h__\h] yeah all these
[\h__\h] out here
oh dear oh my god chad does does fana
ever say that effort has she ever said
it before
every time so i like actually i don't
swear genuinely people don't believe me
they think that i swear off stream but i
really don't no
they say no
never wow how do you have that control
because you just don't really swear and
like yeah i just never picked up the
habit i actually have a story about why
i swear it's it all started in middle
school
i was
oh oh
suddenly i'm a bit scared
um
it all started in middle school i was
friends with this very nice very
innocent girl
um
oh you know the type and
the the unpopular kind
um i mean
because i was always only friends of the
unpopular the most unpopular kid was
always my best friend which turned me
into the second most unpopular kid
yeah well i don't know i mean i wasn't
popular and she wasn't popular either
but i don't think we weren't like picked
on in class thankfully but
um we were in gym class good for you
geez this is getting very scary yeah i
think i don't think
uh now i think i don't see anything
anymore up here
fauna
oh fauna
[Music]
uh uh
damn it should have started first uh
but if i do this one true you only get
one box i think
that's good
i'll take my box um anyway we're in gym
class and we're playing dodgeball and i
hated dodgeball
and you know in my middle school angst i
decided to be a little bit edgy so i
said
i
effing but i really said it i think hey
dodgeball
and she looked at me my friend looked at
me with such disgust like how could you
say that and she was like what did you
say
and so i quickly amended myself and i
said um um i said i freaking hate
dodgeball
and
the shame that i felt after that i think
was enough because i never now i never
swear
i know
so how do i do the same thing that you
just ah
maybe here
nah
how do i get you to only get one box
damn it
um
the
dang
it
oh wait oh
oh
no this one i mean that gives you
one
pure strategy now
now it's not tough now i need to
think think
uh
oh wait um oh god uh if i do this one
then you
can close the box but then you can
continue on to closing more one more
so what if i do this one
you
can close this box ah
and then you can't close them anymore i
think okay let's do this
i feel like we're right trading oh
you're right because
yeah
oh no
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
oh wait did you get all of the boxes
oh i hope so i certainly hope so
i think that you get all of the boxes
now oh
finally a word for your opponent to play
dots and boxes of me
oh wait wait throw away wait
wait no wait we were throwing away
oh no no
when will she's oh god this does not
stop until the end does it there is no
stopping on you
my switch is broken i
i've been seeing blurry lines since like
a couple minutes ago
that is why i missed it can we like do a
restart like
well
i mean i think it's only fair
i can't believe we both missed that
we're actually
it was there for a while i think i think
it was we were so focused on
i'm not letting the mother win that we
missed it even if we would have done
that one earlier then uh
the other boxes that that were still not
you know ready to close with one line
that would that's where you would have
stopped so it would have not been a
whole that's true
you know we did the ground work together
and then you know as a senpai i feel
like you know gotta give the kohai a
winner
yes
by the way because you were speaking
about you're talking about dodgeball
um
i was really bad in sports class
and in gym class but
um like for dodgeball i'm generally i
was i was so bad at
like any ball game in general where i
had to throw a ball
but i was good at dodging
so whenever we had to dodge ball
i i would did you guys also do it like
with like a field in the middle and then
out of field surrounding it
oh
like outside
yeah oh we usually played inside
oh we had like two we had a middle field
separated in the mid in the very middle
of a line and then an outside field
surrounding it so for example if uh here
this is one team
i'm telling you how our dodgeball works
with this one this is perfect and then
here
is where the opposite team's
dead players would hang out oh wait wait
yeah we did that yes you're right is
there a specific
name for that dodgeball and these
outside players would shoot the inside
of this team and the same way as
mirrored on this side so i would stay
like in this uh inner circle
like pretty much until the end just by
dodging not really like participating
much in throwing the balls
just dodging dodging but then
i would feel really cool but then at the
very end
like
uh it would only be me left in the field
and everybody would [\h__\h]
oh running from one side to the other
and
but then the the problem is like i can't
save it by catching the ball and
throwing and you know
getting back some power because that's
that's that's where i lose so oh yeah we
call it a [\h__\h] in german
it's called prison ball
in english really
prison ball i've never heard of that
wait if you i see in the chat your
batteries are dying are you good uh
the ones that you are using you can only
use wireless right yeah
can connect um yeah i have other
joy-cons which may or may not be charged
that i can go try to find if these die
but i don't know
those other joy-cons in the in the
switch right now to charge a little bit
should i do that
yes okay i'll have to go run away for a
second okay i'll talk to your chat let
me do some asmr
yes please
okay
is she gone she gone is here to hear
some
tt packages asmr
so i have some tea for
here do you hear this chat and this card
maybe it's like filtering it out but and
it is some this is some tea for your
road yeah yeah and you want me i don't
have a hot water with me right now but
you would like open this up when here it
open it i listen to this opening sound
oh oh
wow
i don't have an asmr microphone but now
i take it out and i dangle it and i i
punch the microphone with the
with the tea bag how does it feel soft
right oh yeah sure i need a whisper here
i'm touching your face with the tea bag
i found a tea bag
how does it feel to be punched with a
soft tea bag there's herbs in their hips
it feels so soothing
right so healing
yeah it doesn't only heal your throat it
heals your face it gets that acne going
um backwards and inside
it it it heals your your acne scars if
you have any let's be real we all do
okay okay the asmr queen is back so i'm
gonna stop now
no i
know i i wish i know i know you've said
before that asmr is not really your
thing
oh my god wait
that reminds me because the chest
oh my god that was this one time wait
where was
uh oh garlic filled with some people and
and someone throw the for the prompt was
it good uh the the fruit of prompt uh of
tea bagging at me i think so i drew a
who was at at a supermarket on the
counter and um
putting the the letter t into a grocery
bag because i still don't know what it
means
you still don't know you didn't look it
up after that
no maybe someone told me but i already
forgot oh
is this something you buy
um
it's pretty yeah bye but
uh but it's
it has the context in
video and games that makes it seem not
as bad as it really is oh wonderful okay
[Laughter]
ah
maybe i should look it up
oh that has good memories good memories
[Laughter]
tell her i don't know if i can tell you
you can tell me anything fauna i'm your
senpai well
well in video games it's what you do
when someone
um when you like kill someone in like an
fps game you go over to their their body
and you ah um crowds
up and down
ah
oh oh
no oh no
okay
oh no
i no
no
no no no no no
no no it seems like you put the rest of
it together
no no no no no no no no no no no i'm so
sorry i already brought dirt to your
channel i i i am a disgrace i might not
swear but i think they're used to the
to being cursed
oh really this guy's this car is pretty
curious i don't even know what it means
but just finding out was
terrible
oh man oh my god i'm so sorry let's
change the topic how about we talk about
cats
yes
how many cats have you had in your
lifetime fauna oh i've had
um
wait wait
one two
three
four
wow four
four four
four
and now you have two
yes now i have two
oh
that's like a sad mathematical equation
but
yeah i know it's okay it's okay and cat
heaven or something like that
yes
how many cups have you had
um
wait i've reached an impasse uh
fauna help me
oh no
how does how does it happen again
[Music]
wait there must be one
or
there must be one if i do this you can
close one no you can close you could at
least close all of these but it would
stop then
um if i know this one you can call
ah
that's where it would stop i think
that's that's where it would stop
i think
okay let's try that i have had
one two
three four
depends on how you count it
but
maybe i had a maybe i had some
schrodinger's cats
not quite your cat
yeah but part of still like uh liv was
stayed over sometimes and uh
it was
temporarily my cat maybe
uh-huh
[Music]
ah but now i'm gonna open one up for you
again am i not
and
[Music]
this game is kind of brutal isn't it
yeah because you get only huge wins
yeah
most of the time
what if i if i don't
and you go like this and then you go
like huh
what if i do here and this is no
difference now i think it makes no
difference now
it's a cruel game these dawson boxes
they are deceptively
evil can't do it but i did everything
right
i did nothing wrong
just make it quick fauna
i wish i could make it quicker
but they still make you go through the
motions
yeah
did you just make it
oh
that is
yeah you know what that wouldn't have
happened if you had a pro controller oh
you're right because you have better
control with a pro controller of course
wow
i already gave up in my heart but there
you go this is my life this is literally
my life senpai attacks the senpai you
already give up but then you end up
still winning that's that's wow so
inspiring very
uh you love the story of the underdog
yes how to turn tables am i my my on the
turntables let the sink in it's knocking
at your door fauna
do you know that meme
oh let the sink yes let me sink it
i love that that poor sink just let it
in already we're doing four in a row now
someone mentioned that this is kind of
like tic-tac-toe but with more
dimensions
wait you don't know this one no i know
it but i never thought of it as like
advanced tic-tac-toe
but it almost is
i guess so i mean it has the same logic
behind it
all right
let's see
we're going from simple games to
difficult games it seems um is this one
difficult
no it's still simple so very simple okay
we're starting okay so we'll end with
chess
yeah but that will be never ending
someone will have to end us
that's right which will be chat probably
because they will hate us so much for
just dragging it out endlessly and
they'll be like oh my god you guys are
so stupid how are you guys not seeing
this oh my god you're unbelievable oh my
god it's like i can hear them already
yeah
[Music]
but then they're like sooner than
they're like wow this was horrible but
we want more chess anyway uh-huh
so that is unbelievable
pre-triggered do you do you know of the
the legendary uh chess game with me and
amen
no
what happened that's why chess has such
a
bad history in whole life
yeah we played clubhouse games and then
we played chess
in clubhouse games
and um
we both were not particularly
particularly good at it people like to
say i was worse
but
i'm i'm not sure about that
but yeah because of that it just went on
for hours and hours and everybody hated
chess after that and then they i thought
we weren't that bad but
everybody said we were
super bad
was it really hours
it was that hours i think so yeah
um
but history repeats itself you know
it does yeah it feels like that's
everyone's chest experience now
thank you fauna wait did you win oh my
goodness i didn't even see
of course not so if you would have seen
you would have prevented it
oh i got outplayed
do you know the strategy in this one of
how to do the double setup like that
no no i was just hoping for you not to
notice so maybe i was personally
distracting you
do you want to revenge
sure we can try again
okay
what's sandbagging first we have tea
bagging what's sandbagging i saw that in
the chat is that like dragging someone
behind it's when you pretend to be bad
at a game but then you're actually good
also throwing
no it's like the opposite of throwing
it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
that kind of uh um
um what would have to say that that that
this values my efforts
saying i sandbagged no no no no no no no
no nothing like that here all right next
question about cat's phone i have
actually a memo
oh do you perfect yes
um
did you ever go to a cat cafe yeah i
have been to some
in
not in japan i assume no i've never been
to japan
i assume that the the cat cafes outside
of japan are kind of different but
uh still have like roughly the same
concept
but
how did the cats treat you
um well actually one i went to
um i kind of got ignored by most of the
cats there were like some kids there and
there were a lot of kittens and they
were like really
oh kitties they were very interested in
the
battery depleted
now this is how i win
she's she's throwing now she doesn't
want to lose anymore so her batteries
she drained them herself
oh is she gone uh-huh
welcome back to
asmr my batteries
wait what am i
wait why am i
not
did you put the other ones into the
switch
yes okay okay yes now we're good i have
battery
noise
how much though it looked pretty full it
looked halfway
okay
okay that gives me hope yes the heads at
the cat calf oh wait it's my turn oh
um i'm kind of scared i see don't be
scared father
[Music]
yeah why don't you be scared a lot of
things like a nice scam time yeah
but
um
[Music]
some of them
oh there was one that came and sat on my
lap
oh
but a lot of them are more
than a cat's god yeah they sit on your
lap oh my god
i know this was actually it was when i
was looking
um
to adopt a cat before i adopted my last
cat and i really wanted to adopt that
cat that sat on my lap but she was not
up for adoption of course she was like
the
resident
cat you know
uh
damn was she an old one
um i think she's an adult i don't know
how old she was though
oh i see what you're doing fona
what could you possibly see
you shall not pass
um
we're both stopping each other um
constantly
um i'm going to try not to lose the same
way again
but i'm not sure
so
i am of course also the type who gets
ignored
ignore that cat cat face i've been to so
many different ones when i lived in
japan trying oh
fauna
okay trying to find one convey that
you know where the cats would like me
but uh-huh it's just it's just i walk in
there and then after me a different
chick walks in into the cat cafe and she
sits down and immediately a cat will
come and sit on her lap like i don't
understand yeah what
what does she do different from what i'm
doing
also sitting down
and then i and i try to go to the cats
who are like chilling somewhere and i
try to pet them and then they walk away
and find a different place to sit yeah
that's sad
it's so sad it's so depressing i know
that does happen doesn't it yeah
i mean that's not fair how cats are you
know
i don't know i don't understand
maybe she wrapped oh yeah she probably
rubbed catnip on herself
yeah that's smart if you do you know
droughts
oh it's probably a different name
yes
you know it yes
another prologue to chess
true i don't know draft checkers is more
fun than chess
and it doesn't last two hours
yeah it's even more simple yeah
but the thing is with this one on on on
the switch it shows you what you can do
like you cannot make a mistake
oh
it literally shows you all your options
that you have oh
i forgot this joy-con has some severe
joy-con drift
well i did see a red super chat uh
before that sent a
a message that you should use it for a
pro controller so
so thank you hi to super chatter i will
do so
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i will check up on you maybe one month
later if you have a pro con at that time
i will i'll do it yeah maybe right after
this
so i don't forget
okay uh
where was i
oh yeah so also not only uh cat cafe
cats dislike me but also like um when i
still lived with my mom we had a cat
and
that one also really disliked me
because partially probably because i was
too
hot to say too pushy
but i wouldn't only blame it on that
also i was younger
but but
that's kind of like when i decided one
day i would raise my own cats and they
will love me no matter what
and it worked out for you yeah even
though i'm super pushy and like um
sticky
that's a wrap clingy clingy super clingy
with my own cats they they're also super
clingy back to me because that's how i
raised them yeah
yeah
just gotta get your own cats and then
things work out yeah i was actually
saying almost the exact same thing
in my stream yesterday
ah cause i was talking about my cat
snail is a total lab cat and he's quite
friendly like he'll sit on anyone's lap
which like you know maybe that feels
like a betrayal you know like snail the
new one on the old one snail's a new one
oh
like maybe
you know maybe he would love anyone
but
at the end of the day
he is my cat and nobody else's yeah
he can he can sit on laps but
but he's staying at my house at the end
of the day my cat only
oh
my my babies they were lab cats when
they were kittens but they stopped doing
that when they grew up but i'm hoping
they will like
become lab cats again circle back into
it yeah full circle
how old are your cats
they're like
i think
four or four years now both of them
they're sisters
um
but
i
they're like super clingy like they want
to sleep right next to me and they
always follow me but they just don't
like like sitting on me or being carried
around the whole time and all that
so yeah
muzukashi
we're we're
not giving each other anything huh
no
no presents today
i know i don't i don't even
well
just oh no
no don't go that far you cheater
yeah the game doesn't let you cheat
that's surreal yeah oversized
so you can't fool someone who doesn't
know
um
how the game works also i find it
interesting that if you are able to
get someone the game forces you to go
they don't let me move anything else
because sometimes that's not a good
strategy
yeah but i wonder if that's that is a
rule oh you're forced
to really
wait is there no double jumping
in this one
home rules homebrewed
that's always how i played
oh
so you don't want to get yourself in
that position of
although i mean yeah you do want to put
yourself in the position because in the
end you want those you want those coins
no
no no no
oh you can double jump oh it's just one
at a time ah yeah only if you have like
yes yes um and you cannot go backwards
as far as i know yeah unless you reach
the other side yeah
all right
i missed my thing that was good i didn't
know you could double jump
[Applause]
you need to take it slowly fauna
too too preoccupied thinking about cats
you know
always always
before hollow when i had a normal day
job
even if i was just gone for eight hours
for a shift i missed my cat so bad do
you have that too yeah i don't know like
now i don't know how i like i know when
i finally go out to eat lunch or
something i miss my cats
i don't know how i would
be able to go back you know
yeah
yeah it's it's so ridiculous because you
see them all the time 24 7 at home but
you leave them for a few hours and you
miss them i know they're not like a sign
that you're too too addicted i worry
about them too i'm like oh no are they
sad and lonely without me are they okay
do they miss me
that was my biggest worry when i was in
japan for one year and somebody was
taking my old roommate was taking care
of my kitty cats for one year
and
i was planning to
you know visit them
uh like
every three months or so and i wanted to
fly back to austria
to see them
but then the moment i
um arrived in japan the sea thing
started out so i could not leave japan
because if i would have left japan i
couldn't have gone back and my visa
would have been a complete waste so i
was like stuck
and i was so sad like i was i was
getting actually like really really
depressed because i closed using my cats
and i was stuck in my apartment in my
tiny apartment in japan
no
yeah yeah i think that would be really
hard
it was so hard it was so hard and then
finally after one full year
oh
oh dear
i come back home and i see my cats for
the first time in one year that was
that was
oh
can you imagine leaving your cats for
one year i don't know how i dated but i
think it would be a full year if i would
have yeah i don't know if i would have
done it
yeah did your cats how did they respond
when they saw you
they were
it's not like they were like
acting angry or cold or anything
actually pretty fast they on the same
day they were already like
um
like chilling with me following me and
yeah but then it took a
two or three days maybe for them to be
hundred percent back to normal i think
but that was a relief they did not
um
they were not mad at me
yeah maybe i was worried like about the
cat's perception of time
if like one year feels really long for
them yeah but i'm not sure
i hope it didn't feel too long for you i
have heard that cats have good long term
memory so they'll definitely remember
you
[Music]
cat's arts and that
that is true
syndicates
[Music]
shield what should i do i'll go here
you're just
taking a walk with your king yeah a coin
huh uh-huh
i don't really i don't know
the strategies
hmm
i'm just i'm just strolling stop calling
me
what i can't follow you
no
you don't want to go on a walk together
i need to start dominating this somehow
oh no you're gonna
[Music]
yo
over now
oh
yes
i'm just gonna i just gotta um
waste so much time that your next
controller runs out of batteries this
one this one's half full we're going to
be there in a while
which one is the best choice
um
i'm gonna have to
take it with that one
[Music]
and then then um
or i just don't move any of those and
then
i
um
[Music]
oh
wait your strategy is actually working
oh really batteries yes
i swear i said it was helpful
you said almost familiar
i thought it was half a full oh no your
strategy is working
oh
too bad how unfortunate
[Music]
do you like do you like the naked cats i
think they're called sphinx cats oh
to be honest they're not my favorite
they are cute though i like them
but they're not
the most cute cat for me
yeah yeah
i this is cat discrimination i'm sorry
about that but i i don't really
like them either
yeah i think they're cute they're kind
of like ugly they have cute moments
[Music]
it looks so cold
yeah have you seen when they wear a
sweater
i don't think i've seen
anyone
speaking of cats wearing sweaters do you
ever like make your cats wear clothes oh
i have so my really old cat clover i
have um
put him in a sweater before because oh
well i thought he's so old and skinny
you know so i feel like he gets cold
and did you only do it [\h__\h] momentarily
or
well he actually hated it so i had to
take the sweater off of him
but i don't i want him to wear it
because he's cold you know
he probably it'd be because she's gonna
be warm
i mean he hasn't told me
but what if he's cold you know what if
what if what if he's hot
yeah that's true
that's true but i keep it pretty cold in
my cottage
well i keep it not as cold as i would
like it
for the sake of my cats but
do you have air conditioning
yeah i do
so in summer you can at least um keep
your
kitties
uh like grab
at least not super hot i can't really do
that in austria
most apartments i would say 95
apartments
at least don't have a
uh air conditioner like japanese
apartments too and probably i think i
think uh
um
in i think i've seen like uh
air conditioning units like the japanese
people use also in like north american
uh houses and apartments but we don't
use those
[Music]
i wish we had air conditioning it gets
pretty hot here too in austria yeah
air conditioning
damage is very nice
i like it really cold when i sleep i
sleep with a fan too
with a fat uh huh even though you have
air conditioning yeah i sleep with both
that's hey that's so loud and blue i
like the noise though i like the white
brilliance
yeah white noise is clean yeah if it's
just really low then it can be a nice
white noise yeah
what do we what do you want to play next
um do you like the color
uh wait which one it's the one
i'm not sure i know how to play this
let me listen
what
which might be like a dots and boxes if
you don't know how to play
i think i tried it before but
ah
[Music]
oh i see
ah
and drop them in their feed
you get to choose yeah four pockets to
move stones from
okay
yeah
but like yeah you don't want
you don't want all of them to end up in
the other side yeah and you get a bonus
turn if you land exactly in the big
the big piece
you should know so if you well i think
they're going to tell you that right now
actually if you drop your last stone in
an empty pocket
it's capturing ah in an empty
yeah that is also a rule they are not
using the optimal strategy right now
though in this tutorial i'm already i'm
backstaging them they should have moved
the four pocket
and then the one pocket and then the
five pocket and then the sixth pocket
but but who am i to say
you you already sound like you know this
game too well
this was my one of my favorite games
okay
yeah we'll figure it out as we go let's
do that i think it might be i don't know
i'm gonna feel bad though
now you can teach me okay i'll teach you
ramen trying to destroy me you can try
to teach me
i will show you the optimal strategies
to destroy your opponents with
oh yeah we could do this like we do one
turn and one round where you just tell
me what the best thing to do with my in
my turns and then i'm the ones we do
around where you don't tell me sure
all right well you probably want to
start well maybe you already know
let me try uh if i start with these four
it drops one two three four the last one
will be in the big one right
okay
all right okay
extra turn ah uh in that case
i can't really do the same thing again
so
i don't know i mean there's probably
debate at this point about what the best
move is probably at least i don't want
to drop them in yours yeah you probably
don't want to do that so i'll just do
this maybe
yeah that's probably good i can drop the
five ones uh next time
on the on the left side okay
okay
i think
i like the sounds so nice
this is the kind of asmr that i i i i
understand yeah
i don't understand asmr with voices you
know i don't know it doesn't do anything
for me
but like sounds like these i think
they're nice
yeah i also love like visual asmr
and stuff like this
visual asmr you mean like satisfying
youtube videos
cut like cleaning something
i get that generally but i watched like
i watched uh oh god i'm dropping too
many there i watched a video that's
supposedly like satisfying a cleaning of
horses
hoofs
yeah i've seen those too i cannot get
into those either right because they're
like uh it's painful to watch i feel
like like
that looks so painful i know it's not
painful for the horse
but
well youtube was pushing that so yeah
for me
i saw a really gross one too actually
the first one i saw was really gross and
then i never watched any after that but
i think that one was unusually gross
yeah it was like
pimple popping almost oh god but a horse
hoof all right so that's what i thought
they all were
but i think really
it's not what they all are
ah you just get one
i don't know
yeah i can get really dangerous if you
have these big
pockets and someone steals them
ah i want a big pocket from you i want
that
[Music]
but you guys wanna there's a lot of asmr
footage it's like really pretty stuff
like crafting and stuff i really like
those kinds
of videos
yeah i got done but sometimes also uh
cooking video videos that are like on
the asmr side where they just have no
voice over just the cooking sounds
cutting and chopping and all that that's
that sounds pretty nice yeah
so you do listen to asmr in your private
time
i do not as much as people might think
though and a lot of the time when you
listen to like a voiced asmr it's like
it's not for
enjoyment it's for like learning and
like studying
like seeing what other people are doing
and seeing like how they do things and
how i can
also do that that kind of thing
for learning okay i think i
um either
uh no waiter senpai or someone else i
think who i interviewed on whole talk i
think they have a similar thing where
they create a lot of asmr but they
themselves don't really like listen to
others asmrs
uh-huh because maybe maybe they are not
interested or it doesn't do anything for
them or so but yeah they're just the
creators they don't do they don't listen
to it themselves
yeah actually somebody said that oh do
you want me to tell you something well
maybe you know when you have this set up
where it's like one and then two you can
actually get all of them into your
pocket if you do the one first and then
two and then the one oh
yeah because if i drop it in the big one
then i get another turn
and then you can steal mine actually too
if i start with this one yeah
um
yeah it might be in trouble actually
really
should have dropped the one okay okay
okay okay okay okay it's okay and this
time i leave you
to see another day
so
if i drop this one next doors then
do i i don't get another turn right just
if i drop the one
no other turn this one one two three one
two three four five one two three ah
this one
yeah
wow
and then
this one
uh-huh oh one two three four one ah
let's do this one
more
very nice
now that's a thank you oh i could
if i drop um
i'll drop these ones
genius the genius inside of me is slowly
starting to
show its face yes i'm not really doing
much this game to be honest
[Music]
i don't know
i feel like i hyped myself up too much
as a man called a genius
well we can do a second run where you
don't teach me anything anymore
and we'll see how that one goes under
three room two ah two
wow very nice
[Music]
hmm
maybe i'll just do some prep work
good thinking
no
[Music]
i don't know if i do this and it's free
and then here's five but then
i'll just do this one i don't know oh
that was a good move i was about to
steal that one
with the two ones that you have
yeah
i don't know what i should do
and let me repeat in order to steal
someone's you have to drop the last one
in an empty one right and then you get
the oh yeah an empty one across from it
oh for example you can steal mine yeah
yeah
i saw that
but it's just one ah oh i thought you
bring it back into your side but you
just drop it in the big one now yeah
yeah
extra ten
oh oh oh wow wow fauna is on the road
open the window yeah you're totally
going to win because at the end of the
game you get all of the stones on the
other side of your
of your um
your board
oh so i don't know
i don't want to give too much of them
away right now so i'll start on this
side or something
just
just sitting there
oh wow
shiny stones as a bird i really like
those shiny stones
i know i always liked playing with these
as a kid just because it's so pretty
that's so cool
thank you for teaching me properly now i
think i probably understand good job i
want to try again sure
okay nice i like it now we're free we're
well very evenly matched
let's go let's do this gg rematch
rematch time
where is this from again
this game i don't know chad probably
knows
questions
it looks kind of oriental judging from
the um the carpet um
like
is that is the beginning distribution
distribution random i know everyone
starts at four nothing yeah
so you should always start with this one
one two three four no battery at all oh
africa oh
battery battery sun daijoubu
um
[Music]
this one
thank you
oh
i didn't do anything big did i
give me an extra turn
it's moroccan
i actually
say morocco because i don't know it the
rug reminds me of like moroccan
i've been to morocco before oh have you
yeah
with my mom and my brother
it was um an interesting vacation
many weird things happened for example
my mom trying to uh oh considering to
sell me for a camel
oh
i think you're worth at least at least a
couple camels oh thank you
i think it was supposed to be two camels
hmm i'd say you're worth at least three
camels
that's so that's so nice of you
but one thing i really liked there was
this one dish i forgot what it was
called but we ate it with
i think we ate it with fingers and it
was uh it was like
uh
everyone was eating it together
okay that's probably it doesn't really
describe it very well
well i've had like
ethiopian food before i really like
ethiopian food that one is like a bunch
of dishes that you eat with your your
hands or with like the ongera the bread
tagine was the one i was thinking of oh
nice oh
that was a good movie oh my goodness
whoa
i didn't even think that far
okay okay that's okay
one two three four five six seven eight
nine no
um but i think i might still lose though
because now i gave you all these
beautiful stones oh but i got those okay
oh my
oh my oh my
looking interesting here it is
interesting isn't it you still have so
many on your side but i only have one
left which i guess i'll keep on moving
one by one
i think oh
i think i know what to do
are you really
i think i know i only have one choice at
this point i don't even have to think
oh no smart that is smart fauna
big brain there's no surprising amount
of strategy in this simple game
wow
i think the scores were flipped this
time
i think the scores i think you got 30
last time and i got 18. i think we
exactly flipped the scores wow
we tabled the turns again
why and why am i
i want to try yeah
oh yeah i want to play yotai
i don't quite understand it um 100
but i just randomly do things 100
luck
i mean you can pretend that it's skill
based on which one you mark off but at
the end of the day
you just have to get to good roles
yeah that is true that is true
i know that uh sample is a yacht uh
genius
professional she's very very
enthusiastic and
passionate when it comes to
this game i want to shake shake shake
[Music]
a full house what
do i just keep everything well it's
honestly not the best full house though
because you have some ones in there
oh but it's up to you
it's when you have three of one dice
yeah oh but do you get the points based
on the
like the value of the die so
oh yeah okay
uh how was this again how many can i
only rewrote one or two you can reroll
as many as you want
so i think you choose the ones you want
to keep
ah
you can re-roll two more times oh the
game has just started let's
let's do it oh you're going for once
i wanted to roll the ones
okay uh everyone let's go
shake shake shake shake shake shake
shake
what's your favorite kind of milkshake
oh
maybe i don't know i really like
strawberry but also like um oreo like
cookies and cream yes oh my god did you
ever try the oreo shake from burger king
why had the mcflurry from mcdonald's
oreo mcflurry i don't know if i've had
the burger king one
what is this
what is this what did i do i think you
want fours
because you have three fours
i
said
said life
shake shake shake it shake it shake it
shake shake shake shake shake shake how
do i
[Music]
oh okay
oh
i want the shoes
[Music]
doing a big concern oh no oh no you're
doing me a big concern
i'm kind of blocking the the board want
a bamboozle um
i want sorry i i didn't mention this i'm
playing through obs because well
we couldn't get the
the elgato program to work properly so i
i can't see because i'm covering it
myself i would like four of a kind
please
but you know
those those um
troubles that we had i feel like they i
felt more connected to you after knowing
that we both use the same capture card
and we both have the same issues oh my
goodness you keep rolling well how is
this but i don't want it
i don't want this low full house but
maybe i should just take it i don't know
not very well
uh because but then i actually
i did a good uh
senpai move i was able to solve one of
those problems
successfully the audio crackling i gave
her a good advice
so she doesn't
wow
that's the kind of full house i want to
see
although my original one was even better
than that one i think the one the first
one
wasn't that 24 was it
because it was uh
uh free no i don't know maybe not no
maybe this is better okay
nice
i was 14 ah okay
but unfortunately we couldn't fix the
the one thing with the window not
opening that's why you're playing with
obs yes
but i have the same issues so often but
the trick for me is uh that one uh
combination of uh windows key and arrow
up but it didn't work for fauna
i never get like technical things i have
this so often that like i try a solution
that the internet or whatever tells me
and
i try it exactly the way the internet
tells me but it doesn't work for me
it only works for other people but it
never works for me
i don't like my role right now
thanks fauna i don't
i don't like my role at all yeah it's
not a good role
i don't know much about uh you know
these values and all that but i know
this is not a good role
i don't think it's smart to go for two
so early oh especially if you don't yeah
yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
that looks pretty
i will
risk it and try to get like
all sixes or something like that yacht
of sixes that would be beautiful
oh
so close four of a kind
i feel like i feel one
again i have a guaranteed four of a kind
so
let's roll this girl
come on mother fauna
okay
let's go
that's okay it's only worth one more
than my four of a kind
i won up to you anyway just by one point
what do you have there three you know
let's go for her
this is probably not smart
oh is that
what are you making
a straight
a straight but i need a roll of five
is that small is it is it straight uh
having a
a different number of each like
um i think yeah it's like oh gosh this
is not smart
you're right i should discard the six
i think
oh who's going to chat chat
[Music]
have you ever been to europe have i
asked you that before i have i've been
to
um france and italy
president italy
it was quite a long time ago though i
really want to go back
i don't know what should i do
another full house you keep rolling four
houses
yeah
aces deuces freeze and so on that's like
only having
uh ones and only having twos or one yeah
you get points for however many you have
when you get um 63 total in that
category you get a 35 point bonus you
can see that's like at the bottom of the
top of the scorecard like yours is 12
out of 63 right now wow
i don't like this
oh this is a bedroom i mean you have
three ones
that's
fine i want one more oops
i want one more one please about aces is
a classic one too
to get rid of when you have a bad roll
because it's not worth many points
okay then i don't feel so bad about it
all right
i actually speak some
of some italian did you know
i'm not surprised
many languages yeah it's a neighboring
country so
um austria likes to offer italian as a
language to study in school sometimes
so yeah but but my italian it's been a
while so
i only know uh
italian
for tourism tourism related italian
this i'm so upset right now
oh no
nothing goes well for you mamma mia
don't give up
i won't give up
i
speak only a bit of french
oh my god that is very charming
oh
two possible
well because you have a commercial
um
damn it now i forgot everything
oh italian is not my strength
french is not my french i mean french is
not my french
excuse my french
i'm getting confused here
oh
what is these
choices is like you get just the some
value of all your diets when you don't
know what to pick but you could pick two
just because you have two tubes
yeah
i will do that
shake shake and shake up
what is this
we only get stupid rules game is rigged
can i have a small straight at least
wait this is
no you know it's not what that's not
what you wanted i'm missing
fives
yeah
oh no
why don't you reroll both can you have
capped the six
uh well the six
would have
worked sort of
only if i had gotten a three though not
a one
i don't know this is not good
oh someone's asking for french only asmr
i wanna hear that that would be so
sensual i think i'm carrying this one
i know i should probably do a large
stream maybe oh no you should get
someone to write you like a french
script oh that would be good because
then i don't have to rely on my
that's a good idea actually i haven't
thought about that someone else to write
the script
oh my goodness you just rolled a large
straight
pain
oh here comes them and that's the peck
without fan inside of me
nice
not even trying
[Music]
oh i know what game we're going to play
next
chess
uh no uh what's it called again um
that one poker game that i know how to
play
president one poke no
uh i played it in uh when i played
yakuza blackjack
that's easy that's an easy one i know
blackjack i don't have to know anything
yeah i was scared you're gonna ask me to
play actual poker for a second
i don't even know how to play a normal
poker me neither i don't know good all
right let's try it again
i don't know
oh what what is the difference between a
large straight and a small straight um
large shirt is every number is ascending
and small straight is
what only
four
so our trade is all five and small
straight is only four
and it has to be in the right order up
at the top of where we put the oh no
well no yeah it doesn't have to be like
physically in the right order you just
have to have all of them
okay
but i don't know
i don't know no no no no i will try a
yacht
or we're going for a yacht
wait that is that i don't know why that
i guess that's not a yacht oh that would
be a large straight again what i'm going
for i'm gonna go for a small straight
though because you don't know i hope
these ones right
okay
let's see so i would need a five five
yeah
okay
there's a freaking five oh wow wait do
you need a three as well wait
all right look at that
so close
[Music]
choice
one one higher than yours
oh
i'm having some girls come over from
some whole girls in
some time in the next
let's say half year
and uh maybe we should do strip poker um
um
that's just me uh giving everyone
fantasy sorry about that
[Laughter]
we would never play such a thing no no
no no no no they the audience doesn't
have to know
no they'd be playing and no one would
know we are stripping maybe we are not
stripping who knows who knows
who knows if you play regular pokemon
no one will know what's happening
oh my gosh
what is this
oh today's such a wonderful day such a
beautiful day
oh this is a small straight that i just
rolled though after i already exited off
oh
oh i'm in trouble
oh i know
i can only win at this point
is getting me destroyed goodbye
no more i'm relying on a yacht if i get
a yacht i can still win
once you once you um
set something you can't redo it anymore
right like
memo okay yeah
oh that's also almost a full house
again oh yeah that is true
uh so far yeah i need all the same
numbers right four yes we can do five
over one original one we could do sixes
yeah
so and if we're lucky we'll not only get
sixes but a yacht
is oh no if you get a yacht i just have
to i just have to
end it
phoenix
come on let's go
[Applause]
did you watch game of thrones no i
didn't
oh my god why did you is it good
well to be honest i was kind of scared
because of um
all of these
and yeah they're topics that they go
into
that was actually i um didn't watch game
of thrones until uh the second last
season that's when i started watching it
because i also um like stayed away from
it for several reasons i just didn't
think um i would like it
but
well yeah there are some
there are some sensitive scenes but
it's not all about that and if you watch
it alone then you don't have to feel so
embarrassed about it
that's true
you know
like i really feel uncomfortable
watching stuff like that with someone
else yeah me too
especially your family like your parents
that one is the worst
yeah we me and my friends like from work
we watched the whole game of thrones
last season together every episode we
came together and ate like uh
some dinner together and then watched uh
the last season together but
i think in the last season there were
not so many
se
scenes
so it wasn't that awkward yeah
dosio
freeze fives yachts
i think you have to go for fives yeah i
think so too
won't get much out of it probably but oh
well
i'm starting to understand
all these games way better thanks to
playing them with you fauna oh
i'm
glad oh i saw i saw that those fives
that turned around in front of my eyes
how dare you also for this one you might
want to go three because yeah yeah lower
value volume could still get a higher
one out of the fives right yeah yeah i
see you i see you father yep this is the
strategy the strategy
oh wow
just what i needed
i mean it looks nice i don't even know
should i keep the sixes and go for a
full house i don't know
go for it
this is not a full house
it's not a four either
this is how you gamble oh no oh no
thank god this is not about money
i'm
oh
i think i have to
do i have to get a yacht to win
i feel like i have to go for the yacht
that won't help you if i also get a
yacht yeah
yeah
i'm banking on the yacht
we need to we need to
um if you lose this maybe we need a
punishment game for you oh no
why just on the why only on your dice
why didn't we do the punishment came
from hong kong because
because this is your channel and uh we
like to see
some nice
punished fauna everything you know you
know
i can be into a punishment so
okay
i saw a clip of you actually today um
doing push-ups and being out of shape
oh yeah i'm actually i'm mad at that
clip because everyone's like oh my gosh
she's so out of shape she did 34 squats
in a row and she was tired and i'm like
yeah how about you guys do 34 squats in
a row and see if that makes you sweat a
little bit
if that makes you wind it a little bit
but you don't work out like generally
right you don't do any work i try to but
yeah i'm it's sort of a truck every once
in a while i go to the trash
i go to the gym every once in a while
really how long does this one every once
in a while whenever i remember too
it's good sometimes it's like multiple
times a week other times it's like never
but also going quite a bit i walk around
my forest and i go hiking and so far but
would you really go hiking yeah
well okay i'm not going well i mean you
guys work out more than other council
members
i mean yeah i don't i don't really but i
don't know i'm just like
i think
people should do 34 squats and then they
can call me out of shape oh that's right
that's right also you're getting a four
is nice i almost fought a yacht
nine but i didn't oh i get the bonus
though
there is hope oh no i should have kept
the full house
turned i have to get a yacht to win it's
not good
[Music]
you don't need a yacht you could get
zero and snow in
please oh no
oh no
this is where everything changes and i
regret everything i said until now oh no
pray to lady luck i mean you're not in a
bad spot i need to get a yacht to win
what are the chances of getting a yacht
you'll probably be able to do it
you're gonna go for freeze or six i
don't know do i go for threes there's
three is no three is my lucky number so
i go for three
[Laughter]
at least it wasn't it was closer than
than i thought it would be
you caught up because of the bonus that
you got yeah all those zeroes at the
bottom are looking pretty sad though no
not bad they're not bad
it says too bad though too bad
no
not bad not bad not a bad um
number
no no
we like to see that that's a decent
decent jump
um
you know what we're gonna finish it off
with a
uh
blackjack yeah that was good
unless
let's do blackjack and then see how we
feel was it sevens no um where's
blackjack
did they call it something else
yeah
okay
chad is asking for chess now but then if
we play chess they're going to be like
this is pain this is something
they want
to
play now because it's probably going to
take half an hour at least we should
play a blackjack i think really
i would rather play blackjack than half
an hour of chess
i think
okay
i mean unless you really want to play
chess
i'm not sure what i want i'm indecisive
what does
you could do a poll in the chat and let
them decide but they're just control
their dude's control
[Music]
there's a fair amount that doesn't want
chess maybe
what the silent majority has
they're just face palming right now i'm
gonna vote for blackjack to give me a
chance
but if they vote for chess then they
have no right to complain unless they
just want to complain
also the problem is if we play chess is
your controller even gonna be
working
how's it looking how's the blackjack is
actually winning 55
oh
oh wow okay let's give them like give
them an asmr countdown oh how far should
we count out from
from ten okay
you do you do like uh the
the ten and i do the nine and okay okay
okay
ten
seven
six
um
okay
looks like blackjack won it didn't
change at all in that time
so sad for the chess fans man
it's okay it'll be all right
so the thing is here we're also going to
play against npcs
oh there's a chance that the npc wins
and that one that's the worst ending if
the bot wins
how many rounds five or ten oh i don't
know
i'm not sure how long it takes yeah
double down what was double down against
double doubt i [\h__\h]
is that ten rounds okay kfc item
double down
sounds like a brand new double down or
kfp maybe
maybe you could offer it at kfp
we actually recently uh
i i renewed my my menu um oh we have a
really realistic menu right now
um
and i want to do like a like a cooking
contest like have people recreate my
burgers and menu items yeah and then
judge them and maybe do some myself too
oh that's such a good idea
yeah
oh
oh they're all i don't know
i don't know i don't know what
oh we're bedding yeah you already got to
start bedding i kind of want to go all
in
that's a really bad idea
with how you how lucky you were in yacht
i don't think you should go all in
how about half half in
okay
uh
what was again we went trying to reach
21 right oh
was it oh
but 17 seems bad
wait we want to reach 21 right yeah
and what's the highest card
oh god
wait is it king in the highest
and how much does that give
17 is good
but this this person already has 19.
oh but maybe they'll bust but they
probably won't play
though oh face cards are all 10.
wait a second 11 or one
aces 11 or one
both
oh it's us versus the dealer not us
versus each other oh yeah okay
actually i kind of forgot i'll just
learn by doing um i'll hit
[\h__\h]
i was i will stand
stand stand strong fauna stand strong
oh oh busted yeah
i'm rich
i should have gone all in
oh the temptation to go all in is so so
strong but it shouldn't
no no don't do it don't do it you have
to this is if you go all in that's
that's where your life will be in
shambles you should be careful this is
gambling it may only be within
a switch but
but still
there's a nintendo
oh my gosh it's rigged they only voted
16 though okay good i will
stand
yes
i will
hit
hit oh did you watch
anime oh that was cruel
what
did you watch kakegurui the anime oh i
didn't
i didn't hear about it oh my god
blackjack so rigged
it's rained it's rigged
oh my god not fair
i watched kakaguru it was kind of crazy
yeah i've heard that i've heard it's
just insanity or what about um
devil man cry baby
did you watch that one
no meaning there but i feel like it's
kind of
similar well they're both on netflix and
they're both crazy i think
oh
i actually completely stopped watching
anime do you still watch anime i do not
that much
huh what are you currently watching um
what am i watching
well i was going to watch attack on
titan but then i heard that it's still
not done after this season so now i'm
like what's the point
i want to wait but i think there are so
many episodes like that like even if you
start watching now
have anyone catch up anyway everything
except for the last season which was it
was supposed to be the final season
but um
but they faked us well actually the last
season was supposed to be the final
season but it wasn't and then this
season was also supposed to be the
finals but then it wasn't it will be the
first season the last one was called
attack on titan the final season and
then this this one was called attack on
titan the final season part two and now
we're getting the final season part
three
why would they do that what i don't know
because they're cruel and there's only
like eight chapters left to cover in the
anime which is not that much i feel like
they could have just squeezed it in
but i don't know why
unbelievable i don't know so i was gonna
watch that but now i'm like what what's
the point it's gonna be another year
before yeah the next before it's
actually done
they're just trolling at that point
oh my god
yes hit
i barely have coins left can you um
can you buy a brother i want to borrow
some coins please
please fauna
um please we think you should have cpu
too
yeah they got too many we need to
destroy them i know
they're hitting because i'm like what
can i lose at this point
ah
i'll stand
i'm just hoping that the dealer does a
bad job
kiara we're losing to the bot
yeah actually i think we're losing to
both bots
there's always like one one npc that is
just too good
oh it's done already
never mind five more rounds uh-oh i have
to be careful now
chiara full
almost solid
oh
king and queen wow wait i'm so cool
you're 21. that's so good
that's beautiful that's a beautiful
moment yeah i will stand
that must be a win come on how can i not
win
busted
yeah
i'm so upset this happened again i'm so
excited
[Music]
that sounds silly
oh my gosh busting busting busting
buttons we will have to write a strongly
worded letter to nintendo i'm gonna i
wish i could cheat in this game i would
just sneak some coins from
cpu number
two
all in wait can i annie more than i have
what what
okay
what i didn't know you could go bankrupt
if i knew that i would have i would have
bet like 200 on the first one
but wow like if you lose then you're
like outfit i don't know what i mean i
mean what are they gonna do to me like
come to my house and demand real money
what it's just a game
but then you don't eat it you don't
but i guess the more you go uh negative
then the more it will be difficult to oh
recover after that
that's okay i'll just bet infinitely
more
does that really work that way
i'm working myself i just have to win
the last one that's all
i guess so
[Laughter]
did someone ever have an intervention
with you before
no
it's so cool more than tv shows but
never had one
well why would you want one
i don't know it's just kind of cool
is it cool
i don't know
i don't know i mean do you want me to
have an intervention online cats with
you
car you have wait why would you have a
convention with me about cats
yeah it's more like we both need
in those terms
yeah maybe we can when we go into old
ladies we can both um be each other's
bad influence and be like oh yeah you
can totally get another cat
it's fine
oh we're gonna be like oh
no the other day i got this new cat
called tom but he really doesn't get
along with jerry can i send tom to you
and you take care of him better maybe oh
yes and we still should be treated happy
but you please must take away
um a little
little pause from me
oh i'll gladly take little paws cause
he's my favorite last time i visited him
he was uh nibbling on my little finger
and it felt like oh it felt like i don't
know i was like his mommy was making me
lovely i love you
oh he does love me i think so he's
better off with me give him to me
perfect
ooh 20.
got a 20. look how many points i have
251 tokens this is not a good look for
you fauna no it's 251.
see i have something you're negative
gambling but you're the council of
nature it's not a good look i don't see
any negative here
[Music]
how come i didn't go to 300.
you can't
shouldn't they have gone to 300 oh is
that the maximum or something i don't
know
i have so many dudes
in real life can you negative gamble
it's not it's not 300 yes you
privately you can
it's not
advisable though mm-hmm
oh
cpu time
there we go oh so many points i have 300
points
wow
uh
oh my god i was so scared okay now i'll
stand no no oh it was my accident i want
some frisbee
oh my gosh they got blackjack
this game is rigged it's the second time
they got blackjack this game is rigged
fana i think you and me we will have to
meet the the blackjack dude the dealer
in the back gallery i think the stream
too
there's some consequences for these
actions
yes don't make these girls angry no no
no no no
i have
oh wow 20 again oh my god i don't get
some good numbers dude i'm good but the
dealer's just going to get a blackjack
again so it doesn't matter
no i will not let them the dealer is too
lucky for my taste oh my god there we go
oh my gosh that's the wind in the back
for me
i'm second rat now all right last one i
must be first place because i have 450.
that was it
look at your scorpion i am not ashamed
look at those numbers i see a big number
big absolute value what we learned from
this is um
never let fauna go close to a casino
ever
have you been to a casino i've never
been yes or you have been
i've been to a casino once for like a
christmas dinner for work and then but i
only had the dinner there and then i
left while my colleagues went inside the
cuisine casino but i didn't want to go
but then i also went to casino once uh
with some friends in
czech i think
uh-huh
yeah i wonder if it's very different it
feels like it would be very different in
europe that was the only time in my
whole life that i was in a casino and i
only used um
something really basic where you don't
need to know
anything i don't know anymore what it
was
um
but i didn't win
anything i probably just lost like five
euros and that was it
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah check republic yes
yes slots no not slots sauces uh scary
um i think the whole casino is scary i
don't know i don't know why anyone would
go to a casino and you could go to an
arcade instead
like you're gonna spend your money but
at least you can like have fun
exactly
all right well uh no wait no ch check
check check no i don't know uh whatever
uh congratulations npc
for winning congratulations
so deserved i'm so proud of you
ah
ah this is i can't even i can't no i
can't
uh was this the last game well can we do
one short one yeah can we do an action
one maybe an action oh there please not
we're not boxing not the boxing
maybe we have a pro controller maybe i
have a chance against you oh
also i'm playing with the delay on obs
oh you know what i have confidence
like which one do you want i don't know
air hockey is pretty fun air hockey
hockey
okay with the delay are you sure it'll
be fine
people always say oh don't play in obs
there's so much delay but like i never
really noticed yeah that much too late i
don't notice it too much either
five point that's a five point match all
right this is a quickie
let's go i'm ready
let's see how bad this delay is showdown
wait what is that smash oh
smash
oh my gosh
so fast fauna
oh no i i feel
more than delay i just feel like that i
guess that is delay isn't it lag
terribly oh nice oh god but i'm not good
at this game even feels just stressful
it's
easier to play this in real life
friendly fire
okay oh is it the ping maybe it's the
pink
yeah that's honestly
you always feel so bad when you throw it
into your own but that's like half of
their hockey anyways just trying not to
throw it into your own goal
yeah that is so difficult like also with
um a table
soccer table
table tennis
no not table tennis table soccer oh
foosball it's what we call it here ah
yeah with that one two oh that i'm even
worse with that because you need to
control so many things at once yeah
right
we're gonna do a ten point match
okay okay
full spell is originally german so oh
that's just how we call the norman the
normal foosball normal fool's home oh
nice start
oh no okay i have to swap my battery
again
yes of course
of course but it's just
oh
oh oh no
oh god
oh
i don't even know what's happening
i'm just i'm just smashing i'm just
i'm just smashing
oh no
you know what i learned today
what penguin sounds like what does
penguin sound like
what
uh
oh no and penguin yeah it sounds a
little bit like spongebob
but they got kind of like they go down
and then they go up
like a roller coaster oh oh my god
goodness
this round is not going well
no
just just end it
just
i don't know
your defense is weak as you fo oh
it's fun
i could still come back from this
this could decide the match fauna
i can come back
the comeback the comeback
where where is the comeback doko doku
come back
show me a good comeback
[Music]
[Laughter]
i just want you to leave the stream on a
high note you know for your sake oh yeah
yeah i don't want to remind you i don't
want you to lose too big because you
might never collab with me again
no no
just one point away
no no it's okay
i was starting to believe i was starting
to need to believe too
oh
i'm going to lincoln's fauna foreign
well overall
overall we're looking at uh
we're looking at what's the score over
wrong don't remember i feel like it was
pretty even
even well it isn't that beautiful good
ending
beautiful
happy ending yeah true ending unlocked
the best kind of ending
i like this
yes
instead of preparing a game
impregnating a game what
what impregnating
can you get pregnant from
clubhouse games 51. uh
frank prague nino for a goat oh sorry i
like that meme do you know that meme
i think so
what is it the same as done how is baby
formed
how is bambi formed pregnante
yeah i think so yeah that one where
where like it's a video compilation of
like
uh people asking on those asking
websites
yeah
you know and always misspelling the word
pregnancy
is so funny i was so into that video i
had a laughing fit one of the biggest
ones in my whole life
i don't know many memes but the ones i
do know i'm proud of knowing them very
much you know it's hard for me to keep
up with you girls with your with your
english memes
it's for the best really just means
we're on the internet too much
spending too much time
online yeah
i know all some old memes but then
there's like a big gap because i think
that's where i only picked up like
japanese memes because i was too much in
like the japanese internet and i ignored
the english side of the internet
yeah and so when i just
didn't pick up anything and now now
so often i have like my my viewers like
throwing memes at me and like super
chats and so on and i'm just like
i know i'm supposed to laugh here but i
don't know what you're saying i'm so
sorry it's so awkward old man's not the
best ones though they're like classics
now
thank you i love a good
a good um rage face
the rage comics
you know like them forever alone
the troll face
epic troll
i think i know loving adorable
animals too don't forget about advice
animals advice son
totally
socially awkward penguin
yeah yeah yeah yeah
everyone knows
yeah the socially awkward penguin
advice owl
you mean duolingo
see i understand everything perfectly
yeah yeah
they only mean boomer phone if i was a
boomer then i would understand these
memes no yeah exactly i'm the boomer
right now
these are the old memes
lady age
and that is to be honest hashtag goals
exactly ain't nobody gonna tell me
anything different do you also do
fauna um
i feel like i could relate to you on
this on this note um do your viewers
maybe sometimes
worry about you
being like ending up as a cat lady
i don't know i feel like
my viewers are down for that future
really
the cat lady future
i think hopefully
it's fine
yeah it's nothing negative it's a it's
beautiful
you know when i feel happiest when i'm
around my cat so why should i not be the
happiest you know
why should i choose to be sad exactly
when there is happiness right there to
grasp and touch and fluff and pat and
move for most and sniff
i would never choose a different life
yeah do you ever just like put your face
in your cat like in their lives
me too i feel like it annoys them though
no
no no no no no no you have to get them
to get used to it i also love that you
have your cats as your emotes i also
have some of my cats
yeah
it shows that
it shows that who who we really love is
our cat's ass girl yes i wanted to i was
thinking about um you know having my
cats as part of like birthday
merchandise like for example some
keychains or
[Music]
maybe you shouldn't because you may love
your cats so much and want them a change
to your keys but maybe other people
don't like that that much maybe they're
not interested
i thought about it too like um
well maybe this bit like the the brand
you know like as a as a streamer you
have to present your brand to the world
cats are our brand now you're saying
that yeah but it's like
should they be
our brand or do it should we be other
things you know i don't know
we can we can be several brands yes but
i think yeah cats have become
just uh
in my streams a big part of my life and
uh i must therefore share me and not
share
wait
you know and you know those do you know
those um uh uh maybe it's only german tv
but like back in the day like i didn't
like those shows but they were like uh
tv shows like um
exchanging partners or exchanging
families
yeah yeah we should talk like a cat swap
and live in each other's apartments or
houses for like
a week and see
i mean we miss our cats
our cats forever that is impossible but
i would like to get to know your cats
and you should get
i feel bad though my cats are
they're probably a lot more work than
your cats they're like
they're old men you know
they what's so what's so difficult about
well you know we don't see any diapers
he kind of does well clover he's so old
you know he doesn't always make it to
the litter box and that's just kind of
how it is
yeah oh dear
yeah oh
oh it's is it that far already
oh there
he's
yeah he's 21 or 22 years old he's
extremely old i love that though you're
so lucky that that he is like living
that long yeah that's how i feel i feel
very lucky that he has lived what's the
key did you feed him lots of veggies or
no did you make him work out a lot when
he was younger no i think
i don't i think it's just that he's like
he's um i like a mutt kind of like a cat
like he's not a specific breed he's just
like
standard shelter cat
so
yeah i think he just has good
good genes you know
i hope mine do too i want them also to
live 21 years at least that one would be
lovely yeah this cat he actually clover
has a brother had a brother oh it's one
of the cats i had before who also lived
a really long time who lived to be i
think um
19 or 20.
so yeah their siblings and they both
lived really
really long
wow
still is still kicking
yeah
that's also cool that you know how like
their relatives are doing like my cats
have relatives too but i don't know who
owns them well this is my catalyst as
well i had
his brother as well i had both of them
uh-huh
oh no
is that one of the four cats yeah yeah
that's the one in the [\h__\h]
oh
okay i see
well well my dear fauna
um
thank you very much for playing with me
today yeah this is a lot of fun
it was it was more it left me more
satisfied than um monopoly
yes i know
monopoly i don't know i
i think monopoly might not be a very
good game after we played it i'm like no
it's a cool game it's a good game i
don't know i think any game that's
designed to where you have to
win by utterly destroying your opponent
to where they're they're sad and broken
i'm not sure that's a well-designed game
you have a point but i don't know i
still like it even though i there's like
a
love-hate relationship there
and i want i want to i want somebody
somebody or
cover themselves to create a whole live
monopoly oh that would be amazing but
now you're right
i can't see too many ben
i think that would be really cool
monopoly is a great game if they will
put us on their boards yes
yes
yes i'm sorry you can hear my stomach
rumbling ah i didn't really hear it i
didn't really
hear it don't listen i'm using asmr
microphone right now no i'm not i have
my regular mics hopefully they can't
hear but
well maybe one day
if i ever if i ever
come close to where you live maybe i
might convince you when you come yeah
you should meet my cats now i would love
to sit on this say you're going to teach
me how to do an asmr but yeah
it's more important of course that's the
priority here
yes of course
i would love to uh i need to i need to
come as soon as possible i want to visit
you girls over there yeah
senators are visiting me but i also want
to visit you girls yeah hopefully we can
down
another big meetup
i'll fly over there no matter how long
it takes me probably yeah 14 hours or
something like that
like it's pretty much like europe is
like in the middle so wherever i go it
takes me 11 to 15 hours
that's okay i'm used to it
it's okay
i'm used to it i i just try to sleep
through it it's okay
it could be like that yeah okay thanks
for playing the games
we all got some nice wins yeah it was
fun
it was yeah it was nice talking to you
too nice conversation
about cats
finally was our first one-on-one collab
actually i know yeah
so yeah
yeah definitely a second one on one cool
at any time yeah
prepared i'm ready to meet my um mother
of broccoli again
you're you're what mother of my mother
broccoli
oh
yes
broccoli
oh actually no you know what today was
not our first one-on-one collab
i did a lot of one-on-one collabing
review yesterday in sims
yeah i didn't have a chance to look at
the archive yet but i want to see i want
to see you then
i was taking care of the animals
which is exactly what i went to you were
cleaning and milking the cows you
weren't milking the cows funny
um
you were hugging and petting the chicks
it's it was great you were you are my
pickpins i really want chickens one day
that's one of my goals
really yeah i love chickens they're so
cute and fluffy
yes
you should get them because we have so
many eggs every day yeah it wasn't bad
five eggs ever again fresh eggs man
fresh ones
if you ever need advice about that my
mom um knows a lot about keeping
chickens
you can i can set you up with my mom i
want them one day
all right but that's probably gonna be
quite a bit further in the future when
we have about 10 more cats both of us
yes i won like a whole farm to be honest
i want i want alpacas
too i actually i collect alpacas
oh like the alpaca sauce plushies
yeah all kinds of them like
like cute looking ones from japan but
also like more realistic looking ones
like the ones that are real alpaca yes
yes i have like a couple ones made out
of real alpaca fur they're so fluffy and
so big and i also have a blanket made
out of alpaca food flour fur
by hand and all that so lots of alpacas
yeah yeah
one of my favorite plushies is an alpaca
ah
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes
you could almost say i have an alpaca
farm at home so you can come visit it
yes
many many alpacas
they're so cute and soft yum
have you have you met a real one before
no i don't think i have met a real one i
only can watch them in videos
uh
i've been to an alpaca farm in japan
before
was it amazing and no no no no no not
did they spit on you
it was not the way i dreamed of it
because it was like kind of a rainy day
um and they were not as fluffy as i
thought they would be
yeah they were like they were like wet
and not stinky but
it wasn't so nice the whole ground was
really muddy and
like it was a huge huge farm
and and then
um
indeed like i came um to a spot where
uh there was like a baby alpaca and the
helper um let me carry it
and then i carried it but then the baby
alpaca spit
at me
yes
and it was i'm telling you that is so
stinky
i could not get that smell out of my i
think it was partially in my hair
even after washing my hair once i think
it was still there kind of so i had to
wash my hair several times it was so bad
for them
oh
yeah but it was a cute baby alpaca i
can't be mad at it i still want them i
still want no bad guys
yeah it was probably just because it was
a baby and it was kind of scared or
something but the big ones they behaved
well the the llamas are more the
spitters than the el paso
the big alpacas anyway yeah
yes yes yes yes yeah my mom is also my
mama my mommy is also playing to uh
planning to get some alpacas at some
point as well she's thinking about it
she's living my my dream
your dream yeah
this is what i want whenever i retire
from
whatever whatever i'm retiring from this
is what i want i want to have like a
farm of rescued and that sounds so good
of chicken this is an alpacas
we could work together for that drink
i want that i want a pocket form too
sounds good all right fun and let's talk
about them sometime
let's do it make a big farm i'm sure
amma would probably also be yeah she
probably would too
yeah she seems to me into that kind of
stuff too i think we can have the hollow
hollow animal sanctuary wow yeah we can
rescue all the animals too
let's always let's just buy like a huge
castle and yeah with rescued animals
perfect
a dream come true yes
that's how we invest our money rescue
yeah
i'm not worrying about you know becoming
an old crazy cat lady one day because i
have all this to look forward to
rather than just being a crazy old cat
lady you could always say no you're just
like a shelter for cats yeah
i don't know aren't eccentric old ladies
quite charming you know
quite endearing i've met a charming
eccentric old lady on april 1st and uh
yes i saw her too
oh really yeah
she was she was petting her cats
constantly yeah it looks like finally
her
cats became lap cats after all
dream come true how to learn from learn
from her
yes yes yes
i got a good look at the future let's
just say it like that
all right
fun it's a past midnight for me so i'm
gonna leave you now we should go we're
together i think we can have infinite
tangents
cat tangent the tangent power is is very
strong today but yes
let us say goodbye and let's let us get
some lettuce
lettuce salad broccoli
thank you everyone for watching and
thank you kiara for playing this was a
lot of fun
thank you too
[Music]
i had some time to hang out with you
yeah do you have any announcements
before we go
oh i i put out a new song cover uh yeah
two days ago i think or one day ago it
was so good i loved your singing in that
oh thank you if you guys are interested
it's on my channel
cinderella it's called cinderella but
it's not very cinderella-ish it's more
like a like a really cool
uh
yes i don't i don't really want to it's
your channel i don't want to advertise
my stuff but what thank you advertise
your stuff
no no no no we're not here for
advertising unless you guys want to
work for kfb
join us just kidding
of course all of your people are
vegetarians of course yeah so and
they're going to never join campaigns so
i don't know how good they'll be in the
kitchen
they're not a tree menu though i i did
create while thinking of you i did
create a vegetarian burger oh i wanted
to ask you what you think of my
vegetarian burger
um can i tell you the ingredients and if
you think it would work well if it would
taste good
yeah
it's like a homemade
patty
um well it's it is called first of all
it's called the kusa burger
perfect
the name is already perfect it consists
it consists of a falafel patty oh i love
falafel yeah and then a regular arugula
salad uh-huh
with a also tomato slice in there a big
one
and if you want optionally you can add a
avocado slice
and the sauce is tzatziki sauce
yeah um it will be
vegan satsuki sauce
that sounds really good right i would
eat that for sure i thought about that
very hard and and uh we figured that a
falafel patty with tzatziki sauce would
be a marvelous classic combo
okay so this is fauna proof now i'm
getting the pony stamp right
yes as long as the as long as adding
avocado doesn't cost like four dollars
for actually no it's like 50 cents
probably good good
too many times have i wanted to add
avocado and it's like five dollars
that's probably an exaggeration more
often it's like two dollars but even two
dollars feels like
too much okay so i think we're getting a
good customer in you you'll always get a
burger probably yes
and always add the avocado if it's only
50 cents
yes yes you're welcome at kfp fauna we
think about the vegans the vegetarians
and
the people who eat meat as well so
welcome welcome welcome thank you soon
of course i kind of got to include
everyone kf tree
yes yes i have a tree
okay i'll i'll
i will
take my leave now thank you everybody
i hope i didn't swear too much no you
ain't great
all right bye bye
bye
bye fun well fun wow everybody
thank you
[Music]
foreign