hello oh my gosh are we good oh my
goodness
wow that was a loud one that was a loud
one
hello everyone hello a loud one no let
me kind of Crank that down just
shall we start out Liza introduction and
audio test everyone say their name one
by one and we test each other's audio in
each other's streams yes
am I loud am I quiet what do you think
guys on the other streams
it's fine to me next up who wants to go
next
uh hello testing test test test Emilia
Watson hello everyone whoa whoa whoa
okay thank you thank you
okay I'm gonna say something again
fantastic hello one two three hello
all good all good
next time
howdy check one two oh wow that was loud
for me
hi hello let me turn that down goodness
gracious me I did not realize excuse me
hi my name is uh clappy Murray first
Apprentice Grim Reaper you guys know the
deal hey what's good please die that's
all oh please
I'll die a second time today
okay well you've already filled your
quota then so never mind thank you we're
good all right
good good girl girl say something
yeah okay okay
next
oh man hit that just the way is that not
just the way
hello
[Music]
oh no not the mouse they are still loud
and she's not allowed to me
hello all right OBS decided to set all
my audio settings to default for some
reason
mommy didn't start her streaming oh yeah
oh yeah yeah don't worry you guys yeah
okay I'm just setting up the Discord
thingy stuff okay I will be live in a
moment yeah
live in a moment please wait dark
[Music]
ah the moon's pretty today
the server is coming together so nicely
it's so pretty
all right we're gonna go to the game now
I think so too
um yeah well I think uh we should all
bring uh the stuff that we need and the
chest or two chests so that we can put
it all down safely uh in the in the uh
stronghold
in science so we we have a lot of armor
like in in case we lose it uh we want
some of them some of that in the in the
yeah over there
if you girls planned on doing the bad
strategy but in any case you could bring
at least one block yeah sleep there and
have a safe time so bring your beds
okay you want me to make a chest
uh yeah just bring one chest I guess for
your safe to keep your your belongings
safe once we get there
never mind I just remembered this word
right yeah
I can make more
definitely not gonna chop someone's tree
down not not this time this time no no
other people's trees
what else
I didn't tell them to sleep in the end
I'm telling them to bring a bed to sleep
and before going into the portal so that
we if we die we don't go all the way
back to our it's the ultimate payback
attitude
I got a tip that we should bring bottles
to like capture the Ender breath or
something yeah capture the stinky dragon
breath okay
bottles
yeah
you can just bring some glass and you
can just make a whole bunch of bottles
too
oh I hope I'm lost in the forest it's
really dark I didn't make a bun okay not
like that
where I put my glass like I forget where
I put everything
oh this is a very beautiful area it
might belong to someone I don't know if
I have the the
hands-free to be capturing breath I mean
one person can be hitting the dragon
oh my God
I think you just put you just use the
glass where it's like doing the breath
attack
oh
yeah
Hey where's the diamond armored
let me tell you all right so if you go
uh if you're on the way to my house yes
all the way to my house you will see two
chests
I am standing there as well the left
chest has armor everyone may take uh
two sets I guess
for themselves okay
I don't have many I didn't get many
weapons but
for sure we need to bring food or this
shouldn't be like a
I can't bring food we should probably
always yes we have people too
oh yeah and um after you guys are done
prepping come to my come to my house I
can give you guys some
uh slow falling potions so you don't die
oh yeah I need I need some shoes
um
uh two golden apples from the chest
where the armor is in as well everyone
gets two golden apples okay
foreign
okay
um
Auto sword inventory win what is that
why do you have that no huh
I didn't know you can have an Ender
Chest before going to just eat um
oh
[Music]
yeah yeah
one more set it was literally there and
two sets total okay yeah and then a
golden apple stack right
we have the two two golden apples yep
yep what is super thanks okay
it's fine I'm just gonna I'm just going
on a little journey excess access work
uh if you like the sword is better if
you do like quick uh hits but the ax
does more damage if you do like
shorter slower hits I guess does that
make sense yeah
it's a heavy a single Target yeah yeah
Florida's AOE attack the sword is quick
damage light damage I'm gonna start all
my junk in these chests
LG
okay you guys got the food
got cookies cookies okay come on cookie
ah water book bucket and I wonder if we
want to bring like something like
scaffolding you guys definitely want
some I have some water
I'll bring sand all right forget this
guys I gotta look at the um I have a
bucket maybe not seven what is it okay
the coordinates the coordinates
nothing to buy puffs up right
no no no your graphics card I'm just
kidding
was it F3
I've played this game in so long so yes
are you lost yeah Kelly yup I'm lost
um which is the ferris wheel went to go
get nope went to go get some wood so I
could make a chest but everything around
our areas is owned so I had to kind of
go outside of the area the trees are
known I'll give you a tree a tree I'll
give you a chest if you want yeah just
can't touch anything anymore okay what
is the X what is the X Y middle area I
can't well I I don't know where I am
what is the XY
don't don't hide
Phantoms is it 70 what is it
they can someone tell me where they are
someone please tell me can someone
please tell me where they are
please give me the coordinates please
of where we are you mean what is this
uh X
uh freehand to 26. okay why 79 well y
doesn't really matter and set minus 481
wait out I can minus 401 gotcha
okay
I didn't hit anything uh hello cat
hello yeah they're afraid of cats so
they were attacking us
oh really yeah yeah
that's how I got a lot of the membranes
for the potions
so by the way I'm Brad I'm I'm bringing
sand in case we want to go up to the
towers with sand instead of shooting
them and I'm bringing dirt because we
probably have to build like a bridge
from our portal to
uh the actual main island and what did I
say the coordinates wrong 330.
and that is x and z is minus wait sorry
it was not 400 it was wait what is that
no no minus 480.
and 417 something like that
how did I get this far away I was just
trying to retrace your steps and I was
like what where where did you go
I mean I was walking in the darkness
sorry for yet another delay you guys I
had to continue being useless at least
once
this is basically like getting ready for
the family trip you know yeah everyone
everyone gets ready
when am I gonna get there
are we there
are there yet
what the hell am I talking about I'm
telling her the right coordinates
Chad are you trolling
you I am correct you guys are incorrect
idiots
they must be thrown up
yeah
except yeah thank you Ina thank you
enough
there you see it more clearly
[Music]
this is turning out to be a bad morning
this is a bad morning baby enjoying this
it's Cali I don't know we we all don't
know where she is
oh wait I thought the last time you
played you were like uh doing the ferris
wheel or no oh I know I I was um a
couple minutes ago I went to go make a
chest
um so I went into the darkness and I
went looking for wood and I made sure to
go far away
Mickey Mouse players in Minecraft where
you like shoot it up into the air
yeah
a flare
if you look into the sky do you see some
of our monuments or like the do you see
this guy
I'm thinking about just dying guys like
at this point
I think I think the problem is that
we're giving her our base coordinate
when she's all the way in Phoenix town
where the [\h__\h] yeah
oh uh I I just want to die guys I I
honestly I just like reset
Callie
how to find a dark darkness no God what
is this sheep
stay away you are Callie where are you
tell me your coordinates okay
2.99 299 10.99 77 which doesn't matter
and then this is the one that's effing
me up that I can't see negative
692. it's real is it down
oh not really I guess
oh I think I kind of know where you are
Maybe
I don't know
I'm on my way
[Music]
um
is Ina if you're already going then I'll
stay yeah I'm already on my way you're
better with coordinates can you write
sorry not Cali so I can yeah one sec
hang on
oh sorry okay let's see are you on snow
or grass right now
I'm on grass
uh-huh
glass
she couldn't have gone far yeah exactly
right and there's only one
only one place we can go where there's
trees
pressing on this way
is somebody bringing a leash
so she doesn't get please please do oh
sorry I don't believe it was like a
[\h__\h] leash one of those baby ones
that strap around your chest
oh yeah there's three of them yes and
people like to walk their children yes
one person with three children and
they're like all over the place mommy
shark put me on one of those
oh what color oh
it was like green tartan
print plaid
okay what are the coordinates Cali all
right 305 for x and negative 692 for Z
and you have five
negative what six
I'm thinking like Cali
it's like something that's why I was
calling okay
so I gotta go to Negative X
wow where did you go 305 negative six
nine two I just walked into the darkness
really
just tried to go somewhere away from the
camp turned around couldn't find the
camp anymore
I'm gonna get up on a pillar
okay
what about figures that checks out
like you you got lost really quickly
that might be a record uh that really
probably was a world record
it's definitely a world record yeah we
saw a difference
honestly it would not be surprised would
not be surprised if I was
okay
and closer
smell Cali but it's negative 692 by the
way I'm on a tall pillar
I see it I see
um Kiara and uh because I was about to
say Kiara incusatori Kiara
I think it's kind of hard to miss the um
what's it kind of hard to miss the giant
stairway
yeah there is a giant stairway right
above me too you should follow that yeah
I guess I should okay please just let me
signs of civilization
follow the moss covered rocks oh I came
all the way here for this freaking wood
I will sit here and I will hit it with
my hand until I get it even though my ax
has now just broken
I will hit it with my hand because I got
lost for this wood
determination
hey who was that are you guys all ready
to go by the way remember this uh yeah
please no literally holy [\h__\h] much
[Music]
too
yet I didn't listen to myself
anymore
why don't you even use insects for they
seem useless and ugly ink
it's a stress ball
ER Hotel
just tasting I need to practice
you buckets
did I hit you
all right I'm on my way back oh I
thought I hit it yeah I guess I guess
you're back in base Cali
okay good I have a bucket do you need a
bucket
sorry I have a lot of buckets oh I also
have some drinks
please Rendezvous a Taco Bell you guys
think we can clean some of those those
Minecraft mini games have you seen the
like the Minecraft mini game servers do
you do anymore oh yeah yeah
we could mod our own I could do it
probably it's on the couch maybe a lot
of fun you know
I I you know I'm a Lost Child
slowly slowly all right where's Ina
um
it's too old before not until now I
found the cow welcome
[Music]
we deliver everything from humans wait
oh tape Where'd I get this from
okay
all right Cali in here
okay uh welcome
here please
put chest I can give you one
oh it's okay I have one I made one it's
okay I went out of my way to make one
don't worry everyone
come over here to my to my lab study
time yes open up the right chest and
take some slow falling potions
okay you'll need it you got it this time
I got it now I got it thanks for the
clap clap chat I appreciate it always
clap clap clap it's been a rough morning
uh slow falling potions I think you can
take uh
five one two three yeah I need to take
some photos how many can we take I'm
sorry yina uh four or five I forget oh
four five okay
yeah I mean I'll take the leftovers
myself so don't worry yeah
oh you can't yeah can I have buckets
five each five oh yeah you can open up
uh
there's seven in this chest over here
and there's like four on the outside one
yeah
so feel free to take
okay thank you for all the preparation
you guys did this is really helpful you
guys are amazing Sasuke
wow yeah do you have any extra under
pearls on you
I have one yeah if you guys have any
extras could you
maybe carry some because I'll I'll bring
some place Ross just in case you know
our eye breaks before we find
okay
I have like a boy
I have three and the pearls
uh as for diamond armor is that in front
of Kiara's place yes come to my house
okay
did everyone else already take their
sets of armor that you should like take
probably two but what if we die and burn
and then they all burn but if we die
then we'll just spawn back and spawn and
then we can try to meet back up in the
yeah wait I forgot
wait yeah did you take the under chest
Where'd I put Thunder chest I didn't
take the end of a chin
from myself
okay
yes I see you
left chest here it is uh please take two
two full sets of armor yes ma'am okay
thank you
one you shall wear yeah
the other one in case you die and lose
it
okay oh yeah and then on the right side
okay how do you say shield in Japanese
like what the hell happened here
please take one of the diamond axes
one of the bowls one of them uh maybe
the the second the first row second one
oh yeah okay I'll see you I guess you
can also take that back door
iron sword okay
and then one of the um
one stack of arrows okay one stack of
arrows golden
no the normal ones the golden ones are
not really not really useful yes did you
take an ax as well no the diamond one
the diamond one um
asking all the questions
so now let's actually take one more one
more Bowl because you might lose one
[Music]
which one should I take any of them ah
it doesn't matter
as long as it shoots it's strong
all right and one stack of arrows okay
yeah
um I am also bringing some snowballs but
I don't have many uh you know didn't you
also get to know those are you bringing
them too oh yeah I was gonna make some
snowman Oh I thought it was a shield
guys
why do we need snowballs for
to shoot the towers uh like there's
Towers then you just gotta shoot the top
and the Snowballs are really good for
that I think oh okay guys I'm gonna
build a snowman
you guys know it might be fun
wait Kelly did you get the gold uh you
have to take sorry one more thing the
two golden apples from the chest oh yes
ma'am I'll go ahead and do that
nice crossbow
um
one helmet damn it
Vibes here
[Music]
okay I'm feeling better guys I'm feeling
better now
your arm my arm
I think I should be good there's
somebody more responsible one to hold
the scaffolding because I do not trust
myself
[Music]
often you trust in me
believe in you that believes in you
should I have a pickaxe you guys
[Music]
are you using OptiFine or maybe somebody
was saying might be a shade or just I
don't think so I don't know I am oh you
are okay you must be up to fun then
because you have the three of us yeah
it's turned off oh yeah I should bring
some shovels and stuff too I forgot
it's free to dig
chant I'm so Glory
oh
okay
enough can I give you
um the free enterprise that I have oh
yeah sure
don't lose everything we're safe oh yeah
oh shoot them down so we can get their
membranes
come give me your brains where are you
where are they oh the wrong kind of
membranes but membrane that's like when
when the membrane wall of assist have
you ever seen cyst removals you have to
remove the membrane wall otherwise the
cyst will grow back oh
whoa that's nice
shots shots
absolutely it's one yeah beautiful shots
I can't see anything oh all right so are
we ready
yeah we can start the car yeah everyone
got their snacks you got food snacks
buckle up yep
good all right
[Applause]
[Music]
are we sleeping
it's horrifying yeah I guess so let's go
to sleep
[Music]
there's another bed over here
I think I'll have to go inside the house
can you stop that please stop please
okay okay
sleeping through this night oh
oh there we go all right good morning
everyone
it's time Cali in front of your house
there's a zombie I will destroy it okay
who's gonna be a ball faster it's very
kind to me there's a lot of enemies out
here oh my oh my God why are they after
me are you okay oh yes yes I will just
run so much for oh
alien torches outside your house wait
wait wait there Callie okay I'm not
moving or a scally
right
[Music]
come with me quickly can you take the
ender pearls out of the chest I have a
full inventory okay not this test inside
my house
girl tosser
am I the cheater
that's what they're called right oh
thank you
yeah let's just keep our eyes all right
all right because I have to I have to
grab a chip I'm sorry my stomach hurts
so bad
just enough to not hurt my stomach hold
on
I have a sausage that's supposed to be
spicy but ever since I ate those spicy
noodles nothing has ever been as spicy
thank you for the sausage
okay
[Music]
um
I'm guessing we're not doing the bad
strategy right because I'm breaking I'm
bringing wood and we'll so if you if you
need to make more bets then I have one
two three four five six seven eight but
maybe nine um okay
I think I can't do it normally two but
yeah
normally two depends
oh the pain is going away thank you
everyone okay everyone has checklist
everyone has armor yes everyone has
weapons yes everyone has emeralds yes
everyone has slow falling potions yes
everyone has two golden apples yeah
everyone has a foot some kind of food
yes I have some leftover in case
everyone has uh one chest at least
oh no no I can make it
I mean we probably have enough space
yeah okay and
one or more but more than one water
buckets they could be I mean I don't
know if you if you were if all of us are
that skilled I'm probably not skilled
enough but I brought a couple of water
buckets and because if you fall down
then you can do it and then you land in
the water I have a boat um I guess that
works too yeah probably I don't know
okay
yeah get into it at the right time I
guess now
and I have some building material I
don't think we all need a building
material because yeah just one of us
so as long as I don't push each other
off
okay
okay I'll put some water buckets back or
do I I'll just bring them along whatever
okay let's go yeah let's go all right
I just gotta toss this right and it'll
go towards it yeah yes keep your eyes on
it though because I think you can
collect it again
yeah oh yeah
how do I toss it no idea
whoa they went that way right
behind us wait what we lost it it didn't
even like it usually it travels and then
it pings that ping right away are we um
what
and
I think it went down uh I mean just just
wait here let me see if it works at the
ground
I kind of threw like
horizontally yeah okay
uh
you said chances I went the opposite way
maybe opposite way I went behind oh
there's no way
how far does it go
I don't know uh I have 15 left go try to
look for your heart
okay I'll go see the slit see if it
[Music]
move the extra ones because I will be
lost Sparkle
follow up
hello
you need blade water and the Pearl's
body Ina has all that stuff yeah
her eyes
and it's in another I don't know I don't
know that's what I thought I didn't know
I don't know oh you can do it anywhere
just gotta turn off Katie
it doesn't go that far okay I don't
think we'll find it
in like five minutes probably is there a
radius like if we know a block radius
then we can do like a you know a
circular sweep yeah I think there's a
limit how far it goes but
it's difficult the other way oh we can
calculate from where you know through it
and then we can set it up maybe maybe
throw another one it didn't go that far
because it pinged really quickly
okay so let's go back to the original
one and then search
10 to 15 blocks away from the corner
that you know threw it that's so close
yeah that is pretty close where the heck
I'm sure we're just missing it it could
have broken apparently
ah yeah that's true they break sometimes
right away that was it probably this is
probably broken
okay I'm gonna group up and throw
another one everyone
I'm coming back to Akira's roof or
on the roof roof start there again look
at party ladies
how's that off okay
oh
I I I I look I looked all right
three two one
what what I lost it again it's like a
distance
I don't see anything I was in third
person so I was looking and I didn't see
anything yeah it actually literally just
jumped behind are we all using shaders
unders yeah it says it went down
but I I checked in the case you know I
mean the Kiara's house it's not here I
wonder if it is a shaders thing
[Music]
no I turned off shaders
uh are we right above it
no way there's no way there's no way
and we then we would have probably like
dug into it with Amelia's underground
Subway turns way further that way like
to the left but maybe we should dig
straight down from where you're throwing
it in Kiara's house
Kiara your house is Olivia
under construction you're forbidden to
use it from now on what
I mean try I mean we can try dig down
but
somebody says oh it's not a good idea
it's not a good idea before we saw the
pearls though should we there's no
nowhere all right let's see I have one
too
okay let's try throwing it somewhere
else let's go into a flat field like uh
is there anything yeah my cabin
like near the ocean
oh okay like the flower feels we'll go
back to the cabin yeah like like behind
my houses
yeah
don't worry guys I definitely know where
my cabin is it's just not optimal don't
let your dreams be me dreams we will
finish the cabin
ET
so we already wasted two of those and uh
I have one I think I'm happy to offer it
wait is it in the pearl yeah
I have enough space rods so as long as
there's pearls that's what we need
tell them what
the pearl of travel towards her house
all right this is not very flat are you
sure you're is this what you consider
flat Ina
um
no no you had to do it to him
surrounded by water
yeah
[Music]
uh still alive
we're gonna test at her house over there
we can do that that looks flat
okay
and you want a ride
I would like a ride actually I have a
boat we can use
all right
cool all right
flat
[Music]
yellow soda this cake
it's getting dark
I got a trident on it
wait I tried it thank you all right yeah
this is welcome have you seen your cape
all right pretty cool
all right
I'm sorry okay
wait wait wait wait wait wait I'm not
there yet hold on oh my God it's gonna
be dark
please
[Music]
okay good
towards Ina's Shrine I guess one person
I'm throwing a towards the shrine ruin
I'm gonna look around our village
in the ground I thought you want to
throw it towards like
Shrine some people think oh it's worse
the sky that throws the ground like what
if we need to sleep
slumber party ladies
Outdoors camping
okay
I'll see about your feet
yeah
but what did you say finish what
get a smelly feet
what all right
okay oh maybe if we go maybe enough you
go really high up like on a on some
blocks like this oh okay oh dear all
right let's go easy block okay dirt
would you like a dirt block I'm too high
though because is this good I think
that's good
all right I'm gonna throw it towards
towards the Tory gate okay everyone
ready
I was like a hawk okay three two one
oh
did you see it I didn't expect it it's
right here
should we build the bridge then
is it underwater
don't we have to keep throwing it that
way until it goes down yeah
again okay
oh there it goes It's Working
is it there oh no it went I got it one
more okay should we throw again uh let's
do it from the toy gate it doesn't seem
yeah good idea
you want to throw that one uh you do it
you know it's fine I messed it up
okay
oh wow like really far
oh
no God well maybe the last two times
just broke
that would be pretty unlucky
do we have to I mean we still have like
three spare ones what should we do here
like should we make a bridge or should
we just go in that direction and then do
it again I feel like the bridge is just
gonna be wasting blocks possibly we have
other boats because if we have the other
other boats we could just go in this
direction a little bit yeah
let's go this way until we reach land
yeah I got a bowl who needs a boat I
don't have a boat
thank you gura yes thank you for the
ride one more book let me check in this
chest oh yeah there should be one more
Lobby road on the way here
[Music]
all right I'm coming
what is that oh it's a trident fart
right I built that it's just like a
turkey
okay I'm gonna throw it again hold on
all right
oh okay okay keep calling the Slime
again you know I think we can go a bit
further before the next one because yeah
we're wasting them do you still have
enough you think yeah tall girls 12 plus
three pearls and five plays Rose and
that makes like a couple of Colors Let's
go until we get to land and then uh
[Music]
we have like a perimeter to check this
feels so cool you guys underwater
it could be
done
walking on water damn
what a Pro Gamer I'm a
super oh Pro game okay
I'll go until
um
yeah okay
let's go dolphin
I'm the photographer
I'm taking pictures of us
beautiful
on the way to the Ender Dragon yeah
we're gonna go right up the Ender Dragon
where am I I'm gonna look up epic
Minecraft music all right copyright RTA
let's go
to this Minecraft playlist that I'll put
on like a 10 hour playlist while I play
okay
when everyone gets here
we'll see hold on
I'm gonna play all the nether tracks
oh yeah good idea
oh hello sorry
can I play
another Minecraft yeah look up the
nether tracks
craft tracks no that'll give you remixes
from from other music producers okay so
look up yeah use the nether ones
Minecraft soundtrack all another tracks
2020.
500 sounds trustworthy
everyone here no yes
[Music]
oh she's because she's Googling stuff
hold on
[Music]
um
going in three two one point
oh
we'll go further then we'll get a break
yeah it didn't break it fell
okay
this music is me anxiety
let's keep going for like a couple
minutes yeah how many blocks maybe like
500 blocks is there like only one or is
there like oh we're back at Water maybe
we should go to where those trees
I lost you girls me and Kelly are too
far away from you girls I'm not the only
one yes I'm not the only one that's lost
anymore
uh oh come on I see it I see some names
I found found you Cal you following yeah
yeah go to the top of the hill and you
oh wait hello oh I see them hello hello
um let's have another book
uh about that I can make one I can make
one I'm gonna take that I don't know
I'm joining me yes
all right together how far do we go
okay
wait I have someone's
bed
not mine
[Music]
involved
both
thank you
all right let's go drive girl Drive
drift
Summit drift oh
there was an effort
maybe we should go to the top of the
mountain and then
yeah yeah maybe yeah yeah
let's see is there only one or is there
multiple welcome to the mountains
is there multiple yeah that's the one
there we go yay
there's tons okay okay so I guess it's
just the one we're closest to uh-huh
we should have rollerblades
that'd be sick and go faster
oh those are like speed potion speed
running potions that'd be cool
there's a sloth rails over here yeah
yeah or another another rail
thank you
I also saw like a like a support that is
really close
I'm relatively close I guess
what's what's close I can't wait for
everybody take a little further
uh sure okay just a little
maybe like on top of the yeah
[Music]
all right unexplored territory
it would have been good to bring a map
oh fill in the map zip it
we would have needed a really big map
though if he went real far yeah that's
true I want to make a map of these stuff
shift
yeah
all right that's right here
let's see yeah I'm gonna throw it okay
tree
oh
how is that naturally possible pumpkins
all right guys well which is but I went
straight ah there you are oh okay okay
oh there you go okay three two one
please
wait oh it went the other way okay so
we're here then oh
oh
so now we turn back around we got to
reach Tracer yeah that's interesting so
we use the eye to look for a portal
right yeah we gotta do that one under
the ground oh yeah we got a triangulate
whatever and then we break Minecraft's
number one rule don't dig down that's
what you do I'm gonna throw from here I
love this check
welcome to dig down I will stay behind I
don't want to lose all the stuff [\h__\h] I
did not make a shovel wait where are you
wait I have a shovel I have a shovel I
have a shovel oh llamas
but hey where'd everyone go but happy
Watson oh a mess
yeah let's be on the threes trust me on
the trees okay okay on the way
it's getting dark
hey let's do it one more time before
before it gets dark yes
actually helps
this way guys
no
you have inventory I have one in your
hand yeah yeah I have 11. I need stuff
well it broke okay it broke okay
oh it's stuck on the train on top of it
no it's all on the ground yeah I don't
see it oh it's real dark sleep over time
ladies
sleep soon
[Music]
over there
thank you okay
[Music]
hurry that break it is on the tree but I
thought it still hit the ground what
it's on the creek
I mean we can check hold on oh I have
your oh it's right there I see it there
it is
so much for hearing it no you're on my
bed
[Music]
okay 12. that was your heartbreaking
right you're wrong okay
all right here oh this is nice and open
I don't know anymore me too me too okay
oh oh okay that way
oh oh okay
I kfp workout we do it like at the edge
of this Cliff here yeah
[Music]
watermelons
oh
stand here oh okay and stay they put sit
I can stay
[Music]
I'm really good at standing still and
not doing anything
yeah so the one thing I'm great at this
game
um
yeah someone stands like somewhere here
getting close foreign
yes ma'am
okay so it has to be somewhere like
around here yeah
can I move I already moved
hold on
yeah let's stick where we're amazing oh
okay okay
how far down is it yeah I don't know
until he's far down I think
all right ladies I can help oh no she's
digging straight down
um she'll be fine
okay I'll pick somewhere around here
you'll know that because the stones will
change it'll look like brick Stones I
should probably stay with someone I
don't have a pickaxe you realize
I opened up a cave here there's a cave
down here oh
babe
I'm gonna build some stairs we can Mosey
our way down oh yeah good idea should
have brought torches
I have torches
I
dropped the water uh if you guys want to
jump in my hole
all right wait no I'm gonna throw it in
here like uh oh but I guess it'll go
through the wall huh
I have I have no space in my inventory
well if there's a case though then
there's a there's a chance it's okay
they'll they'll they'll find it
okay I'm gonna stay with you I have no
clue nice
shirts okay I'm gonna start digging down
again just to see
I found it
[Music]
ah there oh
okay I'll put torches outside
oh yeah it's kind of a long way down you
might wanna
okay this is amazing hi so I'm here hold
on there's a creeper head count wait
hold on one okay
well this is cool
and can you open the door for me yeah
yeah there we go oh
there you go
okay nothing here nothing
it's amazing
oh wow so it's like that huh okay so
excited
this is so cool
there's like stairs here all right
nothing we should maybe
water
is that possible
I think so
oh my God oh my God oh my God there's a
lot of people here I don't have any more
uh torches I ran out
don't look at him don't look at him holy
[\h__\h] yeah
got it
okay okay
so awesome
there's a treasure music
there's uh it can be behind a false wall
as well I know there's like cheeky uh uh
uh joke walls
are you doing Watson uh throwing away
blocks
it's
oh
that was scary
this library is so cool
yeah I probably shouldn't try and hit
the spiderwebs we can take them yeah
I've hit the spider webs of the sword
they go down really fast oh cool thanks
oh I think I found it nice there's a
ladder I want parts to get rid of the
spawner though
oh that was that was Ashley Espana that
was really a spot yeah I'm gonna borrow
a torch
here I can give you some I didn't look
at you I did not look at you I just want
to speak yeah
oh you did find it yeah
wait there's like literally no eyes
huh
um
you know what I have exactly enough I
found one more left to make
we're good everyone here
oh my gosh okay yeah someone Mark found
the coordinates for this oh yeah
good idea okay
got it I got the screenshot it's great
let me make sure I'm absolutely prepared
chest should you put on the chest guys
oh yeah
ladies
yeah bed and chest
stupid boy
uh
um
ouch ouch what the hell oh you gotta get
it
oh my God what the frick is wrong with
you
what do we do defense
there's a thing you gotta kill it
they come out of the the walls and stuff
what are we starting in the chest
um like your second set of armor and uh
silverfish
maybe some arrows stop it
some some of the potions we only need
probably one for now
no
that was not me I did not do that oh my
goodness
get rid of them
this is
dangerous
what the hell the bed is about to burn
does it have to be Lava underneath the
portal
well if there's no lab on the pool it'll
really break it for some reason I can't
leave
[Music]
in the lava
yes okay we don't we don't need the lava
hey yeah
okay so let me put my what is sorry
I don't know they don't look edible how
about the uh the potions you guys the
slow following the potion yeah yeah
maybe bring in one one only for now I
think oh yeah because it's pretty dark
yeah I don't have any I want it to me
leave it to me
foreign
I'm putting two books into the chest but
those are those are um mine
it's bad as spawn point yeah okay
um
pickaxe oh yeah I will bring it that's
okay
everyone ready
[Music]
can we take a group picture can everyone
get on the stairs okay I want to take a
picture yeah
[Music]
I have a really cool Cape too
though yeah no yeah level one look to
the front and yeah
I want one too
please okay
I got it thank you me too yay
damn it when you put the under chest
here
wait if the front people use the under
chest does that mean
they have their own storage
I opened yours earlier and I didn't see
anything in it oh that means you guys
can use it too
oh well
okay well I'll put
it
looks like
oh
okay are you in okay okay
let's take a plunge
when you go in what do we do
just jump in
maybe not all at once because we don't
know how big the platform is when we
land and I push each other from where we
stand I'm gonna go first I'm nervous
okay
Watson all right how is it is it is it
very nice I can't see [\h__\h] wait guys
okay it's a small platform
um you guys can oh God do we have
building the dragons right here right
here oh no material
okay
yeah everyone ready no yeah should I be
holding something specific you guys are
holding blocks
yeah to build but yeah to build yeah
I'll help
uh do we use the you know do you think
we should use the falling potion right
away I think when we when we go in we
can use it when we start the trip let me
start fighting okay also uh Kelly don't
there is a lot of Endermans down there
like a [\h__\h] ton um when you go up to the
dragon try to look down because there's
really an army of Ender Dragons don't
look at them they will kill you once you
look at one of them
but Kelly remember we're not fighting
the ender men because that's a fight we
cannot win we try to fight the Ender
Dragon I don't have any more okay and we
can hit that one right
I have to make a bridge you guys yeah
okay
okay all right I'm waiting I'm ready now
ready
one
I'm loading look just wait it's just
loading okay yeah
climatically what the hell it broke
I don't know is this working yeah
do you feel me
I'm inside someone too
you guys look cool he was a badass whoa
I think we should probably make a bridge
over to the bigger plot for me for me
that was too much the portal is too
powerful
what is this place
this is cool okay
I don't know who wants to it felt wrong
Bridge
materials oh here I can I 52.
I also have a lot
okay
[Music]
because the close to our left or should
we just build
s here but when I think we should go to
the main main uh platform over there
where the dragon is
okay
I am in the end
just let Ahmed do her her thing okay
don't go push her what the hell you
won't get anything back
is that normal
what does the sky look like noise to you
as well guys yeah
it doesn't look like that in uh
[Music]
we need to put walls up yeah okay okay
can you I have a question do you know
when you go into The Nether and that
thing that goes can you and you can like
hit him hit the Fireballs back at it can
you do that with the Ender Dragon
I don't think what is the smoke can I
walk into it no that's that's fire on
the ground that's the Ender Dragon's
life oh okay okay
we can't build a puppet
oh God
yeah
oh wow I'm in bad shape right now oh
okay this is bad
this is the best we need to build okay
I'm gonna
yeah yeah
yep it how do we make the fire stop
oh God
don't come in here don't come in yeah
that's a good idea turning off shaders
my baby oh man it collects more
materials
please collect my items please [\h__\h]
um
does it break walls also
it doesn't break
all right we'll have to build your walls
there get your stinky breath out of here
scaly
thing's still there by chance you guys
your stuff is all still here you just
gotta get here okay I'm coming well
actually maybe not for Kelly okay
yeah Fire's done you can come in okay
that's fine I'm not gonna start over the
game
I want my things
all right I got a bunch of stuff oh my
God the diamond armor is already so low
we really should have brought all of it
yeah
one sec you guys
[Music]
okay don't don't walk towards the the
platform yeah
hello Mr Dwayne whoa thank you wait
what's up
oh [\h__\h]
um
it probably game doesn't work anymore
without shaders
I'm in danger
all right
building stairs you really want me to
step outside
I chose
1.171.1 the most recent release
this isn't great guys oh
sure my bow and arrows are gone
um maybe I leave my stuff here for you
guys
please
[Music]
thank you Watson you don't have to
all right
you sure there's there's more outside
do we go outside
Catch the Fire
um I'll go in with um
well turn off the shaders like uh
manually I'll put your eyes in the Sky
What's home
is
[Music]
are you are you guys already fighting a
dragon oh no not yet
oh no
um
oh where where is the setting again guys
okay
no he can't fit in here so okay let me
kill him
did we try to kill him
I mean the others can't see it I mean
this one's already angry so does anyone
have a pickaxe so I can you can't you
can't use uh arrows or arranged attack
for Enderman yeah
so I don't know I think some stuff
ladies and gentlemen yeah
uh
can we get the main platform I died
exactly what Cali died so whoever picked
up Cali stuff might have my stuff
okay
should I turn off shaders did you guys
turn them off or did a message I turned
it off
we have to reload the game if you turn
them off
yes oh my god oh that's bad
I'm coming thank you thank you because
here is a bit safer to give me my stuff
thank you
okay that's a better idea it should feel
one side of armor and like some dirt
blocks some arrows um I only have I only
have one set
[Music]
but you're wearing one side and you have
one nope I'm I'm only wearing the one
that I have where are you guys this is
your this is definitely yours we have
Trax here you go
anger
everything that you have is myself
that's okay
do you have my dirt block they have an
error
yeah wait can somebody kill me so I can
go back okay you know what you keep half
the um
[Music]
no it's fine it's fine there's more
stuff she asked me to
hear stream heart Challenger the ax yeah
yeah
can you bring me one uh yeah we need one
full set of armor because we're sharing
right now yeah there's two full sets
here so I'll bring I don't have one
either
[Music]
oh do you have uh oh damn it the golden
apples uh I have two here I got to check
I just need one one of them
uh
[Music]
a few more arrows please
who is missing armor right now me me and
Kelly yeah I'm missing pants and boots
she has the top cards I have the bottom
Parts okay okay there's enough
uh there's only one bow oh
[Music]
but there's wood I think I can make some
but they won't be enchanted
uh can you bring some building blocks
just in case
yeah
how do we leave do we just leave the
game
oh you have to die all right can I leave
these things here and then come back you
guys
yeah you'll be able to hold my things
real quick
yeah my thing's yes oh yeah I guess
technically yeah yeah oh wow that's loud
all right I'm going to go
be right back okay good luck on my glass
bottles
oh I'm holding a shield
God I'm such an idiot
all right well I got regular bows wait
okay wait what What
potions the top
God [\h__\h] damn it look
s oh it's cool
we have that three armor tops here three
pants okay
one full all right whatever
one full set nothing much
don't don't make anything else for me
please just keep it you guys I always
survive
two sets for everyone so there should be
uh one more set for you and one more set
for me it is missing but I know I have
everything sorry I have it in right now
I was gonna go back with it hold on I'm
gonna be right back
yeah because we could store everything
can I shoot this thing or is it gonna
come after us
depends on what the things
I mean it's gonna heal itself because we
still have the crystals get rid of oh
okay
I have shoes and pants
thank you mint ice cream anyone destroy
the crystals all right Chad
[Music]
speedrunners always have like the uh the
like the program outlines turned on and
stuff it's really [\h__\h] oh oh hi I mean
we just gotta get good and shoot it
thank you
I gotta get good I gotta get into this
ice cream first though crystals are the
things making the beams yeah
okay
nice nice weather here too how's the
weather up there you know
it's a little bit cloudy with the chance
of dragon fireballs
what material is this is it like sponge
can I take the potion I think it's Ender
Stoners whatever yeah Ender sponge
what do I do with this glass bottle to
capture something oh yeah yeah I don't
don't worry about it I guess yeah in
phase two of Ender Dragon it'll come
down and do like a breath attack okay is
it okay to eat the apple now probably
yeah right yeah yeah
wait all right wait where's Cali Cali
said she uh oh I think she can't
re-enter the game I can't re-enter the
game now it says the server is outdated
yeah that's because you turned up the
shaders out
um I had the same thing just now you
have to download or update no use use
the option that it says OptiFine the
normal one that used up until now then
once the screen is open uh you click
into options and turn it off manually
um before logging into the Minecraft
server okay uh you know where you can
choose the Minecraft servers before you
click that you go on options and then
turn off uh at Graphics settings you go
to uh shaders and then turn off the
Shader manual okay
thank you yeah I feel like I feel like
I can't believe when she gets no please
don't give me anything anymore
[Music]
not here
don't don't touch my stuff I'm on my way
you heard her don't touch it I'm not
touching it
all right she's back in the Yukata for
Revenge you need a minute hey I got some
dragon's breath oh nice
don't move for myself yeah
of course tell me guys when you're ready
[Music]
that was sensory overload Captain hold
on I need a what song is this this is
nice
okay video settings and then
let's see
graphic settings yes
sorry keep keep focusing on the game
sorry once uh I need food I need food I
need food I'll give the chickens hey I I
think you picked it up again I didn't oh
my God how do we do this okay
is pig step part of the game or is this
a remix
hello do you have food please ah it
sounds I don't know copyrighted
[Music]
I can't pick this [\h__\h] up yeah I got it
thank you
this is not going well uh are you
running around here
are you inside okay okay
we can start trying to destroy the
towers
can I even shoot that far
there's only one hit what the hell one
hit
what is that oh yeah did someone look at
me don't attack me guys don't attack me
bullet's eye I don't know
okay let's go
[Music]
okay I got a problem I got one
did you get Enderman
hi fellas
excuse me no it's generating Health bags
excuse me
why is the water so tiny okay hold on
all right guys oh yeah we gotta do the
palace first okay water all right
ours first oh okay
what am I shooting at I need I need more
arrows no
uh at the top of the towers you're gonna
there's a
um
it's only those with the cages right
yeah
I almost went out the cages we can do we
want you to watch me yeah we're shooting
arrows
come on do it again Kiana you haven't
done it before
can you can you not drag oh no
drink a potion how do you drink a potion
you eat it like food
the third one
not me yeah hold on
you're going up that way okay oh wait
there's one why do you blow these beds
up
[Music]
a chat okay got one okay
I don't have an ax
better I can actually see okay oh right
click all right
um
I have no more emeralds unfortunately
thanks Jeff oh Soulful I appreciate you
guys I'm good it's gonna be okay
I'll find you guys don't worry
I'll never mind
um I can does anyone have arrows I have
some uh okay uh I have Infinity so I can
spare 14 for you I think oh wait um
I think it's free or something I'm I'm
in front of you monkeys
sorry sorry Callie I'm in front of Inna
I see you guys
goodbye Baby Gotta Get the one inside
the cage thank you yep
got it I don't have a pickaxe we can't
help and you don't have any hooks
oh that would be a good idea
I don't even know anymore
I think someone echoed the Enderman use
some water
oh
hold it
foreign
[Music]
oh
don't taking any energy from any of the
towers anymore is that one
does this means
[Music]
oh nice
I hit him I hit him yay how many is the
bed
it's coming down oh well phase two
oh boy
oh wow
oh am I doing anything to it I don't
know I can't see well I think my arrows
are doing anything
I'm kind of far oh no that's doing
something I
think yeah let's go
foreign
excuse me
I'm still gonna win Enderman get lost
yeah bye nerd
where's my stuff where's my stuff
where's my stuff where did I land oh
it's coming back to the middle I think
what did you see myself
it's raining
out
okay you know what uh
taking back some of my water did he
regenerate or not
yeah
oh
you're gonna fire on top of the water
wait it's all picking in Where's my
water
don't I
until oh wait there's water
there's somebody hit the bed
cameras don't work at first time that
would be too easy huh yeah
all right
I hit the bed nice oh my God
I am dealing with some Enderman here
oh they're really excited to see us
oh my God they really are stay in the
water seen the water
okay okay yeah that's right that's right
oh wow
where are you buddy this is not good
we can do it
[Music]
and I'm gonna kill them in here but
before we kill the chase right oh wait
no [\h__\h] oh they look perfect I can't do
anything
yeah I'm sorry
[Music]
I need to
please
assistant
[Applause]
oh no this is dangerous are they gonna
attack me
I prefer to die I guess I think I feel
sorry to die at this point yeah you can
get a sword
oh yeah all right all right all right
just fill it
okay do it hey
did you take my stuff
stuff
[Music]
okay
we're here I got it excuse me I really
really wants to hang out with me no
I don't wanna grow anymore I don't care
about the water yeah
I have a sword I'll borrow it
oh
yeah but don't don't
oh it's okay
I'm on my way oh
oh wait oh never mind I'm on a journey
we'll be fine
[Music]
hey you guys have is my stuff still
there
you died I'm still looking forward
I'm gonna leave my diamond armor
um
regenerating I threw I threw my things
out there if someone wants to take them
[Music]
thank you
okay
okay there's diamond armor on the floor
okay I think we're okay
are we
um did you pick up my stuff when you
said you were taking my sword yep
was it a yes or no no no
man
it's a creeper okay just kidding time to
go back to you guys
[Music]
foreign
the water killed me
whoa that is a powerful portal
we also looked like it disappeared when
I died right okay
is there a way we can put out this fire
died
I think the sword here's the bottle
there's a fire am I right hold on
[Music]
my stuff okay I am I am useful again
okay let's go
um as long as I have oh shoot I should
be fine
my things
my my helmet and my chest plate I wonder
if my bow is here
are we still doing the the band strategy
I am excited to work
okay it might be a pipe dream
[Music]
yeah I get him that's an experience just
I've only got a shovel but
um
all right all right
there you go
lions
I can definitely be shot who shot that
nice
but I can't do it again and you have
some food
[Music]
I I have a little bit food yes yes he's
coming
all right we got the bed in position
[Music]
oh my God
can I hit it with a shovel
I can't I can't get it there we go
it's like that you jerk assistant
[Music]
I'm definitely not helping but it's well
it's nice to feel like maybe
[Music]
oh the portal
what the heck
are you guys seeing credits audios
nothing credits
she went through the portal already oh
and do we have we have to go yeah okay
[Applause]
[Music]
is it over
here
I was standing on the portal let's go
[Music]
I need to play here you mean
yes take care it has reached the higher
level now
oh there's like metal
hey that's me you can read off right
they're talking to us whoa
yeah
part of the game
wow I like this player it played well it
did not give up it is reading our
thoughts as though we they wear words on
the screen who wants to read next what
about the egg what egg I think we're a
different part egg I think we left
something important just to imagine many
things when it is deep in the dream of a
game it was confusing we go back
can we re-enter the portal yeah yes you
can because
in that and the world there are
treasures and [\h__\h] Cali and so from now
on we can explore that I'm gonna build a
rails in the Ender Portal
yeah please
but yeah uh my my mission is to get an
elytra as soon as possible because of an
elytra you can fly uh yeah as long as
you have fireworks
don't lose it
foreign
so glad we did it together
um
dance club hello can anybody else say
the same that is pretty dope I will say
that is kind of awesome oh I think he
did pretty good with the bed that did a
lot of dance
I think I did one that was like
something out of like a crazy action
movie that was just unbelievable
Speedway do the bad girl do the best
hahaha
funny I think I think I got a lot of uh
Tower shots
first try shots were quite quite a lot
of them I would definitely give TR the
Sharpshooter award
yeah but that was really only luck
with the with the um Festival the Summer
Festival that was also only luck
laughs
skip credit oh how do I skip them can I
scroll up I want to get a screenshot of
delgura player of games that's gonna be
my gamer title now hahaha
I'm changing my manager
with you
do I want to skip in
well
yay how long are they yeah how long is
it the plan I don't know Kiana hello Ian
can I just go jump real quick back
inside
I just want to um
my minor
Hawk Eyes Phoenix eye Kiana
there we go
that was a little nightmare freaking
nightmare
excuse me
a lot of fun to uh oh the Enderman is
still here yeah they live here oh this
is their home huh yes
cool oh I see the I see the portal thing
wait wait
I'll do it oh there's the egg I don't
know it's a stronghold you get spawned
back
there's the portal thing
a woman inhaled on me
it inhale dummy a woman gathered the
items and she inhaled the player in her
body we got bored
are you ready
oh here's the point looks like everybody
else skipped it
wow yeah
you're missing the good stuff here man
where are the treasures from milk and
love the player is made from nothing but
milk and love
wait what are we doing the end is
basically like insanely endlessly huge
so when you ask for the treasure there's
a [\h__\h] ton of treasure spread over
millions and millions of miles oh wow so
you might not find it right away but you
gotta travel from like Islands there's
like all kinds of like Islands separated
you gotta build like Bridges and [\h__\h] to
get to another Island are there more
dragons maybe we can go on a treasure I
think only one dragon
oh
there's millions of Enderman
is that the egg Ina yes but
what does it do
egg and let it land on a torch you can
respawn the dragon with the egg oh just
leave it for now I guess okay the dragon
egg yeah I won't touch it it won't go
anywhere
become Daenerys
whatever
cool uh well should I I don't know do I
want to go there
sometimes
we're being spoken to encode you guys
zeros and ones it's the mark of a true
gamer
wow
Universe said they love you by the way
oh that's nice to know that was very
kind also the universe is inside you
oh that's true that makes me feel
violent
no I'm not skipping the credits I gotta
know more the universe says you're not
alone which is not a scuffed stairwell
egg there's the egg
and then you never said and my mommy
said that you are the Knight and my
mommy said the darkness who fight is
within you and my mommy said to light
your secrets within you and my
you can't get up
girl she's reading the credits wake up I
know I don't wake up from that horrible
dream what the hell is that
what is that wake up wow did this take
us less than two hours you guys
I thought it would take us three
hour and 20 minutes or something
it doesn't take longer to uh find the
place yeah only almost 2 A.M here I
thought it would be much later uh-huh
oh ow don't hurt me oh
you're gonna die
yeah water or jump into the portal oh
water would have been a better choice
here
oh that's okay um
yeah outside still in there yeah outside
we'll we'll make our way back does
anybody have a pickaxe you are the gamer
I have pickaxe where are you uh I'll
come in okay oh they in or out yeah
uh just uh read the title if you want to
use it that's important yay
oh stream heart Challenger and Spark
that's right
nice should I do it stream Sparks
I'm collecting materials
that was so fun thank you guys what are
you doing that's a blast you guys thank
you so much
are you building a what are you building
me
oh
is that a creeper yes
oh no
sorry oh no are you okay
you moved in my line of fire now Mr
President don't worry
I can't wait for the railway railroad
back
I want some books now what do we do it
to be a party do they see this letter
feel the rail
oh nice second floor only take some
books too because I lost so many items
did you guys get his dress up here
there's books in it there's not much oh
well that one hang out the walls I have
so many books okay that's all I wanted
to take just a little bit this place is
so funny
um
I I have something to confess um
huh I
I went I I might have been the first one
to open the chest and I might have been
the one who took something out of the
chest I was in the chest yeah
um
two two two books uh that were in
Enchanted nothing super special oh yeah
well I'm level 68.
wow
as level 30 earlier hey how do we get an
elytra can we get that now oh
wander up you guys I mean I thought it
was gonna take longer to be honest I
wonder how many electrons though are
like who has Bring It Around And there
are enough for Japan members to keep on
getting new ones
even though they lose them all of the
time
don't do
how many lives there is no limit yeah it
will take a while
yeah it might take a while to explore
because you have to find the place where
they have it and then you gotta like
clear out
stuff
gotta kill stuff oh
we wanted to take a picture
should we not take that like in the end
that would wouldn't that be cool yeah
in in the end and then we'll just take a
picture and quickly go outside again
wait where is it where is it on it and
I'm going back into the middle and let
me go down the sticks where the hell is
it
here yes
okay
yes
I think you have to leave it there
leave it don't tell me know how to take
it safely
yeah let's let's get to the egg and take
a picture in front of it yeah let's do
it does anyone of my um silk touch
pickups so it's called one percent I
have cutting corners oh yeah that's mine
Corners cutting corn oh one percent
what is that though
I'm here to reunite you here you go
oh someone looked at this
corner I did not look at them
oh one percent is my other picnic thank
you
that dropped from the thing because I
thought something dropped
uh where do we take the picture
make sure you don't stare at the ender
man
what's that of this of the perch
if I switch views will it make me look
at them
just don't touch it
um not necessarily
app
okay please though I'm ready whenever
you want to take a picture it's me too
everywhere like
you guys gonna get it with a silk touch
this is like operation I don't know
that's how it works
you guys you can't mine it don't touch
it definitely you got it all right don't
touch it no touchy
touch the egg once then break the block
under it with a torch
now the block under it's um
yeah so don't touch it right now
we can take
[Music]
oh I'll take him Cali here you go
oh
[Music]
will it
oh don't touch it there's a little touch
oh yeah Laura
oh
sorry I I panicked I left I panicking
left
that's probably better
okay so coming back okay
no I'm just kidding I won't I promise
you shovel helped achieve Victory
where are you oh
wow they're real quick they like to move
with the blocks
oh yeah they're real men
Adam Watson
I have a sword zoom zoom zoom zoom I'll
sit here for a million years until I get
this I'll just run
is there a way that I can help you no
it's okay
[Music]
oh they're angry this is gonna be tough
I have another uh yeah
where is he okay
I'll be back okay okay
I'll be back thumbs up
this place is a lot less scary without
the uh
dragons
I was gonna say without the shaders but
yeah I was not the dragon as well
yeah the sky is prettier without the
shade but it's not yeah it's much easier
to see without it yeah pitch black but I
mean yeah it wasn't much better when it
was noise
head
use any tool or even your bare hands hit
the Ender Dragon egg Until It Breaks oh
yeah remember remember Mikko Senpai and
suicide Senpai wearing those ender
dragon heads yeah Summer Festival that
was really creepy all right this is good
okay
I guess for every picture we can look
into a different direction okay
yeah I think this angle works for me
okay oh yeah this one works for me too
look look I'll just look where
that works am I looking in the right
side yeah yeah yeah okay okay I'm just
gonna leave this to you a little up
again
okay
get out of here I'll be back in the
portal we got one right I think so oh
wait I didn't get one okay
[Music]
where I stand
to the to the to um more to the front
yeah
and three two one cheese
okay thank you anyone else who wants a
picture
um I'm let's see oh yeah sure I look
over to you then I should be looking in
the right direction yeah everyone look
up this way ready
[Music]
I got it I got it I got it I got it
all right I'm jumping in the portal all
right let's go all right here we go yay
[Music]
does anyone want to like go back home or
like is everyone ending now or because I
feel like it's lost
yeah I want to go treasure hunter later
how do we do that
we'll look at it later
yeah
uh no I have one
can I have one
I'm I'm playing Minecraft later today
guys so I'll just log out here I guess
okay
just don't take all the treasures yes no
no there's infinite Treasures oh cool
but I'll be leaving
yep me too thanks so much everyone for
the fun time
yay I won't forget it
it's quite an experience thank you for
everything you guys did to prepare yes
thank you it would not have been easy
mode without all of your preparation so
no problem
[Music]
is always cooperating whenever you
needed help
thanks for the fun time thank you thanks
guys
[Music]
appreciate your support as always
goodbye goodbye guys
[Music]