[Music]
w
well this is
weird wait I don't see you I don't see I
don't see anything
okay one
sec
hello
[Music]
hello hi everyone how you doing oh I'm
like kind of quiet one sec
boost boost okay now it should be fun
hello today we're going to be playing Su
to die with holy and um I don't know if
we're starting starting starting guess
we're starting I guess I'm just jumping
right
in um yeah so for those who didn't know
so who dies like a zombie apocalypse
game I've played it once before however
that was in the beta so this is the
first time I'm playing it did you nap
good yeah I napped I napped first I
struggled with napping and then I
watched like some streams and then I a
manga and then I napped so now I'm
napping now then I napped and then I
woke up and now I am ready for a little
bit how however I am sleepy but that's
okay um I'm always sleepy so it doesn't
really change anything and um yeah let's
jump into the game let's see spawn it's
creating player I'll show the screen in
a second I just don't want
to I wonder if they added new BM because
I remember when I played this with GG
there was one bgm
only it's
me
[Laughter]
ah
um
hello
hello wait I forgot how to wait I can't
hear you I can't hear her I forgot how
to uh voice voice voice voice voice
voice audio audio audio voice input
enable voice chat
yes
uh don't remember what button it was
audio keyboard
mouse Min youi Miss
V can you hear
me can you hear
me probably not can I hear her or you
just can't
[Music]
hello
nope
oh let's add each other don't you don't
you know that feeling when
you um spawn into a wonderful world and
then you
[Music]
hello
you're nice beard okay you wish you
could
[Music]
thr I can hear you now I was excited
head in the direction of the survivors
okay let's do it wow you
buff okay let's see I know I've been
working out it's tough surviving the
zombie apocalypse where is
oh yeah come to bble to
bble okay let's see you look pretty buff
yourself everybody looks buff I'm sure
well I mean you have to be a certain
level of buff in order to survive the
zombie apocalypse I think although this
is too buff like you would want more fat
but maybe they can't because they don't
find food would make
sense yeah makes sense to me yeah oh
hello hello only we clothes nice
everybody's everybody's joining that's
huge
overturned trailer whoa hold up
hold is this maybe a hole probably
shouldn't loot this we should probably
get to
everybody find you guys or am I going to
SP you have to found us us Spa somewhere
random so come to bio and full
moo well we'll meet where we're at
V
sucks okay meet at the Rock okay okay no
it's not proximity it's weird but when
we were testing it the proximity worked
and now it's not working so I don't know
we'll see but it's okay it's okay I need
clothes very
important let's the tree together okay
for now we can find the
others okay yeah beep this
tree
yeah
thees already punching trees I see
that's good we we're Gathering resources
while you guys try to arrive also did
you punch
me just following what are you
doing from the tree I thought we got all
BL from we we we got this no which
button it's
we we got this it's not
working my mic is it's not it's not it's
not working
mym know if we can swim
CeCe yeah sorry my M my mic was yes
you're good let's go I tried changing
Pusher talk and it didn't work for some
reason that's okay it think there's no
like voice activation I think it's just
push the top yeah no no I meant I I
tried changing my
key yeah I didn't realize you guys were
in voice chat
already actually we're using uh the
party chat there it is but probably move
to Discord afterwards
okay oh it took me seven minutes to die
on there she is yeah I died like s
minutes in ironically I'll just RP
someone that doesn't talk everyone it's
hard to live in the zombie apocalypse
you're also big man
oo wow a lady W you have makeup on how
do you have makeup in Zombie I'm behind
you wow you also a
hello hello dear sir
bowing hello sir nice beard oh nice
beard to you a very clean and nicely
shaven head I wonder how much time that
takes you every
day no I'm just naturally bald I don't
have hair on my head could the has a
long
delay because of the Ping a long delay
maybe maybe maybe we should hop in
Discord lady Discord Jo Discord it's
okay the problem with this was just like
we couldn't do test some of this stuff
before because like you can't go into
the server so
sorry okay let's see now the zombie will
take you I didn't not I think we're
moving to Discord voice
chat all
right hello
[Music]
why is it so quiet
why why is it so
[Music]
quiet Gary in in terms of weight nope
sorry guys sorry sorry sorry s oh so you
can just carry as much as you want
that's
great it's there's inventory slots that
are
finite wait there's a house over here
have it well the big goals for today to
find a place to to chill out in together
um a base even if it's
temporary um well yeah can we take over
this house this looks nice this is
actually a really nice house we did get
lucky this is like The Walking Dead
house
po what is happening cring I don't think
so we may have to take out the enemies
here though I like
crouching what happens if we die yes you
are crouching then we respawn you like a
bed roll really quick oh thank
you we live in this house there's a PC
set up I can stream from
here at this bad sounds huh what Z in
the house oh there's big fatties I
just
no yay zombie noises don't me I thought
she was
dead do you want to come with me to them
uh I'm already trying to make my way
towards uh foku apparently that's where
we're meeting okay okay so I'm I'm
slowly making my way there we are we are
in a thank you that could be our home
base it could be our home there's it
upstairs baby do you want to go upstairs
with me we should go upstairs first bab
okay what nice house are you scared are
you scared that why it is a nice house I
but it has a giant hole I don't know I
don't know about the Integrity of this
house sure we might just need to fill
the hole and then we'll be fine but yeah
you're right come in here yeah that's
true oh there a GU boy don't hurt my new
friends I'm running out of Stam so
easy they're still alive but they're
dead there a walking dead right where'
they go
there he's got a bit of reach on him
okay it's just Dark Souls it's just Dark
Souls oh he
fellon I mean a lot of
room B
F bunk beds down
here I'll take the
couch is there a way to improve the
stamina somehow you might need level up
or
something it's stop being jump scared by
me I'm bonking the truth cuz I need
materials guys on the let's see want to
I want clothes I'm going to go on a trip
to find clothes
guys I'm going to go on a little trip to
find clothes I will be back to this
house our temporary base okay see you
you can craft clothes by the way oh yeah
I'm going to make some armor actually we
don't have to stay naked forever and I'm
going to start cleaning the house cuz
you know you guys know I'm a clean freak
I'm sorry it can't be helped yeah this
house is very messy you already you
already reached a house yeah you guys
can come check it out it's we got really
lucky actually come downstairs
downstairs what do you mean like this is
so broken look at look at it it works it
works for now but it's so broken we're
going to have to repair it so much oh my
God kie can I show you look at this kie
kie look at this giant hole in the
basement BL
it there is a pool table that is a good
point that is a good point so fun us
playing pool together yeah that would be
really cool I think you know what you've
won me over you know a pool pretty good
that's a pretty good it's a fixer upper
as they say fix upper put some blocks
crates and stuff yeah yeah a lot of
blocks a lot of crates but blocks Snak
there's snakes in this game snakes oh
yeah and they're not zombie snakes
they're just normal snakes oh my God
yeah there's maybe I could blow it up
like in Shrek and make a balloon out of
it oh God that there and then does
anyone know how to get plant
fiber plant
grass punch
it there's a water bottle in here
that's I think the one thing I remember
is that it's really important for us to
find water and not to like save it like
save it and not drink it and figure out
how to craft like water reservoirs and
water
Gatherings water yeah murky water will
give you tummy egg probably but you can
try yeah it has dentary in it oh
you think this will work if we
just but's else
[Music]
here
yum is Carl still alive dead
coin see look we can totally block this
hole
dead we have no wood left you see where
I'm getting right you guys see what I'm
getting at yeah I think this is a oh I
found $8 guys anyone want to sell me
something for $8
box this economy uh can you give can you
can I buy
wood I do I have 12 ooh can I have
two okay for $8 wait let me double check
if it's
two yeah it's two yeah for $8 two how do
I how do I drop
something Cecilia and Fu I'm still
waiting for you to accept my friend
request oh sorry you got mine right Kara
no I accepted everybody and got
everybody except Cil and okay I did it
FL how do
I a thing like a
stack you um how you split the stack or
yeah like I can give you two
oh oh I found it totally going to how do
you do it oh hold it to drop a swap
attack okay here you go I dropped it
thanks look what I did I'm so smart I'm
a builder CeCe I'm a
builder oh wow you build already you
need a helmet this is not safe working
environment I do not I don't I don't
think May she's already got D yeah
really well just pluging up the holes
ladies
crack I guess I can craft
multiple
okay I already forgot how to play this
game okay wood
time see now the house is well fortified
cuz there's no hole anymore oh nice nice
the Builder oh my gosh this is going to
be our streamer house we're going to
stream from here and it's like a dream
come we going to one PC that we all have
to share with different profiles PCS
here multiple even okay yeah don't kind
all the off collabs forever have off
collab off collabs
forever I'm so hype let me move my bed
roll I mean even in the zombie
apocalypse entertainment is important I
don't remember what it was but this all
be there where we can get him we can
take him
okay Bonk Bonk B
[Music]
yeah kill him make him pay make him pay
shoes We're such a good team no no never
never I need to punch a couple more
plants
never make sure you guys do your
challenges by pressing why why where are
you did you find your way
here I wonder if K is still making my
fist if he made us we should use it
instead
ofiara and Gigi are pretty far
away he's making her way
downtown walk fast face is past and
she's home
now I have to do
this think they can see where we
are going to mute every once in a while
this is when I want to talk to you guys
this is me by the way way look at
me
I'm oh it went back to my steam name
okay let's
see where okay this can salvage anything
by the way how sorry I didn't listen how
do you salvage anything anything just
hit it okay okay smack it put the stuff
in find in crates I'm going to put some
crates in the house so we can put stuff
in there okay okay okay
do keep out
condemned yeah
yeah for the I mean we can do whatever
we want but for the magazines I think
it's probably best to like keep them and
then see who wants to go into what
because otherwise there won't be enough
like if everyone just uses everything no
one's actually going to level any skill
cuz they're really rare and you need
like 10 of one type in order to get a
level and stuff sometimes so great then
let's have like a magazine crate or
something I personally am going for 4
strength I amick hello there you go eat
it to death guys there's a Farm close
by I got a chicken I just caught his
dinner me to build my first
crafting my first my cloes this is a
good
spot
potato dinner time
baby I
see we can make a bone knife soon
too uh-oh if you find corpses on the
ground hit them ladies hit them oh hit
them good oh I
can that kind of cute need more wood
okay let's let a little further away
kind of a strong zombie I don't
know let's
go hello by the way uh vampire
infection how do
you fix the infection cut off the arm oh
you're infected I'm infected
oh goodbye goodbye goodbye see you just
Dark Souls time to put the cat
down people do you want to go where are
you hey I am here wait where is she
actually I'm here hello I'm here I'm
here where is here where is here in the
hello okay I'll help you with the
infection no no no no no no no stop stop
stop actually it might be worth at the
beginning she's wait where's she going
to respawn is she is she going to
respawn she might respawn all the way in
the beginning don't kill her oh no no no
I work so
hard okay where where I'll just tear off
that limb no we can talk about it I
please no fighting no fighting talk
about it okay okay listen I want to help
I want to get material I want to I want
to help you guys to fight zombies and I
behind you behind you a
zombie a bone knife oh we know where
the it's literally right there don't
want to sleep in the bathroom hello oh
okay but maybe you guys are NPCs oh
Wella that big boy jump if you hear me
Faun I'm crafting my my
my don't remember the get him get him
you guys got this get him from the back
we'll get him in the I keep hitting him
he's not dead he's not dead I need to
figure out how to leave this other party
I'm in that I'm currently not talking
to I'm not muted I'm not muted no we
hear you we hear you
K hear you get bked big boy nice one
[Music]
for have to leave a party that I'm in I
am hurting I can tell we should heal
some
but I made a a bow and I got us meat you
guys I got us meat so I'm going to make
a
crate hey I have a question how do you
actually wear the outfit uh you click on
the item and press W
[Music]
oh our
house you have the best house
ever freaking rocks just got to figure
out how to click
okay okay I'm not Naked Anymore yeah
don't be naked naked's
dangerous we can make two two crates
this my bed now
okay getting some cotton
plants for
medication could have sworn I made too
oh here we go all right I'm finally
where you guys are I think I I'm I'm
there you are
I see you she's here
welcome keep here for now right yay is
it a like yellow the papa residence yeah
yes the papa it that's a streamer house
welcome will it fit all of us you check
it out
yourself iron nitrate
[Music]
powder hello
H did someone put that building block
down there and I accidentally take it
maybe we Pi yeah it's just to block the
door okay oh this even the corn are Dad
here oh there go this place is awesome
so we put our uh bed rolls in here
somewhere did you go do that already yes
you should Kiara oh bed right anywhere
there's actually actual beds in here
there are yeah
wa did you build those beds over they
just bunk beds by
default
us my B pool table you have to craft a
bed roll and then put the bed roll where
you want to spawn
so I'm taking the master bedroom hey a
massive
bedroom in the it too how do we does
anyone know how to make like chests or
something yeah I just made them they're
in the living room living room where oh
they not
thank you I wonder if I can put right
I'll just put all my garbage in here
yeah sure just materials and such
oh on this couch you get to sleep on
this comfy bed
nice lucky right oh there's an
upstairs uh I think got a building Cube
from the house I'm sorry it's
okay I'll Rec recog it click right click
how do you place theed right click right
click okay but I don't I don't know how
to turn it left click Co house on the
top
no oh I guess I can't place it on the
toilet murky
water if you guys find Murky water you
can uh you can boil it in a pot over
fire to clean it what I see oh Network
timeout I got kicked out oh did we all
get kicked out not me no no it
disconnected okay I'm going to sleep
next to the PC then I sleep next to
the down the washing
machine
no ST making
sure what's
wrong water
[Music]
maybe I do want to burn some peee water
huh do it land claim block oh we might
need
that I thing we could do
oh there's a visitor at our humble
abode visitor yeah
someone are they nice I don't know but
they're not
talking Rando NPC uh is it the shieldy
group shieldy that f a group did you
just attack me I like this room I've
claimed the
land oh
nice press
um anyway we claimed this land with this
block uh what are you doing stop it my
beautiful
G A
[Music]
see we had
ADHD stop attacking me guys we hav we
have we have someone evil this this GG
person is attacking
me
I chaos hello jails
[Music]
welcome up you look beautiful look this
is my this is my PC setup you like it oh
nice oh I can sleep on top of it
actually or maybe I
cannot can I sleep I got this place
pretty should I'm going to find a room
very I mean yeah yeah yeah it's a
CO
yeah
too um does anyone want to come I want
to go try going to a
farm I will I will wait outside the
let me just set up home here really
quick let's
go oh we're all going okay then let's
wait for shorty shy did you say you want
to you will come with us or let me just
my bed roll okay okay got to set
that let's wait a
second here or you guys Traer pretty
what did you say I'm pressing e oh right
a Traer near this house no we haven't
found one yet we haven't done
anything I like that even in the
apocalypse Tren thing and we're all
wearing the same
style
Click by the way if you guys open the
map you can set a marker for where home
is open the
map you can set a marker that's
nice this is a home I'm sorry every time
I all tap back in I punch someone oh
that's what
happened okay okay truth truth then
truth truth don't touch me you don't
touch me truth
okay okay Friendly Fire is on guys be
careful don't hit each other guys don't
hit each other guys Friendly Fire is
[Applause]
on all right I'm going stay back so you
guys probably make get him get him get
that yeah oh leg okay this way I think
was the farm oh yep this way wait wait
who am I following everyone looks the
same I'm a little
hungry just follow everybody one withar
IE follow this the the the flo oh dead
corn okay but I'm going to have ADHD on
the way that's okay you can have ADH at
any point you want
go oh there's corn
I think we can pick up the corn yeah we
can pick up the cornn can we make stuff
out this can we cook cuz I so there's
like dead corn and green corn I think
the green one we can there was real corn
[Music]
Isn there is some good corn too ladies I
feel like we should probably be oh
they're dead let's go yeah there is real
corn there can we get can we get seeds
to replant them s stole that I think so
but I don't know how
got to be a good
farmer in this apocalypse with corn
that's all I need I'll survive most of
the Corn are dead
though PL of
good just e the the people
what I mean they're just zombies they
don't
people got to have a supply okay this
one has this area has three three skulls
on it I don't know if we're ready for
that oh that we're going to die look at
the green one the loot probably really
good but I just don't think we're ready
surpris there's like skull images so I
noticed that the green cor actually
contain seeds too probably oh they we
could
set they have something different we
could set up a little farm by our
home yeah let's do that
here yeah but that is this is be careful
this is the three skull area yeah it's a
pretty intense
area there's zombies everywhere run run
run she L surrounded what are they going
to do it's okay run after us what are
they going to do huh eat us oh so much
[Laughter]
corn all right I hope the corn read like
resupplies maybe a farmer shows up and
take care of things hopefully there's a
house
here I have so much corn I'm going back
home I think so out of I don't think it
gives you anything can I eat okay we can
eat wait wait don't leave
me so we just need a big
wine sorry I can't really Reet that much
I get a little bit overwhelmed I hope
everyone doing well
yeah good idea food gatherers this is
just win Gathering and stay at
home wait a minute
time let's go organize what do I found a
land claim block destroyed us oh I think
someone put I just put that there for
the quest worry
not my land claim block is so if you put
a land claim box down
apparently um it applies a hardness
modifier to blocks so it
protects protects damage on something
apparently so like you're safe in this
Zone I guess or something like that or
the player who put it down is safe in
the zone it's like you're L now that
would be good if we had by the house
yeah we have one of those I put one in
the living room oh okay awesome oh we're
in the same uh Al like group too so we
should be good to go it won't be harder
for us to destroy each other's things if
we need to
exactly I have a question um no parties
there
six how do you level
up oh I think he going to kill oh
killing zombies okay yeah yeah find the
Traer gives Quest and he gives a lot of
exp from the quest does anyone want to
go with me on an adventure to see if we
can find the Traer I know where oh you
know where it is already I want to find
yeah I have one on my map too oh okay is
it the White River yeah yeah he should
come to us this way point if he wants to
trade he should come to us that's right
he's not going to do that I
think but then he won't have any not
going to be our face by the way or he's
going to stay hello oh
hello oh I found people
wel
welcome you guys are all wearing
something why AR you wear
your there's a hat yes put your hat on
what you should probably
like kill
it hat
yes for you where is it this one oh oh
wait no I see a hat
oh thank you yes put it on Oh
yay
civilized
y why
um I don't know how to share the way
Mark what what if you send like a
screenshot send a
screenshot loves
pie oh that
work CRA anything just
yet land clim box iar S I can make a
Char
meat this our by the way this is our
base
yeah we should probably do multiple Camp
what is this land claim
block our home base now with this
basically zombies will spawn around you
you see it I put it in the channel of
the map what if we all put our land
claim blocks like around each other so
they won't spawn within a r let's
protect the house can we
get though
so where can't do anything right how to
make land
claim this oh I have a land claim block
um I don't know where to put it though
uh it won't let me put it anywhere where
H they already claim land claim yeah is
there a maximum to can only one person
claim a land sorry Mak sense know how
are you cooking oh this is that's not me
that's Kelly charred meat oh here maybe
right there trying to figure out where
to put this oh yeah I can't put the L
clim yeah it's a pretty it's a large
just put it here I am dying of
hunger oh I found the place we need
unlock
the all
right claimed this
land put it by the river let's see if we
can cook some more for
everybody much here oh we need cooking
items oh I like the their placement of
this
fire we
fire and you julig just put at the
fireplace can't believe it
we should probably try to find um like a
cooking pot and a frying pan so we here
okay
yeah I found cooking a grill outside the
house I
don't the water we have some water in
inventory here near
trees Town
nearby uh there's a town very far away
[Music]
some oh that the hell that's I think eat
scary food oh by the way it's going to
be night time soon everyone um oh you
guys have a nice campire out here
wonderful we canook morees the idea that
I have is that
vc1 is for the home and then all the
other ones are for like going out on
different excursions together okay it's
nice idea yes eating that would be great
sorry hry I would
e
here she's here I know what to do it's
about to be night BR does anyone want to
go in a small focus on finding
food okay I'm I'm going into voice chat
too if anyone wants to go on an
Excursion little my time to stroll
hello nighttime stroll time everyone
yeah night time stroll there a little
night time let's check out when you
there's a map say that I am infected so
if I die at any moment do you have a bed
roll yeah okay then you should respawn
at the
bed yes indeed yeah okay then it should
be fine respawn where you put your bed
we're carrying a lot right now we should
maybe should I die here then and
yeah okay I'll kill you don't worry sah
we'll
help put it in
uhoh no
hesitation you're welcome it's fine
anytime anytime you need for help we'll
help you don't worry no hesitation at
all
wow is there a place that we can put our
stuff in our inventory yeah there's a
box here in the living room oh in the
Liv here these two go then we just put
our okay one moment we
go okay let's put it in there okay
should we check out the area East to
where we are it seems to have like a
little yeah something oh is at the
farm your stuff is where you die okay
I'm going to pick it up yeah that sounds
bad scary sounds all of a
sudden let's take thank you for helping
okay I'm ready actually that's where the
second I'm just putting my stuff away
okay um should we try the one West from
us then people the scary
sounds are okay
right ow ow zombie ah how could this
happen to me
zombie in the zombie game
no is it inside maybe let's close the
door oh oh he in the house it is
[Applause]
T somebody's on
fire you st back I think yeah it's over
yeah e my
back go down back I don't
know yeah
break it doesn't sound good
no how much corn do I have to eat to not
be hungry I think the corn just as it is
this heals one point so it's not worth
eating oh yeah we need to make food we
need to like Grill it
probably okay let me check I have I have
a few eggs maybe oh I got some chicken
soup okay I'll just eat that there is a
lot of zomie sounds going on in the
can sounds sounds yumy sounds
it calls
me
you okay I got some eggs and I don't
think you can do anything with the eggs
yet we need like a pan and
stuff
mayy huh oh my gosh let's close the door
so no trees come through okay were we
were we heading out by the way I'm
scared a little right okay don't be
scared let's go want make me a new um
wooden um it is
time oh we need a new one is can you
make a you can't you can repair your oh
we can yes let's repair it
then oh I can't oh we don't I don't have
the material we don't have the materials
right now second give me a moment we put
it all
away mhm I need some rock from qu
probably also if we had a torch it' be a
little bit easier to see things I can
make boiled eggs you should have one
when you spawn or is it a
torch we have
one oh
clay we need
clay oh gosh what is that what is that
help help help help he's running where
are you he running oh no no no I'm
running
back back
home
it it don't tatch
the let's take some of the rock out and
then fix right now is it that I think
so thank you you saved me let's go
you're
welcome not you b b
welcome the we
it
yay okay is everyone here yeah this
way is in the house the
house okay let's try going for the the M
the area that is left of this down the
street okay out
they're going to be back up maybe should
run away from
them oh he got
me I feel like maybe if better run away
from
them no they will outrun Us in the
night nice does does anybody have extra
Pebbles I want to make a spear we have
trying to do I have
my we are very hungry our maximum status
is summon is reduced we should have some
of our food M down but you don't want to
eat
it there goes our food
okay hungry still hungry yeah I don't
know the beginning is really hard
because this just no food so you're just
going to be hungry I don't know be
hungry hry might be like a way to make
food from the very beginning but I don't
know so maybe we can just like try
finding stuff this ooh cell tower number
one what what's this let's go on in are
you guys are you guys outside right
we're inside the building that we just
oh if you're in the
party ra go towards the pink the pink
water col Okay pink uh
can I can I go past you
please sorry am thank you it's
okay it's okay let's let's break stuff I
think I'm starving I there's water empty
water nothing it's
empty it's empty water cooler not empty
water we
scratching
oh it's okay maybe this is like the PR's
going up maybe the game has like
Communications or something uhoh uhoh I
hear
sounds I want to clb on up oh I can't go
up I'm coming oh there we go can guys no
how do I go up the thead you just you
just go up press
W be careful there's a zombie up here
though so watch out are going to get him
uhoh there's a lot of zes I think you I
think you ran off the C never
mind ah my leg is sprain guys it's over
I'm going to be a dead weight from now
on yeah I fall a little bit
broking the house in the house in the
house this is very
strong no no leave me
alone okay okay okay okay okay let me
let
me oh my gosh my leg is
broken we have 15 Health we're going to
die it's okay I CL
down look down down look down is there
outside I'm going to fight them good
luck wait stay
here don't go down don't go down come
back up come back up and then we like we
kill him in the hole come back
up the I'm on this side
[Applause]
okayoh okay I'm going back down not
asart
back down back down people back down uh
how you go down you just you just like
look down look at the floor
eliminated that
was
oh I let's break
thear okay go out go back
up I'm going to stay inside the
house okay right there uhoh
yummy my stamina is really bad what's
the what's the little thing
that it's not healing very
fast I use a splint do we have one no we
don't have one do we have a splint I
thought was zombie okay I have a spear
do you guys want a spear I have extra
one uh uhoh uhoh here they come can we
make a right now I don't know how to do
that oh is that a weapon yes thank you
take the weapon take the
weapon renge
me
meing uhoh we we
we what
oh my God out of
stamina I'm going to fight
you I really need
a that's a lot of Juicy sounds on on my
bed on my bed on
[Laughter]
my okay I'm going to have to run back oh
it's right there okay that's not too bad
just jumping at each other they're just
having a nice time hey hey I mean we got
absolutely nothing from that so I call
it a success okay okay I'm going
back inventory is hi guys
hi I'm good I'm good thank
[Music]
you wait where are you guys what you
take turns take turns take turns wait
where are you
where are you going almost
done this is one is very
resistant let's go get stuff from our B
I'm this good no she's this way finally
dead hi
guys I went
downstairs where is the sound coming
from that's hi
watch
out that's craft in the meantime you
don't have anything to C you you got the
ball can we use the
ball why what them has red eyes it's
messed up what is that because stronger
or something they're stronger yeah
they're stronger at night oh they run
away from us oh never mind I'll try
burning them he's burning he's
burning burn down burn down ah
let's go put here what are we doing how
are we escaping this little tiny room
get from near my it's okay it's okay I'm
okay
burn burn he's not burning the full moon
oh
oops no
[Music]
no and that is almost over
Rock uhoh oh God okay maybe this wasn't
the best idea I don't know I I'm
not
that oh there's no
door okay
door I don't know if they can get up
here sa here I don't know we'll see
I guess
it okay
it's I it
again okay I say a plant change of plans
everyone go back home pick up your
stuff and run back
home okay home run back home pick up
your backpack don't forget to pick up
your backpack and then run back home you
get a backpack it's going does the
backpack spawn at some point I think we
need to C some better weapons before
going in
adventure well it was still a nice
Adventure it was just
not fruitful oh I haven't said that it
was not a nice
Adventure this blood everywhere no it's
it's
nice look nice okay okay let me see this
way hey the the sky is coming up Dawn is
upon
us okay we need a door P outside there
you
go okay I need to did anyone find
anything was this like successful in
anyway no I didn't find any it but
that's pretty much it what did you find
food that's good I
foundo and some PE hey be careful be
careful be careful
I'm not going to take everything okay
I'm going back to the uh
others I'm at home right now there's
still zombies out there let's make our
own wooden Tre and put it downstairs in
our room and then nobody will get
confused uhoh I
can't
arrows bleeding Arrow AR yeah
maybe you
have I don't know you sound con thank
you thank you for thinking right
now wait she's not in this one oh where
C up oh never
mind okay as as much as I thought thank
you for trying I'm sorry I do not know
as much as you
know don't know what that
was okay hello guys must have been the
wind oh they're inside the zombie inside
that's not good that's not good it's not
very how do I drop this
I uh guys we went on an adventure but we
didn't really find anything so we're
back a a I'm sorry to hear that well
welcome back thanks you did good really
our
home through the
door the good news is uh I found a house
that I think we
can yes why did you take my backpack why
did you punch
me I thought that was from the
zombie just you just committing theft in
daylight no no I thought it was for the
zombie I thought oh my God this guy has
a lot of loot
wow it was me it was me my dad body was
still
decomposing I read your I read your
magazine you read the it's okay it's
okay wor now you know if there's a
backpack that's of a survival probably
well yeah if I if I find two more
magazines I'll give them to you I'll
donate no worries no worries it's okay I
have a question
yeah iron how do I get
IR for I'm not sure about that probably
have to find a rock and
maybe like do I need a lot of stuff in
here or just a stone pickaxe is fine P
your junk in there ax I guess we can
only make thick walls though yeah
Community chest maybe what cute frame oh
I can make grilled corn now I go find
iron then how can you make the grilled
corn
bab that takes wood I use a magazine to
learn cooking skills and now I have
cooking skill up oh maybe you can like
make all the corn I want to find a
magazine oh okay I then I need a cooking
grill but if I if we have a cooking
grill I can cook the corn I think the
leave the the cooking grill at the fire
so everyone can cook then yeah I think
the best way to go about the magazines
is probably to like share them in the
sense that like oh okay one person does
all the cooking one person does this
because otherwise we not actually going
to level anything that's not I have I
have two skill points in cooking already
so I guess I'll cook she's going to be
all cooker let
[Music]
me I have core I'll drop it give give me
your core I should also the chest the
chest is like come with
me no
points how
I'm going to the farm if anyone wants to
come to the farm with me uh come to vc2
I'm going to get materials if someone
wants to come with me
to nothing
okay oh can maybe someone make supposed
be punching corn do you think kie has
like corn and then you get it I can ask
but but they have to be like not dead
corn so the green ones oh God damn
yeah most of them are
dead that one looks alive oh thank God
did you say we had a cooking pot
somewhere no I didn't see it okay um
I'll leave my corn here although I am
hungry okay do we have to steal a
cooking pot or something yeah yeah it's
necessary I think do you guys we also
need to find a source of water and like
to boil it with a pot M okay do you guys
want to try going to the farm oh my god
oh yes it turns out I haven't read your
magazines oh really okay you can have
them back here I put them in this crate
here oh thank you something that anybody
can or are did they disappear afterwards
yeah they disappear afterwards disappear
I see thank you I'm trying to Sur wait
you know what here for for [\h__\h] wait
can't one sec whoops I didn't mean to
say
that I mean oh shoot here here since you
were this is you know when you find a
wallet and you give it back this is your
uh your reward you can read
itk you smart
together smart together ooh the club is
better know Club
okay I'll go with kie if anyone wants to
go kie and I are going to the
farm I'm not going to okay hi hi hi hi
I'm coming too oh cool okay I'm on my
way wait wait can we act as if this is a
this is a
walkie-talkie I am on my way over hello
everyone over uh which direction is the
farm hi guys what's your favorite manga
over
H I love hos no Kuni so much have you
read up to the news um
uploads I'm almost at the end I'm just
trying to be brave enough to read the
ending I haven't even got I haven't
gotten to the ending either it's it's
it's despair but I hope it'll be
okay I hope so too over okay over hi kie
what's your favorite manga over was that
please repeat the question over uh
what's your favorite manga over it's a
secret over it's a secret why over what
do you mean it's a secret is it that
type of not manga that like like that
type of like Chad stop stop outing me is
it is it doesn't you do berserk it's
berserk over oh oh okay okay okay over
also JoJo's over I still haven't read
that I really want to read
berserk because of Dark Souls I heard
it's related so I
over I heard I might be traumatized over
you might over but it'll be like trauma
bonding
over trauma bonding is actually very
effective in Zombie Survival especially
over guys I don't like zombies
over the Grim Reaper doesn't like
zombies I do we really need voice uh the
walkie-talkies when we're next to each
other ladies over look how far away
people is
over oh I I'm I'm entering a tunnel I
can't hear I'm in a
to over oh my god oh this is a new house
I didn't go in here but um we can check
this out oh hello hello zombie okay
watch out I'm being attacked over watch
out watch out over there's a couple of
zombos this item needs repairs got over
I found I found okay so I have one dream
I want to pick up vehicle stuff and uh
maybe medicine stuff I want to be a
Healer maybe maybe uh so if you guys
want anything let me know and I'll I'll
I'll hoard the magazines for now and
then we can like
exchange I I just cooking I guess since
I'm the cook now apparently well it's
only two so if you don't want to you
don't have to but yeah let us know but I
like cooking okay okay then I'll give
you all the cooking
over than please give farming stuff and
uh strength stuff farming that sounds
fun strength uh let me see I have
for okay
okay I hear a zombie uhoh oh they're mad
I don't see it but I hear it she's here
oh I see it I see it it's a lady oh
she's they're angry over oh
he's big lady over two of them
okay be careful behind you K another one
there's actually a lot of them
everywhere uh be careful
over behind you too over it might be
over no it's okay we got this just kite
them K them we can get yeah K them put
walls be between you actually it's okay
it's okay we got this over what if we
lead them away and then and then
scavenge no I think we got them it's got
this we just keep kiting yeah yeah
there's one one's already down it's the
name of the game it's called seven days
to kite yeah seven days to kite it's
true I'm out of stamina one second I'll
just stand here for a
moment oh you have
B
to
ow okay one's dead dead over
good job over nice ah but then there's
another over you got this over oh je
it's over it it might be over for me
over no no no it's okay where are you
I'll help
you are you inside oh there's so many of
them oh
yeah she's tanky zombies are pretty
beefy yeah what do they eat that they
still like this tanky oh she's dead
she's dead oh what a way to die
one
guy we all G up on bull we get him wait
there's some more person here oh it's
cron ohy oh nice crony let's go she's
not in voice but you
know oh a nurse oh doctor
doctor one more hit and it's over for me
over stand behind stand behind Okay
protect me please
okay cook that one knows how to
jump nice one should I tell jump into
voice or oh she's running away should I
okay never
mind it's fine it's fine it's fine let's
see what kind of loot we find in here we
will find all the loot I think I mean
this must have been worth it right I
found some
trash I'm inside of you
let's see must be something good up
here
[Music]
parkour another
ladder I think it's the other side oops
we're really
smart huge brain
people oh no zombie a zombie a
zombie oh up here more could he be
hiding sorry I hit you ow
kick him while he's
down did
you what's in his o it's a blood bag
ammo weapon flashlight Mark schematic
you can take it really I found a bunch
of stuff to in the leather trunk there's
shotgun shells which I definitely will
need uh there's a first aid kit that's
nice oh the great Heist volume two is
this for agility maybe we can give it to
an agility friend oh I'm an agility
friend okay hello
hell hi we're looting what are you guys
up to we loting I found a shovel
chilling stuff may I may I have the
agility book please yeah sure let me
find a way to give it to you hold let me
drop it okay agility and then I found a
medical journal do we have a medic yet
oh I wanted to do medic if that's okay
of course but I will not use it I I'll
wait until the until we reunited with
the others because maybe someone else
already used some so thank you so you
can keep it for now hold to it I'll hold
on to it for now okay do you guys want
to try going you know when you look at
the map the road do you want to try
going further east and seeing if we can
find any
buildings the street there's still one
house that we haven't looted that I
actually opened in this Farm okay okay
maybe we can hit that first that's where
is base and then we can go you trying to
head back to the base
crer yeah
the base is um do you see the red green
square on the map where we are like
right next to it it's like a really big
Square yeah Aang looks like a Swedish
flag or
something and then you follow that thin
Road the thin road to the west and then
there's one little building with like a
little Loop and that's where our
building is our house oh okay yeah thank
you okay I think I know
okay nice ladies if you want to follow
me I can take you to the place that I
busted open okay I'm following okay wait
for me I'm coming okay we'll walk
slowly we're going to RP walk so how
long have you been surviving in this in
this zombie apocalypse
over over oh man about 30 minutes oh why
am I not moving that's 30 minut wow you
must have this this must be like you you
fell into a coma and then you woke up
because it's been 20 years for
me years zombie apocalypse Pig kill it
oh it's alive it's alive oh it's be
careful actually a lot it's going to
attack you probably everything attacks
you I'm going to die I need H I might
actually be dead you are infected take
antibiotics to avoid symptoms
uhoh um where did you guys go um look
for us on your map we're at a big house
I tried to break down there's a sofa in
front of it but might be able to move it
or so hit it there's a lot of isn't this
like a three three skull area
collie yeah but I beat I beat up a
couple of the zombies that were here
okay already let's try I'm coming to you
guys and bringing a pig with me oh is
that a
pet is that is that going to be a
pet um sure sure where you guys having a
hard time oh okay just kidding the
zombies have awoken all right uh time to
lead them out of the
house well we can like get the stuff
around the house or we could try getting
into the house maybe one person can go
in try getting the zombies and then
another person goes in and tries to loot
loot it yeah sure sounds good do you
want to loot I can just lead him away I
can coral them away I'm currently in the
basement trying to be sneaky oh there's
the pig oh God yeah the pig the pig I
have 4 zombies and pig to okay to deal
with okay okay I'm coming
upstairs Pig please I have no quarrel
with
you stupid Pig hi stupid
Pig yeah stupid dummy Pig hi dummy
stupid hi stupid dummy stupid P can't
even
jump ohie dinner uhoh There's a Zombie
it's kind of a strong one he needs a big
bnk oh the pig's not stupid the pig got
out the pig got out very smart oh the
pig is very very smart oh oh God he's
after me all right pig is too fast kill
the pig first Focus Pig Focus Pig
everyone Pig the the turns take turns
doing shots
no I want aveng you I'm almost dead let
me use this I just want to use can't eat
it first that's messed
up maybe I can use this kit I feel bad
oh I killed the pig I killed the pig
nice three HP and a pork dream gonna get
some bacon today nice you got some good
food CeCe hope so I think we need like a
knife or something to to get the meat
out of the pig so but that might be good
food source I have a a bone actually a
bone knife that might help okay you
should do it then I have blade
Specialties now ooh for knives maybe you
can get like extra for it or something
nice I'm getting a ton of stuff off this
pig though with this knife we have food
guys we have procured food with the with
the gatherers no with the hunters yeah
Hunter Gathering yeah yeah hun that's
what we do okay I'm going in I'm going
to try getting them out and just
oh uhoh I some watch out behind us I'm
going okay I do have four HP so I'm not
sure oh maybe we should lead him out
first okay a lot of the doors are locked
it seems okay I'm leading them
outside don't detect them or they'll
lose um
aggro also I'm pretty sure the head is
is like just like usual the weak
point easy I'm watching over your body
well he's got some reach on
him no don't eat her you piece of [\h__\h]
don't eat me don't eat
me or do eat her so she'll be distracted
okay well you know what I'll I'll I'll I
can give you my my meat for
that I'm watching over your backpack you
get you'll get new meat
anyway I don't like how they like trick
you into thinking they're dead when they
lay down on the floor imag we did that
like you get hit and you just
like move they shouldn't be smart enough
be careful there's a big guy let's just
ignore this one he's kind of slow okay
I'm going to go back inside and try to
kite them
out it's in the
basement okay so I got into a room o I
found a gun
magazine um I may or may not
my go I found a cooking pot we can C you
found cing here I
did okay kiting kiting
kiting
okay got a kite so there's three of
them oh I can try taking them on yeah
and it's like a small room so I can't
like really kite
them oh hello I'm about to head towards
your location nice support us in our
battles I found so we can we can make
for when I get back oh oh yummy
corn we also found some be corn
pork tons of pork finally
meat but we need water I think is now
the issue
iide what to do about that to be
honest yeah
okay I got
up ah there's a bunch of people oh my
God cuc okay there's a lot of shipping
crates up here there's a lot of stuff so
if we can get them
somehow so I'm cting them outside so if
someone wants to go all the way up
there's like a lot of stuff I'll
try titing them because I'm on the roof
right now I'll look around okay did you
guys finish looing the farm out of
curiosity I think one of them yeah no
one of the houses but like there's a lot
of zombies around are you okay I see I
see never mind I'm skipping the
far that's bad okay actually maybe I'm
going to kite them so they come down
maybe yeah down are you on the second
floor too CeCe I'm on top of the roof oh
that'll do it here I'm pulling some of
these dudes
out hell all dipped
out oh my goodness so they're jumping
down okay one went back in and two
jumped
down okay okay and they I think they
took some fall damage from that what up
I'm going in we can take him see that
guy that guy's nothing he's
nothing oh there's a lot okay I went I
got in oh by the way there's some more
people coming U maybe like four zom zoms
just to let you know just kidding people
as in Zombies never mind okay there's
only one with me upstairs right now so
I'm going to just loot everything yeah
go for it take what you could
take um I found a paper interesting oh
I'm
dehydrated a big boy yeah there's also
two like right behind
me drink this water I will uh do this
technique I found a medical
journal nice nice and I found some
vitamins hello does anyone have
lockpicks proba they're dumb wait I
think I'm lagging oh I think the
server's lagging yeah she I was going to
say they're dumb they're caught in the
fence
oh whoa whoa wo hello
Dead all right he wants to sell pancakes
oh Yik I have no stamina sounds like me
when I'm hungry cuz I'm
hungry I hear a lot of zombie sounds
maybe that'll help me a little bit here
he's after me so you can probably hit
him during that that's a good idea I can
make I can make tea with that flow okay
tea give them up I found a reinforced
chest and I will spend some time on un
un enforcing it un reinforcing it in up
up up forcing
it it look pretty clear out here now oh
yeah there's only like two zombies to
take up a lot of hits
yeah on the zombie
heads man he has so much health I'm
going to kill the the zombie that's
upstairs for you CC I'm beated thank you
actually we need to find water well
there there's some water here it's just
too bad we can't just eat the snow I
know wouldn't that be great if we could
just eat snow isn't yellow snow isn't it
like the energy you take to melt
if you have a human body
yellow no
Linate sorry I'm not that into your
Jewel of emotions and what no of
emotions I didn't I didn't mean I made
the yellow S I found an egg oh you're
not starting like a lemonade business
with
it man my character's tired go away
zombie I can okay time for me to drink m
i don't have murky water
oh that's how you do it press W it's
going to take some time to
heal okay I'm at 3,400 out of 5,000 oh
he's finally dead it's fine he's not
dead I lied it's fine oh I got the Traer
y I finally got the Traer oh my
gosh oh guy to you guys I need uh use
use your
axe oh my axe oh I I'm like too weak in
general no you're strong to us you can
be like mentally strong even if you're
physically weak it's okay bro I'm tired
my character is
thirsty this guy is like too he's too
big in
health okay I'm leaning him towards you
good luck
so uh what you do before the uh zombie
apocalypse uh CZ oh I was an an interior
designer actually oh wow so you know if
you have design like like housing yeah
mostly like yeah mostly like for like
you know rich people they would hire me
and then I would give them like very
high prices for very minimal work uh but
like but like lovingly and and um oh
thank God that guy would not leave me
alone I would focus on floral vintage
Aesthetics oo some fancy and then uh I
was pretty lonely for a while uh in the
zombie apocalypse but you know I've
found groups like this before but they
are never they never last they never
last um and now I've been on my own for
a while and you know I'm ready I'm ready
to take on another group I'm ready to
open up again and we're glad you're here
thank you thank you I I feel very
welcome to be honest so I'm very happy
about that how about you what did you do
before the zombie apocalypse me I I was
a menace to society I was I did I was
unemployed I had no job I freelo loaded
so I'm kind of glad Society fell during
this zombie apocalypse so everyone can
start over and be equalized because I
was just like some of the earth you know
MH would you argue your life is better
now than before yeah my life is better
now cuz like everybody everybody has
nothing so we're all the same like
playing field now yeah okay don't you
think usually you would want to push
yourself up instead of bringing other
people down well how does that make you
feel now I can now I can you know so you
feel like you've gotten a second chance
this is this is this is my second chance
at like yeah and now you've become like
morally very positive and supportive and
he exactly before I was just like you
know unemployed looking at wow all those
rich people with their um switches and
ps5s and I was really jealous but now
nobody has any and you're like a vtuber
that's unrealistic no one has PS5
somewhere about
it what is a PS5 what is it what is but
no I understand that's good I'm happy
that you get to put on a leave okay I'm
opening
it oh okay one SC fun one first eight
kit pipe baton if anyone wants a baton
Bandit armor plating mod um I'll take
the scrapping for I'll just I'll just oh
no someone else can take it I'm over
encumbered can I take water from here
please do someone want to be a nerd I
have electrical traps magazine and a
medical journal that sounds I want a
medical journal
if I don't want to be a nerd I'm stupid
do you want to pick this up I'm over
inir all I see
scrapping for
fun banded armor actually maybe I want
scrapping instead of medical
H I don't want to make decisions before
we talk to the others maybe they already
made decisions oh it's raining it's
raining it's raining Reapers zombies
Hallelujah there's a house
there I'm going to
keep I don't know I found some good
stuff
oh we still have not found water yeah
water's the big concern
here I'm cucumber I think we have to oh
okay I can take the rest I'm not to
cucumber I'm just going to I'm just
going to put some seeds and flowers I
don't know if we
need okay I think there's like a way I
don't know how but I think there's a way
to craft like a water like a rain okay
oh yeah just a zombie rain collector
St I'm trying to I don't want to be
trapped okay I just put some random
stuff in the
chest oh oh your have phone I want
that it's
[Music]
raining that's weird why is it alive
it's raining myy
dude okay um how are we feeling what
time is it does anyone know what time it
is oh 2 p.m. only we can go we can keep
adventuring if we want to but we are
pretty and
cucumber maybe we should head back to
the farm just once to the farm uh not
the farm sorry our home okay okay okay
okay let's head back home put all our
stuff back and then we can keep if
anybody wants extra arrows I put it in
here cuz I don't have any room oh nice I
need arrows okay nice nice nice I'm
going arrow for where'd you put them B
and this chat okay I'm going to grab it
sorry you guys are going to have to not
see me for a minute um as I'm resetting
stuff oh
nice oo trash
pile M
trash I do think put feathers away put
the
plant oh I can still hear her voice
I can hear come here come
here here
air okay I'll go back for
now okay oh there's a fireplace this
house is kind of nice
actually it is pretty good I'm not going
to Li it seems a little bit better well
well whatever let's just but the other
one has a pool table yeah you're right
sorry and the and the what is it called
the
TVs PCS yeah the PC setup it doesn't
work but it's still really cool yeah all
right we didn't go underground oh she
already is here okay she probably looted
everything scared
me did you loot
everything no I just looked around and
killed things okay let me loot then yeah
yeah so the general rule is uh vc1 is
our home base and then all other ones
are different groups that are going out
on excursions together yeah don't really
know if proximity chat really works in
this game
so was really weird because it worked
the other day when we tested it didn't
it
Kelly yeah it did which is extremely
strange so w maybe it's based on if
there's like less people so smaller
amounts of people could work uh we were
the same though we were four earlier and
we were four the other day as well so
yeah I I tried it earlier during testing
and no one could hear me when I was out
of the party it only worked when I was
in the
party yeah and even then it wasn't
proximity in the party it was just uh
General chat General yeah whatever like
a radio oh well it's okay I feel like
this is working especially when we're in
a little bit smaller
groups oh I think so too yeah yeah
little oh I found gasoline oo
nice uh he's alive beware of dog I'm out
of stamina food in here okay I found
pumpkins and I found eggs and so much
meat there's 30 raw meat bi boo cook us
something delicious please okay I will
let me cook let her cook okay I'm back
at the base so I'll jump into the other
VC for a minute but if you guys want to
do more Adventures I'm down after after
we regroup yeah okay okay
hi
guys how is how do you say it again like
I'm home I'm
[Music]
home no that's the wrong
one okay we got some stuff go you have
food yeah we found food yeah 30 meat we
Hunters we have meat yeah as as the
I I will say you are the leader of this
group am I um wouldn't you say it would
be very much smarter to like move to a
house that is closer to the trader yeah
I think that's a good idea I think for
now this is an okay first base bro you
guys are blocking my way you're
welcome oh no sorry yeah maybe we
shouldn't come here because we have a
crate that's full of food for example
we're going to need to move everything
moving is hard
maybe can make a second house yeah a
second home SL move everything yeah yeah
I'm going to keep these shotgun shells
though yeah any goodies that you find
just dump them and I think everyone
should get um a bone knife at a certain
point cuz they're really
useful bone knife and then I'm going to
make a magazine crate and please only
take the ones that that you think you
want to kind of minmax yourself on I
personally am doing like a fortitude
strength thing but for example there's
like a medical journal I have an
electrical journal for
nerds if you're a freaking nerd what do
you guys have you have you found any
other journals so
far an academic
one an she's a she's a what is it called
she's a
scholar freaking po Dexter all righty
she she did she's the winner she's the
winner of the spelling be so that true
does anyone want to try going to the
trader so we can do some Trader quests
because I feel like that's where the
food and stuff will be easiest to get
and water he doesn't water the water
would be very nice I definely need water
but first can we get a snack can you get
a little snack first I'm very hungry can
you guys who you're at the house when
you go to the trailer can you bring some
food with you the only one that can cook
from us is bi Bo and I don't know where
she is right now so yes we'll TR need
more chefs and I'm so thirsty oh I'm so
water I can give you I'm so thirsty feel
so bad but I about to die take it thank
you take it okay so we let's wait wait
let me ask what B's doing one sec I'll
be right
back B B I'm I'm behind you the P two
people over the what the the H uhhuh
over the what over over the pondera over
the ponderer I thought you were like a
pondering no no no that's not me I'm not
f look you you shank so good for someone
who didn't do anything at past life
shank well that's not me wait you're
like a native Londoner wait that's I had
one skill I had one skill in my in my in
my past and I was shanking people to
survive so you know it carried over
Wonder so you're the
Sherer I'm the shank Shanker she's a
Shanker no I'm the Shanker yes okay
there's like literally not much here
um there's clay okay we're good we I am
I have come here to beg you for food
over oh okay sorry we only have corn
well no I have no we have like a bunch
of meat we have like 30 uncooked meat or
something oh well I'm surviving on
corn eating my corn you want to go home
so we can cook the the corn and then I
can give everybody okay over thank you
see you over okay see you there over
I okay I have begged and the cook is on
her way and she will make us all food
yeah and then we can go on an adventure
to the trader and see if we can oh I
found coffee disgusting you have coffee
we're starving you have
coffee she went to
Starbucks you had like 30 on meat or who
was that was it
you 30 I have dirty meat I put it in the
crate can't you cook
it well it's uncooked it's
uncooked this reaction is
genuine okay let me see if I can cook
this one this one's genuine this one's
genuine wait so how do you get water
from a river do you just like how do you
drink it I'm punching it but I don't get
any water yes I think that's how it
works you punch water to drink you
absorb it through your skin it's
when it's raining look up and then start
with your
mouth that's a
spirit yes ladies yes open you w even
there when we've been through this and
you judged crony for it what what these
other people in this call don't know
that yeah I don't know what you're
talking about what do you mean you
talking about yeah no what you're just
selling CR what are you what what
actually happen or are you guys messing
what I have diarrhea no like it did
happen you have a lot going on yeah a
didn't know you were going to traum like
that all of a sudden I was just reading
out what it said somebody have golden R
flers you know what this is a safe space
everyone should be allowed to like talk
about that oh my God there's a diarrhea
I Ion on the screen oh I don't want to
see what that looks like
jeez whoa I want to see that oh my God
try eating some more sham
sandwiches oh you'll get
there I'm back sorry about that sorry
forit but just a flower is not enough
right you have to O money you have Bo
you have to oh Al I'm infected uh I need
to take Antics we'll call you when the
time comes don't worry yeah no for
infection I've just been uh eating honey
for tree stumps it's really efficient
good idea I'll oh I see the diarrhea
symbol now oh you got diarrhea let's go
diarrhea gir
yeah Yi let's go diarrhea
mating yeah let's share a toilet
together not
to I feel like we've all been like
isolated as survivalists for such a long
time that it's hard to G is that is that
romantic are they flirting I'm not
sure I think it's bonding for sure yeah
it's dire times get
[Applause]
it silly oh welcome home
[Music]
okay I brought
um
pot I dropped like 30 meat on you I can
make bacon and eggs and I can make
boiled meat so I'm going to make God
blessed the heavens I'm staring please
what's full
ky's eggs T mon let me cook so lucky
that we have to make bacon and eggs for
us can you make tea too
bio um let's see with the golden
flowers oh I can found a golden rod flow
oh I Ked
myself water as well oh please yeah we
need that yeah it if you have murky
water I can purify it I have that really
I think we have some wow that's
cool okay I'm going to bake it and eggit
two uh murky water I'll drop it for you
here you go yay y yeah look how cute our
house natural murky for the murkiest
reasons a nice first house but we
definitely want to get one closer to the
Traer yeah actually it's okay since
we're near a river with our empty
bottles we could theoretically go near
it GA water and just like boil that
endlessly I hope wa you guys have
bottles I don't have bottles I thought
the bottle pred infinite water trick you
guys get bottles just open your mouth
look up open your mouth why would they
do
that how do I split a stack I'm
blind I think right right I'm just going
to do a quest now then
okay oh I figured out okay
thanks have you seen the Traer yet K if
anybody has any more cooking books uh
please give them to yes I will give them
to you I do see I don't actually know if
it's like super important to be honest I
don't want to I don't want a railroad
and be like oh we have to be super
careful when I have when I don't know
but this is just like my inclination but
maybe I'm wrong so just take it with a
yes I am at the I have some Golden Rod
flowers can you boil them so that I can
drink them okay we can drink him okay
thank you how do I cup I'll just drop it
okay and I'll also craft armor so I'll
read this I'll go for medic if you want
give me the medic
thingy what's too expensive oh the
medical journal I put in the journal
crate
journalate so I need I need one more
level in cooking if anybody has
any Okay cooking magazine cuz I can't
make te
yet
okay the trader sells the tea that
you're making for 144 coins what I don't
even know to get coins how Earth we have
coins that's crazy that's crazy my
diarrhea is going away on thank you sir
anyway did I take the quest I'm happy
cook a bunch of meat right now I found
some acid if you think that could help
your he
problem it would help with the liquids I
guess don't really oh beep do you want
to put the the cooked food in this one
the storage which one the right one and
we should try to figure out how to make
the one that the one that you're looking
at yeah are where I need to go for my
fetch Quest when did you take this Quest
oh I think you're sharing cuz we're in
the same
party all right I'll put the purified
water in there for now well how are you
already there oh I was just walking wait
I don't think I can do it for you
doesn't let me okay I'll wait here so
you coincidentally there the moment I
took it what oh you can label the
boxes okay I'm on my way
what you cook we can make we can make
glue I can eat
glue no no no no that's not that idea
I'm just grilling meat at the
moment okay awesome like a big
sleepover do yeah I love it you look
like the L how do I how do I take only
one item instead of all the items guys I
don't I know I'm stupid I also do not
know control right cck oh control right
water yeah
sorry I got to drink some that's okay
I've been dehydrated
water control
right am I finally like not as
dehydrated okay I took one water toy as
heck why can my skin not absorb the
water from from the skin can you
dehydrated the glass jars just disappear
not work that's stupid you eat them
why would the glass STS disappear after
using them am I just going to crap out
glass like cards now that makes no sense
the glass guys it's
raining how too bad we can't drink it
open your mouth yeah can I open my mouth
just right down your mou yeah
yeah you just have to look up at the sky
oh my God already drank all the
water excuse me you still at the quest
oh yeah I think you are please I'm so
thirsty and so
unwet we do be
drinking I can't tell if they were
kiding yummy charge me no we're not you
just you have to wait
incremental I've already drank oh spooky
storm okay I'm going to start should I
do is there anything we can do at night
oh oh probably stick around
cry I love cry to supplies in here I
hope the mushrooms grow inside there
golden rod Seed where
seed what there's zombies in here what
zombies what's wrong there's here okay
where is he stuck no I think she's doing
a quest the quest
I'm on my way it's really scary it's
it's dark and
rain oh maybe I can't Farm
[Music]
here I probably need to farm plot a
runting
flashh yeah we need a farm plot if we
want to
farm I'll man I can't make my hops does
anyone want to go to the Traer for Quest
if not it's totally fine oh I didn't run
rush I just thought if you going to do
something else though why can I not use
I got to go there anyway um the is going
to take a couple minutes to cook but I
put I put food in it keeps saying charge
meat B I think you have to like take it
out no no no charred meat is the food it
is the food oh really charred meat meat
is cooking huh at my no that's what it
said that's the option oh that's all I
can make right now I need one more book
to make make better stuff to take both
it's okay it's
okay here I'll put one
back
Chum you're going to eat my Char and
you're going to like it o it's so nice
and dry okay I'll cook some eggs too
I'll cook some eggs I'm dying you have
water wait why are you dying should I
not be here is it here you should be
here what's
happening wait should we go into a VC
the quest yeah we go okay yeah which one
two
four what okay Cecilia you wanted to go
to the right ready whenever you want oh
I want to go to the trader team okay I'm
outside chopping some wood okay Traer
team what VC should we hop into do you
think uh we can there ACH of VCS now
four let's take four Okay jump four
four yeah yeah think I could eat a raw
egg does this take place in America I'm
making I'm making boiled eggs if you
wait like a couple minutes oh cool I'll
just go put this egg back in the crate
then we can go oh it's so longer raining
my free water is gone what a shame I
know they hate me they just want want to
dehydrate my butt so evil they probably
just oh I found some water in the toilet
oh good I give it to me and I can purify
it drink it drink it awesome that' be
huge B I'm going to put it in the food
actually here I'm going to drop it on
the ground I really need water actually
so how can I unlock this drop okay there
you go
okay that's huge that's a really big
deal always check toilets ladies toilets
are full of water that if you boil it
you can drink it okay it takes 1 minute
to cook let me cook I am cooking okay
and then we can definitely we can go to
the tra the Trader's pretty far huh yeah
it's an adventure I mean it's already
9:00 p.m. we might die but that is true
but it's fine well just prepare your
spawn points you got your beds already
yeah that's true also you know we did it
last time it's fine it'll be fine have a
little water drink and then we can go go
sorry if you guys is water still you
guys have enough water you guys have you
guys decent I'm starving and dehydrated
but it's okay just how life is hydrated
but I am hungry oh there's a que I see
how cooking works there's a is that why
your meat is
charred Char meat's pretty good actually
no it's
dry okay he was going to be serving us
up sirloin steaks pretty soon I know it
oo I can't wait let's go my Gordon
Ramsay oh does it go into like straight
into the storage cases if I take it out
it shouldn't that's kind of
strange go
to I'm heading to the trader now I hope
I don't die okay we'll go we will go as
well but if you want to go ahead do it
uh Callie you to I am okay hold
on before it hits
night okay here you go here's some water
all right ready to
go thank you so much bioo let's run
ladies let's run close the door maybe
all right let's go
walking just walk there music now though
repair my
C
oo my map got marked with a traitor
yeah are they
sus we don't know yet no I believe
actually the Traer is very
hot hot as me like he's on fire no like
she's a beautiful lady oh beautiful lady
yeah hey Chad how do I drink my hands
won't let us live with her yeah I know
what a shame right I
know I'm on me way I'm in me m not car I
wish I had a car
empty hands e all right hope you guys
catch up yeah me
too do you know where you're going I'm
just following you I have a mark a
marker on my thing it's not really
working but I'm also dancing with a
zombie right now
[Music]
never
mind is the marker for the Traer is for
you guys is it the uh the orange one
it's called White River citizen for me
but I might be there oh okay yeah me too
everybody at home died what happened
uhoh huh they weren't at home right I
thought theying running I'm just past
the river
Let Me swim to
you oh I'm
wet maybe because I won't say it to make
a de collector a de collector
uhoh say it you
won't exactly challenging I
won't do you really think I will fall
for that trick you are yes how um oh oh
oh hello everyone guys I feel like it's
it's important for a social hierarchy to
find out how guy how old everyone is in
the zombie apocalypse
over oh that's not you guys that's
someone else you never asked a mustache
man is age but a man I thought this was
one of you
over you first over oh okay I'm
actually um
I'm okay I already Ellie I said I've
been in the zombie ocp for 20 years that
was a lie it was a hypoy it's just my
beard makes me look kind of old uh I'm
actually
only when when did the zombie apocalypse
start 30 minutes ago 30 minutes no but
like more like uh 2 hours ago actually
what really I found a wolf should I kill
it over can you take it over I don't
think so I'm running away over oh shoot
I ran the
way um I'm actually
uh I'm
20 forever
22 but mentally I'm 38 I'm 38 guys I'm
38 but I would like to be 22 you do
things for us then I'm I'm 47 I'm I'm
your senior oh oh you're younger than me
you're my k no I'm 40 you didn't you
just say your 30s I'm 470 oh oh wow
you're older than me oh wow you Grandpa
I'm I'm I'm your age plus whatever that
is plus four what so you
know am I a dog who
though okay I guess you are now guys I'm
so stupid I keep like taking my hand and
putting it on my ear like a
phone and I keep getting confused cuz my
hand isn't on my
mouse I'm so stupid can't even see it m
h oh hey hello I just killed like so
many things on the way let's go where's
the
Traer oh up here okay climb this
mountain yeah thought I did it yeah we
got a Skyrim pretend you're a goat yeah
I
did or is it just you wait do goats go
back yeah I I don't know but they do now
yeah
yeah no more thirst issues I found the
did you did you know that that there are
actually goats and sheep hybrids and
they're called
jeep
jeep Traer
wrecked trador act isn't the trader
closing isn't the trader closed yeah it
closes time limit when it show yeah oh
but I am okay I am drink the water if
you guys guys if you're in if you look
up in your map I I found like a whole
like house area maybe that would be nice
yeah you us to meet you there yeah since
I think the trader is closed I might be
wrong maybe check okay let's let's head
towards the CCE Mark then sure yep
yep got go to the CCE C maybe we even
find a house there all you can eat for
only
399 sorry you activated something inside
of me when you said that
I don't .99 commercials that's pretty
cheap oh I found some charred meat oh
this reminds me of people's
cooking tast like's cooking though no
mine has a special touch yeah she puts
like hair in it a special touch what do
you mean hairit of yellow hey just just
because I shed a lot doesn't
mean it gets in the
food that okay
well well yeah I have a lot of hair she
sheds hair she's a wolf yeah I shed like
a okay we're here okay I am here go
around I am in the in the
garage the garage I hear a bunch of zoms
on yeah there's two at the door
knock uhoh they're just they're
everywhere why did do that to fast ow
I'm maybe she wanted to
die I need to
heal wait why why is the door closed all
of a sudden I Clos it so that we don't
get ambushed from the other side I think
we might get ambushed inside though yeah
but it's safe it's
okay okay um I need to make my
bandages nice find though now I will
close the door he fre go oh I'm out of
stamina okay
[Music]
hey don't close
it we have less space
inside okay oh I'll open it yeah it's
not a good
idea definitely going to need to get
prepared ow oh trying to get in there
huh is that the house you guys are in
the walking I guess I can help we're in
the Goldsmith house right now the
Goldsmith residence yeah they like we
can get our own
houses that be great we could each have
our own homes that would be nice oh
sorry sorry I didn't mean it is here
come in come in you know what maybe
I'll I found a hidden basement o what's
in there zombie I hear
them hit him with my Bonk stick oh I'm
going to make more bandages I cannot
make more
bandages help you okay
big
Bonk good thing my strength is
unprecedented nice I've gotten much I
found I found a door to oh
God uhoh that seems bad you okay I fell
in a hole she really gave you a shock
huh all right I
guess
yeah there a lot of people here but it's
okay we keep hide we keep
hide ow ow ow ow hard oh they're all
really
fast she very so I guess it makes sense
okay oh crap oh crap there's two of them
on me I'm going to die guys I love you
good
night can't me
great I should have put a resting
thing no I'm dead there's two of them in
the garage as a head dang it um might
bead
back backpack but I found a really cool
area hole now I'm bleeding what that's
cool I died it's
over it's okay you found a really cool
area though I did find a really cool
area I'm cold and naked is it safe to
get my stuff in the G I think
so are you guys in a
garage I'm in a oh my
God if you're you're in a hole my stuff
is in there I know I'm in the hole but
there's like three in the hole so just
be careful coming up they're folling me
up the
hole that's
hiie okay I'm going to try getting my
backpack well my stuff is in a you guys
look a little different oh
god wow the whole place is just trapped
completely yeah search back everything
uhoh um I might have a problem your
backpack so I'll kill him I think it's
fine I'm
infected I'm stuck I'm stuck between
like five zombies this is not the way to
go I Don't Like
It Goodbye Oh
shoot I'm trapped I'm tra it is a good
good call
okay there is a way to get out yay a
world oh hello can you hey can oh is
that a
zombie all right like to spawn near in
my backpack again um my D is still in a
dream s eater get out of my way could
someone oh jeez leave me alone oh jeez
wish
Rick could someone make me a spear
because my back backpack is all I can't
anything not again no not you because I
think we're all dead oh was everyone
dead yeah am I the only
one uh I I got to get
it oh Jee however I think the tactic is
to oh shoot oh shoot why is
this
this to leave the house leave the house
if you die it's over this is very
interesting I'm taking I'm taking all
your stuff and then I'm running okay
okay I'm out
okay okay I'm outside I will sacrifice
thank you thank you Joy thank you you're
welcome you're welcome oh god oh no I
can't stop I now have to get my items
down there oh no because I took the
backpack I'm so
sorry I'm so sorry I'll run I'll run
back over there I'm so
s what is happening
it'll be fine it'll be fine you're not
that far actually yeah I got to get my
items again um you guys just get your
items and get out then maybe we can come
back as a group yeah I can't get my
stuff cuz cuz it's on the Upper Floor
and I can't reach it okay I got my stuff
I'm going to leave never mind I'm
totally dead no I don't want to die now
because I have Ki
stuff all right I'll wait until she's
back I will have to go and search I
believe in you and chat we already have
a base we have a base but we wanted to
make one closer to the Traer sneak
that's embarrassing I don't want to
sneak i t does feel very long that is
true okay yes it does a man this sucks
we got this we got this yeah we'll be
fine oh shoot this is very cold out
here oh they broke the ladder the r oh
my God
I don't know if I can collect myself St
myself in the I'm just going to kill
everyone in
here if I have to die I will die again
and again and kill everyone and take
them down with me it could be morning
soon you
know it's all right I'm coming back for
you guys mark my
words oh hi colie okay okay I'll drop
all your stuff here okay oh thank you
all of
it yes thank you so much for picking up
my stuff no I'm sorry for making you run
I'm going to kill them clearly you're
good would you be able to make me of
spear then I can help a little bit K
yeah I think I can make
K
oh I don't actually know if this is
yours I'm just punching them all
no let me see if I can make you spear
real quick
I got
out that's good I'm punching all of them
okay here you go even through all the
pain all right I think they should at
least be out at least I hope they stay
nice I got a spear okay okay I'm back up
put
your it should all be outside hopefully
uh can one of you put me out of my
misery okay you want to be
killed you're welcome thank
you always don't never hesitate to
guys we all support each other here
Callie put your clothes on oh shoot
you're right I'm
[Applause]
naked they're after you they're after
you you might want to run
call
actually after me does anyone uh come
after
them I got her arm busy what did you say
are you still in the house really fast
no no I should is that you oh that's you
yeah oh they all after you okay I'll try
going inside getting my backpack yeah
okay okay just keep running so keep
running like in like 5 Seconds keep
running oh we got a lot of exp that's
pretty good must mean we've done
something good okay so you said they
broke the
ladder oh yeah I got to go back there
though for my oh no I mean the the lad M
lad is still
there I got my stuff I got my stuff nice
if you can get my items that's good too
it's at the bottom of the hole though
the bottom of the hole I am currently
like all the way
upstairs that's
fine oh I can't
see oh she's dead nice job
team I sacrificed myself for you
sorry okay I'm going to try to get my
items okay they're kind of quick I got a
I found a sniper magazine like a sniper
book got be stronger I could if anyone
wants that we use a gun gun would be fun
I haven't found a gun I only found like
a magazine for it shot all my items are
recovered even if I die I don't care
yay thank you for cing them all
shy not bad thank
you bad Tech junky Tech
Planet I'll take the sniper magazine I
kind of want to be a sniper okay okay
I'll give it to you later do you guys
find any shotgun mags please tell me
what is music get out of
here it is morning time which means the
zombies should slow down no there's
still one after me if you guys want to
help oh I found medical journal my
backpack oh there you go
I well technically what taking this
house is just the floor sucks right so
we need to rebuild
it yeah I don't know if it's a good idea
living here though why not unless we put
all our blocks down then it could be
okay
yeah okay maybe if they stop
spawning is that a way to like crouch on
the floor do you sometimes see those
like tiny holes do you know if you can
do something about that control control
but it's not much of a Crouch
yeah it's very pitiful
we could also build our own home near
the trader but I think building is at
the beginning is going to be kind of
difficult very hard right yeah I think
so I think it's best to like y a
house okay do you guys want to go to the
trader then or do you want to stick
around here a bit longer sure let me go
there my two Health oh no take out of
her
misery did we pick everything here do we
loot
everything I don't think so I still hear
them in fact
oh hi my hello oh gosh the floor is lava
certainly I know I think you guys go
back inside oh you guys are back inside
yeah I got to get my corn
meal ooh Rotting Flesh yummy yum yum
delici my favorite I
know I am a bit over encumbered if
anyone has space and would like to share
the have no space uhoh I don't really
have space either I have like one slot
open I can't run
anymore it's
over maybe you should eat all your corn
I don't have any
corn oh an archery
guide
o guess I'll use that I could use
it someone's cucumber
this eat my corn meal
stay nice and strong I know heal my five
Health
yeah I was going to say like oh I
haven't been hungry in a while it's just
because we've been in a death Loop and
yeah maybe maybe it's a good tactic
though punishment of death it might be
yeah shame that's about it yeah that's
not I don't have that much it there are
a lot of houses around here right for
the picking though especially in the
morning time yeah I mean if we can
respawn your back packs I think it's
worth doing it um more you should put
clothes on I don't know why yeah you're
naked I accidentally have your clothes I
think when I picked up your backpack it
automatically put on your clothes on me
a that's okay I'm just making new ones
no worries I can I can come down and
just getting some loot real quick
already made it good is there any spam
mail what do you think is in this house
o Urban
combat who wants to learn oh this is for
stealth oh Urban combat combat's good
for everyone
actually Okay who wants to excel at
stealth I might go for archery oh I'm
doing aity so if you want to give me
steal stuff you can okay come here I'm
not I'm not going for strength or
anything but I'm going for I want to go
for strength I speed and Parkour
Speed that's like my aesthetic you guys
killing like an overwork I can't believe
you eh whatever oh hello
all right uh uh beibs I think I was call
you something else did you just call
me almost
apparently now go collect your Urban
combat thank you I'll take your corn in
the
meantime I'm a bit low prob someone in
the closet oh what a nice your backpack
fine one sec I I'll be right back one
sec guys oh yikes oh do you do you guys
know if this back shs do you know if I
can get there somehow
Maybe not maybe that's just like in case
there's monsters or something but it's
frustrating because I see it and I can't
you can't okay that's fine Al what the
heck is that
placement okay I think I got all the Lo
then of this particular area okay I'm
going to go back on another base closer
to the trader huh okay I'm back but I'm
I cannot walk so I think I'm going to go
back home because like I can literally
not walk anymore yeah I might do that
too do you guys want to do that yeah we
go
let's let's loot this house finish
searching this house and then we can go
yeah I'm I'm I have like two slots left
so I can't like I cannot physically do
anything I'm going to go in cucumber
yeah uhoh yeah me too he's waking up
I'll go because I can't Sprint so I'm
going to be slower than you guys I'll
just go home it's okay I'm going to be
slow too we're going to I'll be
slow yeah I'm cucumber now yeah
nice too B crotch shots don't work on
zombies what a shame I was crotching I
don't think they can feel their
crotches there oopsie they can't feel
the love
tonight
G I'm playing a dangerous game
there I don't know what you're talking
about what a small house oh I got a
little achievement for eating Char me
size of the house that matters you're
welcome now who is complaining about my
cooking did I complain or did I say it's
uh wonderful beautiful
amazing guys back me up isn't that what
I said didn't I keep praising her about
her great cooking and how much I love it
oh oh yes I I remember I remember
that it was like yesterday day of
September no I don't remember that
anymore actually I have amnesia
but I don't have real Amnesia I have
plot Amnesia so it's okay when the plot
asks for it I don't know what's going on
so that apparently charred meat will
make you thirsty though so be careful
that makes sense oh no you need you need
something to wash down your steak are
you ready to have back shory yeah I'm
just going to equip the medical thing um
I learned medicine just now because I
don't want to be incumbered okay when do
you when do you want to head back that
let's head back yeah let's head back the
Malone res will be mine though
eventually just not right now oh can we
invite s to the party so I can see your
marker better oh yeah you bet oh I'm in
a different party how do I leave the
party there I sent you a a
request oh okay is this technically
cheating on my other party yes no you're
with us right now they'll understand
they'll understand is this one oh wait
how do I join your party how do I leave
a party
oh I guess I got to got to kick people
out here I'll make GG leader see see you
guys there you
go excellent and then how do I how do I
leave
party that's a good
question okay okay I can join a party
now you might have to send me the thing
again okay let's
see
by great now let's head back to home I
suppose I hope they don't think I'm a
home wrecker or technically you guys are
the home wrecker I guess I mean have
your relationships in that party been
family or relationships
already well well F put her bed next to
mine oh my God I don't want to be any
part of this w sitation a candle in the
room I haven't had time to sleep next to
her yet though cuz we can't really
sleep that is messed up though I can't
believe you would do that to her oh I
didn't do anything you guys are the home
record technically didn't like commit
yet they didn't sleep next sleeping her
on that's messed up I I didn't do
anything I think you guys are a home
record we didn't do anything we didn't
even know you were sleep next to each
other buddies you never asked now you
has to take responsibility
responsibility
disclaim
that not remove the guilt from your
life guil it's
okay I'm morally flexible today more
eggs for bi to cook for me thought yeah
I will cook eggs oh yeah that's a good
idea I'll pick up all the eggs the
killer cook oh wow we did catch up to
yeah I told you I'm really
slow oh you mature okay you're not slow
you're oh wait no that's Callie okay
never mind that's fine we'll catch up to
you
eventually shotgun farmer I do need to
find closer to the home than I am I
think because I'm really really really
slow oh yike man I'm growing tired
because you're cucumber I am oh I am I
am cucumber oh I didn't even know that
we could hold more stuff than we have it
just makes us slower yeah it just makes
you slower yeah I didn't know that I
mean depend on the weight
probably music is actually kind of
nice you have
music yeah I mean it's part of the
game in game music yeah why don't we
meet CeCe to help her carry some stuff
where let me find no it's okay I'm
almost home she too slow she's not on my
map she's the yellow
one oh it's okay it's okay I'm almost
home
here man I feel like a like a jaguar or
something running for
home yeah you're really bounding
bounding for it do have those do those
type of animals have
hes I don't think so I think they just
like sleep wherever well I mean some
animals have dens but I don't
think those that big cat does have like
a d we ask wolves she has a home you
think she just roams around steals
internet from
people yeah yeah just like
beep can't believe it oh my god oh it's
so slow you did say that you were like a
moer in your P left didn't you oh oh
yeah I I was a street
rat
yeah but it's but she's turned off a new
Leaf but it it really talks about how
much you feel that you're openly talking
about it you know yeah you could hided
from us we still don't know what and did
before so you know they might be hiding
something I might be hiding something
they might be hiding something know what
are they hiding let me let me ask kaha
for the book uh or maybe they're out on
adventure still we make gunpowder sure
oh never mind they're like really
far please let me
know all right we can eventually shoot
things I can't
wait yeah we definitely got to talk to
the Trader though cuz that's going to be
a big a big Point turning point for us
so we better go to the trader soon yes
yeah in the next 2 hours or so cuz
that's about all we have right
yeah maybe we can make a little list in
the Discord of like magazines that
people want that might help yeah okay I
want to be a farmer oh yeah I want decks
built related and
cooking
okay I want to be a med and maybe
something like I haven't decided like
Electronics or mechanic or something
maybe mechanic I'm I'm not sure
yet I have a I have a tech
junky you're back oh you're really hot
the you are panting I'm telling you okay
uh the sniper I don't remember who
wanted the sniper I'm putting it in here
oh I want it I'll hard farmer I'll give
you this magazine it's a tech junkie
that might be good for you
okay electrical traps is that the one
or look
that's bu I don't think this Bas pulled
out for like seven days oh hey the trees
s days to
die yeah oh I see what you did did you
end up making new clothes by the way o
armor piercing ammo okay I'll take
that all right should we head out soon
to the Traer so we have like plenty of
time to loot as well
one sec I have to like organize all my
stuff just since it's morning time let
me see if I can make a better
Club you going to go
clubing I wish I want better machine gun
pipe pistol pipe shotgun how do we make
that oh glue short I need four short
iron pipes I think we have that they're
in this one in the one I'm standing in
front really yeah but I'm interacting
with it one sec do I have 9 mm what what
do you say is 9 mm how can you tell like
pistols
maybe also we should try and go after
air drops there should be one every uh
hour but I don't know how to track them
oh they can leave us supplies but they
can't pick us up oh yeah sadly it's
messed up right yeah oh iron pipes yay
and then what was the last one so much
stuff I'm a little bit overwhelmed um my
God
put this in
here pipe
shotgun yay I'm making a pipe pistol
nice cuz I have bullets for it do we do
we have a box for like bullets that I
can put it in no no I don't think so we
I'll just use the one with a magazines
then if you have if you have 9 mm you
can give it to me I'll use it I put it
in the
Box okay this is how do you name boxes
oh
SC um hold e and then there should be a
rename option I think
oh here let me rename the food
one there you go food how do you how is
the Box what's the name so I can make
some huh what is it called in the in the
in the in the building
menu oh it make a box a CRA hold up
building block I think it's and then
when you place it down I think if you
hold R was it yeah hold R it can change
it to different shapes
oh okay I also was able to do it using
the crate thingy I think is this the one
yeah okay thank you oh yeah yeah okay
I'll just put all my stuff in here and
then if you have like a lot of items for
it you can upgrade the building blocks
oh cool look iron building blocks at
some point yeah maybe we want to make we
want to really fortify our home for the
first rush so finding out iron how to
make iron blocks might be really
big we were we'll have to look for
it okay I'll put some here in my B in my
home you might want to make like traps
and stuff like that as well to put
around yeah that'll be
fun what's
wrong did you fall in your own Spike
trap what happened what what happened
what did you do that was such a jump
scare
huh did the game glitch out no no no no
I I one shot I one tapped you in the
head with my gun why would you doing
that you
criminal I didn't think you would kill
her like instantly I didn't
shoot someone in the
head you're so messed up I can't believe
it humans
be can't believe you murdered your
friends messed up thought you cook for
me you served me a meal a five course
meal of death good though it's a lot
here I'll give you I'll give you some
meat as a sorry take take my cooking I
accept your one Shard meat I believe it
thanks
bigups uh your life is only worth like
one charred meat yeah that's horrific I
feel really sad about
that oh well up yeah yeah I just had to
test it one time okay the intrusive
thought took over I didn't think it was
going to kill you and people thought I
was bad
huh let's see where can we put Spike
TRS probably around the house maybe a
little distance though yeah just a bit
of distance I'm going to try to make a
balcony so we have like an Escape Route
a place to shoot
from good
idea weot oh I can technically make I
still I can't really heal yet I need one
more Med kit medical and then I can make
first eight bandage oh nice that's H but
I think I'll probably need
wait two wheels bicycle chass bicycle
handle ball five Medical
okay okay I'm ready whenever for when if
you guys I'm
ready just don't get my way or I might
accidentally shoot you
but accidentally on purpose oh these are
cross bols not arrows
work I was recommended I scrap them can
I not do this hey I completed a
challenge oh it's true it's
[Music]
true yeah iron iron y okay we got to do
something with the iron though we got to
figure out how to cook it or something
like
that I think you can make a furnace at
some point ooh
potato I feel like we need to find a way
to like be able to get
regular water drinking water there must
be a way to mass produce water I think
that's like collecting like collecting
water you know like a rain collector
stuff like that oh oh my God the the
spikes but we also get water from the
trader when we do quests he gives you
like rewards and you can pick water I
think water every single time yeah there
only five shells there's only five all
right is everyone ready yep ready to go
okay I use that on an enemy I must not
let my blood lust take over oh we can C
we can craft a du collector that's what
it is we can craft a d colle so yeah if
we do that that would be nice yeah it's
we need something called a polymer
something or another workstation we have
polymer of those oh yeah workstation uh
so a certain skill will unlock being
able to make the workstation is robotics
oh we like a 100 scrap Hol Advanced
engineering yeah I see well let's the
Traer for now okay and then try and get
the advanced engineering skill under
intelligence you guys that'll help us
create Workshop or workbenches okay all
right why does why does someone put a
random door in
here who could say you're being a little
silly all right Traer
time guys ready to run a kilometer
together yeah this is a bonding
experience should I sing a song do you
guys want to sing a song okay I'll sing
a song I'll sing a song in German uh and
then we all do it together wait how does
it go right you know it's like this 10
bottles on the
door beer on the wall 10 bottles on the
door and tonight will be the night that
that I will fall for
you
[Music]
over another door in here
um and then
um I miss you where are you where are
you
and I cannot sleep I cannot eat
tonight and tonight will be the night
that I will for
you don't worry wait maybe we can make a
song that's like related to us
so we have to
Shaker school trip this all right uh
what's up right we huh oh I just heard
am I crazy I felt like I just heard
someone join the voice call never mind
never mind I'm illusion likeo voice
maybe yeah was I yeah I thought so too
right bye I thought they were there for
a second kill it kill it kill it kill
the rabbit
K what the B the rabbit that's messed
upie I can't believe you just I can't
believe you but it's food I'll miss you
oh it's to fast for me to shoot wait
where is it where is it where'd it go
it's uh over Over
Yonder oh wait how do I how do I
release dang it really worth
it how do I cancel Maybe not maybe the
meat isn't that that worth it may yeah I
don't think it's worth it to waste my
bullet son of funny yeah let's not let's
not do it yeah dang it can't even col my
arrows away all right sorry about that
anyway it's the Ping okay I missed
because of the Ping I don't it's it's
fine no wores I don't believe it's
scroll wheel what I tried I'm I'm
pressing
doubt um this this server is not close
to me there is definite ping here but
people but people haven't you I mean the
Shakura haven't you learned about your
past experiences it's okay to admit
weakness sometimes it means gross yeah
yes and I will admit weakness but it was
definitely the Ping of oh okay so this
you're admitting the weakness of the
server that's one step the server itself
is weak it's like a sideway step I I I
get it you know my dad told me when I
tried to play the bass in his band one
time he said you know myy it's okay to
admit when you suck at something a
that's okay to admit when you suck at
something but that's not
nice hey I I will admit my flaws like I
will definitely go for the beef and
fall oh understandable yeah I've seen
I've seen your tweets so I believe
you hey with the traitor how do you get
in Traer wrecked wait wait this is not
the Traders never mind this is Bor Barn
Fields oh that's a little different yeah
whoopsy Dole oh we can collect corn here
though oh I need corn I'm
hungry Carl would we go to Carl's corn
Carl Carl
Carl are
friends is
that you become one with a
corn corn they're Corning
the cornering cor the corn is cornering
huh hey I found people it looks like
they're digging their grave oh really as
it like real people as it as it w and
crony are here digging their graes that
sounds like something NPC their own
graes yeah I thought they were like real
people anyway I'm going to the trader
yeah I'm also I'm getting distracted but
I'll go to the Traer as well okay I
wonder why they're digging maybe they're
getting items
oh it say they're preparing their
grave I'm at the board barn or something
get stop getting distracted I'm coming
I'm coming and Carl's
corn am I supposed to go to the
barn you can avoid it if you want this
is a nice house not saying that we
should it is a nice house this is a nice
house o I found
the
magazine it's really nice when Farm it's
not nice anyone they're keeping people
in cages no that's that makes it even
nicer actually it's like a
holiday yeah they're like well fed and
taken care of yeah it's like a spa
experience have you never wanted to be
in a you know just
like Grace be behind bars I mean you've
done that a lot so no I I have I've been
in jail enough I do not want to be in
jail again can you believe B's in jail
that's crazy to
me yeah I was are you sure you can't do
you do you really think that's crazy
when I shot you in the head Point Blank
and killed you I mean but that's in the
game right no we're talking about in the
game oh look at the piggy wait aren we
don't kill the piggy I like the piggy oh
never mind kill the piggy kill the piggy
uh-oh having some trouble with the boys
the piggy deserves death now where did I
even put the chat oh my God I'mma eat
your body tonight baby
job I going to skin this pig okay you
shank it she makes a good point
yummy wait am I going the wrong way I'll
see you guys in the Traer I'm orange
what is this there's a pig in a cage I
leave this pig for now pig in a cage you
SS like some Gordon Ramsey recipe
picking a
cage Gordon ramsy recipe I also I'm
indors it's
Smokey why is it so Smokey I think if
you guys follow Callie she's like
basically at the Traer right now okay
sorry we went in this house we're doing
some looting first yeah I got distracted
I found some loots shoots distracted
again yet again oh they have oh wait
there's another Pig Bes prepare to kill
this pig and case it's mean but for now
for now maybe it's okay oh I think it's
just e
I heard there's a for now but
I oh there's a
zombie are you kidding me I did it I'm
got tra Not Dead
Yet Traer
wrecked that's bad that Miss somehow
okay now I got it there was a hot girl
in the in the the trailer not the
trailer the the beginner's course
video who is this guy sorry I'm only
into like that's just an honest
independent business owner okay you have
to stop being so
superficial he's got a lot of good
inventory but do we even have any he
what did you think of
Leon oh he's oh oh it's here he's cute
he's got Al I don't know how to feel cuz
like he might have a thing for aah so I
can't trust a man who might have a thing
for someone else still although I think
that's version yeah oh there's a cooking
grill oh oh we need that I make corn
with it corn I got it
okay we can steal from this I'm probably
going to let myself die cuz I only have
five Health anyway all right I got a
buried treasure Quest but got money all
can you pass me the grill I'll hold on
to it yeah here I dropped it thank you
we can make corn now nice nice that a
big a big thing I won't be too
far actually that's crazy good funly
food yeah finally we have like a regular
food stores with the grill to pay all
the I already made a
shovel all right ready to dig wow I
don't know what happened in this house
but I there's a story oh so they weren't
digging their own Graves they were
digging for for buried
treasure that makes sense part of a
quest I like idea of them uh digging
their own Graves though I have a I have
a weapon for you Sor this one's better
probably here thank you oh I actually
have that too I just don't use it I'll
use it
now oh that one's like not
broken okay what I what should I get rid
of sometimes a zombie might spawn though
if you
dig we k
candles look for that supply
Crate yeah Diggy Diggy Hole all right
are we done here
s now all right I'm coming we're coming
to you
guys oh it's the
big lot of polymers a
big uh I I'm out side of the farm I'll
wait for you oh wait how do you how do
you get out what's the best way get I
jump I jumped out the window that a good
idea oh God my mouse oh my God what's
happening destroy my way out
actually give me give me 5 Seconds
girls
girls I think I'm too sleepy I think I
got to go to bed I was going to ask I
youed yawning a bit yeah
sorry I'll again tomorrow I was
fun thank you for
organizing see you tomorrow good night
see you tomorrow home record home
record
no oh no I'm too sleepy sorry I mean I
streamed quite a bit a little bit so it
was fun I I liked it so far I think the
obviously the beginning is a bit comp uh
chaotic but I feel like we found a very
nice balance of like voice chats and
stuff and it's nice to hang out with the
with the girls and uh I don't know maybe
I shouldn't go M actually maybe I should
let someone else take care of that I'll
become a collector or something
something that isn't too uh but yeah so
tomorrow hey I have a schedule I have a
schedule I can show you my schedule uh
tomorrow I'll join again uh I'm not 100%
sure about like the streaming povs I
kind of want but it's it's it's it's e
well I mean wasn't like hard to do but
I'll think about it I'll let you guys
know um but they will also be a stream
at 900 p.m. CSD uh I will be playing my
own personal horror game which is z ma
mask and then the rest of the week I
it's probably going to be like half life
on Friday
and um maybe again on Sunday I'll let
you guys know I just wanted to get the
schedule out today before the nap so I
didn't finalize any of the games uh is
that a horror game when I played it many
many many many many many years ago the
mask freaked me out so badly I couldn't
get past the first cut scene so this is
me facing my fears quite literally and
we'll see how that goes um I've never
really played a 3D Zelda so I'm kind of
excited actually I did play Ocarina of
Time but like don't really like I didn't
get far and I don't really remember it
like I've played played it but not
really um but yeah have fun thank you
for joining me and see you all for
normal stream tomorrow at night and then
for everything else whenever it happens
my mouse is laggy okay thank you very
much for hanging I know it's a weird
time but I appreciate um and if you're
watching the VOD thank you for watching
the VOD see you all I'm going to go
right to sleep I think I'm really sleepy
actually it kind of hit me just now kind
of hit me okay but I had fun I don't
mind I don't mind being sleep it's just
you know I don't want to I do want to if
I sleep I sleep that's fine okay bye
everyone see
[Music]
ya and so the Ponder pondered some more
sleeping calmly
wondering what for what for Was he alive
what for was he did he take the KN and
RAM it into his enemies because that's
what he wanted to
do what
for what for was his life what for what
for was this knife if not for stubbing
[Music]
to