[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
do
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
hi first of all i know i'm i'm lagging i
know
at least it's working it's weird though
because it's um supposedly a good
internet
but
still legs i don't know why
it's probably because i'm using a
wi-fi not the cable
ah
now me mama say hi
is not gonna be streaming with me but
she's gonna go home now she just helps
me carry my shopping bags
yeah it's really late and i actually
also can't stream for long because i
need to
wake up early
done yeah actually i i stopped calling
her navi mama because
in public it was kind of weird
to say mama to her so i started saying
navi-chan
yeah i'm gonna be done
and then we're done
[Music]
[Laughter]
navi mama
and
we did so many things and yesterday too
so i'm gonna talk a little bit about it
um
but not too much i i think
i know it's already almost midnight so
yeah by almost midnight
[Music]
thank
is
[Music]
oh my god i don't i can't move
do i have to
stop lagging
oh no i keep on lagging sorry guys
better than nothing i think
[Music]
don't leave
it
get home safely
thank you
[Music]
i go
stay safe
[Music]
every day we hang out at the end of the
day her phone batteries are like zero
percent they're they're like three
percent now so i had to charge it a
little bit there you go oh
yeah
18 percent let's go
because we're both the type of people to
not have uh power banks with us
now i don't really need it because at
the end of my day end of the day here my
phone has
71 percent
more than me because she was using like
google maps and taking a lot of photos
[Music]
she never charges her batteries so her
batteries are weak it seems yeah she's
she's here at the end of the day with
three percent well i'm here with 71
damn holy [\h__\h] but yesterday it wasn't
that much i feel like yesterday
um
like when doesn't it kind of like when
you're when when your phone gets really
hot
it uses more batteries right and
yesterday because of the heat outside
my phone was also getting really hot and
then i think it had
way less batteries at the end of the day
yeah yeah yeah true
okay so navitan
totally
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
okay
hello kiki
once again hello
so nabi mama left uh she just said hello
there's actually not gonna be a real of
collab because i think
she doesn't really want to stream
and i will respect that so
i might stream alone tomorrow again
yeah
ah welcome to korea thank you
yes uh i've i arrived
on the 11th and today is
the 13th so
it's been
two days tonight will be my third night
so
but i already feel like i've been here
five days
because i've been doing so much thank
god the rain stopped yeah actually um
weather report for today for example
was like rain almost all day
so i brought my raincoat and
my
um i was wearing my raincoat and my
um i was bringing my umbrella but then
the moment i arrived
in the station
that uh i was gonna meet up with navi
mama
it stopped raining
i was like what the [\h__\h]
and then you know in the rental report
it said it's not gonna rain for two
hours or so and then it starts raining
again but no
the whole day no rain so
i really i will never ever ever believe
anything that a weather report ever
tells me
yeah
they're they're just always lying they
tell you oh it's gonna be so rainy and
you're like [\h__\h] you have it you can't
do [\h__\h] but then it's gonna actually be
a sunny day
and and but even though it wasn't
raining today at least it wasn't that
hot yesterday was so hot
but
yesterday we were doing some crazy
things too so
that kind of accelerated the heat
made it worse let me grab some water
also because i i set my room too cold
and now it's so cold i'm sitting here in
my raincoat just to warm myself up and
not be done was while i'm setting i was
setting up she was
uh
under the covers of my hotel bed
warming up because we are both freezing
alexander have you noticed today i
posted no including yesterday i posted
three pictures right
no way those are all today maybe those
altered all today free pictures
of
interesting chicken or egg related
stores
the first one was i'm not a chicken
the second one was
egg [\h__\h] which was fun to explain to
navi mama
the meaning of it
the moment i saw it i was like
oh my god
what a name for a restaurant
i
i explained it to navi mama in japanese
because we we talk in japanese because
she speaks better japanese than english
um so i said uh
i know
because the egg [\h__\h]
tamago
that's a promiscuous egg
and then and then uh
or is there any other meaning to it am i
taking it wrong is there a different
meaning to excellent and yeah apparently
i know it's not from korea but
i saw
all those
stories in seoul
it means that okay there's only one i
mean i don't know man maybe it had some
other meaning
[Music]
and then later uh those two i saw
yesterday because we were in the
apparently
the biggest shopping mall in
uh or the department
in seoul
i forgot what it's called nanda
oh i don't remember like any names of
the places
it's hard to
say because i don't remember any
names collects
apparently that's the biggest we went
there and it has like so many
restaurants
on one floor
uh and like some of them are like food
trucks inside
yeah so we had like kind of like a
really late lunch and then we
took some food out
uh
oh man where do i even start like i have
so much to tell
already from two days
i don't even know where to start
the car company yeah they i guess they
do more than just cars maybe they
sponsored the
the shopping mall i don't know what
they're doing but the building is called
the
hyundai
um
that was
impressive
the plane ride oh oh we started with the
plane ride huh okay
oh
yeah the plane ride was fine i took
um
[\h__\h] economy class
but
i treated myself to to a direct flight
so
i was thinking even
i take a diary flight
economy class or
i take a premium economy
but not direct because the problem was
um
i flew with korean air but they don't
have premium economy
unfortunately
and business
too
expensive [\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
i still have yet to make the experience
to ever fly in business man and even
though i fly so much in my whole life
it's always like with different airlines
that are not connected with like you
know
umbrella companies or whatever you call
them so i can't collect the miles or
like i i haven't i have yet to collect
miles
properly
to
get
like you know upgrades and [\h__\h]
even though i've
had like a million flights in my life
and also they they do
run out after a year or so right
yeah
korean air is awesome i miss flying with
them yeah so this was the first time i
flew with korean air
and i think it was fine uh
it didn't like
like especially stand out to me
in any way
uh
except oh my that was that way
besides that it was mostly um
just a normal airline nice a very
beautiful
flight attendance
very pretty
and so i got a direct flight and um
and and and holy [\h__\h]
interesting
how
ninety percent nineteen nine zero
percent
of the
flight
guests
were korean
flying back to korea
i was like one of the very few
non-koreans
i felt
like quite the foreigner
so like everyone was talking korean
yeah
that's normal i didn't know like when i
for example when i flew to tokyo a
million times
most of the passengers were foreigners
not japanese people
hmm
like
like normally it's always like a mix but
when flying to korea
there was an overwhelming
um amount of korean people not that
there's a problem with it obviously but
i was surprised
uh yeah i had to get a pcr
before flying and also a pcr when
arriving
which
is a little bit [\h__\h] mendocin very
annoying to have to do all that but at
least there is no quarantine so that's
good
but um you know actually because i i
barely
uh
for the whole
time of
cov id
i
i got you know i got vaccine and all
that and i've had maybe like a few tests
here and there before but not so many so
actually
i've never had
a pcr test
done by someone else that goes through
my nose
uh
i've never had that pleasure before
so
when i arrived in korea
it seems like i had no choice and uh my
virgin
nose was
um
what's the word
taken over
open and
my nose
they went so deep
it was like before
before the swap went in
i said please be gentle
cause i'm ticklish in my nose don't
don't go so deep
and then
yeah
at least it was really short but
it did go pretty deep and it did not
feel nice i don't want to do this thank
god i don't normally
normally i don't need real like pcr
tests for the things i do like a lot of
my friends with a normal job they have
to do regular testing
but you know i work from home so i don't
have to do that
you know
so
that's good but yeah no that was my
first time
i feel like my nose has been violated
[Laughter]
are you hearing me well guys by the way
i'm not really talking into the
microphone
uh
first scene
similar
yeah okay
um
so yeah oh yeah one thing that stood out
to me in korean air was uh
i was i was thinking sa suga
as
not as expected but i'm not surprised
their
um
uh the the flight safety video or was it
a just a pr video i'm not sure but the
thing that they were playing in the tv
inside of the plane on the seats
was [\h__\h] kpop it was some
k-pop boy band that i don't know because
i don't like boy bands
but is that that was that bts i don't
know what bts looks like
i don't know you can look it up probably
if you look up korean air
um in-flight
video or something like that you'll see
it's k-pop and it's like like so serious
but it's a song made for it
with the theme of like flying like they
sing something like fly high
yeah
yeah yeah
i'm like oh my god
honestly
a little bit
cringe when i was watching this
oh man
but so so cool though that day
put something so
modern and
i don't know
hip something so hip in there you know
i was
i was surprised but also
not surprised when i saw
that video come up in front of me
so anyway the the flight was absolutely
packed so
uh i did not have
the luck this time to have a seat empty
next to me
so i slept
in a like what a 10-hour flight i slept
like two hours i was [\h__\h]
like really and my flight
it was like in the evening and it
arrived around like noon
noon in korean time
so
um i was supposed to sleep during that
flight but i couldn't but i also
i didn't even watch
uh
the like in-flight entertainment
so what you might wonder what i was
doing
i didn't want to single thing
on the tv
i
actually i practiced
uh
korean
uh reading
writing reading writing on my phone
for a lot of the time
[Music]
cooking
yeah but i really have to do it every
day because otherwise i forget it even
if i learn like everything in one day
and i feel like oh now i know if i don't
do it for two days and i forget it so
i have to keep up the reading yeah
but i got some good practice yeah
so what else uh uh
[Music]
um
oh yeah
i tried those compression socks
i thought they might help because every
time i'm in a flight it doesn't matter
if it's just if it's a short one or a
long one
i have
really
unbearable
pain
in my legs
that
makes it really difficult to sit
comfortable not difficult impossible to
sit comfortably
so i tried compassion socks thinking
they might help
i think they helped a little bit
i think not hundred percent
but i have a feeling
they worked
to a certain degree which is nice
and uh taking them off was a pain in the
ass
holy [\h__\h] taking him on and off
on putting them on was more of a pain in
the ass
really wow i didn't but one question
are they
not just
um
tight socks
is that just
not just tight socks or is there
actually like something special
is a compression just because they're
tight or
that's it
then why the [\h__\h] did i pay 30 euros for
that couldn't i have just bought tight
socks
i guess normally people don't make tight
socks like not that tight
it did feel like
like you know it goes up to your knees
and at certain points it gets like
bigger and smaller you know like
like it's it's not like a normal sock
would be like the same
circumference
everywhere
uh but the yeah this one
they're like you know properly made
designed for the shape of your cuff to
be tight everywhere
anyway
[Music]
i tried that it says on the package that
the compression effect
loses itself after
half a year and you should buy new ones
is that
true or is that just
uh
so that you buy more
is that just the scam to make you buy
more or is it actually true i wonder
it is true
the fiber stretch
but really in half a year or is that
exaggerated you know like the the um
exp
exp expiration date on food
maybe no need to take it that seriously
a bit of both
ah
depends on how intensely you watch it
yeah apparently you have to be really
careful when you watch them too
anyway i'm sure my korean viewers want
to hear more about me being in korea so
let's um
let's get rid of that story so
i was
nervously
weirdly nervous about entering korea
i'm not sure why i was so nervous
[Music]
i don't know i was scared
that things would go wrong
and
i don't know i was i was really nervous
and also
i had some things
to come up uh
right
bef like
like right when i was like
uh going to korea
um
that were like kind of
time
sensitive and urgent uh and that made me
like
nervous and
stressed too it's like difficult to take
care of these things when i'm
traveling but
yeah
so but yeah i arrived and
holy [\h__\h]
so many
like it already before getting on the
plane
because i was going to korea like so
many password checks well
and then when arriving also everything
the the whole co v
id
process over there they take it really
serious i'm i'm impressed like
um
you
before you go to the passport check you
have to go to the
to the cov id check
and you give them
like a form that you filled out
and then they give you some information
on what you have to do
uh
you know
in in korea once arriving and they
basically force you to take a test
within the first 24 hours and all that
so yeah
yeah they take it pretty seriously
that's good
yeah so i go for that and then i
i went through
a passport check all okay then i waited
a million years for my
for my suitcase
but no worries
[Music]
nami mama was so late
um
so i had so much time
to go
um
get myself a pocket wi-fi
and change clothes out of my sweaty
gloves
and then i got my pcr test you know all
of these things navi mama was supposed
to be there she said she'll be there to
help me
but then i did everything alone
because she was like an hour late you
don't want to know why partially
she she says like she never comes to the
airport so she kind of you know
miscalculated and then
after miscalculating she did also go to
the wrong terminal and
uh going from one terminal to the other
with the train
takes 30 minutes
i've
i
i've been to bigger airports
where it takes less way less time like
uh abu dhabi
dubai sorry
uh
takes
from terminal to terminal
like
five to ten minutes
[Laughter]
but i know i know it wasn't a lie
because i took the same train and then i
realized holy [\h__\h]
it really takes 40 minutes to get from
one terminal to the other
so first she got up in the wrong
terminal
and then
then she went back into the train
because she realized oh [\h__\h]
it's not this terminal oh
so while she was slowly making her way
she arrived by the time that i was done
with everything
and you know what
it was all good it was all pretty easy
all pretty chill
uh
yeah everything went
quite well i changed money i got the
pocket wi-fi
i changed gloves and i got the pcr test
and then
yeah finally
finally i meet navi
and
she
she was
oh my the my first impression was
wow
k-pop idol
wow sasuka sasuka korea
so pretty
and fashionable and elegant and mommy
sorry mommy sorry
mommy sorry
sorry
no
yeah
she
she you know i'm a phoenix i'm pretty
old
and nabi mama is not a phoenix so she's
pretty young
but
navi mama dressed
way more
like an elegant idol than i did
i i dressed way more
childish
compared to her
so that was
that was overwhelming at first i
screamed when i saw him i was like
so cute
oh my god
i was in shock
yeah i was in shock
[Music]
and then she also did the same to me
though she also was like
okay
[Music]
i didn't hug her because i was [\h__\h]
sweaty
i didn't want her to think uh like as a
first impression oh she stinks you know
um
yeah
shockingly cute
so then
uh
she wanted to
um yeah i was saying yeah let's go to
the hotel but i don't think that uh
since you guys don't have uber and i
also think
a normal taxi is not an option because
it seems like it's pretty far
so we should probably go with the train
i said
and
[Music]
it it was interesting because navi mama
wanted to take the lead
and
seem like she wanted to help me
with everything and wanted to be helpful
and and mature
but then
on the first day especially
in many
occasions
she was like
very confused and very lost
like she didn't um know her way around
the airport like i found
where
the
it's my first time in that airport and i
found the the train
uh ticket machine
and the train station itself
uh way before she did
yeah and then uh i asked her
about this uh card uh for the train
because you can get a card here that you
can charge and then you just
put it on the on the date when you enter
um
so i was like
[Music]
mama i need to get this card can you
help me get the card where can i buy it
uh
so we bought it at the
at the convenience store and she wanted
to
she wanted to be cool
and charge it with money for me for some
reason even though
i'm not broke or anything like i don't
need you to charge it for me when she
wanted to for some reason
so she takes out her
credit card you know like a
really cool adult
and she gives it to the convenience
store dude but
he tells her
sorry nah you can't charge it here you
have to charge it at the
at the charging station you know
but then there it says no card cash only
so she says ah sorry sorry kiara
i wanted to i wanted to turn your card
but i don't have any cash i'm sorry
i'm like oh no problem you're not on my
sugar mama i'm
gonna charge my own card don't worry now
my problem is
i
i lacked
an understanding of how much
money i will be using
in korea in general and how much money i
should have on my
card
transport card now i put way too much
money on it and actually
as of today
i have no more cash and the atms here
don't take my card and the restaurants
don't take my card
i'm pretty [\h__\h] right now
all my money is on the transport card
all my all my money is not that much
maybe like
i don't know
a lot though
not not that much maybe like 60 bucks or
80 bucks i don't know
still left on there
and i have i had
i i didn't bring enough cash to begin
with i guess but i had like um
at the beginning
around 500 bucks maybe and i changed it
into one
and uh
now it's a mastercard
not really it's a debit card but it's a
mastercard
and and then yeah bye i only have like
30 bucks left in cash
[Music]
the thing is
uh at the airport they charged my card
for the pocket wi-fi and that seemed to
have worked fine and they charged my
card for the pcr test
at the airport at the airport everything
worked
but then once i left the airport i was
never able to use my card again so i'm
thinking of
maybe my card got blocked and i need to
call the bank or it's actually the the
banks here that don't take my card
could be
both
normally it shouldn't be blocked because
my card is set to
be used um overseas like it's unlocked
it is unlocked i unlocked it
but maybe i don't know
maybe it's really just the airport where
everything works which is
because i'm out of money
so you know in in japan um i also had
problems using my card because my card
is [\h__\h] you know the company that it's
from the bank that it's from is [\h__\h]
like it's a shitty tiny um bank so
one of the few banks i could use in
japan
really like pretty much the only one was
7 11
atm
they have a 7 11 bank there and that's
the only atm i could ever use when i was
living in japan
so i thought here maybe two because they
have 7-eleven too but the atm in the
7-11 here in korea
doesn't seem to be 7-11 bank
it's a different one so my card got
rejected i went to two different
atms and i uh tried at several shops and
restaurants and they never
they never work
shinhan bank
i will have to figure it out tomorrow
i hope i can figure it out i need some
money
it's not like i don't have money i have
money on my account i just don't i can't
get it out
xinhan bank why do you think that that
one works
why why do you think that's the one
that's gonna
work is it famous for
working with foreign cards
shin hongbing
one more thing i have about a 120 us
dollar still from my america trip in
cash in my
in my uh
wallet so worst case tomorrow i'm gonna
change that to one so at least for a
while i have a hundred more bucks
that's all i have
i thought i was just gonna keep it until
the next time i come to america that's
why i didn't change it back to euro when
i came back i was like that's a waste
let's just keep it
let's just keep it until i go back um
yeah well anyway
so that's a problem but okay you know i
want to talk ages with you guys but the
problem is i actually have to wake up
early
i didn't get to talk at all but i do
want to do um
a stream i just wanted to say hi today
because i promised but i'm going to
stream longer tomorrow i'm gonna make
sure to have more time tomorrow
tomorrow
but maybe i can tell you one more story
[Music]
let me check my notes
um
oh let me tell you about the like okay
let me tell you until until the point
where we arrived in the hotel
oh so we got uh the card and we charged
it and i charged it with too much money
and then
we
went to the tracks
and got into the train and
until that point everything cool
but then
uh at the station where we got off
also when we changed in between
for some reason so many
of the places where we had to go through
even though they're like big stations
and all that there were no escalators or
elevators
in many situations
which was an insane problem because my
suitcase at that point um was i think
about 30 kilograms of weight
it was so [\h__\h] heavy and navi mama
was so
uh
so
ah
handsome trying to like she was she was
offering to carry my my suitcase uh up
and down the stairs for me and i was
like no nami mama this suitcase is
[\h__\h]
incredibly
[Music]
uh heavy you look more like a noodle
than i look like a noodle so i i don't
think you should be carrying this
suitcase you're gonna break your [\h__\h]
arms
so we were struggling you know and
several times we were um rescued
by
korean people
helping us
to carry the [\h__\h] heavy suitcase so
i'm like
i was really really touched
i was touched by the kindness
one time
it was like we were looking for an
escalator running around left and right
like where the [\h__\h] why is there no
escalator elevator nothing and an old
korean lady she's like
oh you need help in
korean
and
she was like trying to help us find
an escalator elevator we couldn't and
then we ran in a circle then we came
back and
uh
she
we had to go down so she showed us a
technique
of how to
push the
um
the suitcase down the stairs
and i'm like okay okay okay okay i get
it you don't have to do it anymore stop
stop stop because it still looked
[\h__\h] exhausting it's still exhausting
but
yeah i wanted her to stop because she
was an older lady and i was like okay
okay
no no need no need i will continue but
she didn't let go of my suitcase
until the very end
so sweet and then she was asking navi
mama about me like oh
what's with her like where's she's where
is she from and stuff like that
why are you telling me it's a holiday
because of the banks
what about what about sunday though
tomorrow's sunday are they open on
sundays
oh wait no
wait no no no yeah now it's sunday
oh [\h__\h]
not open on sunday and not open on
monday
uh docile
eh
then i need an atm that works
[Laughter]
[Music]
maybe i can find an atm that works in
that shinhan bank that you guys said
no money
no money maybe at the airport yeah i was
thinking so too maybe my last resort is
going to the airport
[Music]
but
the thing is i didn't try the atm at the
airport so i can't say for sure that it
will work i only like had my card being
charged uh yeah charged there by
by the
pocket wi-fi place and all that
ah
yeah
maybe i'll
have the board i feel weird about
borrowing money like it
i feel weird
i mean obviously i'm gonna give it back
but like
that's embarrassing
we'll see
whatever i have to do to survive
got no choice
yeah so so and then you know another
time when we were we were
we were gonna go out and exit from the
station
and there were like a million stairs but
there were also
like there was an escalator
but it wasn't moving
so we stand in front of the escalator
we're like why the [\h__\h] isn't this
starting to move i'm stepping on it why
is it not moving
and then
a a guy
korean guy comes up behind us and he's
like
uh
he wants to go up the same escalator and
realizes we're standing in front of me
so what does he do he immediately takes
my suitcase
says
uh like something in english
and
then i'm like sorry it's really really
heavy though it's really heavy i'm
trying to you know warn him
but he just he says oh no problem
kenjana and then he starts carrying up
but the moment the moment he carries it
up he seems to i feel regret in his face
especially after he noticed that it's
quite a lot of stairs
more than he expected he was like oh wow
holy [\h__\h]
and i'm like yeah i'm so sorry i'm so
sorry but you are currently our hero
thank you so much i i applaud it
we applauded him at the end he was like
ah
thank you so much my hero
yeah instant regret but
i think that was like three times in
that one trip that
people helped us with my suitcase thank
you so much everybody old ladies
handsome oppas
thank you
come san nida
all good
and we finally made it
and i was a bit shocked
um
[Music]
by my
hotel
but i'm gonna share you the details of
why i'm shocked by my hotel
after i'm leaving it because i don't
want to give anything away
um
also like every time i look at navi
[Music]
i'm like [\h__\h] she's so cute that's she's
so cute how does she do it
she's so sweet
[Music]
she's her face expressions
are like the same
as on stream it feels like
she smiles and laughs a lot and she's
she looks so cute
she's so cute
and she's fashionable and she's so sweet
you're so cute you're so cute
so cute we keep on saying cute cute cute
to each other which is a very wholesome
interaction it's like a cute circle
uh a praising circle
um
it's so wholesome
yeah like we meet today and yesterday in
the morning and we're like i'm like oh
my god nami mama i love your outfit
today so cute and then she she says oh
my god but i love your app it's so cute
oh my god your wrinkle is so cute and so
normal and then i take off my raincoat
and she's like oh my god what are you
wearing underneath it's also so cute i'm
like i'm not as cute as yours
[Music]
yeah very tasty
very very titty what titty um
yeah
cute loop
hope you enjoyed it thank you so far i'm
enjoying it and i have so much to tell
but i'm
running out of time already oh my god
you know see i already did an hour i
didn't even
want to stream i wanted to stream an
hour but i realized i shouldn't because
it's gonna be very late
yeah um
so i'm gonna stream tomorrow or today at
this point because it's past midnight
again
yeah
uh
i i have so much to talk about
also i need to write down things because
like i i forgot to write that i only
have things written down from the first
day
but i think i still remember the problem
is just i don't remember um the names of
the places that we went to
the only place i remember is hongdae
because today today we went to hongdae
which is really a popular
place for young people and hip people
and performers and all that
um it's very busy it's like comparable
like it gave me
vibes depending on the area um some some
of hongdae looked like reminded me of
harajuku and some of whom they reminded
me of shibuya and some of whom they
reminded me of shinjuku and like it's a
mix of all of those places like um
atmosphere-wise which is really
interesting there was one street i kept
asking nabi what's the name of the
street so that i can tell you guys
um but apparently there was no name
but there was this one street which
really felt like a wide version with
more space of takeshita dori
which is really good because takeshita
dori is so [\h__\h] crowded all the time
and
you can't [\h__\h] move and this place is
so wide which was really good to walk
through
[Music]
it i think it's it's on google maps it's
just hongdae shopping street
i think that's the place i walked
through was it this one
maybe i could be wrong
i'm confused
i don't know where i went
no i went home there and uh
home
[Music]
and one more place
one more place
was
[\h__\h]
where was it
ah no
no not only shopping street i don't know
was it i don't know
don't don't believe anything i say
but what was the other
i feel like
we either went to myeongdong or we
wanted to
i feel like i
feel like we went to myeongdong
i think
i think yes and shinchon sounds familiar
too
[Music]
is there isn't there like a way um of
having
google maps tell you where you went
today
yeah i told her to tell me did she tell
me
where we went so far
no she didn't write it to me yet
map timeline
timeline
where is that
map
where where is that i'm on the phone
is that do you have to push your ah your
timeline there it is
uh
no visits for today i guess it's
yesterday then
and then
yeah
[Music]
that was
today and yesterday
yesterday was
[Music]
oh
hello
we back okay so so yes yesterday was uh
no today was your num and
and
the
the other one
i
are you back are we good okay and
yesterday was gyeongbokgung palace
and
oh
[Music]
and before hong kong park
we went to that big uh
the
hyundai
uh shopping mall
very busy
and we went to the hang on park but i
have a whole story about that so
i saw i saw the aftermath of the
flooding
and
yeah there's a whole story about that so
i'll tell you about that
uh
tomorrow hopefully
my throat also really hurts because we
went to karaoke
before we went uh to dinner and i was
very dehydrated so my throat is really
[\h__\h] right now
yeah we went to korean karaoke which is
very different from
then i thought maybe this background
because there's nothing else that fits
uh but yeah we went to karaoke it's very
different from japanese
okay
like photo booth pictures
in korea and i expected it to be a bit
more like the japanese particular but no
it's so different
and the karaoke is so different too i'm
like
what
[Music]
yeah i should stop anyway i should
that's literally what i'm what i'm
saying guys anyway i should stop i need
i really need to go i'm so sorry i'm
i'm gonna be sleep deprived tomorrow
night
i'll see you guys tomorrow okay
or today
let's hope i survived the day without
money
okay okay
i have more stories
next time next time a good night
and
i hope hope you enjoyed the little chit
chat
[Music]
um
sorry for the lag
sorry
leg leg leg leg length lang lang
blankley angling clank leg length wink
of lingling
leg leg
leg
leg okay bye bye
good night
[Music]
you