[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
questions
[Music]
oh no
um
[Music]
hello
hello everybody
this movie was just
sitting right next to my keyboard
partially on my mouse
[Laughter]
staring at the screen as close as you
can possibly get
if my mom was here she would have told
my cat that if she gets any closer and
well actually no of course she probably
would say
she will get square eyes
because she's so close to the TV
that's what my mom used to tell me
if I get too close or if I watch too
much TV I will get square or like not
not square eyes but Square irises I
guess
Square
Square you know you know what I mean
that's a new one really
did no one ever hear that before from
their mothers
pupils yeah the thing around like
everything not only the pupils
did you guys never hear that from your
mom
nah no never
square eyes is a common saying here
where I think it's an Austrian thing no
oh yes I did no yes okay a couple ones a
couple ones hahaha
um
hello everybody
look at this cute guy
look at it
it's cute it's called carto and it came
out in 2020 apparently and oh I didn't
put up the logo let me put up where did
I save the logo here but it's black for
some reason
and doesn't
the contrast is too strong let me try
something can I go
your color correction Maybe
uh
now we got my white there's also no idea
maybe upgrade you know what gray
actually looks good
I think
that is perfect placement gotta have a
clean screen right everything needs to
be in order perfectly I'm but that game
music it will start once I tab into the
game I'm tapped out so it's no game
music
um
I want to start by
telling you guys that uh Holo myth new
song is out on Kelly's Channel
non-fiction
have you guys heard it
it's quite the pretty song
[Music]
I'm going to say behave we say instead
baby
[Music]
yeah it's a cool song very very epic
epic good word to describe it I think
uh yeah it's on Cali's uh Channel
because
um well she pretty much organized all of
it and uh yeah
so it ended up on her Channel please
give it a look maybe I'll sing it you
know without you you know what when when
the mix when the first mix rough came
back and we all gave our feedback I was
like
I don't know what you think Inna but I
don't know if it's your voice or or or
if it's too much autotune or so but you
sound a little bit robotic and then she
said uh no I think that's just my voice
in that tone maybe when when singing
like that yeah she just has um like this
this perfect sound to it so I said well
then then your voice is just too perfect
it's too beautiful
I was just making suggestions you know
what what sounded like what to me so I'm
uh um you know I don't know what you
think you know just
you know you sound like you're being
auto-tuned there's certain people though
do you guys remember there was this uh
TV show
uh uh I don't know uh from what country
it was anymore
but
um
there was like this this this woman who
became really famous
for sounding like it was a lot
supposedly live singing but people
didn't believe it was life-singing it
was like a like a you know with some
judges and she was like auditioning on
stage and she was singing a song uh and
it just sounded way too perfect and the
judges were like I what is this this
must be fake I don't believe you this is
[\h__\h] you must be auto-tuned and then
they made her sing acapella and she
still sounded so perfectly beautifully
altitude and then they were like holy
[\h__\h] no it was not American Idol no no
no no no no no no no no no no no I'm not
talking about Susan Boyle or whoever no
no no no no it's not English it was not
English speaking yeah
um yes
um
yes I don't know her name anymore
maybe if I look it up oh
judges voice
Auto-Tune
I step on
X X Factor
Global ah a woman called Ida
there's the title is is this contestant
really lip syncing really is this
contested really lip syncing real what
kind of like way of phrasing that is it
is is that
uh it was Willow printed it has 48
million views yo
[Music]
a-i-d-a
yeah anyway
so new song is out uh listen to it maybe
I'll try to sing it alone at some point
I remember the first time when I tried
singing journey of a thousand years
Alone
um I failed I fought I thought I could
sing it alone without practicing but I
failed spectacularly
laughs
does Kelly have full control of the
lyrics yeah Kelly wrote the lyrics I
think they're really nice
really pretty I like my my my line and
the bridge
uh uh what was it again and then some
burning numbers and yielding your loves
giving me wings I think it was one key
higher but I'll dance in burning
Emperors on yielding I don't know what
that means but something about dancing
in fire
and your love's giving me wings it's so
romantic
[Music]
yeah yeah so she wrote the lyrics She uh
she did everything she assigned the
lyrics She uh chose an artist she chose
a music video maker it's like also like
it kind of had to be mostly organized by
one person because it was very last
minute decision to make a song uh to
begin with so there was not much time if
we all were like trying to put it all
together together then it would have
probably taken a lot longer and it would
have been a lot more delayed
yeah I said every that's what I'm saying
yo that's why I said this is one of the
reasons this is just one of the
instances why I said we should in the VR
collab we should
um for the sake of the people we work
with
not to everything so last minute the
side things earlier in the coming year
so that you know the people who work
with us don't suffer so much
yeah
because there's more than one instance
there's a million instances where we
just suddenly are like okay let's do
this let's do that let's do a VR collab
with a completely new world we have one
week but we need to have a completely
new world modeled with games uh created
so we needed to be coded as well and
this and that and this and that
yeah like I don't want to know like they
they accept our commissions so
you know okay they think they can do it
but I feel like
you know it would be nicer to not stress
everyone out so much
let's see if you guys can keep it up
next year
so I like so it's also for the
management you know and for us in the
end it's also better for us if we get
more time to work on things and
um
think about things give feedback for
things and all that
um
yeah yeah kanoda has aged 10 years in
the past years that's what I'm thinking
[Music]
more time to make it perfect Yeah well
yeah for anything really any any project
that we undertake or any anything
merchandise
whatever I don't know
um
so uh anyway let's play cattle why are
we talking so much about unrelated
things
before even getting started
[Music]
it's like really
calm
music sounds
it's so cute let's go I saw this
uh in the steam line up thingy I think
and I was like yeah that's so cute let's
play it
let's go
wait coming up for a second Chihuahua is
a little bit too much on
the side okay
[Music]
oh they live in an airship
no grandma your grandma's like snow look
at this
ah so you can take these pieces apart
and then the world will all changes just
like you all want it
oh
okay let me try it I'm gonna put these
together what happens oh
[Music]
my baby what did you do no
no no
don't leave
me alone grandma
voice acting by your strolling
so she put some unfortunate pieces
together which ended up in
yeah destroying the Airship that they
were in
oh
can I I have to use
the arrows oh no can I change it to wasd
please
I can't no I can't
uh
up
down
left I like the sounds
right okay and
um
what what is that it doesn't even have a
key
press key for rotate r
I'll press key for rotate the other way
e
um interact is okay cancels okay map is
okay items has nothing
items is I
okay remember that guys
[Laughter]
remember please wait
why is there new pieces on the eye too I
didn't set that
maybe maybe that's just the same for
whatever reason okay
okay
[Music]
look
cute there's birds flying
so as you can see we're like on a piece
of map here
and it cuts off on the edges
it's so simplistic I'm really liking it
already
[Music]
is that perhaps a piece of map oh
interact
[Music]
yeah the art is so cute
so then I open the map and oh currently
we have like what three pieces welcome
explore and this world is yours to
change you can move any piece of the map
aha
okay and rotate pieces as needed you can
connect pieces with the same type of
Border
I see okay it has to line up shaded
pieces of the map are lands you haven't
explored yet go check them out okay cool
so
so for example
we move this one down here no I can't ah
but I can rotate
like this and then it's connected and
then we can go up yay okay
all right
explore out of the map okay
so now we've attached
a new piece and we go higher what is
these
interact
what was that
hmm
oh also a new piece of map okay
connect New pieces to an existing map to
reveal more of the world pieces of the
map have been scattered everywhere the
more you find the bigger your world will
grow and then maybe we can find our
grandma again we need a happy end
so
ah I
ah oh that one's big
and wait I first kind of like
take this up
uh just place it wherever
ah see that should work
okay
and then uh oh no wait I need to get
used to the controls I'm not using the
mouse at all and then I just place this
here okay
that should work
oh sick
I can move the piece I'm currently on
two ah I was wondering about this oh
look there's a person and another piece
map I'll take that
and I will talk to him
hello
there hi
we don't get new visitors very often or
your family with you too
um don't don't don't talk about that or
see well no matter oh Lord welcome here
and your timing is fortunate for
we celebrate the coming of age of my
dearest niece
Shannon
yes it's very exciting I was so
distracted this morning that I forgot my
bait but no matter it won't be long now
until the ceremony feel free to explore
the island in the meantime and I'll see
you there
okay I don't have much of the island yet
you're welcome to share more with me ah
so this would be me going over to the
other side let me see new piece oh
it's a piece of a house
is that where shiannon is let me go over
there
Iris did it sound like an Irish accent
to you
oh that's a whole family here and the
music is getting happier have you
noticed it's like oh more stuff going on
hi sweetie
where did you come from it's exciting to
meet someone new I barely left the house
and mouse this little bundle of love
keeps me pretty busy did you meet my
husband already especially nearby though
he's probably not counting much that big
luck left without any bait this morning
I guess we'll just have to rely on the
wings of the ocean as we always have
well good thing this little ladybug
likes fish not like that filthy little
fast pot over there
hey
have you visited the other families yet
Callan and her family were the first
ones to come to this island they live
right on the sea
is my sister-in-law she lives in the
forest with her family her daughter
Sienna is coming of Ages today I can't
believe it's her here already
wait well where is this daughter where
is his daughter
ah
who are you
are you 15.
mama said I have to be 15 before I can
have my coming of age if you're not 15
then how did you cross the street oh I
did not cross the street I fell from the
sky I know it sounds like [\h__\h] but
it's true
when someone turns 15 about arrives at
the North Pier a gift from the sea
there's a 10 year old has to get in the
boat and leave the island forever
I want to leave forever it's like above
oh a month feels like forever to you
a month now feels like no time at all to
me and time is so slow it's so fast
there's no at the same time actually
forever I wonder can I get into the
house a dollar
oh a salty snack of minnows drying in
the sun oh what's my nose can I get into
the house no one's inside okay well I
could be inside wait why is this one
blue why is this one plant blue
fish huh okay wait I got a new piece of
map let's check it out
oh it has some some Forest
I think we could just put it there for
now at least
[Music]
so I think later this will be coming a
little bit puzzle puzzly a bit more
maybe you know already
we have to think about what would be
which pieces to connect the more you get
also that was another piece
an unremarkable pile of dirt huh
I hear the boots
yeah the music is really relaxing you
know and I like the concept too
why are you singing Give me give me give
me a man at the midnight Jack before the
darkness
[Music]
ah see I could connect those oh perfect
perfect
[Music]
now we go for the forest ooh scary scary
no not scary
you peace
um I think I read this game is five to
six hours long
um I I started a little bit late today
so I think
I will
um have a second part
why is he there now
isn't that the other father
I'll have a second part next week
oh is that like for me to lay on top of
no
hello
[Music]
no that's a different guy oh no you
don't look familiar I must really be
lost I know it's a small island but I
always get distracted on the way home
the ocean is just so beautiful and full
of mermaids mermaids
this is a bit embarrassing but could I
trouble you to help me home I just
literally just arrived here how would
you expect me to help you home I know
nothing here but I can move the world
and perhaps help you leave away
you seem to know your way around my
house is east of the one on the
grasslands along the sea what
grassland
along the sea do I even have that piece
of bump not if I could only figure out
which way is he is exactly because I can
turn the pieces of maps uh
[Music]
interesting I only saw one house so far
which is that one
[Music]
what
yeah yeah I understand I might have to
put it a certain way but it currently
the only other house I have is connected
already to the map that he's standing on
[Music]
foreign
so that
it connects
Eastway because he said it's in the East
so I need to connect it so that he can
if he goes east he will find it
considering
assuming it's this house but which else
would it be
Africa oh no wait he lives he he lives
east of the house so wait it's the other
way around
sorry big thinking time here
would this be correct then yes
[Music]
oh no wait that just created the house
there
oh a new house
[Music]
so it wasn't his house but by me putting
it together the right way I solved it
and it created the house in the right
[Music]
spots
on this and we get a new piece of math
yeah I like it
a nice mechanic and then we got a new
piece of map uh I suppose on every map
we get a new piece of map
um
would this like be acceptable because
no okay
but oh this would be acceptable
so let's talk to this lady though
thank you for helping my husband home I
love him but he'd forget his nose if it
wasn't attached to his face I don't
think I've seen you here before are you
from another tribe what are your
Traditions are people of pioneers love
to see you once we set sail we're still
on the first island that we find we feel
so lucky that it was this one we just
love it here don't you feel like a
little bit confused because all the time
things are changing around here you
think you got figured out but then
suddenly the supermarket is not just uh
up left up right anymore but now
suddenly it's like all the way across
the ocean huh
isn't that confusing to you
maybe they don't even notice it have you
met xionon yet she's very special to us
it will be hard to say goodbye but we're
excited for her when they sent their
children of 15 years across the sea
that reminds me of the Rings of power
ritual of sending their elves away
into death
to death
I'm sure she'd like to meet you if she
if you get the chance all right maybe
maybe I can join her and then I will
find my grandma
what's up ew that's not my thing
[Music]
no one's inside oh wow no one's ever
inside their houses
never even smaller jar ah
does that mean a jar
a jar
wait Boys Gone
[Music]
oh the boy ran off
a jar slightly open oh what a pun
e
oh okay she's not worried about her son
being gone
[Music]
ah
huh
she lives in the floor is way bigger
than this one oh she lives on her own
interesting very very independent
folk they have here wait do I have
another piece no
she lives in the forest way bigger than
this one maybe maybe he wants me to
connect
these pieces so that it forms one
opposite so that it forms one big
relatively Big Forest
no
oh the birds left maps for me what what
interesting
I think my idea was smart
now you give me the Big Forest okay
um let me move this away
[Music]
um
let me move that here and then move it
move this here and then this
ah
[Music]
it doesn't really matter but I want it
to look nice
oh wait that's difficult whatever I just
leave it like this for now I wonder if
the boy made it back home safely
[Music]
so now we should find Shiana somewhere
in this Forest
hopefully
[Music]
well the water sounds are nice
maybe it does matter no we'll see we'll
see surely it matters somehow up
[\h__\h] he didn't make it back home
you good
tell me if you need a ride home
you should have escaped the piece of map
before I moved it
wait so okay maybe it does matter
so don't wait a minute
[Music]
maybe yeah
[Applause]
yeah spaces need to be connected to form
the biggest forest possible so my
original idea was already correct
did she go
oh
oh I was behind
a wood Chopper's ax
how the how did she ignore me I was
literally right there oh
can I help you couldn't use his private
property do you know oh dear don't shoot
me
sorry it's been a tough few days with
Fiona
he's going through puberty pretty bad
you're really well welcome here
[Music]
not the scene once our people set sail
they must never return to the origin
it's tradition
[Music]
okay so you guys also didn't grow up
here you found this island
after leaving your place for 15 years
well that's like so heartbreaking like
you never see your family again what the
[\h__\h]
oh dear that girl really aborts my blood
sometimes but she's always done things
her own way
I'm left together Shannon probably went
to the link to be alone can you please
check on her young white young one you
know he's a good listener
yeah as soon as I like I'm a I'm one of
those protagonists who cannot talk
no one's dead
[Music]
what am I standing on
yummy ah ew seafood stew never mind
so far everything looked yummy but uh
not really my thing
quiz with clay pots
you said that there's animals weld on
our ancestors Islands oh a bear
I've heard it's called a black bear or
bear blast I didn't know black bear was
shortened to Blair
so smart
we should do the same
it's hard to believe that our animals
they're big I would love to see one
okay so how did you get that one wait
wait a second law you see that
official necklace inside one of the
glowing shells I find a map of Peace a
piece of math sorry
doesn't even feel like the first time I
said that
peace
is it perhaps uh-huh
oh that that fits um perfectly
it's like a heart oh
this is so nice
here she is by the lake
I'm just not ready to leave I know it's
tradition but my family is all I have
and I come back and visit them after
I've set sail our people have had that
tradition for so long but they've
forgotten I didn't do it in the first
place not all Traditions are good you
know sometimes we do them just because
it's what we've always done I'm sorry
I'm upset thank you for listening who
might you'll be
um
no need to be nervous I'm shiannon
Welcome to our Island
I'm about to leave it forever though my
Coming of Age ceremonies today
that's so scary
I guess part of me is excited but I'm
scared that I'll be lonely out there I
might take it might take me a while to
make new friends besides fish endless
fish that I get too close to and then
they heat me up an adventure and
Adventures are always more fun with
someone else sorry it already feels
pretty obvious so that'll be the one by
her side to leave this island after I've
like put everything together
um I know I just met you but would you
maybe want to oh that's fast come with
me that's really fast
you look like you're being a good friend
oh maybe that's not the end Maybe
maybe we just swim
to another Island and then connect that
Island to this island I don't know who
knows
oh I just not
I'm okay with it oh really this is going
to be so much fun I can't wait to tell
my parents what about your family do you
need to tell them to
um
well then we'll just have to go find
them
well there's one last thing I need to do
before we set sail finding a sale
perhaps maybe you can help me
my answers are smileys
cute
Jen said convert
I can't this is what happens yeah to the
children nowaday if you give them phones
and tablets too early they will only
speak to you in emojis
thank you
[Music]
oh I I know this looked unfamiliar to me
I was like what is this right super
chat's currency with the B like like a
Bitcoin or what
it's uh oh Thailand just got super chat
uh options
oh a cipher also sent one with that oh
niceu
the new currency
currency currency currency currency
nice nice
that's nice first time I saw that
oh I'm always
I can't [\h__\h] read I always want to
have my home close by so I need a good
handful of soil to bring with us
I just need a bit more time to say
goodbye to the island that's
understandable I I also when I went to
Japan for a year I cut off
um little pieces of strands of fur for
my cats to bring with me some people say
that's weird even though it's not
nothing weird about that
you can find the best soil where the
forest the coastline and the grassland
meat the forest the coastline and the
grassland
meet
okay I'll put it in the bag okay
the forest
hey was this piece new I didn't even
look at it yet let me look at that first
[Music]
let's go up here is there like a piece
of map here
foreign
[Music]
so she said
I went
easy
wouldn't it be this this piece of map
where the forest
the grassland and the coastline
Maybe
[Music]
what
where the forest
the coastline and
what did she say
yeah but I think
um something will happen if I put
correctly and then we get actually the
dirt that we want
no
Forest Coastline and grassland
[Music]
wait okay let's assume I already saw it
whatever I'm looking for did I already
move it in a way so that I can't find it
anymore I wonder
oh wait that doesn't work
ah yeah well because right
let me make it a bit more compact
foreign
[Music]
whatever
this this part I feel like it's gonna be
pretty useless
[Music]
hold on maybe not
dirt dirt dirt
let's see if we can find some dirt
of course that was an important part
that little patch of dirt that we saw
I just don't remember where it was
um
yeah
it is a creative game isn't it hmm I
moved it away really
[Music]
you guys remembered it
which one uh ah that one maybe
[Music]
like I scooped the poop of my kitty cats
I have yet to use that robot toilet I
haven't had time yet
oh I wonder if that one's enough or if I
need more
I could probably like get to her faster
if I move things around but whatever
poopity poop
[Music]
lady this song looks great thanks
um there's a strange scrap of paper bird
in it oh that's mine please thank you
yeah thank you
I think that was the last thing I needed
I'm ready to set sail the high seas will
be no match for us
oh I can say at least my own name wow
impressive
oh
[Music]
if you want to go get ready I'll meet
you at the North Pier for my ceremony
North Pierre
the one I just got surprise surprise
okay
uh I'll put it here
right where her house is and it's facing
the north so that's correct
[Music]
North North North can I change them see
if this game
all right so everybody's up here now to
Say Goodbye Oh
wow and the music changes
[Music]
Mommy
honey look that boat is Shannon's gift
from the sea it always feels like magic
when they appear
I'm really going to miss triadon who
will help me reel the Nets in I'm so
proud of her though and good on you for
going with her
you could definitely use some claws
though
we made it just in time for the dog show
talk show what dog shop
oh may I ask you a favor
take this Memento with you and if you
meet my son I feel like this is the
tutorial map and then with her we go to
the actual place
Maybe
if you meet my son somewhere out there
give it to him the odds are low but I'll
take any chance I get to send him our
love
amazing bless your voice with happiness
so lucky to have a friend like you
I suppose it's not in my ear and you'll
be joining xi'anon that's very kind of
you
okay I spoke with everyone and I was
worth it because I got an item
hi Kato I can't believe the boat really
came
so I'm ready to go what about you
I hope you have some survival skills
because I don't really have anything
besides God's power to move things
around according to my wish
but I mean that's that's pretty pretty
op I guess
let's get this ceremony started
oh
and get kicked out just I'm joining her
on purpose because she feels like a soul
mate to me
my dearest
good for you
a necklace made from swordfish bones
oh can I have one too no
may bring you peace and perseverance
perseverance probably in the company you
day and night my beautiful daughter
wow
oh no
what about daddy
close your eyes and feel a gentle
Embrace of the Wind
AKA My Embrace oh
oh no there's no Embrace may I find may
you find your destiny as we found ours
we love you shionon
that's why we don't want to see you ever
again [\h__\h] off
we're sick sick and tired of cooking for
you every morning God damn it go make
your own food
not even paying for the services
you're 15 now
too long it has been
thank you everyone for your blessings
even though some of them were
questionable especially from my parents
I've come of age and the world Waits
we'll be right back I should really
intends to come back
say hi
there cool is talking poodle
he's he means the boy the little boy
they're real everyone we'll see you
later
come on Cat Let's Ride these waves let's
go
oh wait
wait
my I hear my phone alarm going off
somewhere let me turn it off
foreign
I have I have alarms in the most random
times wait was this continuing
look is this continuing without me or oh
sure nothing happened right oh sure okay
yeah
oh
we made it
I still can't believe you'd never been
sailing before your salty old Sea Dog
Out There cattle I'll never know how you
got us through that vlog
[Laughter]
I won't share my Secrets because then
you think I'm crazy
I know a tradition says that I am
supposed to settle on the first island I
find and I think I'll do just a bit more
exploring there's a whole world out
there
this grassland does look nice though how
about you have a look around and I'll
check out some nearby Islands we can
meet back here tomorrow okay I'm totally
going to find the sunken city I swear I
saw it Oh Atlantic City what Atlanta
what
wait what's it called
pee
Atlanta
[Laughter]
oh I got confused
it sounds way too similar come on
[Laughter]
okay bye bye
ah a piece of snap
[Laughter]
capital of Georgia
all right what else do we have oh yeah
[Music]
yeah
oh my God you sound so cute
[Music]
anyway is there v-sync um in this game
because
no okay I don't think uh you guys see it
but there's like some weird lagging on
my side but I think it's only on my side
and not I'm not on the obs
oh
or another one and
below
screen tearing no no it just looks like
it's like rumbling
you and that sheep should come together
and make more ships just an idea
the more the merrier you know okay let's
see what we can do
oh
let's connect this
and
these oh ah
for example like this
all right
a spicy the Lord area
me thank you oh
my snack commissioned officer oh
what
tomorrow I have night time tactical
marching if you don't mind can you cheer
for me fighting
what
you you're in high school but also a
soldier well you mean you just graduated
high school and now you're a soldier
or do you have to do that at the same
time
fighting fighting when you're done watch
Chihuahua every day but I'm happy you're
already trying to watch my streams even
though you have to balance it with that
good luck
[Music]
it can start very early
what
what man I'm I'm happy I'm a girl when
it comes to things like this
[Music]
hello
have you seen my shape
my sheep must have wandered away they
can't get it off of those snow or
flowers that says they taste like
marshmallows so she must have overheard
will you help me wrap them up yep
leave it to me I don't know how wait how
do I oh do I just how do I round them up
I guess I have to move some map pieces
but this one is right at your place
still
[Music]
maybe this one has to be there too and
then maybe this one
like this
I mean how do I oh I just have to talk
to them
what
it's farting at me
what do you mean what do you want
how do I help you round them up dude
babies
yeah
they must really mean s his flowers they
won't follow you unless you have
something even more delicious okay it
was worth talking one more time to him
[Music]
I'm farmer gouda
rhythm game
player
disgusting I have never smelt
sheep's fart before what I can imagine
it's not very nice
all right where is this aunt tuya
[Music]
wait do we have corn
I was like no lots of sheep are getting
typical how can you be shattered when
counting sheep puts you right to sleep
and now I suppose she's asked you to
round them up
my birthday for you if you had some
honey fruit just don't confuse the honey
frilled with the Red Devils that grow
around here we even have a song about it
boobs of orange sweetest sugar only has
one stem don't confuse it with the devil
steer well clear of them
wait so what is I guess it's not funny
we could have to scale to me I feel like
but okay
how I'm going to take I didn't see
anything lying around
[Music]
but can you give it to me
oh she's just singing now
[Music]
um
did I get wet that looks so yeah okay
is that the one
[Music]
I hope it doesn't kill you
there's one sheep
[Music]
yo
really you found him just three more to
go okay don't let him go again please
but do I have to get more of that fruit
I think
yay wait it's already running away you
[\h__\h] idiot
[Music]
the other one is right there literally
right there
yeah well the icon for the berry had
three different berries on it so I think
it's realistic that I can use it three
times
oh maybe I never actually gave it to
them I just you know let them sniff it
is
I don't remember another sheep
into our secret spot in the middle of
the snowy flowers
[Music]
I don't remember another sheep
and I feel like I've seen all those
snowy flower Fields about what
do I need to make it so that it looks
more Secret
[Music]
in the middle
I don't know
I wait I need to make it so that it
forms like a circle Maybe
no wait
oh what
I'm a [\h__\h] genius
oh
whoa
whoa I kind of did that annoyingly I
thought like what I was thinking what
should I fill that with anyway but
whoa ten seconds
wow
[Music]
here take this now I don't remember
which direction we're supposed to go uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
my seat
oh what are you pooping on a piece of
paper
oh no you you you
um threw it up you didn't poop it out
okay I prefer that to be honest thank
you
both was terrible though
laughs
I know it's somewhere we would have to
get a new piece of paper
up up we go
I love that the chirping noise
maybe I can do an M uh cricket
can I do that does it sound like a
cricket
that's so oh it's so nice listen to this
did you hear it
[Music]
that's so nice and Zoo finally returns
oh yeah that reminds me I wanted to
um
announce something
next week
Sunday
10 P.M jst
Revival
let's go
[Applause]
[\h__\h] finally it's about [\h__\h] time
I finally was able to
schedule
uh a guest
s yeah finally finally finally with both
of our times aligned I was I was
actually actually like trying to you
know figure it out between two people
um
I I wasn't just aiming for one I was
hoping that one of them would be
available and I will announce it with my
schedule on Sunday or Monday or so
yeah then you will know which guest it
is now I will still keep it to myself
[Music]
give us a hint
you don't need a hint
you know it's between three people
that's already cornering it into three
people
and keep your secrets yes I will
um
so
exciting I already will start to try to
figure out a time for the next guest
I just kind of
I didn't want to skip over them
and move on to you know
um 4th gen because I there's still
members missing from Gamers and
I'm a senpai was the first gen I think
so I feel like it would be too much to
skip them to move on to the fourth
um so I want to get those freedom and
then we can move on
yeah oh second second oh yes yes
anyway
we got oh what is this
I'll let you know and I would find this
oh my dear sweet car auto that was quite
some excitement I'm sure you're scared
but my granddaughter is strong and don't
worry about me the Airship is fine she's
been For Worse oh
the people of this land are kind kind of
odd
I know we'll find a way back to each
other soon it's in our blood you're far
from body from my body but you'll never
be far from my heart oh
oh and make sure to gather any pieces of
our map that you see it will help you
find your way in the world now get out
there and have some fun
she's so positive
kill even the little drawing
[Music]
night time
only without you Grandma I'm scared I'm
scared
well let's see
what this is peace oh interesting
ah that game was a freebie
oh music
[Music]
ah
I feel like I really needed a game like
this
[Music]
all right blood has its own Rhythm if
you pay attention listen
galliva cheese packages
they're already growing twice as fast
now quite the quit interrupting me okay
sorry
I I know I know that was cabbage
backwards what else would it be
straight roads to bridge
ha
huh
that's not what you wanted me to do
but straight it's straight
okay we'll think about it
we'll think about it there's a piece of
map here anyway
hussy
what about this
[Music]
hmm
I need to place a bridge there
eventually
[Music]
it's so peaceful
useful knowing the kitchen no no we'll
talk to talk Sally don't worry I know
that in this game it's it seems very
important to talk to everybody it's like
the experience you know
this is a lunar Lotus it blooms in the
Moonlight and barrels on the ground
during the day
[Music]
this is a bee bristle it looks soft but
don't touch it or you'll get a nasty
sting wow wait that little child looks
literally just like a tiny grandma
maybe you guys don't see it so well but
do you see that that lady in the middle
with the with the curly hair and the
necklace and the socks and the shoes and
I don't know whatever she's wearing it
just looks to me like a really really
tiny Grandma not like a child
yeah the blue-haired one
huh
we're getting fooled we're getting
bamboozled
don't let it fool you
she just wants to feel young again
probably
oh hello there don't mind us we're just
in the middle of class are you looking
for Mo this is his usual route home
just follow the curved roads and you'll
see his tent sometimes he stops by the
Riverdale you can follow the straight
roads there
well that sounds very important wait
stops by the river
so I need to make the straight road go
to a river right and please tell him
that his sheep got into my cabbages
again
I
I'm not old I'm not old not that old
I'm gonna become a master plant
collector like bomb car
[Music]
s
okay
a river
I don't have that what is there another
piece somewhere
curved roads to tents
curved
[Music]
nyani
you know I was hoping that it would
suddenly build something
and now I'm a little bit confused
[Music]
make a long straight row to spawn the
bridge isn't that what I already did
uh I went
I don't know I'm just gonna try some
things
haha
[Music]
no way
I don't know
foreign
[Music]
how are you I'm fine thank you how are
you
uh I'll have have anywhere to go
foreign
[Music]
what are you it's hard to understand
what you guys are talking about Middle
Road up and then straight what
wait
curved roads two tents
wouldn't that be correct
[Music]
there's a curved ruined
and then
[Music]
straight roads to bridge
straight huh
[Music]
what
use both straight roads
right
did they already do that a million times
and what about the top ones
[Music]
I don't know first let's go down
and
I need more curved rest okay maybe we'll
find something down here maybe it was
not available yet on purpose
hello
I wanted to write my secret mission
I mean my regular normal test and I
definitely can't talk about look I
really can't say anything interested I'm
looking for the head of the river
we heard that a special plant appears
there under right conditions and then it
might be the ghostly but that's all I
can tell you nothing else I have to get
back to the mission I'm so close
uh-huh
[Music]
no road ahead you don't want me to put a
road there
who
that's us
[Music]
of course that falls away
that is fine I'll make it easy for
myself wait
um
[Music]
okay nothing else here okay okay
um
I don't necessarily think that that
needs to go there because you can
already see the path there is
disappearing I think that's just you
know it just means like it won't
continue here
because it's already disappearing
already fainting
oh
[Music]
completely different houses here
oh you made it I tried to get some
um
yes
I want to introduce you to my father
he's collecting plants from all over
maybe you could help him find some new
ones
it's just for the curtain over there
curtain
ah over there okay wait a second let me
look at the stuff Let's Dance
[Music]
sweet for a descent emanating from women
a hearty Hive pun
[Music]
curtain where my delete well I know
where it will lead but why won't it let
me go there didn't you tell me to go
there
oh I was like no way I can change it in
here too oh
[Music]
hello
just like your son or may I say your son
looks just like you
[Music]
wait where will I land if I go out there
my son boo tells me you help him find
his sheep my thanks young sapling
[Music]
implying I am one of fauna's viewers
don't be shy whomever comes to this
grassland is our friend my name is
monkard and mighty a mighty fine plant
collector to other swim
I regularly travel to other grasslands
with my buddies to research plants
we also exchange seats with other tribes
so that they can grow every type of
plant
do you guys also send your people away
when they're 15 years old well are you
not that cruel
[Music]
we're always keeping an eye out for new
species just yesterday we discovered a
new type of rose
now if only we could come up with any
other name for it but enough about me
tell me about your grassland
I live in the sky much cooler than what
you guys do
I don't say a word I bet I can guess
where you're from I haven't seen a rope
like that before because you come from
across the ocean
huh
that could be literally anywhere and
everybody who's not from this island is
from across the ocean no
[Music]
see where in your air was a dead
giveaway
uh well
which island don't tell me I have an
idea hello Monica you clever Cactus my
notebook in the other room is a
compedium of plants that I've
encountered on my travels have a look at
it and tell me if you recognize any
plans for me Hometown huh
huh
from that surely I can surmise what you
hail from hail
that's pretty much exactly the way that
I came down
from heaven a honey fruit sapling
uh-huh
chill area
grasty
well if you guys like grass so much then
you
you wouldn't be so unhappy with my grass
meals from Cult of the Lamb huh well now
I have permission to look at this
yeah
I think a notebook filled with
handwritten notes about different plants
dancing Pines they swaying to The
rhythms of I would like to see like
pictures
and then sashing into adjacent Forest
the sour potato only one can grow every
square mile
having absorbed the ambient sourness of
all surrounding plant life false Moss
not actually Moss at all but a carpet of
pygmy grasshoppers
gooseberries they taste horrible and so
so many more hmm
[Music]
oh
anyway okay I'm not sure what that told
me
uh
on a separate piece of map huh
[Music]
now it's as if it's a different house
interesting
even though it's kind of the same house
it was just a second floor or so
sample of six don't get stuck
[Music]
cute a hanging garden of exotic spices
swamp you got there
very nice a planet that smells strongly
of caramel caramel
what
[Music]
how
what did you put there sex full of
flourishing flowers
[Music]
the marshmallow plant
you had better leave it alone well if
I'd only been alone What's it gonna do
to me
basket of orange fruit orange you glad
you saw some
okay okay okay that's it that's it
enough Ena has to play this game
it's as if Ina was part of the script
dialogue writing team
foreign
[Music]
all right
um wait I didn't find a piece of map
on on this piece of map
that is sus to me
[Music]
no piece of map here
foreign
oh well we have yet to go up here I
think oh no no we have it up here
why why was it grayed out I thought the
grayed out ones I've been to no I have
not been here
no this is the new curve that we got
that I didn't look at yet
right
okay but there's no piece of map here
either so I guess now I have to
um
come
on
what did it say on it
[Music]
no
oh what did it say on that one
on this one
river river wait uh Reba
wait
I don't know which side it is anymore
uh
wrong side
[Music]
wrong side wasn't there something about
you know
let me go read
yeah
Kirk wrote to tense
[Music]
and then
ah enough River Bridge Okay straight
road to bridge
yeah so we have a bridge here
um you're telling me that doesn't work
what
maybe I have to walk away
now he's here
was he wait was he almost here huh
[Music]
I'm pondering
wait is that also a joke
it's not a pawn still
foreign
[Music]
I tried to put this there and that
didn't work
[Music]
no
that's just a dead end
oh
um
[Music]
no no no these I can't attach another
road to it it doesn't work
[Music]
um a straight Road between the curve and
the bridge
yeah okay
I can see that as a possibility
oh but it didn't seem to work
[Music]
didn't make anything new pop up at least
foreign
[Music]
missing the forest by the trees but
attached Forest
ah it's a heart again but that didn't do
anything
um
oops
[Music]
now I made this really long
at least it looks cute
so many hearts
[Music]
okay what do we do I'm confused
talk to the dead again
[Music]
on the extra house
okay
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah because I looked at his book
did you find my notebook you didn't see
any plans for your Island dear how was
that possible what exotic land have you
traveled from what manner of Florida
grows there
clouds
such a curiosity you are I can see why
Mo brought you to me
[Music]
okay
what it wasn't Mo I brought myself to
you I'm an independent woman
also I need some I need some cough cough
drops and all making all these voices
hurts my throat so much
[Music]
Smiley flower
so when will you learn to communicate
communication is important
[Music]
I need plants plant plant grows in each
class and knowledge is a mysterious
Ghostly
um ephemeral as its name
can I have some of your soup please
I haven't eaten in a long time because
all they had was like seafood stuff I
didn't like that please you have at
least something with grass
veggies oh you poor girl you must be
famished look at me prowling on about
plants we want to stay for dinner and
back here for the night oh then it will
be the next day and we can meet our
friend again
oh wait maybe we then go again to
another Island we don't continue to just
stay here
we continue going to new places again
and again
thank you guys it's okay
mom
can you wrestle up some dinner and send
an extra place for a guest that's so
sweet
in the meantime can you do me a favor
young sapling we ran out of glow leave
last night I asked ganga Pokemon
to fetch some from the forest but it's
been gone for a while can you please
check on him I'm going to get some air
in the meantime I can't be away from
nature for too long
he's such a hippie
okay
piece of math please
unless you want me to go to the forest
that I
already have
um
that's all I got
[Music]
um
near near the forest
and wait did we already find him
the river guy
okay let's see
I don't remember if he told me his name
oh
the boy's all alone here
never mind it was not the river guy I
think
this Forest in here
I don't see him though
what are you talking about
how about we've completed now maybe he's
just in here now but normally the map
shows me
it's Forest this
what
uh interesting they're all pointing
towards it but hmm
when
[Music]
what about what about
what about here
[Music]
into this Forest
oh
[Music]
foreign
pieces
I can't make it into into one piece one
big piece
[Music]
unless no
the flowers
oh no that that won't connect the forest
has to be connected with forests
[Music]
wait
that's not broke my microphone I did
that before but I did it like in a
different way right I did like like one
like on this side oh yeah
what's the most confident okay wow
I did that before I had the right idea
but I wonder why why it didn't work
before why did it have to be like this
foreign
because last time I don't think it
matters what's surrounding it because
last time we had an unfitting pieces
surrounding something that was newly
created it was just popped off and it
flew like to the side so that shouldn't
be a problem but oh well
ah I need to I needed to talk to them
or maybe hmm
did that dude
him it is him
uh I don't remember the voice anymore I
finally found the head of the river
already time flies when you're solving
Mysteries I guess I should come eat
can't wait to explore the River tomorrow
we finally found together thanks to me
you know that was all me
[Music]
I don't think these little urchins will
let me go will you might bring this glow
Leaf to mocker for me oh I I'm bringing
okay that's fine with me
I prefer it that way but let me check if
there's like a piece of map here now
[Music]
maybe maybe maybe who knows who knows no
okay
uh
[Music]
I'll just put his hair
connect with us
sauce
[Music]
yeah
is this one you were looking for
ah some glowy if you must have found
ganga yeah yep
it was it was like looking for a rare
Pokemon
this is what we used to let everyone
know it's time for dinner
you burned a leaf
it tastes like the riverbed but it has
almost the most alluring aroma
oh you think that everybody will smell
this and come here is that so
interesting
they all get here
because I don't think I had everything
properly connected but that's so cute I
can grab
CLA
[Music]
it's like one of those animal Crossing
like endings
like you know when they have a little
concert
let's go with it yeah okay everything's
fine this is normal
hey oh they let me sleep over so nice
[Music]
stuff my mom taught me how to make it
before she passed on it always reminds
me of the
SE Among the Stars now
[Music]
like I was singing wait who's singing
this is harmony with the grasslands
if you listen closely
mom taught him to sing with the seeds
and he's going to teach me soon I can't
wait
well you have to wait
you have to be patient
very sweet story
rise and shine we have a very exciting
situation developing at the river
yeah
everyone's on their way there come join
us okay
oh
so here right
I guess I can just go down
he's slowly becoming told you
my it's my kusogaki voice you know my my
male kusagati boys
oh the music is nice oh this is so
friendly I can't wait to teach my class
about it I would have brought them with
but they're way too noisy
she's hiding why are you hiding
oh
what
[Music]
I heard that this plant is very shy
I have to make it I have to talk to
everyone so I make them hard and then it
will show up huh
the way he just really carefully moved
over here cute
morning I saw the ghostly for a second
but then the flow of the river changed
we'll have to wait until the direction
changes for it to appear again oh
if only we could change the flow of the
river
interesting how would you like me to
like like this
right
[Music]
no or what
yeah no it's weird like here it goes
that way and here it goes that way
[Music]
what would they do without me yeah
maybe
um
does that make sense
but I already switched I already flipped
that one though and I didn't know I
should have liked them
it's fine I'll figure it out
I just need um a piece of
Forest there
[Music]
goes to the right side goes to the right
side goes to the right
and now they're still hiding
[Music]
floating no we just need to hide okay me
too late for me wait for me I don't want
to mess it up
no I never had any spot oh you have
space okay okay
I'm coming
why are we hiding though
oh
Pokeball in it
[Music]
oh oh
it has an eye no no
no
oh
it's a little [\h__\h]
[Music]
to go
when you mean he just I just wanted to
take a look nobody told him you know we
should have just brought him here in the
first place oh it's stuck here don't
worry guys
I'll take it let's see I'm stuck
try to untangle it of course oh
where are we going no
game over
what
is this a game over
or am I going to a new island uh well
that's kind of a weird way to say
goodbye to everybody
this is still the same place
what about my blue-haired girlfriend
we're gonna meet up in the other Island
oh
oh no
[Music]
I wonder what would have happened if I
would have just left it there if maybe
nothing at all would have happened and I
would have been forced to eventually try
to untangle it because that seems to be
the flow of the game
I'm stranded
sorry I'm excited it's very cute
foreign
to get to where the owl is
which is
a riddle on its own
I just make a circle Maybe
oh God
but am I not in
I was gonna say am I not enclosed then
into the middle and then I can't wait a
second hold on I'll get to you
eventually
are you an owl person
how did Europe get here what a strange
places is
are you a messenger too where's your
beard
beard why do I need a beard I don't grow
beards sorry to disappoint you I my
beard is if anything on my head my
Fringe it's an upside down beard indeed
indeed
trust me bro
oh no matter look at this strange Leaf
it's your phone doesn't mean anything to
you
thank you that's Forest interesting
shall we keep exploring
oh
this property it's tragedy
there's an owl person and he uses owl
puns for puns
yeah
yay
oh oh I'll see you there
he
Trevor G after riding a really smarty
pants uh pun Super Chat
don't forget your sampling
what did you give me
a piece of map oh
okay let me
turn this around to the mountain
[Music]
if I do it like this
wait
the owl is on this one I think if I do
it like this I should be able to reach
the owl
and then I should also
be able to reach the fireplace I think
unless I'll change the positions just
now
okay
it's gone
what where did it go my cute burp
I wanted to meet the cute owl well this
this Forest is really fake
scary
kind of scary these people with their
animals come on did they eat the oh he's
looking at me
did they eat
the owl
also he has funny ear flaps like he has
leaves
on top of his head
like there's some animal ears cute
I'm scared of them Kawaii enemy of
Orlando of course everyone is friendly
right in this game
a fair Force to you oh did you find you
went to the wild world small one
you came from across the sea but
adventured deep Inland curious
I'm wreckage of the Redwood Forest
this man is deep of the barons
we Messengers have our animals to guide
us but this can be confusing play ah so
for the other one his messenger wants
the owl
but it's gonna be a confusing place for
her Fighters
the forest will show you a way out good
luck
foreign
what the [\h__\h] does the fox say
very graceful indeed
she has amazing hearing and often hunts
down our dinner for us
um
please tell me you're not hunting down
the house
blue
roads within the fork Fork was in the
mind Focus deep it will go deeper eyes
open
it's scary quiet
I'll grow your eyes open
what's your best companion flies High
strong beak prepare excellent Foods so
Noble
my friend
very Noble very Noble burp not as Noble
as a chicken have you ever heard of this
thing called Garden bird
yeah Garden bird is a very very
luxurious Noble
sophisticated
boob the most sophisticated of them all
please warm Yourself by the fire if you
like okay thank you
okay two pieces of map here very
generous
oh we're fog
for your wheel oh
yeah oh yeah
we're making our own base
I'm not talking about myself
I'm famous I'm also for sophisticated
interesting a strip of Club tied around
the tree
hot
food
I see I see I see how to connect them
so
like these
right
yeah oh music
ah
did I do it wrong because now it's yeah
but it made a sound as if it was correct
Maybe
it wants me to continue
ah wait
no I would have
huh oh
yeah I had to do it twice
wait and now the thing is still on that
side
oh
does it matter
how I connect it now because the ribbon
currently is
on the left side of that map and on the
left side of this map
let's see if it matters oh okay that
seems wrong
aha
so
um
this I think
now we're puzzling guys we do be
puzzling yeah yeah yeah
it keeps on changing I think because now
it should have been up there the ribbon
should have been upside
and now it's on the left side
oh
uh this way
[Music]
one more ah okay
uh
twice
[Music]
this game makes me happy
I'm going further and further away from
the island oh the [\h__\h] and lifted
I love this game I'm loving it so far
too it's very very sweet very Charming
this is again wow
go
oh
that's like a a dark dark wood
I can't connect these I can connect oh
this I cannot connect anywhere
maybe I need to find something that goes
from normal Forest into Dark Forest
mm-hmm
hello
bed it's a brown bear not a black bear
as we learned in this game a black bear
is a Blair so a brown bear would be a
bear mm-hmm
[Music]
going by the game's logic
is that your your messenger
hello foreign
companion don't worry he's your friend
too
where is your animal companion
I don't have one
oh I'm sorry how rude of way to assume
Wildwood is so dangerous and never
changing even with Messengers cannot
navigate it alone
it's amazing that you've come this far
without a companion
we grow up alongside our animals and
they help us find a way to murder
they help us search for fruit protect us
from danger and keep us warm at night
great friends
perhaps you'll see or even deeper in
world food across the guidance of the
forest even when it looks like there is
no path through
no I know
I know yeah I know what you're talking
about
oh
yeah I don't fit in your tummy I'm
poisonous believe me
who may not be a part finder but his
strength is mighty no obstacle
Constructors
um I'm I'm not here to stop you please
be nice to me
but these are just curves
let me move this away this is apparently
right now useless
um
okay
another little maze
[Laughter]
I see so this is a sign that it wants me
to go to the right side
which I would have done anyway
wait a second
foreign
wants me to move it to the left side
wait so you want me to go just back
yeah okay
okay it's coincidentally already correct
oh body what's up
nice to see you bye-bye
okay this one wants me to go to the left
so um
wait do I have to turn it though because
I can't turn it because then it won't
connect
ah okay it's fine and now wants me to go
out okay okay no problem
easy
hey
um
even more pieces
I didn't expect you know this kind of
riddle in this game
a pleasant surprise oh and look would
you look at that
we can connect these two but I still
can't really get there
soon TM
oh hello oh you all met up thanks to me
you should be thanking me guys this
little girl with no beard except for a
forehead beard
managed to make you all find your way
together again
what are you doing here
we forget
sweet but you guys should not be hugging
the brown bear
uh unless the brown bears on this island
in this world are nicer
I haven't heard good things about
incidents when you hug a brown bear
um
it's called a bear hug for a reason ah
Bears give the best hugs don't say that
that's kind of like
dark
samples
never heard of a bear hugger no
I too have a forehead beard trim cost me
twenty dollars hey yo I never get my
bangs trimmed at the salon I always trim
them myself because I don't think it's
worth you know paying someone for that
our tribes are Sport and we schedule
Christmas
feel closer to each other
a hooker to make scratchy does she live
for me you want grassy
we had someone make grass tea
I didn't expect to see you or get a
small one but here you are the world was
unpredictable While others have been
ushered out it seems to have brought you
deeper in we almost said mother look how
dense to the trees grow here oh you mean
[Music]
I will continue over there
Road ended still on path remakes
oh wait I got another one
rest and go yeah thank you
by the way guys I got my mustache today
finally it was
marvelous
marvelous ah
I really needed that it was really good
and at the end my body has been cracked
in ways it has never been cracked ever
before
twisted and turned in directions
well my body went like
a million times
in one go
and then we did it the other way and it
did it again my back my my spine went
like
holy [\h__\h] and then it was not only my
spine but also my neck
holy [\h__\h] I thought I thought my neck
would snap and I would die
thankfully I'm alive
[Laughter]
well okay that was wrong but how would I
have known like where where is the sign
how ah wait is it the way that the trees
sway
all right any chance
these trees sway to the left
y
[Music]
well now it's still swaying to the left
but I have to connect this piece again
was that correct because I've never paid
attention to that until now
so I connected over there
is it a coincidence it was not a
coincidence it was a coincidence that
it's way to the right side again okay so
now to the right side
okay
and again to the right side oh
[Music]
you know one thing though about the
massage
I chose a massage place where I haven't
been before too
and I did not expect
this
at all
this place had cats
cats
two cake ads and they loved me
they were so freaking adorable
like you know how the massage table has
like a hole where you put your head
through and you could you basically face
the bottom all the time
well that would look down there the cat
would pass walk by
and I would grab I would touch and pet
the the cat with my hands
and one of them would sleep under the
table and then you know I was really
excited about the cats so the massage
person noticed that and and like tried
to put because the other cat was
sleeping somewhere else and we tried to
put the cat on top of me
but the cat didn't stay for long
on my on my legs for a few like a minute
and then it left it was so cute they
loved me so much they cuddled so much
with them
um oh can I read that too
oh damn yeah cat massage not quite
though
I hope you're having the best Adventures
did you visit the grassland I'm sure you
learned about some new plants if you did
I did go there now I'm somewhere in a
spooky place
the Airship is finally operational again
she's humming along better than ever I'm
dropping this letter in the Wildwood
hoping you'll pass through if you ever
find yourself lost in their head toward
the center of the forest huh
uh-huh an old friend of mine watches
over a special tree I wonder if he'd
remember me I'll keep searching and keep
your eyes to the skies we'll be together
again before you know it oh love you
Grandma I love you
no no junkers and smoothie whenever I go
to a place with cats and I come back
supposedly smelling like another cat
they never care or they never ah there
you go
that's what I was looking for aha wait
they're never they never complain or act
weird not at all it's normal
everything's always very normal
oh
that one's just no
no that's just part of it okay
and now we reach
the final the middle part oh oh
this feels like
um from Lord of the Rings the the forest
wizard would live in here
what was his name the one who was riding
on like a Santa cart
powered by bunnies and rabbits
or something like that I was more
thinking of ratatosk though
oh
this is also amazed and there's like oh
like some kind of bug
another hotel
there we go smart me
oh he was in The Hobbit not Lord of the
Rings huh was that so
but that's because tastes wasn't funny
uh
[Music]
interesting that they allowed me to
connect those pieces because
those paths don't align
[Music]
eyes
wait can that be fishing bait in the
first island I don't know if I'll ever
go back there
is bending its own rules here this game
allowing me that also okay they they
completely abandoned their own rules I
think did you have a second breakfast
today me no but smoothie yes I don't
know why you're asking me that but
this movie that little [\h__\h] she just
will not
listen to me anymore you know she used
to always be like
like she always waited for me to wake up
properly and then she would meow
endlessly oh the one oh
oh what happened so
oh it's going through
here I'll help you I guess I'm not only
helping myself here
foreign
wait wait
what
thinking hard really hard it doesn't
connect
is there another piece of map that I
don't have yet for this place
hmm
[Music]
give me a second
what was I saying oh yeah it's moving
nowadays since like a week ago what she
will do is wake me up before I'm
actually awake
and then
she will not stop meowing until I give
her breakfast
so
today was one of those days where I I
just could not fall asleep anymore I got
up and I gave her a breakfast
and then I went back to sleep for
another two hours and I woke up again
and then
instantly meowing at me again as if she
hadn't had breakfast before trying to
get a second breakfast out of me and I'm
like no you little [\h__\h] I know you've
already got breakfast today you know wet
food and she always has Kibbles but she
just would not stop
so I like before she would meow for like
maybe five minutes and then she would
stop and give up but this time she just
wouldn't give up so I gave her
my second breakfast and sometimes
recently she also even gets thinner wet
food because she will just not
leave me alone
[Laughter]
these days and I I I can't I feel like
I'm being controlled by this movie
nah
this movie is in control now
she's
that stupid little [\h__\h]
needs discipline
[Music]
bragging to my friends about how good my
cats are
how they how I never have to scold them
but now she's she's such a little
Annoying piece of [\h__\h]
ah well um
at least I want to see those lies
foreign anyway what the [\h__\h] are we
doing how is it not possible for me to
connect all of this
it must be possible somehow
or I'm really missing something but
anyway I I I want to go
to hmm
what
can I go like this okay this is why I
wanted to go I have a feeling I need to
go
to the end of that road and I'll find
something
no [\h__\h] what I thought there would be
something here
maybe
no wait that doesn't work what am I
doing
love you thank you thank you
love you too
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
and I don't know what's going on anymore
is that not where I came from that
is that one with the arrow not where I
came from
or is it the other way around
uh okay let me try to go there
oh
foreign
[Music]
this way no
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
also I thought the the worm would move
on to the next map if I connected it
correctly but so far
it did not do it
wait so which piece does this one
connect to this one okay okay
so
I want to get back to where the warm is
no but isn't that not actually where it
came from
is that not actually where it came from
let me go back here
so do it like this and then
hmm
yeah yeah that's just from another angle
I get it maybe maybe not maybe not but
let me see
puzzle baby puzzle time yeah I get it I
get it I'm getting it
now I'm here
where the warm is again and now I can
connect this and we can see if that spot
is where I came from or if there's
something interesting oh
wait what was it about the warm what was
that thing about the worm then
huh
okay
all right we did it we found this
it's scrubber again
you don't want to talk to me
what about you
ah she's right she's always right it's
true true blood's just sapling so
ashamed what my mother think huh
what does trip do where does she go it's
almost time for the ritual and no time
to go back to his Forest
I'm only sure about something to replace
to help him with you mean the warm
oops
huh
the warm
I can't go back inside though
ah
one if I
oh
no I can't go back
to my death
what do you want from me
ah stupid
ah
[Laughter]
this
this is not a sapling
but perhaps it will work I plan to
supplant it's a plant it's better than
not a plant
okay thank you beardless messenger
you're a small and kind
sharp goes gratefully
his legs
ah
there's more
oh no what the [\h__\h]
okay
now maybe we can make the the warm reach
his destination
[Music]
where is this destination ah here
assuming that's the destination
disconnects
or wouldn't it be oh never mind
never mind
I don't think I will be able to solve
this
so easily but I'm just going to try oh
I am just going to try this reminds me
of the golden path
[Music]
ah Doesn't Remind anyone else of the
golden path
oh [\h__\h] genius
[Music]
the golden path is now the brown path
yay
[Music]
well now maybe I have to go where the
worm has moved on to
so let's figure that one out first we
got the the warm going now we have to
get going ourselves
um
maybe it's actually pretty easy it is
pretty [\h__\h] easy production
I wonder what the meaning of that is
also I see the arrow
you want me to go that way
don't give up but I'm done
wait I'm actually done
what if I leave now
can I leave
or do I have to leave through
I have to have to leave for the exit
which is was it always this one
does the Avril mean something though oh
is that a new exit
Mata
okay it's not that easy
okay
well
yeah yeah yeah yes the exit I'm judging
by what it was last time now it should
be this one
I just need to figure out how to attach
it
let's see let's see what fits to the
green one first you know this is just
easy basic puzzling rules
find the pieces that connects to the
edges first oh
ah
interesting go to the one that says
don't give up that's why the arrow was
showing there
because that one connected to that and
it connects today
oh
[Music]
Eerie spooky
what's this
Wasteland
broken Stone bearing part of an
incomplete symbol
a riddle time baby more riddles let's go
let's take a look around first
um
spooky music this whole island
is generally really spooky
very different atmosphere oh
stop stop it's so spooky
okay
it will be
a dirt path another another big
symbol with many meanings
shuttle wait
can I figure it out just by doing it in
the map view
let's see
that doesn't fit does it
it's not a perfect fit
that is that that looks maybe like a
perfect fit
as long as it lets me connected I guess
whatever
that works
but is that really what it wants me to
do
hmm
colors hook a bit off
oh that's just because I didn't go there
I would say oh that works
I don't know what I'm doing
I don't know what I'm doing I don't know
what I'm doing
huh
wait
oh wait never mind [\h__\h] all of that
[Music]
does that even work
those little pieces there you see that
but now I need to go there
foreign
what will we find there
yeah of course and I always know what
I'm doing even when I say I don't know
what I'm doing I of course always know
what I'm doing oh
that's how you want me to build it
or is this how it currently is
huh no
no no okay
Stone bearing on a unique symbol yeah I
see I see
is there anything else here to pick up
perhaps I don't think so but
okay
oh
so
it looks like like a butterfly not
really but let's just remember that
there's like a middle body and there's
two Crossings and one goes outside and
then up and then inwards
and the bottom one goes outside and then
down in a squiggle
okay
I wonder if I already kind of had it
before
and I just didn't recognize it because I
first had to look at this so is it this
way
well the other way around
[Music]
[\h__\h]
should have taken a screenshot
but the apple one oh wait I will know by
seeing what connects with each other and
it looks like this connects with each
other
I said it goes inwards again right and
then we have like squiggles
but first we have another Crossing I'm
so good at this wow I'm such a Puzzler
let's go
uh it goes like and downwards um but
wait
um
wait isn't there something missing
hmm
[Music]
because that doesn't fit
I didn't do something wrong
[Music]
turn the middle one ah
okay okay okay
and then oh well that looks
dad looks like it makes a lot of sense
wow
oh
fun
hello how are you
sleepy head just like me
[Music]
oh I can't hear you because you're too
beardy
yeah
much better I've almost forgotten how to
speak the common language after all
these years alone why is this cheese
mother isn't much of a conversation but
it's good to see you here messenger the
first to arrive Rebel as you know I am
the Watcher
you must have received the signal which
Forest are you joining from and where's
your animal companion
the worm
my tiny friend you can come up now
can I have can I use the worm
oh come closer inspection perhaps you
are not a messenger
went to Traverse these Woods while as
they are
I grant
yeah it was quite a challenge
a fun challenge
navigation is in your blood dear girl
you remind me of someone you know in my
youth across the sea it was a young
woman
do you know my grandma
oh never mind simply a passing
impossibility no no
[Music]
no no
my granddad Maybe
have you caught a glimpse of The
Messengers yet I wonder which will
mother choose huh
mother
oh yes I suppose this ritual would be a
mystery to you Messengers Watchers
saplings Animal Companions it's very
ancient oh very ancient and fascinating
say we take a walk and I can give you
the entire oral history humor and old
man I haven't spoken to anyone in
decades
I will listen gladly
when the mother tree has reached the
hand of her thousand year growth the
current water must put her to sleep
using the Flames of the Wildwood her
life Essence carpets the entire Forest
spurring a millennium of new growth
oh
second one to join I was here best
not hello there listen junip of Barons
wheelchair
travel too far we bring sapling I will
be watch up
hello welcome I'm just in the middle of
a yarn please go and wait for my mother
and we'll be with you shortly
first try yeah
the smoke from mother also access a
signal to the four Stripes which each
send the messenger bearing a sapling
from their Village once the messenger's
reached mother and plant their saplings
they must recite the 87 stances of the
rhyme of the Wildwood
What would
ah more messages
I'm tired Explorer I think you're too
small one and there's no surprise to see
you here Ray cat from the Westwood
Forest by foxy friend and I are ready
for the ritual
back oh do you have a green and the Moon
maybe surely there's an order to be in
mother's Embrace a few calls you already
Messengers and Woodland companions
please gather that mother I'm almost
done regaling our friend we're here
without traditions
a lot of fun Allure yeah
not that the saplings are planted mother
will choose one of them to embody her
regrowth
the messenger Who provided the sapling
will become the new launcher and the
tribe will protect mother throughout her
growth
as each water grows old and never from
their tribe will take over so that the
Elder launcher may go home and live out
their days in the village as you may
have guessed I'm the final launcher of
my line and I'm well ready to return to
my Village
oh I wonder if they still make those
toasted bananas back home the house of
bananas
mmm
try
our final messenger you're just in time
for toasted bananas
finally some good [\h__\h] food
I mean
drum is exhausted but you're a bit
sibling definitely original sample uh
try a pair of the confirm comfortable
trip will surely never be chosen as
Watcher but excited to attend
a glorious day in the Wildwood hello
beardless one
everyone is here it's time to wake
mother let us gather
oh
mother it is time to awaken
yeah wake up wake me up inside
your children have traveled from
farthest Forest Redwood parents
Evergreen Conifer reason
no you're watching ready for my wrist We
Gather here to begin your rebirth
Messengers produce your siblings the
strongest most beautiful specimens
do I have to censor what's gonna happen
now
[Music]
let's plant them and serve mother from
her slumber
hey okay we're good we're good
okay okay okay okay
no funny things here guys
all right all right all right looking
good
oh
boy
very special sapling very special one
oh
my sapling the most special one seems to
become the protagonist here
ah mine worked oh I was like well what a
strange new sapling mine's choice is
clear messages the next Watcher is
oh
Trevor let's go
what
[Music]
else I don't know if it's something to
be happy about but ah who took look at
who's turning its head
oh it's so cute it's like
hahaha look at him look at him he's so
cute
[Music]
I want to be an owl
I want to be an owl because
tiny tree oh
a slightly bigger tree what
[Music]
uh Drive is so confused why is he to
watch her dream is watching of course
this is an hour Link in the 360 no scope
because I'll just say this first well
then at least you don't have to hear any
more insults about other trevors
it's more quiet here
no no crazy Travers
uh crashing helicopters into the big big
towers
[Music]
must have been the sapling you gave
chirp special sapling
[Music]
special too
chip wants to go home
that's not trip home
you're not happy
um
[Music]
good good original was a success mother
chose chips sapling and thus he becomes
a new Watcher he may not feel ready but
mother knows best the mere Act of being
chosen will start him down the path
mother is in no rush
[Music]
perhaps you'd like to say goodbye to the
other Messengers and then I can show you
the path out yeah all right
we're a bit relieved we're having chosen
honestly we love exploring but we're not
as happy staying in one place more than
most you've known that she's so wise
impressive
I don't know it would have been nice to
be chosen but money does what's best for
the entire first we'll stick around for
a bit in case Trump needs any help bye
sweet
old Choice chill but I respected
mother will go taller than Scott want to
witness
[Music]
ah
by the way where are the females on this
island how are you guys
you know making more
of you
how does that work
[Music]
no answer okay I am confused I will
never get the answer
sounds like the other Messengers will be
sticking around a bit longer I'll still
be making my own Junior home once I've
shown trip the ribs may I show you the
pap out of the Wildwood
yes please
oh wait I shook my head oh well In some
cultures that means yes
not
I don't wanna read your fan fiction ah
[Music]
some questions don't need answers
uh-huh
but
I want the answer I'm curious curious
bib
it's time for your first lesson oh oh
okay
what what are you gonna teach him
must learn the language of the trees
once carefully trip
look at him watching look at him
watching
he's like
the foreign
[Music]
thank you Santa Claus
it was destiny that you should come here
and with this you'll never lose your way
and the wife was home
I'm glad you could join us and thank you
for helping trip replacement
how did you know
ah surprise you can fully Watcher chirp
you'll understand one day love it sees
all and she still chose you worry not go
little one I'm sure we'll see you soon I
give my best to you grandmother
is that my grandpa
and then wouldn't he have like you know
wanted to maybe have more of a proper
conversation with me
yummy
travel safe and pray for Troop
in the name of wholly Doodly Doo I wish
you a happy Hut
Duty
cool anyway
I'm so excited
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
I'm thinking since I'm splitting it into
two parts
should I split it now I don't know how
far I am am I like halfway through
does anyone know anyone who played this
before
because I need to read maybe some super
chattels and I also need to get up early
tomorrow
I can check
yeah it's been two and a half hours and
I heard this game is five to six hours
so if I if my progress was
relatively fast then I would be halfway
through
foreign
[Music]
I think my progress was pretty pretty
decent
yeah next time I want to start a bit
earlier just in case indeed
maybe maybe oopsie
I'm only 30 done 40 40. okay yo you
scared me but okay kind of seems about
right okay 40 is fine the next time we
go a little bit longer this one's really
cute
really cute game very chill very
relaxing and makes me feel smart once
again
um
[Music]
oh
so let me move over to the office no
time to waste
um
I have to read some of them
from the amongus and from today and I
stay with my decision that I wanna
um save some super chats from the
members only for a members only Super
Chat rating
um
foreign
less than 100 total oh
thank you you're keeping track huh yeah
members only had
um way more Super chats because it was
an anniversary that's the real challenge
but yeah we'll get there we'll get there
let me move
oh
[Music]
scary it's because of the the movie
watch along
what
Michelle
sorry
that was because I made myself a bit
darker
for the sake of the movie watch along
that we did in my in my darker room
[Music]
great adventure for today I agree
really close the game I'm glad I found
it and it has
um cute dialogue and space for my own
dialogues
oh
[Music]
what time
awesome I think today after the stream I
have nothing like like instant
there's nothing that I can cook
instantly like a
like a pizza or so
but I think I will for sure
make some quick pasta with some pesto
sauce that I have in the fridge
yeah
yeah something relatively simple just
add some cherry tomatoes and then we
could
[Music]
I could order something now but I feel
like
I never really want to order food
because it's so expensive
the current price will be safe okay
so
cute this game
yeah I can't believe I never found it
before in my two years of streaming
because it came out two years ago
and I didn't find it until now even
though I think like it's a pretty cozy
and cute streaming game
haven't seen any other whole life member
played either
but we can play all the games from this
publisher
so
yeah
maybe maybe with me playing it I will
bring some attention to it to some other
whole life English members
um
I was a lot pickier
back then was that
maybe towards like you know shooting
games or so but towards these these kind
of cute games I don't think I would have
said no to it
would I
yeah they publish really cute games
they look pretty good the games they
have
um
let me go to Whole Eliza
oh yeah
was a pretty one
humble games humble games
humble games is the one a lot of Indies
is this considered an indie
is humble game is an indie game
publisher
which is this considered an indie game
a nice thumbnail
if you're a new viewer then how come
you're already calling me uh boss huh or
did you just learn really fast what's
going on here
oh it is oh
you know what I don't mind
all these in the games they have so much
passion so much love
in them oh by the way guys tomorrow
um is in about 14 hours or so is meet
and greet there's two slots one is in
like 14 hours and one is like 10 hours
or so after that
um so
um I have heard
and that's three people no wait one one
maybe they wait they already two of them
already replied right
ah there's one last person that did not
reply to their email
um no I doubt that that person is
coincidentally here but just saying
uh uh one of the 20 winners has yet to
reply
to the email so
please check and reply
if you're here
otherwise uh I don't know if if that
person replies later on then
I'll try to figure out an extra
time for them but maybe they will never
say anything then it's too bad but yeah
yeah
check your spam mail I know the chances
are really low because I'm only looking
for one person
yeah but uh just in case yeah
I'm gonna make a Twitter post yeah I was
so I'm thinking about it
okay anyway also for the new members who
joined in September
um if you haven't gotten the wallpaper
and the animated wallpaper yet
um I uploaded it one more time
uh before the month ends which I mean if
we are in a sea country then it's
already ending
so you'll get the new wallpaper
actually tomorrow if I don't forget
about it
and it's October so expect a little bit
of a spoopy
one okay it's not really spoopy it's
actually cute it's more cute than spoopy
but you know what I mean
[Music]
um
foreign
I'm sure I'm sure you can
all right
um let me
start going through the superchatas
um
it is spooky and cute maybe yeah I put
on those tux but I'm eating right I hope
it isn't too formal wait you're you're
made it into the meet and greet no way
did you
so much
it's time for spooky games no no
no no no no no no no no no no you know
every game is a spooky game for me
October
[Music]
did I last year did I play
what was that game
uh did I play little nightmares two or
only little nightmares one
because that's at least one game we
could play because I I bought it already
last year I only played one ah ah nice
I have the second one in my library for
one whole year already
so we can play that one in October
in the week of oh no we just mentioned
oh that would be nice too
I would be fitting
Alice what was that is that edible um is
that like a French cookie or so
don't know what you're talking about
I'm not so much into French food you
know
we we last we we we last hmm
no
let me read some super chats
I I don't have time for this I need to
read super chats
[Music]
the frame all right I'll think about it
if I have permissions for it
are you guys hearing the music
I think you're hearing a double
no
you haven't said anything about it
sounds fine
he's a man there's no problem
[Music]
no problem
doesn't matter
ha ha ha
ha
I know it's not double
[Music]
um
oh wait this is um
should I pull up the thumbnail
[Music]
thumbnail here
so pretty yo I wanted the thumbnails to
look organized and professional did I do
a good job
I put quite a lot of effort into it you
know
getting some some nice looking resources
for it
and the thing is like
I I took
you know the the photos of everyone by
myself
um you know because I wanted them to
have certain expressions
like interesting expressions and I
wanted them to look straight and all
that so
um you know if I would tell every one of
them to follow certain instructions
first of all it would take a while a
second of all it would often
um not work out uh
because they do it differently not the
way I want it so I just took everything
myself and then the problem was after I
was done with all of them
um one of them told me
[Music]
you may have used
something a look of me that
was not allowed to be shown yet and I I
honestly it looked exactly the same to
me
to something that would be okay to show
so I was like hey hey
[Music]
and then I was like [\h__\h] do I have to do
everything all over again but no I
managed I managed to
um just like copy paste
uh and okay one on top of it
so yeah I kind of had to do it
I sent everyone an updated one
I sent everyone an updated one though I
was like please use this one
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
did she show it though like by now
yeah bye now okay
[Music]
foreign
oh
okay
don't clip this by the way this is not
something that needs to be clipped I
really don't see any value in clipping
this but um
say it's not a big deal but that's not
for me to decide so anyway
yeah
I just wanted to tell you that I had to
make all the thumbnails twice because of
that oopsie
no if I say don't clip it then don't
clip it otherwise I'll I'll delete it
but don't clip it
it's not necessary to clip somebody my
dad unnecessary
what was I even talking about though oh
yeah I was proud
up to it and I thought it looked really
cool
[Music]
um I still need to improve my graphic
creation skills
I wish I could just really easily whip
up something really cool looking but I
still need to experiment here and there
um
but I think it worked out pretty well
and I'm happy that it was an uneven
number of participants because that way
you see here you can like split it up
properly so that there's one big one in
the middle and the other ones are on the
side what's a little beam
yeah there has been worse incidents
before yes yes
foreign
[Music]
but on this one it took me a lot of time
it took me took me like two hours or so
to make all of them
and it was quite an effort
and then oh I didn't talk about this yet
but
you know I was I was like
um two hours before the stream I was
ready to prepare and like several times
I asked everyone to be there at least
one hour now two hours before they were
already a couple Indonesia girls with me
trying to farm some points you know but
we really quickly figured out that
um we can't just like go into a game and
then quickly kill everybody and then get
out no no that doesn't work like that so
we had to play properly and then we also
I mean we were just like five people or
so but we already tried to get the voice
chat thing going and thankfully it
worked all good so
that was nice but then uh gradually a
few more girls would join us
one by one one by one one by one and I
thought okay okay I mean it should be
fine and at the one hour mark I think we
were maybe just missing two people
um so we played a little bit longer and
then half an hour before the stream uh
I think we were just missing one person
so we played a few more games and I said
I told myself and everybody it's gonna
be fine it's gonna be fun it's gonna be
fun no you know what in reality I know I
know somebody will be late
somebody will not be here on time and
something will at the very right before
the stream will stop working so
um both things happened
so this is why I wanted everyone to be
there really early but even when you're
there really early like movie was there
pretty early but then we had a problem
like literally five minutes before the
Stream
suddenly her mic was like you know in in
better crew link it would work in
certain situations and in others it
wouldn't which was really weird like in
meetings
or so we couldn't hear her but in the
lobby we could or so
and also it was quiet so she changed the
microphone five minutes before the
stream which was okay because I was
still waiting for the 11th person to
show up anyway
so I was like yeah okay no problem we
have to wait anyway and then I was like
okay everybody we need to delay 15
minutes so you know for some reason
communication was really problematic
here
I I kept on repeating myself I I said I
said 15 minutes a million times wait so
what are we doing are we are delaying
and I'm like yeah 15 minutes please
and then one minute later uh sorry what
are we doing are we delaying it or not
and I'm like yes 15 minutes delay please
so this is also a problem with so many
girls in one place it's hard to get
everyone to listen to you
uh also when I was trying to do the
better crewing
um like explanations
in her stream that I
got cut off like a million times because
of the lobby falling apart in the mangas
every time I was trying to explain
something
that and like even when it wasn't
falling apart it was still hard
sometimes to get people to listen and
yeah women was like trying to figure out
um the new microphone and then the new
microphone that she attached wasn't
working and we were trying some things
changing some settings and then it was
still not working so I was like maybe
you should use the old microphone the
one from before
definitely magically it worked
and then suddenly
no not suddenly the the last person was
still missing so
I was like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I really wanted
this to start on time because I couldn't
delay it endlessly because for the
Indonesian members it was midnight
you know I didn't want to delay too much
um but then
I
I was able to contact the last person
and uh last person showed up
and we oh yeah I'm almost didn't stream
her POV and she told me she wasn't going
to stream but she ended up streaming it
so
I'm glad she streamed it
I think for amargus very important
to have as many povs as possible and I
liked her her POV teammates were crying
about is that why she ended up streaming
in
ah last person well
I think
had the time wrong
yeah so
finally we had everyone together so that
was literally
the last person uh showed up
uh literally
five minutes before the start of the
time that was already delayed so
yeah or like three minutes even only so
I was like okay okay listen listen I
need to explain these things to you so
better crawling you to this setting and
this setting on and this often this
Anonymous often is under this off and
then for Among Us need to make sure to
have the Cosmic Cube not only redeem but
also activated have you done that yet
and so many times I had to explain also
the thing with the Cosmic Cube because I
asked the girls have you guys activated
it in the game as well and everybody
said yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah but
then turns out when I dig a little bit
deeper because I knew I knew that
surely some of them did not realize that
you also have to activate it in game
when I say activate in-game I mean
activate in game not redeem the code
so then I found out some of them really
didn't activate it and they were like oh
what do you mean and I'm like ah you
have to go in here after Redeeming the
code you have to click here activate
otherwise you will not be able to gain
the points
yeah yeah I did my research and I tried
to share my knowledge
but with 11 members it was really
difficult
yeah
uh that's quite something but I'm glad
everything went pretty well
um like unfortunate that for example
Zetta had internet issues but besides
that I think it went pretty well better
crew link was working
no no problems like last time with Ollie
I was feeling so sorry I didn't want
that to happen again
I mean last time that time I was not the
organizer
um with a better crew link where I only
had problems but but she um had those
problems two times apparently and two
different collabs
um
I just wanted to make sure that
everybody
uh has a good time with better Cooling
yeah no one was left out everything went
rather rather smoothly
and I was literally done explaining
things
at the exact 15 minute Mark and then I
was like okay everybody
let's go let's go let's go let's go
I was like I felt like I was on fire
ah yeah I was so relieved
oh my God
cheerleader
more like a coach not a cheerleader
what could we do without you uh you
could do many things without me
um
believe me don't need me
for that kind of stuff if it wasn't for
me someone else would do it I'm sure
someone else would take the tsukel in
their hands
I mean you guys need me but not
specifically for this kind of stuff
I would say
anyway I need to worry super chats guys
uh stop me from tangenting what the [\h__\h]
ing
cocoon thanks for the pinky you are
absolutely incredible I love the new
song so much your dancing is amazing I
especially love the hip movements your
singing is beautiful and as always with
your songs it gets better the more you
listen to it after moving it for a
million times I can safely say it might
even become my all-time favorite as of
right now it's still fever night oh but
doing is very close you are the best
thank you thank you
I'm happy to hear someone likes people
tonight thank you
engine is the best part of your streams
thank you
uh skydiving
you got this bus John there's no way
you're ever going to be the Imposter hey
everybody kitties for some sassy hole
action I did become the Imposter once
but it's crazy how many times I got the
Imposter in the practice round before
before the stream like a million times
it was impossible three times in a row I
was never a pastor so many times as I
was in that practice session before the
collab what was up with that
Emma was referring so many accusations
yeah she was during the actual
collaboration and I think she was just
[\h__\h] with me
no grounds
uh
[Music]
trust me because of my existence
but
but she's cute so I forgive her
and she's she's
cute it's not ashamed yeah
yeah Kobo was imposter four times which
is crazy I saw her
um using the the heart
heart monitor
heart Challenger
love conqueror
um
she okay she's one of those people with
a standard heart rate of over 100
apparently
was she ever below a hundred
or 110
I don't think she wants
how what I don't understand how can your
as a relatively young person
how can your heart rate
talking about several whole life members
here
be a standard over 100 by default mine
was 116. maybe
oh I understand are you like is that
healthy
are they okay
gouda as well
I think that was one of them who else
has a really high heart rate by default
look I'm
I'm only like
unhealthy but my heart rate is normal
Bae fauna oh yeah oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
I'm not as unhealthy as I think maybe
[Music]
yeah I don't know I don't know what I
don't know what's there to wrongly
configure because when I
used my thing there was nothing to
configure in the first place
[Music]
small animal small animals usually have
higher heart rates
whole
is that why she has such a high heart
rate
but it I feel like everybody
besides me has like an insanely high
heart rate I I don't understand
do I need to make them like a diet plan
of what to eat
to become more healthy
no I'm not the tallest though I'm not
a coffee
they I thank you they all drink coffee
don't they I don't know about Kobo but
like I think
well Bay drinks coffee Iris seems like
someone who drinks coffee oh no this
does this fauna drink coffee
that's gonna drink coffee
coffee crony has a little hard rain
barely hit 90.
thank God thank God there's there's one
whole life English member where I don't
have to worry about a heart attack
but that brings energy drinks oh that's
um bad that's not healthy
it's not healthy healthy
watch out for life
drinks matcha latte
I drink two liters of coffee in it oh my
God stop
what
I have to worry about Courtney dying
because of a week old Subway sandwich
oh God spanking that thank you the game
will create Duncan traveled to Phillips
Duncan Tara Phillips abdom is pram
Duncan
ah a-l-l
aw
boss sorry to bother you I saw some
stuff and one of number 509 Cafe
engineering Supervisor was hang out with
red rats
if you wonder why I'm there nothing I
just passed through it's not about me
it's about them I think you should give
me a promotion
what does this mean
doesn't mean they went to watch Bale's
stream
okay don't worry
so you're snitching on
another employee
and red sounds like bae I guess so
okay
[Music]
spy Australian sister
even though she doesn't call me sister
okay
[Music]
thanks guys for the medals oh my God
I watched I rewatched that moment of me
explaining why Kobo is the Imposter and
that whole Revelation I'm so proud of
myself okay
but I wish I could have given Kobo a hug
but you know I had to I had to like
sound confident and and explain it
properly because if I just like give a
[\h__\h] reason when I have a proper
reason at hand and just like you know
say oh it's Kobo why I don't know
because she is Kobo just believe me no I
have to explain it properly for it to
sound legit and have a good reasoning
and a good base so
I'm sorry Cobble
injected anyway
[Music]
she seemed very happy
she was like um
um it's better if I'm
kicked out anyway you know
trust me bro
[Music]
she calls me out a million times for no
reason and one time I point my finger to
her because she's been pointing all the
fingers it's funny how she's pointing
fingers all the time and then I point
some fingers and she says kiwama You
seem to be pointing a lot of fingers huh
your son's and I'm like hey yo well
you're pointing so
and me it's like you have more than two
hands
[Music]
hmm
you cannot question
my love for amen
you cannot question it seriously I think
we all know
I love amen
I love her
but it's a game
I was a better detective than her
yeah but I had so many like
so many
like ideas oh this this person is
probably imposter I have no reason no no
grounds to explain it but I think it's
them but since I don't have a good
reason for it I I'm keeping I'm holding
back
keeping my opinion to myself but then it
always turned out to be correct
good instincts but zero proves exactly
that's me
yeah Callie I I liked Cali it's like
really confident explanations
um that was it just felt so reassuring
because she also has this something
about her that people will listen to her
when she starts speaking like besides
that you know there would be a lot of
like people talking over one another in
those meetings a lot of you know
interrupting each other but when Cali
would start talking and explaining her
her reasonings yeah she has speech 100.
people would listen and then agree
yes she has a authoritative voice yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes that's what I'm
saying hmm
[Music]
no
uh where was I
had see foundations
thank you everybody
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
Vibes doesn't she
and I said it before but she is a little
bit intimidating
which she can use to her advantage
I think
yeah
okay now we read the ones from this
stream and then we're good
oh wait they don't show up in whole
lines are yet okay
okay okay
then I go through
YouTube Studio
they do huh
what
huh
just not on that page ah
here
oh wait
oh wait that's my stream go away ah here
ah okay I found it
[Music]
salutations tension currently I'm
working to make small Chihuahua sound
pack for World of Warcraft
South Park
well it meant quite the prowess but
can't find line fitting you're staying
in fire alert
please shout at player for standing in
fire
what kind of Fire
standing in a fireplace
with line of your choice
or if you have no idea about Lila I
could just dress the line get the [\h__\h]
out of the fire you little [\h__\h] thank
you I'm friend Angel
share to final result after the sun okay
huh
mod for reading
okay well I don't I don't need to think
too much about it I'll just I'll just do
it
how about that one more
[\h__\h]
how about that
I wouldn't
you're welcome
thank you
for the pinky tensor I trust you you
betrayed me you killed me in spawned
that's not betraying
you were there and I took after him
because that was the Imposter I'm
actually had only two seconds of
gameplay I'm not gonna say it didn't
feel good
but still rude I knew something was off
when you sat in the chat I'm hungry and
looked up to me
but that would have been before I even
got the Imposter Royal note
no no
you know I was just because it was a a
private Members Only
uh not even on stream game
I was just you know trying to get some
quick kills going
I was just I was just messing around I
can do whatever the hell I want
yeah there's nothing like betrayal if
you're the Imposter I'm just doing my
job
and don't worry you're not the only one
I killed I killed a lot of a lot of
people in that round
yeah like all of them my imposter
partner literally did nothing
and I still won I think we did that no
in the end I think I was given the win
but I I held up very long until the very
end at some point it got a little bit
too obvious but anyway
I did really well oh did I win in that
round oh okay in another in another
round I did not window
I think then I was like okay okay just
just give me the win for the points
please
yeah yeah I voted
my
my partner out at some point let's see
Patsy
BB Buster
that could thank you for the red super
chat hey boss awesome to see Julio
getting closer to one million views yeah
it reached 800k today guys thank you
could I dedicate a kiss to non-canon
Gannon he's having a rough job hunt and
I want to give him a motivational kiss
or I think I'm about to get a job
rejection myself but kirala taught us
not to give up oh
no job rejection oh no you deserve you
deserve to get like a job that you enjoy
I hope you find something good too
title
[Music]
I'm sure that
you know depending on where you live it
can be very difficult to find a job and
also depending on the field where you're
working in
but yeah I hope both of you find
something that makes you happy I wish
you all the best support
[Music]
um it's harsh out there oh I believe you
hmm
but you know as long as you guys don't
have a job you have more time to watch
me so
um it's a win-win for me
it's a lose for you in the win for me
sorry
it is what it is
um
[Music]
oh wait yeah weren't you donating in a
different currency before yeah yeah yeah
now you're donating in your own currency
nice
I'm good for you welcome
thank you for the pinky yeah let's say
that you're invited to dinner with
Thomas
and she introduces you to another Amy
who comes from a world where massaging
people's eyelids is a normal way to say
are you okay with this Amish Customs or
really try and avoid it
well
today we played a game where we found
different people from different islands
with different cultures and traditions
and customs
who's to say that we cannot
eat each other
each other's traditions and accept and
adjust to one another
maybe that who massages people's eyelids
will acknowledge that this can lead to
Serious eye infections and then to
blindness
if you have bacteria from your dogs
saliva on your very hands
as dogs like to lick
certain things
and then lick their humans
and then this human will have that
saliva all over their hands so you might
not want to
touch people's eyelids too much
I think
that I am pretty reasonable about this
whatever just don't don't
it's on someone's eyelids
so I will I will I will
certainly be able to
reason with the other Ahmed and get her
to understand and accept
that
any other way of greeting each other
would be better
yeah
theme sickle packaging for the red super
chat oh who are you
who are you new chicken
what do chickens grow on eggplants
[Applause]
you're a funny one I never heard that
one before what the [\h__\h]
that's a very intelligent answer thank
you very much
thank you I while I was saying it I was
very surprised about what I was saying
I was thinking wow that actually for
once makes sense I'm so proud of myself
but yeah female thank you for that pun I
will try to remember that one
I hope I can remember that one that's
really good I like that one genius
you're welcome here more often give me
those puns more often
thank you for the rest of the chat
[Music]
um
thank you for the pinky for the rest of
the chat sorry
I must stream non-fiction Holo Holo
hunger Reaper vs sheep do you top of the
world illusionite rise let's end the
world and over 100 other whole life
songs when do I have time to sleep or do
I need sleep do you
say that this does not keep you from
sleeping and doing other things though
you can make a playlist and have it run
on the side it's not like you have to
actively listen to it at all times don't
make it so complicated
did you know that you can just play it
on the side huh
problem solved ah
I am solving all the problems of
everybody today
I might just
solve the hunger crisis
on this world and every other crisis
as I go
wow wow wow
whoa whoa whoa Modern Problems require
Phoenix solutions
Phoenix solution sounds like a company's
name
can you solve my personal problems too
of course what's what is your problem
let me listen and let me solve
can I solve your marriage you have a
marriage
you have a marriage
why didn't I know that I didn't know
that what the [\h__\h]
I should trade my gun maybe I should
you solve my homework no that's if it's
a math homework that's the only thing I
cannot solve I'm sorry
ew don't tell me about your ingrown
toenail what the [\h__\h] I don't know I'm
so sad yeah
[Music]
laughs
[Laughter]
I'm sorry you're surely you surely have
like
um
confidence issues about your ingrown
toenail
well just thinking about it my toenails
curl
uh outside outwards
oh
oh oh
Flash come
to my stream now
and I can say it so you can hear it
why the [\h__\h] does she want to know how
to pronounce this word
I will say it
are you ready
you know
Ina dm'd me out of nowhere
asking me how to pronounce a German word
that was three minutes ago now she's not
answering me
she's doing a members only stream
what
she's ignoring my messages now
why
god dammit
never mind I'll call her
pick up
thank you hello
oh wait wait
hello hello hi hello hello are you
streaming to your members right now yeah
yeah I am here hello Taco Daddy
thanks guys I
was streaming what a coincidence oh it's
a coincidence how's the game you're
playing what the [\h__\h] oh you should play
it it has a lot of puns I was thinking
of you
it's really chill and really nice I
really recommend it why do you need to
know how to pronounce Vash bear
um because I was talking about raccoons
and then talking about how they wash
their food before they eat yeah yeah
and the song was like oh it's called
it's called this in German yeah they
literally there they they're washed
Bears I was like yeah I don't know how
to pronounce this Kiara Lighthouse it's
very similar to the English
pronunciation though wash bear wash bear
wash Bear yeah okay so cute okay
thank you you're welcome I know I
learned like my German knowledge expands
today
yeah and in German we say
no we say you know you know this
I have to say thank you first okay and
then
[Music]
oh my God
secret Ina members only content leaked
on my channel
I never I never like um
I never
what what was I gonna say where was I
going with this
I forgot what I was gonna say literally
while I was saying
ah
yeah
what's with my brain
brain
never called anyone no I don't know I
don't know whatever I want to get this
done uh smiling brand thank you
in Thailand without VPN here's my first
Super Chat in Thai bot Bach or but how
do you say it oh is that your the name
of your currency
there are people I want a super chat for
this occasion but I postpone it such
important support must be sent to the
most special person after all thank you
for so much for everything Kiana
but ah
so it's like a Silent Age we have that
too in German
thank you for thinking of me first it's
an honor thank you soon I appreciate it
and now yeah it's nice you don't have to
use a VPN this is very annoying I I
don't like using VPN because it never
works for the things I wanted to work
for
so nice good for you here's your first
perhaps first room can you see
[Music]
for the support and maybe I forgot to
give aoshi a kiss there you go
squiggly Monster's face with a pinky I'm
sorry fiery chicken boss I've come today
asking for a divorce
divorce from home
and also is Jen my single asking for no
particular reason related to the divorce
who are you married to
when why do you need my my
uh my acceptance
I don't remember getting married to you
which would be the only reason why you
would need my acceptance but I am not
married to you and stay away from them
I honestly don't know but but just by
the fact love how much she works I
cannot imagine her having a relationship
and if she does then it's probably not a
healthy one because she probably doesn't
interact with with them in that case but
um yeah she's married to her work
definitely
I don't know how she would ever have
time for a partner right now ever ever
No no no no no
no no no I don't have time either if I
don't live down then she doesn't have
time
yes yes me and Gemma are married if
anything
uh sorry for ikados thank you for the
pinky oh finally we're employing for the
Thailand friends can get a paycheck of
two years of postponing
and love you cute thank you hey thank
you very much
another one who went straight to kiwawa
to share their finances with me thank
you so much
[Music]
Garden Park
thank you good morning
um
Super Chat it's my first Super Chat I'm
a Korean kfp in high school that makes
non-commissioned officer whenever I had
a hard time I enjoyed training by
wanting you stream and tomorrow I have
nighttime tactical marching if you don't
mind can you cheer for me I wonder what
that nighttime tactical marching looks
like
you just walk around in the nighttime
well there's some more to it
I wonder I wonder
but I already kind of answered this so
fighting
I was carrying a lot of gear oh
it's not fun oh really
well I guess military is not really
supposed to be fun
yeah
it's miserable oh no
oh no
walking for the night with some
challenges like map rainforest and so on
okay that on its own in theory sounds
fun but I'm guessing it's not okay
good luck I wish you the best yeah I
hope it goes well
[Music]
I think but I have another joke
for the pinky we finally have
oh
well but you're standing up
hi bud super jealous girl it will
probably be more than a year until I get
back to home ah you're from Thailand I'm
I didn't know maybe you told me before
but I didn't know
I'm so happy that I won't have to use
VPN to send you super chat anymore when
I'm back in Thailand
oh
finally more is known about unknown
wow someday maybe you have to change
your name to known
oh because then I will be too
knowledgeable
about you
you are now partially enough
if this alone already means that he's
partially known to me then that means
that the full knowledge is not very much
if it just required me to know
I mean I guess it's just one small part
it doesn't mean it's half
halfully known huh okay you're partially
no no
no don't change your name let's find
this way
one percent known probably if anything
still very unknown yeah
slightly no
uh Strat is fine take its monkey in the
rainbow thank you thank you soon
I can't I'm sorry uh sorry I'm so late
to this life has been quite busy the
past few weeks I wanted to say
congratulations on your two years wow
wow that's a late comment
[Laughter]
I can't believe the time has passed so
quickly it's almost unbelievable and
what a year and has been since the last
thinking back honestly I can't imagine
what the lockdowns would have been
without you those were sad times but you
came into our lives become became
someone who let us laugh through the
hard times hard times
[Music]
sorry the light of our darkness and the
spike of inspiration and as you grew
stronger so did K of pink continuously
encouraging one another as much support
we gave you you gave just as much back
to us ask anyone in kfbi I can guarantee
you have many you have you may you many
have had what I guarantee I can
guarantee you you many have had what
their lives improved due to you okay I
get it and as we continue to March
onwards together into the future I'm
exhilarated to witness what more you'll
achieve in the future return to public
talk more music and your original album
to guess a few as life returns closer to
the pre-virus days we might I might need
to witness the future more and more in
bonds no but now I know that I'll always
be supporting you thank you for
everything kiwawa and truly
now regarding your newest song
dear Lord them hip movements those dance
movements the music the singing the
dancing the Envy all came together to
create absolute gold a round of applause
for everyone involved for blessing us
with it Bank locked my card again oh
were you gonna write more oh no Bank
please unlock please do
so mean
well thank you for the rainbow you were
trying to do a double rainbow maybe I
don't know but thank you so much for the
sweet words
ah I will I will and you will hopefully
too treasure and pressure what
was I got what word am I looking for
prish what
[Music]
ah treasure and
huh
I'm thinking of precious probably
appreciate no appreciate it
and appreciate oh God embarrassing I
want to go I wanna go home
[Music]
I was gonna say something nice and I've
ruined it because I can't speak English
uh okay reset nobody nobody heard that
nobody heard that one more one more
reset beep
clap it inside
um
I hope both you and me will treasure and
appreciate the remaining time we both
have before
you have to go back in the
into a job and work and work work work
work work
and watch my Vlogs then
so enjoy it as long as you can
[Music]
what do you mean it sounds rehearse
there was no rehearsal
no no no there was only failure that's
all there is to it
thank you so much engage monkey
s shoes
[Music]
thank you oh
oh
Highway
[Music]
oh no oh root canal procedure sounds
absolutely [\h__\h] terrible
oh [\h__\h]
I want to give you a hug
feel hugged please
I am very scared to ever face something
like that in my life I hope I don't have
to
ah oh
Bob Dylan you have two jobs what the
[\h__\h]
thank you
well I'll read that now because it
sounds like you have to go to sleep do
you have to go to sleep
and okay
[Music]
um
I don't have much time because of my two
jobs but it always makes me very happy
to hear your voice when I can tune in
for a stream thank you for being such a
warm and loving son in our lives
thank you for still watching me after
such a long time
merci beaucoup
come on
thank you so much
and that sounds really rough I hope I
hope at some point you can stop working
two jobs and just go for one job uh it
sounds too stressful
you deserve a more comfortable life I'm
sure
in five years oh dear
you're already calculated everything
that is very depressing but I wish you
all the best
and thank you thank you for always
trying to be here after you shift you
can always come to kiwawa okay or after
or in between or before
[Music]
secrets
no no no no no no
[Music]
I need to really end it now oh my god
let's go faster
um
thank you for the rainbow the department
manager of the company came to my house
and stayed there for two weeks
what
but it was a serious series of painful
days without even watching a broadcast
for two weeks
what
so I'm glad I got promoted to team
manager
what
what and can give you even more Super
Chat your department manager
stayed at your house for two weeks
you got out of it being promoted to team
manager what happened
level one what happened there and number
two why did they stay on your place in
the first place
hahaha
I have so many questions ah
tomorrow's the day I will be freed from
that pain ask me for words of
encouragement and congratulations no I
have too many questions about it
so many question marks above my head
you need to explain yourself more to me
[Laughter]
is it maybe because I don't know
something in their house was broken but
why would they go to your place
don't they have like a family member or
so that they could go to
that sounds so stressful like I mean in
my old job my Superior
um I had one Superior who I really liked
and
um I wouldn't mind her staying over at
my place if she had to but I'm sure she
would have other options you know
maybe you guys are really if they were
really good friends that would explain
why they would stay over but then then I
think ibade would be able to watch My
Stream still
but anyway hmm
that seems like it's Violet's work
policies
I don't think
that
his company cares about that
unfortunately
[Laughter]
ah
well congratulations on being free
tomorrow
again you can watch my streams more
actively I was dispatching another
everybody gave me one room
oh you were both dispatched
and you had to stay together in one room
so
is that it well you said he came to your
house
maybe in your meant hotel or so
okay but that makes a lot more sense
[Laughter]
I hope you don't get too busy don't get
too busy priorities okay koala is
priority
[Music]
the social artist thank you for the
pinky about your previous thumbnails did
you ever clean the saliva and earwax of
the Wind Waker
wait I remember the earwax one but
saliva was I drooling in one of
those are drooling
what happened there
oh oh oh
[Laughter]
no way I threw it away I threw the Wind
Waker away
my voice
thanks for asking
like Richmond activities
um
refresh
okay okay okay
uh
report from the mines oh the project
fell apart so I got terminated from
there so I'm not in the mines anymore oh
no
I will try to get a new job so I can
keep sending these monthly reports
do you use 10 out of 10 happy to your
membership thank you oh that's bad but
you lost your job
oh
no please find a new job soon that makes
you happy maybe not necessarily one of
the minds maybe one that is more chill
and safe I don't know but whatever you
want to do you should be doing
it was a talk to Japs no problem okay
thank god well then it's maybe good
that it ended like this
um it gives you a good reason to find
something new and yeah a new start a
good opportunity
good reason
yeah thank you for your support
Michael LaRosa Daniel Aziz Duncan
and no thank you you cannot take hobo
from me thank you for Pinky you know
what I meant to send super chat for a
while I couldn't send anything since the
anniversary do you with such a good song
I love you dancing so much
paper knot still has my favorite uh all
my favorite elements and heart
challenging will always be special to me
all your songs are amazing and so it's
very hard to pick a favorite I've been
wanting to draw so many things and I've
been busy I'm kind of sick but I always
have your streams to cheer me up love
kiwama She's events
okay if you don't have so much time
anymore to draw that's fine you're still
here and I see you
you're still there for me thank you so
much and
um I'm glad you like people not and
heart Challenger it was on my
underappreciated song so they deserve
some love thank you very very very Macho
muchacho
and uh
and
dakuma I'm hiring you soon you know what
I'm talking about for a little little
something special a little project
so I'm counting on you
hope you feel better until then
sorry
I didn't even know there's a female form
of that I only knew muchacho
um
[Music]
you're not totally low-key
underappreciated notice
is it I think I feel like it will always
be
appreciated it's just you know I have
five songs now and he not only is like
almost two years old so it's
understandable
yeah I think it's doing fine cow carrot
ah what is under appreciated under
appreciated though is the remixes
yeah those are fire
anyway calculate thanks for the pinky hi
Daniel I've been meaning to send a Super
Chat since the anniversary but I just
can't summarize in a few words how much
of a positive impact you have been in my
life so I'm just gonna keep it simple
and say thank you for being you love ya
well Kyle Kerry if you love me so much I
expect another clip donation coming in
soon just kidding
just kidding I mean you know always
welcome but
I see you we're really busy putting
together that Among Us clip collection
which was badly really good
but
um I'm waiting
and thank you so much for all your
support Kyle carrot you know One hand
washes the other
um
the action
you know there's like other Clippers who
have left me but
as long as I
I got you
I'm happy you went and pudding and my
end some other some other Clippers that
I still have left some
espanol and Korean Clippers
my beloved Clippers my Clipper gang
my beloved Clipper gang
thank you so much kfb Clippers yeah I go
Clips me yeah
thank you
they know how to clip Chihuahua well and
respectfully
um
yeah thank you so much for all the love
and call carrot
for putting so much effort into them
now I think I'm done I think I am free
and I need to quickly quickly make
something to eat because I need to
quickly eat uh sleep sorry
oh wait one more oh my cocoon you always
try to get the first and the last Super
Chat don't you you always want to have
the last mention don't you
don't sure
I see I stand
the last laugh now the last word
two days of nawaba uh well really if I
find time I will try to stream on Sunday
and if you are one of the lucky ones who
made it into the meet and greet then
I'll see you tomorrow
yeah
oh oh guys okay I will not read those
thank you though thank you
[Music]
guys I have to go now I'm sorry I would
like to talk more but I'll go
I have to go ah
but what if I
don't think
what if I you know
What if I
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
Mommy
let's try this
[Music]
can't promise anything
thank you
[Music]
someone upon a time is not where I may
alone through fainted lines of words and
Rhymes
don't practice
[Music]
oh that melody was not quite correct
foreign
instrumental
I have no idea what I'm doing here but
here comes my part
by solid Skies
[Music]
foreign
there's like no breathing in the chorus
oh God where does it continue
foreign
[Music]
hey yay
We rise
[Music]
come alive
smile stand beside among the
Stars
that was terrible
oh no
no
voice left for the song today
why oh hello neighbor don't say it like
that
don't say it so clearly yeah a lot of
The Melodies I still don't really know
how to sing because I I only practiced
My Own Parts there was no time there was
literally no time
yeah but I really love good on his part
like she sings it so beautifully
um
she has this really
ah gentle
gentle vibe to it
gives me Goosebumps all right everybody
I'm sorry for um
you know
ripping your ears apart
bye bye
[Music]
foreign