[Music]
[Applause]
this is
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
laughs
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
laughs
[Music]
Christmas
[Applause]
no no no no no no no no no
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
oops
[Laughter]
it's like you saw me naked
you didn't see
me
[Music]
ah you didn't see anything
right you didn't see anything right
now
hi oh my God
no
oh
are you here in the bgm
um
I only have time for like a
or or nothing really that I don't have
time and I'm only I'm allowed to do one
hour stream
so let's try our best you turn 20
20 you can legal drink now
congratulations
[Music]
at least you spend some of that money
not on alcohol but on kiwawa before
spending it all on quinoa on on alcohol
well well
don't put the pressure on me man
uh speaking of pressure
um
so I felt
extremely pressured
because of all the good feedback last
year that's maybe the bad side of doing
so well oh
especially because everybody was so
excited about the Kitty cake
I felt like I had to live up to that but
I knew I couldn't because I knew I was
gonna do do you
and I know the choreo doesn't really
have something like that that stands out
like that
um
but I was just uh you know when I chose
we're getting right into this because I
don't have time
when I chose you know what song to do
for my solo
you know do you is my most recent song
and it's like it has done extremely well
uh so I thought I should go for that one
now just to get this out of the way I
don't want to be negative but I
I am not not happy I'm not happy with
[Music]
yeah I'm not happy
now I tried my best man I put so much
sweat and blood and energy into it
um especially the dance
because I especially because of all that
pressure and I thought you know it's
just once in a
one year maybe chance to perform in
front of such a huge life audience
and yeah that's just so rare and so
special I I I need to make the most of
it you know
[Music]
um
I just feel like
[Music]
um
do you it's an EDM song
and while it was interesting to hear
it like that
in my opinion it did not suit the song
and I thought it would sound different
so that's that it's cool like it's
interesting on its own but it's not what
I wanted for
this once in a year opportunity you know
what I mean it's cool it's cool sure but
it's not what I wanted
song probably you
um
so that's like what I'm feeling
extremely
uh
mixed about and yeah
um
thank you guys though I I did feel a
little bit better after reading you guys
is a sweet feedback about it but I also
talked about it with like members like
Cali and the others
because Cali was uh watching
and yeah the Cali gets me
[Laughter]
they understand and agree so I I don't
know
I don't know man I and then I I listened
back on to do you the original track
like the music video you know what I
upload on YouTube and I was like well I
guess it's like it is called like if you
if you listen to it even though I have
such a hype EDM image of that song
when I listen to it I guess it does not
uh have many instrumentals until the
chorus hits you
until then
it is actually pretty quiet even though
that's not the image I get from it
thank you guys
uh I don't know but so that aside that
aside I did give it my all
for the dancing and
I
um
I I definitely prefer dancing uh
do you in the idol outfit
compared to normal default
because it's just more fun
and where do I have the
sure do I have some screenshots to show
wait let me grab a screenshot
dancing top level thank you you done so
good thank you
[Music]
oh wait let me I was in the middle of
saving some screenshots from you guys
from the hashtag
I love the performance thank you I was
like wondering
[Music]
or or but then the other is like kind of
agreed with me
and I listened back onto that part
afterwards I was like sorry I was I'm
drinking like something with uh that's
carbonated so it's like coming up in my
body anyway so this was do you
I like the visuals they had in the back
uh because you know they're inspired by
the music video
no no no I'm not building them my body
is muting the burps
I'm a sucker for guitar covers well no I
as I said like in on its own I think
it's an interesting version to have but
it's not what I expected or wanted or or
hoped for you know
I wanted to
I I knew I couldn't possibly like
impress as I did last year
that's like I knew that I knew that
already
but
yeah
I just just I'm disappointed in myself
um but it is what it is uh
um I just had I guess higher
expectations
um but
yo my hair was wet after this
but
um somehow the
like this kind of
[Music]
um
kind of set up
I don't know how to explain it activates
sweat buds what's the word in your body
that you never knew you had before
it's greasy ah
the glance glance yeah
like normally
I don't think I ever made experiences
with
um sweating on my head so much that it
would be noticeable ever before until I
started doing this kind of stuff with
hololive with like really hardcore
dances like like this one and then I um
I took off
that's tiny that's exactly that hats
that very hat I took it off and then I
noticed oh
my hair
ew ew disgusting why is my hair like
what like for real I need a shower
immediately
no well when it's really hot and humid I
do sweat all over my body but not on my
head
now
[Music]
um
yeah that's crazy
crazy
it's disgusting but yeah
um I I still think like you know even if
I would have chosen Sparks I feel like
maybe the outcome would have been the
same because Sparks is also an EDM song
but I guess Sparks even like outside of
the chorus has more instrumentals though
Maybe not maybe Sparks would have been
different I don't know it doesn't matter
at this point it's too late what's done
is done it's over
um
look
to bring do you out there because I'm
proud of the song you know I'm really
proud of Doyle
and um I know that the Japanese Bros
who've heard do you really like it too
um
[Music]
well well it is what it is it was fun
dancing like you know there's some moves
where I like let myself fall and it
doesn't look as spectacular as the kitty
kick but
um the the dance choreo has like some
moves where balance is very important
and I do like stumble and Tumble every
now and then with it
um you really need to like let yourself
fall confidently and then immediately
bring yourself back up that is that is
that one move where I to the left I let
myself my upper body just drop down and
then bring it back up with my with my
arm like raise it all the way to the top
it's like a swing Maybe swingy sushi
movement
I don't know if you know what I'm
talking about and then there's a similar
move
uh somewhere else where I also do
something similar
this and that but
thank you guys thank you
so balance
is difficult and I try to
to dance is very energetically but maybe
it didn't really show in the end
I know
the down to up bending yeah
[Music]
what's your favorite move double dude
after the first chorus you know there's
this part where that I I do like a lot
where
um
oh what um
[Music]
How does it go
but I do this dance before I like jump
jump from uh like one side to another
side while opening the hands with each
jump you guys don't know what I'm
talking about do you do you do you do
you
I like that one it's like uh what
happens do you go again
go again
um
[Music]
there's a little break there
you guys
so common your problem I can solve it
yeah that part around there I
I like that
um dance it's very bouncy
um
and but uh damn I need to look back at
though
Archive of the stream again because I
feel like
I washed it once but I feel like it
didn't show you know there's a lot of
like far away angles so you don't see
the dancing a lot of time so well but I
like the far away angles in this case
because uh you can see the audience yay
and they have the pen lights but yeah
another reason why I knew it wasn't
gonna like stay in everyone's mind as
much as you know Tori is because do you
and I knew this and I still did it but
just because I love do you it gives
never me nor the audience any [\h__\h]
time to brief
as a as someone like only if you really
really know the song
then you can like throw in some chance
and this and that but if you've listened
to it once or never
then you will not know how to react to
the song and that's okay that's okay
really I just wanted to get do you out
there give it some more love
foreign
[Music]
well but so
I hope maybe in the future if kiwama
ever does a solo concert
that you know you guys are dedicated you
guys if it was a kiwawa solo concert
then you guys are gonna go all in
um
anyway
[Music]
oh God [\h__\h] we're almost at half an hour
how am I got I wrote down some notes man
um okay okay okay okay
um so I really like dancing it in the
idol outfit though that was the first
one I think I
did not outfit I think it has like you
know
some cool futuristic and fashionable and
and and I don't know mature Vibes to it
but also still uh it's cute with the
ribbons and all that and I chose the
pants version because yes legs and yeah
um if you did you guys know this during
the unit songs everybody got like extra
big transparent ribbons yo yo that look
nice
MC
with uh Louis without gonna say Senpai
no no no no no no no no no no no no
I was very happy to be assigned to do an
MC
um because I immediately saw it as a
chance to do my wave
yeah I asked Lily beforehand if it's
okay that I Implement that and she said
yeah of course no problemo hmm
yeah I had to and oh it looks so
beautiful
man what a huge huge huge big venue and
museums
well you guys knew you guys knew did
when you guys saw that I was emcee did
you guys think
like oh oh is she gonna do it the things
she always does did you guys think that
yeah
yeah because like in like American and
non-american conventions which generally
like I mean they were I'm saying
American because most of the conventions
we did last year were American
conventions but yeah just saying because
I did it at like every freaking
opportunity I have been given so far
hmm
[Music]
I was just generally more excited you
were picked yeah I was so happy too
because you know not everybody gets to
do an emcee
I was very happy to be allowed to do
that and with Louis even
[Music]
um
there's no way she can name around as
fast for them
no no problem it was fun running over
the stage from one side to the other
side during my uh do you performance you
know I was thinking where to implement
something like that and there's just no
[\h__\h] space for it so I did it during
the the calm uh what's the bridge
what do you call that part well I did it
during that time and just like waved and
you know they did the catcher though I
saw the audience doing the ketchup when
I did the ketchup hmm
so that was nice ketchup is like the
kind of uh I don't know otaku move that
you do when there is a calm part of the
song you like reach your hands slowly to
the front
uh I don't know how to describe it but
it's called ketcha
okay okay I have so many things I want
to say though [\h__\h]
um
man I need more uh screen shuttle
oh let's take a little break from the
fashion I want to mention you know this
so this is the uh
it's confusing maybe if you weren't
there because
I kind of got two kfps
at the Expo
it confused me to it in the very
beginning when I was told about this
um
sorry well well the little burps
yeah why are you surprised you should
know by now
so basically this is before you know all
the people entered but
uh this is the hollow life fried Cafe
boof they called it whole life fried
Cafe
um I guess because it would be weird to
call Kiana fried cafe or Phoenix or
whatever but it's obviously a reference
to that but it would be weird because
it's like supposed to be with all of Ian
but
it's you know the whole theme of it is
basically it's like an audio book that
you walk through
um with all the en members
um and and the theme is like everybody's
working at my kfb Cafe
but there's no actual food that you can
eat here not here
um
it's a parody of a parody but true
[Music]
it's good
and then while you walk through
um if you guys go on like the hashtags I
think you'll find stuff like that but
people posted pictures of what you find
because like for example on these tables
where the standees are you would find
for example AME uh did some notes on
like the members like investigation
notes stuff like that and basically
everybody was assigned to do something
to
um
you know adds to the cafe like Easter
eggs yeah and uh I
I wrote I don't know if they were all on
this play but I wrote 10.
10 of these thank you for uploading this
on Twitter
um there are even numbers this is number
ten yeah yeah did where all ten of them
there they they were I only saw five
what There Were Ten and I I I was
thinking really hard on what to write on
them
um is it noticeable that on number 10
the front one on the bottom one
I was trying to cover up something
and that was like [\h__\h] I'm not doing
this again
it wasn't a real time crunch when I
wrote These
yes okay well
um it's
a heart with an arrow going through it
and I wrote kfp is best but basically I
did a lot of like random notes uh one of
them is like German words that you guys
should know
one of them is like kfp lingo
oh one of them is like lyrics one of
them is my original songs
uh listed up
like that
there should be ten I give them 10.
they're all worth displaying
um
and then and then one more thing uh this
I've I have very complicated feelings
about this
um so I gave this to them and I gave
them a note on how to display them
um I I didn't I didn't say put them on
some Long Tall noodles
um I was just like uh I didn't say you
have to a lot elongate them all to make
them as long as they could possibly be
but I guess it looks funny so why the
hell not
yeah they remind me of that Pokemon the
Pokemon what's it called from the new
game
they stand out oh well I I hope so
I hope so but at the same time I'm
really embarrassed about this like
somehow something about this I realized
after now having this being looked at by
thousands of people
it's just very intimate and it's like
people looking at this really intimate
thing that I did when I was sick and
like I touched all of this and like I
spent hours with this and I I my cat's
hairs are on this the fur is on this and
even other members hands were inside of
these many hands were inside of these
I don't know it's just embarrassing it's
kind of embarrassing to have this out
there
can't go back now uh
not gonna dance
and damn their their mouths are so wide
open what's going on except mine what I
think they go like this by default
though so that's like the problem but I
had them fixing on his head so that the
neck wouldn't be broken by default
um Somebody went in to fix it then
uh
oh man
but I think it's a very interesting art
submission right it's actually cool I
saw some really interesting ones
apparently uh hachama made a chair
[Music]
uh but then there's also really nice
ones like
um uh I miss terrarium really sweet I
love that she did that she did that
while in Japan man she made it in Japan
full astral chair I mean I don't know if
you would call it an actual chair
sit on it it would fall apart from what
I've seen
especially if I would sit on it if you
know what I mean
um
but yeah it's beautiful all of the art
is beautiful and this is mine and I I am
I am so sorry for bringing something so
cursed
but hey it's uh it's a group picture of
all of whole life English isn't that
beautiful
and uh man
I wish I could
like see people's reactions or like hear
what they say what they think in their
minds while walking past this
I really want to know
I really want to know especially what
non-k of people
think about while walking past this
piece of art
according to
[Music]
and by the way
this there's like a sign right I wrote
this while I was streaming so you guys
know kind of what I wrote I think and
I'm sorry it's not in English but the
fact is that
I
I wasn't told to ride I was told either
English or Japanese but I thought well
if it's gonna be like translated to
Japanese anyway might as well write it
in Japanese in my own words right it
turns out same as my my message
um that I'm using as this thumbnail when
you write something in Japanese they are
not gonna bother to translate it to
English back
so it will just be only Japanese it was
funny because apparently
um Anya and me are the only overseas
like non-japanese members who's like
really emotional motivational uh concert
message on the website uh has no English
version or and only Japanese like
people are making jokes about that how
we must be from Whole Life Japan because
our messages are just Japanese but no
that's just because I knew it was going
to be translated to from English to
Japanese anyway if I submitted in
English so I'm just gonna submit it in
Japanese I didn't know they would like
show both if I had both
so and this yeah the same thing happened
the same thing basically happened here
with the sock puppet message as well I'm
sorry but is this just you know well you
know the story behind these sock puppets
so don't worry about it
ah and then oh another thing I found
this on motion motion posted this
what exactly was where could you get
this I don't even know anymore
this is uh this is not a coaster this is
a shikishi I think
foreign
can tell us
where did you get this from
girl let's just posted it eh yeah I know
I got it from your Twitter
but like where where Expo merch gotcha
gotcha merch you had to be lucky to get
this and you actually got lucky
oh did you exchange with someone else
it's available online but only Is Random
foreign
Exchange
Freight Up is real she was lucky
the [\h__\h]
but yeah I wrote this message another
year another Expo thank you for
supporting me and finding me here I
wrote that because I I thought you know
whoever sees this
will be a lucky bastard
I hope you have a great time and make
big memories
I think he made big memories so that's
pretty accurate how the [\h__\h] did I know
yeah and then another thing you could
find was this
uh it's uh like a if this isn't the size
of a business card it comes with
oh I need a picture
it comes with my my chicken poof set
oh let me see let me see let me see let
me see let me see
any good picture of my
of my poof this are all on the hashtag
there's all Festival
pictures where are the man
pictures
[Music]
I'll take this one
yeah but it doesn't show the chicken
this one doesn't show the chicken inside
out of time
[Music]
I already saw some but I was picky I was
like I'm gonna find a better picture
than this one and then then I didn't
find I hear this one it doesn't show the
picture but whatever
so
[Music]
done
hey
[Music]
even brought my uh my small plushie
basically so this is the second Cafe
that I'm talking about but I mean
uh
besides that like in a whole lot of
English experience booth
add the actual food court I don't know
if you can call it a food card
um one of the choices
I was one of the honored members to have
their own very own solo food merchandise
which I am just extremely like happy
about and but it's also like
that's how it's supposed to be
[Music]
in this position of a food themed theme
yes design and then not use it
so finally uh justice has been served
and they actually put effort into it I'm
so happy like they asked me in the very
beginning you know when this came up
they asked me Kiwa we're gonna make
Carefree Fried Chicken uh do you want to
be involved in it and I said uh [\h__\h] yes
so they let me
um look over the design or I could
choose they gave me different designs
for the box and I chose it and I could
give more input if I wanted to but I was
happy with this box and like the card
and everything and and they let me taste
the test yes the fried chicken and told
me to give them feedback if I want to
change anything but the chicken was
honestly delicious so I didn't know what
to change I was like I I it was like uh
I think I told you already when that was
but when that happened you know I I came
to the studio
and I literally just came to the studio
for taste testing Fried Chicken
pretty late at night
so I go there and I'm like oh hello I'm
kiwawa I have arrived to taste some
chicken
and then they brought it
and I ate it and my job there was done
but I was like you know I felt kind of
weird about it because
you know
I'm literally taste testing there and
deciding what thousands of people are
going to get to eat
and what will represent
kfp
but I'm not a professional taste tester
how how can I really judge this I
hmm I should be saying like some really
valid professional sounding criticism
and then feedback when I eat this but
all I came up with was hmm
it's very uh tasty juicy uh the meat is
Juicy the outside is uh crispy
oh very good yummy
thank you
wow that was 100 worth getting
Chihuahua's input on wasn't it
[Music]
so please put in Grace paper because I
knew you guys would want to keep the Box
unfortunately and that wasn't able to be
accommodated
so maybe it was the illusion of a choice
but um I definitely felt like I had a
lot of input in this process and
um I think you guys even without the
grease paper I think you guys can still
keep the Box
[Music]
potatoes which I did not taste test so
I'm sorry if they were bad but uh this
was definitely a meal that would fill
you up decently I would say
they all had like three pieces of fried
chicken bone bony fried chicken and with
a little serving of uh potatoes I mean
it would totally fill me up I don't know
about you guys but it would fill me up
even with some tomato ketchup hmm
Chris helps us remember our fallen
friends so true so true but yeah I
honestly think like if you just wipe it
a little bit it should be fine
like I don't think it's gonna mold
if you get rid of like crumbs and all
that it's gonna be fine because
[Laughter]
uh 15 minutes left oh [\h__\h] well I was
just saying in Japanese that you know
apparently a lot of people threw the way
too which is fine like I'm not gonna
force you to take it home and like I
totally understand if you weren't
interested that much in me to bring back
home a greasy box of paper but there's
so many people out there who couldn't go
to the event so maybe you can take one
home nonetheless and then maybe give it
to a friend who likes me more than you
do if you have one who likes me you know
just in case maybe in the future you get
to know someone who becomes kfp and then
you're like hey I have something for you
that you couldn't get yourself but you
know yeah I see you guys I see you all
want this is
hmm
so um yeah so that was uh that was
really cool like having my own food and
being able to give feedback and be
involved in it so I want to say big big
thank you I don't know why I was blessed
with so much like you know
blessedness you know oh yeah the card
came with this uh it says
so this is
[Music]
to raise these little chickens cute
chickens
um so thank you for eating them in a
delicious way and enjoying them and
please tell me your feelings about it
under the hashtag kfp you know I'm even
like advertising the kfp hashtag here
damn a lot of people did tell me their
feelings about it on Twitter so I
replied to uh pretty much every single
one of them who used the hashtag and
uploaded the picture with even Japanese
or English I just said
like a really professional
thank you for coming to the store today
or thank you for coming for visiting kfp
today thank you for consuming kfv today
seeing people like actually enjoy the
food like apparently and I know this
because I tasted the test taste isn't it
which is actually good I was worried
that maybe my taste buds you know are
very different so maybe you guys
wouldn't enjoy it as much but apparently
it was very enjoyable so yeah
photo
[Music]
buckets for next year oh I'm gonna make
them bigger
from a box to a bucket now honestly I do
feel like for me personally kfp is more
about Burgers than about Fried Chicken
to be very honest so
I would be happy with a burger actually
a burger
yeah why are you guys surprised
why are you guys surprised I'm not all
that hot and excited about Fried Chicken
I prefer burgers
as you should know
but you know my favorite is a chicken
burger I love the crispy chicken from
Burger King
got it
I'm still talking about looking Burger
come on
were we not on the same page guys
what about that page up there
by the way I took like they gave me like
so many of these they told me to write
10 and they gave me so many in case I
make like mistakes so actually
I took the rest I didn't give it back so
I have a lot of these empty pages now
because they're cute because they're
like designed after you know what waiter
Rachel says and waiters right on when I
work in a restaurant so that's really
cute yeah
the fried in kfb yeah what you can have
a fried chicken burger oh also and it's
just kind of like it happened but that
doesn't mean that we have to copy
everything that KFC does you know
what about chicken nuggets I [\h__\h]
love chicken nuggets let's do chicken
nuggets burger or chicken nuggets yeah
what about the bucket icon it doesn't
exist anymore
it's not even in the icons anymore we
already established that
oh you guys are like shook heads
hmm
[Music]
you knew this all along don't act like
this now you knew this was gonna happen
this is this is just how it is
uh anyway
uh what else
oh so look at this
kiwawa not only an idol outfit but also
in
t-shirts
[Music]
so I
I know it's just a t-shirt but I was
really looking forward to wearing this
t-shirt because I when I go to I know
concerts
uh at the end of the concert like they
would change out of their Idol outfits
and they would like use the T-shirt the
merchandise t-shirt they have for that
concert and I guess I mean it's not just
an Idol concert thing but that's just
how I I see it all the time and
ah I don't know so that was really
exciting because it's just so so ah real
and and did you are argue for color
balance this year I wanted to talk about
exactly that so remember last year when
I don't know which day it was but on one
specific day
had all white t-shirts except for akiroz
assembly
she was the only one
with a black T-shirt the rest was all
white and she was on the top left of the
stage I remember and it just stood out a
lot and I mean in the end good for her
right because then everybody was talking
about her and could not keep their eyes
off of her but
I guess I have OCD because I did not
enjoy the imbalance of this so I was
like if this happens next year and if I
got to wear one I will
go out of my way to choose the unpopular
choice
because I want this to be balanced I
don't want this to happen again and then
we were asked Yo which color do you want
um
white or black and I didn't know I
didn't see what the Japanese members
would go for but I did see what the
English members were going for and to be
honest from the get-go it was already
balanced like you know members were
choosing white and black which is pretty
equally so I was like I guess I don't
need to but I was one of the first who
voted so I already went for black
assuming that everybody else would
mostly go for white
because just because
I assumed I went for black and then I
voted and that could have still changed
it but I was like you know what I like I
like um having matching black T-shirt
with some of the others who chose black
so let's [\h__\h] go I'll just keep this
look at that um black works well with
the with the yeah not allow outfit
anyway so what the hell I mean white
looks good too in my opinion but you
know
um oh my God I'm getting exhausted from
trying to squeeze as much but talk as
possible in this short amount of time
man oh
oof
is
[Music]
um
so that was around the end for the big
uh bright parade I actually want to sing
this in this stream so um we're still
got things to do
um yeah and then before that so
basically why I told you guys that this
time will be way more worth it than last
year is because last year I only had one
song right this year it was my solo song
and a unit song and
true
right two big uh group songs the one in
the beginning and the one in the end
that is what one two three four
and then let me see and
any guys
five five times to see me in this
concert and honestly that's like it
couldn't be any more than that because
then it would just be unfair I we were
all equal this time we were all equal
and that means a lot to me as an En
member
to be treated as an equal and to be
given the same amount of like Showtime
roughly hmm
[Music]
I did notice that uh you know in the
first
song
a little bit uh low
do you know what I'm talking about
[Music]
it's okay that's fine
um
it's fun
I'm just so happy that we were involved
so much and that's why I really wanted
you guys to see it yeah and and so
to tell you half of the things that I
wanted to talk about
um so so so so sukijan the song that I
chose
oh yes I chose I guess but it's not like
I chose it's more like
um you know group was decided and then
we were asked so what do you girls want
to sing and everybody could like
anonymously
um on their own give suggestions and I
don't know what the others suggested but
I can definitely imagine that they may
have not suggested anything at all
and I think I suggested like three
different Hello project songs
and one of them was um Smiley just
sukichan smiling is one of my favorite
Idol groups from back in the day they
don't exist anymore I mean they kind of
do but not really they change name and
they change members they added the [\h__\h]
on the members when all the other OG
members are gone by now so it's not the
same group anymore they might still like
perform old songs from back in the day
but you know it's not the same group
anymore but they were called smile
Legend was under their greatest songs
ever that was always so [\h__\h] hype in
concerts because they have uh like
really high fun chance uh calls that the
members do like during the time
part right that was that part right
where we were like Whispering
normally uh and Helen project concerts
the crowd would go like you know there's
just four members right and you repeat
it five times so first you go like for
example
okay
[Applause]
so you know there's like so much going
on there
um not only this part but like you know
during the course as well forever
[Music]
so there's so many parts to like throw
in the calls and I was hoping that maybe
we could like put the chance on the
screen so that I know that so many
people would know the song So for them
that they could maybe follow along by
looking at the screen but I asked for it
and they didn't do it so I guess that's
okay but
um no chance okay okay fine I know this
is fine with my dreams they were
chanting um everything in my dreams in
my hopes and in my dreams in my
imagination the chance were actually
happening I'm just so happy that we were
able to do this together
um and and and ah because it's perfect
it's a four member song and you know I I
just said we have to do this hi this is
so fun we gotta do this one and and oh
yeah dance break cool right yeah um
thank you for letting me do that because
originally I think that part they sent
me like
listen us like choreo uh that we were
gonna learn and then they were like okay
how is this and nobody gave a comment
except for me I was like I think during
this part we should do something more
exciting and because I think originally
maybe it was just like waving the whole
time just waving for like 20 seconds
just waving I was like
anyway
[Music]
I guess I have tangents for next time
then I do want to sing
um our bright parade
it's okay it's it's gonna go like two
minutes over so that would be fine
um
[Music]
because I love the song I love it so
much man do you guys like our new like
big big fun song
hope you like it
you don't hear it
it doesn't go for that audio
let me check
da da da
die
[Music]
okay let's see can I sing this alone
oh
[Music]
foreign
cut it
[Music]
off
butterfly
mother
has a classical
[Music]
studies
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I bet you met honey
[Music]
so much it's so difficult to sing but I
love it so much thank you guys I'll see
you guys soon
[Music]
thank you guys so much for the support
I'll be reading super chat soon and
thank you guys for watching the concert
tomorrow is day two I'll also be uh in
the in the Holo 27 uh concert as well
and if you're gonna check that out
um that would be nice that would be fun
too but yeah it's okay yeah I know the
tickets are expensive so don't force
yourself
um I'm just like I would just say you
know day one was definitely worth it
um thank you so much I also saw you know
kfb in the audience thank you so much
for like you know for presenting can't
be so proudly even though I know we're
small in Japan and yet you are like
making me so proud there and I'm so
happy to have you guys thank you for for
supporting me no matter what and and and
thank you for putting up with my [\h__\h]
and I will continue doing my best and oh
it was finally announced for realzo's
the date for the concert of whole life
English first ever concert in LA in the
YouTube theater on July 2nd and
um
I hope you guys uh can make it I hope
kfp can make it and I hope that you know
we can make that into our own very
special stage to shine
um but yeah for now let's enjoy this and
thank you so much I love you guys I wish
I had more time it's not part of ax no
it's his own uh a lone standing thing
um but yeah maybe some of you guys can
make it would be nice ticket sales are
not starting yet they're starting
eventually even if you don't get a
ticket to be there at the venue uh you
will be able to watch it um you know as
you can all our all our other concerts
online too so don't worry about it yeah
and now I have to go otherwise I get the
the chancla la chancla
bunk stick in my head I don't want that
so bye bye
enjoying myself videos and I love you
guys I love you guys I really want to
talk more of you guys soon TM
I will end it without an ending because
we gotta end it bye bye
I'm gonna go through all the hashtags
[Music]