[Music]
foreign
oh God where's all my stuff there we go
yay oh hi Alfie everybody hi
I need a bgm there no this is a scary
bgm
probably should have planned that before
screen
so cute
yeah and then I put
and then I put Kiowa in the center
because uh I thought it would be cute uh
like that were all like the same height
like this
oh yeah I found out recently
how tall are you 165
one I'm also
165 as well well you two are I think one
centimeter taller than me
I thought that we were all the same okay
okay I was told that we are the same
height so
[Music]
I might be wrong
double audio they're saying or one
person said so
put one for double oh is there double
audio
only one person said so it might be
wrong oh what happens at 165. really
lunch oh oh okay okay then um
then I will I will rate I will put you
back I'm awesome
congrats congratulations why do they
know and I don't know
it's okay I asked people to check how
tall I am fairly frequently because I
don't know what it is in centimeters
because in in America we don't use
centimeters
so we really are the same size
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
how tall are the how tall are the KP I
was scuffed why is my audio scrubbed I'm
with utano then on both of our audio
should be left
it's when you try to talk at the same
time yeah kiwawa is at uh um Pandora's
place at the moment
and then I'm so
[Music]
sorry the Pandora's Box
I'm sorry this is
box I'm lost in it help me
I would
come save you but it sounds like I
honestly wish I was there
yeah it's a nice boxing it's a really
pretty box it's a messy box it's a nice
box than the box that I stayed in when I
lived in Japan last time oh really
yeah
I wish I lived in a place like this it's
pretty nice it's quite big it's a lot of
money
the floors are so pretty
we cleaned them clean them just for you
clean them laughs yeah oh I wish I've
never been to Japan even
[Music]
um
yes hi everybody oh hi Alfie welcome in
uh we are uh if you guys
um well if you guys aren't familiar we
the three of us we are huge fans of
Idols specifically hello projects so
we're going to be talking about hello
project today and
um I think I think I am the biggest fan
uh probably maybe I don't know
because I think I'm a bigger fan on you
I was about to say probably definitely
because like uh because like uh I I was
so nervous because like for me like I
just like I watch the lives and I like
will SOB over like like oh this is the
last moment but I don't I never was
exposed to a lot of it so even today I'm
going to be learning a lot from the both
of you because like yeah
yeah because I never had the resources
to know
yes please teach me
um
is a is a start and it will never end oh
wow Phoenix
oh
there you go or like okay I don't think
uh I think of it wasn't quite done sorry
for interrupting oh no no you're fine
you're fine that's how I talk because I
I always like I have a bad habit of
interrupting because that's just how I
talk to people but uh yeah right it's
like my bro it's the it's the tangent
brain is what I call it
um
yeah okay the thing is reading it I I
felt it felt like it was me who was
actually saying it I it just like felt
relatable especially every time I was
just like I should stop anyway I should
stop it felt like me anyway
okay I need to get back to this I
promise I'll get back to this in just a
second but I need to finish what I'm
saying it was it's so it was just too it
felt too real but
um uh the three little power projects
power projects PowerPoints
[Music]
uh what is it uh she said she says um
Buttercup and Blossom but they just
don't believe me they'll treat me like a
baby oh I'll show them um
this is the this is the iconic line that
she says yeah
she said she like uh uh and then she
goes I'm hard core
and I think that's the one that everyone
that like for the most part but it's a
it's a good classic television show it's
definitely really enjoyable that I
highly recommend
back in the day but I don't even
remember what they sounded like oh yeah
so I couldn't touch
that's fair that's fair but uh but
anyway
should I say what we're doing should I
say it no I was trying to but then I
can't get distracted I get distracted so
easily no I'm not gonna I was gonna go
on a story but anyway we have the three
of us all have a PowerPoint and uh we
all have designated groups are going to
go in the order of Pandora and uh then
kiwawa and then me and
um we're gonna talk about our like
little favorites uh of the group give
you some history I'm going to be
learning from them
as much as you guys are going to be
learning things and uh so and uh so just
so you know there is a test after this
so if you don't pay attention then uh I
don't know how to help you sorry darling
um
but uh do you I mean not that we really
not that we really need to but do you
guys want to introduce yourselves to to
the group
yes yes yes so let's start uh going from
Pandora over to me so Pandora you go
first
um hello
[Music]
but I mainly stream on Twitch nowadays
but maybe one day I'll come back to
YouTube you know the motherland it feels
better
it looks nicer
um
also also we can I can if you if you
stream on on YouTube I can raid you so
that's also a fun little fun
[Music]
I like to make covers and I've like tell
the project since Maybe
20 no no
maybe like when when I was 12 I started
to like them so
much
I think she's no she's trying to she was
looking at me telling me this I think
she's trying to get a certain dominance
okay how many concerts have you been no
no how many classes have you been doing
I'm waiting for the fight fight fight
let's be the ref
[Music]
[Laughter]
we would be on a similar level yeah yeah
it's just like
um
I'm not I was never like that much into
momusu but I would go to a lot of Hello
project concerts that have like all the
groups performing so you know I know
almost her like songs and members as
well but yeah anyway sorry were you done
laughs
yeah what were you done wait were you
done ready yeah yeah
there was no clear indication that you
were done oh okay
um
there we go okay
let's go
indeed uh Echo said that they've only
been to four hell project concerts but
that's better than nothing yo there's so
many here they have no idea what the
[\h__\h] we've been talking about that's
better than me I haven't even been to
one so fake
fans
[Laughter]
it's okay it's okay okay I'm just so I'm
starting to like really feel this need
to assert my dominance as well hello
private fans but there's no need to do
that right there's no need I need to
chill I need to chill I'm ready and um
oh sorry you can go outside oh a candy
pose unfortunately
I'm takanasikiara from home love English
uh myth this is my
is it my is it my first collab with like
non-holos
no because you did uh you did the
promotory
oh well okay um with that I kind of like
you know I guess I mean more like this
is my first collab with like so like
Indies and like smaller pots
[Music]
yeah so it's um
it's um kind of uh interesting fresh
experience
yeah I'm not counting those chat
I'm not counting those it doesn't count
it doesn't count it doesn't count in
this moment
yeah yeah yeah yeah so
um today I will be sharing um actually
this thing that we're doing today I
wanted to do it before with um someone
in whole life but the reason we didn't
do it is because
it would have been a little bit
complicated I would have had to get
um permission for every like slide every
information on this line and all that so
I was like nah it's like kind of killing
my motivation so uh eventually
when I heard you guys all like kind of a
project I was like wow yeah
and all them yeah I don't have to worry
about being bonked so yes you don't
that's why yeah thank you for for
thinking of us and like uh but let's
hang out with you um
it's rare nowadays to find hello project
fans yeah the kind of like dwindling I
think I think nowadays like the the
interest is Shifting elsewhere like in
terms of you know when finding like Idol
groups online yeah well people a lot of
people into Kpop as well you know dances
and stuff yeah and like a lot of the
J-pop groups I like they sort of you
know um during The Panini sort of like
didn't do as much I guess
the food actually I was also thinking
the food
do you always reference
well because I was trying to get you to
t-pose
another r
it's because there's no pictures of the
whole arm they're all doing like oh like
a wave
so okay so I'm doing my best yeah
oh yeah also I'll be introducing Betty's
Coco today my favorite Idol group the
best style group no okay I will not
actually claim that this is the best
Idol group even though I'm [\h__\h]
biased I think I think it's um like I
think it shows like how much you love
them if you don't if you don't think
that it's the best like uh at what it is
like this for me it was the best for me
yeah but in general
like more objective point of view when I
say they're the best album group
um I'm not sure I don't know I'm not
sure about that yeah there's a lot of
things that look really unique about
them and that made them really like
stand out in comparison since like all
their voices were unique like they they
stood out against each other and they
all had their own sort of style and
trying to yeah the arm is like behind
you
oh
it's a power move it's a power stance
that's what I was trying to achieve
I mean you can go in the corner of the
room and keep those teeples if you want
or like no I have to be in the corner of
the teeples like that no it's okay
that's okay this is the only way I can
get it to work
uh yes introduce yourself yes hello
everybody I'm Ophelia midnight of V
referee's gen 1 Catalyst I'm the yantare
yandere Phantom of this gen you can call
me Opie you can call me Ophelia uh some
people call me on their son and uh
yeah or a lot of people call me Mommy
but no matter what you choose to call me
I will always take care of you my
darlings welcome to my channel I hope
that all of you have a ton of fun
um as I've already stated I uh I I'm I'm
gonna be learning a lot uh today as well
I I am a hello project fan but um I
didn't so I mostly was into buono which
is uh a group that is comprised of
members from other groups of hello
project and
um I didn't learn about
um like berries cute and
um and like morning Movement Like until
I was until I was like probably in
acting school I wasn't exposed to a lot
of like Idol culture or anything I
actually I wanted to be but I thought it
was only available in Japan I didn't
realize that there were like Idols like
Western idols
yeah yeah
um
and so like uh what's it called I I
wasn't exposed to a lot of it and
um I didn't know there were like Western
Idols or anything and then that's how I
ended up actually jumping into more
Broadway things because I wanted to sing
and dance but the only way that it was
available to me was through show choir
or doing Broadway so I tried so I I did
a lot of
um stuff uh to go more into that
um I went down that route and then when
I actually got to acting school to study
to be on Broadway I learned that there
were Western idols and things like that
so I'm excited to learn from you both
and uh just generally I'm very excited
that you both are here and want to spend
time with me I've been like so people
like I've been so like uh like like
bashful about it I'm not so like I'm not
normally like this but I've been like
I'm just happy that they want to spend
time with me I could they could have
told me like can you fly to Japan and
like help us dig up rocks like would
have said yes like I was just happy to
hang out and spend time with you both so
uh just in general thank you for
allowing me to be part of this with you
both
so yeah
yeah welcome
yeah well
um
[Music]
wonderful weekend fangirl battle project
today to give us yeah I'm excited I'm
excited
but uh what's it called so Pandora would
you like to wait hold on I just realized
that you're the uh
um my head might walk a few things
um I was about to say I'm going to I'm
going to reorganize this I didn't think
about it when I did it yeah yeah so let
me
know
wait maybe that's too tiny and then
maybe we need a like um also like kind
of a general explanation
um hello project you know we're talking
to a lot of people who don't know what
even hell project is
a whole project yes Idol agency kind of
yeah that is an umbrella kind of for a
lot of idol groups and morning morning
Muslim was their first enter still their
biggest
um group that they have but after a
morning musliment I added
um like kind of like trainees and out of
the trainees they made more grooves like
with his Global and cute and so on and
after that they made even more groups
and then they made subunits and so on so
yeah they trained a lot of idle groups
with different concepts and so on and
that's that's what hello project is so
morning Muslim the most important one
yes starting out with that one
okie dokie well let's go I'm gonna tell
you about the sort of like
I mean in some respects it's the
flagship
um because like they're the ones that
started it um they're the reason hella
project exists
um but they've had a hard journey you
know and it's it's a 25 year 26 years
almost I think 26 years Journey you know
what they are now so I'm going to tell
you about the Eternal Idol group morning
cement let's go okay next slide
next song wow so everything sort of
started in
1997. so they were five runners-up from
an audition where sunka was looking for
like um their producer some good I was
looking for a female singer for his
group
[Music]
um and they they are cute they were yeah
they were challenged with selling 50 000
of an indie single
um
which basically means it just has one
main track yeah
um they did it in four days and the five
girls became the first generation
um I won't say like all the members
names because but they're on the side so
you can read them now
um and might be in different places on
the screen so
um please watch out
um the group along with the winner who
was like also a soul like it's more of a
Solace than like a Singapore the singers
band
um they formed a fan club called hello
which sort of turned into the the whole
family's name you know hello project uh
but
um you know they did their debut single
morning coffee in 1998 but then they
held and a little audition for the
second generation soon after
um and then the second gem were added
um but then
um they started like I think for the
fourth single
um a member graduated
and
um then they decided okay well we're
gonna hold
um auditions for a third generation and
this this era like every every era of
morning with me is very different but
this one is just sort of like just the
beginning era so they were like
I know when I look at these pictures
it's very fitting for the time maybe but
um
I I like to think of this as like the
filter error there was a very like light
filter on them and
um they look really powerful though like
I love the Glamor Shots
lots of red lipstick but um there there
was um in total there was uh eight
members
um but then after one of the first
generation left that's when like they uh
soon after they were like okay we need a
third generation and
um
uh that's when things got amazing oh
next slide please
okay oh I love these outfits you
yeah yeah this is called the Golden Era
so this is from 2000 to 2004. so they
started to have a project started to
grow and add new groups and soloists and
even members from Hawaii
um like they had a vital
um Muslim country Muslim and they had
the Hawaii one called coconuts
also joined you know this was a big era
for um uh uh hella project they also
formed teleport egg like in 2004 so
um also during this era many of the
morning was my members graduated but
stayed within hello projects so they
became like soloists or they joined
subgroups or they form new groups
entirely
um
so the law changed a lot changed during
this time
um and they started using like member
colors as well
um and in 1999 they added a third gen
and they got their first million selling
song I think they only had four that
reached a million but
um
they're most known for the song Love
Machine yeah
so we'll do like they're keeping up the
Rhythm and and they added a fourth gen
in 2000 and then a fifth gen in 2001 and
a sixth generation in 2002 only the end
the 2002
um but this also the Sixth Gen is very
interesting because they also added
um Fujimoto Mickey who was already a
soloist in Hell project but they added
her into morning Muslim which was the
first time that sort of thing happened
um and this era is called the Golden Era
because of pretty much these outfits uh
the point is at the wrong bit but it's
okay
um oh because you were talking about
sixth generation so it was pointing it
there
[Music]
Arrow I made oh the arrow you made
okay don't look at this one this the one
that I'm using
um
um people think like a lot of critics
say this is the best error but
um for me it's a different era but um
well this is when when they had a lot of
members they split into two groups
ultimagumi and sakuragumi and each of
the groups had
two singles and had tools
um so they at one point they were so big
I think they had like 15 members
um they were like okay we need to we
need to do we need to split up and kick
some girls out they
um well I had holes with the smaller
group so there was so much going on
during this era so many subgroups as
well literally one single subgroups like
death Diva not Yuri natsumi or like you
know stuff that didn't last that long
but um they did a lot they did a lot at
this time
um but then things changed after
2004. oh [\h__\h] what happened
tell us well next slide at the edge of
myself
like
but
um someone called it the Twilight era so
I never heard of that naming yeah it's
not on the official one but someone on
YouTube called it the Twilight era and I
was like okay I'll just put Twilight
error question mark so this is important
because from 2004 2007 um the hell up
for kids debuted into two groups during
this time and had subgroups of their own
and also small groups started from the
Heller Pro eggs but they weren't really
that big or they got transferred to like
nice girl project which is Sunco the
produces other stuff
um and then they also hold held a an
audition
um for the seventh gem but nobody passed
um which was the first time that
happened and then in 2005 again and
finally someone passed only one person
um she's
amazing
I'll just say because I think this this
will make people familiar with uh
she's the one that's saying
the one that also uh me and gura
performed in her birthday yeah
yes so she she um she was uh voicing a
character in an anime
um but also singing the the character
was an idol as well and she was singing
the characters songs and the openings
and the endings and that also had
subunits and everything so it's a whole
she had quite a successful solo because
she did yeah
especially that's my favorite something
what was that pumpkin
yeah
and the one with the star what was that
oh
yeah I I own a lot but the tambourine's
like one of my favorites because it's
Unique
[Music]
um but yeah in 2006 another generation
was added that but this one again was
only one member
um
the interesting thing about this gen is
it was this is only part one of the
eighth generation they added more later
on
um oh that was weird I forgot that did
you forget yeah
oh you'll find out in the next slide
so 2007 most special group celebrated
their 10th anniversary
um even though it's not the best selling
era many fans think it is the best yes I
agree possibly yeah because I think the
the the genres of their songs was really
like special yeah and the lyrics were
good yes dancing was great
good balance of members yeah I was about
to say this is probably the era that I
am most familiar with when it comes to
yeah
there are a lot of people yeah
I feel like it's probably really biased
like everyone who says this is my best
error and this is my best error because
it's probably just like where you were
like kind of like where you got into it
for most people yeah like because that's
the era when I got into it too so that's
why I think that's the best ERA like I
couldn't really a little bit before yeah
I think you're maybe a little bit of an
exception but this is
the best ERA yeah yeah so this
is an interesting error because they
didn't change usually they held an uh
graduation or added members every single
year but
um from
2007 to 2009 they didn't have any
graduations well mid-2007 to late 2009.
it was so stable yeah it was very stable
this thing is a nine piece for a while
you felt that really yeah I think that's
also why a lot of people might think
that this is the best ERA as well
because of that yeah yeah you guys and
you get used to it you're like this is
it now you can't like get used to it if
you're planning new members and getting
rid of them yeah exactly but um
sorry let's let the lady talk
um yeah
yes they didn't change so yeah it was
stable and people got used to the image
of it they also didn't change their look
much like they all pretty much stayed
similar similar hair colors similar you
know Styles so it wasn't too different
maybe you know a bit short but I'd say
they pretty much stayed the same like um
so
um they also performed it wasn't their
first time for me abroad but they
performed an Anime Expo in America and
they also performed in Paris for an
expert too
um
so basically in 2007
linlin the girl on the right was a
helipro egg which is the trainee thing
back in the day
um
she was already sort of like doing stuff
with haloper eggs as a dancer but she
wasn't named she wasn't actually named
she wasn't on the website at all she's
just appearing at concerts and then but
who introduced to her and was like yeah
become a trainee and then Funko went to
China and um he uh did some sort of like
auditions with Runners up from a Chinese
singing competition and he found jinjin
um they were given the nicknames junjun
linlin
um based on their real names and uh they
uh make up the second part of the eighth
Generation
Um they didn't stay in the group that
long like it was only three years it's
so sad because they're both really um
but um you know I really liked them I
have a lot of Ginger much
um so oh yeah I think you told me yeah
uh
um uh yeah so this was this is my
favorite era but they also they didn't
hold an audition for four years pretty
much the last audition was like late
2006.
um like official audition can I say
something this era with them adding two
Chinese members made me feel so hopeful
because that was the first time when
they added like foreigners basically
other than coconuts yeah yeah but this
like really felt like it oh oh they're
like serious now they really considered
foreigners so I was like maybe I can
join too they did auditions in countries
like Korea and stuff but they didn't do
much with them like there was also ice
cream with some man and all that like a
lot going on in Asia in 2009 and 10 but
it didn't last very long unfortunately
but they put them in the main group yeah
yeah that's true
it made me hopeful too I was like oh
goodness yeah but I do
um I think I read or heard something
about
um
um kind of like looking back on their
experience and like not really being
very happy with it
yeah I'd love to have them you know
doing more songs and songs and stuff
because they were very they had very
unique voices but I think they were just
like not given so many parts Singapore
eyes and not so much attention and so on
and that's like what maybe soured the
experience a little bit but I think they
were great members and they they really
they made this into an interesting era I
will say that the thing that that makes
it a lot of stable is you see that
picture like
um on the right pretty much that's the
lineup they used for a lot of pictures
or they would have like free free free
and Junior Linden were always on the
sides yeah yeah so and you know the ones
at the front would always be at the
front
um and uh you know it it that's probably
why it was also almost stable is because
they didn't change much they didn't
change the hair colors or Cuts much they
didn't change the way they stood but um
still the music for me and the dancers
were just great like yeah
um oh but I did make a mistake it's not
supposed to say golden error it's
supposed to say
um supposed to say uh
um Platinum era I am yeah hang on
flatten them I can change that right now
oh I was just gonna come back we're just
gonna cover it like
well this is the Platinum era because
um
well it's uh
yeah I updated it can you refresh
it's very important yeah it's very very
important very important okay okay okay
a lot of my favorite morning most of my
songs also come from this era there we
go pretty much all my names there we go
there we go
um but yeah this is called the Platinum
era because they're wearing those
Platinum outfits and the album was
called Platinum nine disco the first
well technically they did a cover album
but before that but the first proper
album
um they did was called Platinum nine
disco
um
okay next slide next um
okay so after 2010 it was a very 2010
was a very sad year for morning miss me
because junjun linen and kame Eddie
oh yeah they had a graduation concert
for all three of them right yeah I
really liked anything down so sad and um
the concert was amazing honestly and I
love when they wear the outfits or their
colors yeah it's so cute
um but um after the after that
um they did perform one concert with
just five members it was a hella project
concert yeah and then they added four
new ones for the 9th gen
um so this generation contained members
you know from 5th to 11th Generations
um so this is important because Takashi
I and nigahiriza became the first
members to reach 10 years in the group
yeah um nigaki stayed the longest in
this era but then was beaten by Michigan
who stayed in the group for 11 years 10
months um and in 2011
free members were added for the knife
gem but
one Heller Pro egg was also added as a
surprise you didn't even know
okay yeah she didn't even know she was
gonna be added I was so happy for her
yeah because she was a egg for quite a
long time right she was she wasn't she
that was when they like right after that
was when they changed the eggs to
kenshouse and um her and a cardi were
eggs for a really long time so
um yeah it's very lovely
um for her she didn't even know she was
going to be added in
um but during the Spring did you did you
clearly say what the eggs are oh well
the eggs the hell perks were changing
for this chat the trainees into them
thousand and I think two they added the
kids
um and but in in 2004 they added the
eggs which there was a load of them
um and from the eggs King groups like
smiling yeah they were basically always
waiting to be put into a new group and
but some of them are like trainees for
years and years and years and never end
up in group stones but the the thing is
like that this was she was the first if
you don't count little in because she
wasn't an egg for very long
um Mizuki was the first egg to be added
um
[Music]
um because London was like barely an egg
she wasn't even on the website or
anything
um but okay during the Spring tour they
announced another generation I think at
this point they were like okay all our
older members are probably gonna
graduate soon so
um we have to put in some new new kids
um already and um so the tempting were
added
um during the Autumn tour
um with free winners include no full
winners sorry including a hello broken
shoe say an egg because that's when they
change the name to can choose say and um
in 2012 though another audition was
announced
um the winner was from the 11th of Jan I
think they announced
like I think that what they did do an
audition where nobody won but then they
did another audition
um
and then yeah they got they got order
Sakura they're only I love her yeah I
love it she's such a great singer and
then so they really this generation is
important because the dancing got
um like really oh Kiara's flying it got
really like full like formation style
like they've really worked on their
synchronizing and stuff but can I say
that
starting from especially the 10th
Generation but already kind of in the
ninth generation they kind of lost me
there because that's when they started
um doing all these like kind of weird
EDM music
style also changed into like before they
were singing more like I guess how would
you describe it more melodically so but
then later on it would get more like
they cut off every little
syllables
definitely from the 50th single that's
when the style went in that direction
and they stayed in that for like a good
a good while
um it was it was pretty much EDM style
yeah um but not the kind of idiom that I
like
you know I just I couldn't really I
think it was like I didn't feel like I
could get into the groove of it the same
because like uh like even though I
didn't I wasn't like I wasn't super like
aware of like a lot of the history or
the details musically I'm always very
much I was very much into the more of
the things that I felt like I could I I
could enjoy more musically and like
there was more of like uh I guess like
um I don't know with like uh with the
EDM it felt like there wasn't as much
like
cute joy that went into it if that makes
sense I don't know how to describe it
but I hope that makes sense
from a really cute song
guys you KFC has to listen
because they're wearing chicken
um
that's the lowest selling single ever
yeah I mean I understand
[Music]
they started the they started the year
in chicken suits and ended like doing
EDM so I think the thing was that like
AKB was getting more and more popular oh
yeah and they were all wearing like
really cute like school uniform Idol
outfits and then you have one who used
to be the most popular Idol group in
Japan and now they're wearing these
fluffy big now the chicken outfits and
and I think the members were probably
also wondering like are you even
by the way yeah we have a problem that
um it's already like we're at 50 minutes
already okay
so it has to be still I'll be speeding
yeah yeah yeah yeah so in 2014
um they started naming themselves after
the year so every year every year was
different so now we're on morning Muslim
at 23 or two free no not 23 too free
okay next slide next slide next slide
okay
okay so this is the longest error this
is the current error and it's spanning
eight years so far but it's really named
after the leaders so fire what I didn't
know they are named it out there yeah
it's just um it's just fukamura Mizuki
era because she's been the leader for a
very long time
um but she's gonna graduate you know
so this the this era
um also marks the 10-year Mark for
Mizuki Arena masaki and Sakura well
they've also been around for a while
yeah it's weird it's weird to think that
Minsky and aarona
um hold the title for the longest
serving members with over 12 years wow
that's amazing and then
joined right after Siamese graduation
um two of them being can you say 30th
gen joined there was no audition
actually they were just added
um because one was literally uh can you
say for like two minutes
um and then 14th Jan joined there was a
no audition Eva it was just chisaki who
was a member of country girls but that
group is founded in 2019.
and then they kind of like distributed
those members into other groups yeah
they did too because they were
apparently too busy yeah
um
um disappeared into the void yeah and
then uh 15th Jan joined 2019 after an
audition one was a Ken shoe set trainee
and finally this year they added the
16th gen [\h__\h] we're already at six damn
what the [\h__\h] yeah I'm like I can't wait
for like the 20th and then everyone's
like holy [\h__\h] you know
the average age now is 20. like a lot of
them now are in their 20s
um it's weird to think but there were
times when the average age was lower
than that yeah yeah definitely like
especially in the Pokemon era there's
it's been lower but now a lot of them
are older that's good next slide
next time
[Music]
um so this is the current lineup we have
um going from top left to right we have
pink is Mizuki then we have uh Sakura
and then akane and then uh Reyna and
then Ayumi and then Arena and then on
the on the left on the side we have May
and Maria and then on the right oh my
goodness I can't even read my writing
um what does that say I can't read so
pixelated
um
oh you have to say something special
about Mickey also Mickey you can explain
why especially yeah so she's she lived
um in America for a long time and it's
thanks to her that they released a song
entirely in English and she's really
helped the group
um go overseas and stuff because like in
Kpop I feel like you know a lot of the
groups nowadays have like fluent a lot
of fluent English speakers
in English this
so so my groundbreaking AKB they have
been talking about this whole project
teleported no no so suddenly there's an
English speaker and like Wow Wow Wow
Let's Go communication let's go
accessibility
uh real and real there's two reels and
um it's interesting because the real the
real s
um she's the first member to use the
color milk tea oh so Brown you mean
Brown was always such a popular member
didn't she change it though because she
was unhappy with it I changed it to
Yellow because she's like well yellow's
free why don't I get this in there yeah
what the hell why does she have to have
brown man do an idol [\h__\h] Brown so I
just said that they were like uh it's
amazing I don't feel bad Everyone likes
milk tea like obviously
they could have done they could [\h__\h]
um emerald green nobody has that yeah
but black and white too
my daddy was white oh yeah yeah it was
used before why not bring white back I
think white is a nice color
yeah they tend to not use the colors of
someone who just
um graduated recently but Arena was
originally purple and then they tend to
not use the color from someone who
graduated recently sounds like like out
of respect like because as if they just
died so let's not use their color
all right next slide oh Romaine shambles
oh well she looks good in brown okay it
has a good color to wear I will say
yes yeah they've had 72 singles 16
original albums plus loads of more
confirmation compilations and lots of
appearances and other things 26 years in
the biz they pour a ton
um they've won many awards
um overall there's been 45 members some
of them are born even after the
formation of the group now some of them
are going after 2 000. yeah a lot of
them yeah
oh my God
oh my god
um they've sold a lot you know um 2008
2020 were the only years that nobody
knew joined and there was no graduation
and a lot of members after they graduate
they become like actresses or
newscasters or musical performances or
soloists
um or they just quit showers completely
ah oh yeah okay next slide I'll be quick
next slide okay
okay my favorites from the graduated
members I like Kama Eddie wait
I also like comedy and you know who has
like kamehame
orange lovers let's go so many orange
lovers
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
orange is my favorite color even before
I met well I didn't meet her but even
before I knew it was like oh all right
all right all right and then my favorite
current member is
and then era my favorite error is
platinum ERA
[Music]
this is the Eric Eddie online yeah
um okay next slide
and then my favorite single is
so good it's good
yeah I struggled a lot but Platinum nine
disco probably is a really good one I
think that one's just the most iconic
like look at them
and then my favorite concert is rival
survival all night smile like it was a
toss-up but that's fair because I love
them
but rival survival just was epic
um okay next slide
that's
um why I like morning Muslim
um uh they always try new approaches and
keep things fresh the dances are fun
um my Japanese pronunciation improved by
singing them they adapt well to new
genres and changing generation of Music
even when times are tough they keep
trying to push food the lyrics
um are really interesting to read and
they inspired me a lot um
[Music]
[Applause]
beautiful beautiful
very important much to talk about when
it comes to momosu too much but now we
talk about very cool
what the hell is Betty's Google
don't you also sometimes I want is
talking about vegetable open your Google
and type in no me no yeah
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is a picture of Betty's Coco on the
left side is uh around there and debut
time yeah when they still had one two
three four five six eight members mm-hmm
and then you see on the right picture
they're missing one member now these
this island group is different from
morning musume
um they don't have this system where
they keep on adding new members even
when they lost one member they decided
to just go with the flow and keep this
form and actually the the one member
that left left really early so to me
Betty's Google always was this this
group here
I think regret that they were gonna do
with the kids
okay
yeah
and next side yes yes that's just you
know yeah you see how cute they were oh
yeah that was actually the the writing
yeah seven eight memories
and can you just look at for example the
left picture if you look at the very
left girl on the bottom that is the same
girl as on the right picture the very
right bottom girl yeah
I was just I was just thinking about it
too I was like they look so baby over
here
is also the one on the middle left on
the right picture she changed a lot
that's kept in and then my Oshi for
example on the right picture she's
wearing the black hat on the bottom left
and on the left picture she's on the
bottom right she's
their faces are so cute even the way
they smile like you can really see it I
love it so much
oh Nami looks the exact same she died
when she cut her hair short like this
but also I was like oh yeah
she's got her hair short such one time
but what I think it's really cute in
this picture is you can see that
um in in like Japanese idol industry how
the styles of like what's what's the
popular hairstyle is changed like in the
left picture you see a popular thing was
like these like spiky looking bands and
hair updos and all that like really
fluffy with hairspray I don't know right
outside you see modern times so yeah
they can do more modern stuff yeah next
slide next one
yeah so Feliz Kobo means Betty's
Workshop yeah back when they were
announced uh when they found out what
their name is they were so young so they
didn't even they couldn't even reach the
candy they were like what does that mean
so cute they're so cute but the girls
were originally part of the helipot kids
you may have heard about that from the
morning
um Nation yeah they were kind of the
trainees and they were chosen to be part
of the lineup and originally the plan
was to change the lineup from time to
time but instead
um the members that were you know left
over in the kids and were supposed to
like rotate or whatever
um we're used to form another unit
called cute now that is I wish we had
the presentation today about cute
because cute is also [\h__\h] amazing
maybe a double day
yeah we could make another one of these
because we I feel like we need to cover
cute and smiley and maybe
yeah
cover smiling do it anyway anyway so
yeah next time
thank you yeah I'm gonna introduce you
to the members including the one member
that left the one that looks super young
in here
yeah she kind of stands out
and so shimi susaki is the leader of the
group but they call the leader captain
in this case so that was also her
nickname everyone called her uh captain
captain and her image color was yellow
and even though she was the captain she
actually didn't get that much Spotlight
I have to say unfortunately I like her
she's a really cute
um girl and she's an incredible dancer
right she was really well known for
being a great dancer
um but she was not really that much in
the spotlight no yeah yeah
right next to her
isako who was very much in the spotlight
they were like free members that they
always put in the middle in the center
and gave them the most lines and one of
them was
she was such a she's such a good singer
such a good singer hell yeah a moment
the thing is though that she is the
youngest member yeah and yet she always
had such an incredible voice and she
kind of grew into such a beautiful like
Diva looking lady even though she does
not have the diva personality at all in
my opinion but if you compare her looks
from when she was small but now yeah um
or like to den
um she like I don't know she grew I
think she had some of the best like
close-up shots in the music videos too
like she really knew how to learn
this is so embarrassing but I used to
pose for pictures because
um because of her because I thought she
looked so cool so I used to post the
pictures the exact same way and so I was
like hello I was like oh maybe this will
make me look cool
and so I have like several pictures of
me just like doing her face yeah like it
was always piloting always counting but
it made her look so I don't know what's
so weird
I think she looks very like yes like
Suave or like uh mysterious kind of
[Music]
stuff I'm not sure what the word is I'm
looking for but yeah anyway I need to
speed up she's my ultimate my queen for
uh image color is red she's in my
opinion the best singer
and Buddy there's other great singers
but in my opinion she's the best I mean
I think she's the best too thank you
thank you yeah
um and then uh on the bottom left we
have ishimura maiha who when I got into
Bettis Kobo was not there anymore she
graduated one year in and this group was
around for
over 10 years yeah yeah I was about to
say when when I got into Barry's she was
not into the in the group anymore
yeah yeah since she was only there for
like 10 percent
now not even probably
wait ten years
one percent of the time I was gonna say
it is one percent no
but it was like one percent it feels
like she was around for only one percent
of the time
she was there for a month you know what
I mean
yeah really though when she was like not
really like if you if you think back on
base couple's time as an active Idol
group you don't think I'm so sorry but
you don't know
yeah seven member lineup yeah so yeah
that's I can't really say much about her
her image color was light blue she was
kind of cute like she's like
really really really early but she
doesn't have many lines yeah
they have like a front like a front team
and a back team and she was in the back
team in a way yeah like they went
official teams but they were like the
ones that didn't get
speaking of the back team another one
who was kind of like more treated like a
backup dancer most of the time
even though she's such a sweetheart and
I wrote Subaru there because she reminds
me of silver if I had to recreate
Betty's Kobe with home life members I
would put some Senpai in her wait
because she reminds me of her she's
energetic she's cute okay tall is maybe
not how you describe but you know mostly
short hair for the most every time she
has short hair just like super the same
time and yeah her uh orange she's a very
very funny cute girl she always was like
the sunlight of the group
yeah like the quirky kind of yeah yes
yes she has a very
um like positive smile yes she was
always smiling
like her smell she's so pretty too she's
so cute yeah
yeah she's a sweetheart next slide
and then we have Kumai yulina who is the
tallest member like for real like the
funny thing is about but it's cool when
you make them line up then
like you know there's no average height
it goes like up and down and up and down
because momoko is really tiny and then
it's so tall and then
yeah you know like I would get cute and
who looked really similar like they look
like they would be in Friendship group
at school
Barry's always stood out individually
and they would like make jokes about
that
um when like they were filming stuff
like sometimes uh urina's head would be
cut off because she's too tall
yeah in camera shots and also you know
because she was so tall she would like
after the music videos and concerts
would be the only one not wearing heels
trying to be a little bit smaller to
kind of line up more with the other
members and not stand out too much
because of her height however now her
height helps her because after Venice
Cobo was kind of like disbanded she now
has been working as a model pretty looks
pretty successful I've been following
her yeah image color green also not
really
um getting many lines unfortunately
though she got more than the back team
but still not as she was like yeah I
feel like especially in the last couple
of years of Freddy's Global she was
getting more lines than in the early
days like she was was being recognized a
bit more I guess you know and on the
right side next year we have tsukunaga
momoko she's a very very very special
character
um in this picture you see her really
iconic outfit and hairstyle especially
the hairstyle the hairstyle
of her
oh oh yeah
but this is what really like shaped her
character and and gave her the chance to
stand out in their entertainment world
because she is pretty much the only one
out of this group who during her
activities had a really successful solo
career yes yeah variety
so busy
from in the last few years of feather
school but she got so busy she was like
on so many shows and I was kind of
hoping that her solo popularity would
like move over to Betty's Kobo and bring
in Vegas Cuba more fans unfortunately
that never really worked out it never
really happened
yeah um by the way Senpai is uh her or
she is momochi but she's like more of a
fan of momochi than she is Google oh
yeah so that again how much is
popularity didn't really help the group
but at least I don't know it gave them
at least some what more of a like yeah
get their name out like it makes sense
like listening when she finished that
like she became a teacher afterwards
like that she didn't want to do like
entertainment anymore because of how
crazy she was
I was so surprised because she was doing
so well at that time that is cool but
disappears and she oh I did not think
she would like completely disappear from
the surface she joined country
girls okay she was doing that for a
while longer yeah
he was like I'm done she's just gone and
I I guess I kind of understand it it
must have been like really hard to like
keep up that like like 15 years yeah
yeah for all of them all of them they
did not really have a proper childhood
because they all joined when they were
around 11. yeah yeah yeah
okay yeah if you count their kids time
as well they were so many some were six
crazy crazy honestly if I had kids I
would never allow my kid to do something
like this no because I don't want them
to stop like this and lose their
childhood for it yeah anyway that's when
that was the topic I was about to say I
could get into that I have yeah
even though I wanted to do it I wanted
to joined hello project but I would
never let my child do this okay yeah I
was about to say I think like as an
adult like you when you're young like
when I was a kid I used to be so like I
used to want to go to like a bunch of
casting calls and stuff that were in my
area but my mother never let me and I
used to really upset me but like as I've
gotten older and like you start to work
in entertainment yeah you start to work
in entertainment and you go oh no I'm no
I it's I would not want any child to go
through any of that definitely feels
like JP Idols work a lot full
all right next number is
she was also a very popular member she's
one of the like three main members like
Momo teams I feel like they were always
in the middle always in the center
always getting the lines she's a great
singer too her English is purple I feel
like she kind kind of with the years
turned into kind of like a ghetto like
her Aesthetics yeah fashionista and like
such a like Diva lady not the not her
attitude not just the looks were so deep
alike and so yeah she was so willing to
try any kind of fashion style she was so
yes when she was like
a lot
the blondes
her hair a lot she's cut it short kind
of long had extension yeah I loved
everybody also
were both in Bono which we will hear
about later yeah and then last but not
least we have sudo Masa image color blue
she kind of has a lower voice and kind
of like a mama a little person in the
group of course she also didn't get many
lines ever and I feel like she maybe had
a really hard time in Venice Kobo and
I think she did get like
body shamed a lot yeah in the industry
it by the pants
um because like throughout the year she
maybe gained a little bit of weight
which is still I feel like for Western
standards it was nothing but for like
Japanese Sanders yeah but it's kind of
yeah it happened
yeah that's well that must have been
really stressful for her but she's a
great Idol a great person a great
performer and she has a great
personality
um
okay so here's a wrap
um idea of what happened the first
couple of years like really rough just
the most important things in between
they were constantly performing and
releasing singles but 2004 was their
debut 2005 is as you can see immediately
shimura leaves the group 2007 they were
the youngest act to ever perform inside
the masupa arena I think they were like
oh
I think the average age at that point
would have been 12 yeah I should say I
think it was like 11 or 12.
yes yes and they were so good 2008 they
won the best Asian newcomer award yeah
yeah yeah next slide which is weird
because they
did you're a newcomer until you hit
yourself
second half actually like putting it
together like this and just to two
slides in a couple of years it feels
like they didn't do anything but they
were around for such a long time and did
so much but this is really just I don't
know things that I thought were
significant 2009 they started making a
lot of ending themes for you imagine 11
which is why some of you guys maybe
actually know some of their songs I
noticed when I like covered a song in a
kalahoka stream some people actually
recognized it from all to my 11.
hell yeah so that's maybe where they got
um more more popularity maybe I mean
it's a big deal also yeah
um
2011 they had their first concert
outside of Asia at soccer.com
maybe some people have been to Sakura
Khan before it surprised me that that
was that only to like from 2011 I just
yeah felt it was early for some reason
but no this was the first one before
that they had um a concert like within
Asia outside of Japan but this was the
first one outside
yeah and since then uh they've been to
like Paris like Japan Expo and America
again
while they didn't do they didn't go
overseas
there's like the fan club in Hawaii yes
like all of them a lot of them did fan
club pools in Hawaii but it was like you
had to be in the fan club I love the
DVDs for that though you you know pay so
much to go the plane and you stay in a
room with other fan club members and
yeah
DVDs too oh I love those fan club videos
anyway next is 2012 momochi this is
where Mochi starts to gain big big
populators as a solo Entertainer and
even though she was not my Oshi I just
thought it was like incredible like if
you were there as a fan of fellow
project at the time everyone was like
what the [\h__\h] is going on yeah Mama
she's like [\h__\h] everywhere on TV in
Japan
but it's cool but you wouldn't really
see Betty's Cobble out there on the TV
but then multi was everywhere it was
incredible and we were really proud of
her doing a little cat poem yeah
she was like um
and then like the gag would be like
whoever was presenting with like yeah
yeah it was like she was the the booker
yeah always the book at type yeah
and 2014 was when my life as an idol
otaku was over and I wanted to Forever
cry in my bed because they announced
their Eternal Hiatus announcement
they announced the announcement yes
um and then
well today said Eternal Hiatus but it
was very obvious what they meant is
they're graduating because they just
named it this because they wanted peris
Kobo to not like disappear yeah I think
it makes no difference
no they can't come back momokul like the
Showbiz everyone else is
[\h__\h] kid
like the like agency or in in the agency
but yeah but she's she has two kids
tsunami I think is sculpted as well
however though I don't think that having
two kids stops you from coming back
because morning Muslim has been doing
like like OG things where OG members
come back that are already like married
and have kids and they still like
comebacks only to perform so I guess I'm
still full known I'm not really hopeful
to be honest I feel like they all are
like done with it because we're about to
hit our 10 the 10 years since the since
the announcement
[Music]
yeah next year next year
next door next one uh okay so this call
graphy discography discography
discography discography photography
thanks y'all they have pretty six
singles about 44 if you count the double
singles at some point they started
releasing like all these like double A
sizes
it was the first with berries for like
the you know because they were doing the
the opening things and more endings
whatever floor and as I'm 11 and then
just every group was like we're all
right away sides I was confused double a
size Triple A sides yeah I was confused
but I liked it because that meant for
every single I would get like a double
or a triple sometimes even with no music
videos I was like yo thank you for the
luxury I'm so happy more and more
Betty's the more the Mario yeah and then
nine albums and free compilation albums
they had 16 tours but kind of like more
like 42 uh when counting single day
concerts wait what the [\h__\h] is a
difference in that number
uh 16 is really inaccurate actually 42
is more like it I can't see it overseas
concerts and uh and single day concerts
and so on but omitting each tour day I
wonder how many days it would be if I
counted each date if they performed oh
well next time
if we had time we could count we could
take the time
good
yeah let me start from the left side
that's loving you too much it's actually
out of these songs one of their most
recent ones
um it's a great song with fun Rhythm and
great vocals they even wrapped a little
bit yeah
[Music]
oh yeah I feel like
um they had this thing where they were
doing like Thai songs
is a really popular song out of it is
[Music]
yeah that's why I liked it a lot very
Rocky they're outfits and the
instrumentals very Rocky they have cool
outfits badass song about summer
[Music]
um
so then next to it I chose it was really
hard to choose for but I went with
because that was like he was like very
mean they're so cute I fell in love
again when I watched that music video
for the first time because Lisa looks so
pretty I like their little outfits and
yeah
an addicting song about looking for her
husband
yeah
I like the song and uh one of the
writers I thought I should add like one
of the older ones as well this was 2004
one of the first singles called and
um I thought uh it's a really cool song
every time they perform it again even
now like in the later days
um it's so high it's so freaking hot
oh
[Music]
we're doing the dance moves right now
bring the bus like that has
[Music]
plenty of time
they timed it perfectly so you have the
time
um it's very fun yes it's so much fun it
gets so loud in the concert hall I saw
it live that's how you know though like
when that's how you know that the group
is like always like so like you they
don't you can't really miss when even
like the oldest songs still go as hard
as the new songs do you know yeah hell
yeah yeah
here this is a totally accurate pie
chart
um 48 exactly 38 banter this is one
thing I love about them so much because
they and the members they just tease
them Panthers so much yeah they have a
great relationship to each other
yeah they try and do things like
anything that never will just look at
how like are you serious yeah they
always get so like bad but playfully mad
[Music]
it's so cute you just really notice like
they have been like to I talk about it
as if they were still around but they're
not but anyway you just really notice
something they just have such a bond and
they've been through so much together
they're a family yeah yeah and then 24
exactly 24 good songs I was wondering if
I should write also they have like a
certain amount of percentage of bad
songs because then they're not bad
though but it's kind of like they have a
lot of joke songs that's what to say
like silly questions yeah yeah
why why but this is just the kind of
group they are
yeah you know I'm a vegetable a big fan
but um you know when cute was releasing
all these cool bangers you know and then
Facebook was like dancing in monkey
outfits I'm like oh I guess so I'm a
very small fan all right well this is
Betty's this is just Benny's this is
what you get that's so fair yeah
yeah um and then uh hype concert it's 46
yeah exactly because they have so many
songs and they have a long history and
with that comes really hype concerts
they have so many songs that get so hype
like so many chants and and everybody is
just like one eat taikan there's this
feeling that the audience and and the
group they just become one entity and
it's it's got so hot in the venue so hot
and then I guess I I didn't know what
else to put there so I put graveyard
there
um I don't know if you guys understand
what this is but like in in J-pop
industry the girls put out like photo
books photo books
in cute outfits but also mostly in
bikinis and
um well I mean
I mean I mean I mean some of the some of
it I'm like why when they're like 14 13
yeah and this one that I'm showing is
already a bit older and she just has
these beautiful visuals especially in
this one is so like ethereal in that
picture
she's such a beauty and I had a lot of
the of her photo books and every time
the thing is every time they release a
photo book they would do a handshake
event so I had to go there I had to buy
them for the book to get a handshake and
anyway
okay are we back test test test hello
test test test a one two three
a test test test one two three oh we're
back okay good
sorry about that everything closed
sorry that's my dad okay
okay let me I don't know why that
happened that was weird that's never
happened to me before
I get like uh
um
uh
hold on
Taxi too oh there we go
am I really back yep yeah we're back
well well well I might just have to
take taxi anyway
yeah I'm sorry hello I'll probably take
a Taxis let's just um slow down a little
bit okay okay
chill chill chill
um so yeah uh back to the Rivalry with
cute which doesn't exist because
I don't know I never felt such a thing I
felt a bit sad for Q because like um it
felt like you know they they thought
they were going to be part of berries
but then yeah
you had to do the Indies phase and
um like more musu back in the day
um and berries didn't berries just like
debuted but um there was you know there
was there was like a it was a really
healthy relationship they had like TV
shows together yeah yeah and songs they
had singles together and concerts
together yeah which was really fun they
did but I I don't think it's I think
it's better this way I mean separate
groups there is a common Community yes
yeah I prefer it this way though I'm
glad they didn't like do the whole like
switching members yeah yeah I think it
like made the bond like the bond for
fans better too
it's better this way it's just that cute
um they started out with how many
members they start out with eight one
left right before they debuted as
um uh they had a major debut and they
actually had to change their um debut
single from yukigatiri to sakuragachi
because
[Music]
um they had to Mega me left
um so for a while from 2007 to like 2009
um barriers and cute had the same number
of members so it helped like pairing and
and colors and all that stuff and the
concept was really well yeah yeah yeah
yeah but even though I guess only three
members left for them only it felt like
so much more like yeah for a couple
years it felt like they were constantly
changing and they were just not reaching
their like finals shape and like their
the the way they should be like I don't
know it was always like it felt like
they were falling apart and then yeah
yeah it felt like honestly we talked
about how berries was had like the front
rope and the back group The Fat group
still got some show time you know they
got in the spotlight cute for the first
two years
um uh like after major debut or maybe
even during Indies they it was literally
just two people in the front and the
rest fellow backing nonsense yeah that
was I mean this is really not a cute
PowerPoint presentation but there was
this one time where
had from the sidelines just watched in
in
horror when I saw that they released a
single shock yeah which was so shocking
because it was so disrespectful to all
the other members and fans of the other
members because Heidi Suzuki ID was the
only one singing
yeah they were literally just practical
dancers and it was like why don't you
just release it as a solo single then
for idea yeah yeah everyone I remember
hearing this last time and there was no
I was waiting I was waiting went on the
other singing
um still no yeah yeah and I just felt
like oh and that that was probably the
worst point for yeah like for cute I
feel like everyone was mad yeah but then
afterwards it it got so much better
especially for chisato
like they actually started to get lines
where in the beginning the barely got
anything maybe my got some I really
don't understand that decision I still
to this day do not freaking understand
it she said that was an amazing singer
yes yeah yeah but I don't understand why
they do this with shock like I was
shocked
it was the shock it was a shock you know
ID was great but you could have released
it as a song anyway back to British
school book
so yeah um they debited uh like when
their average age together was around 11
some were even younger yeah
um and they were around the average age
21 around their disbandments so you can
see there were around 10 beautiful
amazing fun-filled yeah and you'll never
get back
[Laughter]
no
no damn I don't I don't know about them
though like they they'll never get their
childhood back but you know I mean they
have a child and it's like a traditional
weird one yeah not the traditional
childhood you'd want for a kid
yep yeah yeah that that berries that
like I said they are they really didn't
look like they would mesh well together
if you saw them in the streets you
wouldn't think they were friends no the
cute little friends they look like a
gang but like a group like yeah but I
very I will say cute had some of the
greatest outfits I know we're not
talking about you anymore but they had
some of the greatest outfits from IMO
visually you could tell they they look
like they look really like comfortable
together they these girls if you looked
at them um you know as they are like
you'd be like they're really different
how are they friends but they just
they're like a loving family that's what
makes you so maintaining though that
friend yeah they can stand out you know
with without having needing to do
anything extra
[Music]
we oh yeah we're already kind of like at
the end
um on their YouTube account they have
uploaded uh officially officials so this
is legal you can watch it without
feeling illegal live performance of live
performances of almost every single and
more on their YouTube account so check
it out if you want to get like a feeling
of what their concerts are like I want
you guys to get a feeling of what the
concerts are like please watch them
they're so funny
yeah in the live concert setting for
very very very much
um and I I wish I could just like watch
a whole concert together with you guys
but those are unfortunately not legally
available and you
on YouTube
so for now
our YouTube channel yeah if you scroll
down a little bit the third playlist
that they have on their channel from the
top the third one is the one with all
the old and new concerts um performances
so check them out
and that I think that was the next slide
is the last slide I think yeah it is
you know at the concert in the beginning
and at the end uh the the crowd will
always stands
that's kind of like their their thing
also the grip themselves before they
start a concert they put together their
hands and then they're like
actually I've really liked this whole
like tradition they have going on so
um the other day when I had the stream
the New Year stream with um some fellow
whole life members
um even though we're not in like an hour
like we're not an idol group as
five but yeah I just felt like doing
something like that yeah so I was like
can we do this you say your name I say
my name and so on everybody everyone
when you say your name you put your hand
in the front and then we say
cool and then we did that that was fun
check out their DVDs videos
was gone I could not ever get into an
auto group anymore this much it was just
the special magic was gone I would look
at the other Idol groups and I would be
like hey they're great I liked their
music the memories look cute and so on
but I could never really feel that like
I found an Oshi again no I guess
I I really loved berries like berries
was mini money and berries were the
first groups I found from this project
so it wasn't morning most of may
actually but
um the special generation was one of the
first songs I saw
um yeah and um I after they graduate I
saw I went to the concert not the
graduation concert but the concert
before the graduation concert like the
in November September or something the
year before and um it was magical
because yeah they just like a lot of
groups they they are in sync they sound
similar they look similar they dress
similar but berries they look different
they have different heights they stand
up their voices are so unique and they
all have so many different personalities
and it just it was easy to recognize
them and they they just looked like
they're having so much fun like some
groups are just too focused that they
forget to have fun yeah but Barry's just
felt like so much fun and I I feel like
I tried to find that magic again with
some of the new groups but no one can
replace Barry's Global like they try
yeah they had a spiritual you know like
they had the spiritual successes of
kobushi factory and
umaki Factory but but it never felt like
to me like it would be a successor no
they're both good in their own right I
mean kobachi doesn't exist anymore but
rip yeah but um they they nobody can
really replace uh fairies like no hello
project group was like Barry's Global
thank you for saying nah like I always I
always feel a little bit
cute
berries look like um a family thing
thank you for paying respect to my
favorite little girl that really moves
me
all right but but the next presentation
that we're seeing Oh you have two
Betty's members so I'll listen gladly I
love Bono yeah let's move on yeah
um got so popular man it did look that
they are definitely killer subunits
right yeah
world of singles complete I mean and
concerts
had a lot of singles but Bono was
probably the most popular yeah yeah
because uh Sugar Sugar
so like that was a huge part of it
um
okay so uh uh
so here we are talking about photo
this is the group that I got into first
um that introduced me to hello project
as a whole and
um they were a subgroup that was formed
to create opening and ending songs to
the magical girl anime
and so like I uh by peach pit and I was
really uh into that anime for a really
long time
yeah I found them through the anime
um I loved oh because they covered
because the opening song was kokoro no
tamago and then they did
for the first season yeah and I I was so
obsessed with the music because I loved
how it sounded and
um it kind of like was just so
incredibly enjoyable for me that I
wanted to listen to it more especially
because like uh their sound was like
really kind of like this like pop pop
punk like pop punk pop uh rock type
sound
[Music]
it feels like Texas
no you're not wrong yeah yeah like they
definitely look that way
yeah uh I couldn't tell you I'm not I'm
not gonna lie to you that those are
probably my least favorite outfits
they've worn
um but they're still iconic though yeah
oh of course like
to get him checked like um because they
have like several like iconic Styles
yeah or like the like Union Jack British
British oh yeah I don't think I included
that in my slide but it's so good it's
literally just like they're they're
giant like dresses with the Union Jack
on them please google it I'm telling you
right now go Google it right now it's so
good
there was
I mean they got rid of like the wet the
Western Chic Vibe um in other songs that
had uh that had flannel in them or
Tartan in them but um what's it called I
uh
that's how I got into them because uh
for the first season of the anime they
did the ending and openings but then for
the second season they only did the
endings because uh the opening things
themes were uh covered by uh sugakata
egg and then Guardians four
um
is doing the openings and they had three
of the members from who were going to be
in smile age eventually and then
Guardian School came and the sugar egg
members changed apart from one
um and they just did like a b side or a
cover of the Guardians 4 single on the
Guardians 4 single like they just did
the cover of it so they didn't really
you know when Mizuki wasn't it like
sugar got an egg and stuff they didn't
really get to do songs
a cover of the actual song but sugar
kind of egg was so cute it was cosplayed
the yeah
so that music video and was the reason
why uh I tried to cosplay
for the first time
um music video oh the uh um
and so like uh I
um
I was a huge fan of Sue from uh the show
she was one of the the eggs she was uh
amulet Clover and I she has the green
one and
um I I loved her so much I loved the
pigtails I loved the the big puffy skirt
and that like it was the thing that
inspired me but anyway
um there are three members in Bono uh uh
momoko and Miyabi from berries and then
Irene from cute I put my two favorite
pictures of the group
on here and then put some arrows so you
guys could see there's irie
and then uh Mia right there
so basically the most popular members of
the respective group I was about to say
except now
yeah I was about to say the nudge nudge
yeah the interesting thing
about though is
the pigtails she didn't carry any of
that into balmy yes she she lost the wax
in her hair and the yeah the pigtails
and she went from the phase that she
does and yeah thank God yeah yeah that's
what uh Pandora we're talking and that's
what I was saying Pandora and I have a
thought on it we were I was like I
didn't know I did not like the the
pigtails at all personally I didn't
um they weren't for me so like when she
started to put her hair down and have
like natural clip hmm
you wouldn't do your hair like that no
no also my hair is too long and like I
have really thick hair so it's like
trying to do that
all the time you could do it too
well look well okay I'm good I was gonna
talk about this later but I didn't think
I was cute enough to be mama momoko so I
um I used to try to emulate uh Miyabi
so
um like her fashion and her style so I
got I got really into like any any
fashion trend she was into I was into
um like if I saw her dress or like do
her hair a certain way I was like cool
guess that's what I'm doing
um I didn't think I just didn't think I
was cute enough
um because I I always wanted to be cute
but I didn't think I could ever get away
with it so I was like I guess I'll just
try to be pretty
well I mean this was then in comparison
to now I'm awesome but um
uh
but uh yeah at the time I uh I didn't
think that I could get away with it
especially because I was uh also very
much a like a tomboy when I was um when
I was into Bono so like
so uh yeah but anyway next slide so part
two so this is about all of their music
so we've got their debut single honto
nojibune was the best-selling hello
project single until 2012.
um if I remember correctly it was they
sold like
40 over 40 000 I think it was
yeah like they're singles
yeah
did really well like yeah yeah because
it was the best selling single for a
while and then uh I just remember I
think it's I think it's like over 40K
um
and then and then they start in a movie
a horror movie that uh yeah
I never watched that oh my text messages
yeah I don't like horror movies
uh I I didn't
um
I didn't I don't like yeah I don't like
horror movies okay hold wait hold on I
put the pointer so
like horror movies but I would watch
this
the horrible
um
a berries and cutie is actually quite
good the old summer game ah um
Serena got like a time to shine
yeah I don't really get into [\h__\h]
I'm not I'm not really good with horror
in general
I was more of a fan of not the horror
movies but they're like
um musicals that they did yes
kimchi
was good oh Cinderella almost good oh
I I watched some of the musicals in
person
that they had a smiley and they swapped
they swapped roles like different
versions anyway anyway
it's already no no no I like hearing
about it because like because it's like
I feel because I get to I feel like I
get to live vicariously through because
like that wasn't available to me so like
uh anytime
I tried to get DVDs but uh what's it
called yeah every time any time I try to
get DVDs at the time they were always
almost like too expensive for me to
afford so I just was like okay I wait I
wait until never
um
[Music]
really expensive especially anime like
yeah in the west I was so used to buying
it Blu-ray and have like Ahoy
yeah so it's like uh too expensive
Ahoy oh hi do you know what that means
Ahoy are you getting what I'm trying to
say a high she doesn't get it
no no no oh hi okay I get it I'll get it
really okay well he but hey you could
like I have
behind me
only have two episodes
well the rest
Ahoy anyway
I was
stuck getting it okay
no no no oh I mean yes
I don't know I don't know anyway
okay I was like I was like are we are we
what's happening
yeah we have reaching understanding I
see it
uh but but
they had uh three uh Studio albums Cafe
Bono and then Bono two and then we are
Bono I uh
what's it called I used to uh I used to
like okay
I used to uh make like make my own CDs
of their music
because we because I couldn't get there
yeah my dad taught me how to so I would
do that because we I didn't have like
access to like getting my own version of
the CDs so I'd find out what the track
list was and then I would make my own
CDs to listen to in my stereo because it
was because I want it back in the day
they mostly they weren't I guess they
weren't doing much of like digital
releases like Spotify wasn't the thing
no Spotify
[Music]
yeah I had iTunes
play Asia and stuff it was hard to get
the series like I won a CD one time but
it's like they didn't want overseas
people to listen to their music
almost
yeah but we did we did we did we found a
way we found a way yeah I mean they
didn't do
too many things overseas like I remember
they were supposed to do something but
then it like got canceled like right
before it they were supposed to do it in
like Sweden
or somewhere
yeah even got entirely canceled yeah
yeah it got it got like a it was because
the I think the convention itself got
canceled like but right before because
um the convention was like oh there's
too much competition in the industry so
uh we didn't and we so we didn't have a
lot of really good like ticket sales so
we're just gonna cancel the event
um
over some things eventually yeah like
they eventually did
um they performed at uh
uh they performed in France and then I
think yeah yeah they did they were in
Paris
I think they went like twice if I recall
correctly
so yeah
okay yeah they also never came to
Austria nobody [\h__\h] comes to Austria
man you can't people still come more
often through the UK to put them there
then they come to Austria we did get
juice juice uh-huh that's it nobody
[\h__\h] gives a [\h__\h] about Austria I'm
like what is Austria Australia okay can
be considered awesome I'm not an idol
group but I've been to Austria does that
make it better
oh that makes together yeah it does oh
thank you the Austria is really
beautiful I had a lot of fun when I went
okay but let's talk about it
but anyway uh and then they have the two
they had too many albums and two best
albums but they and then they have 13
major singles
renai Rider uh kiss kiss
my boy take it easy bravo bravo our
songs and then
hatsukui cider uh and I think the ones
that people every single one of them is
a [\h__\h] Banger they really are they
didn't
what are your favorite what is your
favorites what is your favorites like
out of out of the major singles
um for me
my boy take it easy is great
um
yes
[Music]
whatever it is yeah and hatsukui side is
a good one because I just I love the the
old style like
um like
I don't know like the outfits are cute
as well yeah
and it had been a while since between
our songs and Zazzle
it was since they released a single yeah
like um what's it called I also
had a big gap too yeah
what's it called
what are your favorite what are your
five or like your four yeah it's pretty
much like the same ones almost more or
less uh I would say
kiss kiss
and
um
take it easy because take it easy has a
special meaning to me but yeah
to me is like I freaking love it but
um I feel like
has been a little bit ruined for me
because I've
just heard it too many times because it
gets
um covered in uh underground Idol
concerts
covered to death and I feel like but
they just they just don't
pay enough respective that that opening
the ID sings for that song especially
when she does a long version yeah it's
really good yeah it is really good like
I understand why it's very iconic though
um you feel good yeah very very iconic
but just a little bit overdone in my
head from my experience
as well they literally went from like
and kiss kiss was very school style was
like like more chill and relax it
definitely that was the start of time
you know like the the scarf around your
neck that wasn't a scarf I had one of
them too I wanted to look like the the
guitar I had so many of those I had so
many and wore them with every yeah with
every outfit I can send you guys
pictures of just every photo
but by the way
um
so going all started out with like doing
these anime endings right yeah but later
on they were is it they didn't do the
anime songs anymore right they were just
doing things on their own just yeah
because they were just doing so well and
that's so impressive yeah yeah
even even though there was singles it
didn't mean there was gaps in their
activities
Oh yeah like uh um what's it called they
uh
what is the word that I am looking for
um they
what is the word that I want oh they
were doing a lot of advertisements and
things
um outside of that yeah
they did that and they went on tour a
lot too so like like they went yeah and
um
if there was ever like a berry event
like and Bono came out it was the hype
like yeah everyone was so excited hell
yeah oh yeah so they also did
um Sashi haralino's um Idol Matsuri oh
yeah yeah
[Music]
like they did so many like they did so
much
and like uh like even once um the anime
ended they
actually I put well I put it in the in
the PowerPoint later
um is it the next one no it's not it
means in Italian I thought that'd be
really fun well I I really just I wanted
to just add these pictures really I
needed I wanted
something
um
but that's what that means in Italian uh
and these are the members
so
Umi was until 201 yeah hold on I'll fix
it I'll fit
uh
it's supposed to be Momo cattle
I want you guys to know I made this
literally so late at night I was so
painfully tired
I'm trying to figure out how to
oopsie there we go
we had the name already corrected in my
slide
oh goodness
colors so in the um
they had different colors and iron was
green and when Miyabi uh early on some
of them had different colors not
everyone but some of them are different
colors and they would change a little
bit and Miyabi was red so they kept
those colors because that's the colors
they had when Bono started and they
decided well just keep them instead of
changing to purple and Iris was pink so
oh yeah doesn't Mia have purple and Bono
no it's red it's red oh red yeah because
as I say their colors are different
yeah
but they have
they had different colors here yeah yeah
because if because then cute I had a
pink
or yeah
Erica and Kanna left in 2009 they were
just like we lost our red and yellow
let's change the colors yeah and so irie
went from
so you still have an apple and a last
name but let's just keep it this way oh
my God her name is really long her name
is so long
but just that's because just just go to
the next time
I was gonna say I spelled it I spelled
it right everywhere else but the members
page that like that's the that's the
worst part I spelled it right everywhere
else
anyway but uh this is like a very
brief timeline of like the stuff that
they did so like 2007 is when they
debuted and then uh they had their first
solo live in 2008.
um and Cafe Cafe Bono was the if I
remember it's the
highest selling album of hello project
at that time or no hello project kids
Hello project kids at the time
and um and then uh rocking rock and Bono
was the was a fan club special if I
remember as well and then that year also
that was the year that they
um
yeah
and then uh that was the year that they
also did the pizza
he did that more than one stone yeah
they did a couple times yeah yeah and
they're they're back yeah like the same
band they were like girls right yeah
um I think they had a different name
when they started but I'm not I don't
remember it uh very well
um but yeah so they felt like they were
parties going on yeah and like the the
their backing band also super like super
well-dressed and very cute as well
um and then uh 2000 well in 2009 I
didn't add 2009 because I only had so
much space but uh 2009 they came out
with Bono 2 and then
um that was their first album to make
the top 10 or top 10 charts
um then they had their like hybrid Punch
tour and then uh mama uh momoko was
became like the leader that year of Bono
or like she was appointed that year and
then um and then they also had another
tour like a winter tour
um and then yeah and then stuff yeah
like uh what's it called they were doing
that's why like from like uh until until
like a lot later I had no clue because
of how busy they were I just assumed
that they were one group for the longest
time until a lot later
um and then uh the following year they
released their we are bonus uh
album I think that's the album I
listened to the most probably but that
year um but uh that was the year that
the anime ended so they didn't have any
like new release songs
um and but they were still doing like uh
they were still doing like
advertisements and stuff and then um
they came out with like their first
compilation album called the best of
best of Bono or best Bono and then um
they switched labels that year
as well they moved from Pony Canyon to
the uh zetima label
um
so I think Momos is on that
yes I think yeah yeah yeah it is yeah it
is because uh they're I think there's
yeah they're still signed with them
um but yeah they switch labels uh
because the anime was over and but um
the following year that's when they
opened up their like YouTube channel so
you would have more so people started to
have more access to like finally yeah
yeah they didn't have a presence on
YouTube they were on this website
um releasing stuff like it was still
like a video sharing but it was like
Japan it wasn't neat no no it was called
like something up
oh I didn't have access to it so I don't
know you would always yeah you'd always
see their videos from that place on
YouTube but they didn't have an official
Channel yeah like uh it was about time
like uh like literally the only way that
I ever found anything was like through
deep like deep
just so I just recommend that interested
me though free albums and freeze like
it's not common nowadays but back in
like from maybe like 20 2006 to 2010 it
was very common for most of the groups
to release an album every year like what
sometimes they do too
like yeah like 2010 they did too 2010
they did too I mean one of them was a
compilation album but it was still two
albums you know on on top of like
whatever other like projects they were
doing
um but yeah 20 2011 like uh leading up
to that point I was like doing like
really deep Dives to find like
like any sort of like Bono anything
um so when they opened up thank you
that was the website oh there we go
yeah
yeah yeah so it doesn't exist too
nostalgic
yeah so old yeah no it's not it's like
uh uh what is what is it LimeWire no one
uses that anymore either
um
[Laughter]
yes the the your best friend from those
years of like 2006 to like 2010 or
something like that
but um yeah when the YouTube channel
opened I I remember for me like I was
like this is a game changer thank you ah
um but that was the year they also put
out the horror movie and then they
announced that year that they would do
the
um the convention in Sweden but then
obviously like like I said it got
canceled so
um
like uh
there's and then like they did a bunch
of stuff in between but
um what's it called like they went to a
bunch of other they went to a bunch of
like other Idol events
um also in 2011 they had like a full
like rock and Bueno like
um
live stream
on their YouTube which was pretty sick
um
and then uh and then like um what's it
called
trying to think
I guess like in 2013 they also did so
2013 they did some more events and then
uh oh in 2014 they were taken off the
website
um even though they were still
considered like a main Act
and uh they were still doing like this
the radio show that they were doing
um well even when me and me was still in
berries and and mama called was in
berries too they took them I guess well
that oh they they were taken off the
hello project website yeah that's kind
of sad yeah in in 20 it was like 20 2013
2014 they were taken off the website
even though they were still doing a
bunch of projects for hello project
yeah it probably was like that was
really the point when they because I
think 2012 to 2016 they didn't do
release much yeah no like so they
probably will like uh you it's just a
subgroup they don't know yeah they
weren't really active yeah because like
they didn't release music for like five
like four or five years
um after uh after uh
she gonna try to um ended
[Music]
there was a big gap when they did had so
excited that was
[Music]
that was cool
um TV show and then
that was there was like a big while yeah
but when sorachi doll released
after such a long time well I was so
excited I was like finally they're back
I really needed them to be back
2016. finally some light in this dark
dark world yeah like uh I mean that's
the thing though is like even though
they weren't on the website anymore
it didn't have a a proper like
full-on Dance I mean they just had
microphones and I just I wanted to learn
the dance but there was no dance I was
like what is this that's that's how you
want to know the true sadness is when
you don't have something to dance to to
like your favorite song
Let's Dance
there's no dance
with a mic or jumping around and like
getting the audience hype up and
everything you know but like they did
but like uh even though like because
they still they also had like a wet a
web a web web show I think is the word
web show or something like that uh for
hello project that they were still doing
and then they like still participated in
like hello project concerts
um yeah like uh they did
um like they did the berries Kobo
Matsuri as well and then
um on their like 100th episode of their
radio show they like ended it
um as well and I think like so like
around like 2015 and onward you kind of
like knew that there was never gonna be
anything ever again type of deal because
like they were it was like kind of like
a it wasn't even like a they shut it
down right away it was like a really
slow shutdown like kind of like weaning
people off of them basically
and
um
20 2016 like they they released their
first single in like four or five years
and it didn't do really well but I think
the song is awesome so they it was so
Lassie dough yeah yeah
you know why it didn't do so well
because there was no dance
though
it was good it was good yeah but yeah I
do agree uh what's it called
um
yeah uh and then 2017
they held their last concert
and uh
I have every typo Under the Sun I
literally am looking at this like that
you you would have written only wrong on
the on the I did it right on YouTube oh
my God
I'm literally
a mess I'm a mess and a half
[Music]
don't worry but uh either way
just one oh I just oh no oh
oh oh
um but yeah
it's okay I'll be I think I can I can
well I was gonna say I could live with
myself but I'm dead so it doesn't really
work that way
um
but uh irie and momoko they graduated
from Hello project
um yeah because uh
uh momoko she said I think it was she
became a teacher
if I recall correctly yeah
um
and then an ID is now really popular as
a solo artist doing like anime
a little bit
thank you
probably yeah
she's she's really she's done like solo
concerts and everything and then she's
even covered Bono songs yeah I know yeah
I already had I had well more way more
well-known after she ended all of those
like 10 years of activities now through
the anime music that she's been doing
which it's kind of like sad like I think
all the new ID fans they they should
have gotten to Nowhere before they moved
so much
I think I missed that one that's fine we
need to catch up hopefully they've been
catching up on all that old good stuff
especially
you you should know
[Music]
okay we're dancing again anyway please
continue okay oh this is a really random
fact that I just feel it's not
well it's just it's just a really random
fact but um what's it called
uh I
this was this used to be like my fun
fact that I thought would make me seem
cool when I went to conventions I'd be
like did you know that irie is the child
of two professional golfers I don't know
why I thought that was
yeah I used to throw that at people and
they were like they'd be like that's
really random and I'd be like I'm just
trying to fit in
um but yeah and then uh uh Miyabi also
formed a new group as well
um and then just Bono officially
disbanded but Miyabi's group was also
disbanded as well
yeah
I was like gonna do the auditions and
look for people and then the group was
formed and then Reyna's rock band was
formed yeah I didn't really get into
those yeah
yeah
kind of like really only about they know
even though they had those on the
members but it was only about they know
yeah I don't what's it called I think
you felt a little bit that way with pink
dress
the girls got lines
I I don't think because like pink
looking at me when I was spitting out my
flag
don't look at me
if you were okay yeah I'm like spitting
in tomorrow she's looking at me close
your eyes close your eyes Close Your
Eyes giving her the eyes look it away
but she looks at me
you might have to like hurry up because
I'm like getting really tired oh yeah
yeah okay okay but anyway
fun fact this right I wanted to add this
because it felt like it was really
important so this is the uh single that
our thumbnail is based off of
um
yeah so I thought it would be really
cute to add it this song slaps so hard
it's so good in the dance is super fun
please go watch it please go enjoy it
learn the dance
um you'll make all of this proud
um but yeah anyway what what what time
like is this like 80s 90s outfit I would
probably say this is supposed to be like
it's like 70s
probably like 70s 70s 80s maybe yeah
so but mod style so good so cute anyway
I think the whole MV is in that really
nice it's like Retros TV recording yeah
so special oh yeah and like the filter
they used so good in like the entire
State like the entire set rather so oh
so good
um I was literally listening to it right
before we got into call so
uh
yeah okay so my favorites so
um
I just shoved them all into one so um my
favorite like I said this earlier but my
favorite was uh momoko but I always like
uh learned Miyabi's uh dances and like
tried to emulate her because I never
thought that I'd be cute
um
and then my favorites are bravo bravo uh
kachinko and then rotara hatsukui cider
and then last forever
um my favorite MV is never gonna stop I
really like that MV because they just
look like they're having fun and I love
their clothes and I love the lighting
and like it just looks like a it it's a
really casual Envy I think and that's
the way I like it a lot
um bravo bravo is the favorite dance
that I learned and then my favorite live
was the is the 2017
um like their last uh concert because it
makes me cry when I watch it so I like
it and that's why I like it
um
I can't I can't watch that anymore I
watched it like like a month or two ago
a little bit again and I was like I
can't watch this I'm crying
already though because like I'm I don't
I'm not a crier I don't cry very often
but this one like definitely gets me and
like so if like I'm in the mood to like
feel really sentimental
so literally when the concert's starting
I start to cry yeah just like the moment
that everything starts to start sobbing
but I'm that way with like anything that
means a lot to me
thank you for listening thank you
[Music]
all know it's like the Best of Both
Worlds yeah buddies and cute together
made into such a legendary group that
has the perfect balance and even though
none of them wear my ooshies I
appreciate them so much and every song
for that was a banger they're really
great can always recommend them like if
I had to recommend a group from or music
from Hello project to people of online
on the top of my list one of the tops
would definitely always be Bono because
you can always rely on Bono impressing
people and dragging them into them
like it's they're like a really good
introduction one because that's what it
made me want to listen to all the other
groups in hello projects
so and they don't change the lineup you
know so they they sound all good
together yeah yeah
like the energy is just really good
very very important
[Music]
it also means good not just yummy Bono
is
[Applause]
let's learn something
did you guys did you guys uh feel like
you are educated enough to take a test
now do you feel like you can tell are
you interested in listening to their
music that's what I want to know yeah
let's go listen to your room yeah
literally listen to all of them I I was
uh while I was getting ready and making
my coffee this morning I was listening
to like my Barry's Moana playlist
I mean it might be kind of like
um more or less a bit it might seem
meaningless to get into a group that
doesn't exist anymore that's not active
anymore yeah but for morning Muslim for
example they go around you can see them
and then still go to from them but I
think even though very scuba is not
around anymore I I I wish people would
not forget them because they surely
don't want to be forget forgotten ever
they don't want their years and years of
work they're 10 years of work to be
forgotten so yeah check it out yeah
definitely
and
um
a nice way of you know remembering them
but there's nothing that beats the
original you can't beat the original oh
yeah
like morning miss me at certain points
in the history yes or yeah the originals
and I think it also it's just nice to
like pay homage to a lot of like the
older I don't like to like older Idol
groups and like um Idol like uh
um disbanded groups just because as new
ones come out there's always like groups
that like like they had to come from
somewhere or like
um like you know so it's nice
yeah so it's like uh in a way playing
like like letting them live on and pay
homage to them and stuff like that so
definitely definitely listen
um
[Applause]
one more thing I want to say but I kind
of forgot to say oh
um one reason why I got so much into
hello project but not into AKB
um was because I think utano will
definitely agree with me uh hello
project focuses so much on being able to
give a great performance life
they dance really intricate dances yeah
but they always sing live and you if you
listen to them for the first time on
like to a concert recording you may not
re realize there's life because they're
really good at it you don't even hear
them breathing because they're trained
so well yeah yeah
and you know every performance will be a
little bit differently they'll put Power
in one bit and like hype up another bit
um so it's not it's not like um it's not
lip synced yeah but it just shows to me
the all the effort they put into it and
all the professionalism and it just
shows the skill you're so good at what
they do this is their job they put so
many years into it they take it so
serious and I feel the passion when I
look at their concerts at their
performances and it's just so much as a
fan I can be so proud of them and I can
so proudly recommend them to others
because
they are just the greatest in the
industry at what they do yeah even
though it's a joy to listening to them
it could be rise I think like what each
like AKB momokla and teleported focused
on very different things
um momoklow was very much like keeping a
standard and
um
AKB was members and votings and looking
cute and like like having a big Unison
in chorus theme whereas how the project
really focused on Shining the
individuality of the girls yes you don't
see it but I'm nodding my head very
strongly
but
um it like there's so many like members
and I feel like there was a very little
chance for my Oshi to shine
whereas in you know in her project
um even if they didn't have lines on a
single they for certain had lines on an
album or a B-side you know like the ones
who didn't get as many lines as others
right so that made me very happy yes
yeah
hello Project Life performances are the
best
their performances
you know and they will live on forever
they will never die but um like for me
hello project is just such a big part of
me learning Japanese and and wanting to
you know prove my language skills this
is a live performance
when we get into Japan more and wanting
to become an idol hello project is the
reason why I wanted to become alive
like I said earlier I did I wanted to go
on Broadway like uh
so like so for me watching the lives
that I could get to see like even if it
was just like on the screen like
um it was very inspiring to see how they
would perform and how much energy and
individuality you would got you get to
see like regardless of how tired they
were or how long they've been singing I
know that was like really a huge yeah
like they could be sweating like crazy
but they wouldn't drop the smile they
would still sound so good
yeah and like so I was like I want to be
that so yeah
[Music]
yeah they
um they're they're a bunch of hard
workers and even though like a lot of
them uh graduated their groups they
still work hard in different fields
I still hope one day for a Bono reunion
and but you know
yeah difficult to see I think once
actually like me I'll be an idea would
do it but no I don't think she wants to
go back no I mean
yeah I mean they did um
they did um what's it called during
covet like the pandemic like in 2020
they they live streamed
um their last Live on YouTube but then
and then Miyabi and then irie they did
um alive together on Instagram and then
um I read that did another uh like like
um after party on her own YouTube
channel
um so just just from that alone I think
that like uh I think it's kind of safe
to say that maybe Momo like she would
not come back because even for that
reunion it was only the two of them yeah
yeah yeah yeah so it's okay though I'm
not angry at her or anything she just
wants to move on which I think is fair
she was doing so much during that maybe
there's it could also be things that we
don't even consider like maybe like
contract contracts yeah that's true as
well because there's always a lot of the
contract stuff
he like helped country girls I mean even
though country girls didn't survive long
after she left she really helped them
grow and molded them was it was a big
support to help a project into places
that they wouldn't have been able to
before
it's just cool to see like in every
I guess like uh
like as time moves on you can start to
like you can see how um
certain like uh members regardless of
group can make it make it make a
difference and an impact for hello
project and like what they do and so
it's really fun to like see that
you
so I you know I hope that if any of you
do become a fan of hello project and you
go to a concert Heller project and you
hear a song and it says on the like the
the you know that sometimes they have
like a on the big um screen in the
background they have like the original
artists and stuff and you think oh
that's not the same one as the ones
performing I hope that you like oh
Barry's cool but oh maybe I can look up
Barry's Cup oh this looks good like you
know you know like look into the history
because there there are some groups that
you know might not have a long history
in hella project but and there's some
that have a long one but Barry's Global
has a very
um various cobal cute and Bono
especially have ones that really I think
changed like you know a lot of things in
hella projects
yeah yeah definitely
but uh yeah yeah we did it
yes we did the PowerPoint presentation
as if we were in school I know yeah
I was I I was such a bad student so I
literally had to ask Pandora to show me
like her Powerpoint so I could figure
out what to do with mine
because I I because I didn't do power
points like so like uh I did PowerPoints
when I was
no it wasn't that we just so like uh I I
would do like PowerPoint instead of
PowerPoints I used to convince my
teachers to let me use Windows Movie
Maker because that was what I understood
and I used to I had more Liberty to make
it creative that way and that and it
suited me better to like be goofy that
way and so I never really used it and
then when I got to acting school
what am I gonna put on a PowerPoint my
monologue that I have to act out do I
put it like there was no there was
nothing really for me to use at
PowerPoint for when I got to acting
school so I've so I was like I was like
Pandora can you please show me I don't
know what I'm doing I don't want to like
be super embarrassing but
I'm it's gonna be kind of scuff so
that's what so um
that's that's like I was so nervous I
was like okay well I'll figure out how
to do the PowerPoint
and you did it good job yeah
but we did it yay
yeah I hope you guys enjoyed
um but what's it called I know uh kiwawa
you said that you were getting tired and
sweepy yes I'm very tired and it's late
yeah
I already missed all the trains but I've
never understood why trains here are
like they'll go past that and like you
think in the one of the busiest cities
in the world yeah yeah they would go a
little bit longer but I mean they have
to end at some points like Capital
hotels I guess that's all such a good
business yeah well I paid 5 000 bucks
for my hotel so I don't want to stay at
the capsule hotel tonight gonna try to
get back to it that's super Fair
[Music]
I ripped it out of her hands twice yeah
Pandora told me and I was like
that's fair
oh don't worry I got my plus back she
hasn't stolen my idea she got the purse
back yeah I'm not a criminal
I'm not a criminal not yet if you were
we'd close our eyes to it
[Laughter]
if anything I'm just a smooth criminal
um
[Laughter]
oh yeah
okay but can you close it for us okay
yes I can
uh but anyway thank you guys I'm going
to I'm going to be uh I need to I'm
going to thank all the super chats and
donos after this so uh if if you want to
stick around feel free to but uh uh
Kiara and Pandora thank you for joining
me thank you for uh letting me play part
of this
foreign
make it safe back to your hotel
and uh I will probably
yeah I will I would probably DM you guys
later but like my usual here's a meme
here's a song I was thinking about and I
thought of you all that kind of stuff so
um but I hope you guys have a good night
get good rest
nice save at the end
uh no oh yeah no
I will not forgive the typos oh okay
okay then uh well uh I guess [\h__\h] me I
guess
um
just you can you get uh you get you know
a few points marked off your you know
especially because
I know Miss writing the name of you also
I know well because I always just wrote
Momo whenever I would talk about her and
so I always felt really awesome so you
know but whatever I it's mean anyway
like you I don't know do you even do you
even speak uh I don't even know if you
speak Japanese I've tried to all the
time but the but the thing is my I get
um I hyper fixated on it for a really
long time and then I always manage to
re relearn
um
like all my hiragana and then like half
of the Katakana and then right as I'm
about to get to like kanji my hyper
fixation starts to fall off and it's not
because I think it's intimidating it's
just like it starts to fall off because
I get busy or something like that and so
I've been trying to learn for like years
but it's it's kind of hard for me to do
it on my own so I think I'd need like a
tutor to probably properly teach me
can give you private lessons I was not
too busy
no I'm kidding um I I just uh yeah I I
want to learn
I mean we could we could have happened
we could say we could share chicken
nuggies since that's what you like no
you always like nuggies it's
it's a
it's an addiction um
yeah every time Pandora comes to the
stream she goes would you like to share
my nut like my chicken nuggies and I'm
like oh
it's like the food she mentions the most
these nugs
oh
because I thought I thought it sounded
like it no it's very clever I actually
really like these mugs
double G hey
that's the new that's the new that's the
new like Trend it's decent I think I'll
get myself some nuts
do it I'm good these nugs these dogs
okay but anyway
thank you ladies I appreciate it I don't
want I don't want to keep you any longer
than you need to of course have a good
night
bye
[Music]
okay
hold on let me oh wait I can probably
just move here okay
hi everybody thank you guys for coming
I tried not to embarrass myself too much
and hopefully I got away away with like
10 of it but
I'm so not good with PowerPoint
presentation
I was like uh uh uh uh
but thank you guys for coming thank you
again to uh Pandora and kiwawa for
joining I really do appreciate it thank
you for staying up so late
um
I know that uh the time was not very
um convenient for either of you but I do
appreciate it regardless
um but I just wanted to say thank you to
I wanted to um say thank you to all the
super all the super chats and stuff
first
um before we bouncy outed it was so
lovely to have all of you if it's your
first time piano or anything like that I
hope you had a good time and
um yeah thank you thank you
also I saw someone said like didn't you
have debut slides I didn't make my debut
slides my gen mate did them
so I don't count that
um
but uh really quickly uh
uh uh food thank you for the super chats
guy thank you for the Super Chat Pat
thank you for the Super Chat uh Jane
thank you for the Super Chat yeah of
course you can call me step mama honey
uh
uh Caster thank you for the doll for the
don't know
um
uh jkh monkey thank you for the Super
Chat miss fish thank you for gifting
um
thank you for gifting memberships
Duke thank you for the Super Chat GD
thank you for the Super Chat uh thank
you for the passionate presentations
came here yesterday after Kiara's
geoguessr video and looking forward to
binge your backlog of how to sound like
videos ah I hope you like them
I hope you like them genuinely
um I'm not it's not exposing okay Power
it's not exposing I just I will openly
admit I didn't make my PowerPoint I just
I just told her what I wanted to go on
it
I didn't I didn't bully her I asked her
for help because I didn't know what to
do and she was watching me try to make
it and she thought it was sad so she
offered to help
me
she offered to help me because she
thought it was sad watching me make a
PowerPoint
um but I'm I hope that you enjoy the how
to sound like videos
um I'm I'm really passionate about the
voice and voice acting and um just like
Linguistics in general and I think
that's a lot of like in that's
information for like voice actors that's
not available anywhere else or not
anywhere else but like I I had to go to
school to study it so I hope that you
get a lot out of it and if there's
anything that you do get out of it I
hope that it's learning that uh learning
how unique and special the voice is
so
yeah she thought it was sad
uh like she made it for me she was like
Opie do you want help and I was like I
got it and she was like clean just let
me help
uh Ruka thank you for the Super Chat uh
looking for the top thank you for the
Super Chat let's see if you always sing
I don't do songs got me interested in
that music since 2020. I'm glad three of
you you three dorks found each other to
guess about your passion I I wish I
could I wish I knew more I always like
was uh what's it called I always used to
like read on what what I could find and
like what was available on like the
groups that I liked but I could never I
never was like really exposed to like um
certain things uh involving Idols just
because it wasn't available to me so
being able to listen to Pandora and
Kiara like talk about it in more depth
with like information that like I like
half knew but then like it was like
elaborated that was really lovely and I
really it was just nice
laughs
uh uh fried screw thank you for the
Super Chat thank you girls for the idol
presentation it was super fun and I
actually learned at least a little bit
about hello project good please check
them out like they really do have
awesome music I really love listening to
them
um I I was literally listening to them
all day yesterday and then I was
listening this um this morning while I
was getting ready
um Arthur thank you for the Super Chat
thank you guys for the lovely stream
really learned a lot the info was all
concise and easy to follow along with
felt like it could be a college seminar
ah yeah with the PowerPoint like
especially if it's like simplified
enough
so
uh amazing stream ophi as always weeaboo
thank you for the Super Chat you're so
sweet thank you
I'm surprised how long you avoided
PowerPoint
Zeta
thank you for this Super Chat and is it
impressive that I avoided PowerPoint
that long I think the last time I made a
PowerPoint
was it was for a book that I read I
think it was for this book called A
Wrinkle in Time and I was a kid
I was a kid with it
so I you know
if you are thank you for the Super Chat
uh no uh a Maddie donate uh five dollar
Super Chat thank you my brain is full of
cute Idol facts now thank you thank you
thank you for being here thank you for
coming
uh this street uh folk thing oh happy
happy four months fall happy four months
darling
thank you for being a poltergeist I hope
you
I I hope to have many more months with
you darling this stream was once
wonderful I fully enjoyed listening to
you three and still could have listened
for hours more I really hope for a part
two you three clapping again I like how
you match in your Chemistry you're so
sweet
I would love to of course like uh if a
schedule scheduling allows um you happy
eight months thank you
for you thank you for the Super Chat
everyone goes away tomorrow so I just
want to say thank you for being awesome
oh if you had a love learn had fun
learning about Idols with you pan and
Kiara thank you for the for thank you
for the for the message Darren's I
really appreciate it
um
easily followed the info retained zero
of it that you know what that's
completely valid whenever I used to
watch PowerPoints in school I would
never retain any of it so I was just I
would literally sit and clap okay I'm
very open about the fact that I was not
a good student so
um to me I guess this isn't anything new
but I used to like sit in class and just
listen to the PowerPoint and not really
retain any of it and then just learn on
my own time so if that's how you like to
learn or anything like that or like you
like to have a more personal exposure to
information please just go listen to
their music it's literally so fun and um
you know I think it's also a really good
representation of that individuality
that we kept talking about too so a
wrinkle in time is the special that
places my heart from growing up uh it's
such a good book isn't it but like I I
didn't read I don't read really
um
not because uh I don't I think like not
because I think reading is cringe or
something but I just don't have the um
like uh I guess not the time but um
uh I don't have the detention span to
read a book so
audiobooks my brain doesn't sit there in
a long and um for long periods of time
uh
Noida Maddie thank you for becoming a
member
no or a door when I love to see the
three of you having so much fun
scheduling timelines are the only
restraint from the tangents yeah I was
about to say I have such a bad habit of
going off topic so easily so I kept I
kept staying quiet for a lot of it and
just listening because I was like I know
if I open my mouth I'm gonna I'm gonna
get distressed
but happy four months Misfits thank you
oh Danny Denny happy wait not happy uh
no I mean I am happy
thank you darling thank you for becoming
a darling Phantasm thank you for
becoming a tier 3 member honey
got free chat it was a great stream I'm
glad I'm glad you enjoyed it happy four
months GD
four months here too and I'm Blown Away
how I've already been a ghosty for that
long I'm very grateful that I found this
awesome community that we have Sev
you're so sweet thank you honey thank
you I'm glad that you've been enjoying
your time here it's always a joy to have
all of you around and
um spend time with me it really
genuinely means a lot thank you for the
awesome collab and facts about Idols
clearly your PowerPoint skills are
something that can't be replicated yeah
because they don't exist
happy eight months Ricardo
there's no stranger to tangent so no
worries yeah well it's more so like I
didn't want to inconvenience the other
two because it was very it was very late
it was very very late and
um because like uh for me I had to wake
up really early and then they were
staying up pretty late and I was like I
was like I'm I'm gonna keep my mouth
shut uh unless I have something really
that I need to say
um because I I have this habit of like
if I have if I think of something to say
I need to say it but um I didn't want to
inconvenience them too much
um
mumbles happy two months Ophelia V
boober Queen tangents
I think I would share that title with
quite a few YouTubers I I always find
myself
um and have like a talking most with uh
YouTubers that are very tangent uh
tangent uh prone
thank you for restraining your tangent
power because the three would never
would it would be exponential and never
end otherwise yeah I even told I I'm
supposed I was supposed to have a
meeting and then I
and then I told and then I told staff
son I was like uh I don't know how long
it's going to be but I when the collab
is done it's done
you did great today love the stream
learned a bunch too I'm so glad and
happy three months Dominic I'm glad I'm
glad that you did genuinely we mean it
go check out hella project
time's gonna suck yeah exactly
um
I can only imagine a collab without such
strict timer constraints honestly if I
could just if we if I could have a
stream
actually no I was gonna say if I could
just if we could just like sit and have
a gazatsu that would be really fun
um but the problem is uh for anybody who
is new here
um I once scheduled a zazudon
and my managers roasted me they were
like why are you scheduling and I was
like well like because I want to talk to
them and they were like don't don't you
don't isn't every single one of your
streams of zatsudon isn't isn't every
single one like the game the game like
yeah you're playing a game but it's
really secondary
hello
you know
happy four months Skye
congrats amazing collab was lots of fun
the moments of tangents were so funny
you're also amazing wonderful oh
brooksie happy eight months thank you
tangent prone that's Kiara in a nutshell
yeah I'm also very I'm very tangent
prone something that I say quite often
is okay I will get back to the game in
just a second but let me finish this
thought or okay I need to get back to
this you guys I need to get back to this
like I am very I I've told the story
like one time I was playing Valhalla
in an entire stream I maybe played for
about 10 minutes and then it was just I
was just talking about everything and
doing everything but the game for four
hours because I kept getting enabled to
talk about it and I kept saying I have
to get back to the game but let me
finish this thought
the other sweethearts loved hearing how
passion you guys about Idols it's crazy
to think that this love perhaps brought
us together oh
I I genuinely like um
uh what's it called
I I very much like enjoy and admire the
love especially that they too the that
the two of them have for Idols it's
really lovely to to like see and listen
to I love listening to people be
passionate about things
um it's something that brings me joy so
it was really lovely
um
you again soon sometimes would be better
for next time that is true that is true
lunchbox
yeah they said why schedule azatsu
a credit card please notice me I showed
you my view
ER V boober I'm at your door why don't
you pay attention to me V boober
happy eight months Sarah Stefan is
ruthless just a smidge they're silly
there's stuff's on silly
Opie's streams are always satsu streams
there are no games what do you mean
I play games I played cuphead cuphead
counts like I didn't talk while I uh
that much I talked enough
foreign
pretty often in gaming alone yeah I get
that it's relatable
it's it's that it's relatable I felt it
Buffy worst enemy hardcore game which
cannot pass randomly okay
I'd have to pause cuphead in between
like during runs like I'd be fighting a
boss and I'd pause it halfway through
and be like okay let let me talk about
this and I talk about it for 10 minutes
and then I suddenly look at my screen
and remember that I was playing a game
okay I don't understand any First Strike
separation between game and zatsu that's
understandable
Opie's were like it just it's like it's
oh it's not a bad thing I think there I
I always like uh I always I consider
myself like um capable of listening or
not listening but being able to talk
about a lot of stuff like even if I
don't know a lot about it I feel like
I'm able to talk about it for a while
just because I'm also I'm also I love
like listening and learning new things
so
um
you know uh
so I I feel like that makes me a pretty
decent conversationalist
so
yeah uh Kiara's uh we orig it was
originally supposed to be we were only
it was supposed to be at an hour and a
half
um she was supposed to she needed to
bounce the Audi because uh she had to
catch her train
um
but uh what's it called
we were still on her slides uh from hers
uh so I think she I think she's getting
a taxi I hope uh but I do hope that she
makes it home okay
um
Okay so
speaking of 12-hour Marathon streams so
I have a bad habit not bad habit I have
a habit of doing endurance streams and
the thing is I said okay I said this to
staff son okay
this is really this is really important
okay so I told staffson I wanted to do a
12-hour stream I think it was for my
Christmas party and or I but then I had
to shorten it to six because I've been
really I was really I have been really
busy rather and so I was like okay I
have to shorten it to six hours because
we do 12 hours I'm not gonna have enough
time to do more work after the stream is
over
oh sheesh
um and after this so uh but I was like I
don't know that's really sh and they
were like okay that's pretty long and I
was like I don't know I think six hours
is pretty short out of I feel like six
hours is not that bad like I really
wanted to do a 12 hour Christmas party
but it just seemed like 12 hours wasn't
enough time either I so I just I just
picked six
and they were like you think 12 hours is
short and I was like yes
my click Plus show the new bait the
newbies baby mode Anya Keck booba Crush
okay okay if you're new here if you're
new here spam fire in chat
if you're new here spam firing chat if
you are a member
um spam rise and chat let me see it I
want to see I want to see the power no
12 isn't enough hours do you literally
if you give that's all like if you give
four hours each that's only three that's
only three different games
it's only three only three different
games
yes yes yes
let me see it let me see let me see the
fire
yes yes
[Music]
foreign
and then I think this is nope that's not
it this one
this one this one nope this one
this one
oh
which one's baby mode uh-oh this one
there it is hey
hi
[Music]
baby mode
foreign
[Music]
welcome to Baby mode
no I don't remember my toggles you think
I'm gonna remember my toggles
in English in the English anime I think
because I did a uh 10 characters in two
hours voice acting Challenge and I think
like one of the I think one of the lines
that Anya says was like they went to a
museum and then she says to Lloyd
um she goes Papa this one has boobies
because she's looking at her picture in
a museum
laughs
oh you want to know about the booba
crushing okay hold on I need to I need
to properly prep for this
okay if you want the booba crushing I
need you guys to spam
um
I want you guys ooh
I want you guys to spam
like some kind of like explosion emote
okay
hold on I'm gonna make this work
oh if you sound so natural with that
what do you mean because of the because
of the line
oh yes
okay
please perceive
this beautiful moment
uh uh
what
this goes here oh I see okay now we have
our beautiful our beautiful ghosties on
the screen
are you ready
three
two
two one
let's go
boom
[Laughter]
that's the booba crash
where am I I I'd have to look for you
there's so many of you I don't know if I
can find
foreign
[Laughter]
so there you go
it was requested and then also as
requested we do this also around here
um
we also do this around here
I do this thing called a mic lick where
someone does a ten dollar Super Chat
though and then I do a my click so
um I hope that
thank you for the Super Chat Ruka
uh so uh
uh this is I I don't want to the thing
is I the way that it works is that you I
usually don't tell you when I'm about to
do it because typically that means
um when uh I will no because that means
like you guys have time to mute it and
it's not as fun if you guys have to if
you guys mute it so
um I don't I don't I don't usually let
you know when it's gonna happen I missed
it wait what did oh you missed getting
crushed it's okay Sai
I can take care of you later hmm
[Laughter]
uh so but it and also with the Super
Chat you have to either allude to it or
you have to mention it clearly because
otherwise I just won't do it
um
so you're trying to hurt us you mean no
no no no I'm trying to cause uh some
form of either Whiplash well I guess
Whiplash is pain
it's love though it's it's affectionate
whiplash
it's
it's affectionate whiplash
um
it's affectionate
um so I hope that makes sense
[Laughter]
there you go
affectionate Whiplash it's it's what I
like to do here
um someone I think was it the other day
someone was like the greatest way to
explain Opie's dreams is just Whiplash
and I was like is that true and the
amount of people that were just like yes
laughs
it's a yandere type of love right
exactly I'm glad you understand thank
you my darling
yes there you go
there you go
thank you for this
we do have a Discord if you want to join
the Discord
um I hang out in there sometimes and
there's a bunch of people there's a
bunch of ghosties and it's just it's a
Discord that is shared with my uh my gen
mates as well but there's an Ophelia
section and you guys are more than
welcome to join if that's something
you're interested in uh the link is in
the YouTube description I think it was
emotional Whiplash I like affectionate
lip Whiplash because it's way more
um
I think it has more of a
more it's more maternally
um it's very much it's a lot more uh
matronly
um
oh my God how many more how many do I
have to do
bro
[Music]
come for the zatsu stay for the chaos I
yeah yeah I mean that if that's what if
that's what if that's what tickles your
fancy or uh floats your boat rather then
party hard
affectionate lip wash I mean I guess we
can call it lip wash I give you guys
enough kisses like
[Laughter]
oh my God
one more not the one
12 hour stream I
you guys
[Laughter]
oh my goodness oh my God
now it's two more I don't have a two
more emote one more time with feeling
yeah this time I Gotta Give it the old
College try
I'm supposed to just be reading the
super chats that that like is supposed
to be on screen or not on screen also um
for some reason my my list thing doesn't
show all of them
um so uh I apologize if I do miss one of
yours like if you gifted memberships or
uh donors or anything
um
I don't know why it doesn't sometimes
work but I I will I will do my best to
make sure I don't miss any
um
fried screw thank you for adding to the
pile of licks I appreciate it
better read quick at this rate I look
I'm trying hold on I I needed to pull up
the secondary list
okay hold on hold on hold on
okay yeah we okay thank you
okay so according to according to this
secondary list I haven't missed any
super chats okay
[Laughter]
okay super chats I'm I'm trying I'm
trying I'm trying I'm trying okay okay
pile of licks you might as well cut my
tongue off
can you imagine the day that I just I'm
not able to do this
like okay like you guys like I wouldn't
be able to do the my click thing anymore
you guys would have to live without it
and I'm sure you'd be okay I'm sure
you'll be fine
because it's not like all of me is gone
it's not like all of me is gone
today
my love is here to stay and I
[Music]
would have it no other way
yeah
okay oh my God
there's so many
all three of you are cute thank you
oh and first Opie reading supas on my
phone battery no no
fill out one lick to bully chat yeah
yeah we can so that means that means uh
fried screws
uh my click is gone
foreign
s
no more no more mic clicks that means
I'm done that means I'm caught up on the
mic clicks
it means you're it means it's over I
mean there are no more Mike licks needed
to be had
you're welcome
the canceled my click
I mean I mean yeah I guess I mean I it
the last one canceled out the previous
mic click so this will just replace it
I need like a sign or something
I need like a I need a sign
foreign
is that what you want
is that what you want you want my Clips
is that what you want me to do
is that is that three more is that three
more is that three more hmm
oh my darlings I hope you're ready
is that what you want is that what you
want to do hmm
literally
um
is that what you want
what are you gonna do hmm
what are you gonna do if I just decide
to
what if I just don't do it hmm
[Laughter]
What if I
what if I just sat here
ah Darlings
hmm
[Music]
my
you're all so cute
I can do what I want with you all
ah
I would have it no other way
[Laughter]
[Music]
I can't deprive you
oh but my darlings
I really could though
they're really really good
I wouldn't I don't I wouldn't even call
it depriving
I would call it playing with my food
[Laughter]
you want me to just sit here and play
with my food
foreign food my love I think it's the
same
the object of my affections
I think they're quite synonymous
they are synonymous take a breath mint
first Maybe
I'll pop one right now
you get to be in your mouth no no
darling I get to cover you in as many
kisses as I want right that's how that
works
or I could just sit here and stare at
you
[Laughter]
fellow City is it Velo City wow hello
hello Raiders hello boys welcome to the
stream hi
welcome
foreign
I was just talking about how I love how
my my the sweet ghosties front doors and
kfp in the chat however we're just
having a grand old time how we're just
how we're having a good little time
getting to know each other
thank you for the rate I hope you had a
wonderful stream
also Sona my darling it is totally okay
I'm sure that you'll enjoy the VOD when
it comes up
laughs
[Music]
we came in weird timing you did
thanks you're welcome
I hope you genuinely
despite all this I really do hope that
you guys check out a hello project
they're truly truly an incredible Idol
group and they mean a lot too I think
that hello project means a lot to a lot
of people
and I think that
uh I think that
they are a great
I think a great introduction to Idol
groups
genuinely
despite my appearance I know that might
not seem like it
but I do
I do hope that you guys check them out
can't wait to watch about congrats in
the club thank you thank you hon
um
oh I think I owe one more mic like no
that's for the Raiders
or maybe Asaf and shabir would like me
to dedicate that one to you hmm
would you like that maybe that one was
just for you
since you were so kind to raid me
[Music]
but anyway
anyway
so
there we go I did all the mic clicks
yeah I did all the mic clicks
it's screenshot of the recommendations
hell yeah you have you should let us uh
know like um what your favorites end up
being um
[Music]
so yeah but anyway since we caught up on
super chats
and memberships and everyone who gifted
memberships I saw that there were a
bunch thank you so much for gifting that
was really really kind of you
they want to be the new one of the
newcomers to know and what you were
capable of didn't mean to cause the
chain of licks No Lick here of course
this is a necessity and I wouldn't and
it wouldn't be enough anyway I I see the
nine I see the 98 cents Zayn
being extra Tosca do today hmm
well maybe I could be a little extra
toss Guardian for you huh honey
but uh thank you all for the for all the
gifted memberships and everything
um okay before before another train of
train of
of things appear oh holy cow
oh
wowie zowie
[Laughter]
um thank you guys for the memberships uh
according to this we're at 500 members I
always give the membership count at the
end of the stream so
um thank you thank you holy sh holy [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
500 members what the [\h__\h] thank you so
much
yeah
what
that's insane
I'm gonna cry what the [\h__\h]
thank you
that's really nice thank you guys
whether you guys whether you've been
gifted a membership or if you joined
membership today or anything like that
just um
thank you that's really really kind it
was really a 500 even no no no it's like
over by like two so it's 502 not not
over by two am I okay
um but thank you thank you that's like
uh genuinely that's really really kind I
really do appreciate it
adding to Zayn from Mike like no that's
all right that's too much Ricardo
they didn't it's two cents they it was
two cents off not two not two pounds off
yeah
foreign
I don't know if that's how that works
maybe you need a nap I might need a nap
um I I have some things that I need to
do after this I actually have a meeting
in a little in um a little while so
um that's that's a big thing but
um yeah thank you just thanks that was
really kind I didn't expect to see that
number actually
um so just thank you I
I wish I had more words than just thank
you but I hope that I hope that um
my my gratefulness comes across even
just by saying thank you
um
um but also thank you really quickly to
my tier three members uh Denny flute fro
goat outcaster flash Omni Zane Harper
brooksie Highway Q Ranger damper wall
Vara and Ricardo thank you guys for
being my tier three members as always
here are your kisses like
[Laughter]
Tony oh my gosh already two my clicks
again
okay
there
there's one I will and then I'll do a
second one in a bit
um
but uh
thank you guys thank you for the super
chats um I really I really really truly
appreciate it
um really quick announcements
um
uh the digital merch I have digital
merch I think that today yes today is
the last day for my holiday voice pack
so if you like listening to my voice
um the I have a digital pack that that's
out right now today is the last day to
get it you can find the link for that in
the YouTube description
um
and uh it's a little goofier than my
previous voice packs but I don't think
there will ever be a rerun of it either
so this is your last opportunity to grab
it and
um tomorrow will be the last day to get
physical merch the link for that is in
the YouTube description as well so if
that is something you're interested in
uh feel free to go for it please do not
feel obligated by any means
um
I uh
if you are able to please enjoy and and
please do not feel
um bad if you are unable to get it at
the moment I'm sure we'll be having more
merch in the future and
um
uh I'm trying to think
um oh and then tomorrow so if you are
new to this channel I do a series called
how to sound like uh I do a how to sound
like Series where I study the uh vocal
patterns and um the structure and
idiolact uh V tubers
um because Ina is coming back from her
Hiatus uh tomorrow we are going to be
studying Ina's voice
um to celebrate her return
um because I thought I just thought it
would be really nice to
um celebrate that because I know it's
been a couple months
um since uh the takodachis have been
able to watch
um an Ina stream so
um
uh uh I I thought it would be super
duper fun so
um you know Ina to celebrate her return
um
we are going to be studying her voice
tomorrow so if that is something that
you're interested in we get into the
Linguistics of it
um structure of where sound comes from
in your in your body not just your face
but sound does come from large parts of
your other parts of your body as well
and
um the uh I introduced this thing called
The International International Phonetic
Alphabet
um during those times and we get to
watch clips and I get to do a breakdown
of what I'm personally hearing
um and talk about like the geographical
things and introduce new concepts of
what makes up your voice and so
um it'll be super duper fun it'd be
it'll be tomorrow and
um
so if you um if that's something that
you're interested in I hope that I get
to see you tomorrow
um
and uh I'm trying to think I'm trying to
think what else am I missing oh also
next week I'll be going on vacation I'm
going to be going to I'm oh I'm going to
be going to I am going to be traveling
uh with my family I'm going to be
um
I'm going to be traveling with my family
I'm going to be go I'm going to go see
um some
um some shows and things with my family
and spend time with them I haven't had
um I haven't had like a vacation since I
debuted so I think that this will be a
lot of I think this would be really nice
I told myself that I would I told myself
that I would go on vacation when
um
I
uh when the New Year began so
um it'll be it'll be good and I will
tell you all about it when I get back
but um if uh I just want to give that
heads up because it will reflect in my
schedule when it comes out uh tomorrow
would this be your first break yes it
would be my it'll be my first like break
because um anytime I've taken a break
before quote unquote break it was
because the first time I got coved and
so I was out for like a week because I
was I had covid the second time I was
out was because I moved and even then I
shoved all my streams together right the
day before I moved took three or four
days to move
as fast as I could and then even though
I would it wasn't I wasn't in a suitable
place to be streaming I still streamed
anyway
um for everybody so
[Music]
um
so I haven't gone on a real vacation and
so I think
um this will be this will be really fun
and I'm excited to go do it and I'm
excited to tell you guys about it when I
come back so
um
I think that's all of my announcements I
don't think that there's anything else
mods can you guys confirm whether or not
that I'm missing anything I don't think
so
laughs
[Music]
um but anyway uh regardless
um thank you so much everybody
um for spending time with me thank you
so much for if you are kfp and you're
new here
um thank you for taking the time to come
join the three of us uh for this collab
and if you decided to stick around after
um uh Miss Kiowa and Miss Pandora had to
um had to leave
um thank you for sticking around and
letting me chat with you I appreciate
that as well and
um
I'm trying to think uh uh just yeah I
looked if and um and if this if you had
a good time I I hope that I get to see
you again I look forward to getting to
know you more if you're new here and
um I look forward to uh you know all of
that fun good stuff that we can do
together but anyway
um that being said if you guys haven't
please consider liking this dream it
helps me out a ton and when the stream
ends I'm going to be raiding my the
waiting room for my vocal study stream
tomorrow so please come back to this VOD
and comment on it it helps me out a ton
and also
um
also everybody in the chat say hi to
void gang
um void gang if you've made it this far
thank you so much for watching the VOD I
really appreciate it thank you for
letting me be part of your day and
um uh you know whether I'm in the
background or something you're actively
watching I really do appreciate it and
as always if you guys want to we do have
a Discord server so
and so if I don't see you in tomorrow's
stream I will see you in the Discord
server you can find the link for the
Discord server in the YouTube
description and if I don't see you in
the Discord server I will see you on
Twitter and if I don't see uh you on
Twitter then I will see you when I see
you my darlings so I hope that you all
have a lovely lovely weekend I hope that
I get to see you later if I don't then I
hope that
um that I wish you all the best my
darlings
what's the healthy everybody what's the
Elfie
bye bye
[Music]
foreign