e
n
[Music]
[Applause]
e
[Music]
[Applause]
l
[Music]
[Applause]
yes ah
[Music]
okay oops
oops good morning good afternoon good
evening good night good night hello
hello
J can you hear me yeah I'm sorry I'm a
big cat I'm sorry I don't fit the screen
I don't
fit so big
I threw water on me [\h__\h] one sec I want
to
drink oh guys um can you hear any
difference to my audio because I I was
like I did some settings
and I I changed some settings I do you
hear me
better
hello m
hello G Geto oh my god let's go actually
I'm going
to stay here okay hi
everyone mus mush oh I M it mush
mush you picked up my car good time yeah
hello
do do you do you want to do the dungeon
together yeah I think I need to make the
quest first the the main quest first do
you have to do that too we have
investigate the Ocean Temple dungeon and
speak to the Scarlet Wand G oh I need I
need to I need to go on the quest if you
want to wait for me a little bit oh okay
I don't know I can't remember what quest
H the quest to get to the dungeon
actually M you have to go a little bit
for a few quests and and then you get
access to uh the
dungeon if you guys want to wait for me
I think it's going to take not too long
but if you want to go if you want to go
feel free to and maybe we can do it
again together I don't know when where
you going to go we can meet you there oh
I I I I think oh okay okay I see you
there bye-bye okay
[Music]
okay you seeing
where hello
I was talking to M uh the
phone uh what are your plans I want to
do you want to do the ding together I
need to make the quest yeah yeah you
want to make a
party yeah yeah were were you going to
go with Muk no no no I told them if they
if they want to go later we can go all
together but now I need to make my
quests oh okay yeah yi
yi all right I think then we can go
together in a moment um okay I'm I'm I'm
smelting some iron right now the side
quest okay okay okay I'll wait for you
don't worry I follow you okay yeah oh
can I call you on the phone so we have
we do the party call oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah uh if you however um are seen with
me uh can you pretend I am in the Jade
Guild
okay it seems that people are have
something out for the Amber corinn Guild
and because it is dangerous um right now
to be in the ambercoin guild okay where
am I then well I'm not sure if they when
they see you if they immediately know
already that you're in the ambercoin
guild if they don't you can also
probably pretend to be in the Jade Guild
I am in the Jade okay
okay oh wait We call we do the call we
do the
call calling
me by the way I watched a clip of you
and crony like a really long a long
version the Tim tandis and I literally
snort it because it was so fun I was
like I can't recreate it this so
funny yeah I generally didn't understand
was was talking about
it
bartender she cannot know that I am
in what are you Whispering about oh
hell Jonathan
J
murderer what I didn't do
anything yesterday you were talking
about how you wanted to kill everyone H
what why you would put such words in my
mouth what are you talking about Jordan
I would not put words in your mouth you
said it you said said it with your own
words you said you wanted everyone to
die what are you talking about why are
you guys light everyone yeah gasl her
gasl her why is she gaslighting everyone
I'm not gaslighting you you are trying
to why you gaslighting me gas you know
who said that wanted to kill the king
said you know what you know what you
know who said wanted to kill the king
you you said it you said it you said it
I you say it with your own bra you said
it oh my God I can't believe this girl
like
oh my
Mia what is all of this
oh oh I can cook now as you can cook
iron yeah like it looks so fancy I've
never seen this
[Music]
before away from me
murck kill me G how was I'm not allow
you to kill come here come here come
here I want to I want to I want I want
to do something come here come here come
here be come here come here come here
come here come here come here come here
come here come here come here hurt me
come here come here come here you
promise hurt I promise I promise come
here come here come here come here come
here come here come here closer okay now
you
kneel why I just want to do something
what you kneel I will not kneel to the
likes of you
come here come here come here come here
come here kneel I will only kneel to the
Queen the true Queen come here Tam
Gander come here come here come here you
mean Tim tender come here no Tam Gander
her name iser Tim tenderer
tender Jonathan come here come here come
here come
here do
it why do it trust me why you trust me
do it
yeah I'm your queen
now phone
call
what
what but
but cutie cat I I have
to um be honest I I actually support Tim
tender to be the
contender number one for the queen
it
it's it's okay oh
hello hello listen listen car listen to
me listen yes yes I am a better Queen
than
Bender Bender listen you cannot support
you cannot support
that um I don't I I have to because like
she seems to have the power to save
people from the scammers I save people
from the scammer too and and I also I as
destroy the scammers in fact I actually
want to kill all the
scammers oh okay okay yeah all right I I
if if I see in an action I shall I shall
support whoever brings Justice she is a
SC she's a SC
here got got to believe me yeah I I mean
I would believe you she did she did
however say that she is um she [\h__\h]
uh she's [\h__\h] I'm telling you she is
[\h__\h] she is
[\h__\h] trust
me what what is she F [\h__\h] fake oh
she's trust
me I need to have more evidence I you'll
see you'll see I'll build my castle and
we'll see yeah I I did think uh that she
like left us for good and is with the
Scarlet people but uh then she told me
that she's just a secret agent so what
I'm not sure I told you she's a
scammer I also make nice SC I also I
also make nice uh pasta for my citizen
so citizens citizen so I'm like I have
something uh more than her therefore I
am you even have a cooking pot
I do no you don't I have the cooking
[Music]
pot that's not your business girl where
I put my my cooking where I where I cook
it's my business
[Music]
now
okay uh oh yeah so I'm I finished my
cooking side quest so now we the main
quest says gather 10 rainbow cor we
where we ended yesterday remember
uh-huh
uh-huh how do how does it even work a
cook
a
a what is work it's not finished ah wait
does it go
here no does I'll make the side quest
later mhm I don't know how this works is
there a
manual go back to the tab and
doesn't even know how to tell a quest
wait I think I was doing this the same
side quest as you like I gave a cake to
a chef at some point I don't remember ah
wait it is indeed not completed uh
oopsie God damn it okay it's okay it's
okay take your time the chicken tenders
in a chicken
tenders y ah the
chef the chef
chef oh oh e col you've brought my new
cooking pot with a cooking pot you can
cook delicios food wherever you are
indeed okay and
now oh ah here take this recipe book it
will tell you the ingredients you need
to make each dish just put them into
your handy cooking pot then B
up
yeah oh thank you so much I'm going to
I'm oh wait there's more and also take
this egg and beetroot you can combine
them with ingredients you brought to
make potato salad give it a try oh oh
wait I was doing the the potato cot
Quest too oh yeah but you you probably
didn't finish it right no no no I
haven't finished I left off wa was so
tired okay wait here's the recipe book
interesting I need more I need a lot
task bar
thingy we are in a call so recipe book
potato salad potato egg carrot B
beetroot carrot nourishing soup carrot
potato sweet berries water bucket milk
bucket for butter and this is all too
much
effort lasagna there's a lasagna a wait
what is the cooking for in this just for
better food I guess
[Music]
I feel like we might run out of food
eventually too so maybe not because we
get the meat from the enemies raw C RW
salmon potato butter breakfast toast
bread and that's what I can use a slime
Jam for seafood Ramen o chocolate cake O
A lot of these ingredients I would have
no idea if we can find
them but okay button Kebab ra mutton
bread beet butter
beetroot oh don't hurt your horsey want
to go up
there what's
there are you muted
no I was
exploring okay and I was listening to
your beautiful Italian accent oh than
ah okay um wait help what I still didn't
finish it did I still not finish
it Chef what do you
want oh they want me to make the potato
salad otherwise it's not finished G
potato potato egg carrot beetroot where
do I get the beetroot I have to buy it
the what
beetroot what is it I gave all of it to
me he did
oh okay
so beetroot potato
carrot I only have this egg I don't see
any other egg ah here blind and now Ah
that's when it turns
green wow oh it gives Buffs you me not
just oh it get Buffs jump boost to 30
minutes this is so powerful yummy it
looks good looks I guess I for example
of the dungeon we did yesterday there
was a lot of jumping involved it would
be easier with that
maybe M just spent 680 coins for 68
tickets oh my God wait what she did moku
got scammed big time why wait what is
about scammers now the lottery scam oh
no the lottery
scam spent 68 coins for
what for lottery at uh foundas
establishment no oh my
god oh now now they're going to scam
shieldy what
complete okay Chef last time we talk
hopefully uh ah okay
oh oh I have seven Lucky Seven maybe I
should use all of those at the lot no no
no
assist I have
777 coins
now and I finished my side quest finally
we can go let's go
yay okay so we start with the um main
quest right yeah I think we left off
yesterday at the same spot yeah the
other 10 rainbow corals can you double
check on your
book H oh no no it says rainbow Coral
shards yeah 10 of them and then speak to
the squ I think we just go to the same
place
again
um but wait how do we get out of here
freaking oh no no it's the other side
it's the other side it's the other side
okay I do
remember okay I was just following the
rubi's marker oh okay I think we can go
no no wait I'm
lost oh more I'm going to go moreo one
second
mhm
um there you
[Music]
go I didn't
forget oh I'm still not done with the
quest so maybe like you can go to the
dungeon and then if you want to join me
later we can we can we you can also help
me later
you sure yeah I'm sure it takes a little
while probably so don't worry about me
if you can find a if you if you find a
party go for it and if you not find a
party we go together later together okay
and Elizabeth and I right now okay okay
that's good then if you want to join
just let us know okay you can follow me
again okay okay thank you so much for
calling me byebye if you follow me again
byebye byebye
byebye kid what what what what did M
want to do with you she wanted to make
the dungeon with me but I said I'm not
done with the quest H she can if it's
just her she can probably join us no
because she already she she already
found a party that's what she told me oh
yeah
yeah okay let's go oh
[Music]
hello listen for horse
noises it's this way I'm going to
cook where are we all going yeah let's
go way ah we're back in the call back in
the call okay are you out oh yeah you
are
yes
hello
h i Follow You
Yes actually this is not the right there
is it the right there Direction no no
the other way I was following
them is it this way right yeah yeah yeah
wow how do you remember hey no no is
that is that no it's even farther that's
the other
one no it's over there it's over there
no HH really no no you're not no
invisible
wall is maybe it was where they
went okay follow me follow me I think I
know okay
okay just yeah it's over
there okay making these horses jump is
so
useless wait
uh can I
[Music]
me
check this place is so
big I think that's another dungeon
though
no oh is it oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay yeah yeah yeah okay so it was
rubious ni very pretty very C
guess
jio
Jun is it here
oh
no is it this one I don't think
so is
it oh no it was this one actually okay
it's not scary
get are you mut it's deep it's very
[Music]
deep who how did that happen I finally
did the thing that you've been
doing my father's cousins sisters
they're
Rel you don't have this
hat where the master oh did that oh gosh
did I unlock a a painful memory
it's not a good is
H oh yeah he's somewhere else he's like
get it again I think he's
uh
[Music]
over through the
portal and then I guess back in the
city is it mhm
okay this really feels like an mmpg
this is this is scratching the
itch eh I want to play real MMR pg2
which one do you
like I want to play I thought you
playing blue protocol yeah
but blue protocol is dead because
they're closing the servers and they're
not even doing the English server
anymore they cancel their
plans ah so sad I was waiting for that
game for so long and then got can me too
yeah rubius are you in
here we got to follow rubius probably I
think I found him yeah over here oh yeah
finally I'm still the
entrance oh okay you just got to follow
the mini map
okay uh wait
yes I have found the coral shards let's
go upon receiving word from my colleague
on the coast I immedately set about
making the necessary preparations for
crafting with these shards you have
brought the preparations are complete
now if you will give me but one moment
ooh let's go I found for fun I want to
play Fly for
Fun is there another MMO you would
recommend
like e like not only old ones really M
no at the moment I'm playing um Maple
stor yeah I know H I kind of want to
join you guys if you want to join please
H we can we can Farm together but maple
story is like h a bit it looks very
overwhelming to me it is very
overwhelming I'm going to lie it's not
like the kind of Adventure
MMO you probably looking for because
it's a lot about grinding and stuff no
but I like grinding I like grinding m
but it shouldn't only be grinding uh we
have to go to the dungeon now oh really
okay yeah that was all we had to do oh
that's weird
okay let's go I'm going to follow you
uh wait do we go the same yeah we have
to go
back uh maybe we can call someone and
see if someone wants to join us since we
the thing is it's maximum five people
right and most most uh group most guilds
are already five people by
default
they're and B if they no B is not B's
not
online yeah if she you know it seems
like she's sticking with the the other
girls but if she wants to
come let's see who is there maybe maybe
we can find someone over there oh I call
oh sorry oh
[Music]
hello
hello hello
hello how was the D car of the oranges
oh which is the big
cat we are about to go to the dungeon
now get off the we are about to go to
the dungeon now are you done already
yeah we the dungeon yet we have to go
talk to
Rubi rub is it you
free we're going to go Elizabeth but
Elizabeth yet Elizabeth doesn't have the
rainbow Coral that's okay it doesn't
take very long but like how about we
five go together
yeah do
it that is fine with me orange maiden
and your name is okay okay can I the
part
Shar Shakira I I leave my party now I am
Elizabeth nice to me yes we have already
touched sword tips before you remember
Don you can invite me yes but we did not
exchange names we just exchange tips it
seemed which is the first thing you
should do as a night I
hear um I'm not really sure cuz uh I
don't know about you but i' I've lost a
lot of my memories you you guys feel
free to um proceed with your quest will
wait for you at the dungeon yeah at the
entrance yeah okay Shakira you
soon I have found a new nickname uhhuh
cuz tanaki Shakara is too complicated
for people so short for it is Shakira
[Laughter]
Shakira nothing wrong in the call should
we still be in the call oh yeah sure
sorry the can you not do a call I think
I thought could do a call with like uh
the whole party oh yeah we probably
can when when we meet them we call the
party
okay my Hips Don't Lie yeah hey I lost
um wait there is a wa okay wait one
second one second let me try
[Music]
this Mo this can I
not can you wall
yeah oh now I can
okay it's not what one second um I
[Music]
saw land I want
this
way oh they're making a boat
cool GAA can naturally swim of
course
oh I didn't know I could steal
that click on your phone
and click join
party
c yeah click on your phone and then push
the right the one on the right side that
says join party
call
yeah do
it right click and uh yeah part join
party yeah yeah yeah okay okay now the
others if they do it will all be in the
party C yippee a that's how it works got
it
nice okay and now we
wait
Atlantis the Atlanta
dungeon
tles just like in New York test the part
I don't think there's there's no part
yet huh there's only
like
mans would be cool if we had a party
chat my CH is Frozen one
[Music]
second
my Atlanta has a lot more water than I
would think
yeah Atlanta I thought you were not by
the
ocean I thought you were kind of
in the middle of the country guys I see
you spamming stop just because the chat
is
frozen wow s is private
M see
[Music]
it oh my God look at
them look at them there you go
B
wow I love whispering to people in in
them more
PG
hello I did about at the coast but
somehow everybody got lost when I
a there you go well I hear I even though
there's just one paaa I hear two two
dogs in my ear sometimes it's funny I
don't
know what I don't know how it happens
you
[Music]
know and I look very similar but I don't
know have you found anybody else that
looks very similar to you
here similar yes
Jonathan Jonathan yeah she's orange like
me Jonathan G Jonathan G we need to go
again
the one who just died
hello you made it hello there Fair Cat
hello Elizabeth I think you need to talk
to Corin here maybe
yes know remember also Elizabeth H
Elizabeth of the long sword would you
like to try uh right clicking your radio
and then pressing join party call with
more
really uh join party I did it yes good
job I'm excited for the
dungon yeah
py py Pony
pony very excited for some reason it
wanted I got confused at first cuz uh I
I just suddenly really wanted to trade
with you you know cuz you were in front
of
me want to trade your sword with me I
just had uh I I know I kind of like my
sword I kind of like
oh man unless you just really want to
dual wield no yeah oh dual wielding that
sword damn be difficult I'd love to no
it's like I noticed that you can
actually cook stuff with this
furnace oh you can cook stuff on the
fire too yeah I'm going to go expl
okay oh I'm going to exp are we are we
all okay foodwise because I have some
food on me if anybody wants I have be
fine2
M why are you moo actually why why would
you spend all of your money on the
scammers what
[Music]
you it's
okay you money tomorrow were you
alone no what's the feel
were they with you why did they not did
you girls not realize it's an obvious
scam phone call and final Mar was
open you are so scammed no I got tickets
for tomorrow yeah you're not really
going to win much at all number so f is
helping me with that I think I got a
good couple of them oh
well
um I will pray for you but uh I don't
need your prayers thank
you I don't need your
prayers thank you
orange orange Shakira please
Shakira Shakira orange so before you go
adventuring over there now going
here here what oh Elizabeth explore and
find a dungeon yeah I think it's this
way I think Elizabeth needs a special
the special
[Music]
mustard the
cluster the rainbow the here I have to
get 10 rainbow Coral shards it's it's
the blue ones here oh I see and they
regrow wor that's
easy this is a little bit too simple the
catch uh the catch is just that you have
to go all the way back to the city after
you collected these oh
wonderful materials for my castle Shaka
I have to say um if it isn't too forward
your hips are quite
hypnotizing I was born like
this you remember
yeah uh I'm I'm a bit different from all
of you girls because uh I just like
literally die every once in a while and
and I lose my memories but I regain them
because I'm a phoenix you know it
happens often to meing wow I am getting
free blocks Phoenix yes what I'm getting
blocks so I can build my house later you
are amazing Shakira thank you Elizabeth
you your broke yes I do uh so I have to
go all the way back to the Scarlet W
yeah I can accomp my pickaxe
broke I I mean it is fine if you do not
wish to make the journey if it's too
much of a bother okay let's let us
travel then
okay without me okay what's wrong my
pickaxe broke where where did you fall I
found a bad place
huh this is the dungeon here right wait
for us um I'm just going back to deliver
the coral and then yeah almost done a
dungeon it'll only be a
moment Mak what have you
found nothing I found out that this is
not the
dungeon I made it back I swim
look what did you just
do why did you break it so she knows the
way oh by the way what uh Elizabeth what
what guil do you belong to I am part of
the same one as the The Fluffy one and
the fuzzy one which is sword it turns
out I am uh kind of part of your guilt
now I hope that's okay yeah me too me
too why I did not even know that was
possible Mory copine has um invited me
so to say um
as I was have aligned I see I was in a
little bit of a pickle as they say in my
home Home Country everybody go you see
this
oh
oh where where did everybody
[Music]
go everybody we're going
down
oh
oh yeah
no I'm here behind you behind you behind
you come here come
here let's go explore bues earlier and
explore where did you
go doesn't say on my mouth what is this
maybe we want to find that treasure no
there's actually nothing there's nothing
here you sure
yeah that's so
sad the path I was expecting to find
something I don't oh it's shiny here is
this the right way maybe to the cor I'm
coming before we get forever oh the
water okay I found the way back up oh
good job what is that
thing what a cool guy we can go up from
here maybe yes I have the Cor
okay uh we shall
return let's go ride
weird the here where did everybody else
go how do we go over here we
can't I
[Music]
forgot
you I'm here
wait I found a way I found a way you
found a way I don't know I I think I
found I've forgotten the Navigator where
is
everybody I'm chopped I like how just
ignores all of
this I don't know I I have I have this
feeling uh it brings back
memories of hearing stuff like this and
just rolling with
it can can you make your War my I guess
I'm just used to it
Shira me can can you hear you
wait the because it's a little confusing
one sec it's okay we're coming now we're
coming we we're nearly there no no no
don't worry
because what you do you might need to
you might need to open your your magic
books and transport where'd you get
stuffff
[Music]
dropped let's open the magic book and
let's go outside okay magic book yeah on
the third page on the fourth page it
says uh no wait what is it it says
what water or I don't know what happened
to them just so this means I can breathe
underwater now party this party this is
amazing how do we respond
H what didn't realize I don't know oh
page
three so P three yeah this is amazing
okay no we cannot it doesn't
work it
works if only we had a swimming
attire oh yeah it's not good to soak my
armor and my beautiful
clo so soggy thank god let's find
everyone smells like wet dog
here a little bit I'm sorry not you not
you oh you mean ah yes ha you're very
funny
Shak
back let's swim
where's
there okay now we can go
can go okay I'm going to put is it this
way yeah it's probably that way oh do I
need the
coral I think we're good just as we are
oh maybe we can make like a boat oh
let's make a boat I know how to make it
come here come here come here A B I make
a boat I make two bats I mean we learned
how to uh breathe on the water but sure
let's make a boat a boat okay this is
for you
[Music]
this is from oh no actually I need to
trade you guys the boat one second oh
okay okay I'm going to trade one for FL
and C okay okay but we need three boats
then and this one why do we need boats
we we really don't we really
don't thank you you're welcome and I
make another
one and
pie oh sorry tra there go accept
my and this one oh thank
you and Lia you want to come with
me yes I I would join
you okay you it's okay it's okay I'm now
I'm in the boat I've never been on a
boat before no how do we go forward on
the
boat one sec girls why are you standing
on come here come here come come with me
my queen come okay let's
go
Queen oh I don't know I had laps I don't
know why I called you like that I am the
queen
here ah yes you are the queen of the
boat I want to become I want to become
the queen of
liasan let's go I'll make you going to
marry that little King yeah I want to I
I don't want to marry the king I want to
be I want to be a single
queen why are we talking about marrying
the king I think she wants to kill the
king I want to kill the king come unle
wait I want to take a picture of all of
us on the
boat
stop it look up
up cute okay a beautiful let's go okay
where are we going this way follow the
lights the on
what this is where I want to be let's go
is there right here no we want to go we
want to go look at the map look at the
map oh
right oh it's that way yeah that way is
this is nice this is
comy
see I think this is better than swimming
please please yeah if I kill the king
what you what you
me uh I'm pretty loyal to the the Jade
sword and we are loyal to our Lord
Abandoned Ship an empty boat oh a
shipwreck what happened look like we're
not the only ones who had the ship idea
the boat do we have to swim now I don't
think so I'm so bad at this get out of
the
boat I don't think so I see nothing here
how do I get oh everybody has there's a
wall there but
how do I get out of the boat oh with
shift uh sorry sneak maybe oh goodbye
boat we can't go there I think we have
to go oh we can't what the
heck I'm going the wrong way hi where
did your girls go
oh huh
huh there's an invisible World though
there is a an invisible wall keeping
us in the distance yeah Elizabeth is
right there's an invisible wall get back
to the
boat I I think back to the boats is best
I can swim in the
boat oh okay wait is it there
no wait for some reason I'm not
drawing what you mean you're drowning
not Dr yeah because of the coral
Coral you know the rainbow Coral we have
yeah yeah yeah
yeah yes it's magical it helps us
breathe
underwater I have a feeling maybe the
entrance is
through uh yeah the building over there
where's Big oh I'm lost the temple
looking small building this one over
this way yeah where the lamps were
guided
maybe I don't know am I going the right
way maybe we shouldn't have skipped all
the dialogue
yeah
skip
ah I don't know why I thought that I
should get into a boat where you uh the
one controlling
it to the left to the left wait wait
don't leave me behind one sec I thought
it's I don't know where you are
uh I honestly don't know either but we
got to try I'm find I'm going to find
you yeah let's let's go let's go over
there where are them okay it's not here
I found you not really yeah did you look
hello did you look thoroughly not
thoroughly okay we must look thoroughly
okay we need to find the
dungeon H I have the feeling that it's
underwater because why would they make
us like
yeah actually yeah what would they make
us like breath under the water if it was
not under the water
no yeah
uh uh big cat let us go underwater and
see if there's anything under here okay
I
fall I mean there's some there's some
ruins over here underwater big
cat it te my God eyes to
see God eyes
see if I can find
it oh what is this over here this big
hole here in the ground oh yeah there
find something yeah if you just go to
the lamps and then go on water you may
find a big hole leading deeper and
deeper look for a big hole in so like
arrows there's Arrow literally oh I see
Elizabeth solid
ah there we go that's a good way of
showing you where I am it down down down
down by the
arrows there we
go oh so
cool can't see my map can you see it
okay
down
what oh oh wow I made it through oh gosh
there's a whole extra world
good job ladies
hello okay there we are so many nice
beautiful Jam Stones
yeah I'm
wor I'm where we going I wonder if we
can dig down here as well uh the the
Diamond we need the iron pickaxe for the
diamond but true we can come back here
for digging at a later time maybe this
is so cool I didn't expect to find a big
thing behind like under the sea so
cool
Elizabeth you made it water anymore no
are we all
together all together okay let's go
let's
go
more are you okay
foodwise yeah I have lots of bread oh no
I need to
eat n n n n n n n n good job I I have
potato
salad no worries
[Music]
here okay ready up
everybody
yeah ready ready up ready up wait a sec
it doesn't make me
click okay done
done
okay nice
what is this place so
beautiful it's so
cool oh the water what I thought there'd
be more water it is beautiful it is so
nice wow look at those blue
trees I stood at the Pinnacle of
civilization but
then one had taken a thousand years to
build was rased in a single
M catastrophe which
catastrophe oh so beautiful this place
is Big
it's what wow it's a blue tree and
thought is a purple tree somehow somehow
a lot of this looks or feels very
familiar to me I'm not sure
why like as if I've been here
before m
those fish well I wouldn't put it where
are the fish fish there's a big fish I
could believe that Shira with all our
memories being taken mhm a new
checkpoint unlocked what is this for
that's right huh this is
Burger rle time okay not
sure it go fiz go fiz can we change the
direction of this h no
interesting what it's not making
card oh those are arrows I didn't know
this before yeah how do you make it like
this no it
[Music]
go okay so we
have oh wait wait
[Music]
wait I don't see anything happening can
we both press the right direction at the
same time oh
yeah three two
1 nothing happened you press the wrong
one maybe no I didn't the right one
right direction you this one I want to
check if there's a more there are more
butons around maybe not
[Music]
actually this this is H suspicious
M so we
have a few
blocks
huh just by randomly pressing everything
let's
go
uh put it back put it back yeah yeah
yeah yeah
oh oh wait wait wait stop
stop where do we want it oh we want
stacking we're playing the stacking game
oh green has to go first yes green has
to go next you can actually climb the
wines so we want to climb the wines you
know the yellow oh yeah green one in the
middle yeah it's the
biggest that over can I try can I try to
I want to try moving something too okay
oh okay I see the yellow to move though
how do yeah how do we get the maybe the
put the red one right to the very side
yeah yeah yeah over
job wow good
job easy it took us a while to
understand I don't understand but for me
didn't
worked is tricky I like this
riddle there's in here I think I think
this is the next three though no oh this
no did anything happen maybe there's an
oh I was going to say maybe there's an
invisible path but apparently
not no it just was this must have
triggered something that just for fun
maybe it was ahead we triggered a button
something ahead maybe it's okay maybe
yeah did we not have to do that maybe we
did I guess it did open a door some oh
yeah it did open the door yes it must do
oh wait my map is now
up the logo
just go I had the same thing happened
just now I just I took out my
map yet where one people had been wiped
out another took his place and lived a
new happy and peaceful life this place
is so boring perhaps even a bit too
peaceful I'm getting out of here you'll
see after day the little girl planned
her Great
Escape oh little girl little girl h
this is a big big girl Great Escape oh
we need everybody here okay we can get
let's
go that's the
important it's okay because if I if I
don't eat now I don't I'm going to just
respond time reading the lord it's
important yeah it's important take it
all in take it all
in I want to eat
go enjoying I'm enjoying the story
yeah it's good to enjoy stuff these
trees are crazy I
agree we
Flex o a
interesting what is this am I jumping
more
[Laughter]
my jump are isn't it good in this realm
we we can come back to life jump
jump oh I broke it there was a bat in
here am I jumping
higher no oh no I am I am a little bit
right minimal nothing changes though
what's going on doesn't even stand out
so did this not do anything oh leave
that leave that there we go oh over here
a
hey what
happened oh it was only 30 seconds oh
whoops yeah yeah I think it had a
timer I I had timer or maybe my my hand
slipped I'm sorry happen if I pressed
that fair Maiden I I you're a phoenix I
thought you could fly um uh I was just
trying to fit in you know this
the yellow bridge I thank you for trying
to like be with be with us peasants you
know on the ground he is what if I go
over there and I click this again maybe
something changes in the other side
maybe oh the yellow Bridge disappeared
again oh is there a blue or a
green one that we can press in front of
us but we can't well there's a
red oh that resets it I see yeah it's
it's button has the own bridge this one
ISD wait what happened there oh maybe
here hey hey hey oh it goes
away nice how did that go away because I
I clicked the button I clicked the
button I clicked the button over there
oh you clicked the button
yeah the Red Bridge started the Red
Bridge uh it's like a puzzle see if see
if that button does anything I can go
touch it touch it again the green one
yeah okay oh the red
one we have to
do we have to do like back and forth
touch the other one wait touch the
yellow one oh gosh that was close not
very safe work environment again please
touch it again okay wait don't touch
anything
okay oh yellow oh we just need this bit
to go away I the red one
here oh don't touch
anything knows what I'm doing okay I
have another level here should I press
it going to press it I need the red
touch the
red I touch the pink touch the
red pink is good but I need red touched
there's no red over here to touch oh
there's a red over there oh yeah over
here actually
you want me to do it oh oh
that's tou the
red this is good this is good this is
good wait is this is this a
door
no put the pink back put the I I want a
one yeah
pink what that
do oh is it the
no goodbye everybody else goodbye
goodbye oh you made it too I made it
well if you if you reached the uh the
checkpoint have you reached the
checkpoint yeah you can just fall down
if you wanted to let's
go oh there's did you go read the text
here oh no let's read I shall I shall
read it this time yeah okay there was no
nice way to put it the girl was sick of
the underwater Kingdom and she tried
constantly to leave it behind no oh no
they got me again yet with the guard
being ever watchful this was anything
but easy she'd probably been caught a
hundred times by now even so giving up
was the last thing on her mind each
failure instead served as inspiration
for a new attempt am I just going about
this the wrong way
yeah I know what I'll do next and so
another day of planning began
oh very
good interesting nice reading more
puzzles more puzzles over here let's go
so many puzzles I love puzzles
direction oh it changes
[Music]
Direction uh okay I think I probably
got what do we have to do we probably
over here yeah a pu from this oh a pu
for this guy yeah for this
guy oh well didn't he already make it
where is he going out to the other
side oh no no we have to this yeah yeah
we have to turn the the
arrows okay oh there's buttons on here
before but now there
isn't where the oh maybe
it's oh
are
back we need him to go somewhere he
needs to go does he does he need to go
into
here I think he does he need to go into
this this cage over here yeah into the
cage can he get should be easy you can
send him already take a shortcut just
like right yeah I imagine so so maybe it
doesn't work how do we send him with the
try that click him click it come on oh
easy go go go it's about the laser is
the laser okay yeah it's okay was that
it okay it made
a he's in there he's inside more than
one over
here nothing he probably has to do
something else wait I don't understand
why there is there are some gold there's
some
yeah some gold in
here maybe I have to go through
it we can try it yeah let's go then yeah
maybe needs to cross the golden let's go
go down this the golden so here first
and then here and then go
here fluffy one click the click the
button click the diamond button yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah like that and then
it goes back the button
oh okay I'm going to click the button no
wait wait wait okay no oh wait okay ah
no no no it's not no no no uh oh oh
close but not F it's going to work it's
going to work didn't see that one I
still have one okay let's try this again
then one more down mhm
down down
[Music]
there this way this one what about this
one
yeah I have to go back here and then oh
then he can he can go this way then he
can't go that way yeah he has to go that
way for I'm
overseeing yeah so it goes like
that
yeah that I don't no because it goes in
a circle like
that oh there you go and now here that
should be now here wait have we gone to
this one work so down
here wait see what goes
wrong okay back around back
up we're missing this is good oh I know
which one to change yeah we change this
one hey wait
wait stop that man stop him stop him
enough okay try that I think to go that
uh wait no don't try that wait
SEC uh the go try that okay oh gosh try
it
[Music]
uh oh I missed that one I think now oops
I think this one he's going to be stuck
ining forever can I try one yeah left
here mhm that it
right here MH right here yeah left here
and left again wait wait actually if you
keep going down right yeah right down
here and then left and then up and then
right yeah and hey nice
one
go good job go go go go go little buddy
you can do it you can do it yeah follow
the light follow the gold this way this
way there we
go oh oh that was supposed to go
straight oh
no wait I'm going to close it there you
go again again again now that was on the
wrong
direction there's only one
direction straight come on I'm going to
go go go yeah yeah yeah I
believe
yeah over
here yeah
[Music]
don't mindlessly follow him into the
laser I was chasing
him are you okay are you
okay look like of it this is why you get
scammed you follow things mindlessly oh
no okay what you do
now where we going worse than me guys
worse than me
oh there's another puzzle here
[Music]
no there's like three lights on before
there were no lights on right oh really
it's like a chest maybe there's a
treasure or
something it's green I would to go in
there green oh this
time we have to oh we actually need to
follow this path what about here oh in
theer how we try going up this C here
wait wait oh yeah yeah yeah yeah there's
another one here cool what is this this
oh gosh oh go oh gosh it's a Lain
no there's
water there's water for water I'll stand
on it water
go
water go up I
fell I can go have to go can we go up in
oh
no I don't think so it doesn't go
anywhere oh yeah we can go up but it's
just the exit over here so this is at
the very
end I think I think ow yellow except for
one it says green did it come oh where
did you go guys can you can you try to
come here actually up okay go up yeah uh
somebody has to stand on it no wait no
no no we have to open the chest first
never
mind no no no no
no light hasn't open yet there's
something
here how do I go
down there we go she thank you oh it's
to reset and go I have an idea I have an
idea she got it she got it I have an
idea yeah I have an idea stop
okay straight what is your idea straight
left uh-huh left oh yeah yeah I has to
go away left leave the field and then
okay I don't know I can't change this
one but let's I think that oh and then
he probably go into that and then we'll
see what happens there let's try it
them interesting do we need to change
anything
though W he's leaving foundaries what
the he he's leaving yay what the how
poetic and now now we'll see what does
this do oh oh that's it okay cool he met
s up
okay what about the chest yeah what
about the chest so that one is
interesting one light left I want to get
the chest no I think can you press light
more no there was more lights
before you think
it says it says up it says up here
please wait for all party members before
proceeding yeah there's a chest okay
okay there is a there is a message on
the chest no oh no no no no no no no
well I think if we send him for here he
will stand on the button and then the
chest room will
open wait but the question is just how
do we lead him over the arrow
moment when this arrow is straight how
do we lead him to go that way Arrow
again oh yeah I guess the when the
buttons are back we can just move the
arrow to the right okay I'll I'll
refresh this okay we'll probably have to
send him straight again later cuz that
might have uh that might have gotten rid
of it yeah press it is there an arrow
there's no Buton
no we might all need to go up here
because it says we can't proceed until
we're all up there anyway okay maybe the
chest is later I want to get the
chest yeah yeah yeah I'll send him again
if anything we can come back later in
these Dungeons and and do that again
together true yeah and get the
chest oh maybe maybe this is the you
know the right order maybe we come back
here
anyway all right let's
go I don't know unless there's a secret
button of some sort we haven't found
probably some puzzle or something maybe
we have to come back later who
knows maybe the real treasure was the
friends we made along the way yeah
definitely I need to eat
food
[Music]
here wait we're missing oh ah Elizabeth
yeah sorry one sec
okay huh I was just checking around oh
yeah
my still not s
so I'm
[Music]
sorry okay let's go let's go wait okay
no okay I guess it
isn't it's
[Music]
oh yeah oh wait let me get the video
first has it huh yeah let's get the
video memories you've recovered a
portion of your memories all the
memories
wow I didn't download the video yet yeah
me
neither
okay I'll do now the
video the
vision yeah
wait wa wait they they haven't
downloaded the
[Music]
video wait wait okay one second I'm
almost ready one almost ready one sec
what the
H wait a
minute you recovered a portion of your
memories okay wait wait wait wait wait
wait almost have it I almost have it I
almost have it okay I'm ready okay uh
wait wait wait
wait Advanced Audio
properties monitor only okay what does
that
mean okay uh I think I'm ready three two
two one
go
oh kill it
no a she's very busy
stinks I'm out of
here ah she's the one that tried to
escape every time that's the girl we we
read
about that that's familiar that's what I
had wait she the one in the
Hat but I she got the because she wanted
to Trop us and then I'll be free she
want to fool us or so I
thought she's a
criminal is she she making she's a
scammer yeah she's a
scammer scumpy she's fast now we're
never let see what this thing can
do wow oh she did it oh my God wait that
glass ceiling I saw it outside when we
reached the
temple break out of it too that's the
barrier so cute my Story begins
here so cute Our Story begins
here
[Music]
amazing what an interesting
memory made it we made
it go back in let's go back in and get
the chest cuz oh yeah I think we need to
take the chest I think we can figure it
out we cannot leave until we get the
chest
100% get back in there nobody
oh go by the way a new weapon we got to
do the the bridges again the shine is
yellow instead now oh and the stacking
too
can you guys hear me yeah I said that
the star on your weapon now is yellow
instead of white
oh is it there's a different new shine
to our weapons yeah wow I think I think
it got stronger
now you're
right Thor looks great jump farther I'll
press the
buttons okay okay we we we're good now
uh oh
mhm can I can you try as well yeah oh uh
I already ran out of brain energy oh all
right too that's how it works so we need
to put everything on the left first wait
wait over
there need to go over here yeah yeah
yeah oh yeah go over and green goes and
then goes and another one left and this
one
left it's
easy easy peasy actually I'll go this
way feels like we already made
it feel simple Speed Run speed
Runners now this our first first try yes
oh yeah
definitely God it's so fast
unbelievable we need to solve the f i
I'm really cursed to see what's going to
what there is in the what is in the
chest hopefully something we can all
share like maybe
friendship that's don't we have don't we
have friendship along the way though are
we not that we're not friends but this
this will
like finalize I don't know it will put a
ring on our yeah yeah ring we're getting
married friendship friendship ring
friendship ring I didn't realize it was
this kind of
commitment I'm going to press the L and
then we go there do it do it press it
press it
yeah and then come over here the yellow
one yellow one I'll stay with the Fluffy
one this time okay I like fluffy wait
doesn't work yellow one it doesn't work
huh oh why what PR huh I don't know my
this B here huh let me try one we're
looking for the yellow uh we're stuck oh
no no
wait you're so fluffy let me fluffy wait
the ears of the tail there's a door
there's a door you let me pit you no let
me stop stop stop stop stop how do you
know what I'm trying to do let me P you
let me P you wait this is
wait this is
what over
there for you look so fluffy may I pet
you do we need to press the red
one or the blue
one no oh no you did that to
me no I'll come pick you up
no we a littleit go I'm a little bit
confused where should we
go I'm I to my D sorry sorry
no I got so excited for your fluffiness
I'm so
sorry can somebody press the red one
yeah the red one please how are you sh
I'll do myself I feel so fluffy now I
found it I thought it was the other this
is a fond memory with you above pink can
you wait for me all right it's like
almost as if we were here before I'm
stuck here
crazy looks familiar let me see if I can
help you the glassing time here first
time
totally so quick at these puzzles the
yellow amazing yeah I the yellow would
beer if I didn't push for
wa sorry about that I mean luckily in
this realm we can come back to life
it work yeah I'll get the checkpoint
um
checkpoint all
[Music]
right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I could
have helped you with that but that's
good okay uh I have um I I know how to
solve the
puzzle you do yeah so I think the
skeleton or did chatini tell you no no
actually no actually no um I think the
uh the doll has to go through the gold
like
twice oh so like we we have to make a
loop and then go but I'm not actually
sure loop I I mean that's my idea I'm
not sure if it's that that's correct I I
just I just
assumed maybe it has like to make I
think I this down
now it has to go double time on the cold
so maybe like goes like
you want me to press it press it maybe
let's
see
one no
I okay let me let me just try one two he
needs to Loop better a place
that
oh no this needs to go back
up oh wait you're right you're right
you're right you're right can need the
multiple times he needs to go five he
needs to go over it five times so it
lights it all up there five lights so he
need to go over five times and then
do yeah that's what I
mean smart okay we can do that we can do
that which way we want to go this way
it's over be like um me send them over
the same one several times right yeah
you have to make it oh I I think I found
the
way wait isn't this like already a loop
yeah we pressed it so now it should be
one does the same one not
count no it didn't make sound did he go
over it okay he went over it it lit up
once but we only have
three we need little tree yeah we need
little tree plus
two no that's not right how do we get
the other two wait can I can I try
it
okay this one and then goes here and
then go here and then like that
again
uh there's no lights yet oh yeah they're
still preparing is there is there lights
let me let me let me try one thing
because
P I have figured it out oh figed it out
yes have you done the previous bit oh PR
have you done the previous
bit bit before the chest yeah we should
do it again right okay so you have to
make the guy go towards me through the
little door I am down here I'm outside
come back WS from where we went on the
bridges make the guy come this way hello
hello hello make the guy come this way
no way what what what what I out the
bridges so that he can he can make a a
little travel down here so you got to
make him come through the door you got
to make him come through that
[Music]
door well that's quite oh oh yeah it
leads like here okay okay he's got
to I see I see let's reset it
yeah then this which
down here oh I see there's a little door
but at the end I guess we probably still
want to get the golden ones that are
here too I think right maybe we don't oh
yeah maybe we need a later yeah we
probably want all of them we actually
need it yeah yeah I'll tell you when it
lights up okay wait there is a gold
thing oh yeah there is I think we need
to that set one more time that was go
through there he can go through there
but you cannot you cannot pass you shall
not pass okay here we go he's coming
yeah you can test with that one but it's
not going to have enough gold we have to
uh reset the
path let's
go go go go go go go
go I didn't notice there was like the
gold on the on the on the floor there we
go off he goes off he goes
wo yeah he's made it missing one he
didn't get all them over here
here flppy oh then then then set it up
so you get it I'll reset okay let
me let me
reset down here down down and then yeah
down and then left and
then up and then right and okay now now
we can send him okay I'm going to send
him let's
go I'm excited going on a long trip
mhm okay too
late good job good job to good
[Music]
job yes he will do it I believe in him
100% then
okay huzzah
H I cannot go over there go backwards
that's you cannot go through
[Laughter]
there I'm going to wait on he goes off
he goes he's
coming I'mma die thank you
forever oh
no I'm back didn't open it it didn't
open he's coming back still he's coming
back he's coming he's coming he's going
to
stand going to do
[Music]
the here we go
exting
I'm not reflect reflect oh we got a a
vinyl that makes
cool wait what did what did did you guys
get a vinyl too yeah yeah we prob need a
juke box for playing the game the music
one question girls you all did the
dungeon yesterday right yes you have you
gotten a vinyl there no no I think after
all that one PA that I fought there must
be a treasure chest because my RPG
senses were tingling it must have a
treasure chest with an Cali vinyl there
that probably no one found so far and I
think I know where it
is shall we shall we
another adventure yeah let's go let's go
let's go let
travel oh we have to finish it again we
have to we have to made the guy go I
think we can just leave the dungeon on
from the book I know okay I'm so excited
I'm so excited yeah it's my
RPG okay uh basically same path but not
down here but up right yeah
no yeah yeah yeah this way this way this
way this
way this way that way yeah yeah yeah
yeah right I forgot I know and then it
goes over there and then we can get out
okay we don't need any more of the gold
no no no we don't need any anything
anymore
yeah are you
okay I'm not
hungry overing
good job yeah thank you Eliz here she go
you feel we make an excellent
team I got the
treasure yeah we got
music that was
me it's very
Prett let's go okay let's go good job
let's go to find more CD y
MH let's go I hope there
is get by where do you think it is I
will show you I'll show you okay okay
are stronger now
again again I don't know your
memories let's
go okay
uh who wants to lead us to the first
dungeon oh let's travel back oh yes my
brain is empty horses empty
brain into the water we go we have to go
to the water horses into the water yeah
the horse that was a really good dungeon
though a
seahorse my horse doesn't doesn't don't
don't get off the horse the poor horse
my
God my horse doesn't like the swim too
much yeah I don't think it knows how how
to breathe underwat it's
beautiful nice so creamy I really love
this area it was it was very nice and
beautiful even the map was very well
done like I like the details A Beautiful
World wait where did you
go yeah let's meet at the guy the guy
we're floating guy with the corals yeah
are
ships it's okay you can leave the ships
I don't think we need them anymore more
I can always make new
[Music]
ones so
slow I'm going as fast as I can okay I
think we have to go over here
again the
queen
no the queen
no I refused oh no
the queen Tim
chanders Tim
tenders Tim Tim who Tim ters Tim ters
Tim
ters what an interesting
name who's him it's okay the queen I'll
claim my my statues myself I don't need
anyone to give me
validation I don't need the Scarlet wine
gild master
we have to find oh oh yeah I guess we
got to go there we can go yeah let's go
to the
um let us travel
first
theut
cut get out of the way
cow are you running over cows with your
horse yeah I'll run over
everything you're going to R right yep
okay just to make
[Music]
sure turn this way I'm
done turn are we ready I'm
ready let us
travel uh now that we're in this city
I'm going to put something on the chat
chest and then we go
back okay what chest where oh I have um
I have a chest on the place where you um
can build stuff wow I I made like two
chest so I can deposit
like my my my
items does she notice
it fascinating oh I'm going to mute
now fascinating Most Fascinating yet
more evidence of this ruins are somehow
connect what is more I sense that the
power of Revelation within you has grown
more po potent May mayhaps by exploring
more ruins and obtaining more fragment
of memories your revelation will be
empowered
as it goes too fast oh there you go as
well if so we must find the experience
PA H all of us together will surely make
short work of This
research
oops as a matter of fact we just
received a most intriguing
report Scout of the ruin cup aspired
that the same mysterious light coming
from the forest along the m road may
mayh you are visit their Guild and speak
with the Guild Master Celesta keep your
ah keep your WIS about you hero Excel
okay see don't skiper skiper everything
Sor
currently I'm currently communicating
with the queen give me one moment what
queen a queen king that's me you can
tell me
directly I met this queen before you can
you can talk to me Direct was that t oh
I
[Laughter]
remember this
is this is the most terrible oh I got to
deposit myself I'll be right back okay
there wait for
[Music]
me going that way yeah yeah yeah is it
over here I never been
there what I don't
remember be oh yeah it's over here over
here there you go oh this is i ph oh
they're making a house
cute Mar lottery
tick Lottery
ti so is where the uh the the for witch
who sells is that the place where we are
able to
build is that the only place yeah this
is the only place we can build m what
yeah I see where did everybody
go I'm going to put my stuff over
here and later I'm going to build
something where go did you go up the
room
yeah up here too okay sorry I I'm done
uh are you girl on on the way to the
dungeon no where you going I'm over here
I talk to Rubi they're over wait you
haven't talked to rubius oh yeah sorry I
was kind of busy um no no we'll go back
go back and talk to him
okay okay
okay oh okay I guess they're leading us
to the next dungeon with that one but we
wouldn't go to this is a not
yeah guys what m oh no wait it doesn't
work never
[Music]
mind peace
work it doesn't work I know how to open
those more I need a d box what is for
doing yeah I need ax we do later I'm
actually going to put this
[Music]
here yeah you
actually know I'm going to keep it here
[Music]
that I don't remember very well huh what
happened I got
disconnected
what what
happened
huh what
happened hello
there's a side quest for a res oh I got
kicked out from the
party I think they ended the
Party theed by
Ruby wait what we going to do
now we're going to do the first dungeon
again because there's also a side quest
for revisiting the first dungeon oh is
there so we go to the quest wall yeah
yeah we can kill two birds with one
stone okay um do we have to do the party
grp again the call nobody in
my yeah my
party yeah
party yeah let's pick the party I
did wait how do you I forgot I know how
I know how to do it I know I think I'm
going to accept everything just in
case well I'm in the party
call yes I think I should probably end
the party call cuz this is probably
where I should stop for today you end
you end for okay that's fine I'll go
with ra and perhaps Liz I'm not sure if
she wants to go yeah we'll have to find
the stuff door
okay thank you thank you so much have
fun have fun take care fluzzy fluzzy
ones thank
you
bye save journey to you to
[Music]
Travelers thank
you
Revelation
Revelation fuzzy okay which one's
the side quest I got all of them just in
case milkshake
P challenge Brutus add a light and
stains go go back to the underworld
dungeon investigate it again then report
your findings to the quest Master yeah
there's also another quest for good ass
dungeon as well yeah oh you and me we
will be the first ones probably to find
the C record you go I'm excited it will
be a rare item that only we have mhm
okay yeah are you sure okay okay I'll
try but I don't know should we uh check
with her a there you oh there Iris oh
hello hello those of ambercoin I not
Amber coin we're not ambercoin oh oh not
Amber coin we Jade now we're Jade oh
Jade Jade people we Chang skills we
changed skills that is a very listen to
me right now listen Queen yes Queen yes
thank you hello tender I
KN thank you thank you what is your I
don't need that I don't need Val I am
Tanisha caria of the oranges sa of the
Les
[Laughter]
letian sorry what did you call our
Beloved Country again uh a a uh
[Applause]
totally not on purpose um yeah you can
call me Shakira um you have heard my
report
chakira what Chira you heard my report
is it true Queen have you already looked
into it we are looking into it right now
there have been please elaborate for the
rest of us okay well uh there have
already been plenty of victims so far I
also here this is the this is the
detective that I have uh asked to help
me
pear yes so the Red Hats married the Red
Hats of the Scarlet wand they uh have
put up a shop uh to scam people with
lottery tickets they say it's for the
library but in reality it's not and and
they're trying to make use of the people
who have amnesia and can't read so they
can't read the the the the contract
yeah don't buy don't buy into the scam
don't buy L tiets where is this poster I
came to look at the poster oh check it
was sent by pigeon I I sent you pigeon
oh pigeons my pigeon okay let me let me
just check my pige mailx okay hold on
just be careful of the Red Hats the red
hats are dangerous they they want to
take over the country probably I see I
see the pigeon I'm a literate though uh
we can you can can you can you read it
to me
please yes yeah yes yes yes please give
it to look at Al the pigeon
mail are you both going to seek the the
dungeon oh it is fart yes in a moment
her name is spicy situation at the quest
uh board where is the pige she's
speaking about wow the jackpot is 740
gold I no she's talking to she's talking
to uh to other people
now but we could win and and it's it's
held daily come to the
come to the quest money but we can win
money you're not going to win money no
you're not going to win money happening
I don't know I like money but think
about it if everyone is thinking it's a
scam that means not many people are
betting which means there's a good
chance no it's not no it's
not honestly it already it already has
become a worst chance because Moko got
scammed and gave them 680
coins come here blinded by money
is Queen you must do something my
gambling and I have 500 now see you are
exactly the kind of person they're
looking
for I I would like to increase my my
savings don't do it you're weak to
you're weak to
gambling I will try my best to I Goa
keep myself yes we must we must
exterminate you must we must exterminate
both the star Scarlet Guild and the
ambercoin guild yeah ambercoin of course
to ambercoin Guild is evil who is left
in the ambercoin if you two have left
then who is left I was never in
ambercoin of course not that's a lie no
I'm I'm in
Jade way I'm in Jade though I've never
seen oh that hello
Gan that your guild is full of scammers
can you verify that you are with this
member is
I literally just went with Fu and and
Herb which are Jade members uh to the
dungeon right herb they're like semi
honorary we we we get along kop has
invited me into the guild personally
wait a second isn't
she I guess you are you areal Enemy
oural
enemy listen it doesn't even matter
Queen there is que red thing that red
thing is of Jade sword and not of Amber
coin thank you my the name of Amber coin
que I don't trust it I trust it ah so
you are the Tim I've heard about it's
him you are the
Tim Timmy I don't know what is a Tim
was like what what is this queen Tim how
silly of a
[Applause]
name I have not been C I do not know
what you speak what is disgusting you
are the first to call me of this I do
not understand because everybody was too
polite but I of higher polite you have
you have yes you are right you have not
been polite you are correct on that I
have been very polite to you actually oh
well as soon as you found
out yeah you were my kidnapp that was
good I wasid testing you oh uh that was
a misunderstanding yes I was testing you
why you the queen yes I was testing you
where who are you affiliated with she's
with the
red the moment I don't understand the
green wait we have heard
you we don't trust you I'm okay to be
don't
plotting a
scam heard of
your getting too
chaotic I gave her a kiss without asking
for coin have planted the seed of Truth
why everyone is mad at ambercoin the
first seed of
truth the truth you do anything I like
Amber coin I think I'll stick with it
I don't
mind I'll be the only person in Amber
coin wait you want to go yeah I'm here
I'm on party call with you oh okay
please
join we in party call again join us if
you
like yeah geky geky has really has it
out for or Amber coin m i don't mind I
want to stay in Amber coin I like
it people hate us though
why there's a lot of like slander being
spread about let them hate who
cares it's okay I'm a freelancer it's
okay yeah it's okay is a guild made by
one person which is me it's fine oh
let's go to the dungeon
don't worry I'm I I all that matters is
that we are together
now how does it work when you with the
others you part of other girls when with
me part of the
Amber why are you complaining we went
together to the dungeon with the J how
does it work
and don't question it don't question it
it's
complicated okay we got to straight
straight straight oh yeah straight
right uh let's go I'm going to call Li
in private and ask her if she wants to
join before it one sec
[Music]
okay
mus hello dear kitty cat come to the
arena I'm about to fight the queen oh
she is fighting we we about to go to the
dungeon want to uh it would only take a
moment come come over to the arena okay
okay I'll be right back where is the
fraking
entrance
uh pie we should go to the let's go to
the arena can you join the party call
yeah let's go to the arena they're
fighting I cannot miss that
are they going to
fight what is
[Music]
happening look at
see where is the
arena run hello hello hello I like your
hat I really love your hat one day I
hope I can get a hat like
that how much money do you have I have
two MO two
coins okay I have 11 so we're not that
okay listen if I get 10 coins I'll buy
you hat how about that no no this is
attached to my head if I take it off
then I'm going to die and two other
people will die now cuz we're all
connected I see um then it's okay you
can keep your hat I'll one day I'll find
same hot one day H you can buy it
yeah Money Record G oh you found it got
it it was bra feel it was quite
difficult a while it took us a while
too because because the the the the the
gate signifies the end of a puzzle so
you wouldn't backtrack right backtracked
anyway like why why what why we had to
back back track we had to there was
Choice there was an obvious treasure
hidden good job you know what I'll I'm
glad you made it out of that uh glass
Hall of Atlantis the force field the the
thing the force field I'm glad I'm glad
you're free in the world now to do
whatever you
please but I shall not support the scam
of the Red Hats so that's another story
I'm going to see if it's a hat the scam
of the Red Hats
uhhuh rightly
well
I
okay uh they might be in the arena I
wanted to go there too yeah they were F
might be in the arena a big fight to the
death good
luck what are you up
to
I don't
know I was going to side quest or
something something or maybe maybe uh uh
maybe wind down for the day yeah good
luck then with your
quest thank you Raa your red hat yeah I
hope one day I'll get the same big hat I
hope you will I know thank you thank you
for believing see you around how do you
say goodbye and in Italian
t t t t
C how you say how you say bye-bye in
American uh in
English how you say
that you
[Music]
say yes see you later alligator see you
later alligator
bye-bye
[Music]
t wait I got this fries but is it
actually just
SC right right right click to use it how
you say
that how you use that see you little
alligator
huh
and oh how do you enter the
arena
huh what is it this entrance
[Music]
oh the
fighting oh how do you
enter
a I'm
[Music]
spectating over there
there we go
NE Jonathan you trust me right there was
a force in that Arena a ghost that pulls
me
around Huns this Arena it name is
Ping Ping who is Ping
Ping sounds like a skill the penguin in
my favor no it's in the history books in
the green Guild I believe that is a
skill I thought you could not read see a
ren I was
told beautiful
Raven excuse me beautiful Raven you are
here yes yes it is I I have missed you
Jonathan I have missed you too
little wait can you can can you guys
hear
me so the me the hot pink um the hot
pink one the hot pink one I seeing your
strength in battle it was very exting I
applaud
you right let us go yipp let's
go the ghost ping attacked me I was
being I was being pulled around I I
couldn't even move
properly do not H me we we have been on
an adventure together in the dungeon I
would not
lie I though like I I love both of you
but our political um interests seem to
go into very different directions but
that shall not stop us from being
friends right I don't care I don't mind
a you know I I feel like we have a new
rule in the in the Jade sword that we
all must agree to adding other members
ah I I I I forgot about this it's okay I
don't need I don't need a guild I'm I'm
with the queen I'm her guard her Knight
so I shall be Guiltless then although I
do have a special invitation from kopen
the uh owner of the first dungeon so I
think that kind of counts pretty big she
owns the dungeon
yeah H speaking of the dungeon shall we
go back at Le can you Jo the party call
please yeah
[Music]
she always runs into me with a
horse that is quite dangerous uh so they
do not know how to ride their horses in
that Guild no yeah you know she's
usually being carried by a horse
carriage so she's she's a little bit um
yeah unskilled when it comes to a snooty
Tooty
Queen but she she's you know she wants
to help with the scam in the problems so
the scam what scam problems here this
this is the the the lottery the lottery
the lottery oh the witch the Witch
oh how come you call her a witch okay
hello there we oh hello
hello you you how' you like if I ran
over you with my horse you mean you
what's happening excuse me excuse me
excuse me excuse me excuse me excuse me
excuse me where are you which which
Guild are you
from
uh um are you with that
clown which clown clown I hav't I think
you should look in the mirror
oh I sorry and also learn how to ride
your
horse you seem to run into people well
you seem to be doing that first to begin
with no I am not why don't you look
oh I want to I want to no you're a horse
you're a horse looks
very yeah I go idle meeting for a moment
with a freakishly large sword of
yours I I I'll put it back for a second
I'll put it back one second one second
one
second I'm you know what I'm gonna I'm
gonna stare here so you guys can
can you hear what they saying very
diabetic later on I'll be right
back already went so you believe that
your horse diabetic your horse is
disgusting my horse is beautiful your
horse is disgusting I see I do not judge
I do not judge horses I do not judge a
book by its cover this horse is
brilliant well it looks like a runt
anyway I must wait very along the way
yes my queen just one thing yes it seems
I am in a um pickle once again um I do
not know where I belong anymore but I
know one thing that my whole duty of my
life it is protecting you and I know
that I have a destiny to be by your side
as your
personal uh King hero uh not King I mean
Knight night hero guard may I please
serve you no matter what Guild I am of I
don't want to be uh known as anybody's
besides
yours well for swearing Your Allegiance
you are a mighty Phoenix what are you
doing gring to her hey hey talking to
you outcast out with
you you judging books by their covers
she is a mighty Phoenix and you are
allowing her to just continue to B to
you absolutely into the
planes awful absolutely awful well the
planes is where we were going anyway um
bloody looking
thing bloody looking like blood
disgusting makes me sick you are the
image
of war and everything
file just like the words coming out of
your mouth my
lady good
whenever you meet me call my name
Shakira Shakira okay Shakira Shakira I
shall be of your service forever and
ever hey hello was I talking to you get
the hell out of here I mean um get the
way you let this Mighty Phoenix bow and
grubble to you is disgusting yes that
means she knows her standards
spe
[Music]
I'm
back
oh even if your sword is glowing yellow
you still lost to
Pink that was the ghost
P want to mix it up some climing that
you're the queen it was it was the queen
I was being pulled around the arena I
have better things to do Thunder good
day Thunder Farewell My Queen called
Thunder this we had this entire exchange
yesterday no that's not what I want to
talk about you
about well you didn't just go to to me
without food yeah that's rude are you
getting chickenend I don't actually care
because I'm the queen so I do whatever I
want yes you're the second I know no you
are the second you're the second you're
the
concubine not
what porcupine oh sorry listen um
porcupines on my team team Bish um I
want to say one thing to you this is so
disrespectful I can't even I want to say
one thing to you and I'm not going to
repeat
myself you are a queen okay anyway you
are Queen without a castle yes walk away
in sty my queen you have no house you H
you pathetic you are a mighty Phoenix
you need to toughen up and not grel so
much to
this you see my shield and my sword I
must give it to someone she was rude to
your guild
member she left because she's a coward
no I must have my my honor and those oh
no now she's going to oh no I am I am
absolutely shook by your women my Pol
our political Ambitions shall not
destroy our friendship you're
C what's it called hey what are you
group call hey a c hey hey what C
what can't believe
it where did the music come
[Music]
from
a the
jbx all right I'm here you got me into
something okay shall we go shall we go
anyway yeah
Follow The Queen the true
one oh
the for I'm
meeting
Brey at 1: p.m. but still
no no no no okay are we ready where
them this is Mor's mory's dungeon
right
oh
[Music]
hello are you okay I'm
okay oh you want to get into a party
code a yeah I think we're we're looking
past our problems right now and just
going to do the dungeon
so I have no problem in the first place
good she did not have a problem it was
it was the
queen well the Tim Tam Queen The Tam Tim
whatever her name is I I we we're all
learning a lesson um sorry I need to
correct you the name of the queen is RA
but yeah you can fix it but that is your
name yeah exactly disand the party B
away and make a new one probably yeah I
do not
know uh let's see I'll leave this party
cuz I think yeah let's the party one oh
yes the the fuzzy and the fluffy one are
still intertwined okay hey go I invite
you girls oh
okay I leave party uh okay I left the
party I can be invited
now oh one second uh doesn't make me
leave the party
huh
[Music]
yeah I have
left okay Queen I invited you and I am
inviting you too Queen of the Tim
Hortons thank you all right and drink
water remember uh can you invite me one
more time I'm sorry of
course invite
you yay
the outcast the S and the the
panther which one am I what are you
speaking of to yourself I I received a a
pigeon carried message uh of pink color
that says I'm loving this episode of The
Chronicles of
the Les lesbians the outcast the S and
the
panther which is I guess us but I'm not
a panther
yeah yeah she's the panther who's the
outcast and who's the S I guess I'm the
S but you're not much of an
outcast uh well I am a aone warrior most
of the time that's okay together we are
not alone
anymore unless you s then I will walk
away just just look away just look away
I can't watch you do that go can you
guys press ready wait I think there's a
bug it because it says underworld
dungeon one out of
two shouldn't be one out of three
because it's I'm ready let me unready
and ready
again
there okay now La I think you're not
ready yeah I
think also you need to be getting get
yourself into the the call I am oh oh no
you are in the cor yeah I'm on about uh
Shakira okay Shakira is in and there we
go all right let's do this again yeah oh
yeah it's juming I love the jumping I
mean oh yes this is I am great with the
parkour m w I feel like you could use
your big sword as like a
pole like what do you call it pole
jumping what do you call
it well I would not dance with it no
it's not over here it's not over here no
no not dancing I mean the jump
over here Oh you mean like a long pole
long jump a pole vaulting yeah pole
vaulting oh like yeah like in the che
the
o o
impix oh wait checkpoint okay yes we got
it we got
it we certain sausage just got
caught what got nobody that's good
that's good
sausages have you seen oh my God you
seen
it have you not witnessed it you
probably have forgotten it because of
the Amia I forgot everything but I
remember I am the actual queen of
liis mhh
yeah seems people saying they are a
queen have you got to a checkpoint yeah
yeah again don't worry we'll carry
you we'll bring you to the goal I do not
need carrying I was just you know I was
just taking my time at having a merry
stroll I know you could do it with that
pole of yours so don't worry we we just
don't want to we want to save your your
your energy and all that you know yes
for the battle I'm at the next
checkpoint good job oh yippee how you
how are you getting there so fast skill
she's a child I guess so are you flying
are you cheat are you flying cheating I
may I may be flying a little bit here
and there what you you were criticizing
me for not using my wings now I am
true that is true you know got to you
know speed it up a little
bit uh oh you caught up wait I forgot
where does it go from here probably left
oh yeah and then here and here here
[Music]
here almost there oh y
okay oh it's up
here if only I was this good at jumping
at that one competition last year the
the Trident only
up I you got the next
checkpoint almost almost
almost don't wor you bling about do you
remember something oh am my old M I
already I already oh I did win yeah but
bad it I could have been
better it's the
pressure it's the pressure guys yeah
what is the what is the music
thing whoa you zip Zapped well well well
ping diff the Ping the Ping ghost is
back
ping
ping all right it starts with the maze
we all have a you know
uh a like a catchphrase as we attack
right oh yeah
totally yes are you going to are you
going to say
it uh uh Eternal Fire To The World of
stability and Harmony
wa not bad kick it it
kick Phoenix
Flames I got a couple
they're short though wow you have more
than
one do we have uh the shapes already I
got a
triangle I have a triangle sorry I was
doing something another
one what is you doing you start good
another triangle where is the thing to
fill it
in oh oh there's so many I'm going to
die no you're not going to die I got a
triangle no I got a start yeah I have a
star oh there we go triang I have a
circle we have everything we just got to
find the the forms I found it oh yeah me
too you got
everything uh I forgot oh there we
go
nice good job next
step oh I forgot to change my bgms even
though I prepared so many
no to honestly I keep forget my bgm
bgm okay now there's
one okay I turned it off for the cut
scene for the ga cut scene
yeah okay so that cut so good I love
those cat
scenes the cat I love cat scenes too I
want more cat scenes cat
scenes meow um the treasure is from what
I believe uh where those uh trees are
but this we first have to solve this
puzzle once again I remember how to make
it if that makes oh let's go can you
speedrun it yeah yeah
yeah what is the answer big cat uh just
like um the lights on the left are going
to light up so you got to make sure that
you click oh she's fast yeah yeah yeah
she does remember I do remember there
you go wow well
done well I I think my my my uh dungeon
buddy kind of did it on a whim so it
wasn't really sure how they they cracked
it yeah it took us a long time too the
first time yeah the first time was
difficult because I couldn't figure it
out the
mechanism
like so where do you think this ah I
think oh well first we got to do this
thing with where he gets rid of the
bridge right oh yeah shoot us shoot us
do
it you have to go very close to coward
don't you won't
coward does it oh there
are let's keep going
forward I
tried I
tried okay we oh okay I'm here welcome
welcome no it's different right well
believe me I'm sure uh that I know where
this treasure is that we're not even
100% sure that exists but I'm sure so
first of all let's do the whole thing
again with growing the tree okay we have
to make on top of the mushroom us come
here come
here yeah there we go let's make it as
tall as
possible speed speed speed more
in Shakira We Trust Shakira
Shakira those hips don't lie
baby press
four okay yeah too F the tree is too big
another
wine yeah come here come here come here
come
here job can we get another one
yeah Elizabeth are you okay oh no I'm at
the topop you're at the top you're on
the top maybe we we can go on the top oh
no no no I think it can still grow one
more bigger yeah let's no you can get up
oh but I want it to be bigger I'm not
going where go big or go home as they
say
exactly what do you think it is the next
the chest the secret chest don't I
think that it is and I think now it
might be able
to I think it is uh you know how we
climbed up this tree and we went like to
the next
trees we want to go the opposite
direction oh because I've noticed that
the tree when fully grown reaches the
other side the other platform Which is
higher than where we originally went out
but it's hard to climb
yeah don't don't go so don't make the
big jump if you're at the top don't make
the big jump I want to jump together
okay we jump together don't worry I'll
wait for you I'll wait for you but we
got to find the right path this is
difficult
huh Elizabeth we uh we uh you at the top
of the
tree oh let's try to get to the very top
of the tree because I think if
oh yeah yeah it goes because it reaches
just the perfect height you know and
that already looked suspicious to me
when I first one was in this dungeon and
my RPG senses were T tingling yeah but
how do you jump from
here well we got to find a way it must
be possible otherwise I don't think the
tree would like really grow this big do
you remember you made you cooked
something to make the J the jump higher
can you make can you can you give one to
me as well I want to try if you have
more
I would need I already ate the first one
and I don't have anym I would need more
ingredients but I think we should be
able to do it without because honestly
the jump it didn't get much bigger it
was just like like 5 cm I don't know if
it's possible
from there yeah um there must be a
different path I guess a different path
yeah from the first
side definitely not it
or I wonder if it can grow if this is
the last stage of the tree
Grove honestly I'm not even like 100%
sure about any of this of course
but I just had a feeling you
know yeah I mean we we here to explore
it's fine worst case we just go back
wait wait how did you oh how did you get
there uh just uh in front of me
so you go
around yeah but I'm not really sure
where to go from here I don't think it I
don't think it helps what I've
done yeah there's buttons here too which
some people say the buttons uh show like
the way to the next like jumpy platforms
but it doesn't really because it shows
you maybe we do need a
potion I don't the potion okay listen I
try to jump and are you at the bottom
yeah can you try leading another
skeleton leading another there no more
skeletons they go there's no more oh so
it is the maximum okay interesting
yeah let's see what if we may maybe the
the trees over there
connect
uh oh we can try uh growing those again
and see yeah if it maybe helps us
not sure CU those would be growing so
far
away well I mean me and my my party
members yesterday didn't grow them to
their fullest so oh let's do that then
no oh no no wa is there is there a
checkpoint there
too oh man I cannot jump yeah there is
that
there oh it's not activating I'm stupid
what okay but I my party M
stupid what if it really is stupid
though okay one tree
grow or what if there's no more
skeletons down there I wonder can we Le
the skeleton down to the tree that we're
growing and grow it even more no because
you're going to D you're going to it's
going to make full damage
the fall for could I guess
so but if we like can you uh Elizabeth
can you try to uh wait never mind I'll
I'll try sorry it's okay it's okay
that's fine too okay come come come come
but don't kill
[Music]
me oops I want him to
face going to die a moment okay abort
abort abort doesn't work kill him h no
it's it's a bit difficult I want to I
want him to face the tree and then I
want to push him down of the sword
because then he falls down some momentum
have it might actually yeah if we clim
yeah it does it
connects it does it does w all right all
right all right all right all right all
right all right okay
maybe I want to come come here come here
come here I come okay probably enough if
we just grow this tree then if it's
connecting or oh maybe we need all of
them CU honestly it was really complic
to get the other CD the V vinyl yeah so
maybe if we jump from One Tree to the
other tree to the other tree yeah you
know maybe we'll bring it over here
because oh oh you think that's uh it
finished growing this one uh I feel like
wait where where it connects though are
you sure at the top if you come over to
where we are you can see that the tree
is reaching out to the other tree and
you could probably make that jump
[Music]
okay from there to there I
am nice nice nice nice I am on the top
of this
tree kill me no
no you just not want to heal
no a waste of bread
okay another
SK running out of
bread I I can give I give okay I still
have
meat I cook some meat
before probably from this to this to
there so this one has to
grow yes is that is that it
okay I've grown both trees to its
fullest there's no more skeleton
spawning so I
think let me
see I'm finding a way to Jo to jump on
the next
tree come over here no no I'm already on
the top which top never mind now
[Laughter]
I never mind this this is the thing with
cats climbing trees yeah sometime
happens you know you you get too
confident you think you can reach it and
then you fall yeah or or you get stuck
exactly but cats always fall on their
paws supposedly sometime I don't the
other tree if I'm
e you feel sleepy
I'm
oh you made it I'm almost there for like
go
okay no hold on it's still kind of far
so I got to go to the top and then fall
down okay
okay and where do we go now this not
quite it this this is it I'm getting so
excited I can smell the treasure I
believe you can find it can you can you
wait off to open it yes I will wait if I
find
it um I am I am confident you can find I
think that is like it makes sense that
there is one
though 100% like I I thought there was
something there the first time there's
there's a reason why these uh trees grow
this tall and not just as tall as we
need it yeah and those like the normal
path yeah now that we have the vinyl
from one dungeon we know there must be a
vinyl here
[Music]
too what this this is not this is too
far hello hi we need to go higher like
it looks like you can reach from here
but it's not quite enough we need to
fall from
higher so like we keep on jumping from
wait you can jump over here no yeah but
from there it's still too far I think
the other tree we have to go from higher
no here go
no oh you can no ah you mean to the left
tree
is this the tree you were talking about
uh I I thought you were thought I
thought you thought you could already
jump to the front tree but yeah I
probably cuz I'm stuck
here stop dying I
stucked got stucked
no but I see yeah yeah yeah you found
the you found the way
yeah I found the I will I will continue
your legacy okay I am happy to
contribute a little
[Music]
bit that should
work yeah you're doing it Elizabeth wait
am from here how did
you
mhm oh oh oh we're doing it we're I
think I can totally see a treasure there
there there's one I believe it there's a
reason for all of this there's totally a
reason okay that wait I'm lost I cannot
find the way anymore
what it was on the uh the tiger looking
parts of the tree that there was like
another passage yeah you start from the
left and you go to the right tree then
the left okay now I'm on the very top of
the tree where you jump right where you
got to
jump and from there I don't know where
to go I had to go underneath on like
some Tiger Tiger tree looking bits like
walk underneath okay and I kind of fell
so I kind of accidentally found
it welcome let's wait for her here okay
I'm scared of this
jump but yeah it's it's totally totally
doable oh you're still on the middle
tree on the first tree L yeah I cannot
find the path to go to the second
anymore wait I see the chest now I see
the chest you see it there it's a chest
we see
it I see it dang it there is no
checkpoint though so be
careful good
job I'm looking for the puff I need a i
guys kfp Clippers I need a clip from me
doing the dungeon the first time and
then abandoning this but I always knew I
always
knew there's something more to this
dungeon we share our findings with the
others or should we keep it a secret
well we know you to the you the first I
will not tell the queen I will not I am
the queen I already know that
silly
oh this this guys are silly today
I I don't know I have a feeling that you
will probably say to her I know where
they are there is another treasure my
queen so please let me be your
night kiss her her feet I think expose
the relas go yes no we should just like
how the mighty Phoenix is Fallen we
should when we're at the chest we should
take a an a me me meor me Meo picture of
us together and then Flex it to
everybody that we were the first ones to
find this yeah and then they can try
finding it too yeah I canot find
my uh let me see where are you
uh the first come on the first tree
you've done this first tree several
times no it's silly no I mean I I'm done
on the first tree oh God damn it's fine
just okay listen I'm it's fine just take
it take your time we we'll wait okay can
you wait yeah yeah yeah take good
time I'm
sad oh should we sell this information
wait I'm stupid maybe I was stucked on
this tree wait no of course you say that
Amber how very Amber of you no no I
don't want to I just read I think the
message but I don't want I'm not like
those scammers
from hats I'm not like you mean the the
wand uh I think this is a good point for
us to hydrate uh Shakira I'm always
hydrating don't worry oh well done good
job I'm just going to look over Yonder
and and do and hydrate okay I'm running
out of water
again okay I'm coming now I I was stuck
to the first tree for some reason like I
thought that was the actual last tree I
don't know why yeah little silly t
doesn't believe your words what of
course she
does she doubting
me no way I must who's dting
you no no no one I'm sure no
one I'm getting here
okay you know I couldn't have done it
without these girls because uh wasn't it
Elizabeth who had the idea to continue
growing the other trees too cuz it
looked like this tree alone could
already reach it but and it does but you
need the other trees all connected all
of them which makes sense with like how
complicated the other chest was in the
other dungeon you have to com uh combine
several riddles
yes yes I'm almost how you
doing where are you uh at the top pretty
much like in the where the trees connect
all three of
them if you look up you probably see
your names somewhere I don't see yours
right now oh I see you guys hello oh
there ah the tree
cat tree cat
hello and now from here come on ah uh
first to the side I
think yeah and then the next one on the
side and then I think it it's hard to
tell from here but I think you can reach
if you you got to run don't fall don't
fall you have to run when you
jump don't don't get you can do it I
will catch
you yes
yes now
carefully does everybody have full
health because the fall might do some
Dam damage yes I do I need to make we'll
go down to this tree
first yeah this ready fall yeah I think
it's pretty safe you go first oh okay
ouch yeah I'm fine
cat
yes you can do
it nice okay get up fly Phoenix
good job we're doing it good
job no one is all fall
now unless the unless the Ping ghost
gets me then I might
fall
yes oh my God this is so
exciting we take a picture we'll take a
picture picture up like here
maybe stand next to me girl yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yeah
yes Elizabeth oh sorry I was I was
clicking uh I mean I was I was jumping
and when I jumped twice it did something
weird I was
confused and let's look to the other
side too okay
[Music]
Chee y
we're the first
ones probably ex CU my
rudness oh please
rip oh my God I love we did it we did
God I love this one
yay I'm sure other people will come to
the conclusion that if the Atlantis
dungeon had a city the others should
have one too but I don't think many
people know where the the treasure would
be
no what don't ouch
don't I get
confidence you can let me know when you
get to the
checkpoint okay thank you it's only cuz
uh my my tum tum is turning so after
jumping yes after jumping so much on
those trees so I'll wait until you're
there and then I will
oh does it give you motion sickness yeah
I I get motion sickness oh no I hear a
lot about people getting motion signal
from Minecraft I'm so glad I'm not
affected but sounds right yeah I I out
of character I get it I yeah I get it a
fair
bit yeah wait where does it go
again is it like every
time that you after like a like around
uh 2ish hour like on the 2 hour I get
bit like Sicky or like a bit after a
while it depends what I'm doing too if
I'm like jumping a lot and all that it
might but I think my sick bands helped
me a little bit today my wrist band oh
well I think yeah with all this jumping
it's very understandable you've done
greatly Brave War yeah that that
actually was way difficult I'm a brave
warrior with tummy issues
you know we all have some you know
realistic human problems I'm only human
yeah the Phoenix and the panther I'm
only human but even even I get Tommy
H tmy H the way I got the checkpoint
yeah please you did okay I'm I'm going
die thank you forever I'm going die
thank you forever but yeah it's so it
was pretty difficult jumping on the tree
it requires a little bit of skills
SC hey good job get high enough to jump
again to my demise oh that was not it
but well after this was it just uh the
end of the dungeon right away or I think
so
okay I'm also sick of jumping at this
point feel like C after 24 hours of
jumping man oh my
God her her legendary this was before
your time girls legary jump King
streams frustrating like water a water
stream uh yeah yeah yeah yeah uh she
jumped stream of water you were jumping
in the water and you were a king is that
why you grel to the queen copine she
used to jump over streams of water water
endlessly and they would lead her to
pretty high places like the it's like
the water streams were coming from the
mountains
W that is
amazing wait I'm almost almost dead how
powerful you're almost dead oh
finally nice yippe let's
go wow w
wow yeah
so good
job thank you for aiding me in the quest
of this because nice I would have never
been satisfied otherwise my pleasure
thank you for inviting us on your Noble
Quest dear Phoenix it's so worth it it
was so fun worth it is there any place
to play these uh
vinyls yeah yeah there's a juke box at
the at the beginning of the city oh can
we go listen yeah yeah let's go listen
let's go let us go let us travel Have
you listened to the Atlantis one already
yeah it was playing the background oh
okay me I haven't listened to it I I
show you now I show you now don't
worry Shakir
Shakir what is this song you sing
Shakira oh it's my original song your
original
yes I sometimes perform in taverns with
um you are a b uh no I'm more like the
serator I I work with other B oh yes I
hello
hello kop kopine k please come with us
please come with us we have a surprise
for you we have a surprise for you
surprise surprise yes kind of surprise
come with us can you bring us like come
here come here come here come here come
here don't tell her yet come here come
here come here it's a surprise it's a
perfect timing all right come with me ah
sorry one sec
oh oh no no no no no no no no no no no
no follow me follow me follow me follow
me follow me follow me follow me follow
me follow me follow me follow
me you're you're timing come here come
here come here here okay here okay can
everybody around it hear it I think so
right over here over here come here come
here hold on just one moment just one
moment uhhuh oh I'm sorry I had Kiara up
by like 50% or something like that sorry
about that that is my fault all right
hello hello hello are you ready are you
ready are you ready go two one go
where you going where you
[Music]
going
human what is
going see you no one's going to BU I
believe
youing here
we're getting down this is
[Music]
a don't
know fing
say we found
it we're the first ones in your dungeon
it was secretly party
[Music]
with
the glad that you are having a good time
that is what matters it was great which
one thank you for playing my wow look at
how many people came in here yeah
party maybe your voice is like a siren
it brought everyone here oh thank you
I'm sorry hold on a second I got
to would you like to hear it too
beautiful you didn't hear it at all
maybe you have like she came too
late
everybody oh I yeah oh my good
go wow
everybody something is here
Revelation revelation
[Applause]
[Music]
wo fing
say
[Music]
does
remember little days her memory is back
your div
business how much are you pay are you
charging for it's going to be um 500
coins for a divorce wow that's no why
you have this
business what is what's going on no
divorce we don't need your
business that's what you say that's you
say but they'll come crawling to me in
demand between who could
if it means if it means that I get to
not be the backup plan anymore become
the real
plan I'm not no no I mean for for other
people for other people I can I instead
and divorc from John Watson you
shouldn't do because John
wat Waton to be
hurt let
[Music]
me confirm with your price a th000 coins
no no no no no Co
[Music]
all the music I think I'm assuming they
have all the myth music the
[Music]
first yeah bam w
hay hit
it slight memory that you were used to
be a maid and now you're striving for a
higher
position
hello a
meow a
meow meow that weapon is so shiny oh
that's scary you like it it's it's a
very sharp weapon it's it's beautiful
but looks very deadly I'm not going to
hurt you because you cute I'm going to
I'm going to kill the fake the fake
queen though you're the fake queen wait
is call don't do
that so funny today are you are you gr
than the clown University H second in
the clown University
huh I you
know it's okay it's okay you're not
you're not
so what makes you the queen what wait
wait I can't can't hear you come here
come here come here let's let's let's
talk one on one yeah so what makes you
think you are the next Queen because I
feel
that you feel that did you have an
interaction with the King no I want to I
I don't want I I don't want to I don't
want that that case Clos you are not the
[Music]
queen no connection what's about what
about what about the
king yes what about the king like what's
about the king do you think I'm opening
going to admit that iron
you huh like it's a secret I'm not going
to tell
you best choose your words carefully
yeah I need
okay listen if you if me and you make an
aliens right yes uh I can you can be you
can be the second Queen and me and you
can rule this word together but no
second no second that that that that
that you know you're the second in
position we can unite our power and yeah
and
and arrange an aliens and become
stronger together I do like the idea of
that however I believe the second should
be the other way
around we someone is
listening hey this is privacy social
dist we were talking of Jo day
you guys are pcking Cal down Cal down
Cal down C down come
down let us go to the underwater dungeon
let us go
[Music]
us where is norissa ravencraft and Mory
copi yeah yeah where' they go we we talk
another time mayhaps we should call it's
too dangerous now
I will
call
okay I'm going to I I don't I'm not
going to tell you I don't trust you I'm
sorry what no after you left Amber con I
don't trust you
anymore I thought you both left
ambercoin do not pry Shakira Shakira
Shakira what do you mean I when you talk
like that I know but still do not do not
cry it is business between us two I am
concerned because I have been told that
you may actually be leading me on bu we
are busy you're leading me on aren't
youing oh leading you on I don't know
how I have to phe it leeding you on am I
really your your KN in your service or
am I less than that to you you
oh hi
[Music]
hell patat pat pat thank you pat pat how
you doing I'm doing good I heard I heard
your your team is are you heard of the
scammers oh uh yeah yeah I heard of the
scammers I'm going to kill them oh oh
okay you're going to kill him okay I'm
going to take care of it yeah yes yes we
make Justice we bring Justice in this
word yeah oh your your weapon is yellow
shiny oh yeah because I did the second
dungeon and I think when you make when
you make the second dungeon too you
become
stronger oh I oh your yellow too I must
gain the strength that you guys
have I will do my best yeah yeah
yeah good luck with your with your
dungeon thank you thank you
yeah oh oh you guys are so close to
me
okay thank you rock that that that girl
looks like a rock have you noticed that
e yeah kind rocks have you seen so far I
don't know she looks like a rock I don't
know why looks like a gem if anything to
me sparkling gem I don't know to me it
was more like a
rock so I don't know we did we did the
things we wanted to do
um I like when the go the go by with the
horse is
funnym there's always like something
going on you got to watch all the PE of
these guys yeah ah ah we got we ah turn
we can turn in the side quest
yeah I I have to I have to uh go
now okay but I'll continue my side quest
tomorrow or tonight night we'll see okay
thank you so much I'll see you soon in
uh like in three days oh yeah well when
you come back okay we me I want to help
you with all the dances okay I promise
okay like since there is revisiting side
quests yeah you can revisit them well it
is my first time yeah yeah I want to
play with you so please uh let me know
what time you come so I I make sure to
be here for you okay
you watching out for me thank you yeah
of course we do together we are a team
even even that what politics come
between us ah even if you regret being a
Amber coin I am a a loyal Amber Co and
even if you don't recognize yourself as
an ember Co member I do think you are
always part of this Guild even if you
don't think so I mean I don't know it's
not like that I don't think uh uh so
just you know like um I I feel like I
needed some company and it was offered
to me
kindly I see I see I didn't want to be
on my own too much no because I'm always
here for you yeah you are you are that's
true it's all right I got you it's the
best don't worry thank you I see you
soon okay take care of you all right
thank you for playing with me it was fun
thank you too byebye Amber coin Amber am
coin Amber coin
yay byebye I'm going
out I'm leaving
byebye bye byebye
[Music]
byebye see you later byee
byebye
s all right
dintino I go
now and I'll uh I'll I'll talk to you I
I don't know I was thinking to play
again tonight because I want
to I want to finish the side quest so uh
uh we'll
see later I don't know I'll tell you
okay gorilla stream
eventually um if we don't uh meet each
other
tonight um let's meet tomorrow at the
same time as today
okay I appreciate you Sai thank you so
much for watching and thank you so much
for the members and everything for thank
you so much for supporting this pink
pper I see you guys soon thank you come
here come here give me hug come here
come here come here come here come
here
[Music]
bye-bye T thank you so much
bye I have to say one thing one
thing I want to say I want to say one
thing before I
leave big cat me big
trouble
byebye my OBS broke I don't see oh oh no
I see byebye
[Music]
I
H one sec uh another thing I want to say
you uh can you can you make a nice raid
message for GIS and Pie everyone make
make sure to to ra Caris and Pie okay
give her so much love
[Music]
raate you guys byebye
oh am
going thank you
[Music]