[Music]
What's wrong Kia-
chan, it's embarrassing, it's embarrassing
, that's how it started. Comments too.  It's
okay if it's not the first time. [Music] So, let's introduce ourselves. Let's go. Yes, let's go. Commas Noel Shirokane, a member of the 3rd generation of Ruful Live. [Music] Why are you so embarrassed?
Um, Hololive English, uh,
Fujinaga, uh, I'm Etaka from Austria. I've
never done ASMR before.
Thank you. I've never done it before
. That's great. I
have something to teach you. Wait.
Today, that Kia-chan asked the ringmaster to
teach us about ASMR,
so we did a collaboration.
Why? I was thinking of doing SM.
Well, I guess it's just an off-collaboration idea with Noiru-senpai, but I thought it would be no good if it wasn't this one. Well, if that's the case, let's do ASMR. Oh yeah, I don't know
if I can do that much on my own.  I
may not have any plans to do it,
but I think it would be better if Noru-senpai taught me at least once.  I
'm looking for it, I think it's the person who's looking for it, because
when the group leader set up this frame, he said, Wow, I'm
looking forward to Kiara-chan's AS. There's
already a lot of things like that. He
said it like a bar in a foreign language, so don't get used to it.
Please, wait a minute, that's right, the comment is
dead. It's been a long time since I've been. I've always
been like that. When I erase it once, I feel like if I
change just one pixel, it's ok. It's fixed. It's fixed.
go home
Alright,
ah, let's go home. Alright, that's right. Today, I'm
wearing that Liandre costume that looks delicious. Ah, ah, no do
. Please try saying it properly in German. Diandru, diandru, ah, dean, guesu, ah, that's right. Today, I'm going to Mamoru Anoma.
Well, it's been 1 year and 5 months since I
last attended the ASMR course.Who was the
last one?Well, I guess it was Rene.  I'm
pretty sure that's what happened, so after that, I continued to watch a series of birds,
and as usual, I taught Chiara-chan a lot of things,
like how to clean her ears, and then I taught her how to clean her ears, and then after
that, Chiara-chan
tried out the actual battle by herself.  But after that,
while Chiara-chan took the trouble to teach me some words, we both said, ``I
wish we could do some SMR together.''
Actually, I thought about ear cleaning, but actually,
if I got hit with that stick, I'd be
really bad at it. That's right.
Yeah, yeah, maybe this
is Japanese culture. Well, yeah, that's fine, but when I
stream ASMR overseas, I'm really bad at it.  They look at me quite a lot,
but it's special, special, special, and so on.It
may not be only in Japan,
but at least in Europe, ear
cleaning isn't something relaxing.  I see.  I do
n't have any words to say that it feels good,
but I don't like it at all.I'm
making some adjustments.I don't know if it's
good or not, but I'll
try it anyway.  Let's
do this as usual,
but please
try cleaning your ears with this cotton swab. By the way, I
'd like to say something to those commenters and listeners.  and today's sound
Hmm, I wonder what they say on the left and right sides of KU100,
so the
leader may be on the left on the screen, but for
KU100, the right ear is in charge of that.
Please,
please use the k100 standard. I see. I
don't understand what you're saying. Yes,
there's a left and a right. Why is it the other way around? Why is it the other way around?  It's
facing me, so it's facing me, so it's
right. It's okay if you use OBS to reverse it
. There are so
many things. Let's just do it as it is. We
did it.  You
can put it in, will
cle. Don't be too strong. I
did it a little bit so you don't break it.
[Music]
I hope you get caught, but it's in.
But this is what I was called by a doctor before,
but really, this is what I say in my ear. But this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, that
cotton swab, that's it. When I
put it in this way, this way, this way, this way, it
's not good, it's natural.
Yes, you should take out the garbage. Hira-
chan Yes, this is JMR. It's not real.
Yes, in real life, if you
were to clean your ears like you would with an SMR, your
ears would be damaged if you were a normal person. But that's true.  It's a
world of imagination, after
all. You shouldn't use your imagination, so it's a little
different from reality. Noel, senpai.
Have you ever had a clogged ear? It was so clogged that you had to go to the doctor. It was
so clogged that you couldn't hear anything.
Yes, no, no, no, no, no, no, I have
to go to the doctor. First of all,
what do you call that floor? It's not an electric fan, it's not a fan. How do you say that floor?
After that, I took a shower and had my
ears showered in a small shower.The
shower was really strong and stinging.It
was a really strange feeling.
Well,
maybe the sensitivity of the microphone is too high,
and it might damage everyone's ears.I
see, there are things like that.Well, it's a good
learning experience.Have a chair.
Please come in. That's right, Kia-chan. I
'm feeling her ear picks right now, but I can feel her gentleness. It
doesn't feel good at all, it
feels good, but after all, Kiara-chan
herself is the type of person who doesn't pick her ears up in moderation. So
what should we do about this?  I don't know what to do,
but I
think it's about time for the comment section to go a little deeper.
Seriously, it's so loud.  It's
not too loud, it's not noisy, it's okay
By the way, the cat inside this ear is white. Yeah, it's
because of that microphone part. Don't
push it too hard because it will break a little
. Ah, here, here, right, right, right here, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right here, right?
Okay, oh, I'm sure there's
something wrong with Dada,
red, red,
bladingOhmyLetmerid
oftheBL, stop it, stop it.
I'll give it to you Kira-chan, yes, everyone in the comment section is crying. Don't say things like that. It's just your imagination. Yes, that's right. If it hurts, everyone will be in pain. It's okay. I'm your nurse. I'm going to treat this. I
'll fix it. I'll fix it.  Good,
good, I will
heal your ears that Ibroke I broke my ears.
By the way, in addition to cleaning your ears,
can you also wipe your nose? By the way, you can also do that nose spray.
By the way, just a little bit more. Is
this really
okay? Even if I go, it'll be too much. Hey,
yeah, yeah, that's
right.  It might be Hara-chan's own place name. I'm
not good at this when it comes to things I'm not
good at. I'm not good at this, like getting hit with zaza zaza. Everyone loves this, I like it.
Gorigori is okay, gorigori.  I
can only hear the deep noise, but that's what it is.There
are all kinds of sounds, but
when you're a baby, you're in your mother's womb, and you're
submerged in water.  It's like the
bass A is still flowing,
so it's not completely silent, so
even though something like this is rustling, it
feels like it's so comfortable that it
feels like it's manly.
[Music]
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh It seems like I'm
choosing a radio channel It's my
first time listening to music, so I can't think of anything
But it's
okay to scratch your ears Oh, I'm so
sweaty over there I can see it,
sweat on my face  I'm sweating so much, I'm nervous, but that's
amazing.I'm not the type of person who sweats because of the wind on my hands, but I'm
sweating a lot.I'm
nervous, my heart is pounding.Okay,
yeah, that's it.  I
probably should have gone, but
now that I'm doing SMR this time, Hara-
chan, what do you want to do? Yes, she said that she's not good at listening,
but I think it's okay to do it for her, even though she's not good at
listening.  Oh really,
then let's try being kind. There's only one thing left
for me. Even if I make a sound that you all will love very much,
I'll make a sound
that you will love
very
much.
What kind of sound does it make?
Eh, what?
Change it? The K100 is a little
too big and in the way. I never thought I could
see it. I couldn't see it. Do it one more time.
Do it one more time. Look at me.  I'm watching,
yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, it's Francael, oh, it
's locked, can it be locked, wait, no, it's not, it's
totally different, it's different, it's the
same fish face, but it's completely different, yeah, let's do it, it's close,
it's
close, it's close  I do
n't think I'll ever be able to teach you how to make a frog cry,
but imitation is my specialty. But this
is the strength of ASMR. That's right, other people
can't do it, so I'll
do ASMR, Chiara-chan. I'll do ASMR in the future.
I don't know what it is like overseas, where you hear frogs crying at night.Maybe if you live in the countryside
, you can hear all kinds of things.It's
like in Japan.Even in the countryside, you can hear frogs.It's
like something you hear in the summer.
Yeah, that's right, I can't do cicadas anymore Well then, I can't do
cicadas Labora
Collaboration Ah,
this is what it's like Summer night If it's ASMR like this, I'd
like to hear a little more Oh, I see, but it's
fresh and good. I don't know anyone. But hey, yeah,
Kira-chan, this is the world.  There
was a Chinese phrase for demand and supply.Do you know the words demand and supply?
What do you know?What do you know?
What everyone wants and
what you deliver.  It
seems like we're all in agreement, I get it, what everyone wants, yeah, yeah, what they want, I get it, I get it, I get it, I get it, I think it's probably not a frog, I think it's probably not going home.  Well then, let's take a moment to look at that Brahma.
Yes, this Brahma that that leader is holding in his left hand. Hey, it's cute. I'll give it to you.
With this, I'll clean your ears again.
By the way, yes,
with those eyelashes.  I'm going to scratch my
ears with my eyelashes, I
'm going to scratch my ears, or rather, I can make a sound, but I can't make a sound.I can't feel it.I can make a sound, but I can't
make a sound.The existence of eyelashes.
This
kind of thing is called a butterfly kiss.When a
baby's kiss touches my skin, it
feels like a gentle butterfly kiss.  What is it, I've
never heard of it, no, I've never heard of it.
Yeah, yeah,
myes. Give me a little kiss
. I'll give you a butterfly kiss right now. I'm not a
Butterfly Keith. No, I've never heard of it. But it
's definitely something.  The face and
yeah, the leader is going to learn a little bit. Now I
remember the frog, too.
Why are butterflies growing in my ears? Oh, this is that
one. I'm going to go with that one.
Oh, you're so kind.
Alright, alright, alright, I worked hard overtime today.
That's amazing.
Reality Reality SM Overtime might be good, but it's
work, right? You worked hard at work and school, right
? Kia
is the type who only talks about realistic things, and that's it.  I'm
sorry, that's fine, that's just my personality. So please do
n't take the last train home today.
Let's go home early.
The weather wasn't so good today, isn't it?
Moo, I'm relieved that summer is finally over.
I don't like summer in Japan. It's hot. Hello,
hello.
Hello, hello. It's hot. I'm glad it's over. Akia
-chan, Kiara-chan, I understand too.
Kiara-chan is a poisonous and creative mama.  I don't like it,
but the whispers are
really good. Thank you. Just one time last time,
yeah, just as a joke, I
did ASMR on that computer. That's right. That's right, that
computer that runs on Minecraft.  I
read out the specs and said, ``I do
n't know what that means,''
but I read the name and number of the graphics card, etc. Oh yeah,
yeah, but I've been
invited to various SMR lectures so far.
Kia-chan is really good,
thank you so much, Kukukuku, Marine, and
Hanesake. Her voice is a little quiet, but
she's so big
. I had a hard time, but Kiara-chan...  That
's amazing, that's great.
Thank you, Noel-senpai, you're good too. Thank you very much.
So, both of you should collaborate.
Collaboration, collaboration, bofu size bohuen
[Music]
E
like
here. Sue, there's
no Brahma like this in other countries. I
wonder if this is a cat.  It's not a toy, it's
different. There's something like this, so I do
n't know what to say. I don't know how to describe it. It's true, it's Ponte Ponte Ponte. For those
overseas who are currently in the comment section,
this is what Noel is holding in his left hand.  I'm
doing this right now.
[Music]
Yeah, I'm telling you that sound now.
For my birthday last year, I was
surprised that you brought out a blanket for me.I got it
from Shihanesa, so I put it on the sofa.Thank
you, by the way, from earlier.
It's the leader who's stomach is making noises. I can't hear
it. It's true, but it was found out in the comments section. It's true that everyone has good ears. It's because everyone is saying this. Surprisingly, everyone has become dumb.  I don't have any, so I'm sensitive. I
haven't eaten, no, I've eaten, but I
get hungry when Mamoru comes in.
Ah, I get that kind of thing, just like that. It's
nice to hear that cat make that noise.
Yo,
that's amazing, that cat is lurrrrrrrrrrrrrrrggggggrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
But the first time I heard him imitate his own cat for the first time with an ASR microphone,
it was like an ASMR mic.  Then, the
image is completely different. Ah, I guess it's a bit different
. Yes, it's different from usual. Drink some water. Yes,
Papa. It
sounds like a park car. It sounds like an engine.
Engine, no, the cat is an engine. That's right.
Yeah
, yeah, it's better than the bridge. Nemi-o, cat-chan, Mio. There's a cat in my left ear. I'm hungry, and there's a tulle. It's a cat. It's a cat. The senior who is kicking the cat is also spinning around. Hey, it's long. I can't shake that bell.  Tan: I
can't do something like roll or dollar,
so I probably can't do that either. Yeah, I
thought if I were Japanese, I could probably pronounce that R because of that.
But you know, I'm a little short on the bottom. I
can't get it out, I can't get it out, wait, I can't get it out either. That's
right, that new En member,
Nerisa-chan, can't get it either. Lately, I think I've realized that she can't get it either.  I
was really happy, but I can't believe
there's another person like me. I'm so
happy that I can only do so much.
It's the first time I've ever been a voice actor.  I
took a lesson with the Flo Live members, and
at that time we talked about the length of the tongue.It
was embarrassing, but the leader was short, but that's why he was
shorter than everyone else, and no one was the
same.So we're all the same.I'm so happy.  Yes,
sometimes when I go to the dentist or something, they
ask me to ring the bell, but I try to give more,
but every time they ask me to give more, please
give more.  I'm going to get killed
But I can't get it out. I ca
n't get out what I can't get out. I can't get it out, so I
guess they won't understand. It's hard to eat ice cream. Yeah, I know it's hard to eat. I know, I'll chew on ice cream. But it's too late.
But Kiara-chan moves a lot, so I'm going to talk
to Mike.
If you don't let me get too close to you, you'll have to
stretch a little more. Your body is so
stiff. I'll help you stretch. If you
try it here, you'll start screaming.  It
's hard, it's hard, it's hard, it's hard, I'm going to play around with
it a little bit more. I
had a massage today. I had a massage.
I had an oil massage. Oh, it was really good. I
also massaged my ears, and I can feel my penis.
Wait a minute, I've got some tissues, so wait a minute. It's okay to just sweat
. Lie, what's this? What's this? It's
oil. It's hair oil.
You're so kind. You're like this.
[Music] Oh,
how are you? How
can you be so arrogant? It's so
good. No, it's not like you've given me an oil massage like this. I've
had you avoid my head, right? Usually,
normally.  You know, I don't know if it hurts my ears or my head, but I
had my shoulders rubbed really hard,
oh, so hard, so
hard, I can't hear anymore.
No, I can hear it. I can hear it,
but it's sealed up.
What were you trying to do
if you couldn't hear me? Hey, just a little. I'll tell you all about Noel-senpai, so please don't listen to me. I
won't ask. Well, I don't have
anything to say. Let's
see.  I wanted to try something like that.Ah,
you all couldn't hear me, right?That
's amazing, Chiara-chan.By the way,
there's a trick to covering your ears.In the book, it
seems like it's a little disappointing right now.  It's too much
of a secret right now. I
don't want to hear it, but I'm too eager to hear it. I
put too much effort into it. After all, this
KU100 is a precision opportunity, so if I
put too much effort into it,  You know, no matter how you
apply pressure, you
end up making noise, right? Actually, I
couldn't really hear it. How do you do it? It's
difficult to adjust it like this. You have to adjust the amount of pressure.
[Music]
This is difficult, but this is what it feels like.
Everyone ca
n't hear me, so Noel,
Senpai, you
can't hear me, you can't hear me. It's
okay, ok, I feel like I was in a swimming pool.
I know, I know, because I'm being squeezed, I
know, I know, I feel like I'm being squeezed by the water pressure, and I
'm so sorry, I
didwanttodrownyou,
what does "drown" mean in Japanese?
What do you mean you can't breathe when you're inside? I'm
drowning. I'm sorry for
spilling
on you. I'm sorry for spilling on you. I didn't particularly plan on hurting you.
Yeah, I'm sorry, I'm your nurse.
So live, live.  It's okay because this nurse
just does funny things like frog cries.
That's an entertainment program. I
really like all kinds of programs.
Well, it's about time for a massage,
ear cleaning, tissues, tissues, etc. It's nice and clean,
and there's a trash can in the back.Okay, that's
good.It's okay for today.The
leader noticed that, ok,
no.  I'm here. What are you saying? What are
you saying? No, that Kihara-chan can stand by herself.
Yes, it looks like she's running an errand for the first time. Without the leader,
I usually whisper to that KFP-san.  I
mean, it's like that aim
Yeah, try it ShesaysShe
isn't needed here, I'm
watching you, I'm watching you around here, you're
not leaving the room, okay?  It
seems like it's just Kia-chan. I'm
sorry, but I'm using your channel.
From today onwards, it
's my channel. I'm about to cry. What should I do?
No, you can use only the winnings. That's right.
Hello. I'm here too. I'm
heretohowyoudo. Can you all speak English?
LetdosomeenglASMR
If you can't speak English, there's a book out recently called Horrive
English's Hollistening,
so that's right.  I'm
sure there are some mistakes in the book, so please
refer to them.
Well then, that's what I'm saying in SMR. It's
great to be alive, oh praise, praise, nobi,
English praise, praise, homu, homu nobi,
praise, praise, oorets do insh,
praise, nobee. You have to
get into the e zone. Go
in, do your best, zon in.  Oh
IAmserNowlet
ser
youdidSUagreatJ
today
Ah,
youlook
beauti
Beautiful Beautiful
Beautiful Even
Beautiful So beautiful
Aah
useyouSUagoodgood
personGMaybeifyouto
begoodMakeYoufood
later
OK SoWhatwouldyoulike
toeat laterorWouldyou prefertojustgo outtoa restMaybeWeshouldGO Yakiniku to Yakiniku Yakiniku Yakiniku Yakiniku is
good.
Kana
Yaki Taiyaki Yaki
What's this? It's a bit of a head.
Spar is good. I'm going to go back to the leader for a moment. Go back and
go back to the destination. Oh, it's
small. It's
small. Thank
you for the rescue.
Noel Rescue.
Okay. Well, I'm grilling yakiniku, so please leave.
Yeah, I can't do that.  I want to order something.I want to order
something.It looks
delicious.
Hey, it's
delicious. Let's
bake it on high heat. Let's grill it on high heat. It
's
okay. I'll leave it to you. Yes, it's delicious.  I
wanted to hold my hands together, hold my hands together, hold my hands together, hold them
together, hold them together, it's
stiff, it's stiff,
it's sweat, oil,
oil.  It's a
mixture of all sorts of things, so yeah, it's amazing,
moist and moist, oh
my sweat, to-stis spaghetti. That
sweaty in English is
Sweaty, it's called spaghetti.
Yes, it's
called spaghetti. Sweaty spaghetti, oh, sweaty, spaghetti. Yes, it's
sweaty.  It's good, I
'm sorry, I'm sorry, it was
delicious, it was delicious.
Well, I'm done eating. I'm done eating. I guess I'm
done. I'm going to eat Yakiniku. Thank you for the
feast. It was delicious.
ThankyoufortheF
Dessert Dessert
Dessert Dessert Is there something
wrong with this? What kind of technique is this time? Um, okay.
Let's see what's out. I
just put this out last night. Try it. Eating Japanese is Japanese. It's
scary and scary. I
think that's what I'm eating.
Yes,
it's good. Yes, I'll eat anything. It's
good. It's delicious. Yes, it's ASR, and it sounds like it's chewed a lot. It
's a Japanese sweet that many people eat. I see. Small
fish white and small fish white.
Copa, Kojiro, Kojiro, and by the
way, thank you very
much, Mr. I got it, thank you,
and thank you for the meal.
Before I go to pay, to pay, to pay,
take a moment to take a look at that leftover drink.Okay, I'm going to drink it at the same time.Yo, it looks like it's really rich.I
can't drink it.I don't know if my throat is
big, but it's amazing.My throat is so big.  I
heard that.
Ah, ok, I'm full. If I'm
full, I'll pay.
Please, Mama, I'm a senior, so I'm sure.
Credit card or cash.
Well, I don't have a card with me right now, so I'm going to use a
card,
so I'm going to
use a passmo.Is it okay to use a passmo?What should I do with a passmo?  Is it
okay for me to play with this
even though Nol-senpai is paying for it? Well then, you can use Pasmo. Are
there any other point cards? I
don't have any points saved up. I see, you can use Pasmo.  Well, I'll
just ask you once. Then I'll
put it
here. Wow, it wasn't here. Yes, it was Pasmo 100. I hit it with Pasmo. Please be kind, gentle, gentle right now. Okay, pipi. Well, I don't have any money in it. Enter.  I did
n't know what to do. Do you want to do something else? Well then, on your smartphone, on your smartphone, on your smartphone,
on your smartphone, okay, okay,
on your smartphone, there's no sound on your smartphone. There's no sound on your smartphone. I'll
press it again and make a sound. It's
scary, scary, scary.  It's
scary No matter what kind of sound I try to
make, it's so loud I don't know what it's like. Hey, but it's not even making a sound. What kind of sound is
it? The
smmr isn't making any noise. It looks like it's going to die. It's a
commemorative dust.
It's a commemorative one.
And smile, yes,
pose, wow, yes, yes
, yes, I did it. I did a
great job. It's a great memory of Japan, Noiru.
Maybe my seniors did something today as well.  I'm
doing something that I haven't done, no, I've already done everything.
It's more like I was imagining it. I'm
sorry, I don't want to do it. It's okay. It's
fresh, it's very fresh. But there's only one thing, ah, I guess that's
Noil-senpai.  I've done it many times, and
I've felt like I have to do it.What's
that?My heart beats, my heart beats, my heart beats.Yes, I
want to do it, but does that mean I have to take my clothes off?  Okay, I can go, just
put my chest on your chest. I can
hear the sound of your heart in your ears.
Oh, my stomach, my stomach, my stomach. It's so
good. My, I'd rather listen to the beat. That's
embarrassing, my heart.  Where is my heart
? Where is my heart? I
wonder if it's not beating that much. I can
hear Chiara's heart. It's dead right now.  I
can barely hear it, I
can't hear it, I'm dead, no, I can hear it.Everyone can hear
it.The secret is that you can hear it.That's the
heart beat.
By the way, I usually take my clothes off because I'm alone.
Maybe it's because it's different than usual.
Okay, everyone is doing it pretty
hard.  I
heard you, I'm glad you're alive
, I'm glad you're alive. I guess that's how you do
it. The face was the same when I was with Marine. I think it would be nice to have a look like this, and then we could do this and that together.  I'm
with you. It's
embarrassing, here, here, here, here,
here, here, here, here, here, and
here. Yeah, it smells really good. You
don't know who is who, right? I get it.  It was
happening, it was really happening,
but Noyle-senpai's heart beat,
but you know, I learned a lot, you know,
when we were together with Marin, we were both embarrassed,
so we tried not to touch each other anymore.  I was
trying not to, but Kia-chan
hugged me. She put her arms around me.
Otherwise, it would be difficult.
Well, it's amazing. You smell like sweat. I'm sorry,
that hot Noil-senpai.  I
turned off the air conditioner, so that's what happened before. I
turned on the air conditioner to prevent the noise. I think that's totally possible.
But hey, it's normal, but it seems like it's noisy. Let's
turn it back on.
Okay, let's go home.
Well, I guess I should take it out, take it out, or take it out.
It's a little more, so don't worry about it.
Chiara-chan, you're good at this, but I'm
sure everyone will be happy, so I'm going to take
it out. Yeah, that's
amazing.
[Music]
Eh, I haven't been there until now.I
have a strange feeling.It's really good, but it's so
good.It's so good, but it's so long.I did my
best.Request and request.Um, I'll listen to you in the chair.  I
said, ``OK,'' like before, ``
Yes, I'm listening to you.'' Why are you so embarrassed?
Wait, it's already over here.  It's so bad,
we go all the way to that point. It's really hard, but it's
true. It's amazing. Oh my ears, too. [Music] [Music] It's so warm. What on earth are you
thinking of? Oh, my ears are so hot.  It's a
little hard to cover your ears.You
see, your ears are full of nerves,
so they're sensitive, right?I get a tingle.It's so
refreshing.Is it true?Yes, it's scary.
Isn't it scary? Isn't it scary? It's
not that bad. Isn't it the
hurricane that everyone is talking about?
What is Kiara's hurricane?
If it was like that, it would
be even stronger. Yes, it's quite a difficult feeling, but
Chiara-chan is a constant.  I
think I'm good at pretending. That's amazing.
Then that thing is running.
Yeah, I'm going to die. Oh, then I'm getting a little embarrassed. I'm
getting embarrassed. Let's stop doing that.  Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe.  I get it, it's
nice to know, it feels good. I
want to ask you,
is it now?
No, no, it's okay if it's unreasonable, but it's okay,
daddy, squat squats, etc.  It does
n't have to be a soft skirt if you look like you're looking really big.
Yeah, I
just want to get my heart rate up. I wonder
if I can do that? It's okay, Shehas. The
shape of the knife is really messy. I wonder if you
can tell that the form is good
now.  Slowly, slowly, slowly,
fasta, fasta, fasta,
fastaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah
Oh, I heard you're dead,
but oh, it's a little faster
[music],
and I'm sure it's getting better.  There
are some sounds that I haven't tried yet.
And then there's the gel ball, and
there's this, and it's amazing. When I put it in my ear,
I have
something.
[Applause] Oh, it's
delicious.
Okay, let's do it on the other side.
Okay, first-timers will do things so vigorously
that they'll get pissed off. They'll
break
things. But they
know how to do it, and they're good at it. [Applause] It sounds like they're washing their ears.  I wonder, but Gel
Gol is like the sound of an ear massage,
so this was a comment in English,
but yeah, it feels like it's in a flyer.The
sound of my Niflyer is burning, it's burning.
Hueraku Spicy Chicken Crispy Chicken
Yara-chan looks delicious SMR is good,
but everything goes in that direction.
My audience is M.
This is your fate. Fate, oh, you're
going to be burned.
Okay, eventually this
will happen.  And I
[applause] I can't
eat it, but I can't watch it, Chiara-chan. So,
yes, yes, yes, I turn into tiles and come back to life. That's
right, that's right.
What about everyone on KFP?
Kepi was originally a garden chicken, but
if you put it in the fryer that one time and it dies, I'll give you those feathers,
so it'll
come back to life as that fucho-chicken hybrid, so it's
okay. Yes, it's okay. It'll come back to life as many times as you like.  I
'll only do it once, just once, I'll
revive you, ah, I'll revive you the second time, yeah, you
can't give it up, right? That's right, I'll
do that second time.
Because I can't do it, I have a job. Well, I
originally worked at a fast food restaurant, so
eventually,
if I wasn't old enough to work, I would put it in the fryer and
make it into rice and eat it for the customers.  By the
time I was able to revive the river, I was already
doing that fighting part-time job, and
everyone from there was
helping out, so I
guess I could eat it at least once.  experience fate
If you don't have it, you won't be able to go to war.That
's right.That's right.I
wonder if it's because I want to prove my worth.It's like that kind of spirit to me.  To test Nakagami, I asked Ifraa
how far he would go.The
leader heard this and
said that everyone in KF KFP was having a hard time.Everyone
was happy.That's why they
were burned and burned.  I want to
Nice nice Yeah, great, even now Yes, I remembered it when I didn't watch it,
but yes, I recently bought a cat chime.
Hello, there's a
theme to it.
Nehina's theme is Hinahi Hinamatsuri Fire
Faaa  It's a fire, right? The
chime sounds perfect for Chiara-chan. I
feel like I want to go to sleep. I
'm going back to the way I praised my baby when she was a baby.
Yes, you did your best today
. Let's do our best today and tomorrow. Let's do our
best. Let's do our best.
Well then, the time is right, so
that kind of music really makes Kia-chan
feel good. Oh yeah, and it
kind of sounds like the school chime.  Eh, school It's
different like this overseas, but
when I was in Japan, I sometimes heard
all kinds of sounds on the streets.Children are very confused, so
please write them down.Aaah, there they are.Yeah, something like that,
something here, something in my intestines.  I'm
worried about the group leader, even if it's something like an announcement.It's
okay, Kia-chan.I was
wondering if that SMR teacher could have done it.I was just asking him to tell me.I feel like it's about international exchange.It's
about international exchange.  I seem to have learned a
lot of things from the chair, such as those amazing sticks, and it
seems like it's okay to put in forcefully.I'm
surprised that the listener's ears are listening.  It's
kinda M, so I get
it, so there are a lot of people who like it stronger.If you
do SMR, make it a little stronger.Maybe KFP-san,
everyone likes it stronger.Ah, at the end, I hope
KFP can record one thing.  I
wonder if it's okay to say it as a selfie? Of
course, it's okay, use the left and right, use the left and right, it's okay
.  I
always tube when it's Aspa-chan, so that
's right, that's
right, that's right, Chichi's ASMR version.  It's
not like that, but
thank you very much, Noel-senpai
, Akiara-
chan,
Chie-chan, then in the end it's just the two of us. Well then, that's it,
listeners, LINE-san
and kfp-san, no way.
So, I thought I'd say, ``Would you like to send me a message? Message me?'' I thought I'd say, ``
Let's play together.'' So, um, that's
it. Wait a minute. It's really
hot.
Well, the leader
says, ``Yes, thank you for your continued support.''
Yes, Kiara-chan, yes, I love you. Yes,
say it.
Let's finish it later. Okay
, O message
. Oh, then I'll go.
Yes, thank you for always cheering me
on. Bye-bye-bye. I'm sorry for bothering you.
See you bye bye bye bye too