[Music]
ha
darling ha darling power washing hell
Darlings hello Darlings hello Darlings
shall we introduce ourselves so people
know everyone in the herum of that is
narissa my
herum oh sorry so I mean our holy
Christian Club of course yeah yeah yeah
yeah that
I never agreed to be in a
harm I didn't
know guess it just
happen sister Val here at your service H
lives holy sister Follow
by oh who whom you by me okay but shoo
you're still you're still nunning it up
I it's I will I will be the nun until no
nut November ends then you have no nuns
no n no no n
November okay good to
know I am Tak I don't have a stream open
so now I have free chats open I have all
of y'all's chats open I'm watching
everybody and first time playing the
game let's go wo first time yay first
time power watching you made me buy the
game girls hell
yeah nice
sorry well uh hi ings this is hello live
English Advent devilish Diva the one and
only narissa Raven coft
[Music]
Dio welcome is sweet power wash she is
the hor owner
yes roses are red the fire of my heart
is blue also known as The Scarlet Queen
the harbinger of order leader of Justice
I am Elizabeth Rose blood flame lovely
you to see you
lovely love
hello lovely do you have a short version
of your introduction too or do you
always do the long one no complaints but
that one you do that one dang know
that's her intro there's no shortening
it well the r will be Mighty sad if I
didn't they'll
cry they'll they'll give a big war cry
if not do you think maybe after like 3 4
years or so of doing this you'll you'll
maybe shorten it cuz you'll get too
tired of it cuz recently I even get
tired or like embarrassed about saying
Kik Kitty ke how could you get tired of
saying Kitty key
it's I feel like an impostor these days
oh my gosh are you okay yeah yeah I'm
fine I just I don't know the Kitt key
ain't kiky keing anymore a but you're a
chicken maybe need c what does that have
to do with anything you have to kittyy
it's in your blood uh well try I'll
continue trying what did you do like a k
oh actually how do you say it I struggle
with that ky ky K KY it's more like a
k
k like a one of those trickster
Rhymes k
[Music]
k how is it rhyming not not a rhyme but
like those the tongue twisters for me I
[Music]
struggle that is so we're clean now
right it's okay yeah yeah yeah yeah we
just chilling I'm hoping like do we have
to save water no no screw the screw the
ecosystem
here yeah no don't worry about anything
just have fun the main purpose of this
game is to have a good time yeah okay I
hope there bodies I want to there's no
bodies what but it's Halloween I that's
a different kind of game sh have to find
that game then that will be my comfort
game what's Mory assistance for example
oh I I like that game I just don't like
being
timed yeah that one's really stressful
oh I see I see like I would
play um that game without having to do
things within a certain time
mhm well sh it's time to make your own
game how about that about cleaning hes
this we'll
have we can play that game too the
viseral cleanup thing I only play I
think oh is that about cleaning corpses
yeah yeah actually oh my
God yeah literally you have to burn them
you have to burn the bodies
is that it do you have to find them yeah
yeah you have to go through a room you
have to find them you have to clean up
all the blood you have to clean up all
the bullet holes you have to clean up
all the all the
monsters clean up a prime
scene a game of that coming
out I you know something's like
completely clean does it have 100%
here stop and make a sound and go Bing
okay the thing is I stopped paying
attention
um also when you hover over it and when
if you look up in the upper left corner
it says how much of the map is finished
but if you hover over something and it
doesn't have a like a bar like a white
bar that means it's clean
so for whatever reason I'm not getting
any pings I don't know why I got P I got
like four ping so far I know I hear you
guys getting pings and it's making me
jealous so I'm going to go do something
else I can ping you on Discord if you
want no it's
okay often enough oh my gosh the
jealousy the
drama I rarely get pinked by Nissa these
days I don't ping anybody on Discord so
you're not alone in that I will I have
most I sent you my
kitty please
respond you got this see him pretty much
first as soon as it was confirmed you
were the first person I sent the video
to if you don't continue sending me
weekly updates I will divorce you once I
get him it's going to be so over how are
you holding up herb while they
flirt I'm fine I'm just jumping on uh
you just cleaning uh kotus Empire's
head not feeling anything you're so
strong yeah she's light
my pain tolerance is very
high I don't feel
B um so for first fire fire doesn't hurt
each other for first time players uh if
you hit the the tab Button as Kara
mentioned it'll light up all the dirt so
if you're like missing dirt and you
haven't gotten a ping but also if you
hit Escape you can go through and see
all the different things that need to be
clean if you select one of those things
it'll make it light up on the map like
it'll start kind of like blowing in and
out white so you can actually then go
and find if you're like oh what's
missing I have like 1% left on this
thing but I don't know where it is
that's how you can find it no while
you're talking you're glitching
throughout my entire screen which I find
hilarious that's
so I wonder if anything I'm cleaning is
actually like cleaning
then it's okay we just yapping she's a
ghost we yapping
I'm ghost you're not here to clean
you're here to Yap we were hired to Yap
exactly y oh this is pretty light I like
this did you guys do anything for
Halloween actually ground hit by storm
uh what if we did anything yeah dress up
or anything well I stream yeah
I we dragged you guys to a a a haunted
mansion oh yeah oh that's right and
everything worked perfect
so I heard it was there's a first time
for everything and you got to like you
know slowly ease into the VR world yeah
yeah no no wait at
all you know what the the Ian uh fandom
is very used to having to wait an
extended time for the streams to start
if it's a VR
stream they know there'll be more
waiting time than like if the official
start in time is like whatever 8:00 p.m.
they know it will not start until 10:00
p.m. usually you he that guys future
future reference we no don't don't don't
listen just in case we start on time
that's true yeah you got to be ring at
all
times yeah just make sure you have like
a snack an extra snack or something else
to do just in and 10 cups of coffee so
you could stay up yeah yeah that Red
Bull mhm I haven't tried Red Bull before
actually what yeah
monster oh my God I think that's good
because they're really bad for your
health and they don't oh you shouldn't
drink them all the time but no no no no
you encourage I like every now and
again Shori I'm going to leave can you
invite me back okay
bye everywhere do you are you ready to
be invited I think I can join I'm
joining okay I
S yeah something's happening I need a
young priest and old com for you yeah
literally Sayan no power of the Gods
canar
you you know what I feel like right now
EV you need a you feel evil yeah cuz I'm
I'm um power washing the uh tombstones
and it's reminding me of that girl who
is like cleaning uh Graves oh yeah that
one yeah and she's doing it with like
not the right product
yeah and like kind of like like it can
be respectful there's people who do it
respectfully but that girl I don't know
she's just selling her product I think
so I feel like her right now no it's
okay these are just Halloween
decorations okay I mean in Japan
go down to the gravestones and clean
them
up everything's got to be clean in
Japan clean and
beautiful I think that's really nice oh
I never get to see the the graveyard in
Japan I wanted to see what you wanted to
see a graveyard in Japan yeah cuz they
look a lot different cuz your your
headstones are like more rectangular
than ours ah plus there was like a
temple there I could have seen a monk
and be like what's up monk but in
English true I guess they are pretty
different yeah Shori it won't let me
back in oh no n i able to join trying to
steal your
harm yeah she's stealing my Harum
successfully she's claiming it for I
just I'm just so visible I guess here
let me let me try again it's it's not I
don't know if maybe we need to restart
it and it's just glitched out resum yeah
let me go back to the thing sorry
everyone
no I've been cleaning so much no it job
yeah it should save all the progress
yeah so how do I like get to the menu
though is my my question oh that's a
good question I have no answer I see you
probably just have to quit
dang this feels good oh just save button
too okay still like zooming everywhere
for me I'm not even I'm not even I had a
close was the game that's crazy okay I I
invited you again just to try it one
more time and then after this let's see
if I can like uh go
back I for you if you're like Zip
zapping everywhere like it it won't load
you don't understand oh man okay let me
let me see career let me just go to a
random mode and leave you guys trying
trying to join you is crashing the game
for me what is the online mode not so
stable in this game it usually is this
is happened before but a long time
ago okay sometimes the game's just crazy
I don't know the best way to leave this
thing cuz the menu is actually like a
tablet yeah everyone everyone completely
leave maybe close the game completely
and then reopen it all right get the
heck out
everyone you're wonderful
though oh oh got kicked out nice yeah
yeah I'm following her
rules the M completely shutting the game
down I did just in case yeah all right
yes
ma'am I mean I'm not doing what you say
advin I'm just I'm with the floor you
know why would you do what we say you
know I'm doing what I want I want to
close
it okay open it me too I'm resuming the
Halloween
Town okay and then you can just send out
invites again it's a magical day don't
start don't start cleaning until you
send out invites as soon as you said
Halloween Town like a certain song came
to mind that I cannot sing out loud you
can say it out loud you can no I can't I
can't sing it out loud oh you can't sing
it okay yeah all right I'm inviting you
guys
[Music]
again it's not all right I hope it
worked oh
yeah is it not working oh it's it's
connecting slowly it's loading it's
downloading dirt wa
dirt I'm going to I'm going to go clean
I see you guys don't start until we're
in don't start until we're in okay okay
okay I don't I don't see that's the
issue is because the dirt is constantly
changing it has a hard time loading you
in oh okay okay now we just wait for
herb and hopefully the game won't glit
yeah I'm I'm I'm slowly getting in there
she's getting in her F she going to come
out when she's all her the herb is the
word yeah her there go welcome back
welcome back okay
cleaning we're not going to have to
restart yeah we just wish I raved our
game
wow so
beautiful wow oh so I have this hanging
body in my place it's like one of those
fake Halloween decorations for St okay
that that's okay I nearly took out my
like notebook and I was like uhhuh
yeah and the in the hanging body like I
got it for like $5 it's supposed to
shake if you have batteries inside it
but it's kind of like not realistic
which makes sense it was cheap I just
have ground bu it because of Halloween
or just because of for your own
Aesthetics
yes
any well I think it was on sale cuz it
was after Halloween by then it empty I
was going to throw it away and I left it
on the floor and my pile of throw away
or like a maybe donate but then my cat
managed to go inside it and then it was
like it was so cute it's like oh they're
hiding in the little body bag and the is
just like a butterfly so I'm hoping that
they do it again so I have a reason to
keep it
around a yeah I hope they you got to
keep it if if it became the cat toy I
know I want them to sleep in there
more you are so cute and unhinged shwy
it's not even unhinged I just think it's
funny it's a little unhinged really your
definition of unh is weird well you know
we some people have their Christmas
decorations out for another five months
she on her
floor that's that's fine my parents did
that with the Christmas light before
they kept it for a year cuz they didn't
want to take it down that's
valon Quon style are your parents Quon
no she has her Christmas things up all
the time at least on her screen oh she
plays Christmas music all the time
that's cuz she's spreading the joy of
giving yeah
yeah my pumpkin my
pumpkin
hello wa I was going to say Red Bull did
you know it's from Austria really like
the headquarters are also in Austria was
like one of the few famous things we
have I guess but it seems so americ tour
at the factory
there yeah yeah you can and like they
sponsor a lot of like Austrian um oh
there you go sports people and all that
like I don't know why they spor me
though they say that you want to like
get drunk off your
thing get drunk off the Red Bull you
mean yeah you want to drink it up guzzle
it up you know if you have a Jaga
buom oh the thing is normally I try to
avoid red bu looks like my emergency
solution if I'm really tired cuz I
[Music]
don't only an
emergencies understandable I just feel
the pain of tiredness you already have
Wing you don't need it me oh thank
you oh I'm wingless yeah yeah you can't
fly oh yeah it's Red Bull for light blue
girl ger
hell who the heck is Megan I was not
listening to her who Megan oh the m is
texting me yeah so that's that that's
the person who has paid you to do this
so you can read the backstory in which
they'll tell you the lore of why it got
dirty like this or just random lore of
the game I the lore was that she was too
lazy to
clean probably
huh do you see on the
pumpkin I see you on there oh yeah okay
I don't know how you got there
Wings you guys watch those hoarder
channels and then they clean up the
hoarder stuff I kind of like those I do
too it brings me joy yeah are you a
hoarder is anybody a hoarder no uh I
can't be the queen mother doesn't like
it I
cannot I want to try to control myself
stressed things in the past a little bit
but not like sickly yeah yeah yeah oh
they just like collect a
bunch
yeah like things from Japan
don't and now I'm hoarding like band
letters like after 4 years there's so
many I don't want to like get rid of
them so they'll just get more and more
and more buy a buy a storage unit then
buy a a storage unit for just
it might not be worth a storage unit yet
but we can work on that
right more letters more
letters I used to get a different size
ones usually when it comes to storage
units baby storage units yeah you can
you can get like one that's like a
locker okay in great Exodia you
can I used to hoard like homework from
like this years thinking maybe I'm going
to need this for my next class the next
semester and then once everything was
done it's like see you I'm out I think
that's kind of smart keeping materials
from previous
years materials but I'd keep them
because I'd sketch in them and I'd be
like that's a cute picture I drew then
i' keep
it me to I remember at the end of the
year people would clean out their
lockers mine was pretty clean but every
everyone would just have tons of
homework on in theirs and they have to
get like a giant trash can to clean it
up and there'd be like a maybe a roting
sandwich for some of their lockers
yeah I think
funny we should power wash a school it
seems there's potential there
potential more money from our power
okay pumpkin are you finished
[Music]
finally
it's little bit here so relaxing and
maybe a little dizzying actually oh uh
hit the C
button oh I see yeah that feels weird
you can hit it and unhit it so it'll
lock um your screen a bit so that way
you can instead of you know having your
head move with the power washer it's
just Frozen
Yeah it it helps with the motion
sickness
yeah n has so much experience with this
game I love this
game wow one of my
favorites you're also one of my favor
well well
shi's
I you too
Queeny what's up
you ever heard of a poonal bubble poonal
bubble I'm on top of the well for
me why am I in your
screen
uh yes spice is something happening on
your interet sucks oh my internet's fine
your Internet sucks maybe your Internet
sucks you're the one who's like
glitching around you're on top of the
well I was I'm off now oh now I'm on top
of the well I didn't even know yeah you
are
yeah what's your favorite no girl you
lighting my gas uh good I like use the
yellow one the yellow or the red
one he what was the
question what your favorite no are am I
still glitching on your screen herb
a I think she's hallucinating I think
this map is just
haunted see
everywhere that house should be just
chori I mean I'm on a t Sor it makes
sense that's true like a
stalker are you cheating on me herb I
thought you were monitoring
me
excuse what's going on there I don't
know I think I
think it didn't say monitor just
narissa yeah but I'm your favorite
monitoring your back I mean I monitor
you probably the most but that's besides
the
point you need like extra watching
that's why okay I guess I can share you
with
youi you know what they say happy wife
happy life you mean allow me to sh what
the me what to do this the most rotation
attempt
I've all of my flirtation attempts are
awkward what are you talking
about well I didn't want to say that but
okay did you see my my stream title for
this by the way I did I did yeah I saw
people tweeting about it I just like it
was a funny title
cool
yeah what is it again don't worry about
ittle yes worry about it oh I I'll let
your chat tell you I I I'll let them
surprise copy paste my
Halloween happy
Halloween man I love
Halloween me too I'm a Christmas girl
it's all right I like Christmas I like
dressing
up yeah yeah you never sent me that
picture of you in your costume oh I
ended up feeling sick so I ended up not
changing and dressing up after all it
was really depressing for me I know I
wanted to die I wanted to die so bad
like you could dress up
maybe today tomorrow you can still dress
up yeah you can always dress up but now
I'm looking for like I want to find a
cute dress to wear for
Christmas cuz I don't have one
just go
naked no you can't go naked it's
Christmas yeah it'll be like a Christmas
present no like Merry Christmas Shivers
put a ribbon around your
body that's like some fancy laun type
yeah you guys are
sick for what you're sick no yeah I am
sick actually
yeah what about
it it's getting six season again
everybody careful I'm healing now though
thankfully I don't want to travel
sick
yeah I don't want you to travel sick
either
yeah I think I need a lad
there well luckily there's tons around
the map
where's all the water coming
from uh your heart does this not have
Collision I'm sorry what oh I guess only
you guys could pass
through I I cannot seem to climb the
ladder I will I will go save just in
case skill issue yeah skill issue maybe
I was the ghost all along
I like that that plot twist
yeah I would like to go back to the old
house is that a musical song or no I
thought was another house in this game
no it's the
Smiths oh that band that only I like
Smith don't they have some like famous
songs I'm sure I like song at least yeah
how soon is now from Charmed is the
Smith song ah there you go there you go
Lissa strong
already Charmed let's freaking
go it's it's funny cuz I heard it first
from Charmed and I was like this is the
best song I've ever heard and I never
knew that that wasn't like the official
version and then I found it later by
tattoo that one that one band what they
also one they covered it yeah and I was
like oh my God this is amazing it's the
song from Charmed and then I found when
I got really into dismiss I found that
and I was like are you kidding
me this is where that song is
from need to research more yeah oh yeah
you know my my void songs My we stuff
you're my little wee oh I thank you
you're my little
pony you always be in my heart
wow okay there
Tarzan my
littley Che nandos that's what you are
you're my little cheeky Nando what is
that cheeky Nando what she say to me
chcken nando
me have you never heard of nandos before
like a chicken
nuggets it's a it's a restaurant where
they they mostly spicy chicken with
Terry Perry the best it's very yummy
yummy not as good
as uh no but I'm aware of it oh I'll
treat you one day okay okay interesting
I got to study my rivals in the business
I'm in yeah coming
over
yeah I will steal herb from narissa
because I am geographically closer to
her anyway oh this is some NTR
happening actually owns me what
the Yeah I I I don't I don't own herb
herb it's her own woman yeah she just
monitors me don't you
know what if we collector like a like a
Pokemon we just throw a ball at herb see
who gets her first will that work
herb can you get my ball if I ask nicely
please oh anything for you sweetheart
I'll jump into you what the [\h__\h] let me
just squeeze on
in one foot then the other let's go I'm
going to write my twit longer right now
o your Google Document let's go because
I
with herb yeah oh my God don't is your
account not um verified don't you can't
you write long tweets on your own
without long I but I feel like the twit
longer is more dramatic oh yeah yeah it
is and then like the white background
which is yeah like reading like my story
and then a link to a twit longer is like
so much better than like you know
opening up a tweet and seeing that it's
like a novel and then you're like I
didn't sign up for this honestly
whenever I see those I just don't click
I'm just too tired
same I can't read time a good in between
is um posting a picture of your
notes oh okay but what if you have
really bad
handwriting no no no no on your iPhone
or whatever oh okay like your notes
app that's how you the evidence where's
the
screenshots where's the
Discord he just got to believe it I
guess so or or in the
replies proof in
replies yeah end
pudding just well and done well well
well well well well well well well this
well is not complete can I climb these
stairs oh my God I
couldn't the game is just I through it
me too
actually what hey did you climbed up on
the roof no oh for the well one oh no no
I I face through the the the steps over
here I face through the ladder but I can
climb up these stairs near the house
oh like I said I'm just a
ghosty Ghost with the most easy mode
everything is easy mode for sh
no yeah use your um the R
button it's true Shri is a force to be
reckoned with yeah she's scary she
scares me
man we have two children together and
I'm still terrified of her I don't even
remember how the heck that happened I
just woke up with it she told me you got
children like are you sure oh sh Nissa I
thought Urban so I was going to be
worried she's probably going to have
children with her
soon yeah yeah espe done right actual
fan and it was cute but I mean we
actually did have a child together K
remember you killed you them no no no
that's a different dimension that we're
talking about yeah yeah one that's a
whole different universe and two even
then it wasn't real it was
just child are you going to be mad mad
at me and like Ian REO season 2 as well
about that so or you going to forget
about it we already we're it's already
water under the bridge right I think so
too well it depends would the Nissa of
that that realm
remember
yeah you don't remember anything that
happened oh I have a bad memory
so well got to rewatch before before we
get back into that that Universe yeah
like an AI generated
summary yeah there's still a lot of time
we'll we'll be forgetting even more cuz
it's going to be in spring
right that's too far for me I want have
I remember I left with a
child who left you with a child it was
it was that one girl and then you
stepped
up one girl I will have for the college
yeah yeah yeah now I remember it's okay
cuz I I I gave you money remember that's
true I can't wait for the college
tuition
Arc oh
fre wait you had a shiori of inreco had
a child yeah yeah technically if you can
call it
that I don't remember what name I gave
it though to be honest
child I either but child that's our baby
now because I I wasn't the Father I
remember
yeah hell yeah I want the K to be in
Reverse so it's like someone who who
didn't know how to spell spelled
it why are you not mentioning who the
the other girl was maybe maybe she won't
remember we'll have to
see H it wasn't me
right I I I don't know if we'll have to
see Kiara I don't think it remember a
fun night in town with
me I don't think I was involved with
that many people
anyway my wives are going
crazy
spicy I want to live in this house was
uh in Reco
why yeah she we combined the seed and
the
Egg yeah she left you I I didn't want to
put pressure on her you know even though
I am totally
betrayed it's okay because now you have
a rich a rich Gambler wife
husband gamble way to college tuition no
I only get rich don't
worry it's my it's my it's my lore story
now oh do you have a
strategy yeah is it have blackj
no I I make I make money through honest
means in andreco through
etco Elizabeth was poor because she was
did you say gambling how I don't gamble
I gamble for fun I make my money through
honest means and then I gamble for
fun mhm I don't know if I can trust The
Gambler though
what are the honest means then it's
potato salad one Quest yeah come here ah
yeah salad I'd love some potato salad I
know right you prefer potato salad like
uh in the version that is like mayoni or
do you prefer the one that is like
oily vinegar
Mayon I don't know what oily salad is
let me through shiori huh I don't even
know where you are behind you you're
over there you can come you're def on my
screen what the heck I'm literally right
behind you cleaning the door oh I'm not
near the door I'm on a tower what the
heck remember I'm a
ghost get wet get wet what's
happening what if you see me just assume
I'm I'm not actually there I've moved on
it wouldn't let me move past you it was
crazy I'm sorry about that I can't help
my ghosty
butt
phenomenon
phenomenon ohing the tower is difficult
yeah but you're doing great I'm I'm
pretty sure you can buy a ladder can't
you there's already ladders on around
the map you just need to find them and
then place them up oh yeah actually have
to move them I see yeah
is there ladders that go that
high uh
yes there's if you come to the back of
the building there's a really really big
like it's not a ladder but it's like um
it's a
lad wait I I can't inter yeah it's like
scaffolding and you can move it I only
know this word thanks to
Minecraft
same I'm already up here so I'm going to
just try to brood force it while I'm
here yeah I can't break my legs anyway
scaffolding yeah there's ladders too
actually there's
ladders what's your Minecraft experience
herb my Minecraft experience
uh uh I enjoy it after a while I get
motion sick but I enjoy it are you
motion sick right now okay they should
playing third
person yeah I did that at smidge when we
when did in Reco but it was just I mean
you were with me actually Kato when we
when I when we were uh going through one
of the dungeons we had to jump around a
lot they got to a point where I was just
like after this man you're debuffed you
have to live with this debuff but but
now we know justi more skill
[Music]
I mean I didn't get thank you for
telling
us oh yeah totally you you don't you
were just you were just messing with us
obvious I'm still very powerful so it
doesn't really not really much of a you
know I'll just truck on through it I'll
walk it yeah yeah walk it off yeah so
what you're saying is uh you want to go
to a fair together and go on one of the
really really spinny rides and spin
really really fast yeah I can do it yeah
you can do it no you could just do them
back to back to back to back leave her
alone no don't live her suffer through
it no she's hand it yeah are you calling
herb a
liar yeah we'll go we're going on the
teacups or the spinning Dragon you can
just do the Minion ride with me I
promise it's it's
lighter the Minion ride is
great A I do like minions I think
they're
cute nice I
[Music]
like in the in the realm of the Shad the
green green uh which is very similar to
Islands there was there's a a game
called dizzy dragons where you just
spin yeah I I know
that I love the Dizzy dragons I don't
know if I want my dragon to be
dizzy disy dragons are everywhere the
game in my youth
yeah
yep and you didn't
die he's still alive as you can
see I'm a ghost now just like Shi we're
all
GH please don't haunt me I'm scared of
the
dark what a Twist huh what a t oh am I
the Scrooge am I Scrooge make duck and
this is the you know the what is that
movie called
uh the mean know what you're talking
about yeah
yeah I love the way you associate uh the
Christmas carol first with screw there's
a lot of
versions oh is the most popular one
technically yeah it's very for like
kids there's no Barbie Barbie with the
Scrooge is that no no unfortunately has
so many movies I'm surprised I know they
didn't want to make her a
[\h__\h] that's really true actually
yeah has to be nice yeah I liked her in
the
Nutcracker yeah I don't remember the
Nutcracker
One I Love The Nutcracker
valet and I used to play with Barbies
and I just made them all G for each
other I
see it was usually the Disney Barbie
dolls too like I ship them with the most
random ships like I I paired someone
with Ursula I don't know who though oh
wow yeah it's like enemies to lovers
let's
go that's a
Vibe how we going to get up to the top
of that uh Tower you got
legs wings would help
more I can't activate this game can't
you see me on the top of the tower that
you're talking about well yeah now I see
you going up there I've been up here I
tried jumping
but that's a skill issue yeah okay now
I'm on there there you go you got skills
you good yeah I'm fine don't
worry I'm being
professional okay yeah don't worry about
it okay she's so professional yeah I'm
leader Justice I professional yeah very
professional you officially the the
leader yeah she's been the leader
realized now she's the henchman
now yeah sure's the leader of ADV yeah
I'm I'm just the
babysitter hey I don't need to be babies
that that's true well technically you
have two babysitters
Nissa what
oh you're shury and then you have me
that's true why do I have so many
babysitters well you want to be looked
after though you want to be like a a
baby yeah you're a baby right yeah
Google gaga Google gaga take care of me
Google gaga w w w w wow
oh
no enion reminds me of an ASMR I watched
earli oh is it the the yeah I tuned in I
didn't know what it was about I was just
like ah nice Whispers And then she
translated it for me and I was like oh
no that moment when the ASMR artist like
knows how to speak English too and
notices you in chat and translates and
I'm like
no she's like please you want milk my
milk I'm
like did you say yes what was your
answer we need to
know uh no comment
[Music]
oh I I always treat myself to like a
pint of milk when I'm not recording or
singing and stuff I love
milk
wow I hate milk on its own oh on its own
I like
it that's cuz you're built different I
guess so I just like ice cream and
cheese yum when I was out with Justice
in the far e i I like when we'd be at a
cafe I'd buy
milk
damn just milk yeah just milk
wow it's cuz I saw it I was like oh my
God I can get this mil
and I always just got water when we went
to the to the east
mhm I remember like you guys want the
fullon drinks the drink bar I'm like
I'll just get
water I liked getting the drink bar in
Japan because they always had matcha
latte oh yeah it's good it's good and I
was like what do you mean I can just
have matcha latte whenever I want I
missed the drink bars I wish they were
more common here along with like the
iPads the iPads for I love not having to
talk to people yeah that's why I love
going to family restaurants and I could
be I could be weirder because they can't
understand me they be like a a silly gu
no I love I love that I just love I love
not talking to
people not
[Music]
either oh my God that was so funny I saw
the clip of you and uh Rica
and you forgot she speaks English oh my
God you're commenting on her her
her view
yeah like I don't know English nor
Japanese let's
go oh my God how do you pick up these
scaffolding things if you get close to
it you should be able to it should pop
up f uh you can't move it on the
roof I just want to like go around the
building but it doesn't show up with f
yeah I don't know it wasn't showing up
for me either and I'm concerned about it
because we kind of need
that we can fly we're at
96% we're actually getting through
pretty fast 96 mine only says 90 what do
you mean oh
sorry I'm I'm definitely adding another
6%
weird it says
92 do you want to host the next
map maybe maybe it'll be better yeah
maybe maybe it won't be better no I'm
sure it will be anything for
Nissa it's it's going to be your birth
week after all it has to be better
you're true it is my birth week yeah the
day you skip wom yay
we I can't wait to have everyone at my
[Music]
birthday everyone except shiori happy
birthday thank you hey we're technically
celebrating early Zen I'm making
youting the 21st 21st oh oh yeah yeah
yeah why why do you not sound so excited
oh cuz I'm gone on that day
oh on your oh why is my screen like
having an earthquake
now oh stopped I guess it
do oh it's because you're shooting me oh
I
see I was like why is there an
earthquake here N I don't know what
you're talking
about you just cuz you you know you've
been cleaning so much you got a bit on
your on my on my wear my wear exactly
my mask you a head piece I don't
know I remember when I was uh at the
starting screen I just aim for your
crotch right there it's like I'm going
to stay here and aim at it until she
comes back how dare you I was cleaning
it I'm making sure you're all well
cleaned thank you I appreciate it you
know I know isn't she so
considerate that is very bre this I
don't want to stop stream being like uh
oh stinky and stuff yeah I'm watching
you washing Away The Sins oh nice thank
you sister you guys should play cookie
on me to see how considerate you really
are apparently there one yeah I should
another one there's a fourth one I saw
it in the game perm updates it said
cookie yomi 4 I was like hey I didn't
even play the
first go go you have so much to catch up
they're long games yeah they're pretty
short but they're fun they're really
good oneoff games and there's an online
one oh an online like a co-op no wait I
don't I think it's online it's a like
multiplayer but you have to be off
collabing I think oh that's true maybe
you have to be like considerate to each
other in real life no it's like a battle
of to see who is most considerate I see
you're not considerate to each other no
no no that would be crazy yeah screw you
guys I love you
like I'm getting mixed
messages want to get up on the
hat you jump on the one of the boards
the little boards yeah on this
rock I'm
up try the
billboard oh that works maybe bro what's
going on
we're cleaning cooked we're so
cooked what does that mean
95%
like
oh but like you know without the
cursing
oh almost
done so at this point if you can't find
what to clean well you can uh click Tab
and then it'll show you what's not done
yet you can go clean
it that one side of the tower that's
just really hard to reach if we can't
move the SC thing yeah it is that's a
skill
issue but things also just are like not
pinging like it said the well was dirty
so I came and cleaned it but it still
says this
dirty oh
I blame Shi this is all her
fault yeah it was
me the whole
time I would have gone away with it too
if it wasn't for
my the cookie kids the
cookie I'm at 99%
I'm at 96 me too she getting there why
are you ahead of
us she's just that good it's cuz I'm
locked
in it's cuz hers since she's running the
game I think there's no lag on her side
technically so that's why like know I
saw you
zipping well you you can host the next
one so you can get like
uh can you try going to the scaffolding
and see if you can move it does it say f
you you mean this tiny ladder or the big
one no the the big the big scaffolding
oh I I passed right through it let me
try am I supposed to press F yeah it
should it should pop up a thing that
says like press F to move or whatever no
I see nothing for this
one Dam that's
rough um you can get an extender if you
hit e you can change the things for your
power
washer and at the very least you can get
an extender you can reach
higher I'm just not oh I know where to
hit I climbed there before I can do it
again oh the Apothecary
Hut yay seems pretty
clean what else is there find out how to
get
there
stairs I'm so sad if some body in here
oh my
God what about our bodies are we not
good no no they have to be
dead I can be dead and then revive if
you want if somebody kills me dang are
you
okay no there's no dying in this
game no I mean you know IRL like Phoenix
you know um
yeah yeah yeah I could get tired of
dying though you
know uh well i' I'd prefer to stay alive
because when I revive I I just I forget
who I am for a little while it comes
back to me but it's not really
convenient yeah yeah you know just
Phenix
things it's just how it is sometimes no
issue I can't reach
impos booo oh somebody missed this
spot you guys want to know something
random what what I had an audible
subscription for like over a year
probably two years or so I probably and
I opened the app for the first time in
the long time today and I saw I have
like a lot of credits so I bought all of
the Game of Thrones book readings oh
hell yeah and all of the Lord of the
Rings including the still merilan and
stuff like that oh
yeah you reading that on kind no not
Kindle it's audible oh audible right
yeah yeah
hash uh now I have like
probably o over 300 hours of stuff to
listen to
that's
good yeah but I don't even like like
listening to somebody reading to me that
much but I got I'm going to force myself
cuz I don't like uh reading either so
it's got to be one of them reading or
being read too say you go pick
one yeah I'm going to be picking being
read too I guess I mean some of the some
uh what is it some uh audio books have
like celebrities reading them and stuff
so yeah like step fry you know he's a
celebrity I didn't know that St fry he's
a National Treasure I don't pay
attention to like Media stuff though
isn't he the dude from like Sherlock
Holmes based on what he
reads well well whenever I see audible
it's like this is Red by stepen fry oh
he's famous in the UK oh sorry pretty
sure he's like red
like a bunch of stuff on
ably okay Shori it's up to
you your game is loaded the most you
need to hit escape and clean everything
that's at not at
100% I'm try you escape I'm just it's
the house dmer
roof it's still not getting
there how's your game though are you at
99% what if do that 1% to haunt us
forever um you have to finish
it is this like your OCD stuff no you
have to finish
it I'm not
being is on a a uh like a funny talk
show and U one of my favorite jokes of
his is like he goes uh what is it I'm
little teapot short and stout here is my
handle he puts his arm out and he puts
his other arm out he went oh no I'm a
sugar ball
that's my favorite he a sugar bowl yeah
oh it's hilarious you know it's better
want you know you physically look at
someone doing ever yeah of course of
course of course it's
hilarious well there's another one to do
with happiness but like I don't know
about saying
no why is it embarrassing no I mean it's
it's mostly an accent
joke do it oh just just about a lady
who's like I wish for
happiness
oh I see happiness the dirt nice you
know your
happiness M I can't
get I see I get it now got to say it
slowly oh oh you didn't say it sh don't
do it in your bra say it out loud no we
don't sayoud I've said it once good I've
said it once oh man you know jokes on is
funny if you say
them but then who nobody hears
them it's
fine I need to hear I need to
witness oh another one of my favorite
jokes not by stepen FR though it's uh
what is it um a German Shepherd jumped
over my fence and pooped in my garden
and he had a dog
what do you need a
dog because what that was that the last
sentence a German Shepherd jumped over
my fence and pooped in my garden and
you're a
dog and ah ah ah okay okay okay okay
took me a moment no I mean that was very
good you picked that very quickly
especially I'm always like really like
uh um wowed by people who's not that
their first language is in English and
they understand a joke so fast
especially one like that one where it's
to do with like the wording and things
you're so
nice just saying the
truth I'm going to jump I'm going to
jump sure he put us out of our misery
what's how do you check like the last
one I need you need hit the escape
button and then you will have a clean
the Halloween house you can go through
the list and then scroll through all of
them and it'll say ones are not at 100
yet Apothecary lanterns then and the
Pumpkin shed chimney and red Tower
walls you like one these lanterns
Apothecary
Lantern if if you click it it'll make it
light up so you can see you want
cheating then it's notop cheating what
I'll do the this one then let me up does
it show for you guys or this one no
it'll it'll only show on your side but
I see are you at 99% as well
yeah these
lanterns
parkour there you go
parkour parkour
parkour M land
turn Okay so that's done oh you've got
it there's an around the other side herb
house base
well I'mma die thank for oh no fall
damage no fall damage I'm die thank
[Music]
you I'm a die thank you oh I can get
this one yay nice Halloween sign where
be
that maybe in the somewhere in the
beginning in the FR it's the graves
actually yeah those are Halloween signs
apparently
what map do you want to do next by the
way a good question there's a Christmas
one for free well I don't know what you
downloaded but we can let whatever the
cruise ship and the Halloween
ones ship oh no please let's show me the
last one what a piece of
ship herb
language no oh myties are my treasures I
would never how could
you yeah herb what the [\h__\h] oh my
gosh WR a tweet longer last
[Music]
longer stor
jeez jeez it's okay l so if you wanted
to swear you could get away
with st how
stormy I think it's more fun coming up
with other words yeah yep I'm not so
creative ah I see one spot but it's at
the tower like kind of
[Music]
unreasonable you got to use the extender
you can maybe that could help EXT oh
yeah you can extend yeah if you if you
hit e the extension you can put on a
super long
one
long okay
[Music]
the roof something at the
roof there's this game I want a perms
for it's like uh you clean the house but
it's haunted and that's pretty much
it I see it seems kind of relaxing I
want to play it see some
ghosties does it have to 100% in order
to like get out of the map it's it's
re's preference no it's not my
preference you do not win the game it is
not optional you have to complete it
100% you can win the game sounds like
the game has an end oh it does just like
uh you did it you cleaned everything
yeah oh you know why I'm on the
roof no cuz the drinks are on the
house oh
oh I'm sending you to jail I'm sending
you to jail hey is this bad humor she is
she's becoming a dad no I'm an uncle
congratulations Mor's dad
Uncle come on shiori it's all up to you
I'm I'm working on
it working I
believe where is
theing you hit the escape button then
you can look through herb but ours
aren't updating for some reason very
well uh Apothecary
Lantern but I think she already you guys
to do things at least you already get
lanterns yeah may maybe for me it's see
the dirty
still I can't see the dirt yeah this is
still
dirty what's wrong with
it it's getting
better getting there
has to be this like this one
shingle mhm spamming my
tab maybe we just need to wait for it to
catch up I am losing it it's never going
to catch
up I got to wait Year we're so
clook oh let me just skip this one for
now is it oh wait but you have to do
like 100% for each thing right yeah
everything has to be it's not going to
round up that's so weird cuz sometimes
it rounds up the
dirt yeah it it it it does if you get to
like a certain point even if there's
still like a little bit left it'll 100%
clear it come on it's 99% where are you
dirt so strict I
know no it's just it's being bad right
now because everything's glitching out
but usually it's not like
this okay now the window
what window though I need the house
Dormer window along with the eaves
whatever that
is
MHM I think I found the
eaves oh it's showing
me it looks clean to me now what's wrong
with it the t button U maybe it's the
I'm I'm spamming
tab everything looks CLE
there's some tiny dirt on the
Windows Eve where are
you Eve what is an
eve uh the area between the roof and the
house
wall so basically any Gap I assume it's
not a gap it's like a wood framing yeah
like underneath yeah yeah yeah
but where's the dirty Eve that's the
question it should light it up for you
I'm I'm spamming I'm trying to find it
as a thing oh if you click on it it'll
just make it light up for you so you'll
be able to see what specific Eve it is
oh no I i' I've clicked on it I just
don't know where it is essentially where
the I see it it's here but I cleaned it
I see
now Eve all right Eve's done now I need
a ROM window yippe
yippe yippee window which oh this
one
okay a house small
trim how small trim where are
[Laughter]
you this is really cursed it's so
Halloweeny in every sense of the of the
way yes
you find a
trim I got the Apothecary uh house
entrance
E I can't find a window wait what am I
looking for window to the
wall chat do you see the small trim
wherever that
is spamming 10 our suffering
[Music]
go go go the front door you
think that looks like a big trim oh hey
there's ladder icons for some reason
now
God oh wait can I climb the
ladder uh around the door by the stairs
oh my
God Rea needs it to be perfect I don't
need it to be perfect that's how the
game
works but how often am I going to play
this no it's just how the game works I'm
not making up rules that's just how it
works okay okay okay there there there's
there how about we all leave and leave
shiori and then see if anything
fixes all right because I feel like this
the map is clean we've all individually
find tiny tiny tiny things yeah what I'm
saying is some of the things that we're
cleaning are things that another person
has already fully
cleaned but it just hasn't pinged on
your
map mhm all right so so go ahead and
manually leave then and maybe you can
come back safely all right okay look for
a garil leave cop game goodbye
goodbye So Long Farewell har say I'll
see you again goodbye night oh hey I can
finally climb the stairs now that you're
gone wow just no offense no offense to
pick it up
now can can we rejoin now did everyone
leave are you able to do you need
another invite no it might be broken you
just have to finish it you have to
finish the shory oh man that's a lot of
you're putting a a lot of stress on here
for a power wash
game good good luck I didn't expect this
on my my last day guys where's the
gargoyle I thought we were going to do
another map is it we we're going to do
another map but you need to finish this
map
why it's power
simulator quick chat where's gargoyle
what looks like a g to your [\h__\h] is it is
it the cats at the
entrance I don't know okay let me get
anything on the roof first before I go
to the perimeter
yeah red Tower wall all of this looks
like a giant red Tower wall to
me you can do it I
believei she that's me what do you want
me to do want me to dance for you I'm
dancing dance what else you want me to
do huh I want you dance me dance I'm
dance my anxiety is so
high yeah you've got to clean clean
everything C what if I just what if I
just say like ooh 100% let me Photoshop
it really
quick I only have a c things I just need
to freaking get the gargoyle these
things I guess you must you must clean
it all for justice yeah you got to clean
it all for justice I don't believe in
Justice what is this a good World got to
clean it all for our
Rebellion I don't know about that that's
telling you what to
do ignite our beating hearts with the
power wash Dance
Dance come on cat Okay gargoyles clean
pathway post decoration what the heck do
oh I
seea has invited you to
play I guess oh I've been
invited yay wait is this a same map what
is this no just leave I she's finally
letting guys oh I
know I knowe finally wow 100% we did it
we did it yeah now we're in Santa's
work everything's all GRE
s is it orange this place is very orange
oh that's probably the wood it was
Christmas Eve Eve a night we look
forward to for one special reason this
is French Bob by the way it's the last
night that our inventor Ivor Nidia
pitches the last year's star toy to
Santa or next year star toy what why is
everything covered in dirt we're going
to find out from the L however this was
suppos to carry them through to Santa's
office in a big box to stop anyone from
peeking maybe they filmed the spicy
movie in here oh my God nightm chist
we knew that had to be really
good the movie and no I'm I'm reading
I'm reading the lore I'm reading the
lore you see how you see what they do to
me
chat they don't care about the
lore yeah I don't know about if I care
much about the power wash lore I know
I'm just cleaning that's how you find
out how we like this oh don't you want
to know so what's the
tldr I don't know yet every time we
clear a certain percent it'll give us
more of the
story so far someone was going to show
they were going to show Santa a new a
new star design and they're bringing it
in a box and everyone is really excited
and then dot do dot now we're waiting
for the rest yeah
probably probably like a goo star
I think they're releasing a Dracula
movie for Christmas I want to watch it
what yeah Dracula for Christmas I know I
was Bamboozled I am excited maybe they
wanted to release for Halloween but it
got delayed maybe hallow was probably
too competitive have you seen the van
housing movie oh I don't know I might
have but I
forgot I watch that at some point oh
yeah you haven't haven't yeah it's a few
vampire movies and stuff you haven't
seen yeah I still need to watch Dracula
dos
[Music]
musical Das musical right I love how you
you you make the Das sound so
important yes German
article
yes this looks like Jinx was in here a
little bit
is anyone watching
Arcane yeah but I didn't watch the most
recent like new ones the first three I
watched from the second season mhm I
haven't seen any of them what about
season one I haven't seen any of them oh
not even season one no I'm waiting till
it's like done done and then I'm going
to watch it oh oh that was what I was
thinking for o
no I very recently started watching ing
Arcane and it's so good it makes me want
to play league
amazing you should play league it's fine
my chat tells me I shouldn't they're
lying to you but like as long as it's
with friends they say it's okay league
is fun even when you play with random
people they're so protective they're
like don't don't talk to strangers cuz
they're evil I got kidnapped in the
channel so yeah
yeah that's the need an eternal how evil
are they going to be in League of
Legends they're going to yeah oh no it
can't be that bad they're going to Flame
you they're going to be toxic they're
going to tell their mommies on you wow
not the mommies yeah anything about the
MERS hey what percentage is
everyone 11% eight oh God it's F wait
what per are you 12
it's fine there's no problem with that
we just you you just have to reach 100%
reset it's okay yeah you love 100% yeah
you got to yourself to
everyone it's not about proving it's how
the game works Shori
Noella yeah but how often am I going to
play this game no it it doesn't have
anything to do with
that I love how she Y is making rage
love it more don't please leave me alone
I don't deserve this I'm just telling
you it's just 100% you know I don't care
about reaching 100% but map you seem to
really care about finishing it seem to
care a lot you finish the
map it seems really important to you
indeed I know we're just chilling and Y
how the game works I in
fact we're just cleaning Arisa we're
just here never playing power wash with
you guys again except for Liz she
understands me when we play TR Liz I
will invite you for
power Anda could just watch in the
corner say
try I know my God she maxing in this
game
maxing
power I mean she's a pro at this so
yeah that's cuz it's a good game she's
going to go into the power wash orts I
know I believe you you guys you guys are
never going to get to Atlantis and that
just makes me sad Atlantis is where the
is that where the Championships are
being held no it's one of the maps
a I thought you wanted to down in the
water don't worry never getting to
Atlantis is kind of a thing in my I
know so I need to continue the
tradition I
see and now we went from Halloween to
Christmas you guys feel it's just like
Works speed running 2024 be like
H
yeah the entrance Academy still has
dirt
lies don't believe
it believe
it let's go
Naruto yeah let's go Shi
oh we're going to save Sasuke I think
sang that song in wish that they became
a
thing what song say the believer Naruto
s that's not
ger he's really cool Sakura the
beautyful right it wasn't German but I
did sing it in Koka before yeah it's
it's
funny what else did they say Sakura was
cool yeah no they say Sasuke he's really
sakur the beautiful
[Music]
beautiful do we have ladders this time
that we can use there should be some
somewhere I'm not sure you can also use
an extender no it's more like I need to
like get a difference like from above po
extender there there should be one
somewhere he's really
coola the Beautiful the beautiful my God
there's a window you can see outside
it's so pretty let's break it
open are we
stuck entrance what else do I got to
clean here why do you think we're
stuck cuz she wants to break it open to
see the outside everyone is hard out
work said French a mess oh there's like
an elf thing here like a shadow that's
cute I leave that for now
bangs was testing the durability of
their rocket ships on the ceiling whilst
mullet was fine tuning the high notes of
the
xylophones I I still don't see how that
leads to this sort of mess across the
way high top fade had made some planes
with Precision Engineering whilst padora
had made some dolls that probably needed
more work really ah he's kind of mean to
his fellow elves French bomb you
[\h__\h]
scandalous I'm cleaning my
hardest BB are you raising your chat up
secretly I I would never mute and talk
to chat I I see your chat reacting very
fondly what did you say to them that you
cannot share with the class said to them
they were uh oh stinky and they need to
go back in the
mines you told them they're
stinky well I mean I was saying there
there was they were like stinky
socks wow they seem to think they're
presents
oh something sweet is going on she's
flirting with them cute
unbelievable even though we're right
here your food literally
how dare you yeah how can you get
distracted when these ladies are around
you yeah you know uh you know Takashi K
you should be part of Justice you're
really good at
monitoring you know I should the high up
like hi
you all right okay I can have a side job
yeah I'll take it I'll help you guys out
you know want to help me monit
Advent you know geographically I think
there there will be some good Synergy
too I'm close to Exodia was
it
ex that's the Yu-Gi-Oh
card enough I know get mistaken all the
time wait why is why is it laugh why are
they laughing cuz you said Exodia Exodia
which is a Yu-Gi-Oh card [\h__\h] it just
seems like you're super strong you know
no wait what is it
called it's
Exodia exia how do you spell it right
Exodia can you spell it e ex a r d i a e
ex a r ah damn it close enough it's okay
it's close it's close close yeah yeah
I'm sure the Yu-Gi-Oh people would be
very flattered you thought that it was
exia be like oh my God yeah there seem
to be a lot of Yu-Gi-Oh people in all of
your chats that's how great exia was
made by the gods one gave their arm
another gave it their other arm and
another gave their torso and leg so on
and so forth and that's that's how great
exia was made wow that was
great that's why I say bye the
gods have you girl played Yu-Gi-Oh
before I used to be an aid collector of
the cards when I was younger I collected
it for the pretty boys I had a frog deck
frog I only played Magic the Gathering
that's okay I see I never got into that
one though I have friends who are very
into it the cards look really nice mhm
they're very
pretty yes I
want the Gathering collaboration girl do
you don't know how many times I tried to
get perms for the online magic the
Gathering they they ignore me how could
they do that you're so cute I don't know
they don't give perms to anybody I guess
a gatekeeping magic the Gathering
why let me play please let me play your
game I'm trying to do things the right
way mhm give
us
please just want to play game h
rip guess we'll got to make our own card
game we have one yeah exactly that's
what I'm
saying yeah play the hollow life card
game
yeah I'm getting Ping P P oh yeah wow
there there are some ladders over by the
entrance if you're still looking for
them no now I'm trying to like get
really low get low
lowow [\h__\h] sweat pants and the Rex with
the straps with the
[Music]
straps I sang that truck simulator
before oh yeah that was fun oh
what for EUR truck just a multiplayer
but I think a technically I don't know
if you'd have terms for it
honestly H uh I'm pretty sure the ID go
have played the multiplayer
version I'm multiplayer no you just
drive
together not in the same vehicle right
yeah I don't think the same vehle you
just you exist as truck drivers
oh that's it
fun well if you don't Ram into each
other then you don't even need the
multiplayer mode you can just play the
single player mode at the same time yeah
you can Ram into each other you just
can't share the same vehicle I
think oh so you are on the same map then
you're saying yeah but you like I don't
think you can do much besides
[Music]
drive while can race each other
yeah racing with tracks I as well just
play Mario
Kart no different physics no parking but
Mario Kart has blue shells and you can
hit each other with it [\h__\h] the blue
shells you sound
traumatized
Mario I always get [\h__\h] over in Mario
Kart that's why you try not to be first
you have to be second and maybe you can
get there I gave up on trying to get
good you know my favorite racing game
is Wacky Races on the PlayStation
one ooh sounds wacky yeah sounds very
wack heard of it you never Watch the
cartoon Wacky Races may like a exia
thing
no I think it is it's not it has the
Gastly and mly in it and stuff cool it
has Penelope
pitu oh I love
Penelope you remember it so well
yeah she's got a good memory or
herb have you muted yourself again herb
yeah she's talking [\h__\h]
no stop talking [\h__\h] herb I just keep M
and going poop poop poop
[Music]
po oh is that like a mating
call
yeah stop doxing
[Laughter]
me yeah it's a CL it's a classic cartoon
but they made a a game as well of it and
it was very much like Mario Kart
but with the wacky characters
nice I read a comment the other day when
in some collab stream I mentioned uh I
think it was an Eden Eternal I mentioned
Toontown and everybody agreed that we
like we didn't really understand we only
played it a little bit uh but it's
somewhere in the memories and I I read a
comment that made me realize that and
remember that the problem with Toontown
was that especially if you're young I
guess um the the beginning area that's
free to play is free to play and if you
want to get anywhere else in that game
you have to pay that's why I like only
was in that beginning area and I didn't
understand like where is the party going
on like where is everybody yeah turns
out it's not free to play what the heck
it's a freaking ch's game I heard
about yeah it kind of makes sense in a
way I guess even RuneScape like there's
a free portion of the game that you can
explore and like 20 or some free quests
but then like a lot of the game is like
you have to actually become a member
a Nissa all our money yes what do you
click to like stand still and just move
around your see thank you yeah no
problem anything for you my angel of
music I tried to avoid anything spending
money back then like my first game was
probably Terraria and only because I
woned in a
giveaway
nice
what what about like Pokemon and stuff
like that oh no first steam stuff like I
would have my parents pay for it but I
try not to bother my
parents but I'll get this for Christmas
Christmas Christmas is coming are
getting fat please put the penny in the
old man's hat what that's cute if you
haven't got a penny I it would do if you
haven't got a God bless
you you're just making things up now
yep if that is making up on the spot
then you should be a freestyle rapper
Hest okay a to the B to the C to the D
I love
kfp wow we've got a
winner a rap
god look how Callie Call's been real
quiet since you dropped
[Music]
those Miss KY more you're going to need
to come here and defend yourself hurry
up I love how every time any H member is
like trying to rap like a you know like
a newbie everybody in the chat is always
like Callie's been real quiet since you
oh [\h__\h] as if cie had any kind of
competition well regardless she's like
so unique as well with her rap so I I
don't think anybody could even like be
like her in general so unique so special
very true
go Callie go Callie go
Callie I'm going to be right back and
get some
water well there's water are you sure
are you sure that's what you're going to
do yeah no I am are you not muting and
talking to your chat secretly
no let her mute and talk to her chat
that is her right as a streamer T she
gave me the job now to observe so now
I'm observing desing that's true I see
you monitor you okay he's going to
regret it now I'm on a mission now we're
at 50% completed
wow me and my
40% this is fine this game makes me
sweety it's relaxing right I know it's
also going to give me
arthritis don't get arthritis
you can't tell my rist to do that it has
a mind of its own make them
stop okay you do the rest of the work
then just get good you'll be fine dang
you can do the rest of the work get your
100% you earned
it that's not how it works we have to do
it together because this is
multiplayer dang
I love how all of us are avoiding the
ceiling we're like [\h__\h]
that get oh yeah get there yeah I have
my own ceiling
here your own little area mhm this is my
corner it was made for
me it's like it is your hole that was
made for you this is my hole get out of
my
hole Yeah hole where are
live and I bought more tech gadgets I
love having more Tech like what yeah
what' you get um like another gimbal but
it's like tinier and more compact than
the one I have oh gambles let's go
yeah what are you going to do with it
well hopefully I would like to Vlog but
it depends on the area and the people
who don't get the [\h__\h] out of my way
like get out of here I'm trying to Vlog
and then there's going to be relatives
around so I have to be like get out of
here get out of my Vlog get out of my
Vlog Mommy it's my turn on the
Xbox only the best Vlogs
for we'll see about
that it's so L people around you also uh
did you also get like a extra like
microphone for your vlogging oh no I do
mind silent because I don't want to talk
then you do voice over yeah yeah I also
would be like very embarrassed like last
time when I was in Japan I did a little
Vlog for uh I think I announced my 2.0
for my life to be oh yeah
it um but yeah I I did like a vlog in
Shinjuku uh gave myself some missions to
achieve and and all that and I was like
well I don't want to do a voice over I
want to like you know talk to the camera
basically but I'm like really shy and
also awkward about it too so I just
brought my manager with me so that it
seems like I'm talking to my manager
while I'm filming things and that works
that helped a
lot yeah so I told her to always like
walk right next to me so I don't look
like a freaking
weirdo myself yeah I can't do that I
don't want my relatives like knowing the
channel or anything I keep as hushed as
I can about
it so like I'm just I'm just recording
don't mind me just a video
editor yeah that's all they
know what if something's like way too
close but I have no other way to reach
it either like when you're so close that
you can't like clean it you know what I
mean it's it's hard it sometimes it's
rough like that man nut cracker I love
nut
cracker I I hate their facial hair
though why it's so soft and fuzzy
no I'm A Yank
It okay Queen you live your truth no
facial hair in my world but no if you
got facial hair you're okay it's okay
okay no no she said what she said
novalie she won't accept you she's going
to yank out your hairs one by one facial
hair yeah but I'm not going to hate you
for
it no it's okay keep your facial hair
some you guys probably like
it yeah don't make them feel bad for
facial hair I Canever want some people
just look better with facial hair let's
be real oh yeah yeah I think so
too but but not fictional characters for
me sorry you guys have to yank it
off fical meet you with facial hair no
way get out of here maybe not although
he would look less like a little baby if
he had facial hair I like him being baby
I like nice
Demitri you like nice baby boy Dimitri
yeah that's not what he grows up into I
hate to I didn't like that Arc I was
going to punch the crap out of it
you
don't character AI feel bad for what he
turns into there are definitely
good-looking characters that have facial
hair
definitely name a few name a few I don't
know does Sid have facial hair and Final
Fantasy I think he has like a little bit
Sid right the blonde
dude there's so many different SIDS what
[\h__\h] right I forgot I Hearts vers to be
honest s has some yeah okay depends on
which Sid but Sid has
some I guess I guess Leon from Final
Fantasy could be okay with facial hair
wait sh you like curs things now let me
give you a good example you can't tell
me that Santa Claus doesn't look good
with his facial hair but to be fair
Santa Claus is a mared looks like a
grand F excuse
me well he's rocking it I I don't want
to say he's like
wait are you into the old how dare you
dismiss T
Nissa you for the backup I'm saying he's
my grandfather I'm not going to look at
him in that way he's your grandfather
your grand well that's going to be
awkward
now
what Santa Claus with a Mr Santa Claus I
mean pretty much everything you see that
is like a weird creature is probably
like a demon let's be honest imagine
going around the whole entire world in
one night and delivering presents you
you think anyone could do that some
magic Sant Claus like me you're
different Santa Claus could be human
he's my idol he's your idol sorry make
him dance I want to hear a song
covers wow Santa Claus covers Idol
[Laughter]
gonna crack some bones poor old
guy oh he's very
Nimble I read like some uh I think this
book called cringle which is before
Santa became Santa and when I read that
I just imagined him as an anime
character is Santa Claus real yeah okay
good that we have established that it
was
important why why wouldn't he be
I've never seen
him well he doesn't want to you must be
on the naughty list yeah he doesn't want
to get
dock yeah yeah he's an idol
yeah not very believable but okay what
if Santa is just like anyone with a good
heart yeah I like that theory
yeah I think he's the guy that
goes oh what uh Tim Allen yeah oh yeah
yeah I was thinking Shaggy from Scooby
go or
Scooby I do that a lot I
had
man I had a phase uh I think last year
where I watched from beginning to end
all of the seasons of that show what
Home Improvement yeah it's so good now
that I watch it as an
adult I think I just watched the
episodes like randomly in random order
when I was a child but like now as an
adult it's it gives you a whole new POV
and you really end up liking the mom cuz
I think as a child I didn't care about
the mom character but now she's really I
like her she's cool what exactly is the
show about is it just like this dude who
owns like his instruction stuff and he
does family that's a TV show doesn't he
yeah he has a TV show and he likes you
know doing stuff in the house and car
and he messes up his own house the whole
time too but they have kids they have
free boys and in the beginning of the
show you can really see the actors are
really young and so they grow up like a
lot over the course of the show they
become adults and yeah they go through L
and and puberty and the mom is like
always frustrated with her husband but
it's funny it's like really
funny you
know I heard that that was a show that's
his life around cuz he he had like a
criminal record before I don't know what
from but then he got his [\h__\h] together
and then he started like acting and then
he became like a good role model he had
a criminal record criminal it's probably
just like a DUI I don't
know you have to Google it nah no way
not
him what he was turn his life around
yeah what oh my God he's like w and
breaking bed there you go but he's
learned he got his life together he
became an actor
wow what the heck they bidden lore MH
the
archives can't stop
grunting let's do a
grunt
[Music]
go I like Shaggy and Scooby
who doesn't they're cute yeah I like
them in the live action movie too yeah
oh my God the live action is way too
good like way better than it has any
right
being that's one of the really good like
uh was it cartoon to IRL
um
uh adaptations it really is because
literally the Shaggy actor in that went
on to play Shaggy for like a really long
time as like his voice like in the
animation after that
point they were on point with the cting
yeah they
were and I think another really good
costume yeah
M always it's crazy yeah I think it's
interesting because Daphne's actress and
Fred's act actor are married in real
life yeah
it's Buffy yeah
Buffy it's interesting cuz that they
just kind of [\h__\h] around in the cartoon
depending on the version of it yeah
spicy haven't watched it can't judge
you've never seen
Scooby-Doo not
really there's like a different seasons
of it some are better than others yeah
the show definitely went through a lot
of like change changes yeah like
different writers
voices around for a long
time
classic
classic I should buy like a a big giant
Nutcracker I was tempted before yeah no
reason I just like them do a nut
cracking stream
you're actually not supposed to cck nuts
what why not yeah I don't know it's
because they're not really like meant
for it they're weak well how how can you
get
in a nut cracker why are they called
nutcrackers that they're not supposed to
crack nuts maybe people crack their nuts
Oh Oh I thought you meant you're not
supposed to crack nuts in
general well with them like you know
their mouth I don't think you're
actually supposed to put a nuts in there
it's more just like cute
okay I sure they used to actually be
able to like take it maybe maybe I can
crack my thighs I don't need enough oh
yeah hell
yeah always always done
that just how I do it guys is this Ste
man do me do me do me
present for sister
sh of
the
present
wow oh this
CH I can't get this slay to
Ping but I'm like I'm pretty sure it's
clean so I'm like
hello
H well
having a fun time
wish game I'm thinking about it wait let
see like an actual goody game I'm sure
there's one
somewhere I need to get um some point
and click Adventures of it whenever I
feel like getting
it mhm they so endearing I love point
and click Adventures have you guys
played the wait no I think that's is
that German only Angela a condo no I've
never heard of you know it I know what
you're on about yeah you know the
absolutely cursed game uh no but I I do
remember it CU they had Angela and AA
before the Digimon
movie maybe maybe it was only popular in
like
Europe I think it was made in Australia
wasn't it oh it felt so saying it's a
terrible show yeah they had this point
and click game was so cursed everything
was cursed
cursed style of Animation so like yeah
it was very original very
unique I'm so hungry you're hungry yeah
did you not eat anything
today well I did but it's like uh almost
night now so the last time I ate is a
while ago I need to eat
enough salad and then I hopefully I need
to sleep early but I took a nap today
again I'm such a freaking idiot why do I
keep on taking naps but I was really
tired and I I did some stuff that that
tired out my arms too my noodle arms are
like so weak because I I carried stuff
from the from the post
office I car plates
take yeah it doesn't really work that
well on me but um makes sense it's kind
of like iy I'll still take it hoping
that it will work yeah and maybe you can
get those uh heated eye masks maybe that
could help you I think I still have them
but uh I don't know they're not like the
most amazing
things try it try it maybe it'll help
with the Drone I'll try it before
but combine them for extra efficiency
all right all
right do my
best I'm going to try clear my backlog
while I am away from my
trip yeah what
backlogs I want to play my time at
Sandrock you don't have perms for it
oh
what it's like a it's like a farming
game except it's not really farming it's
more like engineer I think yeah yeah
yeah the only crappy thing is I don't
like the the environment you're in a
desert and I think you're supposed to
make int grass yeah but with your
engineering skills you might be able to
give it
grass and you can marry people oh yeah
great well but why would you want to
marry anybody but Dimitri
because you can't marry theit more than
once in a game and that's it well you
want aren't you happy with that is that
not satisfactory to you no I need more
content I got to I got to go with the
flow yeah I need to get my adrenaline
and my
dopamine my
serotonine serotonin is what like the
Happy thing right yeah yeah do then
serotonin
there
[Music]
related and Santa needs to
hire not
us we are the the higher now yeah we're
getting paid for
this I don't know I feel like we should
demand a ra or maybe more Christmas
presents yeah it's Santa so we he at
least has to for sure bring us a present
I know I better be in a good list
bringing Santa a Pikachu this Christmas
you know Pokemon release the dub release
like some original Christmas songs Back
the no what I didn't know that until a
few years back when I was just randomly
on Spotify looking at Pokmon songs and
it came up with the Christmas like tunes
and I was like oh
oh my God I didn't know that it's kind
of amazing I need to watch a new Pokemon
there SEC a villain in
there oh yeah he has black and white
hair too o I hope he's competent but I
doubt it
villain yeah in in Pokemon it's you know
yeah yeah he's like only so much you can
hope for what's his name is it Larry
who's
Larry Gary
oh my God no it's a Pokemon like human
not not an actual Pokemon no no no I
know but if his name is Larry because
Gary
oh thinking that would be
great all know is a villain and then the
new Pokemon has two protagonists like
some girl and some
boy
yeah I don't know
I missed Ash already they're probably
tired of voice acting yeah it's a mytho
then Ash is at least English voice
actress is still going strong yeah who
else are they voice
him um there's that one anime that came
out I don't remember what it's called
but it's like got that Russian
girl and uh the English voice for ash
she also speaks Russian fluently so she
got that role because that's a whole
like that's one of the big things about
it is like she speaks Russian but like
and doesn't realize the main character
can speak it so she acts like she's
saying mean things to him really she's
like yeah yeah yeah I see I see yeah oh
yeah oh yeah I know what you're talking
about not going to watch it but I know
that's Ash's voice actress it's
crazy Ash a long way becoming a Pokemon
Master to BEC like a Russian girl now
I didn't realize those Gunk on the
ceiling yeah yeah you didn't realize
until now no I had a Daddy Daycare
moment of you know when the kid goes I
miss and then he he walks in and he's
like oh looks around and looks up and
he's like oh
[Music]
God I love you
anyone else go like like randomly don't
noise no I can't make that
noise but CI does a
good close enough I also do like random
sounds like uh out of nowhere it's no I
don't mean to it's just one of my
things yeah I mean you could do ASMR
then cuz that's most of the mouth no
mouth
pops it's your
destiny Shen ASMR
ASMR
yeah just talk about your day I mean
that say too just whisper about your day
yeah I have a dead it's not a real body
my
cat I it but
it's for Christmas too you know
yeah you do that
I'm your ASMR
manager yeah she's going to write all
your scripts for you and then you just
have to record them do you like writing
scripts I don't mind if if I have
time yeah that's a thing yeah time yeah
projects yeah yeah time is a precious
resource these days I
know I just want time to slack off
I might be looking for a script
writer maybe what kind of script writer
for like
're oh no no
uh uh personal uh spicy movie you
know
movie
wow uh secret secret NDA oh okay
okay well I wish you luck I wish you
luck anyone who wants to apply maybe
she'll have a a listing for
you yes yes I'll be setting it out via
DM yeah
M and I love doing random projects
though I want to do this I want to do
that but why I just feel like
it hey that's valid a reason as ever
yeah the only reason you need to do
anything if I want to
yep well you should I mean you should be
passionate about you know what you up
to makes the project even
better there's no purpose but it's
funo wow that side is pretty clean nice
nice yeah I'm doing pretty good oh gosh
it's 2 hours oh
75%
go
uh kind of uh if you have to go get
gone yeah power
wash it's just power wash we won't keep
you yeah there no I didn't mean that in
a mean way wow I didn't mean it in a
mean
way if you want my
I don't want you to leave how will I
ever live without you back to she
Raven she she ised that same line on me
how am I going to live dad you and I
said you have Liz it's
okay you find yourself in a pickle
narissa how about how about Liz and I
make a ship then come on Liz let's go go
ahead I don't
care mix messages here it says doesn't
care but I I think she cares I know she
cares about that 100% too oh my God I
do% we go we'll go out and look for a
cute Christmas dress for
you I like shopping me
too I like the we all like
shopping
like people don't you
know yeah I don't like shopping that
much anymore
um it doesn't bring you Joy and great
happiness now it's stressful and I don't
know it's like hard to
choose
and yeah I love window shopping I like
getting
more I love looking around may or may
not fit my teeths also you get your
steps and walk around M yeah that's true
but then you think that online shopping
will maybe take the stress away but no
online shopping has its own problem so
like you don't know what you're getting
you won't know
[Music]
too lazy to send it back wasting my
money the looking person yeah yeah but
then there's some shops that I really
like there's one shop in particular that
I really really like um but for me they
only have an online shop because like
their real IRL shop is in the country
far away from me but I really want to go
there and and try out all the dresses
you have to go then come with me
okay okay that was easy I wonder what we
it in I mean if the clothes are cute
it's it benefits both of us we can both
try it out right hell yeah I think you
saw me wearing one of their dresses
before ooh if it's what I think then yes
I want to try on their stuff so
bad oh I might not I'm not
sure what's your typical fashion for
stuff I remember you saw me in my weird
dresses
oh sorry well um H my typical Fashions I
used to like one that you're willing to
share yeah no it's fine I used to dress
kind of like how bio dresses now but
that's like when I was younger nowadays
it's like a very toned down version of
it MH
maybe I like to dress kind of elegant
now oh
yeah still like cute Vibes and like fres
and stuff here and there but not too
much and less
patterns
simple they still cute
cute but I've also become so lazy that I
just go in my pajamas everywhere
nowadays H yeah that's how you know you
grown
up I don't give any [\h__\h] anymore
yeah I mean especially if you're just
going out to the grocery store who
cares yeah I mean I still wear dresses
but that's cuz I don't like pants
yeah
relatable but in the winter
time a bit more difficult yeah yeah I
like winter fashion like bundling yeah
wear my
dress I I double up on the types usually
from wearing
oh yeah yeah have you consider getting
like the insulated
ones uh I mean sometimes I weather
too
yeah I like those ones a lot but I
always feel like the the ankle area
looks ugly for some
reason yeah sometimes I want the patn
like that's why I double on the like
pattern ones cute
[Music]
yeah I need to eat after this I just
have jagaro as my food jagaro yeah you
still have Jag did you bring it from
Japan no no there's a there's some Asian
stores around oh for like International
Foods or whatever I guess do you usually
go for the snacks and do shops like they
important small it's a very very small
selection so if I pass by the story like
I I'll get it
mhm
not yeah like oh they got this
wow one of the things I like to get from
Asian shops is the
Lun is it like kind of like y I'm not
familiar I know the drink
though is it carbonated yeah m is fizy
yeah but not too crazy not too
much not like a fresh Coca-Cola I was F
I wouldn't drink it but I like the look
of it just open it up and let it stand
for a while
oh carbonation like when carbonated
things have uncarbonated themselves oh
like the I don't mind it huh I know some
people are like oh my
God sometimes I feel like insane I like
when they're uncarbonated too but
sometimes I feel like the flavor is just
weird and that they rely on the
carbonation to make it taste quote
unquote good I like I love water
uncarbonated yeah wait I've never had
carbonated
sorry I I correct myself because over in
great Gardia lemonade is usually
considered like Sprite and seven up and
all that oh uh and then the the uh
American lemonade is cloudy lemonade
over here cloudy lemonade you're going
to have to do like a lessons in exia
language it's funny because it's or at
least in in my area it was it's
considered like Posh to have like cloudy
lemonade so when I visited like like
Fria and then it like the go-to was like
cloudy lemonade I be like w
fancy cloudy lemonade I love lemonade me
too it's my favor especially like water
though I feel bad for calories yeah same
got to be mindful of the figure you know
mhm
guys oh and then and then
also in great Exodia SL what you say
shades of Greenland uh uh what what is
it called when you have a uh shades of
that's my code name for it at the moment
until I reveal more of the gr exian
map what is it so usually if you have
like a bit of a an upset tummy you like
given a flat a flat
Sprite really
yeah that's so interesting
yeah yeah that's that's right over where
you are it's a ginger yeah go to fizzy
and all oh
fizzy no she she's saying that uh they
they do uh
give uh un fizzy Sprite for it as we
like here we do ginger
ale I just suffer oh ginger ale for me
I what the heck really I don't really
like most pops but I really like ginger
ale I still won't go out of my way to
drink it but like if it's presented to
me I won't say
no I don't like
ginger wow I'm alone in my I'm not sure
what it like I barely have it I think
I'm probably going to hop because I'm
getting a little bit motion sticky so K
thanks for playing with us thanks for
having Meen
you thanks for thinking of me I'm
watching you
[Music]
now abandoned by our
Queen our Scarlet Queen well I hope we
finish it soon cuz I don't want to leave
you behind but I also got
to I'll help her get a 100% we're at
99% oh you are what else do you need
then on you then I'll check at 99 I'm
apparently at 99 how is this 99 like a
lot of the ceiling is still
dark the ceiling is done on M I think
the host gets most of it yeah I'm I
think the whole ceiling just about is
done except for this middle
panel I'll go through and I'll start
checking okay still says 85 I feel like
has barely gone up take her percentage
Yeah that's her test score that we're
stealing yeah
uh I need to get up higher how do I get
up higher use your
wings why do I suck at
jumping I've never been so bad at
jumping is when I've been playing this
with you
guys oh is it our fault now yeah dang
what did we do okay uh let me
start okay what's not clean first we
have bunting what the hell is a
bunting I've heard that word before
bunting isn't it like punching
someone I I don't
know buting
hello oh that's punting oh sorry them I
see it I see it it's the thing on the
top up here and then you guys are
cleaning things too yeah yeah trying Me
Try Me Try oaba OAB boonga clean clean
clean okay cheer Checker base Che
chest okay speed running speed running
yeah we're speed we're speed running
don't
worry we're almost there very
close shy what made you want to play
this game oh I just thought it' be funny
to invite like all these ships you to
have
really that was the concept yeah I just
I didn't realize I didn't realize that
was the concept either no there was a
real concept it's just I can't be there
for your birthday so I figured like
oh that's sweet of you that's awful yeah
so I got all your favorite
[Laughter]
ships here's my
present thank you is it accurate narissa
do you think she got it right very
oh I love all the ladies in this
slam
yeah I hope you have a great birthday do
oh I'm sure I
will there's there's going to be lots of
fun and it's only two days away oh my
God I know can't wait for you to express
your your happiness and joy
espresso stream espresso streaming
services now
yay I've been seeing so much uh Saina
Carpenter on my Twitter
algorithm always like tweets that say
like oh my God I can't believe she's
doing these moves in her concerts in
front of children I saw that to too
actually and to be honest I didn't even
know who the heck Sabrina Carpenter was
but I guess she's like a Disney girl she
was a Disney girl but like that was like
10 years ago dang what did she star in
fishy I I don't even know that's the
crazy
thing everyone's freaking out and I'm
like bro it's fine let her let her be
sexy Decor decoration machine
papers oh she was in boy meat's world
the hell is that was she the girl Girl
Meets World
was she the main
character I guess it's woman Meets World
now
yeah she is a woman in the
[Music]
world she's the bestie okay I don't know
who that is said yeah all I did you ever
did you ever watch that one shy I
watched a boy me real dude but all I
remember is that there's a blonde girl
and there's this like brown curly haired
dude and they like each other I'm pretty
sure that's clearly it yeah I don't
remember anything I don't think I ever
watched it that's all I know I don't
know who these people
are I don't know who you are I don't
know what you want but you move sexy so
Twitter
mad bro why won't this get clean it
doesn't even look dirty get clean get
clean I'm I'm literally I'm trying so
hard I do not see any dirt on it in a
place that is easily
accessible and it will just not you can
do it I'm trying my hardest I believe in
you I won't yell in your ears like you
do with me earlier I wasn't yelling in
your ears I don't
know it's cuz we're like an old married
couple man dang you're just interpret my
me as
nagging what do you think think is she
Naggy is she cooking I'm not I'm always
cooking Happ Che she always cook the
wall is also not clean over
here I'm not sure where it's still dir
either not
clean
yeah
please oh hello the
exorian you have been raided congratul
time to
defend defend against what invasion of
course
exorian Very Justice members remember
just because we're
friendly on the outside doesn't mean
that we shouldn't be prepared on the
inside always be ready always be guarded
M yeah there we go but welcome to my
welcome welcome to your
stream everything yo did you know that
there's an Allison Wonderland DLC in
here no what yeah but we don't have
perms for it oh what we need perms for
each
DLC well I think we only have perms for
like tomb Raiders some Final Fantasy
stuff and like whatever
crap there's a tomb raid DLC in this
game you mean yeah yeah what yeah
not something that would make you happy
yeah you ready to clean some tombs maybe
there's finally a dead body in them you
ready to do some Tomb
Raider could have gone with that huh I
didn't know you were a big Tomb Raider
fan I don't know I'm not I'm not I'm not
I'm just surprised okay okay sorry
misunder hat
them I can't believe she hates Laura
cross
yeah because her boobies are too
triangular let her boob triangle
okay something back what if they like a
different shape
then like a star shape yeah I I was just
thinking of that too that would be
impressive uhhuh and she like shapes the
matte will into Like a Knife oh my God
and then she makes sense for the movie
She's in like genre yeah like she
doesn't need weapons anymore she's got
like mass of
bazon yeah yeah yeah she
doesn't yeah that's all you need that's
all you need to do whatever it is
florcraft is doing she just needs to
be he fireplace
cover hey I'm at 95 can't wait for oh
yeah and only 96%
this it's okay I'm I'm going through
fireplace gonk what the hell is a
gonk it's like a song called
gong it's a gnome why do they call him a
gonk he's going to Gunk it
out I place
presents cleaning presence was the worst
part of this
map what what has been your least
favorite part of the
map
everything I guess maybe the tables cuz
you have to like Crouch every now and
yeah every angle you got to get every
angle you got you do you got to get
every angle I hat the last map yeah oh
trust me if you ever played story mode
there's one where the roof is really
really absurdly high up giant bobles oh
God at least this is more reachable like
the ceiling is more reachable yeah
that's true plus it's all interior so
you don't have to climb much yeah yeah
there there are ones that are really
ungodly I won't
lie there's like a subway station you
would never no it's out of my
character lying hard that's why I just
what one more giant Bobble yet to be
clean the holy sister would never lie
unless
necessary what are you lying about
papers to prove that you're really a
nun starting to doubt it after all I've
heard from you H actually a true nun
would not need papers because we would
not use such things for we are poor I
guess you're poor you don't have to go
to nun College who the heck even like
said such a
thing nun College yeah you think nuns
can afford textbooks in nun College none
of that in here oh my goodness
diori actually when I was growing up I
debated on joining like a n or some [\h__\h]
I did too actually yeah let's go nun
face what
yeah sometimes I I was really into
Hamlet and he says take thee to a Nery
NY which is basically just I'm calling
the girl a
[\h__\h] no it was because he loved her and
he couldn't stand the idea of her with
anyone else but he he was also breaking
up with her
oh in my interpretation he was basically
calling her kind of like you should go
to a nunnery cuz you're dirty and sinful
based on my English laugh anyway I don't
actually remember 100% but I'm pretty
sure probably interpreted multiple he's
a
[\h__\h] yeah he's he's just rude he was a
rude guy I like ailia see though the one
where she dies I kind of likes it I mean
it's poetic so yeah it's pretty it's sad
but it's pretty beautiful mhm plus it
spawns the artwork which is like
neat what artwork are you referring to
there's a pain of her like it's called a
yes I know exactly yeah I love that it's
pretty I don't know what you guys are
talking
about it's okay wait you don't you don't
you don't read
Shakespeare uh basically there's this
girl named ailia he calls her like a
harlot that was his like childhood love
or girlfriend and then she dies cuz I
think camet kills her father and other
people essentially yeah she
she ks's herself it's not that I can't
read okay no I know you can
read this is like a chick no one's
questioning if you can read or not we
all know that you can read not you
girls she's a business woman she
has yeah she's
business but spelled
wrong how is it spelled
v u z you know Z with Z's instead of s's
and maybe like when Z is uh in
Reverse yeah sounds about right can one
of you come over and tell me does this
wall over here say it's dirty for you
bro there's so much dirty stuff in here
I'm at 99% and there's still so much
thing to clean I'll I'll help I'll help
I'll lead us because mine is the correct
one if someone can clean this wall here
and get it to say that it's clean what
wall the one that yeah The Grotto wall
over by
the there's a lot of different Grotto
walls the one over over by the present
machine
yeah I willle what I can
okay I wonder why it's glitching so bad
maybe it's cuz uh we're so far apart in
terms of
Worlds got like mardia two people near
like whatever calers Culver thing you're
at where do you live uh near Culver I
live near the
Culver which
one the good one
obviously the hell
I hate when they make things Orange in
this game because when you hit the cab
button it doesn't help you very much
yeah it's hard to
see at least we're bondon while Kara
starves it's okay starving is just a
small problem I have right now there's
there there's there I still need to
learn Korean on uh in the next um stuff
are you trying to
learn useful words I need to I need to
become fluent in the next 12 hours
that's that's not going to happen even
if you had 20 billion hours well maybe
if you had 20 billion hours but in even
if you had like 20
days yeah well it's okay I know I know
some
things you're going to be okay left and
right good food I can say leg I can say
uh
but I say
cat hopefully will be
enough I mean can they not speak
English
um a little bit probably her English is
probably better than my Korean probably
better than
mine but still I want to like be a
little bit helpful yeah yeah
understandable your Google Translate
just in case no it's okay it's going to
work out yeah yeah if only I would have
kept up my my reps my quean reps ever
since I started them cuz I even had a
private teacher come to my home and do
oneon-one lessons with me I so serious
about it and we did that for like half a
year and then I stopped and I thought
okay I'll just try my best to keep it in
my memory for now and you know cuz I was
just too busy to keep up the lessons so
I thought maybe another time I'll get
back to it but now I need a break and
then that that break continued so long
now I don't bre never ended yeah it kind
of sucks when you want to learn so much
but you don't have like the
time displ some sometimes also I think
it's not just a time anymore like I used
to pick up Japanese so
easily but that was cuz I was
young and now my brain doesn't work the
same way anymore yeah that happens as
you get older picking up stuff like new
languages really recommend learning
languages uh as long as you're so young
if you
can the younger the better for learning
languages I wish I knew more Japanese so
I can read my aomi
games that's your biggest issue right
yeah language not being able to
understand ome game
like even if you can read hiana Katakana
you're not going to know the
vocabulary I don't know what this is
yeah that's learning the the writing is
just the first step I know I don't even
know Kani Kan so much yeah kani's a lot
to try and absorb into your
[Music]
brain place
these okay I can't find like visually if
I look at things everything I'm spamming
Tab and I still don't know where like
the dirt is on the object sometimes
yeah it's they they like to make a lot
of like really difficult
angles or like honestly it's like how
was I ever supposed to find like how am
I supposed to get the dirt
here cuz that's where I'm at I'm like I
don't even see dirt I know it's still
dirty because I've selected it and I
found
it and apparently it's pretty decently
dirty but I can't clean
it despite my best
efforts yeah
L well I'll just let Rea get the
100% also Queen but we're not going to
get 100% but Rea can I believe in her
she's a 100%
go-getter yeah
sorry we're just better sorry we're
go-getters am I right go
get it's crazy I'm locking in but so
many things are like at 99% and I'm
going in and I'm like please game yeah
make it I'm go in the lowest percent
which one Santa's list dirty it's
which
list
this I know looks pretty clean on
me okay play you get it 100% no no no so
we have
only technically eight things left which
is groto skirting groto wall panelings
and
lanterns so where the gro
it's the wall
stuff what all the walls no no no it's
just one one so there's uh if you hit
Escape you can see everything so if you
go to groto skirting nine out of 10 are
finished and the one that isn't finished
is at
99 then there's Roto wall paneling which
is at 98 and one is left please I
don't please and then there's six
lanterns so if you
we have ladders actually where's the
next ladder found a dirty yeah there's
there's ladders over here oh I
see protal wall skirting protal wall
paneling what does that
mean wall paneling my nozzle's too
long stubby gun let's go I love the
stubby
gun it's just so cute such a Vibe how do
I pick stuff up I'm pressing F and it's
like not doing
much maybe I can't
um you can but it's being a
dick yeah I can't get my nozzle back as
well what do you mean I can't pull gun I
guess so I have pickup Place equipment
but no nozzle okay wait oh God it's
getting 99% if you put a one in front of
that I have
199% we're we're so that's
enough all right uh well I can't clean
anymore so I'm just going to chill here
yeah I'm I can't even jump anymore I
know it's cuz you're holding the ladder
oh really I'm not holding anything in my
screen I know it's that's what happened
to me when we when we ended before on
the previous one because I picked up the
Lanter
and quite literally I was unable to then
do anything else I
see game one
cooked I'm just going to stand over
here we're all cooked get to
cleaning I think we're cying we're
finished 100% you call this clean not
until you
[Music]
get here track record no all the lers
are clean so now I don't understand how
can you ever 100% anything in this game
it's not it's not this hard it's not
hard at all I don't know why we're
dying where is this Grotto wall paneling
in this groto
skirting I'm going to I'll give you a
minute okay wait I found I found one of
them I found one of them
100% re 100% think of the children I'm
trying I'm going for it I'm going for
it
I I'm trying my hardest you're doing
great you're doing great okay we just
have f one single thing left and it's
the groto wall paneling if you guys not
be
fi if you go through and you find that
and select it do you see anything
lighting
up grow Groo GR Gro a b c d e f g Gro
Groo what Gro scre paneling wall paning
to walls oh I found it or rather chat
found
it I I'm let's see if it will pop
clean I'm doing my best cuz I I feel
like if I get 100 it should give all of
us 100 right like even even if it's
behind right now who knows I'm just
going to copy your
homework go ahead copy away okay man
people used to copy off of me and they
would admit it to
me job
complete what really not for me but we
good
job
unbelievable we got 100 emphasis on wee
we yay wee well okay close just close
the game just close it it's c
all right well that was a good power
simulator session yeah does anyone have
anything to announce I'm gone see you
bye Queen what about you
Missi well if anybody's awake for my
special collab damn it I still need to
make the thumbnail it's okay you got it
you got it need to need eat need to make
thumnail
Korean you got this um Yos please watch
if you
awake but yeah uh I want to announce
that nissa's birthday is coming up hello
yes on the 21st it is my birthday I'm
having a big birthday bash please come
by it'll be lots of fun for everyone so
you won't want to miss it also stream
espresso on Spotify mhm I'll be there in
spirit yes as a ghost as a ghost
I'll also be there as a ghost I think
yes lots of ghost playing with me it was
fun getting the Y yes thanks for
inviting thank you for inviting me you
have no idea how I was so so surprised
about the invitation oh yeah but it all
makes sense now
social no we'll go we'll do more stuff
when I get back we play more
Eden y Eden Eden Eden yeah sorry no
RuneScape for you reisa but maybe again
someday yeah maybe let not not be no
because of the connection oh it's hard
for connection for RuneScape oh no
RuneScape no because the fans are crazy
oh you got R some RuneScape OG I guess
they they're amazing but they also
crowned and it's hard for me to find you
my noelites are well behaved good she
sheep
wow yeah except for that one that
kidnapped me but they were a fake novite
they were a novite but
anyway I'll see you guys whenever so bye
bye darling y thank you for watching
[Music]
everybody e