foreign
[Music]
thank you
this is
[Music]
thank you
this is
foreign
[Music]
there goes smoothie
King
you can earn plats the points
what
okay
[Music]
hello good evening
hmm
hi
hello
[Music]
gosh that's so noisy in this classroom
can y'all just shut up I'm trying to do
my intro
[Laughter]
no I did not have breakfast in bed I had
breakfast in front of my computer which
is also of uh a very common way of
having your breakfast isn't it
in my head
and now you hear it don't jump now
you're here
on this screen it's so noisy ah Kento I
just updated the the Excel file I wasn't
able to tell you it's not going
according to kekako but at least there's
a video
if you want to check it and send it to
the artist that would be a good because
that you're here so I can talk to you
instead of writing because
yeah it's a video it was a video and
better than no video so now I have the
video for today and for tomorrow let's
go
no delays expected it's amazing
absolutely amazing
[Music]
the video from Google was so funny it
was cute I actually like she was um she
was asking me oh so uh you know anything
fine what can I do and I said yeah
anything fine even a normal greeting
would be fine but maybe if you could do
something with like your cute stickers
that you use like for example for the
your outfit reveal because I thought
they were really funny
did something with stickers and stuff
and doodles
[Laughter]
it's a great event I really like it it
was funny it was creative this is what I
want I want variety you know one day we
have a song one day we have even a
normal message is fun you know just
wishing you a happy holidays one day we
have a poem yeah one day we have a
mental breakdown
yeah all kinds of things
yeah yeah yeah because that was good
hmm
[Laughter]
okay so um I know I said I might finish
it today but I will try
um because
yeah I guess a lot of people even though
first a lot of people were like oh you
could finish it uh in one stream when I
actually said I would try to do that
then people were saying oh that will be
rough
so
um we'll do like maybe four hours today
and then
the rest next time
I don't know uh
or or five hours today of game time I
think
uh the thing is why I was thinking that
is because I ended up getting squeezed
in a sponsorship for cancer
I'll be showing off the game and the
contents uh
yes so
um
I'm actually excited for that because
there's so much yeah
I think they will give me an account
with that character that is necessary
for my skin at least I don't know about
the others but at least for mine
I'm actually excited for that
you know got your sponsorships
but this one's one of the special ones
because we're like there's so much of us
to see there
and I want to check it out like I've
seen a lot of previews obviously a lot
of Art and animations and stuff but I
need I need to like check it out myself
okay
[Music]
I know
gotta check out all the special dialogue
all the wrong lines that I recorded
let's see which ones they picked I I
gave them like
what the [\h__\h] not me
oh oh wait maybe I
there it is I don't know what
disappeared
what was I saying
what was that thing oh yeah
no I forgot what I was saying I was
saying uh looking forward to seeing
which voices they did that which oh yeah
because I did like two or three
um no minimum free takes for every line
and it was like 200 lines or so
yeah
tried my best to give them different
intonations and stuff I'm already
tangenting we haven't even really
started damn
it's a lot
no never really recorded
so many lines for okay this is the most
perhaps this might be the most
um
yeah yeah
first major voice acting
can even call this like a voice acting
thing though because I'm just I'm voice
acting myself so I'm just talking is am
I not just talking then
if you voice act yourself can that even
be considered voice acting am I not just
voicing
because I'm not acting
[Laughter]
I don't know maybe maybe
well hmm good question isn't it
isn't that a good question you counted
hmm okay
voicing myself
voice for Chris Pratt let's because
Chris Pratt voices Chris Pratt
are you
okay we should probably play the game
um so we're gonna play for like four or
five hours
ideally and then read super chats all
right
we
and maybe
uh we should also maybe stop by like
those classes they have
I heard they are actually a little bit
important
[Music]
look at that
no it's all the Pokemon
I just rolled your character yesterday
you're nice well as far as I know you
can get my character for free
um but yeah
oh the rewinds the garbage oh oh
[Laughter]
really
like what like a exp candy or
only the history ones are good
[Music]
at least the history class is important
okay well we can check that one out
maybe get some lore will they teach us
some lore
a free selected ticket later on the can
be used yeah I heard something about
that so even if you have trouble getting
my character now there might be a ticket
coming up
for
getting
your desired any
any character
[Music]
maybe I think yeah I know it's a hard
one but it's actually you know
then you'll have a powerful character
that you can absolutely blast every
every one and everything away with
you'll get the character even if you
can't get the character right away you
can still get the skin and then just you
know try every month to get the
character
I wish I was a guide I feel like I saw
some kfb making a guide
uh
I think it was probably in the kfb tag
if that person is here right now how
about you like post it retweet yourself
quote for tweet yourself in the kfp
hashtag
all right guys just check out that uh uh
yeah helpful guide of how to get kiwawa
and how to play countersad Countryside I
heard there was a bug fix a small one
probably won't be noticeable
uh but maybe there's even more
fix is coming that I will probably not
be experiencing it in time
uh an FPS fix would be nice
um a fix that fixes the
the transforming textures would be nice
because that's a weird one
in my opinion
I don't know if you can fix the FPS
now at this stage though is that
something possible I wonder okay
playing the wrong game I thought
I Tesla Horizon this way but that I was
uh dashing
oopsie doodles
you don't think FPS can be fixed
that is possible
it is possible I feel like
I mean look if they can't do it they
really should try it it's like one of
the most obvious things like it right in
the beginning throughout the whole game
but right in the beginning especially in
that classroom is where it got me where
I was like
oh
um
but they pulled out a statement that
they're working on improving it so I
think there will be more than just one
fix
um
well yeah we'll see we'll see
oops I can't play this game anymore in
that life I pressed B because that's
where on the PlayStation controller X or
so is I think where you would talk to
people
[Music]
I know foreign
no it doesn't have to be 60 FPS but you
know
[Music]
oh I think I can I might be able to
stream until the end because I saw there
were some policy changes at the
beginning of the year
I was like did I miss that
I feel like I I heard that something
happened back then but then I was
not sure if it would apply to me or so
or like to whole life in general but
then I also yesterday
said but I also played past the point
that I had to stop at
so yesterday I was playing
um I was doing like
wait give me something to do first
no no how the [\h__\h] do I play this game
there we go
where do we go first
uh oh next after the psychic Arena
[Music]
ice
or one of the
faces ice Jim oh that will be a walk in
the park I mean go to Firestarter
that will be a walk in the park right I
don't know her level but or his level
um
yeah I think we can just go right away
so
oh we already were there before we just
fly there
easy okay a good warm-up yeah
a good warm up by just taking them apart
breaking them apart
like icicles
oh there's a Snowman Do You Want to
Build a Snowman
hmm
oh a snowstorm for five turns
let's see if we got a present Santa son
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] 10.
but if they already
fainted in a snowstorm
how do you know that they're still out
there able to
fight with me
I didn't see any music I mean this this
could have been a person once
maybe this was one of those trainers
before and now they're snowman so
can you really expect me
to fight 10 Trainers
I don't think so
let me go let me go
oh there's nothing up here is that okay
uh what wait this place is just this
huh
that's it wait wasn't there like a
little city
did that not belong to this area
all right sure
uh
how did I miss you
it's finally time for your last gym
right I heard from Monica but I'm Sarah
percent worried about you I know you got
this even La Primera seems like she
wants to keep an eye on you maybe I'll
go find her so we can cheer you on
together when you battle the gym leader
so go have a battle that's fruitful for
you and for the crowd fruit bro fruitful
fruitful
she's a third person
[Music]
fruitful
all of that
it's fruitful and Japanese
[Music]
wait I knew the meeting for food for
like a fitting meaning for it
[Music]
ah
I'm not
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
guys what the hell
I was trying to find a meaning for
Japanese
I know
it feelings for God's sake
[Music]
okay okay
fruitful neh
[Music]
a
Mama yeah Gusto uh
welcome to the glossary of the gym let
me reduce to you as a challenge or your
name is
great now in order to face Jim leader
Croatia you first need to pass the gym
test
here does the other gym that means doing
the stuff
write a Pokemon
yes let's go
let's go
oh
I was thinking that place was perfect
for skiing
dutchie
oh my God
wait is so um
where does it start
Ed
wait what the the exclamation mark is
still inside
Pokemon Center oh I have to what
I have to talk to him again or what
you know
top of the mountain oh
sexy
I don't know how to control this game
anymore no go away how do I get on my
pets no oh
no
[Music]
Plus
how do I Rush
do I
play PlayStation one day and I don't
know what the [\h__\h] to do
L free ah
okay okay is it you
oh oh that way oh
you think I actually they should put my
pet on on ski thingies though so that I
can go smoothly not run that would be
amazing are you gonna do that
you told excuse to write a Pokemon all
the way down just cause it's like
slippery slideries naturally yeah reason
for this little guitar but you'll have
pressure test ready to attempt gym test
by taking on the snooze slip run yeah
let's go let's go
I was free L free L free
oh
[Music]
let's go
oh
the mountain all right oh cool
wait we're not on skis
it's kind of lame uh that would have
made this perfect because it's not the
same
oh wait there we go
did that count
because I touched the flag Maybe
ah
this is the best gym test
it's like a a different game yeah bye
yeah
[Music]
I think it counted
here I show you my last three in jeans
it counts you can touch the legs you
always see the the Olympic skiers touch
the flags anyways it gives you style
points yeah yeah and dynamic points oh
wait there's a timer
oh as long as I do it under one minute
and 30 it's okay well then
well then
it was fun could have been longer
maybe maybe there's a round two to make
it more difficult because it's because
it's all if it's only this then it would
be too short
it was some of the best learning I've
ever seen but oh I mean I expected
nothing less because you're Austrian
after all so yeah you're done let's
oh man why so short
why so short
so short
[Music]
and they could have added another thing
here doing like ice hockey or so it
would be perfect put a goal here put a
goal on the other side let me control
one
and the NPC will be the other one
right
1080 snowboarding oh isn't that like an
old game I played that I think
pretty sure playing like on the n64s or
or PC or something like that
[Music]
yeah ah so good but why didn't they add
it
stopped wasn't there there's no 10th
Iraq where I was going like let's
[\h__\h] go
yeah
okay why am I still so excited
I'm still freaking out oh my God I'm so
excited oh my god when is it coming when
is it coming I need to I need to I need
to do a stream about it
[Music]
I am going to stream Dad when is it
coming
memory leaving the moment
when when
down there
tell me
what the [\h__\h]
that's impossible
tomorrow
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's [\h__\h] go they said before the
end of 22. it's just literally the end
of 2022 right now
can you see me
foreign
did they [\h__\h] delay it
they would not do that after hearing me
so happy
[Laughter]
no they just want to see me that why
don't I always want to see me so sad
uh yeah let's go
no I can't see your comment it's
invisible
cycle
[Music]
have a lunch what
Avalanche started releasing in 20 years
it wasn't delayed oh okay
going on is she the gym leader
so is this was this a boy or a girl I
think it made you look think it's a girl
but it's a bullet right there you are
I'm freezing what you're freezing
just you should be used to this this
should be your element
oh I take it your Challenger
my name is
I used to be a pro actually
because I played on the Nintendo 64
Avalanche 1080. yeah that makes me a pro
because I was so perverted I played it
every freaking day did you also hear
that they are gonna release it on the
Nintendo switch like in 2023 hopefully
early 2023 because I just wanna be
really nostalgic no it's it's just I
want to go back to those days when I was
a snowboarding Pro because I can't do it
in reality because I I got those those
little noodle legs but only on the
computer I am really strong only only
computer yes games I like games so
anyway let's hope that it releases suit
I don't have a date yet it's [\h__\h]
cold let's go
mm-hmm
still trying to act cool huh that was
pun not intended well this is my job now
so I don't take what I'm about to do
personally
it's gonna battle you until the game
releases you know
get ready for the icy bite of reality
oh
we saw his face for a second oh reveal
foreign
[Music]
let's start buffing our special attack
what level is it
the shiny the shiny that I almost had
but never will
it's all 53. nice smoothie wants to
learn hydro pump oh that's a good attack
who's who's moving again
[Music]
oh maybe I shouldn't have brought you to
this Arena I should have switched out
the team a little bit in case I need uh
something else
[Music]
High chance of missing but uh wait uh
she's a
special attacker
and this is what was that sign again
that's that's special attack though
right what is this sign
should I remove this
okay it's the other side
[Music]
oh ah status move oh okay
all right
beer tick no idea who that is but
I'll stay
we're gonna sleep sweep sweep sweep
another torch song
oh hey
hey you're too strong sister I still
couldn't look at the level gotta look
next time
have a check next time
set to 10. well that is that the round
thing
oh my God it is the evolution
oh it looks very strong
today I'm going one more torch song or
go to Flame Pro because this one looks
like it would have a lot of Defense
[Music]
I mean like I can post one more time
right
I think what is the maximum four times
okay yay
[Music]
keep on singing six times
altario
I love ice book ice Pokemon are just so
pretty
not all of them [\h__\h] I forgot to look at
the level again let's look this side
come on
I'm looking 48 okay easy easy
put fluffy bird so pretty I love this
bird so much this is one of my favorite
Pokemon but I never had it oh you're
gonna crystallize it all right because
it doesn't start out as uh ice doesn't
it's just flying but it looks like it
could be ice well there you go now it's
ice what does this get a hat
something because I stick out one of
those fluffy hats
it's so funny
[Music]
never stole a chance should have
actually not crystallized
I know they do it because that's their
thing
oh that was it but if the AI was smart
okay I or whatever then they would
realize that
yeah it would just make it worse
if they terrestrialize yeah
show off the ice ice crystallization
whatever
[Music]
is
yeah
they're so easy
sweep
an impression you have we will strive
for the Future No Matter What challenges
you face
like how I used to be before I got into
games and couldn't play anything besides
snowboarding I should give you anyway
the ninja
you want a photo as well or a hook I
guess oh
there I'm shy
oh cute
oh very cute I like the character design
on this one too
with agent beds you should be able to
look at this book of any level oh
because wait this was the last Arena
oh oh we have one more Titan left and
two
um
caps I think
oh showed me the face again thank you
get those screenshots get those
screenshots
put it in your secret folders what what
do you mean you guys don't have a folder
for that kind of stuff
on before I forget you should take this
too
and I want your jacket it looks really
warm and the scarf
I spinner
wow you know spinner in German is an
insult
to say
like you're kind of crazy you're crazy
yeah someone who's Crazy you could say
oh you're so you must be crazy
or you can say you're a crazy person to
spinner
um
yes yes
I don't really use it much though ever
I think not this word
[Music]
oh an end spin there without the r is
spider
[Music]
wait I wonder when they where you know
what the history is behind that word
hmm
oh maybe maybe because
someone was spinning a crazy web in
their head
like you know
kind of Illusions and [\h__\h] imagining
[\h__\h] that's not real
uh
like a spider and then
hmm
it could be
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay thank you
Kawaii
Dance Design gasket
[Music]
love those designs
thanks for the warm-up battle
oh oh dear hello
and scale of dirt you're talking to my
Pokemon all right okay it's fine
you did it ah I'm so happy for you this
is the best
I know I said I wasn't worried but my
heart was so pounding the whole time
because you played PlayStation yesterday
so I didn't think it would you know warm
up so easily I thought you would mess up
all the buttons and [\h__\h] but there you
go
most impressive kiwawa a shining display
of talent I must admit
firstly pack yourself on the back you'll
beat every single gym
which means
indeed
now that you've gathered eight gym
badges
all that's left is to take on the
Pokemon League and also fight one more
Titan and two camps
if you hope to stand alongside limona as
a follow-up fellow Champion head to the
Pokemon League that is where you can
take on the champion assessment where's
that
I've never seen it
yeah hurry up and get to my rank I'm
reaching for a battle of equals equal
equal
I've gotta take the time while you're
facing the Pokemon League to fine-tune
my Pokemon's moves and re-round about my
tactics
well good luck you Alan wish me luck too
bye-bye
[Music]
it's in the city ah okay
then maybe I did see it I don't know
it's unusual for me to stay here so
excited though perhaps not for you
she must really be happy that she
finally has a friend who can keep Pace
with her own talents her special kind of
strength that can only be reached by
competing with a good Bridal
count me among those eager to see how
far you two can go I ship it OTP forever
in any case I'll be waiting for you at
the Pokemon League Northwest of misakosa
foreign
[Music]
memberships thank you I'm sure the ones
who received it
are very happy and appreciative wow
wow
um nicer
did you see guys today was outfit for
real of music but I [\h__\h] love it it
looks so good on her boobies look really
good too but the whole design with the
cards so nice
I love it
I'm not the only Hello life member who
noticed your boobies some some other
member also replied to her saying that
reminds of Alice in Wonderland yeah kind
of a little bit I guess because cards
but yeah she could like open uh she
could open a casino
foreign
[Music]
version and big big fluffy hair version
yo yo yesterday I went to Christmas
Market and I got some leftover roasted
almonds and they're so crunchy look ah
foreign
some of these are real Jawbreakers
um
[Music]
that's like Beyond crunch that's not
even crunch anymore that's
what what's a what's a level up version
of crunch
[Music]
um
you don't de-shell them what are you
talking about
oh are you joking these are these are
these shelves and then there's um
they're roasted and there's like a [\h__\h]
ton of sugar on top of it
crash
crash crash crash crash I'm boneless
um
Shadow is the best part no you can't be
serious
um
Christmas Market
oh car
the car Evolution spawns there is that
what you mean what the [\h__\h]
oh we haven't really explored this area
have we
titanistan what's next um Dragon Titan
or should we go to one of the camps
maybe your scam the fighting camp or so
oh fairies next oh
okay we can start from here
and try to descend
into madness like Joker
okay
fairy
what do I have against fairy
[Music]
she wouldn't get
um
feeling poison
[\h__\h] I never know the right glasses
stay on poison
[Music]
what are my options
do I have a poison Pokemon
I don't think I do
not
um
foreign
that's interesting
maybe we can take caspers uh actually
but we would have to crystallize
immediately but that's definitely an
option for the boss fight
um
and then we have medical on caspers does
electric resist poison at least
other Terror GM oh yeah
[Music]
did we get that already
neutral
Still Still immune to him
Electric
okay as long as poison is not super
effective against electric and
Taco land is a fair oh wait why wait why
am I saying poison a fairy fairy fairy
[Music]
Fox was just fire attacks oh
come with that wrecked oh [\h__\h]
um
bring back vital which would also resist
I guess
maybe at least instead of someone else
because some of these were just
temporary anyway
handsome and happy second birthday oh
[Music]
what
what fire
antonym
[Music]
no way
on this same day a year ago I also
fought for the title of champion I
defeated Cynthia with the power of the
Phoenix
and it was also your birthday
on the same day
what
it's true
well then I do have to at least do the
the become a champion today
what
[Music]
I don't think a candle can I
hmm
I may be able to at least buy delete
four
um
in any case that's too funny
oh my God happy birthday
happy freaking birthday I can level up
my Tinker Tink what's Tinka think
I think I think is the fairy Pokemon
oh
it's very steel oh they surely also have
a tinker tinker
they surely have it but
it would be cool to have Tink I think
but this one's only level 11.
I wanna find
a stronger one
somewhere
um
no let's go hunt for stronger Pokemon
okay no no I don't know what I'm
pressing
freaking PlayStation controller from
yesterday
confusing me
spark show p
[Music]
IC the quad Pokemon is still poison but
it's so stupid
no
I just want to get out of the menu
sorry I'm struggling
this this map is always a struggle
though okay I mean okay
why not if it's like on a good level
no
maybe we'll get a shiny that I did not
just did not want at all
but koala
foreign
oh my God thank you
Chris box
don't stop just go your own way
keep your head in the game
keep up keep up and never be afraid to
make it hard like a volcano Striker
strike imagine burn it up kick your feet
up
[Music]
lyrics
and are we surprised at all I'm not
surprised oh sure
all right let's fly
beat the beat of your own drum what Feel
The Beat Feel the beat of your own jump
thank you
I'm not quite Gengar was that a shiny
it's so dark
no
cute
to the beach
I feel like if I heard the music I I
would remember it I think
Maybe
no
wait how do you do it
now
I wanted to do Auto Battle
would I would I don't doubt me don't
tell me
what
ghost poison hmm
but only Gengar wait what the [\h__\h]
happened
you little [\h__\h]
so
I'm gonna do it another time you know
what I'm not I don't care
I'm gonna play with you we're gonna play
those games with you
well
no time for this nonsense exactly
where is your family dude
I'm actually considering
getting that ghost Pokemon if that one's
also poison order is this only poison
when it's Gengar
the entire line
[Music]
having a good time there wait wasn't
that steel too like still eyes or so
we're just probably just seal
that could work too huh wait Fair wait
very very
still wins against Ferry right
or poison what so confused
above
yes
still and poison okay okay here let's
eradicate the whole family
huh
I can't
now I can
I know people say that this is a safe
way to figure out if some things are
shiny
it doesn't want to fight just because
it's stupid
oh there we go there we go can I get
some can I get a uh
uh ghost poison Pokemon
there level 40. hmm
now maybe I should try to get one closer
to the ferry Arena they should be higher
level right
I mean it might not be the same Pokemon
but I'll find something surely right
poison
[Music]
foreign
but only if it's terrestrialized four
stars
Gengar needs trade
no thank you
I'm worrying too much about it am I
hello every thought before now what's up
don't you suck me
subscribe
what's up
Martin Martin
oh he got a fancy Tower wow
the Hills
are empty with the vacuum
.
yeah yeah I mean it's a normal one yeah
yeah I I saw that there's some different
versions of the towers
they have a water version and the fire
version it's pretty cool
ice cold that's right ice cold as cold
baby
why are they all Gathering here
oh
it's an interesting one too the fire
frog and not fire flying I wanted to say
can we should we try to fight it what
would be effective against flying Stone
foreign
Electric
yeah okay let's take it down
because I never do this
a rock was correct
two oh
ice
effective against flying
Marty
a girl oh cuties
[Music]
so yesterday my brother
came by
I told you guys he would come by
yeah yeah
we had something to do holy [\h__\h]
painted it's not supposed to paint
here we go
I guess I'll catch it
yeah my bro Tory that sounds like
broccoli
uh I was like still sleeping I was so
tired when he came but he just uh
he just left his his backpack and then
went out again so I tried to sleep a bit
more
then he came back like two hours later
and I was still tired as [\h__\h]
because I was up all all night again
so [\h__\h]
I can't sleep so landed also poisoned oh
but what level was that
what level was that
probably way too low
I reckon
oh
there's a level the level where it's in
here poison fire
[Music]
no level probably see summary
20 20
when all the surrounding Pokemon are low
level a higher level why is this one so
low
[Music]
don't get it
at least we got a Pokemon that we didn't
have in the Pokedex yet there we go
[Music]
oh yeah I was gonna go
oh it's gonna go to
the car let's check it out I guess
item
yeah anyway
so yeah then finally eventually I woke
up oh I can't do this forever what the
[\h__\h]
how lame
can't even fly properly
oh man
and uh then well I got up eventually
when he came back and
we just had to chat about
what's been going on recently
and yeah a lot a lot
discussed some things
what is that
oh
hopefully not as shiny
hopefully none of these are shinies
falling of style
foreign
let's fight and maybe catch this one do
you also get the coins when you uh catch
it
or maybe I'll just fight it
did you see how it moved over to the
side
I think I caught one of a point so I'm
just gonna try to kill it here we go
yeah apparently I need a lot of coins I
don't know if I don't know what for but
oh this one gave you 16.
if
okay wait is it uh
oh is it over there
to evolve it there's an evolution
oh I didn't know
mess up break there we go
wonder what level they are
do I want to waste a lot of my
candies for this one
I don't want to to be honest
[Music]
maybe I will just
ah
maybe I'll just go with the team I have
Chinese gold is so cool
the car
s
how many
um
the trainer have we fought the trainer
before I don't yeah there we go
using Georgetown over and over let you
Snowball the fairies really
[Music]
you try that yeah yeah and then we still
have I guess the steel from dakuma
uh and
condom
[Music]
electric wheel
that's a problem
[Music]
still TM
yeah who should I teach me if I can
momentarily teach
um my main australium
I know that can learn that
steel or poison right it could be
poisoned too still
or ice but obviously it won't be able to
learn wait if no we're not ice what I'm
insane what am I saying
that's something else
yo where are the steel teams oh here
Gunk shots cannot learn
cannot learn
nobody can learn cannot learn
s
[Music]
smart strike cannot learn
already learned um
not looking very good
what about fight oh yeah if I do I guess
we can bring magnified too
poison coverage rare
um
yeah but mine the one I have is like
level 11 so if anything I would want to
get a higher level one I wonder if we
can
find one somewhere higher leveled
um because I like the Pokemon I kind of
want to put it in my team
this one now
Pokemons
[Music]
it spawns around ruins right where is a
high level ruin
can we see that on the map the ruins
that looks like one where it would spawn
but will it be high level probably not
close to the Spy kitchen very close to
me close to the side
it's like a gems like a gym second Gym
second gym
ah this one perhaps right
check the Pokedex
oh does it show me on the map where it
is huh
okay but uh
I'll be here right
[Music]
where was that ruined
what happened to the bgm just now
okay
yeah okay so then we had a talk me and
my brothers
and then I told him let's go to a
h
let's go to a Christmas Market shall we
so we went to Christmas Market like in
the evening I still it was like
6 00 p.m or so and I still haven't
didn't have breakfast at that point so
is this poison ghost or so it just goes
yep I think it's just ghost right
so I had my breakfast at the Christmas
Market
we walked around and I was looking for
kinds of schmann which is a an Austrian
dessert it's like fluffy pancakes oh
that's psychic okay there's fluffy
pancakes
oh that one
let me look at the level
Fair though isn't it
[Music]
it's kind of cool
but also kind of low
I'll catch it
for now you chill
you still get to feel this
just for now
go ahead bird is just walking never saw
him just walking before
okay so I looked for breakfast but we
just couldn't find a place that was
doing Kaiser's mom what the [\h__\h] but we
went to a really big one
went to a really big Christmas Market
that actually
I think it might have been the biggest
in the city and I realized I may have
never been to this one before that's
that's actually crazy
but it's so it was so big and it had
what is that
teeth it had uh all kinds of things
really cool stuff um bought a little
something for my mom because my brother
is gonna bring it to her my mom's
currently oh hi yeah
my mom's currently very sick and she
might have gotten the sea thing
possibly in
um
possibly in Italy
so I also gave my brother some left over
medicine that I had all kinds of stuff
for the throat
to bring to her
but a lot of things
um left over thankfully
um
[Music]
okay you're not even considering it okay
okay fine
[Music]
apparently has really really really
really really really really really
really really really bad coughs
especially in the night time yeah
but besides that she doesn't seem to
have anything else but you know how I
had this little fruit egg I don't know
if it's connected and I just like
had a better immune system I know I have
a pretty good immune system here
maybe it really was a super super super
super super weak version of Corona what
I had as well I don't know can it be
that weak
because if she really got the seafring
from there we spent three nights uh four
days together
drank from the same bottle occasionally
so I feel like uh if she got it then I
must have gotten it too
[Music]
hmm
I don't know
but yeah I I knew I knew what I had was
not a normal fro today like just the
normal oh room is to dry
kind of fruit egg no and I know it was
like something else because of of course
also because there's been a normal cold
but considering my mom is like currently
suffering from an insane cough
or quite concerning so anyway she's
got some medicine from me all kinds of
different
fruit and and cough
helping things
oh I hope that it helps because she's
had this one for like a week now and
it's not getting better according to my
brother
[Music]
anyway
what else oh yeah the little
little something from the Christmas
Market why are these items so close to
each other
a little something from Christmas Market
and uh yeah
and then we got something similar to
Kaiser shmarn it's called shaita Health
um
uh which directly translates to
um is that a shiny
it looks so bright and blue
the record tablet too
what does it Translate to
how do you call it it's like
you know where you burn a witch or so
oh [\h__\h]
burning steak there you go thanks guys
finish
and it's so funny if you survive this
I'll catch you
oh too bad
oh
I heard you
and it's like um it's a
it's kind of something like
um smashed pancakes but with apples
it's kind of like a leftover
um
dish dessert kind of thing
similar to kaisersman
good eat that and oh dark pose oh
what is that the steel attack
where is that fairy Pokemon oh there we
go
[Music]
I wouldn't mind leveling you up girl
hmm
I don't want to kill it
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm too strong uh let's wait for another
spawn
foreign
[Music]
punch
apple punch a baked apple or something
like that
or roasted apples oh hey there's one up
there
it was not normal apple punch
a special apple punch it was really
yummy come on
[\h__\h]
how are you supposed to get up there
how
what can I just do it from below no
this one's easy to catch when you can
climb
right
right maybe from here
[Music]
oh how annoying
hey
one of the essential things to try to
twist the time there's one going on in
my city oh well who knows if you have
the same kind of things there but
um
ah we'll punch
oh this one survived let's catch it
hunch
there's like usually there's different
types of it there's like orange one and
you know all kinds of things you need to
try all of them
uh mulled wine
um
yeah and well fruit flies usually here
we have
um
all kinds of things
is quite common the the one thing I
cooked after the lasagna I think in my
cooking streams I think right after that
was quiche Festival
that's a very common one in Christmas
markets in Austria
cute this is a cute one
and why is that fairy Pokemon
foreign
[Music]
for a moment
that should be far enough
oh
a different spawn
just look for the stuff that smells good
trust me bro
everything smells good though
oh yeah wait you should get a roasted
almonds and also what they also often
have is
um a chocolate covered fruit
I love getting that those are my two
favorite things why did I not mention it
roasted almonds sometimes they have
different flavors with like cinnamon or
vanilla or so on but the basic ones are
the best to be honest usually
ah
and uh yeah chocolate covered
strawberries
on a stick
all right let's not just these all seem
too powerful to be honest
I feel like I would
hurt her no
[Music]
all right let's go caspers a quick ball
wow never mind
two ways
oh that doesn't do much damage good
and what does the most now because
that's already
rarely effective
oh yeah yeah you guys agree
noise
okay I'll try that one more time and
then maybe I'll start catching
did I catch the legendary arts dance
with a little quick follow it
I think there was something legendary
like that right like something epic
happening
indeed oh my gosh
all right uh here great ball first
see how that goes
[Music]
oh
okay God failed
football first try
[Music]
ah anyway okay so yeah we got some stuff
um and then we went back and then um
basically my brother watched soccer
while I was playing Tales of rice
and I was fun oh my God like going I'll
call her bunk as well going oh it's a
girl going back into the tales of arise
world oh my God it's so beautiful and so
fun and even though you know it takes
some time to remember how to do certain
things in the game
um
[Music]
Palace movie
you were just temporary a temporary
solution
might bring you back though when I need
you
all right now I want to evolve it how do
you evolve this one
just levels
what level was it 48 oh
48 it's already 41. oh do I just have to
like oh
nice
well we still want to level a little bit
higher anyway though right so
um
[Music]
okay
uh where are those level items I hear
what was I saying I forgot already
[Music]
ah it's happening
rights oh yeah yeah yeah yeah so I I
still didn't kind of want to finish the
game so I I did a lot of sad quests
yesterday yay huge Hammer funk
side quests that uh gave also some
important insights about the characters
like for example I did the one wheeler
what was his name LOL got the letter
from his dad
um
I did the one where you see the big
Aurora in the sky a lot of strong
enemies yo
um
hammer
hell yeah
well by having this Pokemon in the team
though we have
uh no wait we don't have a steel overlap
it's just that Takoma knows still but
it's not steel so we can get rid of the
steel attack if we keep this Pokemon
hmm 160
can't be used twice in a row okay but
it's also not like
she she has to wait the next uh turn
[\h__\h]
ing
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
that is hella strong I wanna give her
some more
how far does this get us 44. okay
[Music]
flatter
confuse the target
[Music]
um
child developer is pretty funny
uh yes okay we'll do need
[Music]
um
needs all the EXP I can get
[Music]
wow
a couple more a couple more 47 okay okay
the rest I'll do some other uh bunks
where smack what's that
a bug attack oh we don't have bug
coverage I think
1790 you just get us behind the
character attacks it also lowers the
target special attacks why not
good to have right
instead of what so better than fake out
or slam because slam okay
I wonder what else you can learn maybe a
poison attack
I feel like she could learn poison
she looks like she could
poison
no
[Music]
you can learn bug attacks in general
that's interesting she doesn't really
look like someone who could learn it
[Music]
who
should I give her a foul play
oh no
oh check what the texture can remember
indeed forgot about that
what what a sound
[Music]
astonished Fairwind baby doll eyes
rock smash
um training kids sweet because ah this
one steals HP
foreign
dance
Mash can
yeah that one's special the one I was
looking at
um brutal swing oh
it's called work it's not special
and I mean 60 is okay at least we would
have a good like coverage I don't know
if anyone else had dark red now
oh
should we keep it like this okay okay so
now we have a good Pokemon
oops uh
to bring with us
I can't use
let's see
does that work oh that doesn't work yeah
okay though
[Music]
all right
come on come on
ah yeah bye
I don't know who she can find
[Applause]
[Music]
oopsie
maybe the birds
so cute they're up so high though how
are we gonna get them shoot something
shoot shoot
[Music]
do I get them
I thought she shoots Birds I heard she
shoots the the crows
oh that that one fits okay there we go
Mommy's coming
[Music]
don't fight your sister
I couldn't take it I can't look at that
I would feel guilty
how about this one
yeah
yeah good job
good job
[Music]
she hunts coordinate even though lit
beats her one versus one really
perfect night is the crow Pokemon right
that's what I was talking about
oh yeah bye that was not a good idea
foreign
[Music]
I don't have a clear understanding of
what's what she can find you know the
fire versus ice is so obvious but rest
is like what
[Music]
oh fairy
yeah type matchups I don't know the type
matchups
thank you what about psychic
[Music]
nope
oh no yeah that one was okay and this
one
[Music]
walk the t's break their shells
go get him go get him
beautiful
yeah eat another almond
hmm
good stuff I also have a sandwich
and got a sandwich before the stream to
eat
I was so confused yesterday I think it
was Halloween sandwich was trending on
Twitter I was like what's going on
and then I realized
what was happening
[Music]
they did a oh did they already do it
Sandwich review
it already happened
[Music]
oh it's just scheduled ah
well if you guys are planning on making
a sandwich
don't forget to take a photo and then
post it on hashtag Halloween sandwich
come here
oh no
yeah
yummy yummy yummy we'll take a photo of
mine though because it's not self-made
maybe I should partake in the
in the
uh contest though is there something to
win
if not then
it's not worth my time
just kidding but actually I really don't
have time I need to learn a dance
like
soon ASAP
I have to learn a dance
I need to find time for it
[Music]
and I still need to record so much
I still need to record all those songs
that I said I would record
[Music]
let me see the gig out on camera oh my
God
oh
man now that's a big Hammer Hammer Jam
they got anymore
160 power I don't think I've ever seen
an attack so strong
oh yo girl I didn't tell you to fight
that one I didn't want you to oh [\h__\h]
he was peeping up on it
okay
oh interesting attack super
[Music]
man that's also weak
it's rare
I thought so
okay let me check out uh
the pp app
oh the Almond in my throat
um
[Music]
now it's six should I do one more
ah why not
I'm too lazy by the way to do the team
lineup on on my layout uh again so we're
not doing it anymore
for the last episode when I have a set
team for whatever we're doing in the
last episode
Darkness
that's it
it's a fluffy thingy that uh evolves
into a big fluffy thing
a ghost
weekly tough that's an interesting
four stars can I fight it with my Tinker
Tink funky bunk
[Music]
probably
no
let's do it
I don't think I was healed did I heal
myself
I'll try
sneeze
oh well we're not alone
we're done alone these boys will help me
hopefully
that's done
geez they're bringing in some good
Pokemon though
for once
oh
[Music]
I'm not charged
chat with fake guys
what I don't even know what fake I've
done why are you
me
only on the first turn okay
we know it for next time
it will be fine
don't talk anymore
oh but but it's forcing me anyway even
if that was the case
I saw
on that display just now higher than
what's what it actually has
[Music]
okay
I looked higher
the rest like my pocket I can't
oops I can't now y'all
see
oh it's a known bug oh wait
oh my God the the snake the blue snake
Pokemon is dying
[Music]
can I get much higher
after three hits ah
[Music]
so cute pretty snack
I'm sorry
what the [\h__\h]
wait what happened with my play Rock
I didn't see it happening
do it
oh snake is back
[Music]
I was immobilized I love all
so lovey-dovey
you guys are so useless
people are so useless does anyone
will bring a Pokemon that's super
effective against the one we're fighting
out of the NPCs
[\h__\h]
well this chair do
you love can they heal me
we need to heal
did I oh I did oh
running out of time yeah yeah bye yeah
bye
why you always attacking me what if I go
with kick-ups on Hammer should I should
I continue with play well
okay
it has some stupid Shield right that's
why we're barely doing damage
the most difficult fight
oh well now I can heal again right maybe
maybe come on faster faster faster
faster
can you guys just please attack
oh my God
why is it not doing anything
one more playground
lovey lovey no
stop
no
guys don't stop it you [\h__\h] idiot
these [\h__\h] idiots
[\h__\h] idiots maybe I should have
attacked but no I I was trying to but I
was in love
[\h__\h]
I was so
stop it
whatever
don't care
where are we going anyway we got the
Pokemon we wanted now so we can
we can go where are we going
so the ferry Arena right
now
Love Hurts
[Music]
yeah it's not like I really wanted to
Pokemon I was just almost
[Music]
to be honest
I mean some members have been like hey
let's do rage let's play together blah
blah blah and I said yeah let's do it
but to be honest
uh that feature of the game it does not
really
tickle me
that much I'm not that interested in it
I mean I would still do it if I Really
Gonna
do a corable
I mean it's just
fighting a fight and that's it
I don't know it feels kind of boring
um yeah
but so far it has only been hey let's do
it and everyone's like yeah let's do it
and
nothing's really good really
coming out of it so far so we'll see
um
this is the right direction
what is the right direction
huh
yeah groups always need a leader yeah
yeah yeah well it's not gonna be me
because I'm not particularly motivated
about this one oh but you know um
[Music]
ah there you go
that's the bug attack more HP drain
bucks bucks have so many HP training
attacks huh
um I was gonna say
I was watching good at stream because I
was staying up way too late
and um
[Music]
saying like hey we should collab again
surprised and then I
um have some ideas
but what could be good
um
and
uh already
wrote some ideas to her but also uh
she's gonna be participating in the
weather fight we're gonna do it with a
fight next week currently we have four
members participating I originally
thought that it was just gonna be me and
fauna
when we first talked about it
I thought it was going to be like our
thing you know but fauna was thinking
we're gonna have more people
but then the skull collecting part was
just us so I still had that impression
but then eventually
the misunderstanding has been cleared up
[Music]
and I mean it's okay it doesn't have to
be just us
yeah
um so now we are waiting for people to
answer whoever wants to join can join
currently we're just poor though
don't despise what is that
it's not a dark Pokemon or so
I know it's just that stupid [\h__\h]
feel the hammer
oh you wanna be
if
no
yeah but I think it's gonna be fun
though with the fight it's gonna be fun
and uh chaotic because
we are going to do it underground but
like we're gonna look for a big big big
space on the ground
um so not just like a tunnel a self-made
tunnel no we're gonna just look for a
big cave
so that we have a big area to fight so
it's not too easy but still
um
uh no big damage overground you know
right
here I guessed it uh she can fight all
the ice Pokemon because of her steel
right
thank you
I don't know I kind of like the other
day when I was asking gurua to make a
video for the Advent calendar
um
she was
motivated I guess and then I was just
randomly up when I was watching her
stream
and then I commented
and normally I'm gonna be honest like
I've noticed a long time before when I
commented in her chat
I saw like one or two stupid comments in
the chat being like go away Kiana or
[\h__\h] like that and that honestly is just
I don't know it's not very welcoming so
I stopped commenting since then I mean
usually she streams during a time where
I'm not really up for watching streams
anyway
yeah I think you know it's not her fault
or so but her her view is there's a lot
of viewers that don't watch any other
hello love English member I think laughs
so sometimes
I guess they're they might not be so
welcoming sometimes it's okay though I
just I don't know ever since then I
didn't feel so
welcome but then yesterday it was
yesterday was it day before yesterday
I didn't notice such a thing and then
gouda was
quite chatty and excited so
that was nice
um
and he you know she said that she likes
My Sims 4
um playthroughs I actually saw
um that there's a mod for Sims 4
multiplayer
and I'm requesting permission to use it
really loud if we if I can get
permission but I was thinking well if
you like my Sims 4 streams and you like
to play Sims 4 as well we could try the
multiplayers in school
good yeah it had one for a long time
already and it's actually working really
well
you can especially like if you have the
same expansion packs for example the the
newest High School one and you can go
together to the high school
um but yeah whatever pack you have
together you can play that together if
someone doesn't have the same packs then
you can like make the settings so that
you just play certain packs and so on
just activate certain ones it's a really
good um
really good mod
it's very stable from what I've seen
I've seen some people use it
and I think Sims 4 like Max's MEA
is generally quite open to mods being
used
The Sims like
the people behind Sims 4 seem to be
pretty
um supportive of what the community
creates you know
so I think there's a chance that they
allow it
[Music]
and if that's the case then we can do a
Sims 4 multiplayer stream look good
yeah we'll see what's kind of
shenanigans we can get up to
please please please
and she's already level 50 now
soon
no no
no no no no no
oh even oh nice this one
[Music]
um yep
so I'm looking forward to that if that
works out
wow strong
[Music]
foreign
exciting another Minecraft Arc
it's been a while
that we had something
on our server it's probably been a while
that there were four people or more
online at the same time or even more
than three people online at the same
time on the en Minecraft server
probably even more than two more than
two that's uh also already a big
event
or maybe not I guess council did
something recently never mind
but still it's it's
especially for men
first time in a long time server not
might not be able to handle it yeah
[Music]
let me check my Pokemon
what could she be leading with
no idea
let's go
can't complain at
[Music]
the fans some Korean fans finished the
Korean version of do you they put so
much work into it
so it took a while
oh what's that
but there's now proper very beautiful
sounding Korean
what should I use Korean lyrics
with even a guide on how to sing it so
I'm going to try my best to learn it get
out of there
[Music]
what is that Pokemon like ground ground
fire because it looks like a
[Music]
use water ground it's by around
I got rid of my water Pokemon
oh man
[Music]
okay
what was I just saying I had a Korean
version Maybe
one second please
[Music]
foreign
and uh
-huh
[Music]
sorry
important call I'm just so popular
[Music]
hahaha
where's my Pokemon I know it's really
gone oh my God where'd it go panic
come back we're talking about [\h__\h]
fell asleep under the ground she's gonna
die
there she is
come on attack
please no wake up wake up wake up wake
up okay okay
wake up
well that reminds me
something
oh wake up wake up wake up wake up wake
up wake up
oh still sleeping
uh
give you one more chance I think it's
hello hello hello hello hi
wow
no
that's [\h__\h] bastard I hit one to take
welcome back but then it made me sleep
again
I swear to God
[Music]
swear
what a boring tactic
foreign
[Music]
first
I'll take first stuff
yeah I was also thinking maybe Shadow
Ball
come on come on yes okay critical of
them
I'm dying
I've been loser
um no idea what that was
that
I'm okay
it's water no let's want a psychic
welcome valuza
let's stay in
at that fish
let's go
them
no it's just the Almond stuck in my
throat guys don't worry little particles
of almond
those nuts I swear to God but then
I think I had a chance against the den
with Blanc
[Music]
oh wait
I'll win
I was thinking of a different Pokemon
[Music]
oh
wow this is like a stone oh
I can't fight that holy [\h__\h]
oh
no
mom
oh wow that was pure sugar there was not
even an almond in there
hmm
bye bye teeth it was nice having you
foreign
[Music]
nice music oh there's a Pokemon Center
over there
[Music]
should be fine for the ferry Camp well
yeah I'm heading there I'm not really
trying to level but
why not
what
ah
more oh [\h__\h]
I'm losing my team
that one tasted weird
you guys have to get roasted almonds at
the Christmas Market
oh
thank you
I'm so excited to show
Christmas markets to my friend
my secret friend
um
I hope my secret friend will like
Christmas markets I think my secret
friend will like the Christmas markets
Secret
I think it's members only information
for now oopsie
I thought that was an item on the ground
she
said
yeah yeah yeah be careful
be careful chat
um
oh God damn it
hey we got audience they're kind of
close though
foreign
I think
despite a little blue water drops on his
why are you crying
don't cry just because I switch Pokemon
I know it's not fair I know I know I
have too much coverage I'm sorry
but
I'm planning to become the champion you
know
it's all right rolls
the sorrow our trolls this is so funny
yeah it worked anyway wait that means I
have the power us anyway
okay
um
there we go
wait if so I didn't see so closely door
Ark currently is a different Pokemon
that you've also fought before uh
does it also show you the
um efficiencies
for the Pokemon that she's displaying
or for herself
or not at all
[Music]
Miss Martinez
right side
there you go
I think the Pokemon I see okay
uh assuming that I have afforded before
oh yeah have I mentioned before by the
way speaking of hypertrand have I
mentioned
it but the the calendar
now even has
little artworks
um
displayed after you've opened a door
it's so cute
I don't know if I pronounced that
correctly
yeah they're funny they're cute and they
also kind of always reflect what
happened in the video
yeah it's another cute little extra
touch
yeah I think now the Advent calendar has
reached more or less a final State I
think there's not much really that we
need to improve or so
at this point I am quite satisfied with
it
that cup too
stood not a single chance
love this Pokemon
spoon
Sana would have loved this one I think
I've said it before
what reached gold status
or DLC for the Advent house
um there is one day
that I already want to say is important
day 10.
you guys will have to watch that one
early I might even request to have day
10 released five minutes or so early
that one is going to be very special
um
[Music]
I want you guys to watch it
the moment it releases
I don't want to calendar
it is
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
so far things are going pretty well
everyone is mostly also
or so far I mean the Cali thing was just
you know
an accident but so far everyone gave me
their videos on time
right
[Music]
even earlier than they needed a dragon
um
whatever that thing was called
interesting
Minecraft
yeah technically Cali gave it to me on
uh on time as well it was just like she
had to redo it
but that's actually quite surprising to
me that everyone was on time so far
thanks to my good organization skills
I'm I'm also
um I've been sending everyone like
reminders
uh a day or so before if they haven't
sent it yet
you know keeping everything under
control
I wouldn't be mad if there were one or
two delays or so I wouldn't even be mad
because it happens it will be like that
but I'm gonna go grateful that everyone
is trying their best
has this one always looked like this
because it looks like an
um
it reminds me of one of the toys in Toy
Story I think
because of that antenna that it has
but that one was green you know which
one I'm thinking of
unfortunately
[Laughter]
I think they also just have one big eye
in the middle right
it may have sturdy oh is that the one
that keeps it alive
foreign
[Music]
I'll just stay because I don't know what
to do
can't unsee
what what did I just say well
again I will stay
ah that thing
let's try
no not tomato that sound
I I don't know why but uh
it sounds like Tom Auto calm out which
is dream car dream car in German
foreign
[Music]
why can't I seem to capture your data
oh you tried to hack me hacker that's
not a shiny but it's beautiful
nonetheless
I wonder how many shinies as I've
actually missed but you know that
YouTuber that I watch
who also plays Pokemon at the moment on
his channel
got quite a bunch of Chinese some of
them randomly and some of them hunted on
purpose
but didn't even take so much time
apparently
man man
give me some Chinese too oh yeah wait
what is that
that is
some ruin please is that a coin Pokemon
what uh what do we have here overheat oh
I think that's a decent attack
could be an option
Kyla was also lucky recently Kyla well I
feel like she's always lucky
and when she's not lucky she makes
herself the luck she creates the luck
she makes it happen she forces it to
happen
I'm gonna do it yourself sometimes you
know
I think the best things happen
for yourself
instead of waiting for things to happen
so Disney
#philosophical Phoenix
I think that's the camp over there isn't
it
let's sit down there
attack
ah those
uh what the [\h__\h] is that Pokemon doing
here you're not supposed to stand here
this is neutral grounds oh boy were you
chilling and healing yourself at the
Pokemon Center hmm can uh random Stray
Pokemon go to the Pokemon Center and let
themselves be healed
I don't think they would turn it down I
guess
shouldn't
it would be too heartless where is that
coin Pokemon that I just heard
is it on the roof
wait let's see
[Music]
John ah there it is I think I said yeah
yeah you think you're smart hiding up
there huh
machine
Stray Pokemon chatting up Julia
[Music]
yeah
when she popped in
no way
look at that in the back there's um the
water Eevee evolution
or the ice one the ice one never mind
the ice one
[Music]
um
all right
so we are going in with
when when we have to fight with free
Pokemon I guess Sparks and
bunk
uh
and what should be our third one what do
you think
has dig but gets bonked by the fairy
type so maybe Caster so I don't know
as partner
[Music]
all rested up ready for action that's
right that's right although there's a
trainer here oh oh
population bump no I need to get rid of
caspers anyway it's not good for the
normal playthrough
hi there
okay Roblox I haven't seen you in a
while uh operation Starfall is going
well wouldn't you say only two bosses
left now and I heard you also finished
all the gyms basically you were done
with the game not quite yet though this
whole experience has been eye-opening to
say the least I'm glad I could take part
gives me a good reason to make my hair
look so fancy I'm curious what do you
think of costume video
um
I don't know
what here she's not
so
personally I don't think costume feels
any hate or resentment towards team star
no there must be some other reason
behind operation Starfall but what could
it be
reunion
well I'd better get back to keep putting
watch call for me if you decide to take
on the base well you're making me feel
very satis right now look at flowers
here wow it's quite pretty oh
oh final evolution of that
pretty
praying mantis Pokemon
I love it I love it
and oh my God the flowers are actually
pretty here
fluid's cute
I'll battle the trainer and any other
any other trainer I can find around here
and then we'll go one more time to the
Pokemon Center I guess
I hear sound crackling
such beauty
me oh gosh stop
I know but you don't have to say it out
loud you make me blush
embarrassing
oh you meant the flowers here all right
understandable oh
hmm
I'm gonna try this it might not be the
right attack oh I mean it wasn't the
worst
back oh
okay
there's mag
[Music]
oh what some of you guys all trying to
make me go to sleep
so fast
also why is she bloating
[Music]
oh man
ah
I'll wait for a couple turns
[Music]
she doesn't have anything strong anyway
wow what a riveting battle it's so
exciting
foreign
[Music]
no one who remembers does anyone
remember the song
oh my God y'all are such Zoomers
should I
yes there we go yay
I loved that one song back in the day
hmm
she didn't get them
I think you're just too old
all right Richard that's [\h__\h] it
you are going to the usual room you
can't just
say that you think I'm too
usual room for you
reflect on die actions for 300 seconds
I got better okay last resort
[Music]
can be used only after the user has used
all the other moves it knows in the
battle
uh okay no
interesting attack though
okay faster faster faster faster
was there any other trainer around here
and look she's so round she's got the
egg
egg we stole an egg she's running away
because she knows
stole something precious from me
out
a great ball
I need a new job
how bad you become a YouTuber this this
is your audition let me test your skills
all right first of all let me hear your
voice
let me hear your voice
hello
well if you want to be a V2 but you have
to let me hear your voice
hello
well
I don't think you're really motivated
that's like cause I don't know you
already failed at the first stage girl
don't know if I can help you like this
is
too bad Pokemon doesn't have voice over
I saw some
some like voiceover clips
people doing voiceovers oh great
[Music]
pretty cool
what would I use it no I wouldn't
already caught a normal one anyway well
yeah I saw yeah yeah people do I guess
also since a long time ago they do like
voiceovers
for
trainers and so on gym leaders and so on
and
I mean it's cool
to imagine
Pokemon games with voiceovers but I
understand why they still don't do it
it's just their thing it would be weird
I guess put your son I mean I would
still appreciate it I think but
I think it's their choice just their
choice maybe also just to um
I should have switched
[Music]
maybe also just
to continue it will happen
continue uh tradition
um
of course it would be nice to have
voiceover but it's just kind of like a
set and stone thing it feels like and
yes it's also cheaper
um
I feel like they will never add voice
over
there
more
subscribe
well
but they still didn't do it with Pokemon
at this point so I doubt it
well I mean I would like to would like
to be proven wrong
but you know they put out what one game
per year minimum
adding voicing
they'll leave more than more time than
one year per game
and who knows if they can
if they want that
wow
if they want that not us it doesn't
matter what you know if we if we don't
mind them using more than a year
of time
thank you
yeah well we'll see why do you keep
dividing what the Axel [\h__\h]
what's going on
maybe it was the first time maybe I'm
overreacting
anyway
come
but yeah it would be cool if one day
they have voice over I just don't see it
happening anytime
soon or ever
but uh you guys can continue being
hopeful maybe maybe it will happen
and then you can say kiwawa there you go
I told you it would happen
I told you
and I'll be like well you are right once
in your lifetime
okay well we're always right but this
time you were right pollen Puff
bug attack or plant attack is it good
once in a lifetime all right
grass plant attacks
crap
dire hit
oh there's some
something in the back perhaps is there
any Islands by the way
hi
what are you doing here
hello
hello Pokemon
whoa whoa
all the burps
okay I will enter from the front because
they probably require me to a little bit
from the front hello
Birds
looks like an outbreak
okay yeah
foreign
whatever that cutie was
I never know their names
I never do
okay I'll heal first Joe I could have
probably teleported but oh well
get it moving
swap blue
Express never got the sale Pokemon which
one
you mean those birds I just saw that's
supposed to be a seagull
doesn't look like a seagull
to me I mean wengo yeah Wingo cute but I
was focusing on on newer Pokemons
[Music]
um
all right let's go
inch that
tall
oh wow oh wow wow they're like where's
the answers I thought this was the
entrance
on it
that was that's that's quite the lag oh
there we go here with activates
oh who's this
oh well we'll return later when it is
time for the young masters piano lesson
oh
spoiled child care adding all the
instrument lessons from his family
until then please give him my regards
here's Mrs Harrington and Mr Harrington
who might you be here young lady a
friend of the young Master perhaps also
this this here right next to where I'm
looking
censored or so
uh young Master Dallas
I see since you see him on the web I
must inform you that this is the base of
the team Stars fairy crew the [\h__\h] Squad
let's play Young master
hurry time I don't think we're supposed
to be giving out that information
no then please accept my apologies
do you have any ideas to who this young
lady might be
she's no friend of ours you know I think
she might be here to try and take us on
understood in that case I take your own
adversary of the young master
um I don't think so
but okay
well okay that leaves me with one
question would you be so kind as to
indulge your fight
not the ground
I'm fighting a piano teacher
[Music]
whoa
I um forgot that looks like that
[Music]
wait if I keep on using the hammer
though it only has seven PP
oh
even the HP went down was slower yes
maybe I should teach her one
um
[Music]
steel attack that has a more PPE just
for this purpose
oh and I also can't use it twice in a
row right
I need something to alternate
[Music]
what should I use against
that was so cute
[Music]
I love it
it's so cute Kawaii I can't see it
though because of the hammer
oh
wait
[Music]
oh it's because of Torment
I was confused about gigas on Hammer
suddenly affects every attack I have but
it didn't say so in the in the
description oh come on
[Music]
well so was that worth it dude good
Pokemon you got though not bad for piano
teacher
an outstanding performance however be
aware that the young Master will take us
battle prowess before I suppresses my
poultry skills he would do well to take
care now if you'll excuse me
ah she says that
the gentlemanly guy used to be the
director of the Academy I think at least
that's what I heard oh
interesting
now he's like you're turning the bus or
something he shows up here sometimes to
take the bus to his lessons hang on why
am I explaining this to you there's no
doubting you're here to make trouble so
I gotta let everyone know
s
hey
ya
oh I see the girl that has been dead
with a good job
foreign
gets his grants to do all the dirty work
for him but his weak point is his short
fuse getting good and angry and it'll
match much at the front lines to deal
with you himself in terms of tactics
there's nothing else for it but to take
down all the luckies you send your way
just tap it out until the Ortega shows
up and go from there ring the bell on
the gates and once you're ready to kick
off this face of the operation time to
wipe the squad of the map
let's go
[Music]
kinda wanna
hear my pee pee
I don't want to use my e first e first
don't come
so easy
all right is that
in the snow that's the one
just
just once you know yeah since it's right
there before we go in I don't mind
anymore
[Music]
and I guess let's add another steel
attack
[Music]
just for this occasion
is
[Music]
so mad
and
so oh
something that's not special right
[Music]
um
what do we got
maybe also something that she could
remember but metal claw
smart strike
smart strike never misses
70 power
no that's dark
metal cloth
metal clone the other one
protect
craft protect can I
see
but that's just the protect
that's not an attack is it
remember mental call for free
what the hell there it is
no there's no protect
I couldn't make any of them anyway
either
unfortunately
Hammer protect Hammer protect not a
hotel unfortunately I can't do that but
I will let her remember
the 21st of September
what am I doing
oh
here
and metal claw
so we can do Cricket on Hammer metal
clock he got on Hammer metal clock you
gotta have more metal clock
but get rid of
fake out or play rough or scared or
smack it's just for this time but
I have to let it go no
no
wow
would you guys be
um up for watching me finish Tales of a
rise on stream by the way would you guys
want to watch that I know it's been a
while since I played it on my channel
but would you want to see that yeah
it'd be great to be able to
ah
have the finale on my channel
foreign
I did some side quests
so we would really only focus on the
finale I think on it let me in
[Music]
um
super delayed yeah because I didn't
really expect this to be possible
I was gonna finish it alone on my own
but if we get promised and I think we
already have friends I'm just trying to
make it clear
and I think it would be something
I'm not like really excited to play
Tesla Verizon it was a lot of fun last
night I was just so tired I could barely
keep my eyes open at the point of like
uh already 9 p.m or so and yet I stayed
up so long again because I could not
sleep even when I'm freaking tired as
hell
I don't know man don't get it attack
something you stupid crocodile
[Music]
oh as papa is not handling that one well
oh
[Music]
leg oh my God
well we can handle it with just two
Pokemon just fine
we don't need the help
of another one
[Music]
that was quite the lag
oh
man oh slow motion
let's go
[Music]
all right
oh
is the time going by in slow motion too
is that one normal two one
because that wouldn't be fair
[Music]
if it goes by normally now I'm the only
one suffering
[Music]
oh my God
this is oh my God have you guys
experienced it the same way because this
is actually painful
play a little bit
oh not like this
oh oh oh my God
they heard my calls for help
[Music]
oh never mind
[Applause]
come on
oh yeah just one more
awesome
oh my God
ah our defenses are breached up to the
boss now I had the sister in the poison
Forest Area
kill pink
oh my God
oh my God baby girl
likes fantastic it's fantastic you can
touch my hair and brush me everywhere I
don't know what that is about to live
bro
your body
[Music]
okay
talk about underwhelming I was expecting
someone I don't know a little more
beefed up well whatever I don't care who
you are not like I'm gonna lose to you
anyway if you think fairy types are all
about cuteness you're in for a nasty
surprise oh wait one of my Pokemon is
dead isn't it
oh well
ah life is sunset it's fantastic wow
[Applause]
[Music]
I promise I'll play nice so don't blame
me when this battle sends you a
blubbering back home
uh-huh I have nothing effective right
now that absolutely sucks
wild charge is super effective oh and
bullet seeds well then I'll take this
opportunity to switch out
um
[Music]
I switched to dakoma
what a fairy very nice at least we have
some variety and I can use other Pokemon
too
let's see did you just realize how
unmatched you are if you want to give up
Now's the Time
please tell me I'm faster I am of course
faster now
one down
and Wigglytuff I will switch because
that come already pretty hard but uh
briefly tough
shall we
go to Bunk now
okay
[Music]
Papa
watch
him
a little bit
at least they're holding up quite well
with their levels
that's fun
oh
[Music]
God
dog
[Music]
have a taste of this slick move but you
can't handle my Pokemon's adorable
strength
um at the Christmas mask and it was so
pretty damn I want to get this time
again
it's so beautiful and fluffy
oh
I'm gonna get one and I have a house one
day
[Music]
either somewhere yet or or
um
a corgi Corky let's work
but someone needs more fluffy but I like
them both they [\h__\h] like crazy yeah my
cats already do as well
I will become
a fluffy monster myself what the heck
why is my team on the ropes that's
totally not fair
is it car time
[Music]
is that is it yeah wait still
very steal
[Music]
um
this is a problem
will it make me more defensive if I
terrestrializer will that not help me at
all this one's just very
well one made me like it won't help my
metal claw I know that but
don't do it okay
yeah bye please don't die I feel like
the car attacks first yeah oh oh
[Music]
wow but this one's a toughie I think
I'll have to heal
it's okay
[Music]
back in the game
spin out
if he used spin out last time he might
have killed me I feel like but not sure
[Music]
the guitar going strong
hey
oh I cannot be confused I have such a
skill
that is absolutely perfect for this
occasion
yo that attack does nothing damn even
though it's super effective this is the
toughest
car fight I've had so far even though I
have something super effective
is it possible that Bonk is not a very
strong Pokemon
play rough I could do more damage
oh I got minus two attacks from Jackson
oh
okay hmm
oh well uh how could I lose what the
heck
to be like that sometimes
sorry about a year and a half ago
ah what the heck
your Thai car didn't bite an angel huh
I told you it's not a toy it's called
The Star mobile and I was up all night
building it
the probe is cool either we're not
giving it enough juice you deciding this
thing to be powered by too sure could
there but it's just too heavy
that's such a shame I want to see the
looks on everybody's faces once we got
it moving
I'm sorry I really thought it would work
come good fellow there's no occasion for
melancholy why to make such a remarkable
Contraption by thine own hand genius thy
name is Ortega
yeah well there's no point if it doesn't
work it is there if I knew all that
effort would have zero payout I'd have
just asked mother to buy a car for us oh
he's a rich boy after all
saying this is why people don't take you
seriously you say some stupid things you
know that what oh
would you
yeah how about now I mean we even put
this in the code for crying out loud
when we started team style we swore to
quit relying on our parents or bags of
cash to fix our problems for us so did
you forget
oh
if that hunk of junk doesn't move get it
moving if we showed on juice just gonna
crank up the power somehow doesn't take
a genius man
it's easy enough to say Melly do you
have an actual plan
yeah I'm gonna train up my Shark Cadet
and have him a bomb they're boosted
Firepower will get the Star mobile
moving no sweat
but the yellowware of operation star is
nigh at hand will you succeed in time
oh I'll get it done
she did indeed get it done belly wait
you know Miller shoot your mouth open up
a lot but she means well
you know ah this sucks
and
they got into a fight to there
this sucks I hate myself for losing but
I also can't get over how awesome you
were in that battle oh we're getting
recognized
let me take a fruit candy because that
dialogue really hurts for some reason
if any of our Squad bosses are defeated
that means we have to step down and go
against our code would make a traitor to
the team
and uh fine not like I have a choice
anyway so take the badge already you'd
better treat it with the respect it
deserves
[Music]
shaking hands kind of loot but
it's all right you know the badge looks
kind of weird
is that like
supposed to be color
on it
why
I'm not done yet here's my favorite tm2
feel free to Marvel or DC at how awesome
it is whichever you prefer Dancing Queen
um
I've seen that one used before
and just so you know you are the worst
like the most annoying person ever
but I get it you're super strong I'll
admit that much you've even busted up my
Starmobile
now let's go back to piano lessons all
right
Mr Harrington
I guess it's time for my piano lesson as
it happens I just lost my boss title so
I'm all good to head on home
oh actually a different matter brought
to me there's somebody I would like you
to meet huh
I think we're having
one of the bosses meets the dude
he's uh they send acquaintance of mine
yeah no surprise
the two directors
the name's Clive
okay
what's your business here
I want you to tell me something you're
the son of a wealthy family and there to
a major apparel company so I joined a
group like teamstop
want a question to ask someone you've
just met well my answer is the same as
everyone else in the team it's because I
was being bullied
so the academy really did used to have
an issue with bullying
who would guess right the school is all
rainbows and butterflies these days oh
well then how about you come back all of
y'all
and the bullets from back then don't
even go to the academy anymore
well then let's go let's go to school
huh
why what happened to them
Lester former director of the Academy I
believe I'm best positioned to answer
that question
Mr Harrington
about 18 months ago the members of
teamstar confronted the students who
used to bully them and then altercation
broke out between the groups though we
did not escalate into a major incident
the alteration nonetheless caused a
scandal of hyper to unknown proportions
as a result of what occurred today the
students who had perpetrated The
Bullying dropped out of the academy one
after another
Academy
no I should imagine not my former deputy
who deleted all records of the incident
you see what why would anyone do that
just as I was puzzling over how best to
deal with the team star in the aftermath
of the incident a certain student came
to see me the student declared that they
would take all the responsibility for
team's action
s
in exchange they requested that I
actually want to read the other students
of teamstar for many blame
oh no no one told me that
I accepted their request and agreed not
to take disciplinary action against
people
then I assigned 18 months of overseas
study to the student which is explained
why she only calls you you from the
phone that doesn't talk to us
who took responsibility for the team
a year and a half studying abroad
this was not in and this was not
intended as punishment you understand
teamstar were the victims after all I
wanted a student to take some time to
rest so I had them return home to the
gala region under the pretext of
overseas study
home
around the time however the former
deputy director took it upon himself to
raise all Races of the incident from the
academy service
it appears his intent was to Shield
himself from any blame his
his
so he tried to cover up the whole thing
that's terrible
after we discovered what he had done I
dealt with him appropriately of course
but the inability of myself and the rest
of the teaching stuff prevented terrible
act also represented a grave blunder on
our part
I accepted to blame that lay at my feet
and resigned from my position as
director the rest of teachings to have
then joined me in handling in their
notices handy
so that's why the current teachers were
all brought in a year and a half ago
I understand my actions have caused you
a great deal of trouble you have my
sincere apologies
hang on Mr Harrington how come you
suddenly decided to talk about this now
fashion
I merely wish especially because we're
taking them all down there's only one
left and they have to resign right
when they're
um when they lost the fight
I merely wish to give you a chance to
charge a better course
well there's no way I'm abandoning my
friends and going to school without them
not after we've come this far
are you aware that
four of you five
already are defeated
I guess I'm doing him a favor by if I
take the the fighting one down as well
then they can all go to school
s do they have to do
nothing
hmm
[Music]
your friends and team star must mean a
great deal to you
isn't that obvious
it's cause you know they're my greatest
treasure in the world
oh and this little boy is at sundara
hmm
don't worry dude I got you covered I
will make your last friend boss lose his
job or her job as well
and then
no more excuses
start [\h__\h] to you then
I see with its boss no longer Squad is
good as finished
I'm sorry we're almost there now just
one boss left the operations been a huge
success thanks to you kiwawa and collab
has also performed admirably as your
support
I remember him saying that your
acquaintances have you known each other
alone
not really
well is clearly a reliable friend it
almost reminds me of the gang back in
the day oh
okay
as you know team star was formed by a
group of students who were being bullied
at school
um
shortly after forming the team these
students none other than the squad
bosses themselves confronted their
bullies add on the outcome was a
resounding Victory first team star
although you could hardly call it a
contest
the police didn't even put up a fight
they all bolted from Battle the first
chance they got
squared speedless of Teamster the
bullies then dropped out of school one
after another and Teamster ended up the
villains of the story
but that's never here nor there forget
that I mentioned it now about your
reward I transfer some milky
yo we got so much LP we need to use it
again
buying something but what
ah
make good use of those DMS they should
help you take down the last remaining
boss
TMS
and clothes Aya
uh here I am
stay in your Pokeball for once will ya
dub
hi it's movie Walking By
[Music]
strutting her stuff
ah team star went for all that huh they
just wanted to bullies to go away but
then they became the bad guys in
everyone's eyes
what a joke the students the teachers
they're also messed up
if even just one of them had been paying
attention when everyone was getting
bullied they'd have been able to tell
right away that team star wasn't the one
in the wrong
but I guess the big boss was the one who
urged everybody to face their bullies
despite knowing how messed up the
academy is with a massive idiot creating
team star and just hoping their plan
with miraculously work out
[Music]
I'm sure of it well here's your reward
thank you thank you
next bus is the very last one we're
counting on Yuki Wawa laughs
that's not my little boy voice that's my
little shy girl voice
inside
whoa
pimping no bikes
and because I think there's items in
here to get
what did I just hear
ah there
up there no no the vending machine this
thing yeah
there's a difference I'm trying
supposedly there was supposed to be
different yeah
[Music]
oh
my God
oh wait there's one more there
you know one reminded me when this movie
was walking but I guess today I wrote it
in the pre-chat but
I had an accident with chunkers and
honestly I feel so bad about it that was
one of the reasons I couldn't sleep
because Chunky's was sleeping next to me
and I was like looking at her and
thinking about her
because she was in so much pain
um
it was an accident but I never ever
heard a cat scream like that before I
think
I felt so bad I just had to oh my God
cuddle her endlessly
make sure that she knows she's super
super love but she seems really fine
which I I can't believe that's why I
kept on like touching her checking if
any spot hurts I don't know I didn't
really see it that's why I don't really
know which part
would be affected
but she walks normally and she eats
normally and she sleeps normally
she purrs she's happy her tail is up oh
my God
um she seems fine but uh I can't imagine
her being fine to be honest after what
happened I don't even want to say it
because I feel so bad about it but it
was an accident
um
and I feel so bad
I don't know what it is recently with
the accidents man sounds like a healthy
cat well the thing is with cats like
you know they normally don't really I
mean sometimes they show but there's
many cases where they don't really show
that they're in pain
um like for example if cats have like
um
I've I've heard this from a different
cat owner their cat had like really
really bad
uh tooth troubles or so and you don't
know this until it's like really really
late you know
they won't really let you know
on their own
I can't hear injury for us from a while
before we took over that yeah stuff like
that but she is acting very normal but I
don't know maybe I should bring her to
the vet anyway
I don't know
I didn't step on her but um
oh [\h__\h] it was really really really bad
she kind of got stuck somewhere in the
very very painful way
for a moment and
I I that would have even hurt me like
[\h__\h]
so I can't imagine
how she would be fine now you know but
yeah I I should probably take them for a
general checkup anyway it's been a while
maybe on William
need to find some time
until Christmas is kind of packed
everything
I will try to find some time
yeah I want to make sure chances is okay
I mean she really seems fine she's like
we had a good sleep over cuddling I was
just worried as [\h__\h]
I'm fun
I don't know
[Music]
this time I've gone for Stephanie on my
dog I have a mom panic attack
I was I was so close to crying like
after that incident and at night too I
was looking at her thinking I'm sorry
that that happened to you my baby I love
you so much I'm so sorry
oh how could I let that happen
110 85.
should I take this
um
it's kind of stronger than flamethrower
also leaves with a burn
it's just less accurate
[Music]
you can come here
yeah you're gonna jump up here
yes oh hello
flame for a better
some if I somehow put something
I've never seen like it would hurt
[Music]
Fire Blaster misses a lot okay
oh smoothie walking around my table and
in front of my camera oh
smoothie
I can't see
so soft
it made noises like they're dying yeah
they're very very very sensitive when it
comes to their paws or their tail
especially with
like we humans
also cry when we Bonk our toes against
something
for a moment at least it's really
[\h__\h] painful even the smallest thing
what
um
anyway I am
I feel so bad
so bad I feel so [\h__\h] bad it's not
like I directly inflicted the pain onto
her
but it was a crying of an accident where
I was somehow part of it
and I I just can't I feel so bad I feel
so bad I I wanna
I gave her a snack immediately after
that a lick licky licky snack
whatever happens just shove some snacks
down their throat hope that they're fine
she forgave you you should definitely
forgave me she I don't even think she
ever was mad at me
[Music]
um
doesn't see it as I inflicted it on to
her
think so
how long was chungus in that position
um maybe in like two seconds
but the way she screamed I swear I never
heard the cats scream like death before
I've heard cats scream in pain like when
someone steps on their tail or so but
this was the worst I've ever heard
it's literally sounded like
someone was stabbing her
[Music]
thank you
[\h__\h] terrifying
[Music]
I want to go on a
six months break to reflect on what
happened
yeah she screamed like really knock me
out screamed
turtle
like a really really scary movie
[Music]
I don't even want to say what it was
there's a cave over there
[Music]
special Pokemon in here
what is that
oh
well I just saw a big one out there
you beam
a nice seal attack that might have been
could have been interesting for our
fairy fight just oh yeah speaking of
that I wanted to switch out some stuff
but the question is also
I'm keeping her should I keep her I
think I'll keep her for now
um but we'll change the attack again
what did we have
fake out right should we bring it back
only to remember to use it though
let's go annoying some of us
restart the game okay I can do it right
now
uh wait save
[Music]
she's good excellent tapping good moves
kind of fast and bulky oh yeah I mean I
like her design too she's kind of cool
fairy steel is also a type that we
didn't really have so
okay
do be cute yeah
did you find any shiny well yes I found
one
and walked past it
last time
why must you ask such a thing
must see her sleeping animation during
picnics
no that was not just spooked
telling y'all
that was not just her beings
I mean she's ah
probably fine I hope but who knows you
know with cats you don't know so you
gotta be careful there could be
something like I was thinking maybe she
has some internal bleeding or something
that I don't know about
um
I don't know oh my God
okay uh
where to next
the best in your bags are fully in why
thank you
car is important for such a long time
Titan foreign
[Music]
up here
am I okay 11 wise what is strong against
dragon
is it fairy or is it the other way
around very very weak against dragon
and then we can finally learn to climb
yeah apparently that's the last skill
that's left over
fairy arms Dragon okay very eyes Dragon
oh we got some stuff like that
actually we have an ice dragon Pokemon
this one
frogzilla
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh I didn't check those perms but we're
gonna be done this week anyway
[Music]
by the way
you know I'll be in Japan a lot uh
winter spring
um
now I wonder what will happen to all
those plans of me playing RPGs
um
what where does that come from
spring too
um never melt ice oh
yeah guys that's where ice Pokemon
keep on opening the [\h__\h] map
is
Attack stronger
but when those Tales of Symphonia are
released and when does Fire Emblem
release again
I mean handsome handsome Symphony I'm
not feeling rushed at all Fire Emblem I
would like to play when it comes out
though
late January okay
I will I will be back for late January I
think
and then hopefully I can finish it
before
before I go back
okay for Kale's off I think we'll have
to wait but that will be good anyway to
have a break before starting the next
thing
did I find her before I didn't she says
she's strong is she really she's a
dragon trainer
dragon dragon I just learned fairy and
ice
and dragon
really be celebrating New Years with us
in some way or another yes
I will be streaming on the 31st
and there is that
concert right I don't know I can't
remember what time it will be
flying forward
[Music]
so that for sure but maybe also
additionally something else
he
he anyway
I think I want it
just a buff right
27 that's not New Year's
but yeah we didn't talk about it I'll be
um I didn't talk about it right I'll be
featured
in
the concert
not only on like the normal stage
but also we cannot have three stages
this time I guess like free free parts
of the concert
um
one let me explore here a little bit
one is uh you know normal day one where
I will be
and in terms of En members oh
who else is on day one ah look at
here there's no like special Pokemon in
here
that's weird
[Music]
uh-huh
and yeah
uh so I'll be on that day but then on
the second day
oh it's cute I saw you before
that's okay what is that thing I don't
know
and how do I not kill it
it's a weird fish
one
Dragon want a dragon okay
um maybe don't hurt it too much
okay
does it have an evolution
they change color but they're not shiny
uh-huh
what is the shiny color then
no Evolution oh
hope that will not fill it
okay
it has a partner Pokemon oh
Ultra Ball
yeah okay anyway so day two
um will be like all the other em members
uh like I guess Kelly Iris crony
Bales quite a lot on this day I thought
the balance was kind of weird when I
first heard of the lineup
group before him aha
yeah
[Music]
um
there's more en members
on oh there it is the yellow I guess
it's not shiny there's more and members
and maybe also even more ID members on
day two
but
I will take this as a chance
oh it's orange or so
is that shiny
it's funny
[Music]
yellow shiny is orange
but this one's orange but I guess
do they change
is this a different form
not that one but I saw a yellow one was
the yellow one shiny
did you see
it was like a golden yellow one
yellow another form okay
oh well
it's okay don't need it it's not like I
want it anyway
what was I saying oh yeah so hmm
yeah I I thought okay
[Music]
the balance is hmm
but okay
and at least there's a chance for me to
stand out
or maybe
possibly
so I'm still excited and then after I
think it's after day two like date
on the same day as day two
normal
one is the the hollow 27 stage
which is in collaboration with tickle
Mina
and I'm part of that and I when I got
the
I guess info that I will be
participating I did not even realize
that not everybody is participating
not everyone
so I am quite honored
and excited
anymore
shiny
no
just checking
so you guys look forward to what I think
uh I know what I'll be performing
already and I think
it will be epic and you will like it
[Music]
but that's all I can say I'm scared to
say something that I shouldn't be saying
so I will not say much about anything or
anything ever ever
yeah I'm so glad I was chosen and get
more time to perform more opportunities
to perform
[Music]
thank you
and hopefully some of you guys can even
make it to watch it in person and if not
then stream is fine too
uh what's what's next punch Crow
D huh
[Music]
can't see him
even if you can't make it this time
you can still watch the stream and I
think
the stream last year had really really
good camera work in my opinion and
at least the stream is kind of more
immersive
from what I heard
than reality right because it looks
really on the stream it really looks
like we are like right there
with you guys
that's how it felt last year when we
were watching it we were like holy [\h__\h]
this looks so cool
hmm
[Music]
whatever
I think it will be very enjoyable no
matter how you watch it
um
oh yeah the Blu-ray
whoever was at the Blu-ray probably uh
received it by now
who will chat all the the
um what's the word
not FPS but the
um
what was that again
all the problems yeah with the bit rate
now looks much much better on Blu-ray
much more enjoyable
I know
she don't know
[Music]
[Applause]
oh okay cool oh
[Music]
where did I respawn don't talk to me oh
oh it's Ivan where am I
so rumor has the false Dragon Titan
looks somewhere in this Lake yeah not a
single person ever caught a glimpse of
it must be some kind of truly terrifying
beast but how are we supposed to search
for a thing when we don't even know what
it looks like
sure would be handy if it just ran
around crying like Titan or something if
only right
foreign
what the [\h__\h]
it it looks a little bit like that one
no
where's cash baby is this name that I'm
thinking of
it it's huge
but it doesn't really look like a whale
it looks like um what is that kind of
animal's name with those whiskers I
guess a catfish but no not necessarily
what I'm thinking of
you like a catfish
is it supposed to be a catfish why is it
so big why is it bigger than Gyarados
we should only answer you anymore
my fish catfish
I don't want to kill it but let me try
play rough
foreign
but that surprised me that thing is big
so is it water dragon or so
oh I should send like a nest ball or
something
damn it
the slowpoke's so cute
reflection kind of weird though yeah
don't
know
[Music]
water oh it is a catfish big catfish
Pokemon popcorn is a glutton but it's
bad at getting through the teams over
toxic you need to catch prey
wait so is there some something special
if I put them both in my team
oh my God
that is not a Dratini or did you see one
in the distance
I don't see one
double battles only what
interesting oh
it looks so white but it's probably not
white and it's shiny form anyway
no no [\h__\h] it's Dragon huh I didn't want
to kill it
it was too bad
is there a different color
of shiny for each one of the colors of
that fish sushi fish
muscle feather
yeah wow so probably what if we don't
have green
um
[Music]
maybe wine or black or
purple blue there's no blue right so it
could be blue
brown white and orange
but not the same kind of orange that
we've already seen
what are those others
also where's this dragon
where is it
where is the Titan
[Music]
nine
um
peace
which one could fight all this stuff
where did they go
wait now when it's sitting on that thing
it does look like it's a sushi
foreign
[Music]
I'm back
now come on right in front of you do you
need do you need glasses oh
come on you little [\h__\h] that thing is
stalking me oh my God it looks like
it's like just notice it now the nose
part
name
why is everything so laggy
oh my God
the big fish is the sushi shell really
not so cute
looks like we could make a lot of sushi
out of the fish itself though
okay okay okay okay
we're back in the game
um fish
nine nine
I just already saved and restarted five
minutes ago
it's just the area that we're in ah
small fry
ah windbreaker good times I showed my
brother that all those gifts I got from
that Valkyrie connect collabo you know
the Minecraft stuff and the the he also
saw the Wind Waker
link thingy and he really likes that one
oh my God
what
that one this one
yeah he really likes Zelda games too
gotta get him a link plushie sometime
that one's mando
the Wind Waker one attack
oh
no he didn't take it
um
the water reflections
are at fault you think
at least here it doesn't have that weird
bug that I saw elsewhere
rain dance
dance
I already caught this one right yeah
okay
why
mom didn't understand
I got the XP anyway
I heard the audible baseball
well at least you know
I regret it I'm very regretful about my
actions okay
I'm sausage
still haven't found the Titan
[Music]
maybe I check on the map for now I was
just chilling
just hanging
let me see
oh
I'm like completely somewhere else but I
also I'm curious about these islands
um they're making me curious and we got
time anyway because we're doing two
parts anyway not planning on finishing
today after all in case you
guys missed it in the beginning
oh my God
who's that
I can't recognize it what the [\h__\h] is
that
Grill
it looks weird
oh
now you look a little bit more
[Music]
yeah is that also scrap yeah okay it
looks weird
see how that's supposed to be a seahorse
oh
hey
what I hear it still
I hear it still
what's going on here
fine let me go back
to
oh it's gone
maybe if I just run into where I think
it is
it's louder
oh
hot hot cold cold hot
huh stick should be like I was like here
oh not here
okay I guess I can't run into it when
it's um invisible
I never tried filling a picnic before
because the game is just not telling me
how to do it
how come it didn't tell me until now I
thought you know those picnic people
would teach you but no they just heal
you and give you picnic stuff
well not that I need it
flame I don't want to pick dick in
Pokemon
it's more fun in reality
[Music]
sweet sour sauce oh wait this is this
cereal
[Music]
foreign
effects for you bye
getting certain Pokemon
it feels much like when do I go well
windbreaker wasn't so laggy
so no
because I know in the water
I mean they acknowledged it themselves
so I'll acknowledge it as well
reversal
oh
what's that oh sushi
orange Sushi you look like a famine
you look like ah
I'm excited for my hello
package to arrive tonight I'm ready to
cook some stuff
you know that pasta I cooked uh two days
ago
the the pasta noodles
they're called Malta cleati which is
left over
um pasta dough
made into pasta so they're like not
supposed to be perfect shape or whatever
but I find it ironic that they just they
don't just give me no more noodles
because it wasn't like it was actually
leftover noodles they just chose
to give me those noodles I guess for
that recipe because it's fancy I guess
it has a fancy name but then I looked it
up and I found out what is it what it's
supposed to be when you make noodles
yourself
with the leftover dough the cuts
off leftovers you make Malta gliati
but um you know how I made those for the
recipe they send lasagna sheets
soft type donut the hard ones and then I
just cut it in in my
um squares
so it's not really left over
solar beam hmm
it's not really leftover is it I just
needed something special because I guess
normal pasta wasn't good enough
but it's basically the same thing in the
end pasta is pasta more or less pasta
pasta
are you Italian photo
foreign
Austrian pronunciation of it
[Music]
I don't know although maybe it would be
nice if we could get frogzilla to fight
trying to be hipster yeah but you know
then of course I wanted to be hipster
too and I wrote Malta gliati as my tweet
and so many people were like I don't
know what that is there was even like
one just one Italian saying if I'm
Italian I don't know what that is
um
I don't know if I have anything that is
usable against electric do I are you an
Italian
[Music]
ow my neck
out
round I don't have I mean with this one
I'll try and what's my strongest
Dragon claw
[Music]
we're good we're good
need for a massage I would need a
massage every day
I wish I had oh not bad
I wish I had
free massage per day
that would be nice
[Music]
I can teach it earthquake with the balls
oh
come on
I feel like even now it's lagging the
Thunderbolt looks like it's all the
Pokemon everything looks slow to me
why is this just how things are right
now no is that normal
everything that's lagging to me
right
is it because we're close to this big
big freaking Lake
yes it's a lake not an ocean
oh God
luxury ball
anyway I already forgot what I ordered
for my recipes
but
I hope we can finish like at the latest
11 pm
so that I can do some cooking
and I have to eat my sandwich before we
read super chats I hope you guys don't
mind it's probably all soggy already
Soggy Sandwich
yeah mystery meals
also my brother brought me some stuff
from my mom some self-made
um tomato sauce for making the pasta and
some self-made jam and some self-made
pickles
and some self-made uh basil pesto
I love the best also that's very good I
appreciate the best though
everything thank you
yeah yeah she has like a [\h__\h] ton of
tomato
Tomatoes every year
what
[Music]
I thought you already
when
I don't know
but not
hahaha
[Music]
Oh wrong Pokemon [\h__\h] oh that works
though
is there no Pokemon Center around here
thank you
oh yeah
this one but now it's too far
that's weird there should be one
would be nice if there was one closer
have I explored this area before okay
I'll sleep like junkers
thank you guys
you're like so nice like oh my God
I sneeze and everybody's like because
I'm tired oh my God
unbelievable but it's like so funny
Slowpoke looks like even slower now
because of the FBS
like
snow
[Music]
wow pretty gorgeous Gorge oh my God I
know
I'm gonna pluck you
oh
perfectly kind of guessing but clock
itself is not so strong
I'm blessed
oh
[Music]
bam does she do more damage with her not
super effective attacks than I do with
my super effective attack
let's go
I need um a different flying attack for
her
at least I'm just strong
flow of gas I switch
it's a physical move oh
foreign
she's supposed to have a good flying
move even if she's not flying
all right oh you're oh well
let's go
my cute fire boobs
on top of the nose
cute
point of view of Firebird is this
[Music]
that already did more damage not
ES
[Music]
using her beak is beneath her and her
high class royalty
yeah
and then I'm not asking her to use her
beaks she can also use some attack that
uses her wings for flying
doesn't have to be pluck
[Music]
oh level 16.
there's some good levels here didn't get
to watch The Lord of the Rings watch
along yet
shouldn't have been laying there is
robots to catch up on but I will watch
it this weekend
are you
slowpoke
because even if you were late
wait do you mean
the Amazon show that we watched rings of
powers
or do you really mean Lord of the Rings
because that's over a year ago
[Music]
my dear Slavic fellow
how could you wait until now
over two years ago
[Music]
well it's about time
to watch it
go go go go
sushi
Sushi be like
[Music]
can you not
all the confessions what
you want to watch my Sound of Music
watch along oh my God
that one was fun too wow
[Music]
oh my God that was painful come on come
on come on Sparks more more power
we will switch though because we're very
very harmed
[Music]
that is as a fish
so I don't think and electrons
[Music]
what is the name of the little birdie
did I make you guys yawn too
I want to eat my sandwich
I cannot resist
maybe it will wake me up
ah sandwich time
oh I have it with salami and salad and a
piece of cheese and the pepperoni the
pepperoni
Babylon
here's the pepperonomy
could have added one more
um
I'm rearranging the placement because
I'm
very
allergic to
when stuff on a pizza or a sandwich or
anything is not placed in a balanced way
oh
shame
oh soupy was really good
I need to try making them myself
but is it the same as arancini
I will say it's allergic
was ground effective I forgot probably
not
maybe close combat
it isn't the same different ingredients
but like the concept is kind of the same
right now
oh no why is your cat hair now
wild shark or not school
thank you
[Music]
sandwich
let's go
let's go I didn't see it coming at all
oh I don't know what it's gonna look
like
[Music]
oh that's pretty cool
sick
well
that flap in the back looks kind of
annoying but
let's go it's not as cute obviously
anymore but it's not bad you know it
looks powerful
the it did have a really awkward
teenager face
Babyface was super cute then teenager
face was kind of like awkward but now
now we're talking
um
baths caliber
scally Brewing you back I was thinking
like it looks like you could like
someone stab you in the back
hahaha
can someone do him a favor and pull it
out
it looks painful
um
I was one of the last ones clay brush
[Music]
attacks from opposing Pokemon doing the
next turn cannot miss
and
head envelope like double damage
what
I would only do that if
I know it's gonna die like they are
going to die after I do this
oh you can switch it out I guess so
yeah
don't know how often I would use that
um
90 attack nothing is surviving
so what do we let go of
Charlotte if we don't take a signature
attack
um
stupid
[Music]
I wonder if we can one hit the Titan
with this
[Music]
that would be funny
probably not
yeah we need to try
but then if it doesn't then we're kind
of [\h__\h]
because if we attempt to one hit
then we have to do it in the beginning
if we want to experiment
[Music]
um
all right
did I do it
I think I did
oh there's some
other
EB
B I'm gonna go
what a Titan now
where is it
it's gonna follow my arrow
go go go go
maybe on the island oh hello
oh yeah it should be on here
[Music]
I wouldn't do an item right here
maybe not
I arrived at my destination there's so
many of these species isn't this
nah
hi Tom
wait that's not gonna work
is it just me am I imagining this
imagining this I thought at least the
last Pokemon game when the Pokemon was
paralyzed in the battle that after the
bats the paralyzation would be gone
I'll talk to this one all right
no
I thought so
I thought that was a thing
just for parallel
that's what I thought
um well
oopsie
um
and here we go with our fresh Evolution
actually perfect timing to evolve
because we were gonna use him anyway
[Laughter]
that's funny
um I was painting Wheels grow big no no
um
wait the dragon is not this one the
dragon is the small one
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
well that's a [\h__\h] bamboozle
what
oh
Paul's dragon
wow
I'm even confused so that one's online
now
oh well
please don't hit yourself please don't
please
come on yeah
good damage
also hurt myself though oh
mm-hmm
[Music]
in order to don't die
I'll go for full on this oh okay yes
because the other one was what
um
the other one would have taken myself
down as well and you wouldn't have
gotten any speed do I even got exp from
this because it's not really done
hmm Redzone
[Music]
I don't
I'll be right there I just need to check
what's going on here
Oh sushi
this iron was full of sushis
um
mm-hmm
I will heal
after this have you tried culture no
I've got two heads and try the color
donut before
elephant but I have nothing effective
ah fire okay
Fox let's go
foreign
[Music]
wanted to be talked to
okay let me heal
so am I going to fight the big one again
or the small one this time
I'm guessing it's the big one again
where did he go
ah
on the big island here
ah probably right in front of a cane
hello
how do I get up here
yo you sushi Pokemon you have to leave
the big bosses here he's gonna eat you
he's got no mercy he's hungry
he ate one of your friends already or
many of your friends
you should leave
[Music]
what why did that here it is down here
oh
right the little the little Sushi fish
[Music]
thanks for the membership welcome oh
there it goes
it goes in alone
okay whoa what did you find Titan uh
look open your freaking eyes
so that's it shows one big ooh Dragon
wait is it even a dragon or is it a cat
or a fish
it catfished us
funny Titan
I didn't expect to see the food chain in
action today
[Laughter]
baby
here we go
wait
if this now is not Dragon but water
the dragon Arenas I thought we covered
all types was there water Arena
oh
that's water
I'm so confused is he seriously coming
in here with a freaking squirrel
oh my God
useless so useless
at least all for yourself
as the scapegoat come on
[Music]
um
come on Green
oh
one HP
same outcome
don't hit yourself
[Music]
we did it
yeah yeah
damn well charged to Be Wild
I'm sorry that you have to suffer so
much
um
mama
hmm
[Music]
oh
please don't let me start those Splash
now
I was healed
all right all right all right all right
all right
[Music]
but this one is the real dragon Titan
though why does it still say false
dragon
believe in yourself have confidence
dragonfly first
go go go go go go go
[Music]
hmm
gradient is just doing nothing
oh
what was that dance
we defeated two Titans
hmm
hey
um
thank you Arvin
sorry I'm almost done with lime
um sandwich
mm-hmm
two more bites two more
Pokeball is here again
huh
all right this time it actually looks a
little bit different
mm-hmm
[Music]
spicy
spicy Urban mystical supposed to boost
your metabolism
gives you circulation a boost and helps
flush out all those toxins along with a
ton of sweat
you know what's next to Showtime
ciao
[Music]
yeah that's my face because I don't
really like spicy things
forgive me
I'll gladly give that to my bike
yes
[Music]
you're gonna have all of it
vertical surfaces
I know climb a bomb
[Music]
right this was the last Titan so
um
will he be healed
fully
um
[Music]
yeah
come on now bird eat up
it's gonna make you all better I promise
[Music]
and I we really did our best mostly
kiwawa to get this for you
gonna play with your favorite ball as
much as you want
[Music]
you know just like we use
that really sounds like something a dog
owner would say to his sick doggle
percent
[Music]
no please get better
that's all I want really I get you
oh
you just showed up with a square come
my God
hello
my booster
oh
did your best bunny no
nah
it's gonna get up right now
come on
play
that's why that was always a Pokeball
bug here
but I can't even voice like this this is
the meant I'm gonna cry
no
oh I know but me too oh
awkward
but good for you I'm good for them
[Music]
good then he's happy and energetic again
tail and I like the detail of the dude's
eyes twitching
um
foreign yo girl it's not time for this
now we're being emotional here and
you're just telling me about climbing
now we don't give a [\h__\h]
right now
hello this is Sada I thought I was
always important to you what the hell
whoa
seems that corizon has regained all of
its powers except for the power to
battle
it should now be able to climb up any
vertical surfaces it grabs onto while
you're riding opponent
uh-huh jump while facing a wall
okay
I knew you were the right one to entrust
it to entrust it too kimawa
uh listen to you like you had anything
to do with it exactly
that voice what are these brother and
sister because they got a similar hair
color are then are you there
I have been searching so long for a way
to reach you because because no one else
can get into my lab but you
what wait what is this Mom
it sounded like a like a
very spicy pickup line to me
what does he have the keys or what
excuse me
please thank you all bear to the
lighthouse the lamp on vocal fam I can't
oh my God
she doesn't explain what she just said
I will reach out once more when you
arrive there
oh
ah
laughs
he was introduced to Southern sun when I
first met him really well that's ages
ago
for that
I invited
ah you made this that yeah I know
because it's uh Sada is not in violent
um
I guess you probably already know but
that that's my mom oh thank God
oh thank God oh it's buried under her
work off pursuing her own research never
at home with me that's the first time I
even heard her voice in years you know
so mad I know what the first thing I get
is to be treated like some kind of
Aaron's boy he's so mad
[Music]
seriously it's unbelievable
but I'm guessing you and Kota I don't
probably want to go in
I'm gonna lie I feel like my blood's
boiling but
sure fine I'll get you into the lab what
else can I do
why why is he the only one what
the lab is of pokepath at the Lighthouse
where you and me first met
[Music]
come on let's get moving before I change
my mind
[Laughter]
[Music]
because he has the keys
well then don't be so surprised when
you're needed
mom where have you been all this time
and that's a good question
she's a bad mom really
abandoned him how old is he anyway
[Music]
and the mom looks too young as well to
be his mother
this dude got sideburns
and also look at that view
[Music]
ERS looking at
Fiona at the back and he's like
[\h__\h] silver
scared the [\h__\h] out of me
murder space attack
what I never saw this one
going so fast everyone wants to block my
view from the Beauty in the back what
the hell
may I please catch this gorgeous
Gorgeous Beauty oh the babies are so
cute
[Music]
oh wait did I catch it already
I didn't okay
um
how to not
Maybe
or metal claw
the stick even work in the water
let me dig
don't suffocate again
is that me
oh no
well
interesting that that works
safeguard
what does that do does my next attack
not work
I don't know I did that all right it's
time to
[Music]
is that even water it's not water though
is it water
water maybe I'll just uh I just do the
dive ball
Dragon right so time for all the better
option right now
beautiful and popular Pokemon
[Music]
your tongue
pretty dragon girl but we're not gonna
use Dragonair because we already have a
dragon Pokemon that is
um
pretty good I think Dragon Eyes
hovering two types that we need
nice so nice to nasu
don't you dare don't you dare charge at
me like that again
and I called it speeding police
[Applause]
so many feathers here
wow
okay so I guess next is poco pap
we gotta try out the climbing oh I fell
down there so how about we climb back
out remember when I fell down
that was painful
but probably not as painful as when you
guys fell down from the heaven
and there we go
[Music]
yeah that bridge what the [\h__\h]
oh this one's tough maybe it's better
without the mount
I got it
why am I so excited
excited
okay
so I think this way
we need to explore
hello
yellow area is that like an Autumn area
over there
must be happy for urban yeah no that's
a really really nice story ending for
him not quite ended yet I suppose but
the dog always
um all back to its original Glory again
so that was a sweet story you really
want a sweet
what
the Minecraft Pokemon has either a
different form
or another evolution
[Music]
yes does it have
four
looks
the little Stone
and then three evolutions
does that feel like this is the the
fourth one I saw of it
no two of those okay I mean three would
have been insane
you cannot tell me that that's not
freaking Minecraft inspired
I will never believe
look at it
literally Minecraft
I could totally see that as an enemy
I might think different Pokemon nah
for legal reasons no it is
okay okay yes
um
everything I said I take back
uh it's joke
I have a lawyer
as well
lawyer versus loyal
lawyer resists lawyer attacks
what's effective against lawyer
oh pretty snack hi so pretty
it's moving
face looks like smoothly
wow so many pretty boys and girls cute
foreign
at me
oh
okay
it went
oh yeah
[Music]
oh
Nani
whoa
have fun I've been here before
oh
it's connected to that yellow area
Trail
running
[Music]
okay you got the don't hurt yourself
what kind of Pokemon do we have here oh
it's so funny new one
I want fun
it looks so stupid and Derpy but I like
it
big tree
hmm
how is all of this super effective oh my
God
foreign
[Music]
he's [\h__\h] laughing
it's the matter with him
that hurt
you're dying
take the gigas on Hammer
counter
oh Trans physical tag was twice what the
freak damn
crunch
you mean
you mean like
um
[Music]
hmm
Stone
[Music]
um
I like this golden look that this area
has it's quite pretty
quite aesthetic
um there's probably nothing here for me
really right now oh Blitz out
but we got time so why not explore a
little bit
[Music]
sleep talk Kawaii Mori
bunk
oh
it's the bottom
should I try it
um
oh you guys really like this one yeah
get Carefree to have what you wanted
four star might be hard and last time we
only really failed a four star because I
didn't have a fitting Pokemon to fight
itself
Casper's with population bomb I don't
think I have population bomb
oh
um no no
it's fighting
I should have learned it
okay
then uses fellows gather
fellows
in droves to perform a combo attack that
hits the target one to ten times in a
row
okay
with the loaded dice
[Applause]
it's busted really
um
yeah no one can ask you guys to help but
then I have to go online on them
it will be 10 heads a hit
then let's get rid of double heads I
guess let's see oh my God damn it
foreign
[Music]
sorry sometimes I have those streams
where I just eat so much
but if I eat during my long streams
no
does that even work
I mean if you can try to join there you
go try I don't think it would
I don't think I'm online
but why doesn't you tell me I'm offline
um oh it's a local code
no wait will the Pokemon be gone though
no no okay I'm good
mm-hmm
that it does
no I'm out of roasted almonds
and sandwich is gone too
wait can I can I
um
well this will be a problem
[Music]
I can run but can I challenge it again
it won't disappear
okay okay
the battle is the same as losing the
battle duh
did that really just say that
what do you think that I was thinking
that would be
um
um okay
[Music]
yeah I am and I'm so mixed up with what
buttons to push
oh
yeah
I do have this sometimes when I play
different
um kind of
games
in a week
oh yeah I mean those Pokemon look a bit
better than what we had before but I
don't know if they're more helpful
anyway so do I just
win just population bomb it
I terrestrialized oh I can't yet oh yeah
right okay yeah yeah okay
[Music]
one
two three
four
it doesn't even have an animation and
that was only five times what the [\h__\h]
that didn't do so much damage
[Music]
paralyzed
my playwrap is super effective guys
[Music]
oh wide lens
do I have them also I want to see how
much damage this one does
it burn who did that good job
well that wasn't so bad
[Music]
I think this one we can win
foreign
Oh I
thought I did
paralyzation what's up
let me see let me see
oh that does more damage
foreign
[Music]
do I have to
let's see population bomb one more time
I I'm
it doesn't hit eight times but it still
looks like it might have done more at
least more than when they did five times
[Music]
thank you
so stupid
come on
[Music]
nails
at least I won't be paralyzed anymore
yeah
and now let's stop messing around all
right
I'm playing Rap now not being kind
anymore where's the damage
huh
foreign
okay it's broken now right
[Music]
I ain't got the last hit
hey hey it was really close
but we managed in the end and I get the
auto
are you good
is that normal
is it okay
it's normal
he's just quirky
he's bugging
as electric devices like to do sometimes
[Music]
no I don't want to pick a pretty one up
you want to pick a cheap one
I have seven Mansions where are they
coming from
uh-huh
foreign
huh
okay yay
it's busy time
what's the answer to the stream title I
score
don't
it's electricity like body can enter
some kinds of machines and take control
in order to make mistake
and as a ghost I forgot it was Ghost as
well
but you're not getting into the team it
was nice catching you though
only
if only if only
[Music]
all right how my Pokemon doing
let's try the caspers why not
by the way oh I feel like I checked the
time
15 20 minutes ago and that was at three
hours now I am at five hours
how did that happen
10 more minutes until five hours
[Music]
uh
wait what um we can go to that Poco
place
and then I guess end it
and then next time
we do the last
um
the last base count
and
the champ stuff whatever
[Music]
um
what level are the what levels
recommended for the Champs Elite Four
if I can if I find time I can do some
um leveling grinding off screens
number 65 at least okay I'm not so far
from that
all right no no 61 the rest yeah needs
to be leveled a little bit whoa
is that shiny
wow
come on
it's stuck evolution
you funny you think you
think you need
I love Thor Arts they're so funny
they're really entertaining me in this
game
oh that killed you oh I would have
caught you
I don't remember
I don't remember the
um
other previous Pokemon games
having so many or any Zoro accidental I
don't remember like coming across one
I'm gonna get this one
because it's ghost and I already have
my ghost giveaway although that might
hurt a lot as well as in exchange but
hopefully I'll do a lot of damage
[Music]
looks funny
very strong Rock and dark type normally
[Music]
well it's not using Ghost Attacks I
guess it doesn't have a ghost attack
in its smooth set even though
out
coastalized
that's good
very good
[Music]
this one's pretty easy
it's got its Shield up front I could not
correct the wires yet anyway
my help oh here I go
[Music]
Carrot Top is more random
you can cast for changing I'm Gonna
Change cats but probably for the next
episode I don't know what but I'll think
a little bit about which Pokemon could
be helpful what coverage we need
hmm
yeah
wait I peristalized into fire oh well
water coverage well in case of water we
already have some choices
I wanted the dolphin maybe I can try to
evolve the dolphin I know you have to
play like online for that
is there no evolved dolphin in the wild
foreign
has a really strong move
[Music]
so in general very strong
in raids above dolphin
[Music]
why not use on fire there we go
beautiful
foreign
[Music]
Godzilla later on because it more looks
like it will turn into a beautiful
butterfly
[Music]
I probably have things before I just
don't remember right now
what it looked like
[Music]
what well
so many XP candies
never looked at how many you actually
get to know us
it can be a beautiful butterfly if it
wants to be of course of course anyone
can be
don't let your dreams be dreams
this Papa flies around wildly by vending
with great force the gas pressurized
inside its body
[Music]
looks so I'm angry it looks like it
wants to
be released
all right
and
ah
I don't know if I should
destroys area
um even more on stream
there's nothing here right now I wonder
if this also has something else
later on like that muddy area
oh
well yes it has
that's what only the second door that
I've seen so far of those
I thought there would be more but then I
until now I only saw one
answers my question yeah
four
how come I miss
maybe the money area does have one of
those doors and I just didn't see it
because it's seemingly in areas that
don't have anything else in terms of
like a gym or
um a camp
very easy to miss
I think so too
ah I didn't have all the options
there's a Pokeball on the wall
I
[Music]
am
hyper hyper
[Music]
just gonna roughly go through here
a bit more
pretty tucked away
one is literally hidden out of view
unless you climb around what
well then give you hints though when
it's necessary to find them where they
are
and all this one will be here will they
mark it on my map perhaps like they
marked it marked it marked Mark marks
everything else
solo pop I'm in the mood for summer I'm
on it
I feel the sprinkles okay okay good
reason for me to do that
helpful
no I just want normal flavor basic
flavor Ramen
I know there's others
but I like the classic one very much
well now we already know one of those
locations so that's useful for
the future
next time
but I although some
um
we call them
the things that we're sticking
in the ground that you can
pull out
I have barely seen those and I'm pretty
sure there's a lot more
ah eight for each door damn
yeah
if I also get
advice where those are that would be
very nice of the game because those are
even more difficult to find in my
opinion than the big doors
no
I'm going to unlock all code I don't
want to build it first well I mean if
you find some on the way obviously why
would you not
why would you not try to get them
[Music]
I ah and I already got rid of the other
steel attack
oh my track got debuffed again
oh my God and again
well now this should be enough though
yeah I put Baker in again and but I
didn't use it
super effective
[Music]
Natalia the student
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I wonder if there was something else I
wanted to talk about
but in terms of yesterday I think I
told you pretty much
everything
[Music]
I was just hanging with my brother a
little bit but
yeah
and my my cat got hurt and
I play Tales of her eyes it was a nice
day yesterday I was so tired all day
and I still can't sleep early even when
I'm tired
for junkers upcoming streams
[Music]
um
well tomorrow is ring fit
I am so looking forward to that
it's just in a bit of a bother to set up
the 3D stuff
and then I just do it to make myself
suffer of sports
why why
I don't think we can do any exercises
that are like in seated position though
I think because
that motion capture it doesn't really
recognize when you're sitting
on the floor
it's kind of difficult
so we gotta do things that are possible
to do that in in standing position
yeah well I think there's plenty
what
let me up oh there's nothing there never
mind
we don't use hard monitor yeah no
there's already so much stuff on my body
when I do 3D
so
I would try not to oh look at that
there's the the plant plant ones
somewhere here
wow
I wouldn't mind catching her if I see
her lipion
she's cute to like her design too
hey we don't have a plant Pokemon delay
a plant water pokemon would actually
makes sense no
I don't think we have planned all water
at the moment why what's the plan what
I'm sure there's at least one plant
water Pokemon
um no Tad no idea which one that is
see
Colo
which one is not in the game
yeah I mean oh it's so cool
Iris came up with that name I think I
already said that the first time I saw
this Pokemon
I was so cool
oh
gotcha
can't hide from me
all right I didn't see the Leafeon but
[Music]
um
teleport to Poco
path now
Serena and arboliva okay that also means
nothing to me
so right here and the lighthouse let's
see
honey
I can't click the flying icon but we
have to go from here
yeah we're doing it I don't know is that
long
hopefully not too long
okay
story time
ah
that's not here
it's an item
a Pokemon oh
another one here
a potion
finding all those weak ass items now
what have I ever been over there
apparently not
after I learned how to swim I checked
out a different area uh close by
it's motion mentioned and this was a
potion mansion
don't mention motion now
we have someone who's called potion in
here
an emotion Mansion now yes motion
mentioned now
[Music]
thanks for watching
oh yeah write the frame
why is it free looking good
am I supposed to go up
oh that door can open
what no
nevermind
oh
wow
you gotta exercise with me you're gonna
be at the gym you go to the gym noise
all right um you will probably
have way more stamina than me
I'll only be able to do it for maximum
half an hour probably and then in
between some breaks or so but I active
workouts maybe half an hour
actually it's a really old ring foot
that I got
like three years ago or so no maybe not
three years
[Music]
for years
uh I got it when I started Living in
Japan you know during that one year and
I realized I'm
not moving my body much and I don't know
this ring fit game actually looks like
it would be fun and motivating to work
out
and I
was more fun to work out than do normal
workouts
and I didn't like
maybe I used it maybe like three or four
times
[Laughter]
but I still have the game I actually
have a physical copy of that so that's a
game I still have the ring
so it should still work just fine
it also has some stretching exercises so
that's cool too
yes there is no digital because you need
the Ringo true
what if I lose the
the card though
then I'm kind of [\h__\h] I think it's
still in there probably
seriously you beat me here
well I can fly on my Horizon
well this is the lab I used to come here
to play all the time when I was a kid
there would better be a good reason for
calling us here like this
let's find out
everyone always says she's some kind of
Genius
absolutely brilliant as a Pokemon
professor my mom that is but let me tell
you as a parent
she's the worst
[Music]
all she ever does is work she never
comes home
I don't have a single memory of her ever
even playing with me her own kid
my boss that was the only one who was
there for me always
standable
anyway it's open now go in
I just want to get this over with
and where is she
was she locked up inside
what
oh no one's been in here for a while
it's quite Dusty
damn
oh
the spooky [\h__\h] why
I need your help
you good
I'm currently at the deepest point of
area at zero in the great creator of
paldea
oh
I have been researching the unique
Pokemon here for a very long time I'm
asking the two of you to land a hand to
help carry out the final step of the
great Professor status glorious research
so hot
final step
but there's some but there's something
we need first something that can be
found within the lab
what we need is the Scarlet book
[Music]
wait do you mean this book
ah so you took it from the lab that you
haven't
this expedites things bring the Scarlet
book to the deepest depths of area zero
I promise that it will be an experience
worth treasuring if you come
I wasn't allowed to go
I must note however that area zero is
both home to vicious Pokemon an outfit
with powerful cybernetic security
systems
it seems to me that you might struggle
if the two of you were to enter Alone
um
who am I supposed to bring may take the
time to gather some reliable allies
before you come if you feel the need do
you meet Pokemon
I will be waiting you awaiting you in
the deepest part of area zero whenever
you arrive
oh
no no
area zero
now plays bad news I was down an area
zero when marble stiff got wounded in
the first place down in the great Crater
of fall there
in all honesty I had perfect I would be
perfectly happy to never see that place
again
are you gonna go
what toys do I have we might find our
treasure
oh treasure huh yeah I suppose that was
the assignment we were given
and I can't just stand by and watch
while a friend heads off into Danger on
her own
so I guess I'm going to
besides I'd love to give Mom a piece of
my mind
just wow cute he's got quite the courage
to do that all right thank you well
outside we're gonna have a Pokemon
battle receiver really yeah okay
most you see if I'm ready or not let's
go yeah I agree that's more about if you
already know if I'm ready
that is
[Music]
make my wish come true
it's going to stop you
he's really strong I would wait oh
okay if you say that
should I go to the fighting arena first
then would that be the better order
or even even the before
uh Champs or whatever as well first
[Music]
I beat them around this level but now if
you think them
if you're staying at the actual order is
different actual order as in the
recommended level
then
save and try
okay that would be so embarrassing if I
die
um
[Music]
well
I could replace
something still
we've got so many water options
now okay I'm I'm gonna keep this I guess
let's see what happens
finish the latest on the stream oh
ideally
oopsie
but I mean we're right here so I guess
let's try
it
um
[Music]
foreign
I don't want to be killed
imagine how cool you look if you win
um
excellent you're ready too right by
buses
[Music]
well that smile is kind of scary I was
just gonna say I don't want to fight
this cutie patooty
what's a smile belly with mobile stuff
okay yeah I can see why you'll be
worried and maybe don't use them but my
body here is bursting with energy you'd
never know he was so weak just a little
while ago
okay
[Music]
special laws I nearly forgot but he
always did love to battle even if I was
always lost to that student council girl
girl the Battle of fanatic one
all right let's do this who are you
gonna start off with the toku
yeah bye
we're brand new or even in my bookstiff
and we're filling all dashes or maybe
her bashes
let me give you a taste of what we can
do
[Music]
okay
[\h__\h] squirrel all right the squirrel
is no problem unless
the Pokemon that I met during our hunt
for the urban mystical are all stars
every one of them
is okay level wise it's okay
um one question
if I up my special attack and then
switch myself out does it get reset
I think it does
but anyway we start with fourth song
anyway I don't want to switch out
just yet
let's see how far we get oh
this should kill though
um
he's gone
one down
another Minecraft Pokemon isn't that
ground as well
but well try to sleep I'll try to sleep
oh it's not not effective at all oh
but this also uses a special attack so
Shadow Ball is Bob's too
what uh what do I have man
come on come on come on
okay at least it's not like
I mean I prefer that
over an actual
attack
[Music]
Chris Chris please
no but okay one more I
but I attack first
[Music]
next I heal
or a switch if it's really bad
cold
[Music]
oh that's
all it's so cool turned into Toad's
cruel and look
ground grass okay
[Music]
but I need to heal
give me a Max potion please use some
soft buff or something [\h__\h] yourself
do something but don't attack me earth
power
wow [\h__\h]
he was a critical are you kidding me
[Music]
uh is my fire effective
should I heal again
no
I don't know I'll go please please let
me okay I attack first
[Music]
whoa Cloister
the world is my Cloister is that water
well then we might be [\h__\h]
I'll stay anyway
[Music]
Water Ice
I mean fire is good against ice
but water
oh that might not be good
am I fat my factor maybe I can
I can still attack with a Shadow Ball at
least first or flamethrower I wonder
what's better fire is neutral
and and goes
oh damn true okay
might be my last one with Sparks but
we've been sweeping quite nicely so
let's hope for the best
oh
my God
we're
[Music]
this one is plant fire now
again
um
we will just
I hope I'm faster again
[Music]
it's more proud to play
throw it throw him
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
oh I mean not most of my just hurt me
we'll see it looks like a very slow
Pokemon though intimidate my attack fail
that I used special attack so that's
okay
well guys so we're safe I'm still on my
first one
let's celebrate your full recovery with
a glue up time to write to Russell is my
birthday into what
what type is he gonna use
[Music]
that
dark
[Music]
yikes
you're dead
don't underestimate my Sparks oh he goes
first okay never mind
[Music]
can't be helped
oh man sparkly deserves to eat Speedo I
want to revive them
I forgot once again what's good against
dark
fight
okay I hope we can waste uh one round to
revive Sparks
I don't want the ESP
so you think you can do that
[Music]
I want please provide
it's your neck
[Music]
ah
right here
[Music]
you want to say yeah
but okay it's good groundwork it's good
groundwork takuma thank you I guess
you're not getting Speedo because I'm
not gonna do that again I don't think I
can afford to
um
it's just one small hit
let's go is ETC or so I don't care
it's got a lot of exp so uh HP I'm just
hoping that she will survive one hit if
she gets hit first
immune
oh no oh no oh no
[Laughter]
oh no
I don't remember that kind of [\h__\h] guys
of course I don't remember
um
okay well we did it I mean it wasn't
necessary it was not necessary to have
um
my burp dye
That's my kind of I guess also not if I
you know didn't revive
but it wasn't as bad as I expected
because you guys were all like he's too
strong he's too strong
that was Sparks did huge groundwork
hmm
damn this is the strength of someone who
could take down those Titan Pokemon
yo but I think you're ready to go too
no we've been good
I'll just say to admit it I do think
we're gonna need some more support
the Pokemon in there right there are
super strong and there are all sorts of
weird machines they're two machines
say we need at least two more people
somebody with some Champion rank level
skills and somebody who can deal with
crazy Tech
okay so nemona and
maybe the shy girl
oh yeah
this is a triangle Penny oh the student
council girl
the way you ask you asked for those very
specific types of people you should have
known it would be pneumona
[Laughter]
uh should be perfect for the job but I
doubt she'd give us a time of day unless
one of us was on her level as a champion
rank level oh don't worry I'll get there
well we've got to do what we've got to
do whoever you think could be up just
try getting in good with them we'll see
if we can if we can't get a team
together get in touch if you make
progress I'll do the same
path of Legends complete
oh so the Titan one is considered
complete now or what
is that the path of Legends
I'm absolutely wrecked let me go to the
Pokemon Center
hey that's an accomplishment
what
oh hey I'm Healed I never battled you
Nani
this is the nail that I forgot
I mentioned at some point back then that
I feel like I missed a child
this is the missing child I have come
back to retrieve the missing child
I'm so sorry level five push up
I'm so sorry
I'm sorry
oh man
at least I retrieved the missing child
that's more important I will bring it
back to its family
okay hmm honestly the
fighting Camp itself
all those camps normally don't take so
much time so I feel like we could
squeeze it in
and then for next time we just have some
story and the the big four and all that
but what do you think
is that better
if I squeeze the fighting one in as well
yeah I don't think it would take too
long
are they on my level or am I on their
level
better question
um
[Music]
foreign
fighting type
everybody tell me what's um
what's effective but it should be easy
if you beat Arvin
a psychic
all right Zuckerberg
she's getting some action again she
never got a name by the way
I want to keep name
[Music]
psychic Flying Fairy all right we got a
lot of choice
um
verb
it's just pronounced verb
verb literally German verb
simple but effective
yeah b-i-r-b is basically pronounced
verb with uh in German
y
um
cut off
you can't jump into this
dark blue all of this is not enough
well that's a big area why
why is it this weird cut off though
everywhere else is accessible I just
noticed that now
ah do you see ah that makes more sense
okay
oh
wait where am I
can't this
I'm so stop stop it I cannot control
switch anymore I can't but we can climb
up there right
well look at those planktons
oh we're coming back oh
so many so many
[Music]
that sounds like a good poison attack
Firestone Round blonde
[Music]
oh the stone
Polka Doll
[Music]
s
okay
oh one more
no I wanna hmm
there we go revive
all right here we go
wait
hey
oh it's up so high
down
[Music]
fighter
I hear like
Asian music traditional
what
Pokemon
I'm on the top of the
top of the world
oh there's the there's the camp
I can't open the map
yes
what is this secret place
all the access to all the secret places
now
[Music]
yo the music is beautiful here
this is traditional Spanish or we had
the world yet Honestly though what
that's not as shiny is it isn't it shiny
why would it be
you know what I'll catch you
[Music]
that's a big okay I don't have the
patience for that no
no no no no no no no no no no patience
ain't nobody got time for that
that
yo what happened to your climbing skills
is the texture broken on this one
that one too
aren't you supposed to be like that
maybe it's supposed to be like that I
guess it's supposed to be like that look
at all the other ones
looked broken to me
I think
you know like a raping sounding music
I guess that still made somewhat sense
over there
after hearing everybody's explanations
this
I mean I'm enjoying it
it adds to the variety I guess
you can't
I'll see why when I get in there uh-huh
where the hell am I and where am I
heading to oh
[Music]
oh there's a stick
yay
one less to find later on
yay remember this one so we don't look
for it if we use a guide or so
if we end up having to use a guide
where's that thing I heard it
oh is there two why is it true so close
to one another
it's kinda
excuse me may I
okay
what do you want
I don't know
I better not try
well they ran like Naruto
[Music]
where the hell am I
time to check
I'm getting there
[Music]
Oh I thought I saw something shiny there
oh it's just that
[Music]
well
there's a trainer
when he's wearing clothes like that is
he gonna use fighting time
Sasuke he's really cool Sakura the
Beautiful
[Music]
I don't know
I think or Rock oh
hello
poison dark
and poison fighting because you guys
don't fight him
and
it wasn't fighting I don't know if this
is effective but let's give it a try
oh it is
nice
let's go worth it oh
look it's movie swimming over there it's
literally smoothie because I named this
movie
my own one holds movie
[Music]
times
I've got the perfect Pokemon out here to
deal with them
gallate don't know don't care
fighting plants or fighting bug or
fighting something
now you fight me oh
that was psychic
so psychic doesn't really do much
opportunist what
is your skin like doing the same things
as the opponent in terms of
Buffs
okay long
come on
[Music]
ah nice that was super effective I was
hoping for it
didn't think it would be that good
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
we're hanging out so cute
getting along well
oh my God
it's kind of ruined the mood it was good
oh
[Music]
Big Shiny boy
sorry are you mad because of when I said
are they listening to my stream
Go goat go go go away go go go go
what the [\h__\h]
unbelievable
what
how much only a bit okay
I don't think I caught one before so I'm
actually gonna try but just with a great
ball not gonna bless you with anything
better than that
yeah pluck very weak oh it works at work
though that worked
the goatee it's princess hours no
wait 10 minutes ago I was almost at five
hours
how is it now five forty seven
what the [\h__\h]
how does this happen
what oh look this is awful
minutes oh it's right there
oh hello let me enter please
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] am I supposed to enter
through
yeah yeah yeah yeah
I don't like it when you enter from the
Sun I don't know
shut up
where is the entrance
um
I don't want to jump in you know I don't
want to
what
[Music]
don't gotta hide
let me get a good view from above
uh
I think that's the entrance
no no please don't tell me I I intruded
and I didn't
oh it's supposed to be here that's good
that's good
oh
I see you almost start at the fifth base
old up inside there's teams does last
remaining Squad you fought well to make
it this far oh thank you baba
uh
no need
so you made it as well
so you made it as well Cliff of course
it's a lot of space I wouldn't want to
miss out on the action
Club
I owe your mouth
your help has been invaluable to the
operation I'm sorry I was so very of
your first
well that's what a lot under the bridge
but we're finished with this space will
that be the end of operation Starfall
not quite we still need to handle
Teamsters secret Mastermind last of all
is that you Casio pail
I'm hoping they'll come out into the
open once all the squad bosses have
stepped down also I seem to have some
kind of schizophrenia
because I don't realize it's actually me
we've come so far only a few more steps
left don't let me down either of you
ah
that's your beers on the floor defensive
slowly but surely come to understand
team stock
hmm
well
maybe that's why they don't have voice
acting
I know what I need to do and I know what
my final decision will be
for that I can't thank you enough take
care in that base sorry for getting all
polite there I don't know what the
capable of me
well nature
okay oh she's right out there and Clive
too
that [\h__\h] chilling oh what was that
slide
wow beautiful transformations
[Music]
so is there actually a place like this
in Spain
[Music]
I don't know
I mean bamboo also
also is able to
thrive
in a lot of unexpected places I I see
that
classic bamboo forest in Spain
I'm from Savannah I don't think so
hmm
[Music]
obviously
I mean it can even thrive in Minecraft
so who knows
[Music]
shouldn't have healed my verb
if I was gonna come here anyway
thanks please thank you
you'll probably only one or zero
one
okay
well well well I don't want to waste so
much time so I'm gonna ignore that
trainer and go straight in uh but wait
we said
um a fairy and psychic
and Ice was it
right
yes not eyes oopsie
they're flying psychic
and Sparks okay Sparks is a type now
let's see
flying psychic and pay okay
but very strong type
you're pretty skilled not many trainers
can shrug my Pokemon's attacks like that
the same to you very much have clearly
spent a lot of time holding the moves
but I'm surprised to find the post
yourself out here defending the gates
with that face paint looks
and with that outfit in general looks
like um what is it like kiss or
what's that group called
[Music]
dead
that's right yeah
funny
and also honestly
could just literally be how a female
wrestler shows up as a wrestle match
[Music]
just like that in Japan specifically
could also be from a wrestling themed
Idol group because there's literally a
theme an item group of any female out
there
so yeah
don't trust your Grant enough to put
them on guard Duty
what's your mouth I'm here because I
don't want to risk anyone else getting
hurt that's all
on a benevolent bus now if you want to
get on with our bedroom already on my
side
let's look
oh that's the same as interrupting we're
saying something who are you
hello there you are I started talking to
this girl since you looked like she was
a team star then she knew Pokemon came
at me without warning we're just
battling
Lily I know you'd be here who who
oh Grand
come in
are you okay you're not hurt are you I'm
fine honestly now get away from here
it's not safe
no I won't lay down I can't
oh Danny I need to stop doing this
until the big boss comes back I have to
protect all of you in a calf squid squid
and everyone else in team started
[Music]
as a box of Discord I just can't
you please let me friends listen to what
I'm saying
fine I'll go
ah I'm not coming hey
[Music]
time your opponent now you two come on
I'll take you both down
Clive
[\h__\h] off already
yeah yeah yeah yeah of course I can
handle them alone I never expected you
to help me anyway
everything I have
feels so ready
Clive what a jerk
oh man
[Music]
frick
should have started with the bird
no burp spell burp go back up
[Music]
laughs
hey
banger
oh
double shark what is double shock
[Music]
can we replace wild charge
wait what after using this move the user
will no longer be a lecture time
oh it discharges all the electricity uh
oh
I mean for certain moments it might be
useful
[Music]
and maybe even metal claw
because we already have something
someone else that covers metal
it could be useful
oh no see let's see
[Music]
interesting attack though making an
electric Pokemon get rid of its electric
type by using an electric move
cool
okay
[Music]
that's fine my job is done I literally
did nothing but okay bye-bye
now okay you're good you're good you
wanted to help out your boss
that's good
I take it you defeated front
that base is run by Teamsters fighting
crew the Cavs Court the robot series is
skilled Esther and coaches the old team
star in Pokemon battling Of All Bosses
she'll likely be the most alert to
hostilities after our declaration of war
she might try to stop this red in its
tracks by challenging you to battle
before anyone else
huh
oh yeah yeah
I know it tell me what happened
uh I can't speak so she irritated we're
talking about the same area right well
it seems there's nothing for it now but
to attack the base add-on ring the bell
on the gates until ready to kick off the
space of operation
let's go
okay
oh
challenge
let's go
last thing for today and then we really
did look
everything
more than I thought I would do today
damn
yeah
but then next time we'll definitely
finish
and
maybe I can even start an hour or so
later considering a feeling it must not
be
that much left maybe three hours maximum
of gameplay
no it's not lagging yet
pretty decent right now
more
oh man okay
let's start a little bit later but um
they have a nice place for their Camp
you know
attack where my Pokemon what
[Music]
was hanging on to
their dear life
grasping onto it
[Music]
how many more is there anything left
here oh
nice
nice good job good job
[Music]
oh wait you guys get barks until
Halloween
because it's a electric Pokemon
oh well spots is doing fine hey that
guy's doing fine how much in my head
right now is the same thing
I can't change it now
but it works guys
[Music]
wait why did I call my main Pokemon
Sparks
in the beginning it didn't even have the
burp
how did I think Sparks would be sitting
there's a fire okay I guess fire Sparks
well
that's a stretch past kiwawa
that is quite the stretch
[Music]
oh
Tech sets blacks oh okay well well that
gives me good reason yeah yeah Pokedex
okay
boss fight
it's kind of
funny
[Music]
doesn't matter who you are bury anyone
who tries to take down team staff this
time I won't run away
[Music]
he only uses field balls oh that's a
cute detail
oh cute I don't know the look of that
would fit more to someone who uses
poison or fairy
looking at that ball
[Music]
ah why did I have her out front
his face is fresh it's still outside
won't let the spray WS go any further
[Music]
look at that burp number one
get more
girly girl
no
well
I give as good as I get that's a promise
we'll see who's left standing in the end
okay chill chill
holy [\h__\h]
it's got something super effective
oh well
not anymore
now I wonder if I should heal
at least I have a little a little bit of
shell Bell Lucario
if I switch
[Music]
should I switch to bunk
is Tacoma
[Music]
Lucario
still fighting
[Music]
oh so
well chops
[Music]
oh
it's the fun
all right then we kept some trouble from
the bub
we got a little bit of rest in the back
has Simeon what is that
what is that I never heard of it
[Music]
here's Bob
okay we can we're probably faster are we
there are we though
[Music]
oh I was making up a different monkey oh
well I think I'm faster than that one
[Music]
come on come on
I'll terrestrialized
foreign
[Music]
faster
and I want him
coffee
[Music]
Annihilation funky is that what you're
saying
what a name oh my name
I'm staying in
what
is that a regional forum
from the mannequin
holy [\h__\h] that
Pokemon needs a break
it's an evolution oh but it is new okay
well it definitely looks like it needs a
break
oh
it does not look happy
I stayed alive
but I keep on healing myself up with the
Bell nice
okay chill oh rage fizz
[Music]
foreign
girls
oh oh
[Music]
anyway
why are you feeling feisty bucks on
Ellie oh
[Music]
now you have to give them to me because
I want I saw that I I refuse to lose oh
wait it's not one yet
[Music]
la la
the defense Rose
[Music]
shift gear oh at least it's not an
attack I think no
speed Rose we are already faster so
attack Rose oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
I don't think else
survive the next if I might not survive
yeah
holy macaroni
oh
good try good try
caspers
do you want to try cats first
hmm
[Music]
Sparks
okay
[Music]
our safe Choice 200 hp you can't bring
me down
[Music]
oh maybe you can
how much does that do
oh
she's not even
that does more than the super effective
fairy attack then
all right
let's let's finish this
let's finish this
very tanky
damn good fight though
with the car at least
but
you kind of cheated I know you brought
this car to MTV Pimp My Ride with
exhibit
it's not fair
I'm so sorry everyone
shh
about a year and a half ago
I'm so sorry I think I went a little too
far
nah don't worry about it we're the ones
who asked you to put us through some
tough battle practice so we can train up
yeah but
you need not to apologize my lady thanks
to dice age instruction I am making
sweet strides towards mastering the art
of battle
and I could never have evolved my
Pokemon without you already
even a big boss said it's thanks to you
that we have a fighting chance against
our bullies
saying nothing but gratitude to assure
the British star and the whole team
come on quit being silly
um just one thing we've been training
for four whole hours now I'm totally
exhausted
ah I'm sorry you all really should take
a break I'll go for a run while you rest
up
my lady wherefore have each trained in
our turn but you our steadfast Mentor
have breasted not once I cannot help but
worry would I help
thank you for your concerned articles
but lady I feel like I can take anything
even if I'm really tired of villa crying
remember that time we all got together
and ripped on the gym badge designs to
create our baby owned star patches well
I don't know what it is but just looking
at my Starbucks makes me feel so sad
like I want to go no
I gave my all but it wasn't enough it
wasn't enough
you showed amazing strength even if the
code didn't require me to give this to
you I wanted to have this
[Music]
could it be another reference
is this game basically just a bad hole
alive
but she's my sampling
I like to sing you try out my trademark
move too here this one's for you
the close Club I already have that
thanks though
ah next time we did that so much done
today again I know you're part of
operation staffer but I could tell from
my battle that you're not a bad person
the way your Pokemon look at you with
such trust gives it away
do me a favor and look away for a moment
this is a bit much for me to take I just
really
oh
she's she has a sweet sensitive heart
that's like it's all over
honey
this is the team start remember your
battle at the gates earlier I asked her
to come along for a talk
why'd you have to bring her she has a
terrible voice
you seem to be on much friendly in terms
of value compared to the other grunts
why is that foreign
[Music]
wears off they look for something new
the next Target and started bullying me
instead I guess I deserved it but then
Lily she chose to help me even though
Atkins horrible to her she told me that
she understood how hard it is to have no
one on your side
she invited me to team stuff
you're [\h__\h] late I'm about to end it
you can listen to the Super Chat reading
as a punishment
even after you build your like that what
kind of girl
she really is and joining the team has
worked out great for us it's been so
much fun
their room is a team star likewise
engages in bullying
after hearing my story do you really
think that's true
[Music]
oh no I merely
the rest of the team made me who I am
today really on the restroom
please don't take away our greatest
treasure oh she's crying at the back yo
girl
she needs a hug
hmm
[Music]
aggressive stretch
foreign what is it French lady
[Music]
did you do it did you claim every
Stockbridge
without its pose the Cup squad should be
Earth's breath from this bending
so Eddie was the last
all five Squad bosses have now been
topped from their pedestals I imagine
they lived himself before long now that
they've lost their special positions
after that they should soon be back
attending classes at the Academy
[Music]
foreign
thanks
well that reminds me I'm doing the whole
Supply you know the rap thing this time
right
indeed you can go ahead oh where's the
little girl
[Music]
at long last operation Starfall has
entered its final stage there's only one
thing left on the agenda
you must defeat the big boss and have
Team star this band for good
where is Big Boss don't worry there's no
need to search them out
oh
the true identity of the boss
no
I said that's what I said
he's got schizophrenia or something
hahaha
I had a feeling but even not even today
also last time for a moment wasn't I
saying something like it could be her
but then it makes no sense that she
talks about the boss as if it wasn't her
but it does seem like it could be her
[Music]
beginning but then she makes you doubt
it because she always or he talks about
themselves
like a different person
the gospel
I'm sorry I didn't mean to keep it from
you for so long but yeah why do you want
to battle you huh that makes no sense
I'm the one who formed team star and
back then the members of the team were
my closest friends and I treasured them
more than anything if they go on like
these teams that I won't do any good for
anyone they've got to give it up so I'm
using the code we made together to force
them to disband
I'll be waiting for you in the school
year after Dark
you should come as well Clive
spicy
then I'll see you above those
oh
interesting I was the big boss of Team
star wow look us but this Revelation I
just might have an inkling as to their
true identity
since we'll find our answers after dark
in the Academy school year that's let's
prepare as best as we can before heading
over bye uh
I kind of want to do it now but now we
have to we should we should end it
here
[Music]
and read super chattels
the plot chickens
no
my Suzuki
[Music]
on Friday it is finally time
you are all welcome
to come for the finale again
and tell me what Pokemon to use against
what Pokemon
[Laughter]
what attack to use as well while you're
in
so
a save here and a save there here safe
they're safe everywhere assistant
huh
need water coverage okay
no problemio
no
this voice history will be an early one
actually at
very early time 10 AM or something like
that I think for me 10 or 9 A.M
is
yeah
has to be
it's okay though I can make it somehow
um
then I'm not up yet that's okay you can
watch the archive it'll be a one hour
stream or so only I'm pretty sure
yeah
thank you for watching so funny
[Music]
let's watch uh read some super chatos
yeah yeah
shall we
hello
you're welcome to stay and where did I
leave off yeah last time
wouldn't it be nice if we could just
look at them
not have to read them just look at them
scroll by
[Music]
shorts videos
no thank you
[Music]
oh I should probably change screen
and uh yes office of Coach office
here we are
and the chat
to go here
and let me see Wawa
[Music]
oh thank you yesmir yeah it's okay
um
wow
[Music]
the shorts
are don't show up in hololizer
because they don't they didn't even get
super chance because there was no
Premiere whatsoever so
[Music]
no
okay well guess what what
fruit was okay
it's okay
well of course froggy while I was your
froggy while we're always there
always
[Music]
what do you mean I'm too big are you
calling me fat
I oh my God
oh my God I'm gone forever
scrolled in too much
Oh Come Back
[Music]
okay
that looks too small let's do this
I mean I zoom in too much at this up
here I become so big you can't even
see me anymore ironically
and any emotion what are you saying for
me for the short but it got deleted
I don't know what what besides what was
besides the shorts
[Music]
I I really don't know
where where we
did holotalk the last thing I read
foreign
the trailer for YouTube music weekend
oh that doesn't have super jets
then the anarchive scarf 3D karaoke
rebroadcast
also has no super chats
yeah because it couldn't be monetized
then the cow carrot video
has a couple okay
uh Korean red Super Chat message
completely in Korean
let me see
oh
[Music]
what's up
training says I'm going to the training
center next week is that the way it
translates like the the military thing
[Music]
it just translates to training center
no I couldn't
you must already be gone and I couldn't
say happy birthday
[Music]
and you're gonna be gone for so long
right cause for some reason this is
always so long but maybe you can see on
the weekend
Honolulu
[Music]
it's because I read it so late now I
feel so bad
Korean Bros
[Music]
six hours 30 minutes of the Stream
I wished Honolulu a happy birthday
they extended to 21 months what the [\h__\h]
oh
Honolulu happy birthday
why why do my fans have to go to the
military army thingy
why yeah
I'll be waiting for you like in the
movies
I'll try
but it's not so strict right on the
weekend or so they have time for doing
whatever maybe
[Music]
I don't remember how
strict it was
Korean Bros
yeah maybe not in the first few weeks
but
it's less string oh
[Music]
don't forget me
not only Chima
um
[Music]
don't forget
it makes me sad too
[Music]
fighting
birthday
I hope you had a lovely birthday right
before going at least since it was right
before you went to the Army
you had one last chance to do big party
if it was during your time in the Army
who knows you probably wouldn't
have been able to party at all
so I hope you had a great birthday
oh
[Music]
sad
Nancy for you
then say pile she says it's so happily
but I'm sad
space wonderful Duncan Lucas rather than
kitchen there's a vote
happy holidays
oh
yeah
[Music]
okay
super chatos for the little cow carrot
video the yes one
um
thank you
and now we are at the Rome VOD
unbelievable
Italia
gorgeous room
all right here we go here we go
Cruz thank you and Mrs Duncan
congratulations
[Music]
foreign
so big would kiwawa live again soon
um but I think you know I still do a lot
of streams even when I'm in Japan
I I got a hotel as I told you where I
think
sound wise it wouldn't be so bad at
least if it's not in the middle of the
night
um internet wise I don't know will test
it but I also asked Cali don't know if I
told you that but I asked Kelly if I can
stream at her place sometimes alone uh
like not collab but just solo
every once in a while and she said yeah
no problem very kind so maybe twice a
week or so in case in the hotel it
doesn't work out well then I have a good
option for that yeah she says she'll
just leave and go somewhere
when I'm streaming I mean she can also
stay I don't mind but of course it's
actually
um you know if I want to do like a
little bit of a longer stream if that's
possible
during the day
I mean she has a lot of stuff all the
time did you see her she posted a
picture I think of her
calendar where she had an appointment on
every freaking day so she'd probably be
busy and have some days where she isn't
at home anyway so if we can time it well
I'll try to time it so that I
maybe can stream my days at her place
where she's got to do something anyway
um
yeah that would be nice ideal and then
besides that you know I've been planning
some collabos although it's hard to plan
so many
uh following up on everything difficult
for me too
um
I mean don't have to beat too many
though because
more opportunities this year
[Music]
don't get sucked into a work trap though
Japan trips over everything these days
so we're going to enjoy it please
well yeah I mean
besides meeting
all these whole life members I don't
really know what to do anyway
there's some work related things that
I'll have to do
um
but yeah ideally I would love to go to
Nintendo World in Osaka but I don't
think I can get a ticket
I want to go but I don't think I could
cut a ticket especially if I live
overseas then it will be difficult
but maybe if I got someone
[Music]
Kirby Cafe so in Tokyo that sounds fun
you guys gonna give me some ideas
of cool things to do like I mean I've
lived in Japan I've seen a lot of things
already
in Tokyo area and so on but
I'm I'm like I have no
idea what to do
at the moment
hmm
Sky Tree oh the Kirby Cafe is this guy
will really be that long though
I don't really care about aquariums to
be honest
[Music]
day trips somewhere
outside of Tokyo at least for one day I
don't know where I would go though
[Music]
foreign
I actually
um
yeah I don't know
I don't know how far I am myself I would
want to go for the shrine check
uh ideally we would go to one she hasn't
seen before but we haven't decided on
that yet we haven't decided on a date
either yet but
we'll hopefully figure it out
the monkeys I don't think I can see
those monkeys that go into the lands
have you been to Nico no I don't think
so
[Music]
um
there's no world
well you know
I asked speculative about meeting and
she said yes right wasn't it even on
stream but I'm thinking
maybe not following up on that
I don't want to um
make it awkward so
uh but Disneyland I don't know
Disneyland is always
so crowded and so much waiting standing
time
[Music]
um
maybe I'll go but maybe not I wouldn't
mind not going to Disneyland I've been
several times Disneyland and Disney sea
in Japan
maybe it was a small group I don't know
[Music]
yeah
Disneyland is well
it would be fun
probably but I don't necessarily need it
[Music]
I'll think about it though
no I don't think her feelings would get
hurt
I just don't want to push myself onto
her
um
she's a very busy person too
see
Michael moose whatever foreign
you guys don't understand
[Music]
you wouldn't understand
yeah you wouldn't get it
[Music]
I mean this is not like it's the last
chance to do it
as I said there will be more
opportunities I already have a trip
planned after that one so there's many
opportunities
that's why I'm not I don't need to rush
to see as many people as possible in
this one trip
wow
famous monkey
[Laughter]
no honestly I feel like that pet would
freak me out if I see it in reality
the eyes are so fake for the small body
[Music]
scares me
it scares me with the fingers oh the
fingers
I care more about katos
yeah it's like a chihuahua with hands
hahaha
you you're right it's like a chihuahua
but
um
[Laughter]
oh man no
uh
anyway Jacob here's a kiss how did I
make a
how did they make such a tangent out of
a simple Super Chat that said Kiana back
foreign
what happened
how did we get here I'm lost
I was responsible
I'll find a way a make a way
will leave again
[Music]
soon
thank you foreign
German as new language skill nice Tai
Chi
absolutely perfect but you probably just
copy pasted it didn't you
mwah Optimus Prime download
thank you oh merch
getting ships to Canada noise thank you
for getting the merch I appreciate it I
wonder which ones
no not you don't mean almost cat do you
you mean the birthday stuff and so
onions
[Music]
thank you for two pinkies
hi kiwawa while you were Natalia evolved
into the Phoenix oh about this I was
wondering have you ever listened to the
song Phoenix Dance by Azalea from love
live no
that's it they have a song that's called
Phoenix dance
what about singing it in next karaoke or
live I think it's suitable for you by
the way I'm always happy when you when
you go to my country
oh you're from Italy and you were happy
about it yes Rome is so beautiful and
you can easily walk everywhere and
that's the best way to see all its great
sights glad you had a good time there
thank you
oh
yeah yeah it's very walkable
surprisingly and here and there you can
just jump into a bus
um
it's pretty easy to get around Rome I
definitely felt the same way thank you
so much so much and congratulations on
becoming something of a hybrid Phoenix
should listen to it that's another
Phoenix song like the the other one that
uh I sang with Elena
um and her like VR thingy
what was that one called Firebird or so
that one was also a cool one so some
Phoenix themed songs here and there huh
that one is a really cool one indeed
resilient
thank you for telling me about this one
Phoenix dance
I mean I'm not into love life but
look it up
oh it's a trio
right now I'll meet but I'll continue
talking
I'm curious
Trio
this could be good for like
it sounds like K-pop
a little bit more like idiom oh
foreign
it's more about dance than Phoenix so
far
okay it's not really kpop
what does this feel like
well this is gender it sounds kind of um
old still
foreign
yeah
Latin Pop ah that might be it Latin
idiom pop or something like that
oh I mean I could sing at some point if
I find uh
if I find a instrumental
[Music]
but to be honest my priority for
um
songs at the moment is getting more
Hello project songs into set lists
whether it be like you know
future kiwawa Freddy uh
uh performances or
other things anywhere I want to
recommend hey
this in my mind I just want to get more
Hello project out there
because I see like a lot of Vocaloids
being used mostly
Vocaloid songs
for this I don't know 3D concerts how
that whole life does like whether it's
like the big ones or the YouTube only
ones
and I understand you know but
hello project cells have so much
potential you know there's so much
potential so hype
no
hey let the eye notification begin
and then the good thing with the hello
project songs is some of them I already
know how to dance
[Music]
and know how to sing them
easy easy easy
[Music]
anyway where was I oh yeah a kiss for
you perhaps
because
thank you all the for all the questions
by the way
[Music]
should I go to Rome instead of Austria
on my Europe vacation
I mean if you already planned the
Australian you should go to Austria but
I mean it's close Rome is literally like
Italy is neighboring to Austria so
if you have time you could still look
maybe squish it in somehow I would
recommend it but don't don't
skip Austria
the game soon
you also went there before night soon
people collect the coins overnight
they do
overnight oh my God
imagine that job coin collector at the I
think this is Fontana di Trevi that
we're talking about
oof foreign
[Music]
city has two popes per square mile
because it's so small
the game
thank you for the pinky oh you changed
your name to always cheerleader what
happened
here
what happened what about me
what about me they're called
I need cheerleading too
[Music]
found myself a cheerleader
ah you changed it it's driving it's okay
I saw your names
back to the normal State oh I think that
I found myself a cheerleader but he is
cheering for Ollie instead on you
sad I wonder why maybe because of the
anniversary but this Super Chat was
before the anniversary whatever it was I
mean all he deserves support and
cheering too
as long as you're back to me now
a direction I am auntie
thank you
oh what
really cool to see you live you were
there in person and Anime NYC
oh so cool nice Christmas
yeah oh cool I want to visit New York
City in general one day must see cities
but I feel like it would be so
overwhelming holy [\h__\h]
looking for the top down because
oh you met oh that's cool didn't you go
eat dinner together like the dukumi Gang
everybody had dinner together in Germany
too
[Music]
five medium cities on top of each other
why not next to each other why does it
have to be on top of each other
like a sandwich
City sandwich
and make sure you go during the day with
a bodyguard or five in New York City
there's so many people like why would I
need a bodyguard not at least not for
being recognized ran off early because
my feet hurt but everyone was in their
nose oh
I went for West Coast use a wobble
concert West Coast left side
mama
well I don't know about West Coast if we
could do it in West Coast but
somewhere in America hopefully one day
left at California California
here we come
[Music]
um
I've been asking my local convention Oh
California girls are Unforgettable bugs
on top West Coast represent
[Music]
foreign
so put your hair up oh
yeah yeah
hands up love hair okay
it will start with AJ
hmm
Flappy boys sent a recipe saying had an
absolute blast following your travel
report so much in a suddenly long long
to pay the Eternal Studio visit again
myself oh you've been there before but
not before Summer by the way if you
loved Rome you might want to check out
Florence and Venice great to have you
back you well thank you yeah I mean
definitely will visit more cities in
Italy
if you've already been in Rome then you
should also maybe go to other cities
as well but it's cool that you've been
there now so you've seen something very
important very historic
um
you Flappy boy for the sweet sweet words
and yeah I love doing this travel report
so I hope I can do some nice ones next
year again
[Music]
um
don't worry I'm like even if I wanted to
I couldn't go now
or anytime soon my next couple months so
yeah
I think I won't go
anywhere besides what I've already
planned until April or so
ah why is a year so short
I wanna I wanna go to places I want to
go to the Maldives again
but you know what I I I'm a girl the
Maldives when it makes sense to go and
that will be next winter
[Music]
next winter when it's cold as [\h__\h] here
I will go to the Maldives because that's
actually a good time to go
both because
uh it's cold as [\h__\h] here and also
because at least at that time there will
be no storms
foreign
[Music]
and then I also want to go to Bali next
year yeah
Bali I could probably go to Bali in
spring right should be hot
like spring as in March or so
uh April more like April not March can't
go on I don't think I can go in March in
March I should take a break April
Valley and spring basically hell what
you handled volumes what
it's supposed to be hot because I want
to go swim it'll be hot well summer will
be hotter probably
[Laughter]
April weather
one degree Celsius hmm
if you say nice and warm in the evening
so it's always shorts and t-shirts
weather at 28 degrees Celsius the sea is
perfect for swimming 28. poor
deal
there's a 111 millimeter of rain over 11
days how much is that
the [\h__\h] knows how much that is but you
can still expect 12 hours of daylight
with 10 hours of sunshine that's so
specific
I mean
31 degrees is obviously [\h__\h] hot but
well that's what I would hope for when I
go on a vacation
[Music]
it says the best time to visit Bali is
between April and October the Island's
dry season although the weather is ideal
for travels the island is also subject
to soupy humid days throughout the year
well we can also not do April but like
May if that's a bit better maybe
anytime around there but before summer
before actual summer because in summer I
think maybe I'll go to Greece or so
again
or Spain
just for a short trip because that's in
Europe and I can go fast and some if
yeah for quick trip
I can arrive fast and summer at least
here it's also warm
I want to use the side seasons
to go somewhere where it wouldn't be
warm enough to go swimming here but it
would be elsewhere
it's like turned around
excellent choice
and then yeah I think I'll spend a lot
of the summer at home as well though
um
if it gets too hot I might try to escape
somewhere though because this summer I
don't know I couldn't freaking take it
but maybe
maybe something was wrong with my
uh air
fake air conditioned system I don't know
I don't wanna do that again if it's so
bad again and I'll go on a spontaneous
trip somewhere probably
yeah Scandinavia trip exactly which I
wanted to do I wanted to visit
Scandinavia anyway
if it really gets too hot I'll do that
in the summer 2023
and then I hope that in
I mean of course they can always come
things in between if things change up a
little bit
but then in Autumn it would be nice if I
could take a little bit of a break like
two months or three months of not
traveling
right need that kind of time too
[Music]
leaves again but there probably will be
even more little trips in between maybe
I'll also visit Korea again
Maybe
in Autumn short trip in Autumn not in
summer oh hell no I'm not going to
Korean somewhere
laid Autumn if anything
late late autumn
[Music]
I mean I want to make use of this kind
of opportunity also because you know I
like to make content out of my trips
foreign
a few more girls to join I mean it's not
like I'm inviting them but I just want
to be like a little bit open invite
maybe go with like three to four people
I think after seeing the photos from
last time
no one can say no to this Cali would 100
be up for it but that workaholic chick I
don't know if she even has time for it
[Music]
um
but I think
oh super December would probably also
love to go
because you flexed on her didn't we
well I think we can get a couple people
definitely convinced
it will be fun
to go with three to four but four
maximum I don't want more than four
people
I don't want too many people
um
it's about a wood
do it and love it I'm pretty sure
we could
do the
turducken Trio possibly
yeah yeah
company-wide cover trip to the Maldives
thank you no thank you
but then the thing the cool thing would
be if we're a little bit of a bigger
group we can get one of those you know
me and they never looking at some crazy
rooms you know we already had a pretty
dope ass big
Little Villa
um big little
but if we go with like four or five
we can afford one of those big ones that
even come with its own pool above the
ocean and maybe even a slide or so
yeah
we share and then
let me get one of those thick rooms man
it's like a house a big Villa
that would be so cool
yeah as long as you can share the price
isn't so bad
um
business expense vacation
yeah if I stream like last time I should
be able to write it off
yeah I saw some some of the Villas have
slides
so cool
please
[Music]
oh yeah the floaties we shall not go
uh the ring stormy season we don't want
to lose any more floaties
and this time I'll bring my own floating
wait didn't I already bring
[Music]
I did bring my own floaty for that trip
didn't I
I felt extra smart because of it because
they were hella expensive there Lena
bought one
but I think I brought my own
Lena bought her own that's for sure and
the ball we bought a little ball as well
that we didn't really use but I'm pretty
yeah I'm pretty sure I remember because
I know I used that one on a different
the one I had I used it on a different
vacation too
and you lose it
[Music]
mine was rescued but Elena's was lost I
think
hmm
bring your own water
huh
[Music]
you're always driving
I will buy season one you don't have to
buy it don't you have Netflix it's free
on Netflix
but you know stuff like that that has so
many episodes and so many seasons I
don't really want to do a watch long for
those things because it's a big
commitment I do recommend you binge
watching it through
um is it really it is hmm
yup yup yup the whole everything even
the newest weird season that's kind of
like a
reunion style because they were much
older that one wasn't so good
[Music]
um but as a Gilmore Girls fan you have
to watch it it's just
you can't get around it
to remember the Maldives better yeah our
memories are
blurry aren't isn't it
[Music]
all the g girls are good you were
attacking killer girls right
but yeah I'm excited for next year for
all those trips
um
Japan might be a little bit stressful
here and there
in terms of scheduling
but I hope I can enjoy it have a good
time
meet some cutie patooties
and accomplish some things
I'm actually really looking forward to
New Year's
yeah
but I'm nervous too
[Music]
I wish I could go to the Maldives right
now though
How can I
can I go to The Moldy hmm
[Music]
impossible
I don't know if we can make it
is just the first time you visit a
shrine in the year as long as both of us
don't go to any other Shrine before
going together it doesn't have to be the
first the second the third or anything
we'll see it would be nice though
[Music]
make a stop at the Maldives on your
flight to Japan
it's possible
it's kind of possible I guess
but then I would probably have to stop
twice
because there's no direct flight to the
Maldives I think I don't know
at least it wasn't a direct flight last
time
foreign
[Music]
not this time
not going Emirates
[Music]
I'm actually going with an airline that
um
[Music]
even if I tried it before then it was at
the most once
hmm
[Music]
one airline that I don't have much of an
opinion about
see how it goes
no Caleb I love and I've been with KLM
plenty
I feel like I will forget
oh if I forget then I'll have my brother
send me them for mail to Japan
think that should arrive
on time
but yeah good idea maybe remind me again
when I am close to leaving and start
talking about packing Maybe
[Music]
I fly Emirates so much for me not to
like it how can you get through the
absolutely obnoxious security footage
all the time though
huh
that they play three to four times in
different languages
no
the more I see it the more obnoxious it
is to me
so obnoxious ah that freaking voice of
the dude
is so obnoxious
enjoy the in-flight entertainment of
anyways
[Music]
absolutely amazing
oh so obnoxious with his stupid fake
British accent
mine's better
anyway thank you Flappy boy I went on a
tangent again
[Music]
thanks for the pinky thanks for the
wonderful catch up and hope you and the
fam had a wonderful Thanksgiving oh we
don't really do Thanksgiving but thank
you um
we did have um actually
dinner together surprisingly
but it was nothing special it's just a
normal normal meal and then my mom was
like oh
by the way today is Thanksgiving and I'm
like uh-huh
well we never ever have ever celebrated
that even closely so not that it matters
to us
um
we don't have like we have Christmas you
know but Thanksgiving
[Music]
it would be nice though I wouldn't mind
it being a thing but it's so close to
Christmas
and Halloween
yeah no need to squeeze in another thing
there I think
[Music]
um
oh
the music weekend thing has no support
shutters on
why did it not have super Chats on
it it was my own songs why do I die off
[Music]
what
ah well there's a chance since it was a
Premiere that my own songs were flagged
as they always do
and then
when it gets unmonetized
then I think the super chats sometimes
get turned off too
yeah it's kind of weird there's like um
obviously I have the rights to my songs
but on YouTube not really
it goes for something else
and yeah it's stupid I hate seeing it it
triggers me when it says this has been
claimed and I'm like but this is my song
hahaha
Kiana perms lost
but you know I when I first saw that I
obviously talked to janma and yeah it's
normal but it triggers me I don't want
to see those stupid ass claims it's my
song
but that's the system apparently I'm
part of the system
[Music]
I can't believe Kiana blocked Kiana like
what the [\h__\h]
feels like
being claimed
unjustifiedly
not a word
anyway super chattels from Pokemon
Scarlet number one
[Music]
that's that says part two
where's the first one thumbnail
uh uh Pokemon
[Music]
foreign
oh it was part two oh oh
the title kind of implied something else
oh I guess okay because I took a break
makes sense
foreign
[Music]
I had so much fun cooking for you
for me
I didn't eat it you mean I mean for the
can we
can we collab
that implies that I ate something I was
not served any food
[Music]
had so much fun cooking for you and
everyone I'm so happy to grow in this
Hobby and your food on Twitter inspires
me as well
hope you get to share more culinary
ideas with us soon you're the best thank
you well we'll see what I'm cooking up
today
the more time passes the more lazy I get
and don't want to cook anymore today
how did the how did the water soup and
straighten those taste
[\h__\h] that
show the Thanksgiving masterpiece
inspired for your food picks
yeah
[Music]
you showed
what you could do frozen lasagna and
we'd love it I actually do have frozen
lasagna in my freezer
I would love it you would love it
but wherever I would love it
anyway yeah yeah good cooking
good cooking I guess
I guess it wasn't so so bad looking what
you cooked up
I guess it looked edible
laughs
yeah
I'm glad that you could
have some kind of
hmm
place to show off and flex your
Creations I guess
good for you
huh
Sky donkey soon spread the Spy dance
mission for the pinky
before you know honest and kind words on
my Thanksgiving submission key wow oh I
don't remember I'm sorry um I do love my
local Cuisine but this was the first
time I ever really tried to experiment
and come up with an original recipe for
these dishes from scratch oh I got
anxious with the result and since it
turned out to be more Filipino American
Cuisine than how it traditionally is
it meant so much to me to hear that you
loved it
[Music]
I don't remember what it was but I
probably was really good looking
foreign
you you would just cook for anyone
wouldn't you it wasn't just for me
Callie and Nami
you're the type of person who just cooks
for anyone
you could literally be working at a
restaurant because you you just cook for
anyone it's not a special thing to you
wow
has no meaning whatsoever
I thought we were special
wow
damn
that's the reality
ah the one with the Uber cake
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay if be culinary
skills wouldn't you say it's more of a
deadbeat culinary skill I'll see that
then huh
[Music]
well well well well
it's okay I'm just kidding we know that
right
yeah yeah go make a good looking
sandwich
just because there are skulls on the
plane there's literally like a shy guy
Cali skull thingy whatever that is on
your profile picture
can't fool me I know who your number one
or she is
it's good though it's okay whatever
it's fine
[Music]
you can't fool me it's fine though when
you can't fool me there's no doubt
thank you for supporting me
don't leave
[Music]
what was that more of a 2021 quinoa
is that so
that was DDS YouTube about kids
oh
I was
still your first myth girl
huh that doesn't make it better
well at least you're still here that's
the good thing a lot of people come and
they go
but you're still here thank you and all
the others who's still here too a black
one a lot of free kisses
la
[Music]
Grandma kisses
um
[Music]
I'm sorry I've been kind of M.I.A on
your streams I want you to know that I
will always be here now go catch em all
Where Have You Been pong
yo
[Music]
oh
there's no explanation
where did you go
well at least you reassure me you're
still around thank you I'm not gonna
catch them all though you can't tell me
what to do
I'm not planning on catching them all
catching some of them not all of them
very specifically
I guess that's so good though
[Music]
huh what
Mommy
why is Paul making stuff for Gouda
[Music]
oh my God these DVDs yeah yeah yeah
you're the right one to speak
[Music]
of them all
don't want to hear that from you
[Music]
thank you but I don't think I'll be
accepting any Pokemon I know you guys
have been offering here and there and
you know I wish I wish but I feel like
you know
[Music]
oh
it's not special to me if I take it from
someone else than you know
I could have 50 shinies if I did that
but um
it's just not the same
and the moon's boring you know but thank
you for offering
okay thank you soon
[Music]
thank you oh
thank you very super chat since January
2021 wow
[Music]
okay well this is kind of late but Happy
Birthday hi essence
[Music]
techno King 77th Edition production
technology
are playing those games I'm wondering if
you're looking into streaming or playing
Persona games on your channel whatever
the responses I wanted to tell you that
you're awesome and I'm happy to be a
cafe employee thank you
um maybe like Sometime Late next year
when I'm when I run out of games I could
consider it but at the moment we have a
lineup and with the trips we're gonna be
busy anyway uh
uh so next is Fire Emblem and then I'll
look at how things are standing and we
continue with whatever Catherine I don't
have perms for Catherine
maybe you sometime will get it but at
the moment I'm I'm you know I have
already ideas of what to do yeah still
waiting for Square Enix don't even
mention
feels like it's never gonna happen
um
also you know next year maybe will there
be a new Yakuza again I'm not sure but
more than enough options and um
personal games might be taken into
consideration yeah even though they're
hacking along
a fight
yeah they look good I like the visuals
of course
I don't know what I think about the
general like system though
and the theme I prefer like fantasy kind
of
RPGs
uh in terms of like you know what how
how to describe
um personas like modern school life or
something like that right
with surely some like fantasy elements
in it oh but I mean like compared to
tails off games you know and Fire Emblem
and so on
oh yeah urban fantasy that's what I mean
rather than that I prefer the classic
jrpg fantasy world
I think I'll probably enjoy Persona 2 as
well
um oh yeah touring I like to worry that
was interesting
hmm
[Music]
bourbon fencing
Witcher well maybe in 2023
I could give it a try up
well I mean there's so much
so much possibilities
in 2023 we'll see we'll see
Christopher
Martin
hey attention don't forget to open up
poker portal to get the flying Pikachu
it's limited time I already did I'll
still update your Reds raids and stairs
and Eevee event going on
how do you update your range don't worry
you'll get a shiny eventually
bye bye
she said hello but she loved
anyway thank you I got the flying
Pikachu yeah
oh Evie is way over and it doesn't
matter I did get some EVS somewhere
uh in a radar I think
[Music]
I think I got it in a raid maybe that
was by coincidence exactly that
[Music]
waited two years to watch what the [\h__\h]
why another one
huh
what what kept you all from watching
that
thank you
foreign
[Music]
also Christopher I don't have a favorite
all-time Pokemon I think Joey thank you
hello
[Music]
a conduction
garlic Pokemon done
can we get one more in there
[Music]
Another One Bites dust
it's we do we do we do be doing it here
one more
see now you guys also know why I didn't
show you or talk about the Advent Reef
on the Sunday stream
I was like yes I know it's Sunday
because I was planning to light it for
my
Advent calendar video
yeah
also my brother
praised my Advent did I say calendar
yeah I don't Reef
[Music]
my brother praised it
it looks so good
like oh my God
thank you
the question here you actually have
Ollie as your profile picture even
thank you for the pinky and the red
super chat plus you should be resting
why you must be so sweet this should be
a DIY cat cuddling stream while we cook
for you and wouldn't that be nice but
the level insists on giving us Peak DIY
content even when sick appreciate your
Buzz sorry I can't give you a thousand
Euro you'd throw me into the usual room
if I did but here's a contribution to a
new table if the old one can't be fixed
well I think over Christmas I'm not
gonna we're gonna use the same one
yeah I was looking for like the email
confirmation whatever when I purchased
it but I couldn't find it yeah and I've
been looking every single freaking
keyword I looked uh through my emails
with
and I I found every freaking other piece
of furniture that I ordered from my
apartment ever but just not the [\h__\h]
table I don't get it
[Music]
um so I'm having troubles trying to even
check if I am
able to get a refund in the first place
[Music]
I know there's I have a confirmation
somewhere but no freaking keyboard would
work
now I looked for like two email accounts
that could have been it
[Music]
you're thinking ah you mean it didn't
help in terms of yeah already wasting
some time of the guarantee or so I think
so too yeah I think I had standing
around for half a year or so
so if the guarantee is one year then
most likely over
[Music]
um right I don't know I don't remember
when I got it do you guys remember when
I got it
most likely too late y'all which is
[\h__\h] sad because I I paid a lot and
it's really massive I don't even know
how to get rid of it if I wanted to
[Music]
well well well well
yeah no
um
the problem wasn't that it was always
uneven it was like either you build it
so that it would be uneven or you build
it so that it would be not uneven but
very very very wobbly
and then recently I noticed after I came
back from Italy I don't want to say my
brother did anything because I don't
know how you would [\h__\h] it up like that
but it was after that that I noticed
when I was eating my dinner on it I
heard like crackling noises
and I was like where's this coming from
that's weird and then after a while
I noticed wait a second this table is
like really lopsided right now what the
hell is going on
uh it was a miracle that things weren't
rolling off of it so I I realized wait
this crackling sound is coming from the
table I looked around like where is it
crackling and then I found underneath
beneath the table
oh there's like
something just falling apart
I'm trying to try to build a table for
the stream now ah no that's just that's
a different one that's just my streaming
side table
what was it a martial arts term
could have been stressed on the board
itself yeah but I think not on what was
on top but how the possibly how the feet
were assembled because obviously there
was something wrong but we tried
assembling them million times
and never got it right apparently but
like apparently there was something
wrong of it
and that might have um been the reason
why after a long time
a couple months or so
now it's breaking
but one of my chairs has the perfect
height of arms to hold up the table now
it doesn't wobble and it doesn't Lop
side
but yeah
slowly crushed by the weight of its own
tabletop I don't know something like
that I guess
[Music]
um
I'm so pissed off I don't want to buy a
new table dining table
so mad
hire handyman to fix it I don't know
that's fixable
if I buy another one next time I'm just
gonna buy a cheap ass [\h__\h] table from
Ikea
okay not the cheapest one but
oh I'm not gonna waste I don't know how
much I wasted but I'm not gonna waste
like a thousand bucks again for a stupid
table that's gonna break in a year just
because it wasn't properly accepted
well next time I'm gonna buy a table
that doesn't have to [\h__\h] stupid
spider legs
normal four legs
that are
just at the spots where they should be
for every normal table
or one big leg in the middle
where you can't do anything wrong
hmm
just normal legs
yo that
that really massive steel [\h__\h] in it I
don't know how it broke apart
[Music]
anyway thank you
and yeah so new table at some point but
not yet but thank you thank you
and and yeah it was fine I was just a
little bit tiny bit sick and I really
wanted to make that riff it was fun
thank you for watching
do we have one of reef too I
wondered
thank you for the pinky
hope you feel better Kiara this reminds
me of the time my mom promised to make I
read for a ceremony in one hour and we
went running and screaming for Michael's
Michael's is that a store looking for
purple candles oh it had to be purple
wouldn't it have been another color
craft store oh
hmm
cool
are you asking me
to stay that's not New Tokyo Station
okay
[Music]
I don't know there's a lot of places I
would stay uh if you can at the place
that's connected to the Yama note line
because Yama know the line goes all to
all the important places and circles and
it's a really good my favorite train
line in Tokyo
yeah
really convenient anyway
thank you random collusion I do feel
better now thankfully it was only short
I'm relieved that it didn't become
something painfully long
ongoing and and shitty so fancies thanks
to your guys's sweetness I was able to
recover fast yeah
I'm noting that for when I go to Japan
thank you you're welcome
hmm
also I recommend
um
especially if you travel alone I
actually recommend the APA hotels
they're a big line
um of
kind of in terms of size business hotels
in Japan that are pretty like nice and
clean though and they I've made the
experience that they are yeah
I've made the experience that they are
really really easy to book and they're
like everywhere
and they give you free one all the time
and they're not as shitty as a lot of
other business hotels on the same price
range they look quite Fancy from outside
um
the reason why there is to book I've
noticed is you know you know how I don't
have a
um how I don't have a uh a credit card
so for some hotels at some point I had
problems booking them but then I noticed
that if you go on the upper Hotel
website
um they have an English version of their
and
they you don't even you don't even have
to pay upfront or put in a credit card
or anything to book the hotel
it's actually kind of crazy that they do
that and allow that at least it was like
this when I last tried it a couple years
ago two three years ago so
um
so it's incredibly convenient you pay
after at the hotel
and they need nothing for reservation
which as someone who worked in hotels
before honestly makes me wonder
how how can you do that
how did how do you what that's not
normal for hotels in Europe that's for
sure and most hotels all over the world
probably you either pay upfront or you
give some kind of guarantee like a
credit card
remember but for Apple you didn't need
it
and they were really good quality and so
this was just a big relief when I didn't
know yet did I really want to stay there
but in any case I need to stay in a
place that doesn't need a credit card so
here we go
and they have so many locations
yeah I really like them
breakfast I can't really recommend
though in any
business okay maybe some of them are
okay there's some most about hotels are
kind of small but then here and there in
some big locations like
um close to the venue
that
is being used for Tokyo game show I
think and also uh
the whole life concerts
I think yeah there's a big upper hotel
close by
that's that one's huge and therefore
they also have a big
um breakfast uh place but normally the
breakfast is really lame there
but holy [\h__\h] that upper near makuhari
is actually insane
I've stayed there a few times but at
some point when I stayed there I noticed
they made some big changes
I don't want to stay there anymore
because it turned into a hotel that is
so
I don't know how to explain it but it's
so unpersonal
um it's been too long so it's hard for
me to explain but the hotel is so big
that it has different types of
[Music]
um
like separations
and depending on which
Tower you will end up in you will have
to check in somewhere else on the check
and it's kind of weird the check-in is
really not personal at all I don't know
I'm just used to having a more personal
check-in I appreciate a more personal
check-in but it became very robotic I
don't know but at least that hotel it
also has a lot of stuff inside because
it's so big it has a convenience store
inside it has I think an Onsen or
something like that inside as shops
inside big several big restaurants it
has a pool that can be used in summer
well there's a lot of cool stuff if you
ever look for a hotel for going to Tokyo
game show or so you could go there I
guess book early though very early
a lot of I know that for
events at makuhari
a lot of important people
stay at get or the guests get booked
into
um
or all those big hotels around
I'm staying in park right Tokyo oh she's
my friend petal Florence oh another
hotel blah
that's too much but that's a good hotel
anyway I didn't like that but besides
that APA I love all the apples
they have a funny lady
promoting the hotel
on on everywhere on commercials
commercials and on the um the water
bottles
[Music]
you're the funny lady
apologize
[Music]
anyway
I'm back to topic guys guys it's your
fault
[Music]
where was I oh yeah I am random
collusion
how the [\h__\h]
[Music]
makes no sense it's not related at all I
I think I got I was a different
different
Super Chat that popped up that I saw
thank you random collusion we collided
super absolute 113 thank you and happy
holidays to YouTube let's see
[Music]
I am a tea
in the conduction oh thank you for
ordering the kitchen
ah beautiful crafting stream Daniel my
little one was being
glued not hot glue to the screen why you
may laugh thank God
yes yes make your Kato watch me
I want to make a coat with cattle
following me I want a cat following oh
yeah a cat called for me yes
[Laughter]
yes
no no no hot glue cattle no
thank you spanking time greetings to
your cattle
dog
would sing you excited like this rubs up
on me so much
yeah well I don't know I had fun making
that
I'm so proud of it
this is why you guys should make more
stuff yourself as well
then you can be so proud as I am of what
you made I mean obviously some things
will turn out like [\h__\h] but something
like the the Christmas wreath to Adam
and reef it's hard to [\h__\h] that one up
so badly that it wouldn't look pretty
just smack a bunch of decorations on
there and it looks amazing
okay
foreign
[Music]
combinations
um I especially like the ones that are
like white or gold
um but also pink ones pink ones are so
pretty
soft light pink one so pretty yeah it's
a good contrast
of course I had to make it an orange
fully customizable yeah
I I I don't think the green ones are
nice too I'm talking about the
decorations though not the
you understand that right moon dog
but there's green on green as well like
light green on the reef dark green
wouldn't I've never seen dark green
because that doesn't really stand out or
look good
[Music]
yeah yeah
I like green green yeah light green on
on a Christmas wreath looks good too
light green candles I mean
never seen orange Reef but it looks
unique
it
I think it's actually
somewhat common because of the orange
slices are a popular
um decoration it works well works well
with orange
it's midnight you want to start cooking
an hour ago
okay Mom
I'm done anyway almost right
[Music]
oh Denmark thank you hey yeah
you guys I'm done I'll end it here I'll
go cooking now I'll see what I have
and tomorrow I guess I'll lose Freedom
thingy but I think I'll put up the
reservation after I get up
[Music]
I have to do really
urgently recording tomorrow when I wake
up
so hopefully my throat is gonna be okay
hmm
I'm Danny with the funny y'all
I hope Chad behaves tomorrow don't worry
I'll probably mostly not be looking at
it anyway yeah
I think it's good that I waited so long
to do ring fit because I always said it
makes no sense of Life today I will wait
until I can do it with 3D
even if it's scuffed
[Music]
oh
it won't be a long stream anyway because
I will literally faint
okay guys in one hour
update
so keep an eye out on it don't worry
this time it's not me
tomorrow will also not be me
so yeah
[Music]
I'm so happy it's doing so well I'm so
proud so glad I didn't just forget the
idea
to believe in yourself and just do it
just do it
how do we learned this from my video
do it
nothing is impossible
just
do it
just get some Harvard student
to help you and just
do it I'll let it be done
hey yeah okay thanks for watching today
oh my God we're getting to eight hours
seven hours 51 minutes
well I didn't expect that
um
[Music]
oh thank you thank you
soon love you guys oh I showed my 60
year old K-pop loving daddy music and
he's not a fan
did he get into kpop like recently
that's interesting
or like maybe in the past 10 years even
it's possible too okay pop has been
around
uh that's so sweet your dad sounds nice
[Music]
no I'm ending it now don't worry
I was going to end it right now I just
talked about you I said get yourself a
Harvard student
things seem impossible and just do it
anyway thank you guys so much tomorrow
we're gonna work out I guess
[Music]
fun boy
I have to be forced
[Music]
muchas gracias
yes Buenas notice
[Music]
foreign
until 8 hours
[Music]
oh yeah no I'm a meeting in eight hours
let's go I'm still feeling okay I
actually didn't drink that much it's
actually pretty bad
come on
[Music]
shut up don't say it like that
speak more like you speak to a lady
[Music]
mm-hmm
all right I'll be chilling I'll turn it
off
look at on the Big Orange bean bag
all right I have to go cuddle her I'll
turn this off in five minutes
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
a little notepad it's a Pokemon
oh
she smells like that orange bean bag
it's still stinky because she laid on it
and she gets the smell of it
[Music]
oh
that's that was chunker scratching
anyway I lost this movie
sand
[Music]
foreign
okay I think it's time oh yeah it's time
eight hours
[Music]