[Music]
do
so
[Music]
okay
hello
[Music]
i have so much cat hair on my hand
i tried to uh i spent the one hour
cuddling with my cats until the very
last moment
so i had to set up everything during the
loading screen
that's why it took so long i'm okay i'm
okay
um
i'm okay i'm okay yeah yeah yeah
it was like also kind of a power nap i
think i fell asleep for like 15 minutes
when i was cuddling with smoothie
ah it's like a it's [\h__\h] heaven
i
but i also made tea i have a big
big chunk of tea in front of me uh it
just has to cool down a little bit until
i can drink it
because uh we don't want to insult
the tea we want the tea to feel good
about itself and
think it's hot it's even too hot for a
phoenix
yeah yeah yeah yeah a chunk of tea i
don't know what else to say
yeah like a like i'm still drinking like
winter winter themed
tea from winter time
oh let me turn on the game
one second sorry um
gamecap just wish
okay yeah yeah
[Music]
oh you guys see it amazing okay
let's go
oh let's go tell the music
incoming 18 french
stop
oh
okay let's go
let's see how the audio is
let's do it like this now
oh my god
[Music]
okay we're gonna play this again
and i think we're like the good thing is
that i think we're like
in front of a dungeon or something like
that which means that
i probably won't see that many uh npcs
so there probably won't be that much
voice acting today
[Music]
okay
also like i don't really want to bring
this up again
but like okay
yesterday um let me just say this in the
beginning like i don't
um yesterday and
we talked a little bit about it during
my super chat reading
and um i uh
even though i mentioned it in the super
chat reading i didn't feel happy with
the reaction and feedback it got during
the super jack rating so i left another
comment
i just wanna i kind of wanted to keep it
low-key so i left the comment on the
youtube section but everyone saw it
i don't know it kind of blew up and uh
and on twitter and on reddit so i i i i
didn't want to make like such a huge
thing out of it but well here we are so
um i i guess i'll just say
it now here uh what did i say
um see the bottom left thing
i was never really happy like never 100
happy with it but like i saw it as a
joke like i can take jokes okay i can
take some
funny humor and stuff and all that
that's okay so
even though i never really felt like i
am bottom left i still won't agree with
it
but if that's when you guys want to put
me
and i think it's funny i in situations
in certain situations i thought it was
funny too like
if uh as i wrote in the comments don't
apologize it's okay
as i wrote in the comment link when i
play sims 4
i know there are many moments like that
that would be described as bottom left
or whatever
and i think in those moments you can you
can joke about it
and in moments where i don't know where
in rhizome when i first about
rhizome you can joke about it too that's
look that's totally fine
um so infinity moments okay but
um see also then there's stuff like on
reddit
i know that person who uploaded that has
no malicious intent but it's
stuff like that where uh i get put into
bottom left
every goddamn time um
in that in that one million subscriber
achievement thingy
that's not only like like
undermining my accomplishments but every
time someone else gets the one million
uh thingy it undermines the others
accomplishments because the comment
section seemed to always be like
hahahaha kiana is still bottom left
so um stuff like that and like whenever
i
i talk about random things that are
definitely not meant to be
like loot or whatever i would appreciate
it if
we could stop using the bottom left
thing it's not like this is the first
time i bring this up i've said it before
like i've said it before like
and in times when people were like oh
god i'm loving them like i
what well why but yeah i guess this is
the
the time a good time to really make it
clear
um i would like your cooperation
um you can do it whenever it fits but
not when it doesn't fit and when i'm
when i'm like being serious and i'm like
no i don't mean it like that it's i'm
just trying to get a serious point
across
and people are still like x x x x x
it really annoys me and um
yeah generally i can take the joke
generally it's okay
but just oh please try to read the air
everyone uh i i i kind of accept the
fact that
beyond kfp there is no hope
because well they won't
beyonce of kfpk
people probably won't like hear this
anyway
and uh it won't reach them or they won't
give a [\h__\h]
so yeah i i gave up on that that's
whatever
um but just in inside
my community and
maybe we can adjust a little bit and
uh find find other ways
to do it um
thank you um also
i mean
[Music]
uh bottom left if we think back
on what that means it means that
that person even crawling bottom left is
not only
lewd and dirty but also stupid
and over
10 months being that being called that
repeatedly
over and over and over again
most of the time i really have to say i
don't care like it it's
it's not not an issue i know you guys
are joking i'm proud people use it
mostly to describe
lewd moments but don't not
not really thinking about the stupid
part but
and and i i would like to think that you
guys
don't think of me like that in reality
i would like to think that it's just a
joke and most of the time
i i i do realize it but i don't know
maybe we can just kind of like
use it less often and only in fitting
situations
um i would appreciate that
i'm not mad for people who use it until
now
in the wrong situation like it's okay i
know it's like
i know like because it's a meme it's
like easy to throw out there and be like
hahaha bottom left
it's okay it's fine i get that don't
feel bad about it
and also the the reddit thing that i
mentioned don't feel bad about it either
but i don't know please be cooperative
and please try to
maybe help out and this is not only
about
like i saw a lot of discussions on
reddit it's not really only about
me uh because there are so many other
more situations that kind of fit
this topic um but that's for
them to address if whoever is affected
by something like that if they want to
address it then that's for them to do uh
because who knows what they really think
about certain things but this is my
these are my thoughts
these are my thoughts about it and
i love i love my kfp i love my community
i love you chickens
i love everyone who gives me
a chance and supports me and i will
never be angry at you guys i could never
i could never be angry at you guys
just wanna let you guys know that i love
you okay let's play this game
[Music]
okay let's see how many uh
controls i remember
nice okay i love you
[Music]
okay so we went back here to buy some
stuff
how do i do i just how do i get back or
just jump into the void
uh wait how does this work again
do i just jump into the air to get back
to where i was
i love you oh can i the statue
huh i have to ride the birthday
just jump in the hole okay
[Music]
oh my god you i thought you were a cute
cat but you're disgusting
okay no you're cute it's okay but i
remember the time when you looked like a
[\h__\h] terrifying monster
let's come with me come with me
you have a human face it scares me
how do i get over there okay
[Music]
at night it always turns into a
different creature
[Music]
i'm short on money i'm not gonna waste
my money like that but god that pisses
me off so much because i'm just playing
around with the controls
[Music]
i
okay nothing happened
[Music]
is there is there a faster way to reload
really
not that i know of i was trying to find
them uh
out how to eat the baby from the
child hello what what am i doing
no no no stop
what is that anyway
[Music]
use the shield for god's sake
i don't know how to play this game
what is that
[Music]
ah you probably won't subscribe to me
but i don't want to talk to him where he
says
[Music]
stupid
okay let's go flying guys
with you shut up
and pick you up
how do i throw him yeah lamb wire plants
[Music]
thanks very soon so how do i throw you
down there
hold the remote up oh
[Music]
wait how do i fix my camera
wait i'm so sorry i feel so bad he's
still not attacking me i'm surprised
where's it going
well um it probably knows where my house
is
it's probably gonna attack me this night
when i sleep ah it's going back to its
usual spot
oh man i feel so bad it's flying with
its ears
cute
[Music]
okay
okay i'm going going fine i don't know
why i can't just go
straight for god's sake
[Music]
okay
is
it is possible to descend a specific
bird statue on the surface after you
have already visited it and i have
[Music]
oh i thought that was my i was trying to
move my controller
that was my in controller in front of
the text
and press a to confirm it destination
here no i know
[Music]
right this one right okay
i don't have to do it myself anyway nah
oh
uh grab it go up can i go up
uh-huh and then turn around
turn around turn it um
[Music]
go down a bit
slightly okay and
finish up okay swing
one more oh this is fine let's go
[Music]
wait i'm still playing for the obs
screen i'm crazy oh
when that
[Music]
oh a new area deep woods
oh
okay thank you for telling me where the
hell i am
how do i focus on someone again
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
beauty
are you kidding me
[Music]
why did they attack me do i need to
shoot them
[Music]
no don't drink it
how do i use you there we go
is this what i'm supposed to do i'm so
sorry i don't want i didn't want to do
this but
the game basically forced me to do it
mostly
who dropped an item
not that one
[Music]
take the beehive oh
okay it seems like i can't get that one
but but
maybe the other one it's gone by now
these spawns
so fast
[Music]
you always have to do this is there no
like simple button i can press
well this one i cannot pick up well
goddammit okay
[Music]
okay i hate this i hate this
i am i'm doing i'm doing it okay
whatever just
go back like that go like that
that just doesn't work if you tap that
[Music]
eye
i forgot is it important
what's here ah shortcut we can make a
shortcut
[Music]
i don't want to go on top of it
wait can i go back up too please say yes
oh look nice
[Music]
hold focus shake both
isn't that just the whale went ah on
hello
i can talk to you from here
i've got something i need a headboard
come over here take a look i
don't know if i have time for that right
[Music]
no no no but
don't no
[Music]
rare shield why the [\h__\h] does it not
always have the shield out
okay how does this
[Applause]
it's gonna take a while for me to get
used to these controls i'm so horrible
right now you can take put the shield
away put the shield away
okay so what do we do about this
oh i guess i gotta go over there
[Music]
whoa okay lime water energy let's go
are we doing fine really long rope
i don't see any there i think we gotta
go this way
yeah new memory mode yeah i showed them
in the members only stream
hope you're enjoying them i think it
wants me
to shoot him from here oh wait you said
uh ah okay okay the topping worked okay
did i kill you from here can i even do
that or can i only stun you
i think oh no wait wait wait can i go
back
oh no how do i oh okay i have to
no he's coming over here now for god's
sake
go back go back back
well yeah you can get rid of those
things
they don't attack you you're kidding me
also how are you smart enough to balance
your body
on top of that huh i don't believe it
what if i shoot you now
[Music]
no wait why did i get the
item this time is it random
okay
i'm so bad
go walk no
[Music]
what is jostling can you just
walk oh my god
[Music]
what
shake it also which one is red mind them
both black
well i guess it's the right one and i
don't understand
it doesn't move at all
[Music]
i [\h__\h] hate link this is gonna be a
relationship like with me and mario
it's not gonna be a good one oh my god
link's cuter that is true
i'm blowing my uh i'm just blowing my
teeth i'm not like hyperventilating
you thought i was just that mad
oh my god okay yes oh yeah drinking
emotes
what what the hell you want from me
oh my god you know rope is my biggest
[\h__\h] enemy
why is it not wanting me to jostle
anymore
now he wants me to balance why is the
difference
what i'm doing except i hate this
[Music]
what do you want from me you better make
it over there you better make it over
there
you better [\h__\h] you are such a
[Music]
[\h__\h]
yeah you gotta pick that one up huh you
have to pick that one up
all the times we missed it this time you
really have to go get it right
can you fall over on the other side
perhaps so we can go past
it what is going on
yeah fall down on that sign
and just skull
[Music]
for completion's sake
huh
i don't think anyone who played this
game ever had a worse time than i did
with the [\h__\h] ropes
[Music]
i had a lot of issues really i had the
same experience really
i think part of it is maybe because of
the like how i play the game like in fro
squeeze in front of a computer
i don't know maybe that's like maybe it
doesn't like being
in this kind of oh my god oh yeah
holy [\h__\h]
okay oh oh they got the good stuff i
could have easily
jumped uh walked past that but good that
i stayed huh
abs should i save
save and quit yeah i already want to
race quit already
[Music]
eh yeah
that was a nice strike yo
what
[Music]
i have to sprint
grass also drops hard sometimes right
well it's not that bad
only half a heart okay so sprint
okay
[Music]
one more
oh yeah right that's a thing
i'm
[Music]
okay there we go yeah i deserve those
hearts i need them
thank you oh man
i thought you know if this wasn't the
motion controls game then i would
probably be
a bit better at it yeah oh manny
little chest what do we have
nice
okay yeah motion controls i mean they're
they
they did quite well but i'm just i still
suck at them
so what is it
[Music]
could not have been better no yeah i
still belong to one of these ones just
now it looks like
uh just just like something i've seen
you guys answered text
the cube the [\h__\h] kill
game killed better
violence right yep this is one of the
things that uh who live english uh
was looking for all this time i thought
i thought
for um i was gonna sell it on the
marketplace
but all i think was paid way more money
for it
the gods were said to have lost my heart
for the hero of your legend
pretty amazing right i even fought up on
them for these things
i have been calling them goddess girls
make sense right um those ancient texts
say some real interesting stuff about
these things
how did this go again let me see uh
[Music]
someone fought the light from a heavenly
place and
made the swords monster received so
there you have it
i see you've got yourself a sword under
what do you say we try and crack the
mystery of this cube together
yeah yeah i would never stop talking oh
this group is made of some sort of metal
i've never seen
i have whales on it but we have whaled
on it
but nothing happens
i only know whaling from godzilla games
you know but
i would say the key to cracking this up
is that one line
you know the light from the heavenly
blade yeah yeah yeah
you beat up the cube basically wow
and he couldn't do any damage to it well
it obviously looks like something that i
have to
you know handle uh wait
[Music]
okay
did you see that the cube shut up into
the sky
oh finger reacted to the one you beam
thing that shot out of your sword
and right think to keep signing off to
anyhow
this mystery just got a whole lot more
uh
mysterious mr
stop miss diary iris miss iris
cyrus the turks
said there are cubes like that one all
over this land
tell you what you placed as many of
those cubes as you can find
if you find out more about them along
the way you can't see me
okay as long as you stop talking to me
because my fruit is not
feeling well let's see
oh how do i get you do i have to shoot
[Music]
you
well i'm not going to waste my money on
that anymore and my my
my thing is yourself
roll to the train ah
okay wait
[Music]
other side i know it worked
okay i can't cut the flowers interesting
so
i still can't get it to the other side
though
interesting did i miss something
on the left i can't ah over there
yeah it feels good to cut that grass yo
kusa very very kusa
what's up okay
[Music]
what did you guys think of the video by
the way i was awake
i was awake when it came up i watched it
sorry we couldn't watch it together but
[Music]
it was interesting cool sorry about
exactly my thoughts man
how did you know man
[Music]
did i accidentally write a comment that
totally didn't want to do that
that was by accident i just slipped out
of my mind
out of my mind what was that song what
was that song again
out of my mind i don't mind
[Music]
what am i thinking of
right out of my mind
[Music]
sunrise avenue yeah i think that was
probably it you know
boomer stuff oh link don't die on me
[Music]
you know what was fun like when you're
young and you first hear about this
series
and uh you don't know much about it yet
and uh
[Music]
you think that the green boy is zelda
oh what well
he isn't
but don't worry i know i know for a long
time now that that's not the case
that was probably the entry entrance
door huh but i want to check out this
side too
[Music]
wait what is the wiser grave there who
died
who died
[Music]
shame who is that
he who descended from above look to the
star
that the bird rising heaven sword gazes
upon
heaven ward and aim your shot there you
want me to shoot a bird in the sky
that's a bird right here
bob bob williams
[Music]
is this a bird is this how i open the
door
or do i just open it normally a sail
shot i fought so
but it's going to be easy because i just
do this
and i shoot well i should have maybe
shot it towards this thing
wait wait for it
[Music]
yeah no wait
can i shoot that ah
[\h__\h] with the camera ah wait i can't
stay like that okay
uh that is difficult to control maybe i
just use uh
i have it
[Music]
okay her father wants me to use my laser
lisa okay
open the door
this is how you get into doors even if
you don't have the key bring your
slingshot guys
[Music]
are we going in here because you think
zelda is in here i doubt it
i doubt it
but i wanna eat snack
skyview temple wow first dungeon
master i have bad news the aura of many
creatures
reverberate throughout this temple
as a result i can't isolate zelda's aura
you will not be able to track her here
given the situation i suggest you look
around to see where we should move next
okay thank you
sounds good to me
all right
[Music]
no no
hmm
[Music]
nice okay
ah what do we have here
[Music]
panic always works
oops what the [\h__\h] is that
[Music]
okay easy that won't stop me
i'm exhausted tooling already
about okay that was enough good
[Music]
double kill give me the coin
what do we have here oh
i suppose later maybe that's a shortcut
maybe
oh cut it all
cut it off what does that mushroom do
oh it's grass
can i like a bit lower yeah
i split it through the middle how did i
do that no
it disappeared completely nice
hello
[Music]
i'm making what for the fire on my
chimney i don't have a chimney but i'm
making wood for it anyway
so this one is closed okay so we gotta
go upwards
watch waking my shot yeah
i kind of thought that that would happen
so
it was kind of to be expected
[Applause]
on that okay
[Music]
good job on taking your medicine your
own medicine [\h__\h]
oh wait i don't have to use this right i
can just hit it hit it
yeah what happens
the door opens okay
[Music]
okay
oh there must be a hint on this
gravestone again
he who descended from the sky are you
talking to link huh
lend your ear to the wise voice of the
servant who brought you to the firm soil
what you want me to listen hey listen
my mom's can't pick me up
[Music]
ah use feet ah
oh
[Music]
um
follows my sword
[Music]
um
ah
[Music]
okay wait
okay thank you chad i wouldn't have
gotten that idea on my own i think
i'm scared mama
what the hell one's done what was that
i don't want to ask people things people
fans i have
i have a chat
we're doing fine do we want to go
straight first
[Music]
fell down and i couldn't react it wasn't
there though i saw it
i saw it i will try to activate it next
[Music]
ah time i go back up okay
boys boys boys both joey comes down
okay okay it's happening so fast that i
can't really
like react to it because i don't know
what to do
if i knew what to do maybe i would know
maybe i could do it
[Music]
should we go on is there no other door
open
[Music]
nope okay so i guess we gotta do this
one first
okay now drink tea before it gets cold
um
[Music]
that reminds me of there's another zelda
game what the [\h__\h]
uh do i have to shoot you
[Music]
scary spiders
i'm not um it
attack you from the other side
horizontal spin attack
i don't know if i can do that
[Music]
oh good these ones are
they're okay of cute
but i'll give that to you
i wanna i want some help please
give me help no i'm not dead
oh link goes mall
whoa what do we have a statue
oh it opens the next door perhaps it's a
bed
okay
[Music]
oh
oh [\h__\h] did i do that too early
like how do i diet what it
i have to go up here ah
okay i thought i had the diet pack
realized well link cannot die
where do we get out here okay well i
still gotta fight you
[Laughter]
[Music]
ew will you drop
one coin only is going to the ground i
can't even pick it up
ew what does it say
two doors lead to rooms left and right
but they will only open when the
gemstones are struck
yeah okay one is above one below
and i went to the one below
this one is the other one how do i get
to the other side
can i not go there yet
and you gotta go back because with the
water activated
we can probably go to another room now
and maybe come from the other
side to get there eventually
okay so
what is water now
[Music]
where are we able to go
um yeah zelda logic exactly let's just
jump into the water
sealer where read
[Music]
oh there is a coin
yeah nice hat thank you
crossing the road do i look like a
chicken to you
i don't crossroads i fly over them
[Music]
don't answer that yeah you don't have to
answer it it might be smart to not
answer it
um so uh the door opened which one was
it
[Music]
wait no that's where i went through this
one open
is this a new door
hello and i'm new here i just moved in
recently why did you not notice me
what's wrong with you
you got eggs in your eyes
[Music]
hey
do i have to cut the spiderweb first
how would i do that make my laser
[Music]
um
all right i saw you
i gotcha yeah can i get the other one
too from here
i do okay okay okay
strain please
wait maybe you go down a little bit my
dear link can you go down a bit
[Applause]
okay what was that what was that what i
[Music]
said
oh
[Music]
love
did it drop anything
the pointy ends
[Music]
okay what did you say in a room with two
glittering
glittering glittering gemstones you
shall find a temple map
gaze upon that map until your eye finds
the eggs
for it is there that you must strike
another gemstone
to reveal okay well well
okay i think i understand
um
[Music]
what's inside
they have dungeon maps oh yeah
i remember
don't you always get like in most zella
games
you get like two special items like
first of all you always get the dungeon
map first
and then second of all later you get
like a one special item
from each dungeon like like for example
i don't know some weapon right
uh and the key huh ah the compass the
compass
that was it sorry yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah it also reveals the location
of treasure chest so be sure to take a
look
master i have information for you you
have obtained a map of this area you can
view it by pressing
minus the position of doors in their
locks
as well as the position and status of
treasure chests
can be confirmed on the map with marks
such as x
however be aware that you will be unable
to use bacons here to the
indoor nature of this environment
okay minus huh
okay wait what does the x do again what
are the axis again doors
and what are the x's again it is a trans
chassis
zelda you're really there oh
no united
[Music]
well this dungeon isn't that big
so okay
[Music]
let um get rid of those now
stop blocking sometimes
what did it drop
[Music]
double date stream that sounds like a
cute idea oh you know what
maybe i mean it's probably going to turn
into a japanese
um japanese like only stream but how
about
mario party with takamoti and noah
foreign
because that's four people perfect for
mario party
wouldn't that be adorable
[Music]
oh my god that's such a good idea maybe
i should ask right now
but maybe it shouldn't be on my channel
because if it's going to be japanese
only anyway we should do it on like
maybe
senpai or fruity advent channel
[Music]
double date cute good
write that down write that down
oh we can do it both on template let me
send by two that's right but i i kind of
played with both times empire already
true true but i do like norfolk a lot
because i am just a sucker for first gen
you know i don't know about you guys but
i'm just
i'm a sucker for virgin man
i love them yeah
you feel me you feeling me
i'm opening another cookie cookie
absolutely yeah they are so strong man
i love them
[Music]
inside i know like damn gods
divine
which i could understand them well there
are a lot of clips
at least
[Music]
yeah life translators too that's right
um oh wait we're in the middle room
again
[Music]
oh we fell down and got into them oh i
just realized
wait did i mess up
because from there i could have probably
gone over there
and i said should i go back find the
other x wait a second
[Music]
what you want from me we found
did i even find the youngs
no wait a second
go back let's go back
[Music]
hmm
how did i miss that i was just
it i just didn't look how did i miss
that
not done
[Music]
hmm
yeah because of the spiders
[Music]
um
oh i think you're in the same same place
sorry guys i'm kind of taking it easy
today because this is my third stream
today
i want to save some energy you know
so it's just a chill zelda stream
so where are we going now uh well we got
the water
let me see what do we have nothing here
i mean we can go to that door but i
can't i can't open it
[Music]
may i wait wait wait wait with the water
level rising
maybe we can do something in the first
room now
[Music]
was this the first one
okay uh no i thought that maybe the
water would be so high that we could
reach the other side
now that is not the case but is there
anything else i can reach
[Music]
no
i did activate the x dough
[Music]
what am i missing
anything up here i want to go over there
right
wait a second
is there something here something
ah wait i know this
wait i should fight the spider
let me go up please please please please
please let me get on top of the tree
come on
[Music]
can i not okay well that's so annoying
how do i get up
late you don't have those survival
skills i need the breath of the wild
link right now right here
as weak as hell from you
oh shh
don't run away come back here
okay there we go now we can go out
get the coin get the rupee no
it's not always right to aim for the
money
when when the money
gets you off road that's that's when you
have to realize
you have to focus on your goal what is
your goal link
getting zelda it's not to become rich
although that might impress zelda but
i think zelda is the type of girl that
will love you for who you
are right yeah
hashtag philosophical phoenix hello
you do be looking at me huh okay let's
fight
[Music]
okay i need more height
okay going for a little swim that was
100 planned
i don't want to use my potion wait
can i go can i get back no
i can't get back there i need to
oh i see how this is you get
bishop what's bishop in english again
uh what's the word again
punished you get punished funny little
mistakes huh
it's not bad
okay no problem
can you give me a heart
and you ask nicely i didn't even say
please
[Music]
i don't like this guy
okay i think i got it
there we go that's what i'm talking
about now let's make you dizzy
[Music]
sink
okay don't have to do them both at once
look at me yeah that's right no don't
look away
[Music]
face your fate don't run away is this
gonna work
[Music]
okay how about now you want to talk now
oh there we go looking
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay ah that one door
that we were missing in the main room
let's go back this way
[Music]
move the keys
leave it to me
[Music]
this door that's the one i'm coming for
you
[Music]
nice jump open up fbi
i gotta bring my tears so much but it's
getting cold
i put a lot of honey in it
fbatta that's uh
yeah oh wow it's a big room
i see that i see that in front of me
let's see where we are in the mouth
okay oh first of all
do this one nice
[Music]
okay the middle one was there no water
door open
for it hold on
i like the atmosphere here it's really
pretty
it didn't give me the prompts again
oh no you make me lose my heart skin
are you a heart challenger
run run run run run away
hallelujah
[Music]
suddenly have the urge to stream high
challenge i don't know where that comes
from
oh i don't want to drink my holy water
um so
i need it for whatever boss fight comes
here
important times but even then i would
probably panic and be like how do i use
it how do i use it
[Applause]
[Music]
can i get the heart down from that wait
hmm no do i have to shoot it
i don't know oh what is that
what is that
that doesn't work
i am surprised and disappointed
but we have three heights again we
challenge your spider again
i'll get a little bit later okay well i
do want to kill you though
i'm pissed
okay [\h__\h] you
[Music]
what's the cat what's the cat's review
huh
[Music]
can you focus it on
um
okay well i got a few hits yeah yeah
okay i need to learn how to [\h__\h]
block but okay
that was easy so weak the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay i panicked i panicked but we did
well
[Music]
what the hell unexplained power
container when this insect shaped item
allows you to control it
as it flies through the air point the
cursor where you want it to go
and press set r to send it soaring
[Music]
okay
you have quite a new item analysis of
this object's insect-like profile
and wings indicates it can fly
after launching it you can remotely
pilot the device
the sharp structure on the front of the
device consider
the food friends and deliver a blow to
smaller apps so like the box
on the stream press set r to ready the
device for takeoff and press
right to learn more about its operations
[Music]
let's get the heart uh
one more time a bit higher
how long do you fly though oh thank you
thank god
uh how long can i fly let's get the box
movie
oh it feels like i can fly forever
put it yeah
[Music]
open the [\h__\h] door
no the fairy
so how do i get out so i have to open it
up again
i switch
[Music]
okay no one more time a bit higher
go go go go yeah i'm not getting that
i'm not getting that
uh fairy
okay let's let's take a look
can i make a big leap
uh is this how drones work huh
okay now i can do this
okay turn
why is it like that again
now the door is open again i was stuck
but i am no more stuck
for sure noise
i didn't want to end up like that
skeleton right in there
although maybe callie would like me more
if i was a skeleton
[Music]
i hate you so much
why am i even fighting you you don't
give me anything anyway
okay ah
[Music]
and i tagged all of the beetle really
that would be divine
[Music]
i wanted i wanted the fairy though
that would have been nicer
[Music]
but okay okay let's see
if i if i cut the string
maybe
[Music]
oh just some money okay
well let's do this again
[Music]
go
oh
juicy a juicy
all right all right all right we're back
on track we're killing those enemies
like they're flying obviously but
i would like to proceed where do we go
which oh well
where do i continue can i um wait wait
it's still there
um
[Music]
uh uh you have to go slowly
fairy this playful sprite will flashes
six of your hearts doesn't also keep me
from dying
oh nice i need that automatic heel i
need that
because i'm just really horrible at
using items at the right time
[Music]
let's get you down there too from your
throne i think you're cool on something
special
i have oops no mercy no mercy for
spiders like you
[Music]
okay this one can maybe only be killed
with a fatal blow huh
there's no other way to do it i i reckon
[Music]
okay so we eliminated everyone
uh there are a lot of these little
thingies i i suppose that in one of them
maybe there is a another thing to open
another door
and have a switch
let's see i mean i'm really bad at
piloting this right now
oh oh my god what is you ignore me
it isn't there
it is indeed there
just gotta be careful
[Music]
check him out
thank you for the membership welcome
[Music]
okay why is there a safe point right
here
is it gonna be dangerous in there
[Music]
hello
how many dungeons are there in this game
by the way
please let me know
seven i wonder how long each one takes
maybe we can do like one dungeon per
episode or something like that or maybe
sometimes too if it's a short one
thank you for the membership welcome
but there's time in between the dungeons
too of course so
question is how long does that stuff
take
i have to repeat some oh dear oh my god
okay hello
yeah eat this
[Music]
that's it that's it that's all i have to
do
[Music]
well you know today i'm pretty exhausted
and the week has been really exhausting
too
um so i'll finish the dungeon but i
don't know if i'll play much more
after that
the other one won't open so maybe i have
to go up
[Music]
thank you guys for understanding how to
do it from here
no
thank you thank you
oh wait maybe i have to do something
with the beetle but oh well oh
well for now i'll shoot down those
thingies
lunch go
hats many hearts
well i only need one but i'll i'll take
it thank you
how kind of you the current 80 percent
speed run record for this game is 4
hours 47 minutes damn
well but that person knew what the hell
he was doing
i have no idea what i'm doing
i understand completely okay that will
like put me on the higher level so the
upper eye can see me too
okay
i see i see i see how the hell
were those spider webs able to hold that
though
this game took me like 40 what don't say
that that's gonna scare me i thought i
could uh
wait 40 hours actually nevermind on
stream yeah that makes sense though
that's like six seven
eight streams you know it sounded like
really long to me just now but never
mind
i stream a lot of hours
so we're gonna be fine how do i get out
there go
nice and they're looking at me i
know i'm beautiful i'm sexy and i know
it
doo i'm sexy and i know
it yeah
you know you want you don't want to
close your eyes you know you're not
getting sick of this yet i understand
you want to see more i know
i know
hey hey listen
there we go why the circles i'm trying
well they got sick of me eventually
hopefully you guys never get sick of me
you better or not
thank you enjoying 100 thank you
okay so we go outside again
which door is that key for piano
oh what is that really where it came
from
wait isn't that is that another new door
that opened
why did that come from
did i come from the top yes wait
oh
i think
we'll deal with whatever is in front of
me um
ah no i just walked out that i said okay
that stuff up there kind of confused me
what is this battle music it's above me
i can't find it when i can't see it i
didn't wait no i did not
i did not come from what
okay i would like to uh
proceed but i guess i can't proceed here
[Music]
i understand
i see it
[Music]
real gut always man
are you not
[Music]
let's go for this side yeah smoove
smooth club
yeah we got it
and the water again i see
oh my god my friend sent me a million
voice messages i don't know what you
i can't listen to those now oh well
[Music]
by the way guys i i'm gonna try to make
the schedule
for next week and
after this stream it's already pretty
late here but i'm gonna get it done
wait
was that what was that where
yeah i'm planning minecraft for tomorrow
but i'm not sure yet at what time also i
did something weird
just now with my headphones there we go
okay yeah well
don't be too excited there's not many
streams next week
[Music]
toy
are you taking a break not really i'm
going somewhere for work
you guys will be able to watch it i'm
going to docomi
but even though
the event for me is only for one day
i'll be gone for quite long
sorry about that
but i kind of feel like a little break
would be good again anyway i mean
i feel like what it was a beacon
i feel a bit weird because i i i just
took a break i went to greece like just
recently
where when was that was that in june or
july
never mind actually it's already been
almost two months since
wait it's already that wasn't the
beginning of june no
i go back on it feels like it was just
super recently but actually time passes
so
fast it's already august now
oh my god
[Music]
oh come on
just can't fly where i want to fly to
[Music]
can you go a bit higher
yeah near end of
what no was it not in the beginning of
[Music]
june
yeah these last past two weeks whenever
i had a day
off on my schedule
[Music]
um i
i was still working on stuff like i
actually didn't have a proper day off
for weeks now
you came back went to the hospital and
then went to the main review yeah that
was uh
exhausting too yeah
anyway so uh sorry this is this place is
confusing where do i go next
i have a key for that place right
probably
oh yeah can i cut you too
wait mom
[Music]
i want the heart i don't need it right
now anyway never mind
let me cut you i don't eat it
one more
you were no challenge for me
how's the neck i said this a few days
ago but like i mean generally when i'm
in a normal position
it's fine but i definitely feel um
that there is still something broken
in there like it's still strained
um yeah wait it is not not healed
yet even though it's already been to
moms what did the doctor say back then
how many weeks did he say three four
weeks oh my god i hate this so much
is there something down there i wanna
get
[Music]
no oh no
any physical therapy no well the doctor
also didn't like
say anything that that is necessary
but yeah i should i should go to our
wheel doctor
i know i know okay
you know what i will try to go after the
company
i'll try to make time after dokomi when
i come back
[Music]
i said that already what did i say
already
y'all should have to fight this thing
with are you even a boss you don't
really look like
you're kind of lame now why are you not
noticing me yet
why are you not noticing me let me try
to attack you
okay so that doesn't really do anything
anyway you notice me hello
don't tell me that wasn't many of us
i have less problems with that than with
the spiders
young
[Music]
i mean that's one thing i've noticed
about you know i told you
i was watching other people or one
person play
other double games and um
and i really liked watching that
person's uh playthroughs but one thing
i've noticed is that the bosses
not only the mini bosses but also also
the real bosses
their weakest bulk i got lucky with my
sword this time
perhaps okay but still uh
bosses in most zelda games are weak as
hell
yeah which i mean might not necessarily
be a bad thing but i can see why
a lot of people would want it to be more
challenging
i mean being able to kill a final boss
of a dungeon in one minute is
sad and the fight that i've seen like
gone on fights
in some zelda games is also
disappointing because ganon is supposed
to be this like super overpowered
thing that that is the reason why that
game exists in the first place right
because there's trouble because of ghana
and that's why the game is going on
there
during that time but then
being able to kill ganon so [\h__\h]
easily once
something's wrong there let me drink my
teeth
i mean i would probably still have
issues obviously
i like the way you say ghana oh i guess
it's like
in english it's like ganon ganon
the cannon okay so what do we have
we're gonna cut that through
wait no look look straight
[Music]
like that ow
easy i think i have to send my beetle
over there
and through that little thingy is that a
thing could that be
and turn it around like a key
am i the team but i'm probably too far
away now
[Music]
okay i thought okay i was wrong
i thought i was being real smart right
now
[Music]
yeah yeah okay i see you i see uh that
is probably a final though i wouldn't be
able to open it that easily right now
huh
seems like the looks like a final door
that would have been a neat solution
kind of uh
i mean they both have a golden color so
i thought it would be fitting
[Music]
all right next door open
up
[Music]
let's try it again i'll try again
okay i i think it fits but it just
doesn't want me to come for
yet it looks like a special chest
i want that by the way we missed um
we missed the heart uh container in the
in the forest there is one there too
i forgot where but i know there is one
so we gotta get that eventually
so okay what do we have
uh i wait fly it
switch up on which statue from the place
where it just came from
oh yeah i already huh switch it
let's just shoot it oh wait i see i see
this one
that's probably not gonna be necessary
right now
at the very top here
at the top of the previous room
okay but let me check out what we got
here
yeah oh what is there what do we have
there
whoa whoa i'm not going places now
they got around this room
nice jump nice jump
did i miss something here
[Music]
this room the other way the central room
oh i didn't mess anything here all right
you know what's with ina
hey what are you guys saying you know is
ina in the chat
[Music]
huh i was looking at the chat the whole
time i don't see her
the bottom
why
i i know i i kind of know why
but it's still weird because like i have
this thing
on this on this obs scene um
yeah but that should only act what the
hell okay well
when someone joins our like a specific
room
like discord room and voice channel
then uh those pop up
[Music]
weird i wonder why she's in that room to
begin with anyway
um interesting but
yo that gave me firemen flashbacks right
yeah
yeah that was just a discord gimmick um
because she joined the voice chat there
i guess wow i gave me a shock too for a
moment
fire emblem flashback funny
okay so when you say up there
[Music]
on top of that statue
that was really close
[Music]
container
okay what do we do next
it's okay i went here but i couldn't go
over there
i activated that switch
maybe i should try more but there's
nothing here
maybe we should try more of these little
holes up there
what's up there
[Music]
i want the money i want the money i want
the money yeah
[Music]
back to the livestream the one that i
just came from
wait i heard something what was that
i was already here before right
[Music]
doko
what do you want
yeah i just noticed too thank you for
letting me know
please the chat
master potential you you have a maximum
roofing
go spend some money on me now please
give me some pocket money i will take it
off of your hands
sorry i need to i need to understand
where the hell i need to go now
oh there's that last room
the one we just came from maybe yeah you
know what there was a lot to do there
maybe the the thingies
[Music]
i mean that's so far away
but wait what if i go around
maybe i can open that thing from the
other side
[Music]
can i open that
nope okay ah
there's a rope to walk on here
i was right what this
well i'll do that first
ouch eat it
and then you welcome egg
welcome to the membership
this will i mean [\h__\h] this will be
useful at some point
one more time
you like the flying club thingy uh
it's okay it's an interesting
item for the dungeon but wait are
dungeon items like that
uh usable after the dungeon two in this
game
[Music]
yeah they are okay oh there's a [\h__\h]
rope here
oh but he's gonna attack me isn't he i
gotta stun him first
uh
[Music]
you fell down into the nothingness bye
bye my friend okay no not this [\h__\h]
again
[Music]
okay you can do this link you can do
this yeah yeah yeah you're doing it
right yeah
finally go go run that wall
run away walk that runway whatever i
can't speak english unbelievable
why am i in whole live english sometimes
i wonder oh
hello little chest don't give me money i
already have enough money give me
something else
thank you
send it to my bank please my bank
account
how do i get there is that
that seems like a jump that is not
doable
well
[Music]
that sounds familiar to me
isn't it isn't that
and that the image is well
[Music]
why why are you so stupid
do i have to do oh
oh it was not supposed to be walked on
[Music]
okay
i'm not i'm not i'm not doing this
for like on purpose um
believe me [\h__\h] oh my god okay
i thought i was bombing down shinokato
okay
so scared to fall down here
okay be careful link you're such a klutz
honestly oh we're getting
is that the master key the master key is
that what you call in the key for that
big door
that's why the chest looks so special
[Music]
is funny because i am kiana
your boss
so so
that's that's that's funny um
that is the fun that is fun
[Music]
i i'm glad i'm not losing am i losing
anything when i fall down there because
i'm not losing hp
[Music]
hey let me go down go down
or maybe no maybe i should be higher
maybe i should be behind
b higher bees you need higher bees
instead of chicken
i don't know what i'm saying anymore
[Laughter]
okay
maybe i should be lower
[Music]
okay don't fall down anymore please link
please i beg you okay
now it's the goal is straight in front
of us
okay that's the only one you pretty
happy i'm gonna go
[Music]
okay
that was by accident
[Music]
pickle
you
[Music]
i just wanted to jump now
is the boss fight happening then after
this am i already done with this dungeon
is this it this is it
oh my i mean it's obviously a bus
bus door in front of me and the same one
coin
i might have trouble with it oh i see
yeah okay if you say that then i believe
you
ah
this now could be tough oh that is that
about the payback that i get for
roasting
zela games with easy bosses
[Music]
foreign
okay well that's fun ah
[Music]
oh magic insert
wow
that's cool
h what are they trying to tell me
what are you doing
yo we are all freaking hikikomori don't
blind us with that
light like that my people are using dark
mode most of them even
give them a break oh
you look funny uh what do we do
[Music]
i found the tornado i stood up
would have just and torn you apart yet
here you are
not in pieces
[Music]
not that your life or death has any
consequence
it's just a girl that matters now and i
can sense her here
just beyond this door
yes we plucked her back to see from her
perch in the clouds and now she's
ours
but listen to me i'm being positively
uncivil
allow me to introduce myself
[Music]
i am the demon lord who presides over
this land you look down
upon this world you call the surface
you may call me
in truth what's that
i very much prefer to be indulged with
my full
title like his voice broke or something
[Music]
lord kira him but i'm
not fuzzy
[Music]
did you really just draw your sword
foolish boy
by all rights the girl should have
fallen into our hands already
she was nearly the house when that knows
some servant of the goddess snatched
away
do you have any idea how that made me
feel insane
this turn of events has left me with a
strong appetite for bloodshed
still it hardly seems fair
being of my position to take all of my
anger out onto you
which is why i promise up front
not to murder you
no i just beat you within an inch of
your life is
disgusting perfect
oh you're working really slow okay okay
okay that gives me some time to
assess the situation oh sexy walk my
hands are sweating
let's see what we do
easy easy
[Music]
yes
i don't understand
well i still have taken no damage you're
trying to attack me a lot
who is fighting are you fighting me who
are you fighting
i'm okay
[Music]
you see that
i look at this beach okay i'm looking
[Music]
respectfully
did you see that
[Music]
okay
come on
[Music]
you missed [\h__\h]
oh you wanna you wanna dash at me
wait wait wait i don't
[Music]
you shouldn't have think right in front
of me i don't want to get close to me
yeah i know you do everyone wants that
hey
[Music]
wow well
you put me up more of a fight than i
would have thought
possible out of such a soft boy
but don't clap for yourself quite yet
the sword of yours is the only reason
you still live
i fear i spend far too long teasing and
toying with you
the girl's presence has all but faded
from this place which means
there is no reason to linger here
goodbye
sky child run and play this time
get in my way again though and you were
dead
[Music]
oh my god
yay thank you he did he didn't even hit
me once okay
did he i don't remember him hitting me
at all
he did once okay well i'll give him that
heart container life increased by one
yeah
i came for that though all right so i
gotta go for that okay
yeah with a projectile streaming heart
container
[Music]
he licked my ear yeah that was
disgusting and also at the same time
tingly
[Music]
i see fishies can i catch up there she
is
now i'm good zelda is not here anymore
huh
but it's so peaceful and nice here
wow
[Music]
the bibs the burps guys
skyview spring is beautiful hello oh
those birds are so cute
not as cute as you guys though you guys
are cuter
that's me on that one
[Music]
do i have this i know what i have to do
i know i know
[Music]
wow
wow oh
cutscene let's go
he looks content just like me
[Music]
master i have a message written in the
language of the gods of old allow me to
translate for you
[Music]
from the end of time i guide you
the one chosen to carry out the goddess
mission
the spirit maiden who descended from the
clouds must travel to
sacred places to purify her body
you stand in one of those places skyview
spring
the other is known as the earth spring
[Music]
was she still singing no the second
spring is hidden away
deep within the scorched earth of eldon
the spirit maiden ever mindful of the
heavy task and trusted to her has set
out for the second sacred place
are you okay are you okay why are you
gonna stop spinning
[Music]
you cat girl she's want to show off her
uh
skills from a previous life bam
you got the ruby tablet the weathered
surface of this heavy stone and tablet
feels very old
we got the second one
[Music]
as i just translated it would appear
that zelda purified herself
in though oh
there was a bgm i thought someone rang
at my bell rang my
ring at my belt proved by herself in the
waters of the spring
i calculate a 97 chance that
she was already set out for ellen where
another great spring
exists however it is not clear what
method of travel
zelda used to move from here to her next
destination
can i ask one question if zelda is
traveling alone
how does she know like what she has to
do right now how does she know that she
has to go to this other spring and clean
herself because she dirty
how does she know does she also have a
fee that's telling her
that oh i guess she's not alone huh
makes sense
my analysis suggests you should take the
tablet
to the altar in skyloft doing so will
likely open a new column of light on the
surface
allowing you to descend to another area
and continue your search for zelda
let's return to the sky once more before
continuing our search the bird statue
outside can take us back up
all right
[Music]
that was a fun dungeon
hello little baby hi it's mcqueen
you'll find a girl no
oh that's too bad but it sounds like you
at least know where you need to search
next to find her quick
that's something nice you're so kind i
finally been reunited about my keep my
friends it's all thanks to you
cool
[Music]
all right we did it i'm so proud but
it's only been two hours uh we're gonna
do some more i guess
and let's see did i just say
[Music]
hold on yes
great super chats no i don't want to
only play two hours it's like nothing
it's nothing it's not enough
okay we're not gonna fight you though
we need to go and waste our money
we have too much money where do i go
like for real does it want me to go back
to the island from here
no way i want that heart container ah
but i just know it's in the forest i
don't know where exactly
where the seconds before we go to the
island
oh i should stop collecting money yeah i
want the
i want that island with sky loved
want a container
[Music]
while it's heavy i gotta spin it when it
gets too heavy right
and my name i mean if there's a bank
account that i can use i'll gladly put
it in there as well look
i mean sometimes you gotta treat
yourself
right i see bees
probably not here
well that's great is it already
available for me i wonder
i would like to get it oh dear
can i attack it with this thing as well
i'm so sorry but you're kind of in the
way
disturbing my mission i am i was the
close
i was too close yeah
everywhere uh everywhere there's enemies
where did they go okay they're gone why
not use the slingshot no i don't know
i don't think there's really a
[Music]
difference
come on you used to you did so well in
the dungeon
at that last row balancing mission
now you're trying to annoy me again
you just want to spend more time with me
don't chilling
clap quack quack take the shortcut
you can't go back without the shortcut i
can't go back to the temple
okay i'm going back i'm going back
i can't talk
you're not okay now that's for sure
which short
that one
i tossed him yeah wait am i going wait
which which shortcut do you want me to
use guys
[Music]
is there a shortcut here the one that
looks like steps
[Music]
over there
that over there that's a shortcut
[Music]
huh
go for it here
where you want this one
this one
yeah okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
don't you think you're following me
what's going on isn't that where it just
came from
i hate this i'm on the [\h__\h] roof
again
i didn't want to be on the roof again
let's do it this way
jump off i guess i could
so i don't know where you want me to go
well in another case i want the hey
wait where is where is that i know that
goes outside i don't want to go outside
i think
good do i i'm oh wait no i do
i think i kind of do
yeah yeah the heart container
has to be somewhere here
on this part of the map
[Music]
who's walking i hear some walking noises
can i get
uh was it something with that box over
there
the cube can i reach it from here
no no way
[Music]
hmm but i think it must have been
something with that
tracking was bouncing i don't think so
there was no hard option
hard container options
when i look at the map does anyone know
like in what area
the container is
north south
other side of the tree
and i i know i can get it already
i know it
i know there's one i can get
[Music]
above the lake next to the big tree
you know what the hell
above the link
ah that's
that container there
[Music]
so how do i get up there
from from that side
i want you to fly live for me
[Music]
a slingshot
oh yeah you're telling me
that doesn't do anything
but i want that container
i'm never gonna give it up i'm never
gonna let it down
[Music]
you may not have noticed but i'm trying
to hide here could you please screw it
along before you draw monsters over this
way okay
wow okay
now i know there's one that i can
already get now
i know it
[Music]
ah that one is for the hook shot i see i
see it but then there's a different one
[Music]
there's a different one waterfalls
yeah waiting right up in the waterfalls
behind the waterfall
come on
[Music]
wait no there's nothing
around the big tree it's on a platform
entry
ah uh-huh
that that could be true that is uh
possible how do we get out there again
not there
in the trees
[Music]
uh
that's the one that's the one you see it
on that platform
that's the one i meant not the one with
the slingshot you can get up there too
yeah yeah yeah here here
i could probably even get into the
beetle but there it is see
it's so easy to get you don't need an
extra item for that one
hold on walk
one thing you should be able to do is
walk that's all you need to do
oh yeah no i didn't have this one yet
this one is easy to get so i really
wanted to get it
i'm going to kill you link
i'm going to kill you
i already eliminated
another nintendo icon you don't want to
be the next one
[Music]
so now now i'm okay with going back
uh where is uh
where is the thing to go back probably
through there okay
excuse me don't attack me
no heart really
okay so we're going to wait how do we
get there
up there okay we're going back to our
home because i think that's where the
story wants us to go
right and then a new thingy open so we
can jump into the sky again from there
[Music]
first of all let me say you thank you
thank you thank you and i would like to
also jump
and fly thank you
let's go
where where did that sudden air come
from
what's your favorite tale about them uh
there's a cilia one and two
[Applause]
i think
i also liked this barrier and symphonia
and and every game i played
master link when you hit that that
brought this cube with a skyward strike
earlier
i was able to detect a resulting energy
reaction above the clouds
the location i have marked on your map
indicates the spot where i sense an
energy reaction
oh
i advise you to investigate the area
around this location okay
oh where is it i need to see a bacon
where is the bacon
[Music]
is that the one where the goron was
is that that one
can i make it for that hole come on come
on no
[Music]
empty a wallet first wait is that gonna
bring me money
but then i'm gonna go back first okay
[Music]
i wish i could i mean i can i told him i
can if i wanted to i could
totally fly like that it's nothing
stopping me
nothing at all
whoa oh wait that was ah
[Music]
yeah hookah papa is the one stopping me
from doing it
[Music]
okay let's go shopping do i need
anything though
maybe i can upgrade oh can i repair my
shield it's not really broken but
i wonder if there's something we can get
[Music]
jojo's bizarre adventure
oh wait you have something new
what is that a small seat set so this
and you patrick can
carry additional seats i didn't know i
couldn't carry them at all
slingshot ah even those seats oh yes yes
please
i'm buying that
[Music]
not worth it
oh well we have it now what else did i
buy there's a new shield
but i i don't i still want to use my
current one
well on the other end
roll on the counter on the side
what
[Applause]
i need the iron i need it now right now
okay how much is it
i suppose i should warn you that it
won't protect you from electricity which
would be nasty shock ha ha
hundred okay for the next level ah
my current shield will burn oh no my
pouch is full
what do you mean my power oops what do
you mean my pouch is full
this one can i put that away
do i have like a storage
huh
drop stuff at the item shop oh but wait
i have space here what are you talking
about i guess it is not
[Music]
okay good i am sorry i'm not reading the
voices right now
because of reasons
[Music]
move to stories
okay thank you ladies
[Music]
yeah we've already heard that thank you
is the game's on cracking it's just me i
feel like that too
that sometimes happens with the
game capture thingy
oh maybe it's fixed now
it's best to get the new one where
you're wagging it do you want it
okay thank you you wallet you volunteer
yes stop right okay good
i don't see such a thing second shop
outside
oh do i still have enough money though
[Music]
this one
are you gonna come down oh funny
oh i see that's
cute
and up we go yeah that's a cute store
[Music]
hey i want to go on a vacation with you
i want can i rent this place
oh you have a heart container i waste my
money on some other [\h__\h]
oh it's you here's a win too
oh you oh
you've doubled this weight now what
voice do i want for him
oh you've come all this way it's so rare
to have a customer here
ah because angel has everything you
could ever want please take a look
around
and if you actually buy something that
would be even better
which one should we get we only have 100
left maybe this this
guy's hit this one right oh oh that will
increase the
number of items you can carry in your
adventure pouch by one
it has to be the most useful thing
imaginable for an adventure
and yet three hundred
oh well at first wallet or this one oh
and that's an extra wallet it's
amazingly useful
for this you can carry an extra 300
rupees in your wallet
say goodbye to all those times you
couldn't pick up another ruby because
you want your stuffed full
leave no rupee behind you know even when
you must be able to see but whatever
what the [\h__\h] you're buying already
oh i was able to afford this one
[Music]
you say that island might have some
money then let's go there
oh thank you ever so much man you've
given me the strength to keep pedaling
okay bye-bye i'll come back soon with
more money
[Music]
does it even matter where i jump off of
this island doesn't matter it doesn't
i just don't know what to press okay and
i pressed some things
i didn't know what it was
all right
get that money it better be money i can
jump from anywhere okay
[Music]
that's it that's it
yours we're almost there
it's a pumpkin the big pumpkin what does
this place
someone live there
and there we go ouch okay
nice
[Music]
is this how you get the money
will i get um yell bet for doing this
let's see inside first
[Music]
the music
oh i have to turn this up a little bit
for you guys
hello is this a tavern
oh it's like in the final fantasy 14
the can someone give me the copy face
the highly acclaimed uh game that
has a free trial or whatever where you
can get to max level and
[Music]
limbs are dominant yes yes yes that's
what i mean it looks like it a little
bit only a little bit
[Music]
i claim i claim gate wet critically
acclaimed animal
heart container right good
[Music]
where did you see a heart container have
you heard of the critically acclaimed
mmrpg final fantasy family
oh i see a chandelier how do i
you have to ram some i know what i have
to ram
wait but i can't run okay this thing
[Music]
right
the wrap housing on the balcony whatever
yeah okay
[Music]
ah
i'm scared mommy oh no
you've gone and made the travel mess of
things haven't you
well now you're going to be in a world
of trouble oh [\h__\h]
i'm in trouble can i have the heart
container though first before you yell
at me
[Music]
hello and i would like to apologize for
what i've done
and yeah that looks pretty bad uh
honestly i'm surprised you guys are
still sitting at the table
what are you thinking scared a year of
my life what did you want again i lost
my train of fights
you believe me don't you believe what
[Music]
there's a friend of steven living in
this skyloft
i'm telling you i came to supposed to
get eating
eaten by that evil beast you know what
you've gotten a little
night training but you'd better keep
your guard up or he'll take a bite out
of you too
oh i'll take the money not the bite
thank you what about you did any of
those
glass shells get into your eye i hope
that
oh no you've done it now there's no
escaping this one
okay no one's escaping i mean i could it
seems like i could
i wonder what they say if i open the
door ah
[Music]
okay i see oh yeah okay oh
don't even pretend that it was an
accident i put signs up there to warn
people to be careful of the chandelier
and everything
well i washed my hands of the whole
thing don't be surprised if my dad gives
you a royal chewing
out you're cute
what is wrong with you just look at what
you've done
you broke my fancy customer the
chandelier
you're going to be working for me for
free until you pay off everything
i said i made a game i think i've seen
that before
that's right i'm going to hold you
tonight let's not waste any time putting
you to work i need you to deliver my
famous soup to eagers
oh oh no assistant huh
[Music]
egos
was he the guy
wait is that time limited i don't have
an empty bottle
wait so now i can leave now you allow me
to leave i just come back whenever i
have an empty bottle
okay bye bye
ah the guy that taught me how to use the
sword ow okay okay
okay
oh they grew faster don't they
[Music]
they grow up so fast
children
[Music]
so unfortunately i don't have 300 rupees
now
it's a bit disappointing i thought there
would be money on this island
there was a hot container
is there anyone here no
damn it oh wait what
it's a shiny dress oh i love the colors
[Music]
mate
oh that's bloody awesome mate i got a
jet now
i got a jet
okay
[Music]
i yeah a new word an australian word a
fake australian word
you have time to jet skyloft
you mean my home my home island
okay you got a statue
okay i gotta place the table that's
right yeah
thanks guys okay that's right
that is true i forgot about that
what
don't fly to close the sun
what if i look at the sun what happens
then huh
can i look into the sun
[Music]
can we land on on here
i think there's no other way to get up
there anymore oh wait i don't have to go
up
right is it at the bottom or is that the
top
[Music]
wow beautiful well i'll just land here
for now
is it inside totally forgot when it was
with a fingers inside
there we are wow
i have come to deliver the second
piece probably second out of oh
it looks like it might just be three
[Music]
pieces
a lot of cyclists have opened up now oh
a new beacon of light master
i have confirmed the location of a
second opening in the cloud barrier it
is located in the skies to the northeast
this opening will allow you to access a
new area on the surface
i suggest you fly there as soon as you
complete the necessary preparations
hold on
what would be the lessons i feel like i
feel like we already did the necessary
preparation
i love the voice you do for free i have
the perfect voice for free
thanks guys
first is actually pretty easy to
recreate so i'm glad that
she's the one that talks to me all the
time and not someone like
oh jesus
where could that child have gone
cute those eyes oh cookie
where did you go what will i do if she's
been
kidnapped oh link
[Music]
seems like they're forcing a side quest
onto me
what perfect timing you haven't seen my
cookie oh have you
cookie who oh
my daughter she's a little five-year-old
girl
please link won't you help me look for
her
i've been looking everywhere but i can't
find her
i've asked everyone i could find for
help
and a few people have said she's been
spotted with some unknown person with a
scary face
someone else even said they thought
they'd seen her carried off by a monster
a monster she must have been kidnapped
she's so cute and friendly someone must
have just walked off of her
find cookie hill please it breaks my
heart to think she's somewhere out there
crying
please link you got it
thank you the knight academy should be
proud to have a student like you
please find my daughter quickly yeah
okay where the hell is she
is she on this island
monster a monster carried her up
what
[Music]
is there any like hint
oh yeah yeah i
see okay
well what do we do now should we just
jump or do we do side quests
um adam [\h__\h] will tell me
what do you say oh
it was your murder link could you play
cookie out
well cookie was missing oh she was
abducted by a monster
oh you don't think this has anything to
do with all those silly stories about
the horrifying monster that's been
living here and eh
and scotland for interest to you people
say the creature appears
in the day of night scaring folks and
even taking away children
probably nothing more than a scary story
or some older brother made up to
terrorize his younger siblings but still
makes you wonder
[Music]
so i should sleep until night
i guess let's do a side quest i don't i
don't want to
really go to the next area right now i
think
hello this is where my bed is right
can i sleep until night i feel like
there was an option like then
everyone welcome to my crib yo mtv crib
whatever so yeah um
yeah this this crib really cost me about
a 3 million
dollars approximately all of this is
made out of gold
and yeah i've used uh you know gold
gold just kind of like feels like my
element i don't know
about you but it is what it is and those
statues up there you know those are my
emmys i've received them
at the emmy thingy ceremony yeah those
are by far not all
but i don't want to brag too much you
know so
it's just two but in reality i've got
a male you know that over there no no
i'm not making them myself
no ignore that that is just another
hobby and like has nothing to do with
those emmys
no those are real i have a million of
them and they're real okay so shut the
[\h__\h] up
until night
[Music]
do you also jump into your bed like that
every night guys
i need to drink water
now yes bad for
what i don't want to break my bed
okay let's do this it's night time
a backflip noise you're going on to the
next level
going to bed in style with a backflip
so
it's like a prison i'm stuck
there must be away maybe upstairs was i
have
upstairs what about here headmaster
sorry i didn't want to disturb you
what about this door
why is this one open
and the not the others anyway
so a monster
how do we find this monster
let's just look around for a little bit
okay i see bats
that's probably not it
[Music]
we have to kill you
let's see where are we
graveyard
let me put a light there
huh wait can i put a line there i don't
know how
and i'm back with directions wait now
look
there's no that one
somewhere that way
[Music]
wow okay that thing is really creepy
should have heated them all
you've killed them earlier on
where is this grapefruit where am i
why didn't i keep them anyway that's a
good question wait is that
i'm too stupid to find it oh wait i
can't get help over there
yeah this place is dangerous they're all
attacking me
don't disturb me right now i'm on a
mission
but it's supposed to be that direction
i can mold them
[Music]
i mean that's somehow pretty creepy in
itself as well
wasn't there
no mind
brave robbing no i'm looking for a
monster
i'm not i'm not trying to do anything
bad here
is it not behind this
nice and the last one well i did all of
them
right here is it just in here
[Music]
i should whack it
huh
that is so scary
[Music]
i don't like it
what
[Music]
what was her name i'm like cookie
stop stop stop stop stop stop
please
[Music]
isn't that a fun game oh dear perhaps an
explanation is an
order my name is baton
and i am a monster who resides here in
this humble dwelling below
skyloff nice to meet you but please
allow me to correct one popular
misconception
while i'm certainly a monster i wouldn't
dream of terrorizing the people of this
town
you see this adorable little girl is the
only one
who didn't let loose a blood-curdling
scream at the sight of
me since you began to visit me here i
felt positively jubilant
you see my heart's only wish is to
become friends with the lovely people of
sky love
but as you can surely imagine it has
proven quite difficult to break the ice
when they are struck with paralyzing
fear at the mere side of me
also you like my nails i got them done
yesterday um
it's kind of hard to eat with them but
it's
pretty useful when you've got something
in your nose
get it out of there yeah it's pretty
cool
i assure you nothing would fill my heart
with joy more than
to be friends with the fine people of
this town
but as soon as i try to approach any of
them and extend
my claw and friendship they run and
scream as though they've been
as though they've seen a walking
nightmare
all right i've gotten ahead of myself
you see
there's an old tale among my monstrous
king that goes as follows
it seems that when humans make other
humans happy the happy humans produce a
substance known as gratitude crystal
gratitude crystals are quite amazing
just looking at them
and knowing there was such a gratitude
in the world to turn
meat from a monster into a human
[Music]
and goodness nothing would delight me
more than the
to become a human from the moment i
made my regrettably demonic eyes on you
i could tell
you had a gentle and generous height
won't you please gather aggressive
crystals and show them to me
[Music]
truly you'll help me
i've heard that you can obtain pure
accredited crystals by helping people
solve their troubles
they could also be merely lying about
here in skyloft or elsewhere
among the clouds everywhere you find
people i'm sure someone with a heart as
pure and genuine as yours will be able
to see them
please solve some troubles and gather me
all the gratitude crystals you can find
[Music]
any help you can provide will really be
appreciated
i promise your assistance will not go
unrewarded
cute he's got nice pictures on the world
oh there you are what the hell go back
home hi
he's not a bad man he saved me one time
when i
almost fell over the edge and he wants
me come here and scream as loud as i
want
he said it was dangerous to go out alone
at night so i'll just hang out here for
a while
tell me about welcome home in the
morning uh okay
the [\h__\h] you you can't come here a day
how about that not at night you should
you should go
sleep at home at night and maybe playing
during the day
all right but okay it's not my child
whatever
yeah we're gonna bring like i guess from
southwest and stuff we're gonna gather
those
and then bring him to him and then he'll
become human and what do we get from him
in exchange he'd better be a
heart container it better be
at somebody else's problem that's what
we would all like to say sometimes huh
well well hello monsters okay
i guess that is kind of like to motivate
you to do more cyclists and i
am motivated i am
but i also don't know how much longer i
should play it's only been three hours
it's only been three hours
seems rather short
and only that's like nothing i'm so shy
but also i don't know
it's my motivation and
i i don't know
i have to go up you finished one dancing
you
what wait what
yeah i've barely done anything today i
finished that one
done and then that's it
the thumbnail is so pretty
i know that's the weird reason but uh
the phone nail
the phone there though what's that
gonna do something here
where's my home
i i will not reuse it what the hell
foam nails are not meant to be reused
i can't find my way in in here anymore
oh wait i can go up here
super chat reading oh yeah but even with
that like my voice is really
dead i feel like i should read them
tomorrow
maybe i'll end it here
[Music]
oh yeah my room is downstairs right
right oh yeah is this
is this where the girls are i'm down to
keep watching
thank you but i should probably
okay where's jonkerson's movie today
that i didn't show up during my stream
interestingly
i guess because between the streams
today i took some breaks and cuddles of
them
and now it's only been three hours so
they're not asking for new colors
wait a second
[Music]
those look like some japanese candy like
me whoa
whoa we got one he was just lying around
there nice
i sleep until the morning
[Music]
can i save from here from the book that
will be nice no
god damn it you gotta make it
complicated for me huh
i love this music so much
[Music]
oh wait can i enter leave from here no
[\h__\h] no no no that's not where i wanted
to go but wow
you got a nice room
thank you yeah i gotta recharge my own
phoenix energy too thank you for
watching
[Music]
uh i'm also kind of tired as well damn
um yeah i guess that's it for today
uh sorry guys but
i hope you enjoyed all the streams uh
today
we've done quite a lot today
oh but i'm kind of exhausted i
i'll make the schedule now and eat some
food and all that
and um i'll see you tomorrow
probably i have to strain my hair
[Music]
okay
thank you everyone i love you all
i'll see you around and enjoy when we
say
auf wiedersehen bye bye
bye bye
thank you we have something
[Music]
so
do