[Music]
i'm live now
too but loading screen
no i didn't i didn't but i tapped out
too quickly
and then it doesn't like finish the
thing oh they hear me
well kick your key early then
they don't hear you
[Music]
don't worry they don't hear you they
only hear me
[Music]
you want to start okay
what
oh wait i need to unmute you oh there we
go
hello hello
good morning good
good morgan good morning
nice nice i always remember that as
i'll feed us in that's that's three
phrases but
that's um more than three words because
some of those are
are multiple words yeah so you know a
lot of german now
isn't this nice beautiful ah
romantic oh you have a nice cape where
is that is that cake from your shader
well i have a cape yeah you didn't know
i have a cape too i think it comes with
the shaders oh
i have a cape but yours is cuter than
mine because yours is just a smiley
oh i didn't even see it's cute
yes
not as beautiful as you
yeah we had that before i heard that in
our last uh collab with everyone else
we were we're making uh you know when
when i was like doing a flirt with you
um i didn't realize but i saw it in
clips afterwards that apparently
callie was getting jealous and she was
like throwing snowballs at me
like [\h__\h] out of snowballs and i didn't
even notice
[Music]
she was so jealous
it makes me so happy
oh well sorry everyone yes takamori but
today
[Music]
someone suggested to me um
which uh it's funny because because nino
mae
already like kind of is like a twist
joke on words
yes and then with nashi it's like no no
no no no no i don't know
or what was the other one
no bird here wait
that's what's your name that's just my
name cena
don't worry about
oh my god my goddamn neighbors i'm so
angry
oh yeah you guys don't understand my
neighbors um
didn't let me sleep all night okay maybe
not oh i was
up all night until 6 a.m and then i
tried to sleep and then later i woke up
and they
for four hours they've been hammering
and banging at something i don't know
what
what they they're doing some
construction or something it's
so annoying i've been doing it for hours
i barely slept so i'm super tired but
it's okay i am here i would take another
nap later which will then
uh end in me again staying up all night
again as per usual but yeah
anyway if you if you give up on your
sleep schedule it's it's a lot easier
yeah you definitely did too you you
slept
like earlier than me you went to bed
my time my sleeping schedule is
basically
tuned to japan yeah that
that's actually really true yeah
i don't have to get new curtains too
just to block out the sun
i have all those light blocking curtains
too i need them too
uh anyway uh what was i gonna say
oh uh we're we're having a uh
yesterday but let me take a swim in your
pool that's so beautiful oh my god in my
shaders that looks
so beautiful oh my god
well yeah uh i yesterday
i logged into minecraft while i was
watching piccolo's minecraft stream
and i just felt like it i didn't really
have any goal and i was alone i wasn't
streaming i normally don't play games
when i'm not streaming
but i i went online and i was like
i'll do something so i went into the
nether and
i was like i'm not gonna go too far i'm
just gonna explore a little bit
so i went around a little bit in the
never and then of course i got lost
after after a while of finding a lot of
gold
ghasts and figuring out how to fight
them
properly but i did get lost in the end i
didn't really find back anymore
so i went to our i went to our discord
and i wrote
does someone have the coordinates uh of
of of
the what did they what exactly it was
like
homer bass nether you want the
coordinates for it yeah
it was uh we had some communication
issues there
because i wrote does someone have the
coordinates of our main
nava portal i got lost and then i took
the coordinates
right here she sent them to me and then
i was following those coordinates for
like an hour
and i was like i'm pretty much there but
like i can't i can't find
the gate what the hell and on my way to
finding
to following those coordinates i found
guras
nether fortress and i was like wow
it's here that super that must be super
close to the to the
to the nether portal then wow wow that
it was so
close always so i was looking and
looking and looking
but i couldn't find the entrance and
then i wrote
that you know you know was just uh i
don't know
how you were just checking up on me so i
was like
actually i s i still i'm still lost and
never
i just can't find it i'm super close but
i can't find it and then
you realized that i was like here are
you are you in the nether
like yes of
so then she gave me the real coordinates
and then i was following the real
coordinates but they were so far away
and then i i really couldn't find it
anymore and then
then however i i um
i got to the point where i found my path
again at least
and the path was this this single block
path that gura made on the way to her
fortress
and i have a screenshot so you can
imagine it better
let me show you it's on my stream only
but
this one one block path the thing the
problem is on the end of that path
uh you don't see it anymore in this
screenshot because i got
closer and it's over already but at the
end of that path there was a pig
and it's one block and you guys know how
clumsy i am there's no way i could fight
that on this one block path
without falling down so i was like
you know i found the puff again but
there's this pig and
and i don't know what to do it's i i
can't find it and then she was
she was there if you look if you look if
you look close enough
let me make it bigger she's on the other
side what
at the moment i wrote to her that i
can't make it she was already there at
the other side of the uh the present you
said
you said your your uh girl's uh path i
was like i am a girl's path
and i saw this pumbaa on like a path and
i was like oh there's a pumbaa and then
as soon as i saw the pumbaa kiara was
like
you know i have a problem
i can and then she she fought the pig
and uh happy end my life was saved by
inna because otherwise i would have
never made it back
home i just eated
you're such a pro minecraft player you
easily killed that
monster that pig easily you just gotta
be one with the system
and what one more thing i i personally
didn't understand when i tweeted about
it i personally didn't understand why
you wrote hakuna matata
but is it because of the pig
oh my god that is so exciting it is
reaching
that is reaching enough that is not
reaching it's literally pumbaa
i did not realize that until um
someone else like people were trying to
figure out
why uh you wrote hakuna matata and what
actually happened
and then um i saw one person
actually um suggesting that it might be
because of another pig because of that
pig and i was like how do they know
how did they get to that conclusion and
then that is when i realized that makes
sense your hakuna matata
makes sense you're how did you think of
that you're a genius
don't worry about it oh well okay so
after all that's uh introductional
introductional talk
let's go into the never and first of all
find the right spot
for the second kfb branch
yes actually uh wait for a moment i need
to bring
i also want to bring salmon i need to
bring food and i barely have food we're
busy talking that way
well thank you for thank you for saving
me yesterday
ah no worries no no i actually wanted to
go to sleep once but she realized i was
still a lost child and that's when she
decided to save my life
what an angel yes
i need to cook some chicken again i'll
have some food if you want
no it's okay i i i i
i really have more than enough food i
just need to cook it
uh what am i doing i can't seem to find
my crossbow right there put my crossbow
i i learned yesterday i finally learned
how to properly
um how to properly uh
fight a guest with the crossbow but i
also learned how to reflect
um the whatever they shoot the fire
the horrible yeah i can finally reflect
it properly
nice i can't do it properly because of
the latest
wow oh because this server
has like oh because the server is i
guess in japan
is it i think so oh
well silly you're a pro gamer so that's
not a problem
[Laughter]
okay i just have a i have a lot of steak
to fix my mistakes
okay oh by the way um
we are first trying to find a spot and
then come back with materials and we
have to figure out what materials to use
because we can't just use
the wool that i used for the original
kfb
unfortunately
that's
what happened because i was wearing my
golden helmet but yesterday when i came
back here
i was i was waiting in that in that same
house okay i was waiting in the safe
house and then suddenly this dude
comes in and shoots me and i was like
what the [\h__\h] and it was running running
running and he was following me and
shooting me so quickly wait is that for
me i said it was
is that still from yesterday is that it
might be
it was shooting me oh that one was me oh
okay
but what i think it's why didn't you
attack me i didn't do anything though
i don't think he's a i don't think he's
awkward anymore
i was just waiting in here and oh i
think i know but but is that possible
because i wasn't here ina
okay and then he comes in intruding
this safe house oh my god wait he's
coming in no
no okay but then okay let's let's
reenact the scene i
i opened his chest and then he attacked
me does he not want me to open the chest
i wonder
is that his chest oh she opened the oh
chest opening chest ugly oh apparently
oh [\h__\h] that's why i find something new
oh i don't know good that he didn't see
it now
sorry i'm grumpy okay i'm grumpy from
waking up against my
will like grumpy waking up what if we
when if what if we kill him yep
oh i mean is there anyone around
wait i'm gonna die i'm gonna die wait
[Applause]
did you kill him for me oh yeah he's
gone
i wanted to shoot him down there with
one hit but it didn't work
i went to i wanted to see what you
thought
well we got my revenge from yesterday
you got some accessories on your head
yeah don't worry about it okay
let's go oh oh an arrow oh
no yeah that's dead all right that's
fine which way should we expand though
um i think i mean i was thinking about
like near near girls atlantis was a good
spot
the question is though how do we
actually want to
um be helpful with this branch and put
it somewhere where someone might
need an emergency food ration
or do we just plant it wherever it looks
good
yes
i mean where would you travel
here in the nether i think we gotta go
this direction
okay and then uh where this minecart
stops at the gold gacha
uh-huh there's i mean a somewhat flat
area
that is true so i was thinking maybe
there because that's also where you
changed
trains oh that's also where um
there's also um where you can go to the
slime
farm place ah okay at that place too
so have you ever seen it uh the slime
part
a slime
[Laughter]
need to stop leaving minecarts out
but that was because of that stupid pig
because he keeps no maybe not
there's a lot of mine cards oh my oh my
god oh my god oh my god
we'll be back there you go
goddammit i can just have fun with the
roller coaster
okay i got i got one um why is there a
random open spot here
um
remember the first first full club was
it
no that was the second one where he just
jumped here and died
uh-huh i remember i remember
i like her um all right piano proof
doesn't
doesn't only mean what you implied
it also means fireproof because true
because i'm phoenix there are patches on
fire
but don't worry about it but it's okay
yeah okay oh my god yes it's really dark
with the speeders that i have
um i i had to lighten mine up a lot
did you did you visit my where where my
my rail goes
no no no you didn't shall you go
uh it's um on first look it's really
nothing special we would have to travel
further to see
what's special about it
but it's okay this is a this is a good
candidate to put kfp because there's a
lot of customers
around too you know yeah they will have
to uh
and some entertainment with gotcha
the problem here is that there's a lot
of gas always attacking so there's
always a lot of fire
um that is true it's always it might
destroy the building
so we'll have to like guest proof it yes
definitely
but not not only the building but maybe
also the surroundings of it partially
[Music]
excuse me recently whenever i sneeze i
turn on my echo
quickly beautiful also i'm still
drinking my tea because i just woke up
and my voice still
needs to warm up but oh yeah kiara's
blowing into the mic for like
10 minutes i cool down her
it's what you call nekojita
you were jealous do you want to be blown
on or
no cha cha would have been jealous oh
like a special yellow treatment
i do i did blow on them sometimes uh for
as a punishment for sending empty empty
red super chats
what is what what is that silence are
you judging me
no okay well okay so let's build the
let's build it like uh wait uh uh
somewhere right here all these holes and
oh my god
probably a guest let's make it let's
make it um
pretty if uh eventually
i actually need to bring some i didn't i
didn't
i should really uh which is it
bring oh like a chest with like tools
and stuff because you're gonna need
quite a lot
wait one second ina i need to do some
blowing
um close your close your ears or
something
stupid stupid rat super chats write
something in it
god damn it they always do that
it has to be meaningful i'm sorry now
you can
you can open your ears again
okay let me let me show my new skills
let me show them my new skills fight me
[\h__\h]
oh sorry sorry wait wait wait why do i
keep on doing this today
oh because my keyboard is resting on my
graphic tablet oh that's why
bite me fight me uh it's so dark
i will protect inna but don't destroy my
rails please
oh [\h__\h] okay
i can do it though um
okay there we go there we go yeah
well i did it but at what cost uh some
of your rails
no no no
where
it it's not it's not even like it
totally burns
god damn it people are asking for bgm i
didn't turn it on on purpose but i i
guess if you guys really want bgm let me
turn it on
oh oh goddammit oh wait i have to change
the settings
um okay oh it's so dark here
okay there's bgm now is that
inna stream disconnected oh it's it
should be back
oh kelly is in the chat kelly yahoo
kelly
oh did you just fix uh did you bring
rails with you
no it's the ones that broke okay i need
to bring some
later okay um oh we need we're missing
two here though i don't know where they
are yeah there's more
there is more missing down there too but
it's okay i'll bring some i'll bring
some
when we come back we should we should go
and uh bring some materials now
yay so should we put it near
what's his face something phil philip
you gave him a name
i don't know i think girl and uh i'll
make them names
thank you kelly we'll have fun we're
already having lots of fun
we're having lots of fun kelly we're
having so much fun
okay and callie do you see this how much
we love each other we chase each other
because we love you i don't i don't this
is one-sided oh where does that go
this is the slime form oh i never
noticed this one before
um by the way
oh my god
i um i didn't have full hp now
so but anyway that's a shortcut for me i
mean you better bring my stuff over here
[Laughter]
i'm gonna wait i'm gonna wait outside of
the never
[Laughter]
okay so enough yeah
what do we use to build it i don't want
it to be only like
one one boring color i want it to have
bad oh yeah does um
does this wait let me ask my viewers
does this thing does the shrimp light
burn
uh yeah it has a light but but this is
the glowy things on the uh
on the trees or the yeah there's a
doesn't burn
they say it doesn't burn so we can maybe
oh those numbers
so we can use um a combination of uh
like concrete or something like that and
then make it a bit orange with the
shroom light because we need some orange
elements otherwise people are not going
to recognize it as
its original glory over there so uh-huh
uh we gotta clean we gotta i barely have
any though do you have more
uh i have caught i have concrete
oh okay okay um i mean we can collect
the shimmers
at least okay white concrete okay i
might have a few more
here okay but that's not much
brb gonna gonna cook some chicken
yo caffeine boys what up are you guys
working
are you guys working mostly moss
are you working properly i'm so proud of
you guys
i am so proud of you you're doing a
great job here
uh so who is um who is open
for uh changing branches uh it's we're
right now
um planning on opening up a new branch
in a really nice
spot a really nice paradise um
i am putting the applications right here
and you please
fill them out and send them to me i will
need at least
10 workers of you um where you ask oh
don't worry about it it's uh it's pretty
close
okay okay okay okay
i didn't tell them i didn't tell them
where it's gonna be
wait a minute don't these batters
attract
pillagers no i haven't seen them in a
while oh that's fun to fight them well
maybe because
maybe because uh i killed them all
yeah it's fun isn't it it's okay i
didn't really know
i feel like i feel like they came much
more often before i pulled out up these
banners
oh they don't they say they don't okay
okay do you have my
stuff oh i do
here's your assume this is also you oh
that's not yours
this is yours i'll take it anyway i'll
take care of it give me your diamond
sword
give it to me
is my is my golden helmet broken right
there
oh yes oh well it was pretty close
to breaking that's okay and an axe
in your pants do you want your pets back
yes
i had pants oh uh i was i was lacking
shoes i think
thank you thank you um
what else was your shield what about one
about my breast armor
uh there was none
i had like i had a golden helmet i had
breast armor and then i had
either shoes or a pants um
i must have missed it hold on ain't no
are you gonna give me new armor it's the
uh
community chest i put some in there
they're uh they're a little bit used but
it's okay but uh your your your iron
farm
is so useful
it's useful because i just afk in my
uh i'll house some arrows too take your
pick take your money
and now i'm gonna uh i'm gonna make an
eye and go
a golden helmet quickly um
and then the pickaxe i need a pickaxe
all right
and do you know i should bring materials
this time huh yeah
forgot about it so we're using we are
using uh i have your pork chops
oh no it's okay you can keep it you can
keep the pork chops
we're using concrete okay how much do
you have and
what color can we make orange concrete
you can but
i need some concrete powder to do that
concrete powder you mean the color and
some orange
ah there's a concrete powder
what's the recipe well we have a lot of
flowers outside
we need sand and gravel actually i have
quite a bit of sun and gravel oh i can
make you orange uh
[Music]
orange but actually no white is fine
because where do you come from we'll
need some orange too a few people
on the uh first branch what was that
right sorry sorry one
no no if we paste the uh yeah on the
first brand yeah then i need some i need
some white and some orange but the
orange can be
um it can't just be this room light
that's fine
jim that's gonna glow though yeah it's
fancy it's darker than ever anyway so
that's
i think it's fun it's like a nice uh
never version
never version of of the of the but i
also kind of need
i mean if we don't if we really want to
eat red yeah if we really want to copy
it then we need red as well
okay but the orange can be substituted
is that what you would say
it can be some red but okay make more
i guess it's gonna be a somewhat small
branch
it could be a take out branch you know a
pickle oh
like uh only take out good idea
good idea okay but inside
maybe i'll make some what did i make my
chairs
out of and let me see
how did i make my chairs and my tables
oh with a carpet right
oh everything i think yeah with a carpet
and a fence and then a stair okay
okay but that can be out of any material
because that's going to be inside okay
fences and carpet i'm gonna make i'll
make some
white carpets
and
[Music]
carpet uh how many
how many concrete do you think we'll
need
ah how many do you have
we can't we can do it as big as we can
with
how much concrete you have okay hold on
i'll see what i can do that's enough
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
applying for the transfer tension for
real wow we gotta
we got yeah
wow you're getting a medal for being a
brave volunteer
who else wants to working than ever
who wants to do it me too what
wow okay they're actually asking for it
okay
first you're complaining and now they're
all asking for it
interesting i thought you guys didn't
want to go
but they they said that working at kfb
is already hell
so what's the difference that's that's
not true though
it's a beautiful experience to work it
can't be okay
make me sad when you guys say that oh i
should probably bring back my gold
okay i i'm not concentrating we have to
we already spent like
um half a half an hour
i thought i used this before what
it's been no i have this like automatic
like easy to make concrete kind of thing
oh oh i saw
i i used your what's the other what's
the other thing the the
the the the cobblestone thingy
oh that's the it's the thing right
beside it it's the uh
oh uh nina you're like so
innovative that's amazing why did
do you why are you making everything
automatic
you are you are building a nice future
for future whole life english members
oh wow there's so many i'll take some of
these pikachus why is there so many
pickaxes
laying around here
you know oh wait
put that back put it back in the chest
over here on the outside
oh yeah okay but can i can i have like
one you can make iron one wait it
doesn't go there there's plenty of water
it has to go ah that's how it works you
put some pickaxes in there
oh oh my god it keeps on it keeps on
like yeah don't worry about it i'll pick
it up later
quick i'll pick it up later
interesting is that how it's supposed to
work
uh sort of it's supposed to drop down on
its own but it's kind of weird so
i just have to do it manually later
yeah that's so interesting yeah
innovative concrete because you have to
put it in the water
um
no i'm just understanding of you guys
but the cobblestone thingy it's genius
because i'm like
cobblestone is like you would think it's
like super
excessive
accessible and it's everywhere but
but when you need it you don't have any
cobblestone
[Music]
okay um and then we check this here
and then enough
not inaccessible
no it's very accessible not inaccessible
okay um i think i have enough
oh building blocks to go oh no
i also
[Music]
okay i'm gonna
uh make some
[Music]
pickaxes
and then i'll jump into the nether and
wait the the shroom lights
they're supposed to be collected with
pick axes right
i feel like it was no idea
i feel like i collected them yesterday
anything oh okay anything
[Music]
windows windows i'll bring some glass
blocks
yeah should we bring like a furnace and
um
ah uh-huh uh-huh oh yes yeah we need
chests yeah because we're gonna put in
food in there
i don't think we have to put an
automatic cooking device there because
i just that's not that's not how i do it
i don't want it to be automatic because
that seems just like too too horrible
for me
um are you sure that's the real reason
yeah i just feel too bad like i don't
want to make it a farm rain where it
kills the chicken
and then cooks them i don't i can't do
that no that's
that's too insane for me like you might
do that with your
with your automatic farms absolutely
absolutely inna humane unbelievable i
i i don't know how you can be so
so so reckless i don't know i can't even
find the words for it in english you
know i
i roll the tapes roll the tips of
kiara's
deeds come on you mean the one where it
girls like
[Music]
did you see that one where they added
your singing oh
yes you're singing makes you so much
more dramatic
the moment where i had to slay my
chickens and it was
i was just so so devastated i admitted
it she admitted it she
slained the chickens
everyone who heard that you're going to
the usual room
i have i have footage from the usual
room oh oh
where did you get that from uh they
they want to remain anonymous but there
has been reports
i um i don't did you maybe go to the
usual room because you're
kinky like that and wanted to check out
the
legos no no but i heard
ungodly things happening in the usual
room
yeah one of the one of my recent um
uh ideas that i put in there is that
legos
so that like a lot of legos so that when
you walk around in the usual room
you will always step on legos and it
will hurt so
much isn't that a great idea
and you say i'm the inhumane one
legos how could you right out of
everything in the legos and then there's
one more thing
um i put uh i put a uh what how many
pieces was it like a million pieces
uh uh a puzzle and they have to
complete the puzzle but then at some
point they would realize oh god there's
one piece missing after all these
hours of completing the one million
piece puzzle
they realize one piece is missing
ah the pain do they ever say lego
my eggo
my
maybe maybe it's not i don't get it
you don't get that there's a there's a
waffle
um brand called eggo and they're
their slogan is lego my egg
oh
kelly did you get the joke i mean she
probably at least knows the brand
they're probably the frozen well or
waffles that i'll make it
frozen waffles likely yummy
around nina enough playing around let's
go
you love we love eggos in the underworld
echoes
echoes i love eggos oh have you ever
eaten it like cold
i've had i've eaten that i've eaten them
yeah frozen waffles cold
i've eaten frozen waffles before i think
or at least like
like like cream waffles and ice waffles
from uh what's that what's that the the
brand with the actual good waffles
echo no ah
what's it called does someone know
the one from i think from europe
like belgian waffles yeah yeah hmm
there's this one those are frozen
waffles they're fresh
delicious there's this waffle there but
there's just one
brand of belgian waffles that's like
really good frozen waffles yum yum yum
yum yum yum
now that's droop waffles no no no no no
no no no no no does no one know what i'm
talking about
i buy them over here often oh wow anyway
keep on forgetting how to get off of
this
he's still sitting in there if we would
uh
attack his minecart would would that
count as attacking him and he would like
oh as long as you don't hit him i don't
think oh
you're kind of a jamma
but okay if you hit it with the sword
you can get it down in one one go
the minecart ah oh yeah i know actually
but i always forget oh
i need actually i need those i need some
shroom lights i'm gonna get some
swim lights okay should we build it like
right at the um
or should we build it like i think
i think it would be nice if it would be
like against
some kind of uh wall
um cali is riding eggo toaster strips
were the best
you toast them and dip them in the syrup
and it's like french toast
paradise explosion in your mouth and
stuff wow she's getting really
passionate
wow that's why you never like all your
eggs there's
always gas here
where are you no it's okay it doesn't it
didn't see me
well they will see me soon maybe stupid
why should we build it why should we
build it um
well until you figure out the location
oh and what do you do and cast hunting
oh no no i have to it's okay
we'll build it uh
[Music]
where is it i'll see you another time
okay
let's build it oh my god i should've
brought my torches actually
okay let's build it next to that because
there's no nice wall to build it against
so let's build it next to the to the
gate yeah and we build it like over the
gate
over the gate so when you when you when
you come out of the gate you're
basically like at the camp
location it's like it's like one of
those like you know when you go on the
subways but like when you come out it's
like literally just like
food chains like everywhere ah but i
think this part
i think this space would be nice you
know this this right here
yeah okay then can you can you start
filling the concrete foundation or
something like that
and or whatever foundation and alcohol
quickly get some
shroom lights in dysphoria should we
make it though
well as wide as we can with what we have
well the rails like bend here so it
can't be that big
and that's okay
you guys are all very welcome i'm so
jealous i haven't been able to sneeze
for like
the longest time well that must suck yup
you poor poor poor poor
totally human being i totally believe
that why don't why did i bring a white
wound what the hell
um i need some block
[Music]
pump
i don't know what is it today with me
and singing this song
thank you guys thank you for the sneeze
chats
one two three four how big should the
doors be
i hear the guests you hear it
kill it kill it kill your fire
we can't get it yet it's like way above
us stupid gas just waiting for the right
moment
don't hurt don't hurt enough oh
yay i want to hunt it down
do it do it inna follow your instincts
oh i see it
follow your instincts and kill it
where is it where did it go where did
the light go that i wanted to get
um what
it screamed did you heard it yeah nice
one
i wonder like if we is it is it uh
too big of a project to put a
like a cobbles stone ceiling over the
whole area over there
so that they just don't hate too
at least we have your cobblestone
machine that could help with that
this is a crazy idea
i think it's okay you can put glass too
actually so you can see the
like so glass doesn't burn uh in the
never
nope oh but i think they said
they can't see through glass oh really
oh that's that's weird that's so
why can't they see through the glass
they're stupid
you can't see yes their eyes are real um
[Laughter]
um
my chat is going crazy because i missed
some something that kelly said
let me see what did you say want it
mom that wants your attention dad wants
your attention
oh my i scrolled up all the way but i i
couldn't find
what you said it's gone oh i'm sorry
callie
it's oh kelly
kelly wants our attention oh oh
oh oh how
how how nice
pig's attacking me two pigs two pigs
uh there's so many things oh my god
[Music]
oh my god are you following me yes they
are following me
yes they are
help me guys help me what are you here
for aren't you supposed to fight them
oh they don't want to come out of the
forest interesting oh
i brought a pig i think we should um
where are you by the way you're not
looking for you
feel oh you went there to look for me i
think i just saw you
can you kill that oh no it's not
attacking me what's wrong
oh it's going for you now
uh
that's probably not a great place to
stand hmm
why is that was he attacking the the pig
and then accidentally
attacked me
hmm that's two deaths could you pick up
my myself or you think it will could
do you think it will stay back i have a
whole bunch of stuff i don't have a
chest oh no okay i'm running i'm running
i'm running i'm running
i'm guarding it okay it should stay
there it's not that far away
ugh
i thought it was a friendly fire it was
the hawklin
really yeah it did say it did say i was
uh killed by the hogland it did say that
yeah probably
oh my god all the all the cards
five minutes
it's fine oh
wait no one's looking right there's a
there's a hotlist oh they better not
take my golden helmet
wait wait no i don't have a golden
helmet how am i gonna oh [\h__\h]
they're gonna attack me like right away
you bet oh my you know this is oh my god
you know wait
i just realized i just realized this is
gonna be problematic
are you gonna stop attacking me once i
put on my helmet am i gonna even survive
though until that point
oh [\h__\h] there's so many around there oh
god
oh god uh fine ah he doesn't attack me
okay
okay okay i'm running i'm running
they don't see me as is someone
following me
okay i have a golden hammer that could
have
turned into a very difficult situation
there's more stuff here actually
you see okay okay okay okay okay where's
my
there we go i got it all got it all
good oh yeah you must have crossbow
right here oh
i am oh thank you thank you
yes okay um i'll go collect some
mushroom lights again
okay be safe yeah i'll try i'll try
it before you go you should look at how
thick the
location is going oh i saw i think
that's uh all right
what i saw wasn't it no it's okay
that's that's that's a zombie with phil
so nice but um
i think i'm i'm gonna let you get more
carpet and then carpet out the area
inside because i don't want it to be
like that that's uh disgusting
oh the children are running around over
there
uh
you know recently i've been experiencing
some morning sickness why do you think
that is
oh recently i've been experiencing
morning sickness why do you think that
is
did you eat before going to sleep no uh
before going to sleep mm-hmm
well a few hours before like like like
five hours before i sound like i mean
i'm
i would probably be fine if i would eat
uh now because i didn't eat
i just woke up and went straight to the
went straight to the pc yeah
you should digest your food before going
to bed or
sitting down for a long time oh well
i should be the one saying it but i
think it's just because i don't eat
before streaming in the morning mm-hmm
what am i doing you should probably
eat something like like even if uh
even if you have a troubled digestion
stuff maybe get like a
chick or something
well but i'm too lazy my company is
somewhat far away from me
you just sucked up on it just go there
once and buy like 10.
yeah but every time i go to the
convenience store i buy so much as if
i'm going to the supermarket
and i think the person who works there
hates me because i buy so much
and they spend so much time with me
i'm sure i'm sure they're
either they think they're happy until
glare is not as bad as when i went to
buy itunes cards
oh why do you think they wouldn't like
that uh
so when you buy a specific
annoying process there's a there's a
limit to how much you can
put in uh yeah okay so
if you buy multiple of those then you
gotta stand there and scan the cards
many times so
anyways
[Music]
how about that yeah where are you
are you up or down right right right
right side right side right
i see you save me save me
save me wait these are small ones
they're the big ones
they're not that bad come on there's
another one over there
they're not there's like these oh my god
there's a baby
or if you hit them once they run away
the small ones maybe
yeah but they're doing a really bad job
at protecting the forest i thought those
those
villagers or whatever they are are
supposed to protect and kill them
protect the forest and kill them you're
not doing a good job on that
you suck you guys suck all three of you
suck
i died because of you guys because you
are not doing your job
and you know what happens to people who
don't do their job you might not be
working for me but i'll put you in the
usual room anyway i don't care
so it's the usual job or use your room
the uh
yeah a reward
not really but some people maybe take it
as a reward but
but they're they're being very dramatic
about it so i don't i don't think
they're happy about it
oh they're happy don't worry they're
happy but they're always like no no no
no oh they're enjoying it a hundred
thousand dollars
you think they're all masochistic and
they enjoy
um stepping on legos well tonight all
they want but they are
i see you
[Music]
keep on interrupting me we'll never get
done
yeah you kill the gas that's really
that's that's probably oh
they're partying oh my god
and i realized they party after they
kill a pig wow
that's uh what the hell what they're
just here
is that the gas sound ah it's the fire
all right keep doing your senior dude oh
i think i hit one of them by mistake oh
are they following you yes
does it reset when you leave than ever
uh i don't know oh there's a portal
there you think
you're gonna be fine
goddamn pigs oh my god okay is that a
baby that's a baby
die you stupid baby you challenged me
you challenged kfp i have a whole army
we all we watched a lot of the rings
together so we we know how to fight
i still only have 11 how do i only have
how oh i missed how did i only have 11.
do you have some of my shroom lights
when i died
uh don't think so
yes uh you didn't hear anything nope
what is what's going on do you have my
streamlines is that why you
uh no i'm being hunted by zombie pigs
don't worry about it
go for the portal go for the portal
hello where are you
are you guys oba i'm okay
i'll be fine i'll be back in a moment
are you about to know the same yeah one
before when i looked at it you know
well if someone wasn't crying out my
name for help maybe i would have done
something wrong
yeah i was collecting trend lines and i
got more strong lights
nothing changed with the concrete
foundation
i think we're uh you know when i hired
ame and
she was doing so much work so quickly
she was so efficient and you are
inefficient
well that's just how it is oh [\h__\h]
next time next time you cry out my name
i'll just watch you die
you could never do that you could never
do that
you you would always protect me
because you're an angel hear about that
i believe in the goodness in your heart
i have a cross but i'm not afraid to use
it
i think you would always protect me
because you're you're such a
you're just a i'd like a raise please
oh what a raise would probably go into
the negative because
all my kfb employees are paying me so
when they get a raise they pay me more
you're welcome to ask for a raise you
know what i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna
put in my uh letter of resignation
you think you can resign oh that's funny
that's just cute
guys she thinks she can resign isn't
that funny
i'll resign when i die which is what it
might be soon
she's new guys she's new
he doesn't understand how it is kfp
employees trying to
ask me to save them are you talking
about me
who's asking you to save you just you
can't be employees
[Laughter]
yes
don't worry about it i'm sure you can uh
build the uh
space soon
i i i don't i i i mean
i from what i've seen from inna's
uh projects and buildings up until now
i i will i thought it would be a good
idea to
to cooperate with taco bell to get some
of that nice
architecture going but i don't i didn't
see much going on yet
don't worry soon these arrows will find
a new toy
no no no no no you can't do that no no
no no no you love me i love you you love
me we are best friends
you know what happens to when you when
you fall in love
cupid fires an arrow right at your heart
i know that i'm probably
soon gonna fall into lava or something
like that i love running away from the
pigs as
quickly as i can protect me guys protect
me yes yes
i am being protected don't worry i'll be
there soon
good job guys you're not dancing this
time though why not oh oh
oh okay i have
oh oh i have 23 streamlights
but all this time and you only have 23.
i
offended when i died i waved
oh zombie penguin i think i last time
when i died because you didn't pit you
did you you you took some and then you
threw them away you didn't
die wait when i lost her in the first
place
um i think the reason why i died is
because you you you you
you accidentally shot me with an arrow
and the last hit was was done by a
hawkman maybe but maybe other heads were
made back
you shouldn't be standing there
i was just bracing
you know
shake hands and
[Music]
indeed what is the thing
what to kill me okay
no what does it do what is this
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god i just tried to help
oh um all right i'll try to quickly uh
go for the never portal and hope no one
uh
yeah this is really just
i don't know if this location is good
enough potential
return to sender what what what did you
do
what was that i don't know i didn't
wait i guess i uh i think i just like
shot an arrow at the fireball and
returns it to the cast
wait that's the first time you did that
i don't know
okay okay so
this still looks the same interesting no
problem with that it's
totally fine
it looks looks nice
it looks nice looks good job and uh on
the concrete one
yeah yeah anything else
what anything else oh it looks looks
really nice good job thank you
you're lucky today okay
so i i think i think i'll put um
the the shrooms like here
on the on the edges and that would be
the
approximately the height of it and maybe
on top we put one more
layer of white and then in between
do you have glass oh yeah glass oh yeah
oh yeah right
oh yeah we could make that some room
hold on you give me some
glass oh yes
there you go i only have the block style
yeah boxes fire
okay we're finally getting started
well we'll need something some uh big
thinkers need some time to
start their creation so to get fully
inspired and prepared
and all that we're we're not just
messing around here we want to do it
properly
wait this is wool oh this is yours
oh i dropped it i dropped that when i
died oh
yeah i thought it was concrete i was
like this sounds different
i thought it stuck to you i don't
i don't i don't know if i want the whole
wall
from from one side to the other to be
a glass i'm not sure
i think i oh you ah oh
oh good i like that idea
okay this is where the the creative
architecture of
the inside of inna the inner side
wait this is still wool you can give it
back to me
here yes i'll take it i'll take it
and i'll cover up that hole because it's
scaring me
also i should probably eat probably the
chat also keeps on telling me to eat
i mean like in in in the game because
i'm close to dying
but i won't listen
okay where's my pickaxe
oh that looks beautiful that looks
really fancy
gas ah this is like super close the gas
is like super close
hasn't seen us yet wow
i will i will challenge it
oh yeah oh no come on
oh are you playing tennis oh sh
oh try to at least
it doesn't burn i guess yeah
it's okay i'll be there soon oh no
come here come here you little coward
i haven't died in a while come here look
at me
look at me face your destiny
i got two cocky
um
in minecraft oh is it so long ago
pumbaa now
it not see me stupid stupid
it's so far away
wait i don't have a golden helmet oh
dear
oh oh life chance
or did it break ah the what
the fence did you pick some stuff up ah
no
my helmet we have to go back
wow you still don't have your helmet uh
nope
oh oh should i pick it up for you the
helmet
i'm surprised i didn't i am surprised i
didn't see you
oh let me see if there's a golden helmet
um
i don't oh what's that no i think
there's something here
but no golden helmet they don't even
attack you that quickly interesting
i thought that was my shield
wait even my sword is gone oh no
i could give you my sword i have two
how are they not attacking how are they
not attacking you you have a sword
you should you should probably uh go get
some diamonds oh okay
that makes sense hi enderman what's up
is there another guy oh my god yeah
okay fine oh you did it okay it's dead
wow good job
nice okay are you finally leaving us
alone do we have peace now
i think i have to go back to get some
golden armor
okay i'll continue uh building him
i'll continue okay i'll be back oh it's
fine
wow that is a it's a kind of a pain in
the ass to build in the never huh
that was rough
they keep them they keep on attacking us
it's not fair
oops no oh that's broken
wait do you have all the conch oh my god
concrete burn too
it no for real i have plenty left
but we definitely need more i have the
red concrete so
oh okay um i mean we can just make more
more glass walls then
i have the glass the shovel
one one two three four four
four
oh what's this guest here oh
oh yeah because you killed the guest is
that the first time you get a gas tear
oh are they so rare
guys what can what can you do with a
gaster oh my god there's no gas here for
potions apparently
what can you do with a ghast tear oh my
god there's another gas
here ha ha
[Music]
look at me
wait oh disappeared no too bad
wow i feel like if those stupid gas
wouldn't keep
like coming no i'm so stupid
then we would probably already be done
by now oh no
i'm so
[Music]
um
i need more glass at least my bow is
safe okay
um i might have more class okay
or no i can just burn some more now i
have too many
i have too many glowstones now hmm oh
this is really
really small
[Music]
oh i see you there so
uh maybe we should really put a
a cobblestone ceiling over this whole
area because it pisses me off they keep
on attacking and they keep on destroying
them
i mean we could just cover up the rail
but
i mean um yeah the rails
definitely need some protection
and yeah it's okay i'll those are my
rails so i'll take care of those
uh oh well
mama mama she'll bring a chest over
oh yeah can you bring one yes
yay a lot of extra that i made before
yes
time to fight
oh
stupid
you need more rails uh i can bring stuff
for maintenance
uh yeah yeah i love maintenance yes and
sorry guys i didn't i didn't check your
answer so what can you do with the gas
here did you even answer or did you just
own one oh it's another potion for
potions
oh um
potions um um what kind of ocean
regeneration potion
oh there's another one oh my god
ender crystals
oh wait my steaks are gone your sticks
my steaks i have a lot of sticks i'll
have a lot of steaks too but i'll bring
chicken
you'll bring chicken okay which makes me
think i also
have to um go back one time
and get some yeah
mama mama will take care of it
this is this is a business that only
mama kiara can take
care of oh that thing oh
i see oh do you know what i'm talking
about
i have a i have a i can guess
[Music]
um
oh it's so slow oh i see you
you're back oh hello i'm back you're
back you can take my card
because i think we took all of the cards
out of that chest
[Laughter]
my stupid neighbors are still banging
after all these hours they're still
banging on something i'll wait
context i mean i mean they're really
for hours i don't know man i couldn't
sleep i woke up
the context says that they're banging on
something they're doing some
construction or something i think
oh i i
i didn't i didn't mean to
yummy no is it better if i say they're
hammering
does that sound better
apparently not
well then how am i supposed to say it
it's not my fault that english is such a
suggestive language that's not my fault
it's not even my first language
so um
there was an effort yep
yo friends did you fill out your
applications
did you i'll take some of that chicken
and i'll put it into the neighbor
because we we're not gonna we're not
gonna cook the chickens in never that's
just
white chickens no no sorry guys sorry
guys i meant phoenix's sorry sorry
all right obviously sorry about the
confusion guys
uh oh yeah i was gonna make some carpet
yeah
my application is filled up okay okay
okay
imported chicken yes it will be freshly
imported from the
real world isn't that nice
oh i already have the one oh yeah are
you back at base
uh yep uh if you go into my house i was
baking some
glass but i forgot about it wow thanks
over short attendance pan i see
yes i uh
in which house you have a couple of
houses it's kind of confusing i only
have i only have one house
the uh along with all the cats and dogs
okay okay okay is that enough carpet hmm
wait oh it's not how you're gonna do it
uh
you kinda kind of have two houses though
wait what no wait
i didn't wait a second did you get real
did you get rid of the other house yes
ah i don't think this location is safe
potential
yeah i know wait where
were you doing that inside or outside
the
glass oh here i have it i found it
[Music]
um there's two guests
two are you gonna be fine
i'm coming back no fine hopefully i'm
coming back
where'd it go
stop banking oh my god what the hell are
they doing like for real what
they better be done after i'm done with
streaming because i gotta take a nap
mommy's gotta take a nap mommy has to
take a nap
hey i have to stop banging i want to
but the thing is like i i probably don't
even have the
privilege to get mad at them because
they probably think the same of me
because i'm so loud when i stream they
probably hear every word i say
you know oh yeah right
if there is no if
there's no reason to feel like um
embarrassed or flossed or anything
because i'm not
saying anything little i'm just talking
about my stupid neighbors
i'll take care of it don't worry uh come
up with that i'll be getting a walls
ready
okay okay
i got your slime ball nice
are your buddies gonna come up for dumb
i gotta kill
yes uh what happened there uh
a guest happened oh no i thought they
can't burn it
so you asked me burn the ground glass i
have the glass
i'll just place it myself
so we have a pattern here interesting i
hope you like the pattern that i put in
the back yes
oh okay and then i'll copy what you did
on that side
uh yeah oh wait no
i messed no i uh okay yeah and then
there's
what okay okay i thought you got rid of
my
i don't know this just disappears
because okay wait is that correct it
goes like this
yeah and then the glass goes there okay
yes yes
[Music]
this is this is going to be such a
beautiful building in the middle of the
never people are going to be like
they're going to come sightseeing here
and they're going to check it down then
they'll be like
who built this fancy building in the
nether it's so beautiful
and then we're going to be like that was
us
that was us okay are we gonna um keep it
open here or should we build a door
a door might be nice hmm
what kind maybe the the kind of white
door you have at your at your
um home oh the iron and then a double a
double door
oh do you have a crafting table yes
actually
yeah actually i did bring one
i can make it probably all right let's
play i can put the chest down too
actually okay
good and i can put my chicken there uh
iron door
and then we need a button
i don't have a stone though
how how did i deserve that that's empty
red super chat why don't you write the
lookout messages
thank you though thank you um
you maybe have a stone by chance
ah stone a single stone no i don't
i don't have any stones right now i have
more glass
and i have wool and i have a smooth
sandstone stairs and i got sroosh from
lights
oh i can fix this
where am i what can i burn
you you can have that cobblestone
there you go
i'm gonna make the tables now
oh wait i have coal
wait i only need one nevermind i'm just
talking to myself
okay
nice
and then in between i do want to damn it
i don't want it oh
let me put some more glass there
that looks nice doesn't it chat does it
look nice it does dry it so fancy that
looks beautiful
beautiful well that might be a prettier
branch than the outside branch
nice but
maybe oops can we do we have more white
concrete
yeah we do hold on do you think we could
instead of the carpet
and replace all of the all of the ground
with the white concrete because like
even if i put carpet there it's gonna
look through where the table is i have
44 i think that should be enough
cool maybe then
all right i just wanted to put conf or
cobblestone because it was stronger
stronger
hold on against gust and
firewall etc wait you say that there's
still a chance
that my kfb branch can be destroyed by
yes okay but we can we can build the
ceiling with cobblestone
yeah yeah yeah it's just stuff we gotta
make sure they don't see us uh
to the walls somehow okay
it'll be fine they can't see through the
through the
class right and for uh i don't know how
they can be that stupid but
apparently that's the thing
i don't know will i have enough i mean i
have more at home
smooth enough to so smooth
so beautiful almost as smooth
what do you call them those those
sideburns that you have
huh
that wasn't very smooth of you sorry i
don't know what to call them
uh i ran out of more at home
oh okay okay uh i'll continue building
the
the table okay
and if you have time you can get started
on the uh the ceiling
i don't have any cobblestone i know i'll
give you some yeah
all right leave it in the chest actually
okay
thank you
i'm actually gonna move the chest though
filthy okay okay
but it didn't pick it up god damn it
god damn it i have no space
there's a oh remember
you can leave it on the floor while you
move the chest what
fine you said you had no space
yeah you can leave items on the floor
while you move the chest itself and then
stuff everything in the chest
afterwards yeah okay i got it okay
ah building is so cool some lanterns
lanterns oh i mean i don't think we need
them because
we have the glowing stones but oh if you
feel like decorating anymore
it's always good to have a bright face
yeah why not in a fast food restaurant
it will probably make it more
comfortable so
why not need a welcoming environment
especially in another drill where you
can feel safe
yes mmm chicken
okay oh sorry that's phoenix meat excuse
me no confusion there
i'm hungry i almost forgot what i came
here for
sailing sailing sailing
i will build the ceiling
[Music]
uh i just hope no one looks at it from
the top the top the cobblestone doesn't
look so pretty oh my god am i safe
okay he doesn't see me anymore it works
it works he doesn't see me
but i think i have to kill him so that i
can continue working
most restaurants use darkness to hide
while you're eating
what darkness apparently
chad said some restaurants that use the
darkness so you don't really see what
you're eating
is that what happens at cafe no they
know they're eating onix meat
they know they're eating phoenix meat
honest
honestly there's no doubt about what is
inside my burgers i make it very clear
there is no doubt about that
oh it looks really nice on the outside
oh you're back oh
welcome back welcome back and the guest
decided to
ignore me after one of the zombie pixens
are riding on the kfp employee
let me see
that is so cute i saw that before that
is so cute
is this the uh kitty zone for the kids
see my employees are so great they they
wait where's the button on there
they care for the children they hang out
with the children
it's just a great relationship that we
have with our with our guests with our
customers that's why we got such high
ratings everywhere
uh uh-huh i see yes
all right no i'm not doubting you i'm
not telling you not at all
but if you're doubting that what i just
said then you're doubting that my
employees are the best employees
ever and then i don't think they're
happy with that
oh sorry there's i put some cobblestone
where
where it doesn't belong oh hold up
oh my god nice dodge nice dodge kiana
yo i'm here i'm here i'm here
fight me oh i wanted to do the thing
with the sword but okay
we have we have a real french spill
potential
okay i'm trying i'm gonna go up there
again and
probably up until i make it up there
again there's gonna be another gas and
another gas and another cast and another
cast
and another one another one
why did i fall off
ah yeah
all right you keep working tensho yeah
i'm trying i'm trying
i i wanna i wanna get in there
there's just like a giant wall of walls
i'm going to get rid of that eventually
i'll do it now okay
so what else do we need to do though the
cooking station and there's not no no no
no there's
we don't cook it here we we import it uh
from the from the original brand yeah
but you still need
you still need like a cashier and stuff
oh yeah
we need do you have a strategy do you by
any chance have a leftover
bell bill
maybe i have maybe i still have one i
think i still have a leftover bell
is that my counter at the original
branch we have a bell
where you go like full karen and be like
ah
what is with my order i i i i i
don't i've been waiting for so long why
are you telling me to get out of the
store i don't give a [\h__\h] i have rights
to be here
this is unbelievable i will call the
police i will sue your [\h__\h] on you this
is how my
my my wait i ran out of i ran out of
cobblestone
but yeah we welcome we welcome karen's
in our store
we don't have a problem with parents we
can deal with them
yeah another oh i guess there isn't
oh it should be a problem or would hold
on here's the casting oh that's just you
yeah cast here
[Music]
so i guess you don't have cobblestone
then i should i'm gonna go get some
okay okay we're almost done with the
ceiling though the ceiling looks like
[\h__\h] though
i mean maybe from the inside yeah for
stairs by chance
stairs i have a sandstone stairs one
one yeah just one uh wait
how do i there you go oh my god
no there we go again
it's okay i'll fight i'll fight you
look at me
[Applause]
excuse me nice
we're kind of in a bad angle there nice
oh
very nice
professional tennis player
in in one of my favorites the rest
concrete
oh red carpet on the inside
yeah the the serving but actually
uh outside would be nice too to have
some
more color on the outside like maybe
how about
how about using it
i know where to use it i know where to
use it i think
um
uh do you want to give me the red
concrete
yeah i can give you a hug wait thank you
thank you thank god these toys
[Music]
i would say uh it should be
either the ground level because i i
think i made the kfb original branch
also with a red ground
like like no it was it was black and
then i think it was
red maybe or i mean we don't have to
completely cop it
we could make for example this part red
ah
and i think that would look quite nice
i can't pick it up i can't pick it up
let's see i see my inventory
god damn it okay all right nicer
nice oh nice yeah i like it i think i
like it i think good
should we make uh this column here red
too
maybe the one next to the door
yeah okay yeah or the one
yeah probably would have the right one
or
uh or yeah okay okay idea idea
we could wait do you have a silk
attached to not destroy the
the glass oh okay well then it's bye-bye
so i was thinking we put glass
here again so that it said two two
oh got it i don't can we put
uh uh red in the middle
and then instead of yes yes oh we can
okay and then here the glass
oh very nice
oh we don't have glass oh i have a
little bit of glass
i have eight okay and that might just be
enough
that's just enough yeah okay now let's
just leave the back don't mess it up
nice
nice okay the back can stay the latest
oh this looks cute without
this changing color it's nice oh that's
supposed to be the cash register
that's cute that's a cute idea
oh the button you need you need like a
button laura
okay not at home beside you ah
that's fine uh i also prepared
stop banging
where did you put it here
oh this one isn't
wait and oh we don't have a ceiling here
ah yeah i was going to get the
cobblestone but then we did something
else
but i don't like the ceiling is there
nothing prettier that we can use
that's also strong like iron
me that's gonna take a lot of iron but
we have a lot of iron
don't we we could try it oh
or stone actually just not cobblestone
just one it's like polish
oh yeah that sounds good i think i have
a bunch at home okay
let's i think we should make one trip
home
but i am going to leave some of the
materials in the
in the chest
[Music]
i only use pressure plates outside
because the pickled and stuff
what oh chad was saying we should use
pressure plates on the outside too but i
said i don't use it
i mean we can always do like uh
[Music]
okay back to home should we try polish
dirt
polish what polish dye right oh
i think i have some at home it's the
same material as our base in another
so you can see on the way back
i'll bring some minecarts good idea
bye bye
oh you could make a red and white jacket
roof yeah but the roof kind of has to be
something else than concrete because
apparently uh concrete doesn't burn but
it explodes still
so we want to make it out of stone
like some some kind of stone
so not not everything can be fancy but
we'll make it as fancy as possible
quartz block
quartz bug
that would require quite a lot this is
the um
how much it's going away
do we look like we have time for you
we're we're successful
yeah this is what it looks like what do
you think
yep okay okay toy story
okie dokie
so as i was saying we are we are
successful business women we don't have
time to deal with these stupid magma
thingies
okay you bring those was i supposed to
bring something else too
where are we pretty much done i have to
check if i have i want to just look for
a belt
and the site oh i do have quite a lot i
have a lot
whoa okay i can bring some
bell actually do you have a lot of
of those streamlights left ah
i think there's like i think i have like
in the in the nether chest
yeah i think i think
do i not have any bells left
bells no i thought i had like one more
bell do you not see a bell
i don't see a bell i want a bell
i mean maybe if i eventually follow you
can only get from
um village poses right
yeah yeah but i think the the close by
ones
we hold it do you have one
nope i did not um
i think yeah oh you can craft it with
gold
what oh i thought oh
that makes sense belle
what's it called what's it called no you
can't okay
no you can't you can't so i guess it's
just it's an item that you have to get
from a village
unfortunate i'll eventually add one
when i find another one
we're almost done now almost
there i'm gonna start putting the uh
ceiling back
oh you're back in the never oh yes oh
okay
on the way back
[Music]
i wonder what quartz blocks look like
though
we will need to farm a lot of courts
don't we um
but it's everywhere it wouldn't and we
wouldn't like it
i think but um no it's okay with that
die right
although i don't want the one i think
i'll change
why haven't you opened the taco bell yet
uh when is gonna be the opening of a
taco bell i don't know
i haven't thought about what to uh
let's do for the friendship you're sure
well tacos
wait are they tacos in the game like
visual ones
are there tacos i feel like i've seen
them
yeah right oh my obvious disconnected
it'll be back it'll be back oh
it'll be back well good that we have two
streams going
um hello guys how are you doing guys
do you want to fight i don't want to
fight oh you don't want to
you do the either the gas style just
keep things
if i look up like that i'll probably i
am here i see it
not up there that's dangerous
i'm not trying to aggro it i thought you
were fighting it
i was i'm trying to leave it burning
like that uh actually kind of looks
like oh yeah
yeah i mean that we're not gonna be
going up there anyways so
we can just light it on fire with like
foot and steel
that's that's nice i like that because
their boss is a phoenix so
oh nice you killed it
good job good job okay i think i'm
you'll see it from so far away even when
you get lost you'll be like oh yeah
that's kfb
i mean i i don't think anyone will get
lost
here you sure about that i'm i'm now uh
open to the fires opening some
applications welcome
congratulations you are you are part of
kfb now congratulations
congratulations oh they're children
though i need to bring some seats
congratulations you are hired
what's going on over here and you get a
job and you get a job
and you get a job and you get a job
and they're probably going to escape
because um
because of the automatic could be maybe
make the inside a button too so that
they don't escape i wonder
i don't think they can trigger the
pressure plate are you sure about that
they're very smart my employees are very
smart
what do you mean they're gonna die
what what do you guys mean they're gonna
die
yeah they're too light to trigger the
pressure face i think
really no they're triggering it they are
triggering
it but then he didn't make it outside me
but they're they're gonna figure it out
like how my cat figured out to to open
doors
i heard that you're trying to escape huh
mama won't let you escape you applied
for this job and you're gonna work it
now
okay i'll bring some food for you guys
i forgot about just get a top-down view
on everything that's happening
what what
look up hi
though i was surprised myself because
first thing we're like
i don't want that she's making a
branson never i'm not going to work that
as hell
but now they're like super excited about
it i wanted this there there you go
there you go are you guys okay blink
twice if not
i don't think they can blink there you
go so they're okay
should we actually
i mean there's probably gonna be more
guests that are gonna help you with that
they will gladly definitely put more uh
stuff here and they can burn
up i need to dig more of those
though um
problem like
stop i will put you in the usual room
and i will i will keep your eyes open i
have my methods
i didn't you know i didn't wanna i
didn't
didn't want to be
i wanted to be a good leader i wanted to
be
i wanted to be in good minds is not the
answer can't you
i know i know i know but
sometimes they kind of they kind of they
kind of made me who i am now
i didn't want it to be like this i
didn't want to be this violent
i didn't want them to like be scared of
oh
they're running no
[Music]
don't let them go they're still children
they're not going to be okay and they're
never alone
i'm worried about my children
no i'm trying to protect them
i thought a lion raises
their club because tough
they're not gonna be okay i have to
protect them you're free now
no no no
no no no no you guys are all sending me
mixed signals why you guys
what do you mean see your boss you guys
applied for this job and now you want to
run
i don't understand you guys you know
you're so soon
i don't know what you did you really let
them all escape
you know no they did it on their own
they're smart as you said well there's
still a bunch of them in there okay
well good luck surviving okay
good luck i'll give you some food
because i love you
good luck surviving good luck
oh my god there's so many escapers yeah
you were supposed to take care of this
what is it you're not gonna eat my
children are you wait they're coming oh
my god
they're coming after me oh wait oh wait
i can't bring them back hr is not my
my position that's not my job potential
okay my children come over here
come over here let me feed you mama
mama brought some food come here you
love your mama don't you
you don't do you do you do that you love
your mama right
right right right let me feed you
mama got some food come here babies
mommy babies yo no
baby i love you i love you too
oh i'll my cute father i need to bring
some uh
food and stew okay inaudible
oh i'm so proud of you guys and are you
gonna grow up
i'm scared for them why
don't worry about it yes it's mama you
can never resist your mama
come here come here get some food come
here follow me
oh such a good baby a good baby
yes good baby good baby good baby
ah so proud of my babies
um you're going back to the real world
yes could you bring stuff yeah could you
bring um
uh like maybe like uh four fences and
two gates or something i'm not sure how
much i need to make this properly but
yeah we need to i mean i'm just
i'm just doing this for them like if
they're gonna escape then they're gonna
be out there and jump into lava and [\h__\h]
i don't want
that's that's dangerous come here babies
come here
ah they came back to mama
oh that's the right choice babies that's
the right choice
interesting how they see me through the
windows but the ghasts
doesn't gas they don't anyways we always
come back of course you do
did i come here for again what oh flynn
and steel right
oh baby
what happened guys weren't we supposed
to escape no
it's dangerous outside you got to stay
with mama
trust me mama is pistol just sit under
my feathers i'll warm you
i mean it's already pretty warm out here
but still
um actually it might be too wrong for
you guys so maybe i should put some air
conditioning in here but
yeah okay
you know how did you guys ever see like
um
uh an image of of
a chicken and even after after
she um uh hatched her babies
even after that she still uh they did
the
the mama chickens will still sit on
their babies
and then she then they would stand up
and then wow you see
under the fluff coming out so many so
many little babies
it's so cute it's so cute
it's so adorable
ah they're all talking to me they love
their mama
it's too late guys they couldn't make it
it's the right choice
he sit on us they want they want they
like that they want to be sit on
there's two types of employees in the
world
exactly or yes
there's only one time you know
yes are you gonna be back soon come here
oh wait i did have some fans but i
didn't have a gate so
um could you outside of the door because
i'm gonna i'm gonna um
i have there just put all the chickens
here we put the fence right here and
then put the gate right here
but they have to to clean the tables and
stuff
oh you can lift them up once in a while
don't worry about it
but they're gonna no i want them i only
brought one and six fences
we're we're running short but like
if you put it like right in front of the
door the gate there's a truck right
there
oh oh we can move it we can move it
uh we have some customers yeah we're not
open yet dude
we're not open go away i'll just give
you i'll give you the fences you can
i don't need props to mama has to
um i can i can take care of them my
babies i don't know what i can do
oh they're skating
and my babies i just i just hatched them
i can't give them away yet
wait i think you took the youtube
fencing anyways
oh actually you can work while doing the
uh
doing the uh babysitting job
okay but now they're gonna run out
where's my popcorn
where's that popcorn all right
i'm gonna get them back i'm gonna get
them back no problem
[Music]
can it be here i guess it can
wait you only made one like 28.
yeah i had i brought what i had okay
oh that's fine why does it
oh how does it do that because of the
button
why does it do that why does it do that
i don't like it
okay
[Music]
okay this is a really annoying people
are gonna
be really frustrated when they try to
get into kfp
put fences and then put pressure plates
how do you make pressure plates uh
you go to the crafting cable and type
and pressure
do i have any i don't have any of the
material
all right can i not use cobblestone
can you not use cobblestone for that uh
i'm not sure
no apparently not oh
i have iron okay let's go for iron then
you might want to fill in this little
uh
clip of death right beside you there's a
cliff of death
let me see oh my god
stop it go away okay right here
wait a second so if i just put it in
front there it will work
oh it works nice
a second let me hydration time guys
hydrate yourself
okay they're still backing banging i was
unbelievable
context you know the context do i have
to repeat myself
why do i have to repeat my viewers in
the chat
well that's their fault
i'm not gonna keep on explaining myself
also maybe i should just uh
uh
i'm gonna recreate this whole thing i
gotta fix those rails
ah but no problem
um
what is it uh one of your employees
tried to go into the
skated oh he wants to go inside oh i see
now they're regretting
that they left me
you never leave mama it's not gonna end
well
no one wants to leave mama mama's
cooking is the best
although i don't really cook but you
like cooking yep
ah you don't really
i mean i wait
i can cook some french toast and some
wow that fire up there really does look
badass wow that's so good
what is it what is it stupid pink
i ran out of rails again goddammit
oh i thought i brought some oh
but where did you put them uh
i'm not sure where is this a clip of
that
inventory okay is this a clip of that
yeah okay
i'm gonna try to fix it
i don't want my chickens to fall in here
mama takes care of already
so i think uh kfb is done
yeah something sounds like it's opening
but
let's not worry about it
i mean whenever the too many employees
escape
i'm just gonna hire some more until they
understand that escaping is not an
option
one day they will understand run away
they will understand they will
understand that it's better for them to
to just stay right
hey it looks pretty good no okay it's
not
maybe we should have made the ceiling
like too high oh well
good way okay so
uh i'll take everything that is puzzled
to get in
yep oh wait uh wait i'll put the rails
in
the chest i didn't bring any redstone uh
oh actually some stuff though
ah i have one
it's okay i'll fix it eventually
but everything food really everything
sounds like it's burning because of the
seal
that's a nice uh frying sound that's
true that's true
do you have some clothes like fried coal
oh
i know do you want to put it into the
furnace
oh yeah
so we can cook that and then yeah
there's all there's gonna be some fresh
food too
nice actually
[Music]
i guess a fridge the fridge would be
looking good
[Music]
or maybe a red fridge go away
go away baby okay red fridge
totally looks like a fridge nice
yeah with that i think uh
okay has been completed
right there nice
[Music]
the opening of kfb is today
the second branch has been finished
stand here so we can oh yeah i want to
take a
look oh it's looking really good yeah
[Music]
employees look here
let me get another branch wait let me
let me get
let me so we can take a prop right here
guys so we can take a proper
um picture let me
let me let me grab my employees
oopsie okay now they're looking at me
nice cheese
[Music]
i'll hatch it you guys just keep on
laying the eggs
let's take one from the outside but
first we would probably have to kill the
gas
wait a second this is so confusing
oh it's running away coming back i don't
trust it
i'm missing all my shots
nice nice shot
i'm burning i'm burnt i'm burning i'm
burning i'm burning
i'm also burning where are you i
fell down though the pits
the pit of them
is it destroying everything again okay
if you say
okay for now kfb is the the
safest place in the nether now uh
something blew up right outside but it
can be fixed is it my reality maybe we
should reinforce the outside too a
little bit
yeah yeah
and then when i have some time i'll i'll
put some concrete here and there
the real don't worry about it
kill it did it run what
the guest oh think we killed
i think we killed it oh no it's
something is it over there is it that
one
anyway we gotta take a picture quick
yeah okay and
right here on this side but maybe maybe
like from an angle oopsie here
uh which angle just from here is okay
the front ah this angle looks like
anything back
cheese cheese cheese
cheese yum with a jumbo probably trying
to get
do you want to jump on free oh
okay hold on hold on hold on okay one
two three
and that part was made one over there
one
two three okay oh wait wait one more one
more i push the wrong
button one two
okay i'll i'll i'll jump later but you
just jump when you're here free okay
okay one two three four
i kind of support for myself okay maybe
it wasn't the whole second one
one more time one more time one two
three
no why why would i do it i heard it i
only had eggs i don't lay eggs
there's a big difference there
okay babies babies my cute babies
my babies my babies
are they are growing up already yeah
well anyway
they're like eggs so okay
thanks for watching thanks for watching
and i have fun working at kfp we are
still taking applications if you're
looking for a job
this is the time i think at the moment
it's very
a lot of people might be looking for a
job so um i think they're this is a
really great place to work
our employees only have good things to
say about kfp
and um maybe in the future taco bell
will have an opening too
in cooperation with uh with with me i
would love to help you
although you'd probably be better off
thank you for helping me build the
second branch of kfc today
thank you we could have probably done it
much faster
but but yeah we took okay the
the process is part of the fun
yeah nothing yeah i'll end it with
eating some nice cooked pork chop and
nut chicken
we would never we would never cook
chicken
no no no no no no see i have pork chops
in my hand
everything's all right don't worry guys
where did that come from i don't know
quick hide bye bye guys
[Music]
i went to my ending screen did you
okay
oh it looks so nice it looks so pretty
oh wait they still hear me goddammit ah
they still here
[Music]
you