Ade
[Music]
Holo Live production official app that will make you love Pipopapo Oshi even more This is
brought to you by Holo Plus.
Good morning! This is the early spring of Hololive's new staff.
This distribution is a
nurturing student created together with the fans.  Broadcasting is based on the concept,
and plans and questions can be
submitted on the official app Holoplus. We hope that with everyone's help, we and the program
can grow together,
so we are growing in various ways, including home videos.
[Music] I hope
someday it will change into something even more wonderful. I'll do my best. I
'll send you a relaxing message, so
please watch over me warmly
. Well then, let's go, Yosei's Holo Holiday
Kakkokari
[Music]
No, this cat's oyster  Kakokari is also starting to be quite lively, I
think.Look,
the one on the right as you face everyone, I
wanted to come to see you the other day, but it's not that big of a deal.  So, even
though it
's hot in August, I've received a lot of
compliments on sending it to you, so I'd like to go ahead and send it to you.But it's
about time.Today's guest is
here.  It's around that time, but I
wonder if it's about to come. There are loud footsteps.
Aaaah, they're playing ping-pong. Go ahead, pipopipopo
, hey hey, I'm sorry to disturb you. I'm sorry to disturb you.
What a lively audience! So
many people came today.
First of all, Calliope, please introduce yourself.
I'm Ao, I'm Ada,
Mina, Hololive English, I
'm a female Calliope, and I'm a Grim
Reaper. I'm a Lapa singer.  Streamer Calliope Calliope
Thank you very much for your support, Senkyu,
thank you, and Kia Sao,
Hi, Kikeni Hololive English's Emiss
's tall character. Today, I'm not a mayor.  It
's a frog,
it's a frog It seems like Nodoka-chan likes frogs,
and there are some frog-chans here, too.
Wow, good morning, hello,
good evening, holo live, no, it's a mistake.
Thank you.
By the way, welcome to Japan. Ah,
Uruka, go home, go home, go home, go home.
Yes, we had three customers come today from Misu.
Mr. Kaoa, it
's been a while since we've seen each other, but that's right. It's been a
while. And Mr. Inas, it's
nice to meet you. I'm glad to see you.
Oh,
Mito that cute, cute, cute,
but you don't want to be in contact with you.
Yes, I'm so excited. Are you
enjoying Japan to the fullest? It's hot. Yes, it's hot, it's
hot, please stop being so hot. It
's the worst. I'm not really good at hot weather. No, I
love winter. Yes, everyone
loves winter, right?  But it's still fun, you know. Even though it
's still a secret yesterday, I
had a lot of fun. I
wonder if I made a mistake or something.  It's
still a secret. I don't know about these three people. I don't
know. I don't know. They're cute. I'm
looking forward to it. Thank you very much. So, even though it's hot today, I'm going to reveal everything to everyone, so I'm going to have a good time.
Please leave it to me. There's no
Japanese representation, there's no Japanese representation.
Yes, that's right, so this time,
everyone came here on a follow-up holiday. It
's a special party. There was an announcement that three people like this would
come all at once.
Because we have big news  I do
n't
know. I don't know. I want to know. I don't know.
Well, I guess
I can just go and go. Is
that okay?
[Music]
Men Actually, there's an overseas version of Holoplus coming out.
That's right. The
global version of HoloPlus has been officially released.
From this release,
HoloPlus
will be available outside of Japan. And official news and originals.  The
content will now be distributed in English,
and fans
will be able to interact with each other in the language. Yes, the release is coming
soon, so stay
tuned for the next news and check out the announcements on Official X.
Looking forward to it!  It's the best! I've been waiting so long. It looks like I've been
waiting. All of you overseas who have been waiting
can also see the Hololive schedule on the app. Oh
yeah, you can watch the official news
in both Japanese and English. Yeah, I'm happy. I'm
happy. Happy
Iyu.
FinallyMay we use it too
?So we
are always looking for projects expressed in ``Holoplus'', but this time,
as a test before the release of the global version of Holoplus, we are looking for projects in English.
Thank you so much for all the comments from both Japan and overseas.Thank you very much for your
comments.Thank
you very much for your comments.Thank you very much for your comments.Thank you very much for your comments.Thank you very much for your comments.  I'm
preparing for a lot of things, so I'm going to
do a lot of things as much as time allows.Yes, my
toy fingers, duck,
duck, duck, baby, why, why, why, I
'm on top, I'm all alone again.
Isn't that where the tall Doka-chan is? I'm
sure. Today, Ina-san
will be the main character,
and the MC-chan will say yes to the MC,
so this time I'll comment in Japanese.
In addition, there were so many comments from people overseas that we
came up with this lineup.Senior/
Junior ASMR tongue twister drawing contest
JapanPa Yes, I see.There
was also a comment that they wanted us to make a dish.  I wanted to do it for a while,
but I guess I can't cook in the studio.So
for now, let's go ahead and
make something, Nodoka-chan.I want to try some of your cooking next time.I want to
eat your home-cooked meals.
On the other hand, when I cook, the studio
explodes.If it was Sumotokai, I-chan would rather do that baking than cooking.
[Laughs]
Thank you very much.I'm
looking forward to it.Also, I
'd like you to choose from among these.  Everyone,
which one should I choose? Well, you can choose first.
Go ahead, Ape-san, go ahead.
Okay.
Now, tongue twisters. Okay, yes, I came from tongue twisters.
So let's take a look at the comments we received.
Here they are.
Don, no, Japanese is
not, Twister, yes, Japanese-style tongue twister
showdown, and
thank you for your ideas.
So this time, the one that received the most posts both in Japan and overseas was the
pun twister and
tongue twister.  I
'm sure he's good at tongue twisters,
but Mr. Kape does a lot of rapping,
so he's
probably a good rapper.
I said that I wanted to do it myself, but what about Eina-san? I don't mind those
puns, but it's okay.
The words are a little lame, but it's fine.
If you
speak German, you might be able to do it.
Germany.  If that's the case, I'm sure you're good at it.Today I'll probably
be in Japanese.Today I'll be talking
about Nedemo Flow.I've come up with an original tongue twister for Live,
so I'll
challenge you with an original one.Holo
Lifetime Toys Yes Hololai
Since it's Time Star, let's
do our best to adjust to the first theme, Inanis-san. Let's do our
best. Yes, this is it. Don Don, Inanis-san
's nice chair. Oh yes, let's talk fast and
do this three times three times.
Ah, I don't know, that's okay, uh, yeah,
3 times, 3 times, Ina-san's challenge.Twister
twister, start ina, swiss inanis without inis, nice,
inanis, ina, inasu forgets the eni.  It's nice
of
Inasu, try that chair, do your best, do your best, Inasu, nice, nice, nice, nice,
nice to Inasu, nice, nice, nice to Inasu, it's cute, so it's
okay, it's cute, it's clear.  Let
's go,
it's nice, it's nice,
it's soooo
smooth, it
's so smooth.
As expected of Gomai, it's true that Nino is
a bit of a karma, so it's difficult at times.That's
right.When I say my name, I
always say Nino, so when Inanisu is in front of me, I
feel a little emotional.
That's okay.
That one
seems more difficult. That's okay. So, yes, that's okay.
So, yes,
that's the tongue twister, but it goes on and on.
And the second one was done by Chiara-san, Nigiwa-A-Kiwawa-san. I
definitely
can do it. I'm
obviously tired of this
. Chiara isn't tired of this yet. What is this? I see, it looks like it's
going to be good.  I don't know if I can
make it or not, so let's try it three times. It's
A's challenge. It
started clearly in autumn.
[Music]
Thank you for being wonderful.
How about this?
I'll try it.
clearly
Aki, do your best,
do your best Aaaaaaaaaa
clearly not a good thing It's obviously not a good thing Chiara is clearly tired It's clearly a
tired Kiara It's clearly a tired Kia Here it comes That's great
Yeah that's great That's okay
Lastka-chan I can't sleep
Scary scary  If it's scary or scary, then it's
really embarrassing and embarrassing. It's so
true. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right. Yours is extremely difficult. Otherwise, it won't work, right?
So let's take a look at Callio-san's theme.Calliope
Karaoke in Paris
Calliope Karaoke in Paris Oh, Calliope Paris And
Kao Yeah, yeah, but you can say it right now Yeah, I've already
said it, I can say it, I've already got it
Alright, let's go, Calliope-san.
It's a challenge. I'll do my best to see if I can make it.
Start
Calliope, wait a minute, I'm nervous, I'm
nervous. Fall down, wait a minute, one time late.
Calliope, Paris, then I'll do it. Sounds great.  Calliope
in Paris Calliope Calliope
in Paris Calliope Calliope Paris Calliope Paris it's Paris Time Time How about calliope in Paris?
Oh, please stop it, stop it, stop it, stop
it. Stop it. Is that no good? Is it okay?
Official
stream Embarrassing, embarrassing official
Excuse me for my heart-pounding bow.Opera Opera Opera
Opera Opera Opera Opera Opera Opera
But even in the book, I was able to
say it fluently three times, so it was a success for Kao.
But there's one more difficult
word, it seems like there's a tongue twister, but yeah, let's
do it. Ah, this is that. Kaun,
yeah, that's that. Hehe,
everyone. This is all a little too good.  This is a very
expensive proposal from Kia. Let's go
to Zimantan Star. German
quick words are difficult for me too, but I
came up with it at the last minute, so it doesn't appear on that screen.
Yeah, I'll say it once, please.
Yes, hehehehehehehehehehehehe I
can't do that. So
I want everyone to try this. I see.
Fisher's Fritz Fish and
Fritz.  I
wrote it in katakana for the time being
, but first, let's start with Kari-chan, who seems to be good at it. Do your best, Ka-chan, and
do it in an American pronunciation. Let's go to Kao-san.
Let's
start.
Fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish, fish.  It's not just the fish
, it's all turned into a fish.
Now then, I'm going to
make a fufufufufufu. I can do it, fififufufufu.
Can I say Slowly ONE?
[Laughs] I've
made a fish!
Enodoka-chan can you say this?
By the way, what does it mean? Well, what does it mean? The
person who catches that fish, the angler, the angler, the one who
catches that fish, the one who catches the fresh fish.  I
can do it, so I
have Fish Fritz Fish and Flitch Hooka, but I don't think they'll get any faster if I call them,
so please listen to me as much as possible and
try it. I'll try it.
Fushifutsufushifushifushifishhifushi Fish please.
Yes, yes,
thank you very much.
Okay, what shall we do? Hmm, then
I'll choose.Yes, hmm.Next,
let's have a drawing competition.Yes, let's do a
drawing
competition.Here's the post I received.Yes, all
three of us are good at drawing, so
let's do an illustration quiz.  I want you to watch it.
Ina-chan will finally appear on Flo's Holiday, so I
'm really looking forward to it. I
'm going to eat some Japanese sweets, and then I'll watch a video where they draw each other's pictures.  Taito
But for some reason, we
used to do this as a collaboration when we were early on.I
remember the illustrations we did, so much so that I
wanted to do it again.I thought it would be a good
idea to do that project again.  Let's
write it down for
everyone.Use your tablet to draw Calliope,
Kia next door, Kia next door, Enari next door, and Eri next door.Let's
draw Calliope
in about 10 minutes.
Yes, please make a presentation. If the person who wrote it
likes it, it means that it has passed, so let
's go. Okay, okay. Let's get started.
Okay, this is okay. Let's
show them how they are drawing.
Don't show it.
Ki, Ki is a frog right now. There's a frog
in the picture, and then there's Calliope in the picture.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, Ki has that face,
orange, uh, she has bangs.
What is that, everyone? Yes, this shark is
good at drawing. Everyone has their own taste. I
get the impression that you don't like drawing. Everyone,
when did you start drawing? Well, quite a long time
ago, when I was little, I used to draw a lot.
But yeah, yeah, I say when I was little,
but it wasn't that small, but I completely
gave up on it, and I haven't written much about it. That's
amazing. Inanis-san is already
progressing so fast.
Well, we have 10 minutes.
That one minute is enough for Ina-chan.
Is Hae-san the type of person who draws quickly? She's quite fast. She's very quick. Just
like that girl I don't understand.  It's the best!
And it seems that Galio-san is also drawing this frog
Kia-san.
And what's the cute hair style?
What's the name of the Blaze book
? Is it called Braille? Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, wait a minute, now...
Chorogi Wow, Demoi-san also wrote a lot of Ako-
chan. I started to see A-san.
Nesan
[Music]
Oh,
wow, that's amazing. Ina-chan is so
fast. This is so fast.
Wait, Te-
chan
[Music]
Akara's speed.  It's not just that it's
good, it's
amazing because it's of high quality.It's amazing.By the way, I'm the
only one left-handed among them.
Hey, don't look at that cute girl.
Don't look at her. It's okay. Please don't look at her
. She has pointed ears and a round sound.
She's also writing a
cute pose.  I have it, I
have it, I
have it, it's
true, it's cute,
it's cute, so I'm
asking everyone to make something right now.
When we see what you write,
doesn't it make us want to create something?We
have a small announcement.We have
just started recruiting temporary program logos on Holoplus for the holiday program Holo, which is currently being distributed.  They
said yes and it was adopted. Why do we
still have a logo because of Holo's holiday past
? We don't have a budget. It looks like we don't have a budget,
so we're all going to make it and broadcast it.
So we're looking for a logo.
Details of recruitment trips at  Please
take a look at Holoplus. Isn't this even in English
? How do you say it?
[Music]
Thank you for the project. Thank you for your help. Please
take a look at Holoplus for details.
One person can apply as many times as they like.  Yes, it's possible,
but I'd love for everyone to
give me a logo.
Please give me a logo.
What kind of logo would you like Nodoka to have? What's
your ideal? Yes, but I like that frog.  I
think it would be nice if it had a hand-made feel to it, like the one with the frog in it.I think it would be nice if it had a handmade feel to it, like something you'd see on this show.I'm
sure I'd like to go home too.I'll
be waiting for you.
[Music]
Okay, by the way, how's everyone far
? Ah, well, see you then. The picture is being completed, and I
wonder if everyone is writing. By the way, I
wonder what happens when you draw something.  I've
been influenced by this manga and anime, and I
like this anime.Hello, I
watch a lot of anime.What do you
watch?I wonder
what kind of things you like, Ina-san.I
like them all.  I like all of
them. I watch a lot of series, so
yeah, yeah, yeah, I like fantasy. I
like Kado Hunter, so I like
Adventure and Bechi, and
that's Swiss Bifu.
2 Yeah, yeah, it's really all about it. Do you
like Japanese anime? Yes, I like it. Yes,
yes, yes, I might like it.
Can you tell me your name? I think it's okay. I think it's
okay. I'm that monster.  I
like the Monogatari series the most, and apparently there's a
new one coming out right now, but I'm
watching it from beginning to end while simultaneously watching that Megee series.  I'm
looking at it as if I'm remembering it.  It's
actually longer than I expected.I
watched the first movie from the beginning,
but I haven't gotten all the way to the end
and haven't been able to watch the new one yet.Whatever
it is, it's amazing.  It's
been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time, so who is my favorite? Nako-chan has been my favorite for a long time,
but now that I'm watching it again for the first time in a long time, I can't help
but feel that I love Hanekawa and
Hane-chan as well.
Wow, yeah, I get it, I'm Shinobu Shinobu I.
After all, I watched Kizumonogatari and I
love it.Which version of
Shinobu's
version do you like the most?I'm sure there
are many, right?  Nager?
Yes, I like being small. It's
cute, isn't it? Yes, it
's difficult, but I'd like to see it as a teenager once more.
When I say teenager, I mean someone who
looks like a 17-year-old, oh so cute, so cute.They're
all cute and cute.I
like Calliope.There are anime like Aga.Actually, I
like dark fantasy.My favorite is
But, uh, I really don't know, there's a manga
called Acta that I like the most, and it's a
pretty new one, but next year there's
going to be an anime, oh yeah, it's been decided, it's
been decided, it's been decided.
I'm looking forward to it.I really love this series.What do I
like about it?It's art.The
art style is so incredible that it's impossible to imagine.The
designs are
a bit Japanese-style, and there's also a
bit of foreign style in Usu.The
action scenes are the best.  Seriously, it's
the best gacha that's interesting,
it's garbage, it's garbage, you know who
it is, yeah, it's really
garbage, isn't that
what it's about?
Yeah, that's a really good story.
Well, I have one more thing I'd like to ask Kao-san. Yes,
Mr. Cap. Speaking of anime, you
were in charge of the ending of Isekai Suicide Squat. I
made it. Oh yeah.  How did it feel to be in charge of the anime's theme song? No, I
still can't believe it.
Yeah, I can't believe it now, so when I got the offer, I couldn't
believe what happened. I
felt like I was so happy.  I
didn't feel surprised. Actually, I suddenly felt like, "Oh, I see." It's like, "Is it true? I can't believe it." It's true, isn't it? Is it
true? Seriously, I'm starting to feel happy.
That's great.  Thank you very much.
Everyone, please check out Isekai Susite
Squat Ending Theme.
Please, everyone. I wonder if it's
time to play it?
Seriously, I'm the slowest out of all of them,
but it's okay, it's okay, I'm probably cute, I'm
nervous, my hands are sweaty, and that's
so bad, no, no, the pressure of my past is
on Gai-chan.
Everyone's good at it, so I'm sure I like Kia's drawings.It's okay.
I'll come back for more. It's okay.
[Music] The
drawings are a little too simple, but the one you
wrote earlier was amazing.
Thank you. It's hard to write. I'm sorry.  I'm sorry, I'm sorry, it's
okay, but I don't
know what to do. Kia-chan
is cute. Thank you. Draw
her so cute. Well, everyone still has a long way to go.
Nenodoka, before I greeted you a little while ago, I was
actually drawing some of your drawings. Well, it's
a little bit. I
want to see
this.  It's a
big welcome Holoro holiday and it
's the best. I'm
happy.
Thank you.  It's
just the face and the head,
and it's round and I'm sure it's squishy, so
yeah, it's likely to be added to Takayama.I hope it will be
added.It certainly looks like it is, so I
tried to write it with a slightly squishy feel.
Taponiponiponiponi
Poniponi yeah
So it's almost
time to stop playing Calliope It's okay to stop.
This is
good. Kali-chan's is definitely cute.
Her drawing is really cute.
Please, everyone, let's take a look at it starting from the person who tried it. I hope it comes
true, the one who wants to do it is able to do it.
Maybe it's a fishing touch.
Phishing is almost here, soon
Yes, how about Calliope?
Sorry,
hey, cute kfp and cute touches are
amazing. They're so cute, thank you Kiri-chan. I
tried my best. Yes, it's like this.
Yara-chan is cute, so hey, it's delicious.
Well, let's go
ahead and see what's next, Chiara-san, then let's take a look at the next one.
Hold on, let's go together for a moment. Uha, it's
nice. I want to decorate this. It's
really bad. It's so cute! It's so cute!
Alright then, Kia-san
is here, Su-san. Thank you. Add some color. That's
amazing. This pose is cute. It's
cute, isn't it?
[Music]
Wow, this is all decoration.
Thank you so much for being cute. Well, that's the end. Wow,
Innis-san is back. Calliope-
san. You've written to the last minute about me. Let's
take a look at Kao-san. Good.
Here it is.
Usu's favorite piece. The
bag is also really nice.
Yokorere.  Eh, I want to be written about by Ina-chan too. I
want to be written about by Ina-chan. Yoma, I'm such a cute person. Yeah, she's cute. Yoha, she's so cute, so cute, so cute. I feel like I'm writing about something like this.  It's
true that this is sexy.
Oh, I'm so happy. I want to sign something like, ``Thank you, Shinigami.'' I'm sure it's Sai, please.
Even if it's not after me. If I
sign it, I'll be a little
confused. No, I'm not sure if this is me.  I'm
cosplaying Paris-chan Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
What did you write on the first page? Yeah, I'm glad you saw it too. Okay
, let's
move on to the next one. There's probably about one more item left. Okay, so
for the last time, Nijaina-san, I'll let you choose. Which one should I choose? I'm
fine.  Let's talk to Tepa's juniors.
Oh nice. Let's see what this is all about.Here
are the benefits you received.Yes, please tell us as much as you can about each of the Oholomen.
Episodes with your good friends, the JP Holomen, will be posted on Hololive.
Before I join, I want to know if there are any JP Holomen after I join,
so I'm
asking everyone.It seems like I'm curious about the relationship with the members of Hololive JP today.  I'd
like to come,
but I don't know what to do first.Shall I do it?
Tell me some stories,
please.Yes, I have a
junior with whom I got along surprisingly well.Who
is that person?
Well, you're just my junior, so I've only recently
become really good friends with Raden from Leecross, and I
hope we can do one more collaboration all at once.I've
also been good friends with Ririka for
quite some time now.  Yeah, that's right.
Through my recent collaboration with Raden, I
learned a lot about her love for art, and
by that I mean art, she doesn't just love Japanese art,
but art from all over the world.  He
showed me all kinds of books, he
showed me all kinds of art techniques,
and I thought, oh, this kid is really
serious about something, and to my surprise, he
talked a lot about that topic.
If you're interested in Loppa's art museum, and you're
also interested in history, I can't believe you're the
same way.
Every time I collaborate with the Japanese members,
I go on a trip and
ask them to come and visit us in Austria next time, and
everyone says they're going, but they
don't
come, but Lale-chan is pretty serious about it.
Yeah, she said she wanted to go, and
I'm in the middle of making a passport and things like that,
which is amazing.It's progressing, and I'm really excited about living here.And
that's with Lyrica-chan, too.
of  I'd
like to travel a little bit. I'm
doing it. I'm so happy. It's the best. I'm so
happy. I'd love to hear more. I
look forward to hearing from you. There are so many art museums around the world that I'd like to visit.
Please do.
Please cover me if you have to make a passport. Thank you for going. How
about you? Ah, how about you. Honone and you both
also like seniors and juniors who like episodes, and
things like this that happened in the future. JP
members and things like this.  I want to try this  I'd
like to do this with other people.Yes,
that's right.I'm Ina-chan,
so I
talked about meeting a senior I like, and that's how I felt when I
met someone for the first time.Manager-
san  Yeah, yeah, yeah
, yeah, that's right.When I first
met Ren, I was like, Yeah, yeah, Kia
was there, right?That was quite a while ago.It was quite a while ago, really.No, yeah, that's right,
even when I was in the dark.  It's like it's the
manager's gigi, but Ina-
chan and Gai-chan
forced themselves to do it.I thought it was a prank, so I pretended to be that manager.That's
right, that's how it was.I'm a
fan of Un.  I said, ``Yes,
please sign.'' It was my cell phone, maybe it
was my iPad, and I was in the case, and I
said, ``
If you want, I can give you a thumbnail.'' I asked if it was okay, and he said, ``It's
okay,'' and gave me a thumbnail.
But wow, I can't believe it's so obvious.
So I asked her to please write my name as well,
and then I said ``I'm
Inanis'' and it was a huge success. Yes, it was a huge success.
There are a lot of times when I come to the studio
and I've never met that senior person before, and
when it's the first time, I
think it's the staff, oh yeah,
yeah, that's right.
When I met A-senpai for the first time, I thought A-senpai was a staff member, and I thought, "
Thank you for your hard work."
When I walked over to say hello, I
realized that it was Hua-senpai.  That's a bit
embarrassing. Na-chan didn't realize that
someone said that. I thought E-chan
was a staff member. I
thought Pria-senpai was that staff member.  I
don't think so. Yes, yes, that
's a problem with communication
. But some people wear hats, so they
wear hats, masks, and so on.
There are certainly times when it's difficult.
Kari-chan, too.  Oh yeah, it's
embarrassing and embarrassing.
It's a recent story, but we're
going to have a live show soon. We're going to have a live
show. Oh yeah, we're going to have a live show. Oh yeah, we're going to have a live show. Oh yeah, we'll be speaking English,
and we'll have some guests as well. We
'll have guests from JP members. Oh yeah, that's right.
And among those guests, I think there's someone who's
currently on Hololive, and there's someone who's
recommended by Holo, and I don't
really know if that person can speak English,
but I
don't have a lot of confidence in my English.  That's what I was told,
but I gathered up some courage and
decided to send a DM to someone asking them if they had any cute
questions or if they had any English questions, please
let me know.  I
'm sure there are people who speak English better than I do in Japanese, but you
can tell that I want to help somehow. I'm going to
send you a DM and start going around again. That's cute.
Yeah, I got a reply. I got a reply. I'm here. Please help me.  That
was good, that
might be a recommendation, it might be a good idea, it might be a good idea, it might be a good idea, it might be a good idea, it
might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing, it might be embarrassing.
But I don't want to because he's someone I really look up to,
but I understand that
when I met CC-senpai at the studio, my face turned really red.Well,
I get nervous every time, too, and I
wonder what people think of me.  Nanoun is also kind, I helped you, I
helped you in America, please help me a little in America. I
still have to study Japanese,
but I'm good at it. You're too
good. By the way, Mizuo-san.  Is there
anything you'd like to try? Masukari-
chan and I have a lot of
things to do, and there are a lot of things. Um, it's
really cool. I'd
like to take you to a restaurant. I
guess it's good. I'll take you there.
It's nice to have a cool date. I feel so
warm. I
'm praying that all your dreams come true.
Thank you very much. Is the
light coming out?  I'm so excited,
but now that I've heard all about that wonderful, wonderful story, it's almost time to say goodbye. Everyone, it's early. We've been talking about this for so long.
I want to hear what you like about it.
Anyway, I guess I'll do it after this,
but I have other projects that I'd like to do, so I
really
want to listen to ASMR.  I
'm wondering if I can do calliope, so after this, I'm thinking of doing it via membership distribution.As Yes, I think I'll do it
in both English and Japanese.Yeah,
I think it's my second or third time in ASR in my life.  If you
don't have much experience with ASR, you won't be able to participate.
Mina and I do a lot of Neka-chan,
but it's just the ones that hurt. I
'd like you to do something that hasn't hurt recently. So, that's it.
See you then  I'm going to
see you later on the membership-only distribution,
but finally, I heard that
Calliup and Chiara have some announcements for each of them.Okay, I'd
like to hear from Calliope.Yes, Minato,
Calliope recently released a new album.
Yes, it's called Phantomime. Yes, it's
Phantomime. Ah, it looks
amazing. I really worked hard on this album.
There are many wonderful collaborations,
so I want you to give it a listen.
Just yesterday, it
reached number 4 on the iTunes chart.
Yes, the total album is currently 7 or so,
but I want it to be 4 again, please. I
like 44, which is my favorite. I'm a Shinigami, so God's 4.  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, everyone,
I want you to
listen to it on streaming platforms, uh, Spotify, iTunes, etc. And, uh, I want you to buy the CD, too,
like Tower Records or other stores.
Please buy it from the store.There are all kinds of
score goodies, so you can get a lot of
goodies.The goods look great.Everyone is looking good.Oh yeah,
yeah, everyone is pretty good.I've
been listening to a lot of songs today, too.There are a
lot of really cool songs, so please
listen to them.  Please, everyone, I'd be very happy.
Please, please. Thank
you very much. Yes, thank you very much.
Next, Mr. Kia, please. Well, I would
like to give you a message from me. Well, we are where we are right now.
There is also a notice from Nekari-chan and Hi-chan, so yes, August
2425 Eko This week, the
entire 2nd episode of Wae Love English The
local live Breaking Daishi will be held.  It's so
bad,
it's so bad, this week is this week, it's
amazing, it's amazing, everyone, the visuals
are coming out now, it's really cool, and the number
has increased since the last live.  The number of
tickets has increased, and of course we have more guests, so we don't have any on-site tickets anymore, but we do have online tickets, which are on sale right now.
Outline Outline Here is the URL.There
are both Japanese and English versions.Please
support us at Flori Wings.Thank
you very much.It
's this weekend.I'm so excited.
Well, everyone, it's not bad, it's not bad, it's not
bad, but everyone is doing their best, they're doing their best, and I'm looking forward to it, so I want to tell you all that it's
going to be held at the King Theater.Thank you very much.
I
also have some news for you! The
Hollow Live production official app that will make you love Holo even more
will be celebrating its 1st anniversary next week on August 29th. It's the 1st anniversary of its official release.
Congratulations!
Today, on the occasion of our one year anniversary, we are planning to do a little project,
so please take this opportunity
to download it.
Thank you very much for your support.
As I mentioned earlier, the
Holoplus global version will be
officially released soon, so check out the announcement here on Official X.
Check, check, check,
check.  We
're also looking for logo designs, so we're looking forward to your applications.
Please, we'll wait, we
'll wait. So,
thank you very much for coming to visit us today.
Thank you very much.  It
was fun, it was great, thank you. No, I
was happy. So after this, I'm going to try the official
membership deluxe plan
limited edition, and I
'm going to try it out for the ASMR people who couldn't do it this time with the official membership deluxe plan.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
Well, that's it for Holo's holiday. Well
then, everyone, let's go together. Plus bye-bye
again.
[Music]
Bye
OGJA