[Music]
do
ah uh okay
ah go excellent please what the hell is
going on okay cool
got it i had to restart
somehow
i had to restart somehow
i would i i
was like oh yeah time to um time to go
for the stream and then press the um
mutes button on my console and like
why doesn't it
it stays lighting up though it why is it
not a muting
there we go there we go there we go
professional streamer let's go
i had to yeah i i just reinforced it you
know it's the classic have you turn it
on and off again
okay a um okay this is actually for the
room code so uh i'm gonna
okay this this card changes
anyways you're welcome um guys uh so
and today we're gonna do our very very
last individual training um
yay cool right
you wanna play with qr2 yeah yeah um
you some of you guys do i thought she
was streaming at like
in two hours from now
but then
i just saw a waiting room and i wait
isn't it now
so i was like i don't know maybe i'll do
some individual practices and if um
maybe like in an hour or something i
know i'll talk to her too like if she
if she allows me to join in then i'll go
to her place yeah
it'd be like that anyways yeah um
i unlocked some stuff
okay exactly one thing today and it's
not the cloud glider so i don't know how
i feel about that but we're gonna set up
a multi-player room you guys had a
multi-player room in an online playroom
sorry as usual
um warm up for the both of you exactly
um
yes so anyways um did you guys watch
today's uh this morning stream
did you guys watch it how was
[Music]
zero 970 yeah let's use the old one
because i don't really mind
0.977.0846
7755.
oh cool
join jjj and you hope yeah sorry guys
i'm i'm just too lazy to create a new
room
uh yes
it was so fun it was pain hey listen i'm
just gonna be honest with you i'm just
gonna be honest with you um
this morning it really did feel like
i was in
you know
i was surrounded by people who are
really really good
you know
so even if i don't get pro cup like i
got a little taste of it i feel like you
know
it was brutal it was it was but the fact
that you know i was surrounded with so
many strong players
it actually felt really nice um i
thought
oh okay i don't think anybody cares but
after the stream um i sent a message to
sweden senpai
wait what was the word that you taught
me oh it's ke chong ketung
i wanna try my best so i can say like oh
i'm gonna i'm gonna catch on catching
the heck out of you tomorrow
yes yes yes yes love to see salty sauce
salty though exactly
it's not mario kart if there's no salt
so you know what it's whatever
just wait what did i even choose i chose
nothing
so you got no regrets for tomorrow no
regrets for tomorrow why should i be
you know
it is what it is it is what it is um
it's the last day all i can do is train
as hard as i can and whatever will be
you know if i get [\h__\h] over by the rng
like you know it is what it is it is
mario kart yeah
exactly right
[Music]
boko boko
she told me to say that so i gotta at
least perform
um
so that i can say um
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
okay i've never actually gone through
the upper course for this
but um
i really don't know how it is
i saw like a lot of people they do they
go through the upper course
but
i don't know how it is
[Music]
oh no i forgot to put chat uh on the
near my screen
uh i'll do that after this again so i
can see you guys talk but i don't know
you guys sometimes are like granny don't
look at the chat you know so i'm gonna
practice doing that i'm not gonna look
at chat
so i'm gonna i'm gonna talk to myself so
sad right oh my god mrs p fell is
talking to herself
oh my god i don't i can't even see what
i have
that's a bullet bill oh it's another
bullet bill
it's another why don't why do i not get
bullet bills i'm like nine
i feel like i deserve
i deserve to you know the rights to
redeem a bullet bill do you guys think
so i think so
i mean shrooms okay cool shrooms are
fine i mean not really but oh wow
oh my god
oh my god are you serious i got the
power spell
[Music]
[Laughter]
i got a powerful oh my god
my
goodness is for
see that's what happens when orangey
doesn't [\h__\h] me over you know
that's what happens when orangey doesn't
like have me over
all the best best of thank you
okay high roll circuit because i think
okay
isn't even in my blog so never mind
okay senpai seems um
it seems that she likes hyrule circuit
i don't know oh thank you for joining by
the way did you get a plan on how to
seduce nintendo no i don't know
they use uber voice in the collab in the
morning i know
but um
i uh
i don't know oh look it's that guy who
keeps beating the crap out of me every
time i stream
oh god
um
[Music]
there was some joxl um not jaxa i would
say japanglish ish
i don't know
the japan delish valley exactly
who is the favorite to win the
tournament
um i gotta say though because i uh i
played with her today uh sweetie senpai
is undoubtedly very very powerful you
know i'm actually kind of rooting for
her to win
yeah and we had a pleasant conversation
mm-hmm
[Music]
you mark your opponents
so you say simp i'm going to do my best
but
if there's anyone i'm super rooting for
i would say myself
and then so you say i feel like little
no everybody is really cool though
um
[Music]
cece is the last horny winner i think so
a royal raceway we did this one
we did this one too
dude
[Applause]
oh my god are you serious
bye
why why are you like this don't hate me
don't hit me
[Music]
please get away from me
get away from me
there's a banana
oh no i missed the item oops
i missed the item
that's that's what i gotta stop doing
you know missing items that's also what
i'm pretty bad at
yes yes yes yes
at least i got like three coins that's
like better than zero oh god please stop
four coins that's better than zero
that's better than zero i think
that's better than zero i like it
[Music]
oh god
oh no
delicious coins
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no is that a bullet bill
that's so scary i don't want to pull it
though oh god
why do i not get a bullet bill oh god a
mushroom
a mushroom wait look i actually got
oh my god okay
i didn't know that you could actually um
that's office whatever
did the tournament already finish no
tournaments tomorrow
tournament is tomorrow
jammur will help you
jamur will help me sometimes
everyone fears everyone the race i'm
afraid of the service not being nice
well you know i feel like there's
nothing really you can do
[Music]
players to watch out indeed like
literally everybody
[Music]
do you know when d team is racing yes i
do
but i forgot
we do have like a rundown so i mean you
know like d teams d team right so you
probably have an idea like around when
um i think i'm gonna the way i'm gonna
stream is i'm probably gonna stream
soon like before the team segment starts
so um yeah
i'll use your hard eyes to seduce
nintendo should i just start doing that
now
nintendo wink wink wink wink i don't
know
yes yes yes mushroom sometimes isn't bad
well okay sometimes okay sometimes
okay what rainbow road who asked for
that nobody
literally nobody asked for that except
for like one person
like we need we need
we need a vote we need an actual vote
you know
[Music]
we need an actual vote
like
regarding these things
remember like in the morning like oh
like remember like in the morning
i feel like money money samples choices
get chosen like almost all the time
i was like what is going on like what is
she offering that i don't have
what is she offering
do i lack uh do i like an adult um what
do you call it do i like do i like an
adult mediocre
is that what i like
is that what money tempo has that i do
not have
i feel like i have enough
[Music]
wow
oh that that's so crappy like what even
is the one
[Music]
ah that sucks yes
no like the funniest thing is like
the funniest thing is that i don't know
i just wish
okay i think like i'm last ish
so
i really really want something that's
not mushrooms you know there are a lot
of things that are better than mushrooms
especially in these kind of courses they
all like say um i could name a few i
could name a few like a bullet bill
maybe like a bullet bill or a what
like a bullet bill i don't know
bullet bill see it like that what that
person got like what that person got a
bullet bill like why am i not getting a
bullet bill
[Music]
[Applause]
exactly right
like red shells for example exactly when
everyone's like so huddled together so
much like you would think right
people are people are asking like what's
so bad about mushrooms oh first off you
can't protect yourself
from anything
hey
oh
okay
[Music]
yay i'm gonna i'm gonna play with kiara
uh later but i think she's gonna do some
shortcut practices and something so um
i'm going to join her later
i want this i want my wall okay somebody
somebody likes this this is the one of
the courses that we did today
[Music]
good evening mushroom queen good
evening mushroom queen
[Music]
uh i hope i i sure hope i get better
items
[Music]
[Applause]
oh god are you serious
[Music]
funny music though
if i'm at the back i always miss the
thingies especially when everyone's
huddled together
uh
[Music]
wow
ah just my luck
just my luck
just my luck now that i'm ninth in my
phone now are you going to get a good
item of course not because rng is
freaking [\h__\h]
okay
double items
give me something good of course not
because it wants me to suffer
yeah cool
[Music]
yeah of course it gives me mushrooms
yeah
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] everything [\h__\h] the item box
okay
[Music]
maybe some i don't know um bullet bill
or maybe some yeah nice item like
kaminati or bullet bill
oh yeah of course we love mushrooms so
much we love it we love it absolutely
it's our favorite item my favorite item
favorite favorite item
in mario kart it's of course green
shells when there's nobody to hit as
well as
mushrooms
yes amazing
[Applause]
ray no swearing no [\h__\h] off
um electrodrome i think
[Music]
electrode because yeah i see that it
came up a few times
electrode
swears our adult language now can you
officially seduce mario kart true
[Music]
hello today is my birthday happy
birthday have a great one
[Music]
don't be scared
by me
um saying um
things it'd be like that it's a mario
kart stream and be like that all right
electro dome i think is popular true
did you have a good nap a little bit i
rested for like a few hours
i don't know i have lost a sense of time
yes yes yes
but i mean look at that look at look at
what happened to me like i was i was
even when i was 12 7 eight nine six what
do i get three mushrooms one mushroom
what two two one mushrooms
you know
it is how it is you know sometimes it's
not because i'm bad or anything like i'm
i'm bad to some extent but see what see
the first match or something when i
don't really get crap items
you know
so it is an rng thing it's kind of like
you know when you decided to oh i am
gonna dedicate my savings to this gacha
game that is what mario kart is
[Music]
the sooner i accept that the better it
is oh excitebike
[Music]
it is what it is you know
no
it is what it is right right right right
right
oh me avoiding coins
my favorite past time
my favorite pastime avoiding coins
[Music]
did i get it no i did not
[Applause]
oh coins i got two coins i'm so happy
that i got two coins
[Music]
stop it
oh i still got hit are you serious why
why does that happen to me why
why
i demand justice oh my god that's i'm
not getting that i'm not getting justice
so sad
why why would you do that to me
i need um i don't know
wait what
what happened what just happened i have
no idea what happened
i don't even know what happened
there was an explosion and there was
just an explosion i had no idea what
happened
i had no idea i had zero idea what
[Music]
[Applause]
of course
i got three mushrooms
[Music]
ah too late
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah i got a bullet bill but like i
didn't really need that
i got a bullet bill on like a straight
road
ah
too late for placement not only for
bullying exactly you're out you're right
though it's worth it it made me feel
good
um i think we should do big blue or
something
maybe
yeah i feel like the game is just like
taunting me at this point you know like
huh you you said you wanted to pull it
bill hi yeah i'll give you a pull and
phil hahaha yeah
and now all you have to do is drive in
the straight line for the most part but
you know i gave you the bullet bill
[Music]
it's like i mean
like i thought you know uh the fact that
you said that i always give you
mushrooms hey that's wrong i gave you a
bullet bill
maybe you can buy a lottery ticket
tomorrow since you should use them all
but okay listen hey listen after the
mario kart tournament tomorrow
i'm gonna do some gacha
[Music]
what do you propose what kind of gacha
should we do
that's it i'm gonna i'm gonna do it i'm
gonna do it
i'm gonna do it it hasn't i don't know
[Music]
you can't be like you didn't say when
you won the bullet bill though
gotcha game i don't know what's um
oh it's a not very populated race oh
it's fine we can use it as
practice just buy some scratch-offs i
don't know if i can um i'll think about
it
[Music]
you know
no time is wasted
we are all having fun
we are all having fun and it's okay you
know
we're all having fun
and whatever happens
we're gonna you know maybe we're gonna
yell at each other
a little bit
a little bit just a little bit you know
no please
please we'll stop in the corner please
no stop
[Music]
stop it
stop it i don't want it i don't need it
oh no i didn't jump ins i didn't jump
correctly whatever is fine it's okay we
got time we got time we're still third
it's okay there it's not it's not a very
um
[Music]
okay um can we get like something that's
actually good can we get something
that's like actually good i don't know
like um
abort bill for example
[Music]
oh yeah like what that person got a
thunder oh gee when did i ever get a
thunder and the bullet bill gee wow
should feel nice i don't really know how
it feels like to get a bullet bill how
come you get a bullet bill and not me
that's real funny oh somebody else gets
a bullet bill of course
so funny i wonder how it feels though
because i've never really um tasted the
fact that you know i um well how do you
actually get a useful bullet bill like
what even like how i don't really know
like i don't really know like have you
guys ever um
yeah you guys getting all these items i
don't really know how they feel i don't
know how it feels to get um items like
that
yeah
gee i wonder i really really want to
experience something like that once in a
while
electrodrome let's do electro dome again
yay
hyrule circuit i don't want baby park i
hate baby part i'm not gonna be yeah
it's just like
you need like a full speed i don't know
you need like a yeah that my previous
setup uh used to do really good at a
baby park but this setup just plain
sucks
for that but it gives me better control
in other courses so i'm gonna i mean
that's a good trade-off
[Music]
baby part is for babies and we are one
year old adult pea fowl exactly
[Music]
exactly
there's a canadian map
[Music]
[Applause]
i want that cloud glider i just want
that cloud glider please give me
why do i not have a cloud glider i just
want some delicious coins
delicious delicious coins
[Music]
[Applause]
ow
my beloved beloved coins are gone
like a lot of coins
i don't love it okay
that's good that's good enough i got the
old noise
oh so good
that's so nice
oh finally i know the feeling of getting
the feeling of getting a blue shell i am
familiar with it can you believe it i am
actually familiar with the feeling of
getting a blue shell oh my god it's the
best feeling ever not as good as getting
a thunder probably but yeah
at least i know how it feels
you know at least i know how it feels
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my gosh can you believe it i got 10
coins
my goodness i got 10 coins
i got 10 posts can you go wave it
i got it
that's so
scary a boomerang
[Music]
a boomerang
can you imagine getting a boomerang oh
no there's a quota why is it right after
i
get rid of this
okay that's not bad at all
thank you mario kart for loving me this
round
[Music]
i have 10 coins can you believe it i i
pavolia rainey have 10 coins can you
believe it i absolutely absolutely this
is for the happiest day of my life in
which i got got 10 10 10 10 10 10 coins
10 whole coins can you imagine
well
hope you don't run out of luck tomorrow
um it's okay i'm not really hoping for
anything
good game thank you
okay we i'm gonna i'm gonna pick
sunshine airport
[Music]
yeah
i didn't get any mushrooms that race
either oh my god you're absolutely
correct see that's what happens when the
mushroom curse is off
you guys still think why she hate
getting mushrooms oh you will know
if you get only mushrooms for like one
stream or something
[Music]
it's the dahla mentality
can't run a lot if you never had it
exactly you're absolutely correct also
um yeah plan to join practice with
tincho is still on um we talked a little
bit earlier and
[Laughter]
these races
i like mushrooms and soup
how many trees you collected so far i
don't know i'm not gonna count
yeah mushrooms are really good in
moderation like some some stuff where
you're really like in cheeseland i don't
mind getting a lot of mushrooms for
example because um
because we're just basically um
we're just basically uh we need it we
need a lot of mushrooms in cheese land
[Music]
oh no don't steal
my coins do not steal
do not steal my coins
[Music]
anything good anything nice anything
amazing anything amazing for today
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god that's so scary
[Music]
wow who did that that's so awful how
could you how could you
[Music]
yeah
yeah that's what you get
that's what you get
that's what you get if you do evil
thanks to rainey you know
yes
oh my god
i lost some coins
[Music]
it's kind of unfortunate because there's
no more items
i hope somebody like gets another um oh
somebody gets another blue shell or
something
[Music]
ow is that mine is that mine
is that mine
[Music]
is that my own
green shells are mankind's worst
inventions
but anyways um that felt great donut
plants
donut planes it's the central land
i feel like we have to practice this
[Music]
green shell
[Laughter]
oh no
what nobody literally wished for that
left aside from that one person
stop it we need a real voting when it
comes to mario kart map selection you
know
to reduce favoritism
[Music]
okay
see like i thought i got the thing right
but i didn't
[Music]
me getting mushrooms more likely than
you think oh my god stop it with the
quotas like
like can you guys just leave me alone
like
stop flaunting your items at me like we
get it you get good items no need to
flaunt them at me like you feel a lot
better like not you know
you feel good flaunting your op items at
me
is that is that is that you know
is that what you do
flex to the people who don't have a
chance to get
actually decent items
no matter what i do
that's what i get
so sad
like today i'm here in fourth position
holding uh you know this box thing
that may not always work because
everybody's so far ahead of me
god of course it's a freaking mushroom
oh god okay
[Music]
bye
okay at least i got like two boxes
oh yes that felt really nice
i don't know what i should do i really
really don't know what i should do
[Music]
[Applause]
green
[Music]
oh my god
whoa
i can't believe i um dodged that all
wow not that one
not that one definitely i didn't dodge
that one
i didn't dodge that one oh good
oh goodness i got like three mushrooms
that's amazing
okay
two
[Music]
bananas
wow
what i don't know how that happened but
cool
how did that happen i literally have no
idea but cool
it's not it's not necessarily that she's
improving i feel like it's just a lot of
energy
i was like sorry i can't believe it but
i will take it i will take the victory
you know the podium the podium i will
take the podium
even wrecking is a gotcha you know what
i'm i i wholeheartedly believe it
rainbow road or new bowser city i don't
know which one guys
[Music]
yeah the mushrooms are on the right time
exactly like there there was like a
whole straight road and what
rainbow maybe rainbow because i know
rainbow will get chosen like people will
be like
you know like rainbow road right
rainbow
anything that hits gacha pity
hmm
[Music]
i'm sorry i'm sorry oh piranha see it's
always the courses that nobody else
really wished for
it is what it is it is mario kart
[Music]
yeah it's okay we'll we'll fight we'll
fight
we'll do our best
green censor what do you mean greed
sensor that doesn't even make sense
close to real enough not gonna lie what
have i been watching a different person
have we been watching uh different
people
[Music]
me getting the coins look at that look
at me
i'm doing awesome with the coin
collection even if you know whatever i i
may not end up in you know whatever
place i don't know look at me look at me
not collecting the coins but like
collecting some coins
look at that
look at that that's so good
oh god
[Music]
at least i didn't fall
at least i didn't fall you know could uh
something worse could have happened
you know
i'll take that i'll take that i'll take
that
i won't be greedy i will take that
[Music]
oh look at me skipping all the things
wow
oh no
wow we still have one more lap i don't
know how i'm gonna recover from this
we're just gonna try our best okay
just gonna try our best
try our best we're gonna try our best
[Music]
he's gonna try our best oh there's a
bullet pill so scary
[Music]
oh
oh my god
okay well there was a kaminati so um i
don't know
i don't know if that was
[Music]
three mushrooms i can't believe we got
three mushrooms
[Music]
[Applause]
whoa that was a nice dodge question mark
oh yeah that fall was totally
intentional i um i calculated it i
calculated the waves um the i calculated
the bad vibes and decided to fall on
purpose in order to avoid the small
debuff when we got when everybody else
got the kaminari yes
exactly
my pee fell senses are tingling you know
sounds like some bad vibes are coming
the morphogenetic fields alerted me
um toad's turnpike or cheap cheap beach
i feel like i'm just not good at cheap
cheap beach so i'm gonna forget about it
um
maybe toad's turnpike is kinda cool
[Music]
rainy built-in vibe check
yeah it's the one there's the one time
where um
it helps what is this
[Music]
did something away can you at that
collab practice
uh might it awaken my stomach and wanted
to eat
i um i just woke up i basically streamed
with an empty
yeah never stream with an empty stomach
especially when you're
on doing a team race
oh communication error that sucks
oh look at that
let's check it out
[Music]
no
nobody asked for you i mean a zero
roller is okay i'm gonna use this
it's more pea fallion
[Music]
it has the same it has the same stats as
the roller right
it's just like the fancy roller
jj and you hope
it's the same color as me
yes
jj new hope let's go
[Music]
nintendo give ready the cloud glider
challenge 2022
[Music]
i need to drink
why
why is there a communication error
[Music]
nintendo said no to hydration reminder
um
[Laughter]
i don't understand what that means
[Music]
nintendo please
please nintendo
[Music]
please
give me give me give me me
me me me me me give me give me me me
oh there we go
[Music]
um
i'm gonna random it
[Music]
well come back
look i'm stretching
[Music]
i get the air so often i do not know
what it means uh me neither i don't know
what i mean what it means it's a secret
it's a secret of the nintendo i think
i wonder who can decipher
what it actually means warrior stadium i
think kiara kind of likes this one too
hey
nintendo resetting the gacha
okay
[Music]
let's go
i'm eighth
with my new car
i will i do oh there's a link with the
same exact wheels as me
only one person
can have
the things
[Applause]
[Music]
oh no
coins
[Laughter]
[Music]
of course i got a coin i can't defend
myself but i'm first and some i'm so
close
another quota for me
a blue shell oh thank goodness i'm not
first
thank god
thank god i'm not first
oh god i'm first now though
wow i always uh i can't ever do like a
clean uh turn over here
[Music]
okay okay okay
two laps
come on someone someone someone please
get out a blue shield
get out get a blue shell out please
someone get a blue shell out please
i would be so so happy if we get a blue
shell today
[Music]
i thought i pressed back
i thought i pressed back i wonder oh a
bullet goes on
[Music]
oh look at that
somebody
[Music]
oh
ah that wasn't really a clean run so it
was kind of on me but i think i really
do think i'm pretty good at this
course
i really do think i'm actually pretty
good at this course
big blue
[Music]
where's the mushrooms ah so that's why
i'm winning that's why i'm winning
because there's no mushrooms i see
um i kind of want big blue
[Music]
keep the coin to your next item is
guaranteed not a coin ah i see
so that's how it works
[Music]
there wasn't much room for the mushrooms
exactly
[Music]
maybe it's the other way because there
are no mushrooms because you are winning
um that's actually it that is it because
i was first
for like the longest time and like first
second i was like second and first and
second for the longest time that's why
they don't really give me mushrooms
but yeah
good evening rainy we had turkey for
dinner it was good who asked just
kidding i hope you had a good dinner
i had pasta and i think i'm gonna
there's some leftovers i'm gonna eat
them in another eat them in the morning
for today
it's not today tomorrow
[Music]
where is this toad's turnpike okay what
kind of pasta um
is one of those like
clear
pasta i don't know with chicken
[Music]
i really need to train grazing mo heck
off
oh i'm 11.
i'm 11.
wow
i'm 11. i'm 12. is this where i um
is this where i try to get good items
this is where i try to get good items in
hopes that
of course it's gotta be mushrooms of
course
of course that's it that's what's gonna
appear of course of course
of course mushrooms
[Music]
[Applause]
three
[Music]
three quarters
why why are you doing this to me
fancy wall climber
fancy so so fancy
so fancy fancy fancy wall climber
[Music]
fancy
that's not bad
[Music]
see that's what happens when i actually
get decent items
now
wall hacking
yeah officer
hello
[Music]
i mean that's not what wall hack is but
okay
okay i feel like some people would
choose sunshine airport and i'm gonna
pick i feel like nobody is ever gonna
pick bone dry dunes
hmm
don't use all of your luck today rainy
man
no i feel like it's also you know the
fact that it's in the morning
time zone wise
i'm like i'm much more awake i'm much
more awake in at night you know
i'm much more awake at night compared to
like say the morning or the afternoon
and i'm just like more focused and more
attentive in general
yeah
[Music]
so it's just like so i can't really
imagine like say for for example like
some members uh with time zone issues
like the tournament is like super early
in the morning or like super you know in
ungodly hours i can i really just can't
imagine
man
that'd be super
difficult for them
[Music]
that's not the actual code right it is
the code
it is the code if you don't get it and
you you get you say guide to another
room then you know
um i'm just waiting for her like to tell
me like hey if you wanna yeah if it's
okay for me to join
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh my god it's a
it's a two-person race i can't believe
it
[Music]
oh oh my god
a 1v1
it's a date
[Music]
it's a date in the airport
tourism
it's that day in the you know in the
what do you call it
in the in the airport where are we gonna
fly to hey save me some coins please no
heck off oh my god please i can't
believe you just did that
i can't believe you just stole my coins
why are you using gold mario
gold mario is it because gold is my
favorite color
joined up
gg's raining i promise i got no wall
hacks on
really
are you serious you got no wall heads
wait i wonder so if if this is like a
if this is like a 101 is it even like
possible for me to get like
blue shells
or is it like distance based
[Music]
is that like this in space i want to
know
i really really want to know
[Music]
i want to know
that is what i want to know
i don't know either
the only one way to find out i wish like
the gotcha would be kind of nice to me
wait i'm going to try getting the two to
item box
bananas together useless
boomerangs not very useful either
let's see let's keep let's let's try to
at least hit the item boxes
[Music]
give me some time because if you i think
like if the first person crossed the
finish line it's gonna be like over for
me
it's gonna be like oh it's not even
gonna let me like uh go through the
thing
okay i'm not really getting um say like
the kaminati the lightning or the
okay let me let me try this final box
let me try this final box
oh it's a mushroom and a star it's not
really uh
yeah it's not really it didn't really
spawn
[Music]
she got bullied as fourth flavor in the
first was way ahead yeah i guess it's
like distance based right
no kaminati the community has failed me
okay dragon driftway because i'm super
crap at it
dragon dressed away is just like a
really difficult course in general
especially when everybody's like huddled
together
[Music]
second place
[Laughter]
[Applause]
it's time for celebration we got second
place i can't believe it
gosh
we have to celebrate what are we gonna
celebrate with
i can't believe my date left me in the
dust
would not recommend
bad review
okay dragon driftwood let's go
[Music]
that's funny
celebrate with another date another date
with um 11 people
sorry about that oh
there is no forgiveness for you
there is no such thing as forgiveness
for the
for your kind
what is what is your kind actually i
don't know
oh there's a metal mario too
oh my gosh my banana hits somebody wow i
feel so good
okay i got caught but you know it is
fine
[Music]
[Applause]
oh no there's a squid there's a squid oh
[Music]
let's play
there's a squid
[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
how dare you
i dare you how dare you
banana that's so scary please do not
litter everybody nobody litters
in this house
in this household littering is
discouraged
you know that littering is discouraged
yes of course because you are a very uh
very nice
i don't actually know what i'm doing
[Music]
can i get a bullet bill
can i please like get a bullet bill
i want one
[Music]
technically that was like almost point
blank rage so it's not counted you know
you know
you know it's not counted
right
you need to make mushrooms monument for
their service
yes
uh
water park
i think
it was more assault than litter yeah two
different things
do you lay eggs i don't know do you lay
eggs
is it gonna be another date
is it gonna be another day who is gonna
be the lucky person what is that
[Laughter]
what is that i'm a little big but sad
oh no sad bae
hello rainey hello
officer i was a littering officer it was
just assault
[Laughter]
bay but sad
[Music]
e somebody's smiling
shira says hi hi kiara
oh shoot hold on
i saw a message
oh
okay
i'm gonna join your room after this
okay you know i'm gonna call her
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait
uh where is it
[Music]
hey kiara
just get the [\h__\h] out of me
[Music]
it's okay it's okay i um i bought the
side of my car too
okay i'll give you some um
i'll give you some space okay i'm also
racing
oh okay are you not streaming anymore
are you oh i'm still streaming
oh okay
i think you probably didn't even hear my
full screen that was like pure horror
yeah you probably didn't hear me but
this could probably cut it off but that
was done as well oh no man look at me a
heart attack
how's it going over there dana oh me uh
great um
adam's probably not being as bad to me
like this morning
this morning was kind of awful but i
don't know
i feel like one is just very important
in mario kart
yes 100
that is very true
i have i've been the past few races i've
been doing so that um
i wouldn't speak because we've noticed
that i can't
uh play this game
if i talk yeah
which is why i'm now driving worse
okay i'm sorry
nothing no problem no
[Music]
when i did a few races while not
speaking i was much better
okay
do you not have the same problem i do of
course i do
i played um i played when i was on
stream and i was like hey i'm actually
pretty good
yeah yeah yeah right
that's where our full potential is
hidden i know
they don't believe it but it's true and
to be true
such as the life of a streamer it is
okay
oh
[Music]
do you want to
go into the same tournament or what do
you want to do oh yeah sure i'll join
you i'll try joining you okay uh
everybody get out of here
my code wait i'll i'll send you my quote
but oh i can join three new friends i
think
no i think that's only wait let me close
my tournament i'll make a new tournament
the friend one is i think only with npcs
uh
i'll make a new one
what's this
oh okay
uh
create tournament
create an online tournament let me hide
the screen
i'll probably get your cute
uh chibi drawing
oh you need to get your sunscreen too
oh you're so totally wet you're riding
on it
i hope i hope that brings me luck in uh
the race in the tournament i hope i get
the bullet a lot
me too
i got the blue shell though
oh that that that helps i think the one
who froze the blue shell doesn't really
get much out of it because yeah then
you're at the end of the race anyway
yeah it's not gonna happen the hell's
the second place
yeah
that is true so that the second if
there's someone you really like on the
second place and you can give them
number one then yeah true true true
no teams normal items
no no can i do no no cpu
all vehicles smart steering
no smart steering i guess
the time settings don't matter as far as
i know
and public to everyone okay
okey-dokey okay okay i got it i have the
code name okay um let me start it
wait i gotta i gotta make sure i hide
the screen
yeah yeah yeah
and i'll try it i'm gonna put your i'll
find your image i'll find it okay
sure
they drew such cute illustrations for
all of us towards them by
commissioned all of those cute
illustrations for every participant
isn't that so nice i know
i watched everybody and it's like oh so
cute
yeah they look so cute and we got like
per generation they're like from the
same artist so it's kind of matching
that's cute is there a reason why uh
only id second gen is participating uh
i'm really not sure
i'm really nervous maybe it's because
they they participated last year so
they're like oh
second gen girl i may have maybe yes
they have some hams
look at that i love i love the eyes and
in your oh and your kimono is beautiful
too
i love the sparkles in your in your
keyboard
did you did you get in wait i got
nothing but i got it but i'm with like
random people for some reason how did
they get in
how did what how is that possible
[Music]
i'm not even in yet i didn't show them
the code yet
let me get in
oh
did you send it to code recording
i said
wait i like it i'll exit
oh wait
i i set uh
available for everybody
was that was that wrong can i change the
setting of an existing tournament oh yes
you can uh if you check the tournament
and there's a
yes
okay okay
okay
it is okay it is absolutely okay
what they heard bales bales is not in
the voice chat no no
open to everyone code required ah yeah
so we just randomly joined the random
tournament that exists right now in the
world it's just not even viewers
probably yeah yeah yeah
not a hotel okay now you should
be able to join again
and this time
no one else should be joining except for
our viewers okay i already i already
chose the course no oh by accident
so everybody look at the code new code
in three
two
one wait i'm alone there though i'm
alone in here
what
how is that possible did you go into a
different room no
no
no i'm alone for some reason
maybe
how how
how
how white why nintendo what
let me let me exit again oh wait i'm not
joining you i'll just try i'll just try
to join you
okay okay
join kiara
why is it so complicated man you should
be able to join friends as well in these
tournaments and like um this time device
cannot accept any more connections
[Music]
our race is starting right now so i
think you should uh yeah i'll wait until
this one is over sorry that's so awkward
no no no no no that's fine i'll just
spectate so i can join uh the next one
someone looks like konata do you know
lucky star yeah yeah yeah i do i love
lucky stars someone made their mii look
like konata from lucky star ah i i i got
an air the target device cannot accept
any more connections that's so weird but
do they mean your device i don't know
what the target device means
what does that mean chat do you know
chat chat chat
oh wait that's that's a big blue the one
where i learned the shortcut right
is that it was that was that a different
one
oh that means room is full
ah
okay then
i think i'll tell you the moment when
it's ending because that's when i joined
your room yesterday
uh once the other people
um start leaving i think that's when you
should try joining
okay okay okay
so
go go go go
yeah yeah yeah baby that was good whoa
wait let me just oh yeah oh
it's going pretty well so far this is
really awkward like on my end because
i'm not showing any of the game and
you're just like oh
[Laughter]
i bought so yeah
i can't imagine hello everybody from
dana's stream how's it going
how's it going everybody
how is it going everybody it's a live
report i see you guys thank nintendo for
that for making it so difficult yes
item i will wait for you
i'll i'll just play with your tattoo
okay
[Laughter]
the plant is do you like the plant item
the big chomp chomp please i don't i
don't really like it
it's very difficult to control like it's
an inferior star
although it doesn't yeah it doesn't um
it doesn't help you when driving over
grass and stuff
[Music]
hey i'm doing well even though i'm
talking nice
[Music]
let me try to hit someone
i'm so bad at aiming the shell so i
should never try to do that what i got
the bullet filled with the on fifth
fifth
[Music]
this chord is totally cutting off her
laughs
stupid discord okay okay now uh try to
get an l now okay okay
[Music]
hey my skies
it's full it's full it's full
there's like there's like a lot of props
yeah it's full
let me make a new one i'm sorry guys
sorry guys i'm making a new one there's
like a lot of problems
okay i'll make a new one
create tournament can you believe it's
like for me it's it's the tournament is
today
it's in less than 24 hours elena are you
ready
am i ready you know it is what it is i'm
gonna accept whatever it gets thrown at
me
[Music]
what should we name the tournament reina
uh
[Music]
we need to think of a combi name you
know
yeah yeah we don't have one no cause
like we're we're just hollow birds but
there's nothing
[Laughter]
there's oh let me tell can i tell you
some idol nerd talk otaku oh yes of
course
i'm a big fan of this uh
um idol agency called hello project
and you know them
yeah i've heard of them but not much
and they
they they had i mean they had their main
groups and then they had some groups
that are like
they were not that popular and then
there was this group that they called um
i think apple apple
and then
and
so okay for everyone who doesn't know in
japanese
is like kako is the the brackets on the
side the what do you call them in
english yeah brackets
yeah brackets and then cutty is like um
it's like temporary only for now like
it's implying as if they would still
change the name of the idol group
eventually
and uh so they started
making you know they're doing their idol
activities making some songs and they
had this lame name with like up up girls
temporary and
you thought they would change it
eventually but no until the end like
even after 10 years they never changed
the name
yeah it just kept on being like working
title temporary working title kako kari
[Laughter]
i thought that was kind of like
sad but it made them stand out somehow
it's it's it's stylized in a way you
know
yeah we can be like that too oh hold on
let me just um go into yeah i sent you
the code
[Music]
i'm changing the code once i see you in
on the map i'll change the code on my
side
okay
searching for players
we can do it
it's it's there you are yeah okay i'm
there okay cool i'm also gonna show beat
yes
yes okay i'm gonna show the code to um
once you show it
it's okay you can show it now okay bam
and then i'm gonna show you the game
it's me it's so cute it has a like a
duck beak
[Music]
so cute
yeah did you
make that yourself yeah i made it
why did you do that it's um the yellow
lips and then
something else uh i overlapped
i never looked that closely at the
options that you can do when making a me
nah me too me too like somebody made a
baby a rainy with like so they made a
pacifier
i saw the baby elena yesterday
what do you want which one do you want
oh oh doesn't matter not like we really
have a choice true during the tournament
too right
[Music]
yeah
okay okay
are we gonna be quiet
are we gonna be quiet um
we could do a quiet run yeah yeah you
want to try to stay quiet sure sure
it's so hard
it's so hard to stay quiet though i
basically just couldn't stop talking
[Music]
just breathing
our
our uh we can't even exchange emotions
through our like
uh like eye eyes yes not even dad it's
okay we can do telepathy
[Music]
[Applause]
no that doesn't count laughing doesn't
count
[Music]
were three people at the finishing line
did you see it they were just not
driving did they get kicked out i don't
know
maybe they have to go to the bathroom
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
oh my god [\h__\h] what is that
we don't have that much
like
we don't we don't do that many we didn't
do any collabs recently i know that
should i realize i need to talk yeah
i was really happy like after
yesterday's video i was like wait i just
realized that we don't even like talk
that much right and then i was like yeah
i was actually really really happy
oh god
i'm eight
i'm last basically oh it's fun nah
that's fine it's wonderful
no problem yeah but i already feeling i
already told my viewers yesterday um
that we're doing a whole
garlic pho oh yes yes yes i'm excited
for that
oh wait is the game waiting for the
others uh
maybe maybe how long is it gonna wait
for them i don't
know there's like three people waiting
there for people uh okay
okay communication era let's go
oh
yeah looking up i got kicked out of the
tournament as well oh god okay are you
gone you too right um no i up
are you still in i am still in um should
we
can you re-enter stay there i'll stay
there i will try to orienta see this is
how the whole tournament will be like
probably
although for the tournament at least we
can join by friends so yeah yes yes
that's something
yes oh man
nintendo
with me
[Music]
it's currently spectating get ready who
am i expecting
at least
if you're spectacular
no no no no where should i get out
no no no no no no no don't worry about
it
wait is this a phone
okay
um i have a full group here you know
what let's let's race so both uh
once without each other okay yeah sure
of course because i guess your race is
already starting is it no it's not
started yet
but you're you have a full group of
people yeah uh
i i can't count
but
approximately
okay
let's let's at least we're in voice chat
together we're collabing in belize we're
collabing
even though we're separated in courses
we'll still together in the vc
yeah
together together
yes ten nine where are you what are you
doing now
we are gonna be doing mount wario wait
i wanna do mount wario i think we're i
think we're doing rainbow road or
something oh no
i am i actually enjoy mount wario man so
many europeans we're doing the airport
thing
oh oh
have fun right now i wish you the best
yes we're gonna travel
in mario kart we actually since we're oh
[\h__\h] we're actually rivals in the
tournament so i don't know why i'm so
friendly to you
no it's fine it's kind of like you know
those animes you know like oh yeah we're
rivals let's just do our best and
motivate each other that kind of thing
you know very spicy right
i can't i can't feel you
you can't pay for me too you don't want
me
i'm sure okay you can't be too mean
we may be rivals in the tournament but
after that we're hollow tori's forever
you know
yeah
yes
[Music]
i just tried a shortcut and i failed
miserably oh no
do you are you gonna be doing shortcuts
oh um if if possible yes
sometimes it's like i want to but i
can't because somebody's blocking me or
something
[Applause]
thunder why you do this to me
why are you so
mean don't be mean to tiara everybody
[Music]
oh wait i i didn't want to take this
route okay
okay
what what happened
i forgot about another shortcut i don't
want tourism
what pollutory tourism
oh i just got lightning uh
in mid-air and i fell into the scene
elena you know what i was thinking about
yesterday
i was thinking i wanna do a magnet song
cover with you
do you know magnet the vocaloid song
yeah i do wait can we sing magnus
i'm not sure yeah that's the thing
that's the thing
we'll make it happen
well well okay we can we can check we
can check you know i'm like down for
like whatever if it's with my
phoenix brand i love because you have
such a beautiful singing voice
no that's true we haven't done so nice
we haven't done any any covers together
[Music]
we're sure
okay um how do we get together again
i'm not sorry okay i'm done i'm done
okay i'm done oh you're done
[Music]
guys don't join dana's race please don't
join
let me in oh god it's taking too long
already
wanna create a new one
no no no no i'll make
[Music]
[Laughter]
why does it make you choose your stupid
character every time before you go in
how how is it how's it looking searching
for players there's a k there's a person
here called buttress i don't know what
[Music]
i don't know
no i'm expecting no the race is starting
wait no no let's see if it's really uh
if it's really mine
[Music]
uh
the spectating one that one is not you
know i don't care yeah yeah it's a
different one no i think it would be
faster if we just like make a new one
no no well you're sp instead of like
watching instead of spectating you can
make a new room and i'll rejoin
no i feel bad though you've been like
sitting here doing nothing for like two
races
you know what i'll i'll join
a random uh pablo nasty tournament race
and
since you're racing right now too yeah
i'm in movie meadows
i mean this was fun too even when we're
not in the same race
yeah
it's okay our hearts are connected
together even though we're not in the
same race this is so sad
oh apparently there's 3 000 people
trying to get in so yeah the chances are
pretty low oh no
oh who are these people who are these
people trying to get in the way just
kidding oh i mean we could also race
against npcs but i just feel like
they're not strong enough yeah we really
need um strong opponents to practice
yeah i feel like you know even with hard
npcs just do you feel good because oh
you're always like first or second but
you know it doesn't reflect how the
races will be at all
yeah yeah
oh my god stupid cows sorry
[Music]
make color tony proud one of us one of
us has to get into the winners cup i
know
i know i know
the whole thing
is
yeah
at least one whole toy representative
needs to go to the pro cup stupid
lightning
[Music]
yeah i know i know
i'm just spending and they're all right
in the beginning i don't want to wait
that long that is not even me it's not
even me
i want to look at laina
is cute
when she's driving
[Music]
my butt is covered by a turtle shell
though
and then i must destroy it you must
destroy it that's so violent
please have mercy okay my race is done
should we just um what should we do
your race is starting it's done it's
just finished yeah
it says for me currently spectating but
i'm still like i'm not looking at anyone
yet uh
wait
yeah no um oh god uh should we
i i
should i make a new one or should you
make a new one yeah maybe you make a new
one okay i'll make a new one oh my
goodness
[Music]
wasting my time nintendo
do you want to join my old room or uh
maybe i should create a totally new one
i'll try i'll try okay
way too please
hide the game screen
okay
okay let me try this um oh [\h__\h] oops
hours
where did you come from who the hell are
you there's a random here
there we go i'm gonna try to join my own
room
quick quick quick
already in and i show it on screen
okay i'm searching for players i'm
searching for clear crew frozen
you can do this
oh people people joining um
[Music]
oh no i don't see you no
no no
no
no i don't even see him okay dude i'm
sorry i'm going to make a new one
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm going to create
a tournament okay i'm going to delete
jjj a new hope goodbye
jjj a new hope it is time
to die
time to die how long are you planning to
race though search bike uh
uh
maybe one more hour yeah me too we need
rest we need rests
yeah i need a long nap in between
and then it's also amazing birthday
today slash tomorrow depending on your
time zone um
and i want to call into a stream for
that
what fun is it
uh her stream is that midnight for me so
for you you how how far are you behind
jst um like two okay then it would be
six a.m for you i think oh okay the same
time as last year i think or i don't
know i don't remember oh yeah maybe yeah
maybe i think i'ma usually streams
around that time
roughly no smart steer
[Music]
missing those items on a birthday
five she's uh getting uh 78 years old
yeah yeah 78 years old
yeah she's very old yeah old old people
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait you're older
no no no amy's old grandma
okay
wait which pavonashi is it oh oh there
it is there we go
ah did you make it with the same name
yes
that is very confusing no but it has
like a different it has a different icon
okay
i hope you are you can join me
okay as long as you don't show
no i haven't i haven't shown i haven't
shown anything i'm in the second lap
right now are you
ready yeah but getting very close to the
third lap okay i'm gonna i'm gonna
stretch while i wait for you
no i'm so stupid i'm so stupid
oh
i'm so stupid
no you're not stupid let's go redeem
that first place
yes
i mean i had some lucky races today
where i got i got seconds twice today
against viewers that's nice
let's take the luck carry over tomorrow
let's hope for the best for the both of
us i just want to be placed in the
middle of it because i don't wanna
i don't wanna go to another cup you know
really i just wanna go back to sleep you
wanna go back to sleep okay yeah
[Music]
very motivated yes they're not gonna
scream right you're not gonna stream
yeah i'm not i'm not going to
okay i'm going to play but just maybe um
during d teams
race
and then if i don't get and then i'll
end stream if i don't get in any of the
cups i'm gonna end the stream right
there and like here and there okay
my race is done
cool i will join you now sorry also to
the viewers for for doing all this uh
um switching and changing sorry guys
[Laughter]
yeah
now hopefully i will not be kicked out
of the tournament anymore and then we
can stay in the same one for a while
hopefully okay so it's
[Music]
oops
huh
what are you munching on i'm rocky road
i'm sweet rocky road
is that chocolate yeah chocolate with
marshmallows and almond and stuff
oh
i think i've heard of that before is
that the originally american sweet so
what is that maybe
maybe i don't know where it's from it
might be
yes am i in do i see you yes i see you
okay
here's the code everybody okay
we made it oh no tony titties so true
yes okay i'm going to show the game
it's birthday chef it's british
[Music]
yes yes yes yes yes rocky road sounds
like a mario kart course chess is
true
[Music]
british
fresh can can you do can you do a
british accent like this
no i can't i'm sorry
that's so lame we're going to get onto
my level right now
so sad hold on
[Music]
ridiculous oh my god
oh no that that's going more into valley
british british valley girl
the british valley girl
so how do they say yes if they're
british and they're
valley girls
wait do british people say something
do they prefer to say something else
besides yes chat
they say uh
is more like australian i think so
wait that looks like ame behind us oh
where
the me block looks like oh yeah the
blonde one
a cheerio
cheerio
oh the screen is hidden oops sorry
here it is
oh
what's up
it is an i'm in parody
it is
oh my god rainbow one rainbow road
let's go
you know i i bet this is gonna get
chosen i feel like you know somebody's
gonna try to choose this course so
it would be good to trigger everybody
else
oh god stop don't hit me
that was so fun
fell off the track
wait for me everybody
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
rainbow row that's so evil like whoever
did that
no bananas allowed they should be banned
from the rainbow world i know
no bananas in the house
[Music]
means
okay okay okay okay
which place right now
[Music]
that's the only explanation it's mario
kart
oh
come on give me a bullet bill
no i want a bullet
[Music]
but i mean i have to say this is not not
exactly
my fault like a lot of this is really
bad luck
oh my god
[Music]
i took a shortcut by following someone
else and it actually worked but then i
didn't know where to go from there
uh-huh
oh but but you know where it is right
no not really
okay
i just followed someone into the void um
[Music]
have you been using it yeah yeah i
always use it
show me take take my hand right now and
show me i would please don't choose baby
park i beg you
always takes that shortcut too i need to
learn it that's okay i'll try to learn
that one
off screen
yeah do it do it
okay that one should be worth it not
last at least yeah after all that
all that
how am i not last
blue big blue let me do big blue please
yeah i chose big blue too
thank you thank you
yeah i wanna do a big one
[Music]
she has a fierce eyebrows fierce
smile oh my god wait that dude looks
like a bird too
he's like an angry bird
you're right
it looks so angry though what happened
[Music]
yay
do i remember the short cut
better kiara
let's see about that we'll see who's
better yeah
in mario kart at least yeah
okay i'll focus let's focus
okay let's focus
let's kick eddie kick their butts
[Music]
okay i can still catch up
now
i got bullied i can't believe it
[Music]
i never take a sharp enough turn
i managed to do one shortcut but it
didn't help me
where are much
behind you okay better be ours right in
front of me
[Music]
get him get him get him get him
counting fourth
where's better kiana that's all that
matters chiara
[Music]
we showed here he'll be on us
nice nice nice nice
okay okay that was an interesting race
that was interesting
[Music]
what do you mean you can control when
you're tilted
that's so sad
i always i don't know my mario kart
streams i always get mad at so many
things
me too me too i need to control my
aggressions a little bit more you know
it's kind of like you know hey um you
know i have to control uh not show my
pda too much you know public display of
aggression
do you see that piccolo where oh
oh god what is that
you look disgusting
ah dude
what is that oh that's unknown
no there's also another one with like a
grinning
blue lip oh yeah that one looks
funny
it stares straight into your soul
are you guys trying to create a horror
movie
go easy on me
get out of here get out of here
hammer shark it does look a little bit
like a
gouda hammer shark but it's pickled up
okay you guys are crazy crazy crazy
which one which one do you want to go
with um i'm awful at animal crossing so
let's do it
up to you though pearl harbor is also
pretty okay i chose twisted match okay
okay orangey orange orange
people really like animal crossing huh
uh yeah it came up in this morning's
tournament not tournament i mean you do
youtube
my placement is awful that's what it is
empire was part of it right um yeah uh
it's sushi senpai
so it's the same way was also in there
yeah she was in there
uh elena i'm telling you there's nothing
you really about a cup where
uh suse and toast empire
i mean at least you know um
the intention is what matters right
it's not i don't think it's fair to even
put them into the same tournament
it might be beautiful for them
[Music]
hello it's like it's like their
breakfast looks like they're for dinner
they'll have the real tournament for
dinner yes
healthy healthy breakfast i kept getting
so bad items like you know mushrooms
i was doing so well
no stupid quota get the hell out of my
face
i mean my back i guess
my item's breaking
wow i survived this without items
[Music]
there's something called today
oh god
of course i got mushrooms
[Music]
what happened with waluigi
um
[Music]
did you guys see me cutting those uh
roads short did you see that chat are
you proud of me
spicy
[Music]
i'm getting i'm playing the game a
little bit risky now
[Music]
oh no blue shell
oh
i had a different problem there
[Music]
it's okay i got caught on like right in
front of the finish line no big deal
[Music]
why don't we always end up at the bottom
it's not fair
uh i don't know item orangey it is what
it is i think
it's not
what it is
chad you must agree i did better than
that you saw it you saw it i did not
deserve that treatment pinky
i cut the curves and what do i get for
it
bottom grips
[Music]
totally not the driving see
we have chat support
how does that eat two enos and one of
them looks like a paper bag
that's cute
[Music]
oh they're so cute together
let's go everybody let's go okay
let's go let's
[Music]
i used to be so scared of the bowser map
and
i thought it was so difficult but no
nowadays i like it actually nowadays um
i realize there are
much worse
maps out there
yeah i don't hate it as much
yeah
but yeah
royal raceway
what have you been
up to recently anyway you gotta update
me on your life
oh yeah this whole week i've been
streaming mario kart and mario kart only
[Laughter]
before that before that that's a that's
an interesting question i saw you
playing the the objection game ah yes
yes uh i played it every saturday i'm
gonna play that this week too
do you like looks like the objections
objection game an objective game
i i have the game for the ds i think but
i never played it i was always
interested in that though okay yeah i
mean like i like those kind of games
it's kind of like my favorite genre so
oh
um look at
if you look at my screen i'm taking a
very like unorthodox approaching
pathfinding
oh
you're driving against the wall
are you trying to find secret walls
hidden somewhere oh yeah something like
that
well in mario games there's always some
secret yeah
yeah right right right absolutely
look at me look at me look at me in the
mini-map
oh
so sad
[Music]
so man
oh man
once again
back to the bottom
after i've seen the talk
daisy what the [\h__\h]
just because i'm playing daisy these
people are now trying to
show me some cool tricks with their own
daisies
[Music]
blue
shell
who who who
who spawned that blue shell
not me not the army not me either oh
[Applause]
[Music]
at the moment
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh there you are
oh god
[Music]
we're always together though
how do we do that
they're just trying to copy me stupid
copycats yeah they realized daisy is is
the real sh yeah yes
the new
waluigi
yeah yeah it's so boring everybody's
using waluigi and that other weird
whatever i don't know the name hey are
you talking about roy
yeah he has sunglasses on
boring and everyone's using the same
card boring boring
it's okay kiara just because you don't
have the car doesn't mean you have to
say something like that
it's so true
[Laughter]
she roasted me oh she's so right it's
okay we're still best friends right
yes best friends forever is that good or
what that's so cute that's the bubble
bubbles
no that's not cool
oh
on my screen baby rainy was socializing
with you so cute
oh
fried
chicken where is my baby
where's baby chiara
we need some babies i put on my i put on
my pacifier
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
i'm sorry i learned it from
my other
wife friends
they have to go into the corner
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
um
[Applause]
hello
[Music]
hated me
i don't know how to say that yeah i get
what you mean it's natural selections
[Applause]
oh
because she still has that youth energy
you know oh no i didn't what are you
implying kiara
we are we are very very old old boomer
i have my back oh my back
oh for real though my back really hurts
all right yeah me too your back does not
hurt my back hurts my back hurts
it's because it's because wayne and your
cover you you're carrying all that
um
[Music]
i'm trying to say what am i trying to
say i'm trying to say that
you are so
amazing
yes yes you're trying to carry um
no no i'm not trying to say bulba no no
no i i really just can't articulate
myself the way i want to yeah like you
know like oh the pressure for tomorrow's
tournament and every i get what you're
trying to say right right right
[Music]
not quite i'll tell you later in the dm
oh okay you gotta tell me in the dm i
see how it is i will be waiting for your
dm
okay well what should we choose
i'm gonna choose music part because your
voice is like music to my ears no i hate
music park but i don't um i like your
voice i can actually say music park for
you um yes
and communication air has occurred
no
no no
i'm still in you just fell out of it but
i'm alone with one more person okay i'm
gonna join
i'm going back in
uh
oh okay you're going into the same one
yes i'm going to say i'm searching for
players right now okay okay okay i'm
coming i'm coming okay okay okay okay
okay
wait for me
i wonder if there's a higher chance of
getting communication ever when you're
on wi-fi because in my bedroom where
i'll be playing for the tournament i'll
be on wi-fi i wonder if that's a bad
idea
i'm always on wi-fi
oh my god what is this group of people
you're not in here i'm not in here a
communication error has occurred i i i
can't get in
again
i can't get it i'm sorry wow
wait how do you how do you connect your
ethernet cable to the switch
you don't know there is no such option
you can buy an extra adapter that you
attach to the switch because the switch
does not have an ethernet cable port
the dock doesn't have it either
it doesn't
you have to buy an adapter yeah because
that's what i thought and then ah
man i bought one ages ago after like i i
remember i wanted to do a
a collab with vatami senpai um
and then we realized oh my god
on wi-fi it's literally impossible for
me to get together in the same room
so
i was like where can i put in the cable
the internet cable but yeah i didn't
have a slot so i had to buy one and the
collab was postponed
oh oh that dog has an internet porn wait
but if i haven't if i have an oled dock
ah but then i'll have to buy an oled
switch
i would say just get a the usb adapter
no but then like if you do that you
can't play docked right
ah
but maybe maybe for the oled the dock
has the ethernet cable thingies slot
i'm not sure
oh like a dog oh only duck works with
old switch
hmm maybe i'll just buy i hope somebody
can just buy the dock
i don't know i hope somebody uh will
sell it why would you just buy the doc
that's kinda also i'm stuck spectating
i'm stuck
quit
i'm gonna quit so sad
[Music]
i miss you too
i want to spectate you but
did you in the youtube in the youtube
did you have many uh connection errors
or no no not at all actually oh thank
god okay how many races did you do
so we had like so one section one cup is
like four races right so we had that for
the preliminaries and then we had
two times
of red and blue and then we had
and then we had
some other type of team race
and then another cup of codeine race for
the last time so it was like two hours
yeah
well it sounds like fun
sounds like fun sounds like fun yes yes
oh you have usb to ethernet plugs onto
the dock i see
[Music]
i'm i'm in the wrong lobby again
oops
i'm in the wrong lobby as well i think
um
oh yeah oh by the way i need to tell
please
we got
i i did so terribly that in the one of
the last races it was like a race each
team consists of three people it was
okay by iris and me
and thanks to me we got a terrible score
but we scored 69.
[Music]
nice too yeah i just wanted to say that
somebody reminded me on chat
[Music]
no
why do i keep getting the wrong
room
my my my thingy just ended oh
[Applause]
can you get out of it
i don't know oh i'm getting out
i'm gonna mute my voice on stream yes
let's
let's go to
a different tournament
now we have so many tournaments that we
can choose from
i'm hiding the screen okay do they hear
me on your side
oh shoot hold on wait i need i need to
do something i need to do something
first guys um oh i'm not muted there we
go now i'm muted
yes i didn't say anything yet okay let's
go to oh i have a have a good one i have
a good one that they will not expect
okay i send you a code
oh okay
question more
okay i'll add some okay oh wait i'm good
i'm gonna hide this queen
don't worry
can you read lips
okay it's fine
caught in 48 kh set i don't even know
what is going on anymore
one day
[Laughter]
i'm gonna paste it now
yes me too okay
there you go numbers
i wanna do donut flames because i suck
at totally and sancho is really good at
doing a plane so we gotta be good at so
we gotta be decent at donut planes okay
okay okay i saw some sick shortcuts for
donald plane so hard to pull off though
[Music]
chat is muted no no no one's muted
anymore
is free to speak
i would never never
never mute the chat
or the chimpkins voices
freedom of speech yes freedom of speech
oh are you guys coming oh ina with a
beard
okay
okay it's an intimate race
[Music]
we have all different colors
what
rainbow
[Music]
is that shaggy as it is
is that shaggy yeah
get out of here shaggy
out here
they don't deserve it
[Music]
oh by the way
i already i already saw also elena maybe
you will like it too i already saw
cronies
kimono i like it so really
she looks so gorgeous
yeah
there is not happening yet can i see
what you are getting out of it
[Music]
the council is getting it one week later
and then iris will be getting it
eventually okay that's nice i hope maybe
maybe
maybe next year or so
indonesia can get it too
yeah me too i hope so
okay
exactly but yeah hopefully we do get a
real one
yes pray everybody for everybody
everybody needs a kimono in their life
[Music]
it's so it's so peaceful without
a full
12 people race on rainbow room
so peaceful
no
is it already ending oh no
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh thank you for that intimate race now
it's time for new people to come in here
[Music]
[Laughter]
what a shame he says
wait that
those those two people with the
the haircuts uh
are they from naruto
yeah at least the right the right one
but the
the yellow one is from something else
i'm not sure
the right one is from naruto right yeah
the green one i don't know much about
naruto did you watch novel no not at all
i just know like some of the characters
yellow ones from despicable me are you
being serious are you guys being serious
or are you trolling
i think they're trolling
apparently it's rock lee from what
entered the dragon it's a movie
broccoli
right now
[Music]
speak japanese here what about
california
oh i don't know how they speak
they're just valley girls kiara
okay okay
we can do that
you can do that no not i don't like this
rainbow road because
i i fall off the
cliff so often
[Applause]
[Music]
oh no
what happened
well not nothing nothing
just trying my best out here
okay
[Music]
oh
thank you for that thank you
number three everybody
[Music]
how often i'm falling down okay
oh
that was close
nothing helps anymore at this point
nothing they're all so far away oh no
there's a bullet bill number five
oh thank god
okay
[Music]
oh thank you
you did pretty well there
thank you i got i didn't fall as much
tell me
just don't fall
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah i feel like you know even if you
got the course down if somebody just
knocks you off a little bit like your
drifting is going to be off and
everything is just like ah
right and think speed items are actually
pretty difficult to use there
yeah i also when i use them i get too
fast and then i fall off the edge again
it's not your fault if you're too fast
already yeah
speed scenic
help it right
what do we want
i don't know i chose mario kart stadium
i chose ice ice output
okay okay because there's a very like
tricky shortcut and if you can if you
can't nail it it will help like
i practiced it today
nice but i already forgot i already
forgot which one it was oh if it gets
chosen we can both try for it yeah okay
okay
what a funny face
what the funny which one
the one on the very right the black one
the black one oh
yeah i see it
[Music]
no worse chiara they admit their defeat
i like that respect respect i respect
worst chiara
[Music]
meaning your mistakes is the first step
to get better we say that in german i
don't know how you say it in english
wait
is that not how you say it in english
no please don't quote me i'm trying to
get the shortcut please
it didn't get to you unfortunately
did you do it did you make it oh i
didn't complete a full one so it's like
a 75
that was pretty good i'll take that and
fall
nicely
there's another one oh i'm too late for
that one though
[Music]
i'm too late for that one there's a
second one at the end
[Music]
so i'm gonna try that next lap
what happened
i'm
just effing around oh no
i can't do better
oh no now that i'm 10 am i going to
finally get good items
oh 10 oh we're so close
where are you
12.
no it's okay one plus two is three
uh-huh
so i mean
i don't know
math
man that's math how do i how do i get
the second shortcut i wonder do i have
to like drift early
i'll try again i'll try again
no i keep on missing coins and items
no i keep missing
well if we're so far behind we might as
well try
the first one
i think you know the first shortcut
where there's two ramps
i can go over the first round but not
the second one
[Laughter]
at this point it doesn't even
where's where's kiara i wonder
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah we were staying behind the
finishing line just hanging out she was
waiting for me
[Music]
hello everybody my saplings
[Laughter]
[Music]
but i'm not a god i'm just
i need subtitling
yeah that's what everybody says look at
okay what is this
hello okay
it's painful oh no oh no
[Laughter]
are you sure you should be saying that
oh no i keep not getting items
i keep missing the items so sad you know
me too
i keep on missing other things like
curves
i don't know how i match do that on this
map
oh yikes
oh there's
oh there's a quota there
[Applause]
blindly throwing my islands around
oh no
who stole forth
[Music]
wow
it's okay
i did so awful this morning it is okay i
think mario kart's fitting me
i i used to do better too yeah no i know
the things like baby part is
just such a huge mess like everybody's
throwing around items it's just a short
uh course like everyone's cuddling with
one another
yeah i was so lucky like the first few
laps um i got a corner behind me but
somebody else ends up getting it
it's only the last part that i got hit
so i was like wow
the gods of mario karts are protecting
me for today
oh spiderman did you see um the new
spiderman movie i didn't see it yet oh i
did i did i did
oh really was it good oh it was real
good you have to see it i mean if you
like spiderman even if you're just like
a casual fan uh you should i am a casual
fan but i enjoyed it oh everybody likes
that one i think i only
i only watch spider-man 1 so i would
have to first watch spider-man 2 i think
ah okay okay i watched like a few like
there's a really good animated one um i
think it's called into the spider verse
or something
oh yeah there's like an animated movie
it's really cool and i like animation so
i thought it was really cool
[Music]
i basically have not barely like i have
barely seen any any um
marvel movies to begin with i don't know
any marvel movies oh okay okay i just
casually watched
movies
um
i just watch it when i can like it's not
like i'm a super big fan but
you know i feel like i just need to
watch it you know because everybody
watches it it's good anyways
what are you doing here they're racing
at me
[Music]
what do you mean did i distract you with
my people and i don't know whip your
beauty
it was nice being number one for a
little while
uh oh it's okay you know um if you get
good orangey you can change
the world
the world being this course yeah yes i'm
coming back i'm coming back
okay okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
oh shoot
i pressed the wrong thing and i'm gonna
uh
oh no
what happened
i fell down even though that was really
unnecessary
okay come on focus focus
focus
let us show how good i am
[Applause]
[Music]
oh nice
thank you for not hitting me
[Applause]
wow i got killed
awful
[Music]
um
what time is it yes
10 more minutes i would say yeah i'll
start practice some more privately and
then sleep and then go to ame and
[Music]
what
it's okay it's okay
it's okay we'll do our best in the
tournament
[Music]
i'm also scared no the thing is you know
um
group d and like everyone's skill level
is like very very like anything can
happen basically yeah
because everyone's skill level is really
close so anything can happen that might
be true yeah that's just
it it makes you
um
inna as inaudible
[Music]
yes
yeah oh my gosh somebody's called
zakotaro
oh
okay see everyone everyone wanted
grumble volcano but we are in the
opposite in an ice world nice world no
cause i need to cool down
[Music]
we need to cool down
no like from uh from what happened this
morning like even like say uh you think
uh probably like oh we got some really
strong people in the jp part over at dt
yes that is true but also
those same people sometimes they get
even eleventh you know so it's just a
really really
orangey reliance
yeah they will hope for their bad luck
i think that's valid i hope donuts place
never gets chosen
oh god
i don't have a problem with donut planes
but for your sake i will hope it won't
get chosen no no it's like i don't
really have a problem with it either but
there's somebody really really good at
donut planes
uh it's buddy central
oh
my
god she probably got all the shortcuts
down huh yeah no yeah the thing is like
with donut planes it's not just
even if you know the shortcut it's kind
of difficult to pull off
that's why i'm like
i got a traumatic experience
[Music]
i gave up on the shortcuts here i gave
him the shortcut too
i'm not gonna get it
yes kick their butts okay kick their
butts
to victory
let's go
[Music]
donkey kong i will destroy your life and
your family
[Applause]
[Music]
i couldn't drift at the end but okay
that was a good placement wait is diddy
kong donkey kong's family what
they know what the [\h__\h] let's
man i got the shortcut down once and it
was like
yeah
so powerful
i hope we'll get like that i hope both
of us will get lucky tomorrow
mario because it doesn't look like luigi
oh that's like i don't know mario and
luigi's child maybe
yeah a child child number
both people yes
say something
so i can say your name say something
green mommy is something green so we can
know your name
oh my god inna with a butt in her face
what in your face wait are we looking at
the same thing oh i see it at the back
[Music]
oh my god that face
is it a trend because i saw some uh the
exact same face with iris though today
what no i don't think it's a trend he
said yeah
yeah it's not a trend it's not a trend
watch chat be like you know if it's not
trend let's make one
no no what's your name
[Music]
ah
oh
what i
okay
okay i see okay
[Music]
okay oh no you can't show something like
that to idols
yeah
what is that
why are we on rainbow road again i don't
know i'm so sick of rainbow
why oh they have their butts protected
ouija has their butts protected i can't
accept this
protected box
[Music]
[Applause]
oh you're behind me
why am i scared
no
i was too scared to use my mushrooms
already so now i lost i lost my quota
too so sad very very sad
i like the music for rainbow road though
it's really peaceful unlike the track
[Applause]
[Music]
i don't want to use it yet
a little too much too much too much
[Music]
oh yes somebody spawned a blue shell so
good
oh yes
[Music]
okay last round
last laugh
oh god
that's
[Music]
i mean could have been worse you know
could have been shelled in like mid-air
or something
oh god
what are the chances that just happen to
me
oh god yeah okay i'm gonna play so bad
now because i lost my rhythm
man
chad i did not know what i was doing
there i just kind of believed in it
believe
[Music]
because i messed up at the end but i i
accidentally took two shortcuts without
knowing it oh that's nice wait wait wait
wait let's not stop guys okay so you got
it down you can use it in the home
button really i don't remember where it
is
okay
okay you can do it without any speed
items though right um yeah uh yeah as
long as you hit the thing
[Music]
because i was using speed items and i
think that made it a lot easier
i see acaci
can we say next one last one yeah sure
let's try okay let's aim for big blue
okay
or no you know what i'll go for swamp
for ruins because i hadn't didn't have
that one yet today i think sure okay
um
okay
chat um you might want to watch out uh i
might um
notify you guys on twitter when i'm
playing privately if i open my
tournament so i can have some people
practicing with me off screen as well
yeah yeah yeah this is better than
practicing against npcs i think yeah
definitely definitely definitely
practicing against people
now the thing is i kind of want to climb
the worldwide rank so we have like you
know the ratings and everything but i
kind of don't like the fact that you
know we always get 100 cc in the early
ranks or something i want to do 115
mr squeaks
is there oh
oh what is this from oh
yay
oh it's been so long i don't
i haven't done this one in a long time
i don't remember it at all
[Music]
[Applause]
my items but you guys like that
was that a shortcut
bananas
oh my god this is
good
oh nice music on this map
[Music]
it's so medieval
oh [\h__\h]
i'll try this
oh
let's go
[Music]
excuse me
[Applause]
[Music]
hey
you don't have to pull me back
[Music]
nice oh yes yes yes yes
ah too late though that's fine
one more okay okay
holy crap that was so lucky i dodged two
thunders in a match what
i had that before oh yeah when i i think
i dodged like two or three thunders with
what because i always got a star like
one millisecond before the fun day that
was so lucky oh that's so lucky yeah
want to try electrodrome or something i
don't know um
that one or bone dry dunes i didn't have
today yet either what sucks
nobody
my scheduled nap is starting in one hour
okay
[Music]
yeah
um but it's okay uh if i
uh
nap a little bit later i won't be able
to fall asleep right away anyway how
long does it take you to fall asleep and
do you have a problem too to fall asleep
man lately yes because um i because i
don't have much time right so the only
free time for me to like watch youtube
videos or stuff is when i'm in bed or
preparing for bed
so i always end up watching youtube
videos or like i don't know
just use your videos in bed that's it
so it takes a while for me to fall
asleep like probably one two hours
[Music]
if last game is so good that i guess
that's why there is the last game too
okay
believe in yourself believe in yourself
yes believe in the whole verb supremacy
wait ouija and botrax have you guys not
been here
a little bit too long too often thank
you
oh yeah that's what i'll send you to the
usual room afterwards i think this is
like your third race or something
[Applause]
getting to the 12th place and then
getting a super dope item yeah
don't based super lit items
[Music]
that was monkey
i realized when i panicked i absolutely
sound like a monkey
oh
[Music]
it's embarrassing oh [\h__\h] it's like when
you when you scream in panic right
yeah
i could do a good monkey impression
monkey hollow monkeys
yay
and then literally have every member in
it
ow
should we be in uk jungle then oh dang
it
now that i'm in eighth place will i
probably get something good hopefully
yes
[Music]
oh yes oh yes oh yes oh yes yes yes yes
[Applause]
why must you put yourself in this misery
misery
[Music]
this point i guess
one more okay okay okay one more one
more
i want to end on a high note okay okay
okay
whoo
wall hugging yes wall is best friend
dragon driftway is really difficult why
would this i don't know after you let's
do dragon driftway
okay
because also didn't practice this one
today yet i think this one is really
really difficult for me okay um are you
gonna leave luigi or what
are you gonna label what
i'm gonna kick him out
you can't
no no what's that not
tomato oh [\h__\h] uh
come
[Music]
on bye
i'm trying to tell him
thank you for playing
read the airplanes
you should we shall
[Laughter]
ah
this is like your fifth race or so
you don't follow the mario kart manners
what
why
why mamma mia
oh we have some npcs in here yeah we got
two as as as if there weren't already
enough people waiting outside of the
room to join
um
[Music]
because i think like sometimes not that
looks like a real person yeah oh yoshi
what
[Music]
[Applause]
oh i got speed
[Music]
i am getting left here
are you freaking serious
oh well i guess
at least that's where i get
spawned
i was trying to like
move
[Music]
[Applause]
random burp sounds be like
emotion
oh my god somebody
somebody swam
next to me
was that you
you [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
so sad
[Applause]
[Laughter]
with you
[Music]
customization i got a new vehicle
customization i'm gonna check it out
later
of course you're not gonna change it
though because you're gonna rely on the
metal aren't ya
yes because i have the items to do that
yeah
big minnie reigning why do i get them
[Music]
ah that was fun that was fun wait let me
restart the audio because it's like
crackling
a game capture let's go
this kindergartner i'm not a
kindergartner am i dang
okay guys um that was fun that was fun
wait um where's kiara okay there we go
oh okay
nice
ah that was fun that was fun fun fun
um yeah
uh we're gonna check out our uh
we're gonna check out our new
are you
are you gear i hope it's a clock
i don't need that
god i'm so excited
whatever
[Music]
i hate it
[Laughter]
dang it but anyways it's um you know
racing with qr is fun um i'm gonna do my
best for tomorrow
i think i'll uh stop streaming and end
it on uh you know on um on a high note
even though i got 10th you know like one
plus zero is one so same thing right
it's always a fun time to talk with pr i
just realized like right we don't really
collab that we haven't been collabing
that much but you guys heard about the
you know the future collab thing so i'm
excited for it yeah interested uh
excited also to just you know hang out
when we can
to anyways guys thanks for watching this
the tournament is tomorrow and um
i am gonna be uh i am gonna be read not
reading i'm gonna be streaming my part
but i'm gonna stream my part like
probably like a little bit before my d
block starts
yeah because i'm in d block and
so basically i'm just gonna like stream
whenever my turn is um there so yeah
yeah okay okay thank you for the stream
uh i'm gonna
i'm gonna read donations from this
morning as well as
as well as today so um just give me a
sec uh give me a sec and i'll um set up
some stuff
and then
[Laughter]
okay there we go
all right
[Music]
man that was
that was certainly something
uh i hope my hand i hope my left hand
will be okay tomorrow um that was
intense
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's true that's actually true so i'm
gonna do that in tomorrow's tournament
[Laughter]
uh that was so much fun good luck having
the tournament bird strong together
thank you um let's just read donations
okay
let's read donations from this morning
that's uh this morning is very very very
very very fun
too
i felt like i was racing with
pros there were so many good people like
everybody was so huddled together for
most of the time if it really really
felt different um i thought it was like
man so this is hollow live
it certainly seemed
it's really difficult you know than the
normal online races i feel like
[Laughter]
i think like half of
the people from this morning at least
are from the team so it's like hey you
know
who are more tzuyu in your opinion
horror men in your cup or murakyats
different skill levels
moroccans have a different skill level
so you know sometimes there are people
that completely destroy me and i can
just never catch up no matter what
happens but in the you the youtube is
just really really intense because like
throughout
everything like people just like huddle
up together and there's so many possib
you know there's
everything can go wrong i feel like
exactly because everybody is so huddled
together all the freaking time yeah
and now i gotta eat i know i gotta eat
before the tourney i will um i have
leftover spaghetti
yes
um
yeah yeah i want to say how positive are
you on tournament uh probably probably
like a five it's a mixed bag you know
it's rng if rng lets me win then it'll
let me win so
yeah um whatever uh whatever i will get
in this tournament i'm gonna have a lot
of fun because
it's a big event everybody is gonna be
super hyped for it and i'm just happy
that i can be a part of you know this
this event you know
it's really nice it's gonna be my first
one i'm gonna make sure that you know i
try my best i try to race to the fullest
and so and so and so and so
yes what time you'll start streaming
tomorrow uh probably when my d block
starts i don't know when exactly
but yeah don't forget to hydrate as well
thank you thank you thank you
yeah yeah yeah
like um
like what see say senpai told me i um
i'm gonna say oh my okay
yes
[Laughter]
aim for the first place please oh yeah
and um the race starts at uh yabe time
so like 11 am gmt plus 7 aka western
indonesian time or 13 jst
yes yes yes yes yes
very nice
[Music]
okay so first we're going to do from
this morning we have quetzal solo rainy
i'm counting on you to grasp victory as
easily as i grasp this melon
oh you might have some difficulties
though
and quetzalman solo whoops i dropped the
melon yeah exactly
exactly
well well well we have fried cactus
believe in the heart of the coins
reigning they'll help you in your
victory thank you
i i would say i've gotten better in
getting coins right
yes yes yes yes no matter what happens
we are proud of you thank you you guys
are real homies i appreciate it
we have doomsday dan thank you so much
for the mushroom
we have e okay i'll be rooting for rain
tomorrow no matter what so please do
your best my future wifey um get away s
but thank you
you're not holding the melon sperm
enough oh my
i have to do my best
[Music]
yabby o'clock has become new time zones
for maracas exactly
and
we have
rey sending supa to bribe oranges for
reigning thank you
yeah rn jesus needs more bribing
apparently
but today was actually um pretty
interesting i enjoyed today um i got
pretty lucky
um placed quite you know nice placements
and everything yes
yes yes yes yes yes yes
raining has yabby standard time
we have amir kaziah best of luck for
tomorrow rainy thank you
what time you wake up yummy minus three
oh good heavens just look at the time it
is yabby o'clock i see
yst that's so good
we have
we have the
name for the space warrior you did good
ready maybe you should do an english
lesson with suichan one day she won last
year's tourney
maybe maybe maybe if switch
if sweet senpai would be fun is it like
you know
she's pretty she's super cool i would i
would love to have something like that
maybe in the future
if that's possible
[Music]
and oh and then for this donation we
have razor clothes reigning all the best
okay
[Music]
we have
um but i think like anything can happen
so i'm just going to be on standby i
guess
we have um skill paige i hope you win
the tournament thank you thank you it
means a lot i'm gonna absolutely try my
best i'm gonna absolutely try my best
because anything can happen right i just
gotta believe in myself to the very end
so thank you for those poor appreciated
we have rey
sending supa an attempt to reduce seduce
orange jesus for reigning also might i
need to pull a gotcha later
thank you
[Music]
mintake
we have
um cabin crunch 90 red ninty ran out of
mushrooms we need to keep it that way
we have shadow five six two great
trading rain thank you
[Music]
so apparently i guess i'm just going to
start streaming from
uh in the sa during the same time as bae
then
[Music]
is the year of ketone
yes yes yes yes
we have shadow fuzzy secret training
thank you we have merry dude gg is
raining i promise i had no wall hacks on
thank you
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice
[Music]
okay we have baby mike hello wayney
thank you hello to you too i hope you
enjoyed the stream
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
we have
uh we have lololo
uh
oh my god so much korean
[Laughter]
so much korean uh i need to buffer my
brain for this
um
what
er sorry i can't read
[Music]
oh my god john
i don't know man can i i don't know if i
don't know what this means can i read
this can i read this
[Music]
something something yeah okay wait hold
on
[Music]
google google says rainey please show
our manager the spicy taste what what
does that mean
what does that what this rainy please
show our manager oh
our manager is probably tinto
spicy taste is probably yeah something
about i don't know
ah
what what which ones which one's manager
[Music]
well which one's what's manager in
korean
[Music]
spicy spicy
decoding the message
spicy manager
yeah because at first like manager my
manager no i think it's tencho because
it sounds like spicy
[Music]
thank you
yeah i need to learn korean i don't know
any korean
unless
um you know except for the stuff i
learned in dramas like really really
[Music]
phrases that i can't use in real life
most of them are people calling
a terrible names
you're literally the featured dish on
cafe's menu wait no i saw thanksgiving
special or something i saw that
we have cubey incubator good luck in the
tournament thank you
we have
sit down cafe astronomer call me you
need a sponsor for magnet duet cover no
you know what i will actually always
want to have like a duet with kiara but
you know we'll we'll see how it goes
thank you
did you see the kiara crony thing and
which one
[Music]
i need korean lessons i like korean
chicken
that's that's really random nobody asked
that but
yeah
[Music]
baby my hi rainey can i send you a
picture to nasa why
another video hi rainy can i send your
why would you want to send my picture to
nasa why
oh they they sent the super chat twice
but i to ask back why why do you want to
send my picture to nasa
[Music]
because you're a star i don't know
because you're out of this world
i don't understand i was doing rainbow
road i see
because your astronomical astronomically
beautiful oh okay
because you are a planet
okay
oh the one where kiara started speaking
korean and asked for money for breast
milk and crony lost how do i say i want
breast milk in korean
um
[Music]
i want breast milk
um
[Music]
i don't know
uh is that correct to the kr bros
[Music]
just ask kiara okay i will
kiara taunting crony with that i see say
that when you meet crony i will
well what should i say to crony in
korean do you do you have a suggestion
on what i should say to crony uh the
next time cronie sees me
um i'm gonna say something to her in
korean so she's surprised
so she so say that
say the s word no i will not
i will not
the breast milk one is fine okay
i see
um
i won't recommend you what i know
akusayan crony er
okay
um
akusayancrony i love cronie
i don't know
[Music]
i don't understand
where can i get milk from you
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
google translate says it means where can
i get milk from you
can i play stylophone on your abs
can i play silo phone on your abs
oh crony comma
can i play cellophane crony
uh
[Music]
goodness
she loves is that xylophone
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't know
does crony have abs i guess only one way
to find out can we hear google translate
sound
uh i think so sure
cronie
lopez
[Laughter]
[Music]
cronie recently said she has abs
xylophone is very very decay
yes she lost
in korean
fascinating the seduction is working
[Applause]
we have zara zane it was fun racing with
you in kiara rainey even if i got lost
and it was the battle battle race thanks
for racing thank you for
[Music]
i mean i don't see why not right
no it's it's not flirting i'm just
objectively admiring the existence of
the thing that is called abs
right
[Music]
we have doomsday done kiara do you
having rainy spicy oh my
spicy spicy spicy
if there's a collab there's flirting
when no the last time the last time i
tried to talk to cronie she told me to
shut up
[Music]
i have dulcan's day adapter funds thank
you
you have abs rainy i used to
i need to get back in shape
and go back to exercising but exercising
is so tiring
crony isn't sin that's progress oh my
god are you like
serious oh okay
bring back mikasa rainey
yeah doom stay down kiara's showing
raining her kimono in private spicy oh
yeah i need to ask that but i think
she's practicing in private so i'm just
gonna um ask her later
[Music]
mikasa i was lost but not forgotten i
know
yeah for to naza this was so much fun i
can't good luck have fun the tournament
reigning bridge drawn together thank you
i did have fun too i'm glad you had fun
[Music]
abs is good but i prefer pbt
i like abs
i like abs i don't know i feel like it's
just because i use a lot of gmk
i have some pvt uh keycaps though
on
i feel like
it's half and half you know
sort of half and half because i have
like
six
i don't know but it's like kind of half
and half like my um abs and um pbt
collection
do you do you have fun in the tournament
training yes of course i did
uh-huh uh-huh
[Music]
and well you guys are so sweet we have
rg4 i just want to say good luck in the
races later thank you so much uh i'm i i
need to sleep early actually i haven't
consumed any coffee so hopefully i can
rest well i need to wake up early i
think like
earlier than whenever the tournament
starts because
i have to shake off like the groggy
feeling waking up in the morning i need
to eat i need to you know
be on my best
i don't know man but you get what i mean
right if i just woke up and everything
you know
uh judgment's gonna be clouded i'm not
gonna be careful and i gotta do my best
like you know what i'm doing today like
at night during night streams
yes yes yes yes
okay we have um
we have axel dearbest in the tournament
reigning
thank you
yes yes yes yes
um
we have
star steel no matter what happens we are
proud of you thank you
rest well no bugatti tonight no yofkashi
no staying up okay
[Music]
let's go
let's do our best let's have a lot of
fun in the real deal too thank you
yeah
what what's going on what's going on
rainy sounds like she's on a post game
interview for the nba i don't sorry guys
i don't watch mva what does it sound
like
that you're making me curious
we have
anton m oh yeah i forgot to thank you
for the race today i've been busy
fighting the nintendo servers thanks
raining it was fun and good luck at the
tournament tomorrow thank you so much
uh-huh
we have da4289 my rngb with you have fun
of the tourney we're rooting for you
thank you so much
let's go
uh-huh
oh just answering questions about the
game or race or place it for any sport
or competition i see
all right we have a drag electric v49
what did i miss
49 did i accidentally at least
get chucked into cold sleep or something
what
rainy how was moon is supposed to take
off her keycaps appropriately instead of
ripping them off
it
if you have long fingernails you can use
your fingernails but use a keycap
puller wait was the question about
keycap or switches i don't remember
he shifted damn
hydration reminder oh yeah let us drink
real
the real men use teeth
[Music]
man that was real fun though i had a lot
of fun wow i've been streaming for like
three and a half hours i didn't realize
i need to um
i need to make the thumbnail for
tomorrow
[Music]
have any menial best luck to you
tomorrow just remember to try our best
and have fun probably can't watch you
tomorrow due to friday noon and work
playing with you and morocco is so fun
hope you can play again heck yeah thank
you so much thank you so much everybody
for accompanying me um in these like
practice training arcs tomorrow is
finally the real deal let's just do our
best whatever happens the important
thing is that we're having a lot of fun
all right
thank you so much
for today i will see you in the real
deal in the tournament hope you guys
will cheer for me and you know we're
gonna have a lot of fun all right that
is it from me today thank you so much
thank you very much for your attention
and let's catch on catch on everybody
the best we can salam
everybody bye-bye
[Music]
you