n
[Music]
o
1 a
[Music]
n
oh
[Music]
d
KY oh chunky wonky no don't
leave K hello nice whe thank you I I am
not prepared enough oops h
H it's not even
like properly like there's some weird
line
there I don't know if if maybe for the
next stream maybe kfp wants to make a
wheel for
me huh I saw something blue a
herb what's
up it's perfect no it's
not
no I keep getting
hello uh it feels weird to
stream because I feel like I've what I
feel like I've only been doing
collabs and I don't know how to talk to
you guys
anymore uh but
yay ah feels like it's been a while
since the last solo stream that's a bike
wheel duh that's a
joke eh was I playing Z 4 days ago oh
yeah yeah yeah but it really has been a
while it's like I had 2 days off but I
didn't really but I kind of did but I
didn't really I don't
know um I just I just have oh wait when
did I play
Da doesn't matter it just really feels
like I haven't been talking much to you
guys and I haven't been uh around much
but I'm here and if you are out of the
loop and you're wondering why the hell
is kiar playing this game that's a good
valid
question why is s playing this game well
because there is some kind of
competition uh staff came up with the
idea a while ago to have
uh with everybody who wants to
participate
um I I don't know if when I signed up
for it if I was really aware of the time
when it was going to
happen cuz the competi is at 400 a.m.
for me 4 a.m.
4 um but it seems like it w't be too
long it will just be an hour maximum so
I I will survive I will stay up for it
probably because I already messed up my
sleep schedule in a way that I wasn't
planning
to last night I was uh awake past 4:00
a.m. so you know what my strategy is
going to be it's going to be staying up
not waking up her what's your strategy
going to be you're in terms of waking up
for it or or staying up for it cuz cuz
you're also participating
[Music]
right The Meta is staying awake why is
this orange how do they know that I'm
orange probably staying up we'll see if
I get yeah definitely we'll need a nap
can take a nap around like 11:00 p.m. or
so or I don't know how long your naps
usually are but my naps are really
long but yeah
so I thought okay got to do a practice
stream right this will be the practice
stream and then
tomorrow I'm taking like the day off but
the night off tomorrow in my schedule it
might look like I'm not streaming but
it's basically still the same day for me
the night of tomorrow will be the
competition
right that's crazy I don't have that
much time then
um but yeah so I'll be sleeping during
the day and practicing during the
day hopefully I can get good in a short
amount of time I haven't seen anybody
else besides Ina practice though so
maybe I don't need to try so
hard but I seriously don't have
confidence
so the good thing is the one thing that
maybe I got going for myself although I
I would wouldn't really say so H I
bought a wheel not the best wheel on the
market for sure definitely not um but I
bought a wheel cuz people said it makes
it easier because really makes sense
people have been saying like on Mario
Cart whatever but racing games with a
joycon h like with a with a joycon what
you do you call that joyon outside of
Nintendo controller I wait is it always
Joy I for God joystick joystick yeah cuz
the joystick can't really pick up those
movements so well when you're in such a
highpe speed range and you need to have
more sensitive motions right so I
thought oh that makes a lot of sense
maybe I should get a wheel even if it's
a cheap one so my my thing does not have
this thing that's called
force field no what what force something
I don't have that it's not that
fancy uh voice feedback yeah I don't
have that and I don't have clutch only
but I have two pedals and I I got a
Ferrari horse on my on my wheel so if
you're curious It's a what was it a frm
t80 if you're curious it's nothing
special but if I really like it maybe
I'll get a better one but the thing is I
don't know man this is my first time
using it so I don't know if I'll really
be better than send people with a uh a a
joystick I don't think
so but it will surely be fun and feel
much better than using a normal
controller H I wanted to see if you guys
can maybe help me out with the
settings
um let
me oh it's Window mode now why
oh there we go
um let's see K
Tak doesn't like sushi I guess that's
okay every time I see my name written in
that order discontinu no obviously not
cuz I was able to buy mine but it's like
a special edition apparently Ferrari
Edition um so I set these things but I
don't have
clutch uh but like what about these
things do I need to set these to
I have a couple more buttons there's
like PlayStation
buttons do I need to set them I don't
not need it
okay yeah my the the wheel I bought it
had like a little bit of a discount now
one question I want to ask is if it's
normal my pedals they're on the ground
right but when I push a pedal in the
whole like pedal thing will lift off of
the ground do you know what I
mean and so I wonder is this normal I
mean with my other leg I can hold it
down but is that supposed what is that
what you're supposed to do do you never
push both pedals at the same time no
it's not on carpet it's on normal ground
but I can put it on a small carpet that
I have next to me but it's the same
thing yeah is there
like um it has these like
anti or oh wait is this am I supposed to
take these
off no right yeah there's like some
anti- um um ro ro
thing in in in
speaking uh in the practical sense anti
sleep yeah uh do I ever have to press
both pedals I don't I don't have a
license I don't know if that's a thing
do I ever speed and break at the same
time no okay then I can just always hold
down one pedal with one the the whole
thing with one leg and then the other
leg will always activate whatever pedal
I
want oh but then we're good maybe this
is supposed to be like
this okay well let's warm up I guess
let's learn how to [\h__\h] play practice
I don't know um start session I've I
literally only went in to check if the
controls work
I have not done
anything ah uh Drive okay I don't know
how this works ah it's too loud isn't it
it feels too loud
already
okay okay see W it's
working uh was right side speed yeah
okay let's go
slowly no let's go boom I didn't even
choose a c they just gave me a random
car oh is the is the green
line banned can I not step on it no is
it okay okay oh oh shot crap
already it's my first time driving with
a wheel okay please be
nice follow the land okay eyes on the
road right oh this this is a nice C
oh yeah oh
[Laughter]
yeah wait where's the road uh W
beautiful scenery beautiful light this
is in Germany by the way
nice n or something like that let's go
I'm too slow I want to be faster we need
to get these curves all right all right
all right um
what that do work it all I went off the
gas even is that the hardest track wow
why do they give me the hardest track ah
[\h__\h] let's
go who makes roads like this just make
them straight that would be so much
easier why don't you why do you make so
many wait what the
hell why can't I not do
curves ah [\h__\h] ah oh it's telling me
don't go backwards okay yo yo yo yo yo
yo yo yo yo I need I think I need a
chair that isn't um on wheels that would
be like I need a little bit more
stability I think that' be
good it's a bit difficult and I want to
switch to the brake but my whole pedal
thing might go off the ground so I need
to like step one leg back
first see I'm telling you maybe I don't
need a wheel maybe not having a wheel is
better for me maybe a normal controller
would be better for
me but okay we're going to get
going see I break but then I lose my
speed I don't
understand a wheel is always better you
think
so uh it would be cool if I could put
the the gas and the brakes on my on my
wheel I have some the the
metal uh the metal FL flingy things that
I have on my wheel that are like shift
up and down wait
shift does this do anything here what
does this mean I don't understand these
things
ah uh but I would like that to be
my my brakes and
my
gas but what do I even want to be
in ah it's so
bad H why would I change gears why is it
it's automatic anyway is it
not oh there you go it changed on its
own I don't have to worry about it
right oh we're on four five can we get
much
higher that was pretty good I mean come
on speed
faster I'm doing wor way worse than the
Mario
Kart what what a [\h__\h] sake oh
man oh man what holy drift did I
drift well that's a nice
thing oh oh the wheel goes the wheel on
the bus go around and
round they do they do go around don't
they oh that was a good
curve drifting is bad what my whole life
iris is here Iris let me pick you up St
allward hey that was good
I my whole life was a lie I thought
drifting was good they always teach you
drifto Iris don't worry I'm not really
wait you're not actually joining the
race right you're just um commentating
so I was going to say like don't worry
about me I'm obviously not any
competition wait why are you awake
anyway oh guess it's not Dad light it's
like
[Applause]
one first person would be better wait
where am I oh [\h__\h] so I got a little bit
confused how do I how do I change
um how do I change the POV
[\h__\h]
F1 do you like this more or ah oh oh
this is
nice that's a clear view I like this oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah yeah baby oh jle
stop I'm I'm breaking I'm breaking
but then I need to put my leg
off W whoo whoo whoo what's going on in
my
chat if you press F1 multip you can get
third person too a I think I like this
view
advertisement a man of my
country I can't go stay
anymore come on
oh Irish do you know how to play this
game can you can you teach me wait it
says on the top right it says Drive zero
out of 10 Clean Labs I've already driven
a few labs are you saying none of them
were clean I don't know what you mean at
all all right all right here comes a
curve oh oh oh
man this game is extremely hard to yeah
why why why was this game chosen why
couldn't it happen Mario
Kart what was the point of all my Mario
Kart training in my four years of whole
[Music]
life
go drive much slower for the tutorial um
what's the point I'll have to gas gas
gas in the future there's something on
the
road wait wait why were there two road
splits
what did that
mean
okay I can't that can't be the way you
do it like going that
slow on the curve everybody will pass
me that was a pit stop oh how fun oh God
oh God we're so fast
oh oh [\h__\h] right it to
Yokohama that was a shortcut to
Japan red means break mhm yeah I mean I
kind of had a feeling that that's what
they were trying to
say I can't switch that fast because my
pedals are not safely on the
ground I will blame it on
that that was okay but wait too slow
like I don't know how they do it oh that
was okay too
maybe tape your pedals oh I can't do it
now I'm I'm in a
car I'm driving
[Music]
wo use duct tape why is it not like
better why is it not suction cups or so
you're crashing not driving excuse me
I've only crashed like two times or
so
[Laughter]
oh wow I'm getting
tozy that way that way no
no go go just go straight
whatever if I can't get that right let's
just go straight yeah yeah yeah here we
go here we go here we go here we
go the grass is green just like those
arrows so that's a a sign for me
to to go over the
grass oh
[Music]
God go go go go go wait I try to
reposition
[Music]
my tires are where where do you see that
my tires are worn out should I go to a
stop where is the next
[Music]
stop okay no
no
uh red on the bottom right the back oh
oh those are my
tires I
see why is it only the back tires why
are they doing so
bad
uhoh ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow
ow ow
ow maybe I should cancel my
participation in this
tournament
um uh oh wa
wait I want to go there wait wait wait
wait wait is this they said this is the
place the what there's no one
here
what where's
the huh this is the hardest track this
is the hardest track this is
nothing I would imagine something more
difficult ah
here here
hello I want
service where is your
Superior
hello was the right
side turn around how do you go backwards
by the way hi dude what's up are you in
charge of putting all those tires back
up again when somebody crashes against
them no pit crew no wait maybe here
this reminds me of something some core
memory of my childhood is unlocking
right
now I played
[Music]
some some racing game before but I'm not
I don't know
what wait so are we going to have to go
into pit stops during the actual
race uh in the tournament to Grant
Turismo yeah probably that wait who who
will Who will take care of me hello do I
just go into one of
these how do I know H how do I go
backwards I'm all green now oh they just
fixed it by me driving through that's a
good driveth through how do I go
backwards with a
wheel that's not it that's frle
what change gears
ah rever is that
oh
sick all right let's [\h__\h]
go
woohoo let's go
faster ah can't go faster and Fit Stop
huh [\h__\h] slow who the hell are these
guys should I have stopped there what
was that that was some red area
[Music]
[Applause]
no I'm out of
control oh a [\h__\h] okay let's go go
straight go straight when in doubt go
straight who cares what happens to the
tires I'm not paying for it my sponsor
is paying for
it can I play without brakes and just
get let go of the gas I don't really see
a difference
okay now I break but I like break too
much I don't
understand that was good n it wasn't
stop lying to
[Music]
me okay okay okay let's see
oh don't
know oh don't
know
close I wonder wait maybe I can I have
some I have those hand
weights stop moving let me get those
weights and put them on the Wheel
I have two why is she still
driving two two
kg whatever
Waits [\h__\h] automatic driving
service
okay stop rolling around
there okay is this going to work oh yeah
it's holding it down
nice where are we all right here we go
oh this should be better oh yeah me
being able to keep my legs like both of
them at the same time on the pedals cuz
so far I had to always have one leg one
foot on the ground of the pedal thing
because otherwise it was lifting off cuz
it wasn't sticking to the ground if you
know what I mean oh sh immediately kind
of better I mean doubtful but hey I
think it already feels
better
[Music]
y okay here it comes here it
comes no no no no no better better
better better
better oh what we're balling
[Applause]
now
yeah do they have some like Scenic uh
roads like through the mountains or so I
feel like Gran Turismo used to have
stuff like that
right uh uh that was confusing that road
is
confusing Improvement for
sure H do they that's another kind of
racing I guess so this is just boring uh
scenery just the sky I mean the sky is
quite
nice bit and bit EMP
power at least we're in Germany in the
country where I speak the
language hello there's so many people
there wait well sorry I I accidentally
pressed the the shifting ow
why are you going that way come on what
are you
doing all
right all right all right all right all
[Music]
right oh
[Applause]
shortcut oh roller
coaster
[Music]
I oh God
ah has anybody in the chat let's do some
CH chitchat has anybody in the chat ever
used
a um sad lamp cuz I ordered a few things
from Amazon and today the wheel arrived
and my my daylight lamp
arrived and I turned it on and I don't
really know I was expecting because the
reviews were so good but it's really
just a normal lamp so oops
sh W did you see that oh [\h__\h] two Curves
in a row is
mean it's just a really bright lamp but
people say that it's like light therapy
and if you turn it on in the first like
30 minutes of your day like when you
wake up and right away you turn it on
for like 20 or 30 minutes
[Music]
[\h__\h] not that curb
again then um I don't know I don't know
apparently it's supposed to make you
feel better throughout the day which
already sounds like a lot of [\h__\h] to
me but people were like ah yeah like in
the winter time when you don't get so
much daylight it can't be quite
depressing and thus I use this lamp and
I was like okay
yeah it sounds like one of those like
weird crystal science things like like
oh crystals uh
whatever oh what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h]
I I feel like maybe this might give me
motion sickness I'm not sure
yet but that was that was
okay well at least you know
even if it won't help me like that I can
cope that it's just another nice [\h__\h] ah
[\h__\h] it's just a nice little desk clam
for my makeup table cuz my makeup table
is like in a pretty dark room my bedroom
is kind of
dark and I have like the ceiling lamp
which isn't doesn't really make it
bright enough and like two little night
lamps which also don't make it much
brighter so with this sad
lamp oh oh [\h__\h] wait I pressed F1 to
change the angle but I was not in the
game it seems wait going to get sick oh
my
god oh play this game in VR I imagine it
might be oh
cute do you think I might be better in
this
POV oh
God probably know
right but it's it gives me a nice view
of my
[Music]
car third person is easier for a
beginner yeah I mean I'm the one who
insisted on playing Minecraft in third
person when I started
out oh
[\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] I don't know I think this is like I
like having a clear view
so yeah anybody in the chat who used a
lamp like that before and it worked for
them or are you just as
disappointed I mean that was a fine
curve that was a fine curve too yes I
used one it was total garbage oh great
why didn't you not stop
me I had one it's it's
okay I'm reading
comments you didn't
ask well you should have always
anticipated
[Music]
it well the other thing I bought was a a
red light uh infrared light lamp it
hasn't arrived yet but I do kind of
believe believe in the infrared light I
think there's
scientific evidence for red light uh
being able to reach um like your muscles
and stuff and being good for chronic
pain yeah no that's real I think it's
also good for skin but
um yeah for me I want to try it on
like my neck and my
shoulders no those are really you guys
some of you are still like dott dot dot
but no no no no infrared light is
actually uh I think scientifically
proven to be n
beneficial for skin you think only for
skin but I I I I hear good things I I
hear good things yeah trust me
bro no no for real
pretty sure see I'm driving pretty well
for looking at the chat 50% of the
time all right look it up Chad look it
up is red infra infrared light
scientifically proven to be helpful look
it up on Google I can't Google right now
sasani that is
like that's that goes too
far maybe it's time time to race with
CPUs yeah but the shittiest of the
shittiest can I race with you guys did
Ena race with uh the audience I wonder
let me reposition my weights okay nice
drift thank you it's all about the drift
my
friends see only did
solo can I play against you guys is that
possible you going
to really kick my ass though
no but that crack is really mean
ow back to Yokohama it's nice there I
like Yokohama and I think uh what's it
in Yokohama the Yokohama Marin tower now
has Marin SAA as like a mascot or
something I saw that on
Twitter so it's nice to go sightseeing
there now see M
Senpai speaking of M Senpai have you
guys seen the newest Mirage dance
video o okay okay
okay
[Music]
with yeah so we are kind of about to be
two steps ahead right now uh the master
stones are like one step ahead I mean
I'm one step behind
[\h__\h]
uh production sorry it it takes a little
while
H we're trying our
best
but hello that's weird I don't know if
that YouTube or me because my
OBS can I just say
a little bit of German
rage
o br br br bro bro bro bro bro bro bro
what the actual
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is going on
what the [\h__\h]
huh I think now we're back I closed the
game under the suspicion that me loading
into the multiplayer
servers uh was affecting it maybe it
was doubtful but I closed the game and
then it came back and it didn't crash
until I tried to log into the
multiplayer
servers
[Music]
weird let's shall we try again I'll
restart the game see now it's not it's
completely stopped crashing me funny
comment most of the stream was crashing
anyway all right let's try again then
otherwise I'm stuck in Solo play hell I
mean why not
boms you've seen other streams before
with this problem with this game
really I mean my band
with with I don't know
here wait is
you is it just on OBS okay see this
might be goodbye again let's see
what IGT DLC
is right we're fine right now are we
okay if I were to want to play with CPUs
where do I go
career single player
uhhuh
uh one of
these why am I
Italian not that I'm
mind change game
mode what where do you mean like one of
these where it says practice
well what what are
these endurance 24 hours who the [\h__\h]
races for 24 hours crazy bastards quick
race
okay 10 minutes full IRL 10 minutes
sheesh wait so did I choose it no
confirm uh confirm ah ah okay okay wait
I didn't set uh how difficult the
players are
though why don't I get to be
Austrian there's some German names here
look at those cars though
sick wait do I can I change their
difficulty or it won't matter okay cuz
I'm [\h__\h] any anyway even that they're
worst is that what you're saying are you
saying my my nationality won't matter of
course it
matters I'm
[Music]
first what's with my
engine [\h__\h] why is it what what's what
my car's
broken what's with my
[Music]
engine why is it why am I manual shift
what's going
on but I'm winning oh here we go wait
what was that what what was happening
now everybody's
serious they're so
fast wait oopsie
sorry on the left [\h__\h] you
ah [\h__\h] where am
I don't leave me behind oh
[\h__\h] don't leave me behind don't leave
me
behind go go go go no no no no
going
F is there a free two one beep or
so
oh are they just going to fall behind me
whenever I
start is my engine doing this weird
thing again no maybe not this time no
wait it is is it because we haven't
officially started
yet so rolling star
huh huh I see oh I think I've seen that
before on TV like
maybe where they're driving but it
doesn't really start until a certain
point so yeah yeah I think I understand
cuz you got to warm up the engine rev up
that engine
[Music]
right [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] this is a
[\h__\h] nightmare why why are we on this
track again
anyway oh look at her reversing like a
boss a little bit of a
curve heck yeah all right I'm still in
the
game I can still win look at me look at
me
go
oh oh
oh I mean as long as I don't
crash yeah yeah yeah yeah find a
comfortable place Pace oh yeah I'm
finding it finding my most comfortable
Pace oh hey hey hey oh hey hey
oh my so Jo driving J this
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I thought
that would have been enough of a n
[\h__\h] hell this place again I'm sick
of seeing the back side of
that
okay little bit of a little bit of a
break through the
F my favorite
noodles why do I hear weird sparkly
sounds I'm so bad at this
game thought this would be
easier like in the arcades when I was a
child
it's not the
same what's
rocks
[Music]
you focus staying what
where I don't have a license IRL do you
think that would help
me this is basically like I'm playing
solo
oh it's not like I'm playing with CPUs
cuz they're so far from me they finished
30 the last one finished 30 seconds
ago I guess I don't no he's 30 seconds
ahead of me I don't
understand you think honestly yeah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] fu [\h__\h] F Yokohama please no have
mercy
Yokohama oh that mean I take take
that I'll take that as a
win okay I'm going to lock in now going
to catch up with everybody you just wait
you just wait and see
[Music]
I'm a car just
like no [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I was supposed to
lock in I forgot I forgot to lock in I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry can you tell when I'm pushing
which pedal is there an
indication on the bottom right or
so it's kind of embarrassing
oh
[Music]
yeah what a beautiful curve that was a
beautiful curve
move [\h__\h] shitty
car you ruined my momentum
what's the
point we should have a
talk way Mark keep pushing halfway mark
we should have a talk what should we
talk
about oh yeah I I had some
visitation
visitation I had some
acquaintances
visit not really specifically
me
but it all came together so I was like
okay I'll woo I'll show you
around
and so I I showed around this really
sweet cute couple from a different
country and brought them to to a cool
place and they gave me some souvenirs
they gave me a lot of really nice tea
like really nice tea not baged tea but
I'm not saying that bed tea can't be
nice I've been having a lot of nice bed
Australian tea tea to I [\h__\h] love it
it's so good every [\h__\h] bag that I
drink cuz I got like a like mixed
flavors they're so
good T is so nice but now I have uh
T from completely different country now
I'm not going to say which country but
it's a it's a
nor nor yeah SC is it Scandinavian wait
it might not be
scandinav it might be close to
Scandinavia I'm not sure is it SC is
this is it considered
Scandinavia not sure but uh
yeah they brought me lots of tea now I
must consume all I've been drinking a
lot of tea and I've already noticed I
don't know maybe it's the Mario Party
from yesterday but and last time too but
my throat each time after the Mario
Party hurt a lot because I screamed okay
makes sense but just in general I I
think my throat has been a little bit
more prone
to get a little bit roughed up that was
the best time I've ever had that that
curve um what was I saying F car is
approaching what there's a car behind
what why is a car behind me it's
supposed to be in front of me [\h__\h] up
[\h__\h] up [\h__\h] up we're fighting now hey
hey rud
Behavior wait do you get penalties if
you
ciz why you stressing me out go back go
I guess front
whatever they laughed me that's so
[Music]
rude oh we're not supposed to
crash what do you mean we're not
supposed to crash then why do they make
this road so narrow
ah who crashed me which bastard was
itach that was not my fault both cars
received are you [\h__\h] kidding
me all right
I'm just turning why am I just
turning that car is dead he's not
moving ah [\h__\h]
hell easy on the pedal okay okay why why
is he why did he give up on
life Foster car is approaching Foster
car is approaching I am the Foster
car what what what was I talking about I
yeah the air is drying up so now I need
to drink tea every day again it's tea
time
baby with
honey I'll be drinking tea all the time
yippe I love tea time I love tea
season I like tea drinking tea sometimes
in like summer but not so much I'm not
as motivated to drink tea in the summer
unless I'm sick oh [\h__\h]
okay okay okay okay stay calm same right
yeah but then Autumn and spring and
winter definitely tea time I love my tea
time I already had I think three cups of
tea today my third cup of tea is in
front of me but it it already became a
little bit too
chilly wow that was
beautiful
okay will the official rat have damage
on no idea I don't really know the rules
or anything I haven't really paid much
attention I don't know if there's even
the set track that we're racing
[Music]
could have been worse that turn what do
you mean wait
time maximum weight time 3 minutes what
does that
mean oh okay here here comes my favorite
[Music]
turn oh that was all
right we should go to different uh Road
after this I don't want to race here
[Music]
anymore oh that was okay surely there's
better ways to do it
but that that that was okay
too Ina raced on Mon
probably because she's thinking of
monjayaki in her head there's only
[Music]
Monti in my head as well interestingly
enough um I did not want to go in here
honestly but now I'm
in I mean at this point I'm already way
last I'm double last all right check
flag good job did the best you
could did the best you could shut the
[\h__\h] up you silly silly
goose so r
oh yeah I mean I'm still learning
today's my first time using a
wheel how do I
change
um how do I
change the
track change cars to
um does it make a big difference the
middle the middle
mid middle of middle of
what ah
oh
aha let me see is there information in
Discord what we are going to be
racing let's see uh where
[Music]
maybe
not
but I think we are getting signed
certain
cars
uh or are we because there's
a wa
car whatever I I look more into it uh
and practice more tomorrow if there's a
specific track that we should be using
but for now here
Monella Italia
wa where did the German one go and this
is in Austria by the
way okay yeah that looks a little bit
more complicated
than I mean these this one looks weird
what happened here England what is that
supposed to
be looks like a lot of
things all
right snake
oh it's a snake it looks like a hook to
me okay and I can change this here too
can we be uh M
Shuma can I be can I be someone
else change
car let's do um wait I'm driving a for
Ferrari right now let's do a Ferrari
sexy oh
yeah can I make it orange again I don't
like this
color whatever oh I'm oh they boun to
the
car
mhm where are the
austrians what did the austrians drive
ah wait where did the Porsche
go should shouldn't it be Red
Bull B with
Germany yeah B with Germany that's not
that's not
Austria whatever I want to drive in
Aston
Martin sexy yeah because I saw this car
in Japan I remember yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I was like whoa and then I I told
you guys about it remember about the
Aston Martin that I saw in Japan I was
like holy [\h__\h] what is that never seen
that
before can we make it orange whoa what
is that the [\h__\h] is this manyu I don't
understand whatever guess we're not
orange
now here we
go they have a dealership in kba oh
that's so far but kba is like the land
of the rich people okay not really
but I feel like it it has a kind of a
rich
Vibe this is where Ena was practicing it
only has two curves okay maybe three or
four
two and a
half
stay
easy are we doing the rolling start
again I love the rolling start cuz it
feels like I'm first at least for time
being
[Music]
let's
on
gas
yes come on come on come on that's a
really long rolling
start now now now come on
yeah here we
go wow this car makes different noises
sexy noises oh God I losing control I
Los the control I Los the
[Music]
control
oops what's n and why are you guys here
in front of
me sorry
for do I get a penalty for stopping
everybody scy slow car
slow car I just I guess I'll continue
going backwards
now
wait
okay finally I'm in control
again I
was I was by the way considering doing a
a wheel camera but I ran out of time
maybe I can do a wheel camera for the
real re the real
tournament then you'll see my grip but I
don't know if I really want to do that
if I should do that because I'm really
close to the wheel I'm like kind of
hugging it I'm almost leaning on it
cuz that's what feels comfortable right
now so wheel camera kind of difficult
honestly that's not how you drive I've
seen people drive like that
IRL I've seen it
before very close some people are really
far in the back but some are some are
close they're not good drivers but this
feels really safe and
like comfortable right now being close
to my
wheel I want to hug
it don't you dare criticize me for that
I'm a beginner anyway okay whatever
works for
me arms out the
window can't I can't even imagine doing
that right now
I need both both arms both hands on my
wheel both chests on my wheel too here
comes the
curve somehow I think I was about to
lose control but I somehow managed to do
it
hey he
who
y if only there was isn't that weird
start with me like blocking everybody's
path we may have a good chance
here H I really wonder
like what's going on like in the front
is everybody having fun who this is a
weird
place what the [\h__\h] who made this who
thought of
this who's the architect of this road
are they like all
[Music]
mingling in the front I want to see I
want to be one of those people in the
front wait for me what oh they're
finishing they're all finishing right
now can I just go straight through here
like what's the point in not going
straight through I feel like my success
rate is higher if I just go straight
through
yes I can I did so I
can oh not bad look at that look at that
staying in the middle of the road like a
[Music]
boss oh wo whoo wo wo wo wo wo wo wo W
wo wo whoa
who doesn't diminish my accompl ments
okay
um whatever whatever I gave up I gave up
in the middle of
that at the halfway mark I'm at the
halfway mark oh we're halfway there
oh living on a
[Music]
Living on a
Prayer yeah we got to play aerot truck
simulator with this now my
reversals are going to be so good now
like legitimately though I'm not even
joking and reversals aren't even that
important in this game it seems normally
you you just want to go
straight but in the aerot truck
simulator that's a different story
there's many cases where I need to
reverse in that
game you want me to follow the
line okay let's try oh wait oh I
accident ah y
y you confused
me oh what the [\h__\h] dangerous you pieces
of [\h__\h]
hey hey hey hey hey
hey [\h__\h] danger where am I where
where am I supposed to
what can you guys let me in so
inconsiderate
whoa let me
in here we
go what about me you guys are finished
anyway let me through
okay meow meow meow
meow
meow me
[Music]
straight through the middle like you a
little don't want no
[Music]
Riddle that's by the way not the lyrics
it's stay in the middle not straight for
the middle but I think this is the
appropriate lyric change for the
situation
[Music]
I like this
car I like this
car okay curve
this is
fine I will say though I'm glad I got a
wheel because it's kind of fun to just
hold the wheel instead of a
controller but I do wonder if I would be
better with the
controller cuz like using my legs for
something in the first place is
something I've never done before I think
in a game
game except for maybe the few times I
played in an arcade like Mario Kart and
an
arcade so this is very unusual for me
using my legs is unusual maybe for
ringfit adventure or so but obviously
that's a completely different
game no Dan reolution I've never played
any of those kind of dance games at
arcades or so those are at arcades right
oh my God that works shortcut do I get a
penalty for getting through the
shortcut I and I'm aware that it's not
supposed to be used as a shortcut
probably yeah
[\h__\h] then why is it
there why is it there if you're not
supposed to use
it
okay the big curves are fine I can
handle the big curves well [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh
hey sorry I'm a bit tired right now
shouldn't be driving when I'm tired I
didn't have a nap today it's my handicap
sign was worth 100 points like positive
points I feel like you're lying to
me yeah why are they waving their
flags are you using tilt
control I'm using something way better
than tilt controls
[Music]
what do you think of that one how was
that
better better But still [\h__\h] right
[Music]
but I will say having my pedals on the
ground uh definitely helps a lot that's
a big
Improvement oh no they're laughing me
again you sick
bastards you sick sick
bastards flag the best you the did the
best you can
they like making funun of me can we end
this
now yeah let's make the races like 5
minutes H shorter I
mean
um what's the replay oh too
late so here
uh I don't know maybe 6 minutes oh wait
that's not
oh 5 minutes
okay and should we still stay on Mon now
let's try every track that I can this
one's kind of
crazy what is wrong with you for making
this
track who thought of
this stay double
five let's
[Music]
go ow [\h__\h] my [\h__\h] ah my weight I
don't know where it
went okay all right just got to do with
one weit hi
smoothie you want to get into the car
and experience
this hell of a roller coaster it's a bit
too dangerous for you smoothie maybe you
shouldn't but smovie has been so cute
and I bought a new blanket because I
thought M I want my blanket to match the
rest of the
room so I bought a nice uh like Ros oh
[\h__\h] M my wait is
up [\h__\h] a nice p
blanket back I have to re align my
weight I'll rest the race in a
moment what's happening right now you're
missing some critical information there
is a four kog hand weights on
my on my uh
pedals all right here we go crowd not
impressed I'm not impressed with them
either they suck shittiest crowd I've
ever had
man so yeah I bought a new blanket and I
was hoping my cats won't like it they
seem to like it and also I got
new uh Kibbles and they immediately
accepted them
which is
surprising they were like all over The
KES I thought I had to
um thought I had to like step by step
slowly introduce them to the new KES but
no they gobbled them
up and no I don't use a G29 I I didn't
want to spend so much money on my first
wheel rather invest that in a real car
yeah it's just a cheap T8 Ferrari
Edition good
enough green light go go go green light
what who the [\h__\h] pushed me somebody
must have pushed
me you
[\h__\h] what the I feel like I'm being
Let Me
In what happened
what why did I get spun oh [\h__\h] this
[\h__\h] what's going
on what is going
[Music]
on [\h__\h] Wheels I'm going to figure
out a better solution for this
tomorrow go going double file Go
Gentle okay pedal to the
metal I'm a race car driver why would I
be gentle on the wheel h on the
pedal I'm not driving through
downtown making my way down
[Music]
I need see he's right behind me he want
he he's aiming for
me yeah you too right stay away from
me okay gentle why they not gentle at
all
but okay we're we're mingling I haven't
mingled with them in so long this is the
first time I'm mingling at all I
think it's crazy I'm in the middle on on
the
right and do they get like in real races
do they also get some kind of voice in
their head telling them clear on the
right car on the
right yeah
oh damn back
seeding yeah [\h__\h] what is wrong with
you you bastard you bastard why would
you pass me passing bastard [\h__\h] past
you ruined my
momentum swear to
God this could have been so beautiful
we could have we could have really
bonded could have introduced you to my
friends could have shown you around in
my
town you [\h__\h] it up
what the hell did that curve come
from are we doing 10 minutes yeah I
thought we were doing 5
minutes did I not confirm the change
I feel like my chair is constantly
moving back when I go into the
pedals so I have to keep on like pulling
myself back
in [\h__\h] out [\h__\h] shitty ass setup
can I lock in my chair I have
a it doesn't look like it has a
lock maybe that thing down there
is this
like I have I have a a Herman
Miller one of those typical here's
dining chair yeah let me grab a dining
chair
I continue to make improvements oh
that's my dining chair is so
[Music]
cute
okay okie doie cute I'm lower now though
kind of kind of
lower and my weights come on all
right let's restart this
match [\h__\h]
hell here you
go going double file
I can do this no I didn't buy a chair I
only bought a wheel but I did buy the
wheel just for
this but we'll find more uses for it for
sure go W go I'm locked in I'm sitting
so
secure I'm also driving very
slowly which is okay for now
chill slow and
steady
until where are we
starting over there yeah okay here we go
go go go go
[Music]
go these guys are so
rude
you you you you knocked my wheel my my
weight off go [\h__\h]
yourself what do you mean both C what
did I do I literally didn't do
anything why am I getting
[Music]
penalty oh man
hear car
noises you need to shift in the
beginning to be faster shift to
what yeah but like up or
down stay
F yeah automatic gears though why would
I have to
shift I'm automatic bro I can shift if I
want to
but is there a
point need a better rig at least the
budget well well you mean with rigging
you mean a better wheel no my wheel is
fine I love my wheel stop heading on my
wheel I should not have been sitting on
that chair and the pedals are kind of
[\h__\h] weird with them lifting off of
the ground the whole time but beside
that well yeah I think I locked them in
quite nicely now the the pedals
car on the left clear on the left ah
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] sh [\h__\h] I ruined it I
ruin it and I did not lock in my pedals
it
seems oh [\h__\h]
hell better wheel fund
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] feel like I might be the only one
with a
wheel anyway but does anybody else have
a wheel in Hollow uh Ian who's
participating in
this do pre-practice to learn the
basics what what what what I already I
what do you mean this is the same as
free practice because basically no one's
around
[Music]
me see I'm
fine I'm doing fine
but I guess there's going to be a lot of
pushing in
the actual race too so you know maybe
it's good to
be the straightly going for
the big CPU mish
mash can't stay on the baby practice
mode
forever the real world is just not like
this
in the real world everybody wants to
[\h__\h] kill
you all of my
colleagues will want to try to kill
me so there's no point in practicing on
the baby practice
mode I need people around me to motivate
me to tell me how [\h__\h] far they are
from me I think they're about to laugh
me yep I see
them I see
them I dare you I dare you I dare you to
laugh me
no that's the worst kind of lap dance to
get wow
huh no I've never in my life received a
lab dance of course not
you're not IRL GTA maybe
yeah this how you drive IRL I don't
drive
IRL my plan is to get a license after
whole live so whenever that is whenever
I could focus on
learning how to drive
cuzz I suck when it comes to school
things and I don't think I could do both
at the same
time oh God I hate this track what a
shitty [\h__\h]
track which country is this again shitty
track
[Music]
man I hate this track the German one was
better you hear that
England it's the UK yeah no I'm not
surprised not surprised
man this one sucked let's go
Silverstone oh that's also England and
then I don't have really high hopes I
mean look at that what the what the [\h__\h]
is
this I mean okay all of these kinds what
is this
Netherlands what is that supposed to be
okay that looks like a bird I could I
could okay I'm not going to say it in
slang I could enjoy a bird
Road it's my glue gun it's a gun what no
it's a
bird why are you guys so
aggressive shouldn't you have Birds on
your mind at all times already thanks to
me it's a bird it's a
plane oh you know it's really cool
yesterday I was like oh man I really
want to watch something something with
substance so I started watching a
documentary on
Netflix it starts like this are you
kidding me
bro um
what was it what was it called again
some documentary
about an old
guy going around the
Americas to find
out if maybe there was like a proper
civilization before Ice Age and they're
finding quite a lot of interesting
evidence honestly yeah
bit oh
God what course it
not I still didn't watch that I don't
know if it's worth watching
that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry not on purpose
really not on
purpose um but yeah
so one really cool thing that was
fascinating at least at the point until
where I
laed um was like they went to the Amazon
forest jungle
whatever what the hell penalty
now penalty the [\h__\h] out of that bastard
uh yeah they went to
Amazon and um not to Amazon the delivery
company
obviously but they went to a place in
the Amazon where they like got rid of
the
trees which is quite a big
area and which is sad of course but the
cool thing about it is that the trees
have been there for thousands and
thousands of years
right and so now with the trees gone you
can see evidence of Unthinkable things
that were there before the ice
age you can see like some crazy [\h__\h] on
the
ground it's
insane like
markings that indicate
[Music]
that there was some like
systematic properly
intelligent architecture going on with
how there's like these lines and M like
what what the [\h__\h] there's a curve
that's a sharp curve M like uh ups and
downs in the ground
yeah like a layout prop a proper Fus
vintage a proper layout wait where is
back and where is forth where is bogus
vintage sorry I lost
myself can you show me the
way this is a really confusing curve
here
okay slowly on the grass right slowly
slowly just slow go slow slow slow
slow here we go wait I'm still going
backwards
[\h__\h] what's a bus stop what are you
talking
about you're talking about my Amazon
story
some the [\h__\h] bus
St
what what what why is this a bus stop
there's no buses stopping here I no pit
stops what's a bus
stop I want something in my eye really
should not be
like full power on the pedal when I'm
picking my
eye I really feel sorry for the people
who are going to watch the tournament
stream because they like this game and
any kind of racing game and are kind of
like excited Ed for it and then they see
us all driving like the most drunk
[\h__\h] toddlers they've ever [\h__\h]
scen bumping and crashing into each
other driving backwards it's going to be
so [\h__\h] chaotic and not just because
of me I
hope that's going to be the most
amateure race you will ever see in your
life I think
entertainment
baby that's what we're here
for H yeah you want to say that are you
sure are you sure you say that
now maybe you're not so much into racing
but the real
race
otakus maybe see it a little bit
differently that's what is this are they
lap are they are those [\h__\h] about to
lap
me is it time already to be lapped
again what they're called race n are you
kidding
me that's very
misleading
behind hey at least I could imagine that
I'm still in the race here with the
people in front of me I just cope and
say yeah I'm thir right
now I'm
third is is it's giving me
immersion I hate racing right
now I want to go Euro Truck Simulator
can we have a tournament in Euro Truck
Simulator Holan
management who delivers the fastest than
the fuest no the fastest than the
safest your truck simulator tournament
please
oh
man car is approaching I don't know I
kind of gave up already in my
mind I thought this would be more fun
I'm
sorry it's okay to take a break are you
making a pun
drive with
controller what are we going to do if
I'm like going to be immediately a
million times better with a controller
that would be so
depressing steering and breaking assist
even if the game offers that there's no
way that would be loud in the
tournament probably return the wheel
still I probably could but no I I I
would love to try this out with your
truck simulator the
wheel are we halfway through this race
yet or
what kind
of kind of lost interest
here I can try with a control I guess
but I have this whole fat wheel in front
of me stuck on
my
[Music]
uh table just go slower what do you mean
I can't it's difficult to go slower
without being
[Music]
lost who came up with the idea
management and I don't mind the idea I
like the idea but I just
suck okay PS5
[Music]
controller if I'm going to be better
with that then I I would feel so scammed
I would
feel so
scammed here disconnect the
wheel we saying that even cuz I asked
you guys is this going to be is is a
wheel just going to be easier for people
who already know how to drive IRL and
you guys were like no no because like
the joysticks you know they're going to
be like a lot more sensitive wa my PS5
controller already
vibrating why is it why are you
vibrating sure excuse me why you why are
you
vibrating why are you
vibrating different
oh
oh how about
now that was my PS5
controller sounds decent you think so
funny gam pad uh wait so if I play with
the controller now uh are we doing game
pad I don't hear anything oh wait my
output is also PS5 controller or what
the [\h__\h] why why does p PS5 controller
think that I want everything to be
handled by
it ridiculous
game pad yeah do I have to do any
settings
here
a oh I can't
hear [\h__\h] PS5 controller ruined
everything for
me yeah I unplugged the wheel
completely why does it want so much
attention I don't know uh
what
channel oh there we go oh there we go oh
I can hear
again oh now it stopped it stopped
vibrating now okay
so well
let's
try
Okay uh what's gas probably
R1 is
it is it even going to
work going dou file r two
wait I don't know I don't think it's
working it's not
working
oh wait
the nothing no button was
working H should I turn
the
yeah should I turn the steam input on
again
maybe okay restarting
[Music]
game
okay coming up next no more steering
wheel I just want to see if this is
somehow easier for some reason
because I don't have to press pedals or
something that' be so sad
[Music]
though Yokohama oh controller Works
let's go uh
x
x let's
go yeah I can still use use the wheel
see now I'm glad that I didn't buy the
most expensive
one if I bought the most expensive one
and I would be struggling like that I
would be so
mad whoa whoa oh this is really um
sensitive okay only the left door stick
oh I have a feeling I'm going to be
better like
this but okay that's not JX it
oh I think I'm going to be
better well I mean I think I think
that's just because it's my first time
using a steering wheel and my whole life
I have been using controllers now so
it's just a bit more intuitively easy
and let's wait till it lets me Speed 3 2
go oh that feels
so e easy
no I still I still would say
so still got to get used to the Sens
sensitivity hey someone's [\h__\h]
pushing me [\h__\h]
ass
okay okay there's a curve up coming
right okay I slowed down a little bit
too early
oh
[\h__\h] I I still think I'm better like I'm
still around the
people who whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
why did I barely turn joystick my friend
or my enemy
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa who
it doesn't turn it doesn't
turn is it just cuz I'm too
fast oh yeah okay I will say the R2
button I probably press it way too
deeply because it's
just yeah my first time I need to get a
a feeling for
it oh this is so sad I want to use my
wheel
oh my God am I better I think I'm
better oh
no oh
[Music]
no I would love to commit to the wheel
but I don't think like I only have like
one
day I can't even get to this level with
the
[Music]
wheel oh I'm a lot
better
[Music]
H uh my wheel is too sensitive no no no
no I wouldn't say so oh [\h__\h] sorry sorry
that that curve is still uh Weir weird
to me that's a very sharp [\h__\h]
curve the wheels take a while to learn
yeah I I think so
too maybe after a few EUR truck
simulator
sessions I could get decent at handling
a steering
wheel but for now
the controller might still be the better
option by the way I saw this game that
the mik samai played with I think
Kai Senai K Senai where they were like
pigs and other weird animals liar bar
yeah is that fun like it looked
fun from like the short moments that I
saw
so I'm thinking of maybe setting up a
collab oh
dear but do I have to know cards for
that
game it basically there's also guns so
I'm wondering is this the same kind of
as
uh uh what was it
what's the other game that now has
multiplayer back shot roulette yeah is
it going to be like the
same a little bit different
maybe you don't need to know cards okay
good well well well well we're going to
play bushot roulette multiplayer next
week not on my channel I think I don't
think it's uh multiple povs anyway
so if won't be on my channel though
because even though I was thinking about
it last week to organize a collab
somebody
Boxx box shot
rette
uh what what uh yeah somebody was uh a
little bit faster of organizing
something so I am part of a
collaboration with some love lovely
cutie
Patois that I'm really happy
to be
around uh off
with wow oh my God it's so much easier
with a controller I can't [\h__\h]
believe it I got
scammed okay wait wait wait this curve
this curve is so [\h__\h] this curve is so
[\h__\h]
I mean look how look at the map how
sharp that curve is no
wonder
well now I feel a little bit better
sharp curve
incoming I need like a big warning on my
screen I can't can't pay attention to
the mini map over there all the time I
need a big warning on my screen and red
letters sharp curve
incoming that would help me
honestly the red yeah I mean still
because I can't really tell how sharp it
will really be sometimes the line
becomes red and it's really not that
sharp and sometimes it
is I need something
more big a bigger
indicator okay if I can get the curves
down like that in the tournament I feel
like I'll already
be
somewhat good
I can't imagine anybody really like
rocking those curves on the pro
level or can
you how sweaty do you think these girls
will be are the tracks known well I
don't know so I don't I don't know if I
just don't know or if they're really not
known no I did new ring several times in
the
beginning fora very that's okay that's
okay some some can be
sweaty as long as it's not everybody I
was trying to be sweaty with my wheel
but the wheel made me less
sweaty hey at least there's time I'm not
getting laughed this is already a big
Improvement guys
I'm not getting
lefted I'm so proud of
myself taking turns better for
sure heck
yeah
yippe y
all right I'm wondering can I tell you
more about my about
me being tourist guide once
again there's there
something was there what happened
anyway showed them
around back and forth I took an Uber I
was really tired but the Ubers they were
like really talkative it was so unlucky
having such talkative UB again and one
of
them I
think was trying to like hit on
me
weirdo L asked me
like if I uh am if I'm single and why
I'm single and I'm like I I don't know I
have my cats I'm happy happy with my
cats I'm focused on my career right
now and then at the end he was
like uh oh is where I picked you up is
that where you live which is a really
concerning question now that I say it
out loud to you
guys and he was like oh we're neighbors
and I'm like I don't know I don't know
about that are we we're not Neighbors
yeah let's hang out sometime have a
coffee by the way guy looked
like a lot older than
me
[Music]
so I don't know man did I look old on
that
day
yeah that was
weird but I was glad to get out of that
Uber
and then on my way back I also got an
Uber and that was a weird Uber that was
more of a funny Uber I was waiting for
my Uber and uh another Uber driver oh
they're about to laugh me oh [\h__\h] I was
just chilling
tanging not paying
attention another another Uber driver
even though I had my my phone out and
looking at where the Uber driver was so
I had like a rough idea that he was not
there yet but another Uber driver came
up to me and was like ah Uber and I'm
like yeah but I don't think you're my
Uber but he kind
of insisted on him being my Uber I was
like no I don't fix so look look at my
map on my Uber app you shouldn't be here
yet and he was like I'm all the way over
there my car is all the way over there
come with me come me I'm like no I don't
know
man see I think my Uber is about to come
and he's like oh okay maybe maybe I am
not your Uber but my my Uber guests
they're like they don't speak um German
it seems do you speak English I was like
yeah he's like can you can I call them
and you talk in English to them and tell
them where I am and I'm like um I mean
my my Uber is literally around the
corner but
okay I really didn't want
to oh [\h__\h] ah
then he started calling them and they
didn't pick up and then my Uber arrived
so I was like okay bye sorry I'm not I'm
really not my this is my Uber you're not
my Uber I'm sorry good luck he was like
okay sorry bye like he really thought I
was his uh customer he really
did yeah and then the Uber that I did
get
into was like some really interesting
interesting like oldish guy
who um oh Phoenix Racing who I don't
know it's hard to describe he was
like
um I don't know how to even describe
[Music]
him it was like a very friendly
Austrian typically Austrian old guy who
was like venting in a very Austrian way
about other customers but said how nice
I am and all that and and and then he he
got a little bit worried about me when I
um I was just like so tired and out of
social batteries so I became a little
quiet after a few minutes and he was
like are you okay are you feeling okay
and I'm like yeah I guess I feel a
little bit sick from like looking at my
phone uh while we're driving and he's
like oh are you are you going to do you
want to throw up oh oh no oh no and he
got so concerned and wanted to stop the
car for me I was like no no I'm I'm I'm
okay sir it's okay but he told me this
whole story about some some uh girl he
picked up from a concert who fell asleep
in his car and he drove her for like 2
hours or so and uh he told me so many of
his like uber um Adventures driving
someone through uh to a different
country and
stuff yeah and he was nice but he just
yapped so so so so much and my social
batteries were so
dead but he was a an interesting
fellow unlike the other guy that was
just
a an uncomfortable
fellow but both of them wanted to Yap so
much can I just get a quiet Uber
please it's just also cuz I'm so nice
myself you
know uh somebody said go back to mon why
we should try out oh
Barcelona no I want I like this shape
but what should where should we go
Silverstone honestly I
mean sand
Fort that's kind of crazy wait didn't we
already try that one
these are all locked Suzuka is locked oh
my God why I want to do this one that
one looks good
America oh yeah these all look pretty
decent wait that look like Texas that
looks like that looks like
Texas but that's oh wait that's
Australia no but I mean it looks like
the shape of Texas not saying that it is
Texas obviously
Valencia cool I didn't know they had a a
racing track are these like accurately
the IRL
tracks oh that looks very long that one
24 hour what do you mean 24 hour do
people drive does it take 24 hours to
get
around I want to do Red Bull why can I
not
have do I need to it good to get this
one to unlock
it still see it ah
Fu okay let's try um
misano go go go
go
o my neck hurts so much these days so
bad every night I sleep seems to make it
worse even though I think the pillow
that I have right now is pretty good
need to get a
massage just reset everything or try to
it won't be a full real reset but an
attempt will be
made maybe tomorrow what happens to
going one month without cracking it it's
[\h__\h] impossible unless I I don't know
unless I [\h__\h] break my neck or just
die
hey careful buddy real careful now
you're going to get caught in
4k car on the left on the
left these
cars so addicted with
[Music]
me car on the
right I am here stay away from me but
I'm still like what eight let's
go hey what the [\h__\h] is wrong with
you orange I am going to un orange you
un oranges
you the clips from yesterday were so
funny yesterday
really that game was so funny constantly
someone else was
winning it kept on changing
on the right wide and there was just so
much
drama can't believe you did that to on
the
right what do you mean she has to learn
that she can't just mess around with her
St eyes hey stop guys can you be a
little bit
nicer why are you so
fast or are these NPCs so
good well they're so slow now
push on the right y [\h__\h]
slow you slowed me
down on the right clear on the
right how do I catch up when they're
they're all following each other's like
little
ducklings notice how they didn't crash
when they went slow excuse
me I'm just trying to catch
up that's how you race it doesn't look
like racing to me going in one line like
almost hand in hand like you're in
preschool that's not how we do it in
Mario Kart
Mario Kart is more hardcore than this
with all the items and [\h__\h] getting
Mario karted I'm telling
you getting blue
shelled out of nowhere
getting Mario karted is like real life
more than this way more than this real
life is more
unfair in real life we don't walk in
straight
lines one behind
another but
anyway um maybe you guys have noticed I
don't know if anybody in the chat
pointed
out but yesterday sometimes I did call
gigy
GG just because I I got more and more
unsure and I felt more and more Awkward
about calling her G but I do like
calling her
giggy what I like that it's cute to me
and it's how I would intuitively call
her if I didn't
know yeah she responds to both and then
after the stream I did ask her like uh
by the way gigy do you mind if I call
you gigy or she's like no no I don't
mind at all I'm I'm like that's totally
fine I have no problem
that so at least we got the gigy
perms yeah personal nickname until I can
think of a better
one so far I
can't it's hard to find original nice
nicknames especially when her name is
already so
short that was a difficult curve but I'm
definitely a million times better with
my
controller theway halfway mark
best race so far yeah even though I'm
looking at the chat yeah go moies
M can we you know we got some names here
and there gobba is the best name I came
up with ever besides
herb
herb feel like I'm sliding on ice here
pretty good
though but I looked a little bit into
Mario party jere's like eight and 20
player
modes it actually looks kind of
interesting I looked it up because like
um there was somebody in our like collab
chat like he I want to play Mario body
who wants to
play and then like a lot of people were
like like me me me and then the person
was like oh right it has an eight player
mode should we just do eight player mode
I don't know how it works so I looked it
up I did some research to
share cuz I wasn't sure either but I was
kind of
curious yeah so if I understand
correctly in
the eight player mode you kind of fight
Bowser in this field
[Music]
um you just run around freely and every
now and then there's mini games and you
you keep on throwing like items against
Bowser or
so
uh yeah but you do get mini games in
between that are specifically made for
eight players so they are
different
from the other mini games and then I saw
20 player mode was it looked
like um sometimes it looked like
everybody was playing different mini
games at different times at different
Paces um and sometimes it looked like
they were playing it simultaneously I'm
not
sure but
uh in that case there was some kind of
map that everybody o was
on and um everybody was moving at a
different pace depending on when they
finished their Mini game and how many
coins they got from their mini game I
think influenced how far they could
go if I understood that correctly that
it's like a race basically try to mix
finish as many mini games as you can
successfully to get through the board
faster but then sometimes I saw the
because I just watched some stream you
know sometimes it looked like they were
playing mini games together and
sometimes they were definitely just like
playing on their
own and everybody was progressing at
different
[Music]
pace there's no private lobby for the 20
really it looked like in that stream it
was like eight people playing and the
rest of the lobby was filled up with um
CPUs but it was definitely their own
friend Circle
playing those eight people
ah ah so for the 20
person you can't get your own 20 people
in but like you're own eight people what
that makes no sense that's
weird yeah I'm getting the hang of this
even though I'm just
yapping so apparently during the
tournament we're going to be like
everybody's going to be in their own
voice chat but then cie and Iris might
come into our VC every now and then
and like we would hear them and we would
be able to communicate a little bit like
comment on while we're racing oh they're
lapping me really I'm almost done don't
lap me
no I was so close to not getting
lefted approaching oh go away
please hey you [\h__\h] hurt me ow
be careful when you're passing
me up behind you yeah so I'm wondering
if that's going to like make me nervous
when suddenly CI and Iris show up in my
head the voice is in my
head behind I hope they don't give
me uh a jump
scare that' be so [\h__\h] messed up
if I like crash into a wall or so
because they come into my VC and I'm
like you know how easily scared I
am best bring the
back on the ah am is not
racing I'm sorry to disappoint you if
you thought she was
[Music]
racing yeah I'm so jumpy what am I going
to do I'm going to mute myself they
won't be able to talk to
me why is she in the thumbnail well I
don't know
because she's cute it's nice to have her
on the
[Music]
thumbnail
amoko isn't everybody on the
thumbnail and not everybody is
participating
she's killed yeah she's there in
spirit sh only isn't
out Sho wait what thumnail let me
[Music]
see
um there it is
okay I have no explanation for
that is everybody else there except
shoting I have no explanation for that I
mean maybe I do but I don't uh I I I
thought I had but I really don't
huh I don't think they
forgot okay now question can I play
online is there anything bad about
playing online anything dangerous or so
I want to play with you
guys is this
[Music]
possible I might lose of course I will
lose you might do even first
I want to play with you guys
specifically not with
randos actually no never mind yeah you
guys are going to just crash into me on
purpose are
you they might overlap and then block
you what is do they bully do like randos
Bully the newcomers when they see that
somebody's like really really bad and
really slow and once they lap them
they're going to like block them they do
holy holy [\h__\h] The Hazing The
Bullying
rude because it's fun it's not fun
that's not
fun oh they they wouldn't even know that
they're bullying this cute anime girl
and being caught in
4k very
toxic okay I don't know this speaks to
me cuz I like this blue and this red
this is really pretty let's go Paul
Paul Paul
rard
buet we
we
um how do I change that
to uh would you like to drive with me
tonight
anybody who can speak French in the
chat quick
quick how do I pronounce
that hey let's go
[Music]
whoa whoa whoa what is this track holy
[\h__\h] wa but the colors are so pretty and
there's mountains
he France is not this supp pointing me
tonight
sis we
weam
magn oh my God this is very
confusing so many
curves but then fourth
baby
unbelievable stay behind me suckers
I'm going maximum
gas oh beautiful straight
line let's go happy birthday by the way
[Music]
BR the right on the
right oh didn't have to break that hard
huh on the
right on the right holy [\h__\h] I'm
decent on the right clear on the right
shut
up the voice is in my
head a [\h__\h] hell that curve is
mean on the left
all clear oh [\h__\h] you guys they're
blocking me on the left yeah go back
where you came
from [\h__\h] have to go full stop
almost I took him out yeah bastard
bastard I'm passing you
now don't even try to pass me
yeah
oh I like this track this might be my
favorite so far even though it has some
weird ass
curves I'm still
seventh yo I hope they're going to
choose this track
although might be more chaotic with all
the other girls yeah oh [\h__\h] yeah that
might have that might have taken me out
now no I'll have a full
comeback hey don't push
me oh this the lines are so pretty why
is this so pretty it's like a constant
baby gender
reveal right now it's a baby boy why are
you guys so fast what's wrong with me
left on the left a maybe I should stay
on the line cuz they tend to stay on
that line and then I'm blocking
them hey hey hey hey hey
Rouge let's just generally try to see if
I can at all stay on the line [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] f f f f f [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] ah
no CCH up catch up catch up do I have a
chance of catching up only if these
[\h__\h] make a mistake man I wish these
CPUs would make more
mistakes but they're programmed too well
don't worry our Holan girls will make
more human errors
hopefully they're not computers
thankfully okay okay managed to do a
pretty good sharp
turn Ena was watching footage of
Pros how did that help
her I guess like even in Mario Kart when
she was practicing for Mario Kart she
got pretty pretty sweaty and was like
doing all these like ghost uh ooh [\h__\h]
the ghost races trying to beat
yourself you know from the
past so I guess that's kind of
similar can you do ghost races in this
game surely you can
right yeah you know is quite the sweaty
racer
wow wait I'm last
no but it took a while for me to get
last I feel like I'm about to take off
into space with this speed
I'm so happy you're playing this Mario's
entire family [\h__\h]
you wait why are you happy about this
you should be sad because I'm not
playing Mario
Kart and why are you even showing your
face here again I hate
you just kidding you're welcome
but but I hate you I hate you and your
whole
[Music]
family especially
now that account is like so
old you used to troll me back in the day
when I played the Super Mario
64 but uh now it's even more relevant
because of all the
Luigi [\h__\h] that I have to
take times are even worse now I don't
only hate Mario I hate Luigi too now but
especially actually like it's not even
so much Luigi I I kind
of what's the word I put my hate
from toad onto Luigi which
is not so nice I guess I pro project I
project my toad hate onto Luigi and
generally I love toad but in Luigi's
Mansion 2o toad is
the just do
stupidest
being ever to
exist
yeah that's that's how it
is not wrong yeah I know can't blame me
for that yeah right like toad wasn't so
bad in the other Luigi Mansion games it
really was mostly that one
okay I'm I'm going in the straightest
line I could ever go in
[Music]
beautiful
beautiful slowly slowing down a little
bit how much is that enough yeah yeah
yeah I got it all under control
oh oh yeah see I got it I got that m m
schuma
Jean I just had to wake it up it was
like somewhere in my body
hidden oh
[\h__\h] okay we're almost there at the
Finishing Line
yppe wow that that curve I think got me
every single time
now but besides that I like this
track come on E what what that that was
not finish what what I thought we were
done uh I was mentally done with it I I
can tell you that oh God
H oopsy last lap oh my
[Music]
God [\h__\h] I don't even care anymore as
you can
tell I don't care
anymore I'm I'm fine I I don't need to
practice this
anymore seen enough of
it you hate this truck
why it's my favorite so
far CU of the colors and the scenery and
the
driveability feels
good this straight line feels especially
good
oo could have done that faster even
maybe oh I'm so sad I can't play with
the wheel like this I wish I I wish I
had the skill
one day
guys ah damn
it close
[Music]
enough oh the red thing up there is
telling me I'm slower than in my last
lap by one
almost 2
seconds oh that's not even such a big
difference that's pretty stable
though I see now I'm
faster that changed
quickly how much longer how we dare yet
fin leader finished the race bro what
I'm going to get laughed again am I
not oh God oh God oh God oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] that curb again
[Music]
again was a good run I
know feels
good oh there's five fireworks in the
back what just one tiny one though sorry
you can't see it you probably miss it a
there there there you see top right
fireworks up there well now now you
can't see
it
Satia hey what's up Satia to
you did you guys see there was this
really cute um kfp Fe Cafe fan-made
Cafe for like I think one day only in
the
Philippines so cute and then oh my
god um did you see this all happened on
the same day I think I saw that a
certain cosplayer
who I've been well I wouldn't say like a
big fan or so but I I definitely admired
her work in the past a long time ago
already
um actually I don't know if she
pronounces her name like John or Jean
one
one actually don't know never heard it
said out
loud um but she's so
hot and so pretty and so cute and so
fit and a couple days ago like a week or
more she and her friends did uh a
cosplay group of Ki CI and Nissa I think
it was they cosplayed us together and
then let's let's get out of
here and at that time I think uh Jean
Jean John she was doing
Cali and another girl was doing Ki and
she was also really hot she had a lot of
um a lot of tattoos they looked really
cool
yeah but
now
now Jean John she also did me and ah all
these hot ladies are cosplaying me I'm
so
happy everybody's looking so
cute and I'm just thinking to myself
wow like if I told
myself
from over four years ago that all these
amazing ladies like
Han or
Ellie you guys know Ellie e l y she
cosplayed me too she's so
famous and genan one1 if I knew that all
these beautiful amazing cosplay ladies
would cosplay me one day I would be
like why would they do that that
what
what and coefficient
nah coefficient doesn't
count no that's so cool cuz I I've
always had an eye on cosplay
ladies and I was already aware of all of
these ladies before whole
alive and seeing
them dress up as me is such a great
honor and it really means a lot to me
the cosplay
Community I
really like what they
do and I know I know a lot of
people a lot of pretty ladies I mean
I've I I I I want to meet them all I've
met I've had the pleasure to meet Han
but I haven't met a lot of the other
beautiful ladies I hope I can meet all
of them one day that' be so cool
I'm gay keeping
again
yeah I'm so glad too that like I see I
see so many pretty
ladies um cosplaying me nowadays um I
feel like it's been more now in the
later years than uh early on in the
first year remember when I'm met for
like like this cosplay picture where it
was like four out of five of my she
placed herself in that picture to make
sure that somebody's cosplaying me there
there really weren't too many kiata
cosplayers back
then but nowadays there's really quite a
few and even when I bring out new
outfits like even the fever Knight out
this outfit already even even the
freaking alternative color has a
cosplay I think one one cosplayer or two
[Music]
maybe
yeah Gaye keeping has paid off
girls I've gathered all the all the
pretty pretty
cosplayers so many
beautiful W cos blares I can make an
army of wava cos
blares yeah the short skirt so I think
they Shar the cosplay those two because
um the skirt had like these really
particular special Ruffles on the bottom
that I thought were so
adorable and they both had it so I think
they shared a cosplay or so
yeah I think it also is because like f
night outfit and my casual outfit were
um well relatively especially the Casual
my casual outfit was is pretty easy to
do and comfortable to wear and not just
like at home but also at conventions
very comfortable and convenient and and
not like you know you don't have to
worry too much about
you know covering up too much if you're
if that's something you know there's a
lot of people who maybe want to
crossplay certain things but I don't
feel too confident about cosplaying it
because it shows too much skin or so
well my casual outfit shows a decent
amount of skin but like not it it looks
like a normal outfit so you know it's
easier to
wear yeah yeah yeah yeah even my dandle
I think the dle is only difficult
because of the pattern of the dress the
flower
pattern so it's not so easy to make it
yourself
yeah but I'm so happy to see it I would
love to see more more and more and more
W
[Music]
cosplayers so happy to see
cosplayers it's like one of my favorite
parts of um being a member of whole life
and being a part of this community one
of my favorite things about it is that
people cosplay me and I can see their
cosplays of
me it's such an honor really that people
you know even make it themselves or or
spend money to get a cosplay and then
dress up as me and just walk around as
me it's a big honor to me I feel very
flattered yeah Tas
my sister crosss with your worldour
outfit did I see it maybe did she upload
a
picture on Twitter I hope everybody
always makes sure to upload pictures on
Twitter if they cplay me because
otherwise chances of me seeing it are
very low very high if you do upload it
and tag it also I've been seeing so many
like cute Japanese cosplayers
too feel like I've been getting more
here and there
love
him H maybe I already saw
it but yeah very happy I think um for
today that's enough uh it's like it's
been two 2 hours 50 what the hell I
think that's enough racing I'm kind of
getting tired of it now I'll practice
more tomorrow on my
own um
yeah not bad shum thank you good
practice yeah I tried with the
wheel but for the tournament I'll go
with the controller it was a good
experience fun experience though um but
I can't get sweaty with the wheel for
now but I'll definitely do a Euro Truck
Simulator stream sometime
soon with the wheel getting more action
again yeah the pedal move a bunch
definitely didn't help yeah very very
bothersome but yeah my throat also kind
of hurts a little bit so I'm going to go
to Super Chat reading oh you thought I
was going to say I'm not going to read
super chats didn't
you now I'm going to
read and I'm looking
for looking for fro
candies he thought I was going to say oh
no no no I just need a fruit
candy it
hurts it's getting really dry
already and I think from yesterday my
fro is still a little bit
sensitive we're going to close the game
and turn on some bgm thank you you're so
sweet
such a
sweetheart okay what kind of music are
we looking
[Music]
for audio
St thank
you oh hey this is kind of this could
this could have been a good racing music
[Music]
wait now I want to play a short round
with that
bgm wait I'm opening up the game
again I want to play a short round like
I don't knowm it's just audio stock
tracks it doesn't even have a
name but you know what I'll stay quiet
and you can just listen to
it and replay the section if you want to
hear the song
again I just want to completely quietly
with that
music uh do uh a track but wait how do I
change
the rounds again here race length 5
minutes I did not I in fact did not
confirm last
time okay
okay okay
okay I wouldn't even call this Euro beat
but it's like kind of EDM EUR beat I
don't know
[Music]
C
how am I still
first what's happening
uhoh
right
oh oh
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] right
[Music]
the the
left left
left ha
[Music]
C on the [\h__\h] what the the hell someone
pushed me
[Music]
[Applause]
[\h__\h]
you no [\h__\h]
you what did I do wrong otherwi just
going
straight f f f f f f [\h__\h] [\h__\h] fu [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I did that better before okay
the first half of the this race was a
lot
better let me in let me
in my
BFF I think once you're like more in the
back it's really hard to recover because
that just means to messed
up and yeah it will be hard to get back
to where you
were so you really got to just make sure
you make no
mistakes no no no no no no no no no get
off of me ugly ugly green
car sorry no literally not my fault I'm
sorry green car's fault
I did not intend to crash into
you but they
still penalize me don't
they okay
[Music]
no okay as long as I get a placement
that'll be the first time in my
[Music]
life let's lock it oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] hard to right H okay then I shall
go right oo okay oh
[Music]
God wa
sexy oh [\h__\h] oh oh sexy
golden car you will not pass me you
shall not
pass Over My Dead [\h__\h]
body uhoh
no well I'm a phoenix it's okay no no no
I want I want to be over 25
please wait I did wait I did it
oh oh I [\h__\h] did it that's the first
time that's the first
time
yo the music
helped oh the power of music all right I
think that is a that's definitely Pro
is that's
progress
Improvement time to grind off stream
yeah tomorrow I'll have the whole day
basically for grinding off
[Music]
stream oh my neck hurts so much
man okay where shall we go let's go to a
fever night room cuz I am looking like
these Fever
[Music]
Night what's up chat come on where are
you there you
are come on there
you don't be so
shy oh you're broken this
hell then let me pick you up in a
different
form from
[Music]
here well this was a very unusual stream
for
me besides Mario Kart I have never done
a stream like this before in terms of
this
genre
so I really hope you had a good time
even though I don't know I don't know
how entertaining that can really
be but maybe for the race game
otakus that was a
blessing ah yeah I got better
so I
think we're obviously not going to win
but we have a good chance at not being
last maybe oh that'll be so sad that
will age badly if I do get
last it's okay it'll be fun it'll be fun
I'll just try to be really focused and
locked in and listen to music while I
play during the tournament we we will
turn on
music thank you for the memberships
yay don't look at chat yeah I won't I'll
try to not look at chat during the
actual races I think the races itself
are going to be 15 minutes long
though I think that's one thing that
they said which I feel like with how
hard it is to go back to the front when
you fall
behind I mean I guess more the longer it
is the more chances are for the others
to also make more mistakes later on but
I feel like the ones who will be leading
will probably stay
leading
generally and the the Gap will just grow
bigger and bigger when it's that
long well let's hope that even if the
leaders keep on leading let's hope that
everybody below the leaders is more
unstable
and uh
unpredictable let's hope it's
unpredictable like the Mario party we
played
yesterday it's never too late to blunder
I hope so I would hope so I want to see
more blunders i h
yeah you never know you never know pit
stops might be a thing if that's the
case oh yeah yeah yeah with 15 minutes
surely there'll be pit
stops I got to practice longer games
than tomorrow where pit stops are a
[Music]
thing huh not for p oh really you think
15 minutes is still too too short I
guess
so oh okay well thank God I feel like I
would get lost I'll would be like where
the [\h__\h] is the pit stop can't find
it okay uh will somebody tell me where I
have to continue reading super chats
thank
[Music]
you did I stop somewhere randomly last
time what the hell is that stream Arctic
eggs what is that what game is
that hold a talk oh I'm it
oh hopefully there's not too many super
Chads H making eggs in the ice you cook
eggs
interesting sounds cursed a little bit
but maybe it's
wholesome where is the am H talk there
it is
okay it's not that little it's not that
[Music]
little there you
go it's not wholesome oh okay but this
holot talk was
wholesome should it
[Music]
all right here we go oh you know the
other day like two days ago or so think
on my day off I stumbled into coron
senpai's stream where she was just
chatting with an AI that had a cute
voice Japanese AI it was so funny I was
like what the [\h__\h] is wrong with this AI
that was so funny because it's very
different from like how chat GPT would
for example answer questions and
interact it was also very different from
uh neuro neuros
Sumer uh I was like oh my God this is
the the most unhinged conversation I
ever heard between a person and an AI
that's so
[Music]
funny like K Senpai would ask the AI to
sing something and um then it would the
AI would be like they kept on
interrupting each other but the AI would
be like oh okay did you like it and Kun
is like eh you didn't sing anything but
then the AI would insist on it like oh
did did you like it it's just like ah
yeah yeah it was really good just
pretending cuz the uh then the joke was
like oh maybe maybe the AI is doing that
for copyright protection to not [\h__\h]
over Kon Empire with copyright problems
but yeah there was a lot of gaslighting
going
[Music]
on and then they kept on doing monoman
like impersonations and stuff was really
funny I watched quite a bit and then I
told K Senai that was so funny I liked
it
I rarely get time to watch other streams
but I just stumbled into it when it was
live and it was really
[Music]
entertaining if there is an English
version that is that good at being
funny I'd love to do another AI
conversation
stream but I had my fair share of it a
little bit remember a long time ago I
did I did two AI streams basically one
where neuros Sama was basically feeding
me to savings and you guys I was
checking to see how long it would take
you guys to figure out that everything I
was saying was being controlled by nurus
Sama yeah it was I think it was like a
question and answer stream from like me
reading questions from the
chat but um
I think it was noticeable very soon that
it was kind of weird um something weird
was going on and then we did the
fridge
[Music]
review that's a long time
ago so weird I felt so nervous during
that
n is so improved nowadays really she's
so different from back then really I saw
one clip like
maybe three weeks or so
ago but uh of evil neuros Sama I
think specifically evil n when when she
collabed with a a IRL like flesh
tuber uh who was
cooking I
think and was I think forcing her to do
[Music]
things uh yeah no not gidy I think it
was not gidy yeah maybe
Lena
mhm yeah but besides that I haven't seen
much these
[Music]
days but that one was funny that clip
was
funny I'm tired I didn't take a nap
today it's kind of crazy
[Music]
what Nome has an only fans
what what what even is on
there I guess like yeah I could imagine
I
guess can I say
something this month is already almost
over
[Music]
um next
month something exciting is coming
[Music]
up something that has been in the works
for a while
now is going to come up come up next uh
month ear it's going to
be happening early in the next month so
I'm I'm personally very excited for it
so I would like you to be also excited
for
it no not
go but I don't know if that will still
happen then it will probably still take
some time cuz right now there's no
communication going
on but I'm not giving up yet it could
still
happen
3.0 well no but um I guess because CI
already has her 3.0 reservation up I
guess I can also
say um I was surprised by mine also
already being
ready but I'm still going to request
maybe
one change or so
possibly but I'll probably reveal it
quite soon as well mhm mhm
mhm then what was the point um because
they can't make 3.0 without making 2.0
first and all future outfits will be
built with 2.0 not with 3.0 so they need
it as a
base cuz it always functions as a
[Music]
base now was faster than expected I
thought it would take a while longer for
3.0 to follow up on the
2.0 why not build off of 3 because 3.0
is very intricate it has like all kinds
of stuff like the keyboard and the
controller and like waving motions and
stuff that's like yeah that's not going
to be the base for everything cuz that's
too much work for
them yeah but it has a lot of
interesting
stuff um
um I mean I wish I could have it on a on
a different outfit that I use more often
but it's still pretty cool I'm actually
kind of excited about
it yeah for now it's just on the default
outfit yeah which is fine free hats no
no no no or
unless we'll
see we'll see
you know what's weird like
recently
um
staff asked
me and I just feel weird about it uh so
okay on on different occasions in the
past two weeks or so one time I feel
like they're asking for different
reasons but HMA asked
me but I think HMA is just generally
curious about like techn stuff and so on
HMA asked me how I did my fever Knight
3D
stream like what app I used and what um
what accents like version
Etc I was like oh I glad I tell you but
then two days ago management like from a
deeper within Japanese management you
know some department they were like
asking my manager to ask
me what what app or so what's what what
I use to do that stream and I'm like why
are they asking me
now are you asking to improve our
software or are you asking to tell
others other members or are you asking
to Bonk me or are you what are what is
the I'm confused what is the purpose cuz
they didn't really say why they're
asking it yeah so say I asked me in
person about it when we were in New
York she was just asking me in person
cuz she wanted to not about the software
but about the the hardware
basically yeah now maybe they were
asking on a talent's behalf I I could
imagine but I'd like them to tell me
that feels weird when you know I put all
my all my effort into figuring out these
things on my own because it just doesn't
work with our own app so I I figure out
how to uh use other apps how to operate
them and everything cuz it's kind of
complicated and so on and now they want
to know all the details from
[Applause]
Me Without Really explaining why they
want to know well I did share in the end
but I'm hoping that they will use that
information to improve our own software
perhaps consultation
fee yeah transend once
again get a new 3D outfit as a payment
Ah that's not going to
work I guess they must have been really
impressed by my fever night stream that
was quite the impressive stream after
all me twerking endlessly
imagine freaking management watching
that stream and being like H this is
very distracting but uh um I wonder how
she did
this trying to figure out what's going
on while I'm shaking my ass shake that
ass for me shake that ass for me
[Laughter]
say two really good
points no I'm I'm embarrassed stop
watching why is everybody watching that
stream stop I was just messing
around you know why what
yeah because just because the tech is
so
impressive
right it made me think like oh I wonder
if am used to always get asked by staff
how did you do this how did you do that
how can you teach us can you tell us how
did you do this and now am is gone and
I'm I'm not even doing half as amazing
things as am used to do but now I'm
getting asked how did you do this how
did you do
that share your knowledge with
us am I the tech girl
now but I'm not even I'm I suck with
tech I suck with tech but when it comes
to xense I'm like the only one who has
been I I'm not the only owner anymore I
don't know if you guys heard from some
other member but I'm still the only one
who's actively using it I know that the
there's another owner but uh she has yet
to use
it I think as far as I know she has yet
it um but yeah I guess I'm the most
knowledgeable about it now and now a few
people want to get it so I wonder if I'm
going to be like the tech support for
it but I don't even know what I'm doing
most of the time like I'm still troubl
although I mean I've been quite happy
with my map for it recently like it's
been getting smoother I don't know why
but the results of my labor have been
getting the fruits of my labor have been
getting more and more smoother
looking even without too much brush
up
yeah so that's a big relief
um but yeah please hold uh the The
Mirage Milestones will all you know take
a little while now it's moving a lot
faster than I thought we're almost at
750k uh and I I still need
to finish up the 700k reward so please
wait but I literally I just released
today not even 24 hours ago I released
the modding short so it's not like I'm
it's not like you don't have enough to
watch it's just uh it's all happening
too fast I want each short and each
video to have a bit more time to grow on
its own before I slap another one on top
of it um so I think we're all fine with
giving it a bit more um attention
span
right I don't want them to you know
immediately be topped with a different
short and then go go into being
forgotten stream less Mirage no no the
faster we reach it the
[Music]
better
yeah I do want to say by the way um I
said before that like uh reaching
like good
numbers in terms of streaming numbers
will translate into bigger budgets for
future songs um but reaching 1 million
on YouTube doesn't really do
anything um it's just
like yeah it's not like a milestone I
have to hit it's just uh I mean
automatically that means that it's been
streamed a lot the more the Maria uh
even with it reach 1 million there's a
high chance
that
[Music]
the how to
say that I I might still be in the minus
in terms of
production um but it's just yeah it's a
I just you know it's a milestone to work
towards that makes a lot of
sense um yeah
[Music]
the more the Maria the more streams the
better the budget in the
future uh Spotify more important H I
don't know honestly I don't know because
I think YouTube music video streams
count to YouTube music don't
they I think they probably do so it's
like
whatever either either platform any
platform is
fine mhm mhm MH mhm
thank you for streaming Mirage thank you
thank you thank you I appreciate
it okay let's read some super
chats so that my throat doesn't
die but yeah I wanted to say thank you
for all the support so far Mirage has
been doing so well I'm I'm a proud mommy
of my baby my baby Mirage
me you spinning little eyes new disgu on
and on
and me I'm lost and the videos have been
so cute right I've been uploading them
to Tik Tok too if anybody here hasn't
known yet I made myself a Tik Tok
account and I know I know I know I'm not
really I don't know I don't like Tik Tok
in particular either but who knows you
know if I get it running for a while
maybe I'll get lucky um and the Zoomers
notice my music sometime
um yeah I just thought I should get a
presentence on there if I'm focusing so
much on music I should at least have a
presentence so I've been just uploading
the same shorts
basically um if you have a Tik Tok
account please follow
me thank you it's taka
nashik H I don't know I follow two
people I have three videos up try to
find
me h
thank
[Music]
you I know that didn't I saw
that
uh but it's uh kind of weird because so
I don't really I didn't even watch the
original video but I saw that like her
meme was featured on Japanese TV but
they didn't credit her they
showed like a lot of other people
dancing to her audio and doing the my M
dance they showed like 20 videos but
they didn't show or mention their
original which is I guess what
happens sometimes sadly when you get
some meme going on Tik Tok and people
just don't even know anymore where the
source is from
H yeah I don't know how rden feels about
it but in the end I'm I'm still sure
that she got a lot of Tik Tok followers
from that
anyway same thing happened with subu
yeah it's a little bit inevitable but I
would hope that you know at least like a
TV station would do some research I
don't
know like can't expect that from like
YouTube compilations or whatever but I
don't
[Music]
know that gave a very diplomatic answer
says it doesn't bother her but I'm sure
it does well I mean I mean you know
surely in some way she's still like
benefits from it being viral like some
views are still coming back to her I'm
sure from it being viral one way or
another some followers and viewers are
being gained for sure so you know yeah
but now I guess it's like out of control
and then well but it's still
[Music]
exposure it'll trickle down
yeah did she did she get a lot of new
Subs on YouTube really that's good
because usually that this kind of stuff
I guess it stays a lot on Tik Tok and it
doesn't trickle down onto other social
media she did oh I don't
know good for her let's go
120k
what she got 120k subscribers from
[Music]
that
wao all right guys you got to you got to
help me get viral on Tik Tok
[Music]
je
how
how L and Mirage Dance One how many
followers does she have on Tik
Tok start gooing
girl yeah maybe I'll make a m m
video bro well well well we got to help
each other out we're
company of
conics we work
together no I didn't even know but I was
already thinking about well maybe I can
you know I don't know what what else I'm
going to do besides these Mirage videos
once I'm done with the Mirage videos
maybe I'll make a my Tu my Tu
video brain rot I also like this o e e
but I only know it from
L and now I've been seeing some la uh
videos with
the I don't even know what the [\h__\h] is
this meme
but it was funny when NAA was doing it
and the cat is so
[Music]
cute cat brain rot I want to see some
can somebody make that with smoothie and
chunky wonky like draw CH not me into a
cat put my cats into a
cat any artist in the chat who want to
who wants to try that yeah let me try to
recreate it in the in the proper
[Music]
timing let's see if we can find
the o e
e how do I even how do I even what's the
proper what what do I type in nothing
comes up uh
o e i e
sping cat okay let me mute
this this is not the louder
version Oh [\h__\h] this is like some kind
of EDM remix is this so
OG
sh oh
oh oh
[\h__\h] I can't do it that hard oh [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] okay let's do just the
[Music]
beginning okay starts fast then it goes
slow and then then the and then the base
hits really hard
yeah okay here we go hoping that
somebody will make chunky wonky and
smoovie version that will be my brain
Rod
forever oh it just start so suddenly
wait let me Loop
this o e i e o e i e o e i e e i e oh
[\h__\h] I didn't even have to go that
hard I wish you guys could hear the
base let me try again one more
time too fast yeah that's how it goes in
that video let me try the let me find
the
l l o e i
I don't know how to write
it how do I find it maybe can somebody
link an example to me on
Twitter have I still not read a Super
Chat by the
way spinning louder
[Music]
I saw like so many versions already of L
us oh this one
maybe she starts
slow okay here we go three two
one oh wait no three two 1
o e i e e
[Music]
i that's how she go goes the same
speed okay one more time one more time
[Music]
I'm just freestyling at that
point sounds
legit you good no no you good uh I have
an answer for
you e e
e e e e e e
[Laughter]
you know you can just do it once and the
artist will mix it well yeah but I mean
it's
doable I at least got to do the the
first couple of loops on my own when it
speeds up
[Music]
that was that freestyle I didn't listen
to the original
Rhythm started pretty
slow please
somebody chunky wonky movie version
please I would die for
it your cat is
scared weak skill issue your cat is too
weak oh
oh
oh oh this one's
[Music]
cute let's read super
chats pudding pudding pudding explain to
me how come I see more nexit G uh Clips
nowadays in Pudding Clips
ah have we gone back in time are we back
in year number
one sorry for the roast I don't want to
pressure
you I'm
sorry you are secretly I mean that would
would that explain a lot actually no not
really but that would EXP explain why at
some point you were both
slacking but yeah actually I see I might
even maybe not right now but maybe there
was like one month where I saw more LC
Lin clips than anybody else's even
though Elsie Lin is more like a Cali
[Music]
Clipper you guys are taking shifts
you're taking turns
I'm just going to unsub and Report the
stream and cow
carrot what happened with cow carrot cow
carrot kind of sleeping but it's okay
cow carrot can take a break cow carrot
deserves a
break unlike you
pudding had enough of a break now
haven't you he moved to the UK c c that
would be so cute if you guys had a
a living Arrangement that would be so
cute but I would feel bad for cow
carrot poor cow carot does he need to be
[Music]
saved Clipper house yeah imagine a
Clipper
[Music]
house no yeah oh you're starting to
stream at reasonable hours so I can clip
you more what do you mean starting you
mean returning right okay thank you I'm
awaiting the o e
i I mean you don't you don't have to do
the o e i but um what what else could
you do I don't know what's clippable
right
now Super Mario party but wait you did
the clip anyway that clip was funny I
sent it to uh wait no wait was it your
clip or was that someone else's clip see
I'm getting confused
now who who clipped
what damn right it was the giggy one
yeah the one where it kind of gets like
emotional yeah the one where I jumped on
her with the sandwich yeah yeah I sent
it to gigy and I was like I'm so sorry I
didn't even realize
G is so funny she's so
funny and I told
her something yesterday that I wanted to
tell her for a
[Music]
while I told
her that I I really love seeing her
fing right now really proud to see my co
high thve but it's so nice to see her
like being liked and accepted and
welcomed by everybody I think everybody
has a good time collabing with her cuz
she's really easy to talk to and she
fills awkward
silences and she fills it with good
comebacks and she fills it with good
funny jokes and stuff it's just like
really easy to collab with her and yeah
told her I love her Antics and her jokes
and she's a great addition I I'm I love
her love to see her
thve orange power let's
[Music]
go
yeah and then I said I'm
excited for the future when like she
gets to stand on stage in fre
too and then we're going to have orange
pen lights even more now cuz until now
it was only me at Ian concerts but now
with her there'll be more
orange yeah and then she said can't wait
to look out into the sea of orange
together
[Music]
yay orange beautiful color that deserves
more
[Music]
love orange women
yay I hope she behaves so that I so that
I don't have to un orange her
again that'd be such a shame I'd be
alone again in the orange
[Music]
World Tyrant
chw all right guys I shall now finally
read super
chats Jacob 47 D le Dan take Monkey D D
Magista D and now we have a rainbow from
mapin eight
than oh oh yeah yeah I'm doing it wow
well T you my first rainbow was back
during the amator off collab you did
while visiting her studio for the first
time oh and now I will deliver never
I've been an amator fan since the
beginning and I'll never stop being
one than thank you I'm also an amaton
fan what a coincidence your collabs of
Amma and even just the stories of off
stream stuff have always been my
favorite content in all of whole life
thank you now tentu you know how am is
so please continue to keep in touch with
her and visit when you can H why does it
always have to be me she promised to
visit me maybe you can even do the males
with her one year or invite her to Japan
oh I think males is very
unlikely and since this is probably the
last time I can say this you still need
to take her IE skating it's not the last
time you can say it but if she visits
Austria I can take R skating especially
in the winter but I guess it doesn't
have to be
winter of course this is your channel so
I can tell you what that I will continue
to stick with you until the end even
though I know it will hurt when the day
comes thank you for doing this whole t
with Amma and thank you for everything
you did with her and told us about I'm
forever thank you you so much thank you
thank you appreciate it I did always
enjoy spending time with her when I
could
um you know during the projects that we
worked on together and I will forever be
grateful for how she helped me with the
things I wanted to do in terms of 3D
even though it was always quite
difficult and like stressful for both of
us I think
cuz things just didn't go our way a lot
of the
time
yeah but the end results were always fun
and yeah
entertaining and something to be proud
of and and it's really nice to look back
on what we did together
so yeah I'll I'll never forget her
contributions and
I'll never
[Music]
never not be grateful for it she really
helped a
lot yeah so I think all of kfp will
forever be grateful for
that and she didn't only help me she
helped like the whole company honestly
with
her um what's the
[Music]
word what's the word
again innovative
[Music]
ideas like using
certain uh home 3D solutions that were
not on the radar of the company at the
time but ended up being used by
everybody on the I
[Music]
inside yeah I think she really put it on
the radar too not just VR no no no VR
too though yeah but I'm talking about
home
3D
without all the solutions she was trying
to find to make it possible for us to
have a frd debut at home which we didn't
do in the end but you know that's what
kind of brought all of that stuff up
about that I don't know if uh home Frey
would have been such a big thing so
early on at
least would have would have taken
longer and it might have just been stuff
like m later on but yeah we had quite a
few different things on our
radar yeah
so
yeah things would have been very
different without Amy very
different who knows if we would have
ever done anything in the VR world like
that maybe we would have played a VR
game but I don't think we would have had
like our VR worlds and VR models at all
oh I don't think we would have done any
of that if it wasn't
for which if you think about it that
would have been kind of sad and
lonely it definitely
enriched uh the experience in those
especially in those first
years yeah so thank you
Ma for supporting us and I think you can
continue supporting us anyway yeah
no need to stop thank you Kenny stamps
D the paladins announ Flappy Boy Thanks
for the red super chat previously on
holot talk
many JP some special VIPs one and TI Jen
am is toally getting the Royal honor
treatment here as she freaking deserves
may I add a precious parting gift from a
true friend thank you I do want to say
um I was going to do as you know I was
going to Doan and ID interviews at some
point anyway this just kind of sped it
up a little bit um but if I in the
future announce on my schedule or so uh
another Hol talk with a Ian or ID member
or
so don't please don't automatically go
into thinking oh my go just going to
graduate no no no no don't panic please
now that I started with am um um it
might be more likely for uh an member
another Ian member interview to pop up
uh in the near future because I already
started the series so to say so just
because another one might happen doesn't
mean anything okay this one just like it
was always bound to happen but it just
happened ear earlier than I thought and
now I got the ball rolling
so you know might as well
continue with some more Ian uh
interviews cuz at this point myth has
been around for over four years you know
that's a
[Music]
lot yep yep
yep and same with uh ID first gen any
updates on ground there's no rush we're
not rushing with that I just said that
we we want to do that but I wasn't
saying that it's going to be like next
week week or so it might not even be
next
month I just suggested it to the girls
and they were like yeah let's do it but
it's not like let's do it immediately no
no
[Music]
no anyway let's continue FL boy thank
you so much Rogan Striker danan best
girl danan Mr D M arcade
dun d flamable d Amelia simp d so Tom D
edf5 fencer thank you for the red chat
thank you EDF
EDF SP time thank you for the red super
chat as well okay I probably said this
at least 34 times already but best whole
talk ever oh was that already at the end
no not really was it no was
it love am all of them love you all of
am you mean love m m forever thank you
no I do think that was a pretty good
episode um cuz I was able
to because I also know Amma pretty well
as her gen mate I think I was able
to talk
about uh a lot of good topics and so on
and I I I knew am and I was able to show
off all the different am I really like
the am bir it's just like am for am
there's a lot of things to talk
about she is a very
interesting person who you know created
and achieved so many things in in her
time so that's very helpful for all talk
for coming up with
[Music]
questions
tasu f binghe f Nathan cotton thanks for
the red chat hey yo Kmart shout out
let's go Kmart shout
out Kmart was there Kmart shout out was
there
[Music]
wait did I'm a mention
Kmart ah yeah
yeah
[Music]
MH and when it was between Walmart and
Target she just said she preferred
Kmart I don't even know
Kart
interesting is that uh does that stand
for Korea like does it have Korean food
or is what is that is dead
no no it doesn't stand for Korea oh I
don't know could have been a Asian food
store k m
[Music]
a too bad it's dead
now thank you naan for the support
steping earlier spere D and I agree TK
thank you very much D love the
amerse sky dun as like zombie dun not an
English speaker dun
uh KY stamp D AK s TF2 d027 D J 47 D RT
Ronin D random CL thanks for the red
chat thank you so much talking like this
and reminiscing gives my heart some
peace thank you I agree it was nice
reminiscing and trying to
honor her
[Music]
Legacy thank you for listening in and
supporting all of us thank you random
collusion hope I hope you're feeling at
peace now too TV table tree d v faction
d i St I Steve
D
GD
memoryi Mayo musician mango D Cruise D
Vol voltage D earliest for d
d d Jim Tracy D Cruz red D the one in
the background D
Manu
T whoops myad
Moon space thanks for the
pinky Maj sounds very nostalgic you
haven't sent super chat in a while have
you space full sent pinky say thank you
so much for this special hotel Amy and
wa really
interesting knew some things but a lot I
didn't know am is truly amazing since
day one mhm integral part of not just
myth but all of whole life there's no
one like
am yeah I
think like it's it's it doesn't even
feel like she left yet
because it just feels like
I don't know it just feels like
normal there's not too much evidence yet
that she's so to say gone because even
collabs like she wasn't always in every
collab
anyway I don't know
maybe maybe it won't really hit until
like the next big concert or so
[Music]
yeah and I mean maybe I surely it hits
it hits more for like I'm a
fans but in my case I usually wasn't
even awake to catch her streams most of
the
time so for me as a colleague it still
feels like she's just you know nothing
changed so that's maybe also why I can
go about my days
again pretty
normally it doesn't feel different right
now
[Music]
yet
yeah it was pretty real to me when they
was coming up and when on the on the day
the D
day but then after that it was like
hm maybe it was a
dream maybe it was all just a
dream
[Music]
right maybe it
was perhaps it was a
dream I'm fine with it being a dream
[Music]
I don't know guys about myth collabs
um I
definitely not going to initiate the
myth Club anytime
soon because the first time that we'll
do a myth clab with just four
people it will just feel so wrong so I
think we will all avid avoid it for as
long as we
can I am not going to NOP mm
nope we'll just never collab again
[Music]
ever not as four maybe as three or two
but not as
four because four will always just feel
wrong now
man can't get over
that like you know first
hurdle it's too
[Music]
difficult sorry for the jump
scare sound for have an acrylic
stand no
no no no we will not rip off the
Band-Aid it's impossible I will keep on
on the Band-Aid
forever no no no no no it will stay on
but that's really how it feels ripping
off a
Band-Aid all right super chats from
Fallout part
six
pyes d
yeah uh Justin
lber thank you
again
M Nathan coton thank you for
rainbow yo oh [\h__\h] it was your
birthday I'm sorry I'm so late I'm 1
month
late Nathan cotton says hi atten just
like last year was my birthday yesterday
the big fie and it made me realize that
I've spent a good 10% of my life
watching my
Koshi
10% but is that 10 no it's 10
[Music]
years oh
oops I was going to point out that that
just doesn't work I haven't been around
for 10
years MTH was hard
well I would change a lot I wouldn't
trade watching the bird that got me into
YouTubers for anything although maybe I
should make my all September super chats
a tradition what maybe I shouldn't make
my all September super chats a
tradition all September it's getting a
little expensive to have my own yearly
birthday at this point oh I'm looking
forward to getting a chance to see you
perform somewhere other than my desk for
a change huh can't wait for the world to
to come to my neck of the woods this
December the neck of
Atlanta there's Woods
there somewh I imagine Atlanta not
having many forests at
all oh
[Music]
really they have
necks now I know it's an expression but
[Music]
still okay more green than
expected
uh finally I'd like to offer you a kiss
for my birthday since you're always
giving us shoes for our birthdays and
supers I figured you needed some back
CH what makes you think that I consent
to that voice okay come here come here
little chicken Peck me
out hey
your choose kind of hurt we should go
back to me giving you choos M Mah mwah
mwah happy belated
birthday happy birthday to
[Music]
you sorry I'm trying to do something in
my
brain happy birthday happy
birthday Nath and cotton Nathan
cotton happy birthday happy birthday
happy birthday happy birthday NE got
never
got amazing I cooked I
cooked 30 Years
[Music]
baby congratulations sorry I'm so late
now you're 30 years and a month how's
that feel
H happy birthday happy birthday
na sound like a goat oh then oh also
still sounds like a
goat I am a goat I am a goat
oh oh
[\h__\h] when I think of it as me being a
[Music]
goat it kind of goes hard
I'm a goat
oh holy [\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] how am I doing
this
wait
oh oh oh oh
this is
fun [\h__\h] brain
Rod thank you
lder I think the non-o version is better
though but this is pretty skillful I
would
say Kos benedicta D the steel D actually
thank you for two super chats one of
them being a pinky
all right you guys wanted the first
batch what a nice
reminder sorry I was immensely busy when
the first batch came out and missed it
the link no longer allows us to access
it also yesterday was my birthday as
well oh I just want to say thank you to
you and Amy for already granting My Wish
of more Fallout New Vegas and streaming
TF2 two of my favorite games ever made
oh wow you're lucky bastard wow all
[Music]
right I was asked
before um but I didn't do it cuz I was
still like hoping that the new Polaroids
would not
be uh overshadowed and
[Music]
missed I mean I don't even know like
this will be a weird post to make like
hey did you miss the last Polaroids
first batch
should I do it right now otherwise maybe
I'll
forget
Gile I wish I could just like throw it
on my Google Drive and just keep it up
there but I don't
think I don't think management wants us
to do it that
[Music]
way replace the old L I think
um that will make it very hard for
people to notice
[Music]
though I should just make a new
post Fe night
um yeah should be
this all
right I'm uploading them pray for my
internet there just a few
pictures they upload really
[Music]
fast okay I'm uploading them so I'll
continue reading super chats now uh but
yeah and thank you steel the steel Happy
Birthday Happy Birthday Happy
Birthday Happy Birthday Happy Birthday
the steel happy birthday is this not the
kind of birthday song you guys were
expecting
[Music]
happy birthday to
you
m in the H happy birthday D steel okay
you got both both of best worlds but I
kind of
think it can't be topped anymore with
the
[Music]
O
that Ste
the you sent so many super chats thank
you the
Ste Ste thank you you're really into
Fallout
huh certainly thanks for the pinky it
has been a while since I've done this
but I certainly have more metal song
recommendations you may
like the band
apocal is unique because they primarily
play cellos also the song Broken Pieces
features Lacy Storm from fly leaf okay
see that sounds really interesting but I
still don't feel like opening that up on
my YouTube right now you better like
send me a freaking link on Twitter or
so posted in the kfp hashtag or so I
guess but don't don't don't don't start
every everybody don't don't you dare
stop start spamming music in kfp hashtag
you don't have Twitter well time to make
[Music]
one time to make one then I don't have
any more water by the way only the cold
rest of my
[Music]
tea can we get a music recommendation
hashtag I don't know I wouldn't check it
out I'm going to be honest
guys unless you're going to recommend me
cute K-pop girl group songs
[Music]
I'm not going to check it
out is dying I
mean I don't like what's going on with
Twitter generally either but I love
Twitter and I've been on Twitter for my
whole [\h__\h] life
so
I'm as long as it's still our main uh
fan interaction platform I'm going to
definitely stay on
it if only our own
application wasn't just reposting tweets
or so but actually if it was a form of
Twitter that would have been just
genius especially in times like
[Music]
these
right Myspace
[Music]
Myspace I never used Myspace
surprisingly I I think in the German
speaking realm it just
wasn't that popular I might be wrong
maybe it's just me
but wasn't so popular my friend Circle
nobody used my
[Music]
space yeah yeah yeah we had CH love that
exactly didn't want to say it but
[Music]
yeah I was definitely old excuse
me no maybe I wasn't what do you mean
old enough was their minimum
age what no I was uh I wasn't even alive
20 years
ago
shut h h I'm Ling you certainly it does
sound interesting but I don't like
metal I I generally don't even listen to
music besides new jeans these days it's
just hard to get me to listen to music
at all like just for
fun you know I still like
singing uh K and all
that but besides that
[Music]
no just don't really feel like this
desire to listen to anything I just want
things to be quiet around me or watch
Netflix and other stuff like
that just watch TV shows or so that's
the only thing I want to hear besides
that I want
[Music]
silence yeah and even if I like work out
or so which obviously I never do but um
the few days where I used my
treadmill i u was watching Netflix while
on the treadmill not listening to music
that's I guess also where a lot of
people would listen to music okay maybe
if I had a car and if I was driving
around I would listen to
music that's why I need a car and a
license then I would also be on track
with the current popular
music cuz nowadays I don't really know
any new
[Music]
songs then go get a license no I said
after
Holo driving needs music for sure but
actually I don't know cuz I've never
driven a car
so only when I'm in the passenger seat I
feel like oh music would be nice and
even then sometimes I feel like honestly
just silence would be nice
too I don't know what kind of driver I
would be would I be a silent driver or a
music driver could be both depending on
my mood but a lot of time when I'm even
even when I'm just a passenger even then
often I appreciate just
nothing just
[Music]
nothing yeah
g d
the
Johnny your your last name is difficult
to say
elij
d the steel D the Ste D Nightwolf
D
[Music]
wateran Chase Hunter
D red d
thank
you random collusion thanks for the
pinky pink reminder turn system sounds
back on if you haven't already oh yeah I
think I definitely did since then
actually pretty immediately after
immediately the whole time I'm reading
right now I feel like I want to do the o
e i e while I'm
reading like random collusion pink
reminder to turn system sounds back on
if you haven't already
[Music]
NCR triple Scout
D I don't know if I will maybe
not the
dlc's Y call thanks on the red super
chat is that are you saying it's your
birthday cuz you're sending only emojis
but they imply a
birthday y
call Happy Birthday Happ happy birthday
happy birthday y happy birthday happy
birthday happy birthday y birthday y yay
yay congratulations congratulations
congratulations
[Music]
congratulations happy birthday
y m m m m m I'm just assuming it's your
birthday I'm pretty sure it's your
birthday don't call me
grandma I'm a goat if anything
happy birthday happy
[Music]
birthday go mom what that don't make me
sound like some kind of old
[Music]
manager wait what no goat ma is just
goat oh a goat manager that's as if a
goat was managing
[Music]
us woo
hope you had a lovely
birthday
[Music]
congratulations my throat yeah it's
feeling um a little bit
raspy El Compa the Jimmy the C
Dy interesting
name pet sake D the steel D Mex D and
booo 723
[Music]
D all right you know
what we're going to read one
more and that is the cuz that's not so
[Music]
many the
first is it the first I think the
uh the
first
yeah the first D
stream going by order
[Music]
still I'm cute what do you mean
what made you say that this
[Music]
or before the lemon ification
began my best thumbnails
[Music]
ever you like my stream no
stop m
[Music]
what do you mean what do you mean no
what do you mean what do you mean what
do you
[Music]
mean need to get this wheel out of the
way just taking up a lot of space
[Music]
I love my
cats I love my cats so much smoothie
legit
like she loves me too much these
days she's always on that pillow that's
like next to my head you know the pillow
that like is in a
position to be used as if somebody
sleeps next to me but it's just my
cats it's literally like my neighbor
pillow like right next to my my pillow
is
touching and smovie always goes up there
now she used to do that sometimes in the
past but then she would quickly after 2
days or so find a different favorite
spot but now it's always that
pillow so she's always like H in my
reach it's
m and then chunky wonk is on the other
side so yesterday
in order to really properly reach them
and be able
to pet both of them right I have to like
reach out my
arms right right arm to chunky wonky
left arm to Smoothie but I have to kind
of sit up a little bit so I can't really
be falling asleep while um petting both
of them but yesterday I kind of fell
asleep while watching uh TV while being
a little bit
sitting up and I woke up after a while
in that position and I was like [\h__\h] my
neck
hurts cuz I was I was sitting up but I
was not really properly like sitting in
a good
position yeah I was really
uncomfortable but what can I do man I
have to pet my cats equally when I
can it's so nice to have fluff on both
of my hands and arms
yeah the sacrifice one
makes worth it I would
say one thing I don't know if I ever
told you about it
but like in my bedroom I have a lot of
mirrors
and wait I think I want to draw
[Music]
it um
sorry I sound like a cat looking at a
bird wait is that where it comes from is
that where the me comes from any chance
from when cats are at the window looking
at bird and being
like wait wait wait is that what it
comes from there cuz that makes so much
sense
now no but it
should that actually sounds exactly what
that is that why it's a cat yeah cuz
they're
chattering no it's purely nonsensical
what the [\h__\h] what a coincidence that's
exactly what cats do
though they look out the window and they
go like
it's so
cute it's so cute okay so I'm too far
from the from my drawing tablet with my
wheel in the way so I'm just going to
draw with the mouse now so okay um bed
yeah then I have like
a this wasn't always in the bedroom but
when I moved it it didn't have space
anymore where I
originally had
it um but this was like a a a little
Ros bench that I used to have in my
entrance in older
Apartments uh you know little bench to
sit down but now I don't really I don't
know it doesn't work anymore that way so
I just put it in front of my bed cuz I I
know some people have some little
benches there in front of their bed it
looks nice and then and then here is a
actually okay the TV isn't that wide but
I have I have some nice closets here
that I'm so proud of for building
them yeah and this is a drawer and it's
mounted on the wall but above the drawer
is my
TV and
then here W I
sleep
yeah in weird positions here is box for
chunky wonky which is orange I almost
forgot chunky wonky I told you before it
has been sleeping in boxes on my bed
like literal boxes it used to be
carboard boxes nowadays it's um kind of
um fabric box uh so to say with a wire
in it um since forever because I don't
know some at some point I when she was
still Prett young I um recognize that
she likes to fit herself in boxes and
sleep in them um and it's like more
likely for her to stay next to me if
she's in a
box so she's always in the box there
it's not really
luxurious but it might be weird like
whenever I have like friends come over
for for the first time or so which is
rare but it happens here and there and I
show them around and and they see my bed
and they see a [\h__\h]
hairy box because obviously chunky wony
makes it hairy I always have to explain
oh oh I have I have a box there for
chuny wonky you know she loves to sleep
there and then I have another pillow
here and so
recently this movie always takes place
here often she was like going like
sleeping here or here this is very
important by the way for you guys to
know cuz it's important to me whenever
my cats changed their favorite sleeping
position it is excite exciting for me to
see what goes on in their mind but yeah
she would usually back in the day she
was always at the bottom of my
feet um yeah or like often so I have
blanket right normal blanket and then on
top of it I have like a a cuddly blanket
that covers like the
bottom so smoothie would often sleep
here right where the blanket
ends and
then start making cookies here cuz the
blanket she likes that blanket for
cookie
making and sometimes when the blanket is
like not position correctly and it's too
far the moment I put it right in front
of her she will start making cookies all
all you have to do is position it
correctly yeah so a lot of time she uh
was like sleeping there the past uh one
or two or 3
years yeah just right there where the
blanket was O that fluffy and then I
would bend
over like
this with one arm on
tummy uh on on her tummy and another arm
I don't know where that went but I would
always bend over and we would fall fall
asleep like that with her purring and my
whole arm wrapped around her whole body
like I got so much of the
fluff yeah I drew this before this part
I drew before and then sometimes I would
wake up and then I would move back to
the middle but then okay um sometimes of
course I would also fall asleep with my
hand on chunky wonky she's just easier
to
reach but she gets like when she's not
in deep Slumber yet then she like she's
more skiddish she doesn't hate me at all
but she will like just decide to leave
randomly if I do it too early on in the
night but so now my setup ever since I
moved it's interesting I have a mirror
here a fulls size full body mirror that
just works really well I have a lot of
mirrors in this room but this mirror
[Music]
conveniently reflects because I when I
if I didn't have this mirror in previous
situations when I want to cuddle with my
cats properly I always have to lie
sideways but then I can't watch TV
properly at least now in this position I
was able to watch TV kind of
properly but if I lay sideways and have
my hands on this cat or that cat I can't
watch TV but this is genius with chunky
wonky the way she lies there I can kind
of Glimpse at the TV through the
mirror yeah it's [\h__\h] genius I've
like purposefully positioned it like
sometimes I I turn it a little a little
bit a few more degrees so that it's a
bit more
visible I'm cat maxing I am I really am
a special kind of
[Music]
Genius I wonder why you yeah yeah I know
no I I I know why my body hurts it makes
a lot of sense especially like this
wasn't always the case but since the
past maybe 6
months I just I can't help but fall
asleep on my tummy it's just more
comfortable so um
basically well my face goes sideways but
the rest of my body is on the tummy and
then one arm on this cat and sometimes
because I feel bad
I will literally lie like this one arm
here on this cat one arm here on this
cat my head to the side can you imagine
how uncomfortable is this
[Music]
actually
yeah but I have to I don't want like
chunky wonky or smooy smooy doesn't
really care I think but chunky monkey I
think cares a little
bit yeah
so
[\h__\h] yeah the the the problem is my
pillow really isn't made for sleeping on
your tummy so it's like too elevated for
me to sleep like
[Music]
that but it just feels so good to have
the fluff on more percentage of my body
I wish they were lap cats when when they
were babies they were like
sleeping um where's my mouse here here
imagine this is yeah I'm drawing this
with mouse still okay please forgive me
if I I used to sleep sideways more often
okay here's my butt and that's you know
you can tell right so you know where my
freaking cats when they were tiny would
sleep I swear to God this was the cutest
thing ever small
smoothie would just like sleep here like
a little
bunny and chunky wonky sometimes like
would sleep on top of my head or like
here I don't know she would find a good
space somewhere like or here I don't
know I was so
happy like I would sleep sideways so
there's really not much space for them
but they were tiny right so they could
sleep
there but then they lost that um uh
Habit
[Music]
M and when they were tiny they were also
like when I was on my PC they were also
lab cats so they would sit on my lap for
for real for real and I thought oh my
God all of my cat dreams are coming true
and then they grew out of
it and I think chunky
[Music]
wonky like they they are okay with being
carried
around um especially actually
surprisingly smoothie lets me carry her
around quite a bit as long as I'm
walking but if I hold them the same way
as when I carry
them while
sitting no that's
unacceptable you know what I mean when I
walk around standing up holding them
over my shoulder they're fine with it
but if I just sit on the sofa or so
holding them over my shoulder then
that's like unacceptable
H and
um yeah what was I going to
say um I think I feel like chuny wonk is
a little bit
traumatized
from especially like one incident I I I
I could assume that that's why she's a
bit
weird and
skidish when she was still a kitten and
I will forever regret this incident but
yeah there was was an incident where
when I just literally I just got her I
think on the second day or so uh had to
bring her to the emergency vet because
she
overnight
swallowed like a string of a pet toy cuz
she chewed through it yeah and I woke up
to her meowing constantly with no break
in
between and I thought because she was
still new I thought she missed her mommy
or something I wasn't sure what was
going on so I waited for her to see if
she would calm down but even after hours
she was still like I swear not a single
quiet minute would pass she would
continue to
go I felt so bad and it was kind of
making me crazy not going to
lie then I I brought her I was so
stressed out I remember back then I was
so [\h__\h] stressed out cuz I just got
the cats and spent all my savings on
them all my
money and I had no money I was so scared
like oh my God that was going to be
expensive I had to borrow money I think
um and yeah I carried them both because
I I they were still so new it was like
the second day or so I couldn't let one
of them alone at home I think
I yeah I brought both of them to the vet
and then I left chunky wony
there uh she had to stay overnight and
they had to pull that string out of
her one of her holes actually which hole
was it not that it matters
but
yeah and the and then um smoothie I
brought her back home alone and I was so
sad I felt so sad
but she was so
brave chunky wony I think maybe was
traumatized ever since and that's why
she acts a bit weird here and there but
she's still like the sweetest baby
ever yeah I love my babies I feel so bad
that that
happened but
like yeah you learn it was a cat toy it
was literally a cat toy and overnight
they chewed through it and then she just
eats it literally like two days ago uh I
I think I saw a video from just you know
random people who repost viral videos
and it was like a
cat uh I think they were making fun of
cat's lack of survival instincts it was
like a video of a cat like kind of like
you you could see the owner going up to
the cat and the cat had had like
something sticking out their throat and
it was like look it looked like it was
chewing on it and the the owner goes to
the cat and the string the owner starts
pulling the string and it's like this
magic trick where the string just gets
longer and longer and longer and longer
and you can't believe how long the
string is that your cat has been chewing
on and it's like deep deep in their body
already and while he's pulling it out
the cat is like
but also still at the same time still
trying to chew more but I think that's
just a
reflex yeah um by the
way I don't know if you have cats but if
you see your cat doing that don't pull
it out so uh fast because I saw in the
comments somebody was uh saying that
that can or a vet I think was saying
that that can really damage the like I
don't know throat and whatever like all
kinds of in side organs depending on how
deep the string is or whatever your cat
is trying to eat don't pull it out so
slow yeah slowly slowly slowly not so
fast but the owner just ripped it out
there and seemingly the cat was okay
but but I was just thinking
man my it seems like a lot of cats do
this where they start eating things and
then they can't stop eating it and it
they just
like really survival Instinct s
to
H it just goes deeper like at some point
like once it's in their mouth and
starting to go into their throat if it's
a long string I understand that they
literally don't have the I guess the
like the how to say skills skill issue
they can't get it out anymore the only
thing they can do is to bring it deeper
in I guess I they must have a gag reflex
cuz I do see Cats
gagging but it just doesn't work the
same way I guess as for humans I don't
know they just yeah they don't have the
ability so they commit to
it yeah and then that can literally
actually [\h__\h] choke them and kill
them so cats why are you so
stupid oh yeah hair balls yeah they do
like what's wrong with them why are they
trying to kill himself like what the
hell cats
[Music]
please oh my God that's disturbing
Matrix what even
disturbing like pandas no pandas have
even less survival
instincts eating stuff in the garden
okay my cats don't do that
thankfully they've been very behaving
[Music]
what are you seeing in this
picture I just wanted to show off my my
strats for watching TV while petting
your cat sideways is by placing a mirror
in one of these
positions yeah but I I would Place one
here too but I already have too many
mirrors in my
room like there's one here but it
doesn't quite work it doesn't give me
enough reflection it's mounted on the
wall so I can't really change the
angle um but yeah I just want you to
know I'm I'm cat maxing real
hard I'm proud of that actually I'm so
proud of that that um I shared so much
knowledge with you that I'm going to
leave you
now that's what you get this
was so much of my knowledge
[Music]
shared yeah I feel like
Jesus the drawings of a mad woman what
no not Madwoman Catwoman come on make a
difference
differentiate yeah just spreading the
good word is there nobody who does it
the same come on there's some cat owners
in the chat do you not do it like me but
I know some of the cat owners in the
chat are lucky owners who have lap cats
they don't have to do this kind of [\h__\h]
they can just like look straight into
the TV and have their cat on their tummy
or so lucky bastards yeah your cat
sleeps on you how do you do it I think
if my cats would have been
boys then they might still be lab
cats but my ladies they don't like it my
cat oliv lays at the foot of my bed I
don't have a TV in my room oh man you're
not cat maxing and you're not Netflix
maxing net
maxing good for
you your cat will cuddle on you he's a
dude yeah it's always the
dudes dudes the dudes dude on dude
action
[Music]
uh-oh
[Laughter]
sorry not for
real grow bro boy cats are just more
cuddly but I'm still hoping my cats will
get cuddly I I do feel like Smoothie has
been getting cuddlier she always wants
to be by my side on that pillow now and
she curls up in the cutest ways you
don't even get it you don't even
understand my guys are so
cute I miss them it breaks my heart when
I have to like leave to get groceries or
when I have to stream it breaks my heart
because of the hours that I could cuddle
with
them and so ridiculous it's so
ridiculous I've spent years with them
and I'm still getting years of them why
am I so freaking addicted
[Music]
traveling right now with a cat is
sending me daily videos is it a
stranger I usually just get friends to
do it CU I don't even know if we do I
wouldn't want a stranger here as a cats
sitter honestly I wouldn't trust anybody
I have so much like like whole life
related stuff lying around I could just
be a fan right but totally I could but
still it just feels um
weird better have friends in
here there's a cat convention in my city
next month let's go let's go
I'm up to seven straight cats out in my
yard you you get seven straight cats in
your yard a that's we I hope you feed
them good
stuff a cat daycare I wouldn't know of
any honestly I know like there's dog day
carees but cat that just doesn't really
make sense for cats I think most cats
wouldn't feel comfortable with being
brought to a random place that they
don't know and then leave them there I
think
you you generally don't want to do that
with cats cuz they get too anxious and
yeah the Super Chat of Zelda what you
mean there never were such things
planned to be read I don't know what you
mean I don't know what you mean at
all I I stopped since um whatever was
before
that yeah cats would get way too
stressed
[Music]
cuz they're just you know supposed to
stay in the same home
usually they get used to it and then
they get freaked out they freak out even
you know when they're going to the
vet the moment they get into a
car oh my
God I can let two cats and dogs a like
for like when people go on vacation and
stuff yeah with dogs it makes sense with
cats I don't know man
that sounds stressful for the cats most
for most
cats not the best solution better to
bring a cat a even a stranger cats
sitter
honestly yeah into your home if you can
if you feel comfortable with that better
would be friends or
family yeah the moment they're in a
carrier they're like why do you want to
kill me mother what what have I done to
you why are you trying to kill me by
putting me into this cage into this
carrier are you trying to euphan IE me
oh my God this lady is going to kill
me that's what they think is happening
seemingly I'm just trying to help you
man just trying to help
you the usual cage why do you despise me
mother
literally the last time I tried to get
smoothie to the vet oh my God that
was her behavior
was I really thought I couldn't get her
in it was impossible like chuny wonky is
manageable but smoothie holy
[\h__\h] she is too strong and too
flexible
and to like oh my God it's like a
different
cat a cat that I have never seen
before no not having it
uh-uh so my solution was getting a
different carrier that she doesn't
recognize that she's still curious about
because she already recognizes the old
carrier um so next time we go to the vet
it'll be an unrecognizable carer so she
will not freak out as hard immediately
and I can still like kind
[Music]
of um betray
her just [\h__\h] turned
liquid mhm but like really like it's
like wait wait wait one more one more
where's mine
here so imagine
um this is
the cage or the carryer
[Music]
so the moment
I try to put my cat in
there
cat she will
literally can you
imagine like a like a spider spread all
her
Limbs and just like push and and like
you know like it will be exactly on the
edges of the
carrier and there's no way like I can't
push her in it's just
impossible oh it was kind of cut off but
you can probably tell what I was trying
to
[Music]
do strong so [\h__\h] strong
no whose cat goes into carrier on their
own will I've only seen that with like
Instagram cats who are just magic beings
that don't really
exist giant plastic cat interesting you
mean like one of those like toy tunnels
that uh where they play like running
through it h that could
work n maybe
not no yeah they know when I want them
in the carrier anyway hi see got me into
a an endless cat yapping moment where I
just as long as it's about cats I can
literally not stop because I love
talking about my cats I should really
stop I'm going to go um tomorrow or like
the day after tomorrow
really will'll be
[Music]
um
the T
[Music]
um past midnight way past midnight 4
a.m. so it's like yeah it's going to
be Friday for
[Music]
me Friday for me but still kind of
Thursday especially for
na yeah
yay yeah yippee
so I'll see you there and I'll practice
on my own some more during the day
hopefully I will be decent enough during
the race wish me luck now I will rest my
throat it
seems it seems as if dry season is
already getting to me it's not even that
different honestly I don't understand
might just be my Thro right now being a
little bit on the Rough Side
anyway thank you yeah anything not last
place
please bye bye thank you for watching
yay yay yay yay yay than love you guys
I'll work on those YouTube shorts
too hopefully maybe I can get a new one
out maybe
by
Friday
maybe yeah
yeah give it some time hey German we say
in thank you thank you thank you thank
you thank you thank
you thank you thank you B
Beed sorry gy brain rot I had to look it
up I saw a clip of CI and gigy and then
I had to look it up well the clip
actually told me
brain wck
[Music]
n