foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
can you guys hear me attention please
wow
wow hello
[Music]
hello
Oh yay friends surprise everybody we are
having a surprise of collab yes how many
of you how many of you realize or like
you know maybe our collab would be an
off Club how many of you guys expected
that no one no one no
one did yes
because I don't think anyone expected
that I would go to Indonesia during my
Japan trip ah yes yes yes yes but then
people were like thinking like you were
tweeting oh it's so hot yeah at that
time I was like okay I arrived so now we
can now we can say it yeah until then I
wanted to keep it a secret yeah I see I
see see right now
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah is it hot
the temperature change right suddenly
yeah the moment I left the airplane I
realized oh yeah yeah I mean I mean I
knew before I came that it will be hot
and I was like damn I didn't bring any
clothes for that weather and I went
shopping to find something but you know
they only have winter clothes right now
they've got like the most the chillest
clothes I could possibly find this yeah
like she was wearing this and I thought
I thought like well this this is fine
but I guess this is here only
hard still and the air is so humid and
it's like blah blah blah but it's like
you know it's a bit similar to Japanese
summer wait Kiara I think I I did
something wrong can I connect yeah
I'll be back yeah I think we're back
everybody's freaking out everybody's
freaking out I was like oh no connection
but now we're back sorry guys uh as
usual are we though I don't know we're
not moving we're not moving but oops
oops
hello oh
[Music]
but it probably closed the room I think
yeah I think so maybe we should uh and
they're gone well you know guys it's off
collab so you know that's so nice
[Music]
come back
enough if you chant pavanashi before you
go to bed tabonashi will come to you
I think sorry I fixed myself
[Music]
okay okay okay
we have fixed Kiara I think have you
fixed her looks good looks good
I think fix her
fix her now oh it worked it worked okay
[Music]
hello
oh yeah yeah well okay we are here for a
karaoke stream but let's talk first
let's talk first and I think we should
turn on the vgm a little bit okay we
should turn on the vgm a little bit
small Okay small small bgm
[Music]
as I meant I met lace cats
two
you met yeah
when she went here she was like first
asking me like can I see your candle
sure first things first yeah cats first
from on a scale of fluffiness on a scale
of one two very fluffy
very fluffy and very friendly they're
like oh they're like so so sweet and
even though they just got to know me
they immediately wanted to cuddle with
me and they were like
I think it's like that you know like uh
cats can sense like ooh like this person
is a cat lady yes
but I feel like you've raised them well
because they are so so polite and so
open and friendly yeah yeah very very
yeah they're very polite I remember that
one that keeps like leaning against me
so sweet use my knee as like a pillow
yeah that was kneeling on the ground
trying to touch his you know as much fur
as possible with my with my hands I just
wanna I wanna hug hug hug the cartoon I
wanna take to my hotel no
[Music]
my first uh the first things I've
noticed uh-huh when I arrived uh
it's like uh there's so many screens on
the streets oh yeah yeah like
advertisement stuff yeah they're so
bright why is there so many screens
there's so many screens I don't know I
think it's like advertisement stuff you
know yeah but it's more than in other
countries really well
um I also want to ask this to you how's
the traffic
yeah I was you know I got into a taxi
and then I thought oh wow it's not so
far away where I'm going so it should be
fine but wow wow wow the traffic is [\h__\h]
but I thought you know
um I even saw from the plane when the
plane was arriving and got got really
close to the airport I saw on the
streets there won like millions of bikes
yeah because you guys also just like in
the Maldives you guys use a lot of bikes
here too huh so there was so many bikes
but uh actually uh I I noticed at the on
the highway I guess there's no bikes
allowed yeah yeah yeah on the highway
there's no bikes allowed but still the
traffic was really really bad
it took so long there's too many cars
here yeah but that's okay I looked at
all the advertisements outside
was there anything particularly
interesting I don't understand anything
but yeah I didn't really do much yet
right I just pretty much immediately
came to Lena's place and then she's she
fed me yeah the food was so good what
did we eat what was all that ah I fed
her in Asian food because like she told
me that she wanted to try so first we
had like a snack like we had Satay which
is like chicken on a skewer with the
peanuts yeah
so good yeah I love the peanut sauce I
think at home I want to try the same
thing yeah because um she can't handle
spicy food right I usually you know when
there's people coming here I want to
prank them with like there's this really
spicy uh snack spicy macaroni snack or
like yeah cause like we're really
crazy about like you know super spicy
but like I don't want you to die so I
just thank you thank you thank you
yeah but you guys have surprisingly a
lot of food that's not spicy I thought
you guys would have like everything
spicy nah yeah the food that I had you
know it was a mix of everything some
things were a little bit spicy but
mostly it was okay she ate Nasi uduk so
it's like that's YouTube yeah
it's like uh just rice like fragrant
rice and then you had a lot of toppings
here and there right like there's a
chicken yeah that was some chicken and
there's the tempeh which you found a
little bit spicy that was tempeh yeah
the brown one yeah it was good but it
was a little spicy I tried though a few
a few yeah a few times and then there's
the long bean thingy the green one which
is also a little bit I like those I like
that okay okay and then there was like a
corn fritters
awkward so that was perfect and the corn
Fritter and then there's like little
like the little cracker thingies oh yes
yes yes and then there were like two two
of the skewer sauces oh what was that
um it's like it's kind of like sausages
but I guess like more coarse yeah like
they ground it looked like a sausage but
it was not really a sausage yeah not
really a sauce it just looks like it
like on a school or something uh
Satay it's like a type of Satay
yes I was told I need to eat bakso
oh yeah maybe another time maybe another
time
did you know there's a type of Basil
where it's like a really big meatball
and inside there's like small meatballs
more meatballs yeah mythical sections
we can eat you can eat bustle next time
there's a lot of food and there's
dessert oh yes I bought her the ice
cream that's for yours look milkshake
yeah for me some milkshake because it
melted
the famous ice cream apparently yeah
apparently it's very famous in Indonesia
now because of the meme yeah they always
open
they always open the branch so fast
everywhere over the world now
yeah what are you calling
[Laughter]
and then we tried learning the song but
we already forgot
yeah something with whiny yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah something something tell me
[Laughter]
it's me I will no they all know it yeah
they all know it
it's good it was good but honestly mine
it reminded me of that um just a
chocolate sundae from McDonald's yeah
you know this is very for the price it's
very good oh yeah yeah I said it's like
one dollar but it's so much yum it's so
big it's like so much ice cream yeah at
the bottom there's like some kind of
jelly or so so I ordered like two like
for her and for me I just ordered like
the chocolate sundae with mystery
topping and strawberry sundae with
mystery top what was the mystery I think
the jelly was the mystery thing that's a
bottoming okay okay yeah okay mysterious
bottoming I don't think that sounds
right spicy
but yeah she chose the chocolate so I
chose the this one do we have the same
bottom thing yeah mine is also like that
it's a jelly
it's good
good that's pretty good very cold though
yes yes it's a topping technically just
at the bottom of the cup yum thank you
for the good food
[Applause]
and after this stream I'll go back to
the cats
and wait oh when you say like goodbye to
me and you think I left then I'll be
secretly going into the castle wait I
thought
you'll not you won't know you won't know
and then tomorrow you know I slept and I
slept with the cats and then I wake up
and I'm like what
yeah
oh me wearing the same clothes oh that's
just because I didn't have any summer
clothes there's nothing to do with me
sleeping here secretly
Kiara is raining's new cat yes
I think I'll fit in you'll fit in the
camera but honestly like
how how your cats are so different from
mine like the the how they behave how
they behave and how do your cats behave
mine are like when they want to get to
know you and they want to cuddle you but
they're so weird about it you you go
there to touch them especially
um trunkers one kind of called chunkers
she she wants you to follow her so you
touch her and then she goes away and you
you follow her and you touch her and she
goes away but like not because she
doesn't like you she just wants to be
followed and changed wow
wow what a scheming cat I did mine mine
seem more active than yours but maybe
yours were just like calm in that moment
yeah uh I guess um they have their
moments sometimes like you you see like
sometimes they're playing like they're
playing a little bit a little bit yeah a
little bit but I think like when given
the chance or sometimes they're bored
they're playing but they have a lot of
chill moments you know sleeping no yeah
they sleep during the day and they
even tried to lick my my pants yeah
[Music]
my cats don't try to lick me oh really
why no I wonder
yeah you don't know they love me they
love me speaking of love me love me love
me
that sounds familiar oh wait where are
we gonna do karaoke
I think we should sing uh witness song
okay
but let me just warn you I'm I I I don't
I this is the first time I'm singing it
in a karaoke so oh for real I was always
just singing it like on the background
you know uh me even though it's my song
I always look for the lyrics well of
course I also need lyrics for my song I
I can't sing it without lyrics because
you don't want to risk it right you
don't want the risk like okay lyrics
thank you I'm a pro after all yes oh no
this one
no famous
that's the first thing that should show
up not Justin Bieber
okay let's see
look there's my album art where am I
surprised I love that album why am I
surprised okay let's
really
[Music]
sing Green Day even if we think Green
Day if we we can't archive this okay
maybe another time we can because I
think our Maldives uh karaoke was also
archived was that a car it's archive
um well we have to do an on our craft
one someday well maybe maybe okay
um
this one I think this one okay okay
let's do a sound sound check with this
song one two
wrong
[Music]
is
see ya yeah
tonight
[Music]
again
foreign
[Music]
in a knife
tonight
uh
[Music]
you and me
me
[Music]
yeah give me your love [\h__\h]
mother
[Music]
here we go
love me love me
[Music]
I got some instruments
you got instruments can you try playing
it
how do you do this I smell like this
like this like this so guys how about is
the audio mostly okay you know we can't
have like perfect audio obviously
oh okay
[Music]
in front of my face
[Applause]
[Music]
she found a lot of Lotto Guys audio is
fine audio is fine good good good
because was there even a Reverb though
no oh you don't watch it on reverb when
you oh I I forgot sometimes I turn it on
sometimes I turn it off oh my gosh
sorry guys accidentally turned off the
voice changers
so cursed okay
okay I think Echo can be really long
okay Reverb is more important okay
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
but well I have a little something for
you but um
yeah maybe maybe later maybe later wow
oh you don't have to give me on your
phone you you wanna do you want this
yeah I mean they're kind of funny use
rain is use Lotto lotto it's usually
like the one that sells a lot right like
we use tissue
or something
is like I think if you Google it's
called like placards I think it's like
two balls on the string two balls on the
string and then you just like uh swing
it and then they go together and make
noise
[Music]
I think like if you search love me love
me you have to specify the singer
there's a lot of songs
and I think you know since we already
sang your uh not your mind my original
song should have missing yours instead
which one I think we should do the
classic one right okay I don't know
either anything is fine but also I kind
of was saying the classic one okay
did we sing this one in the Maldives too
that's what I'm thinking I think I sang
I think I sang Sparks
[Music]
did we sing this in the Maldives guys
memory jog memory jog the receiver is
our set list yeah who remembers the
setlist in the Maldives
our children
we did not sing do you back then heart
Challenger onigai I don't think you said
you're already songs in the Maldives
they're for real
maybe they're just asking for us to sing
it okay
and then we can sing either okay
is
[Music]
everybody
tell me I can hear it clearly tell me
[Applause]
[Music]
we're having so much
some break I'll never give up don't
break honey
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
but they keep
[Music]
if I go around what awaits me in the
dark
could you tell me please
[Music]
[Applause]
I promise
by you
[Music]
so difficult to do in the Rhythm can you
do it in the Rhythm ah I can try next
time same for them okay
and I was Tina told me
are you spoilering our song Choices
just in time
[Applause]
they're trained the train heads
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
my God Metro Arena Metro
[Music]
bro how long have you been doing
not long but you know when I when I said
to people Mama that yo I just bought a
lot of Lotto you know what she said oh
actually I'm a pro I used to play that
game a lot you know yeah cause like
apparently this is like something really
old that just like resurfaced as a trend
and then I was like damn do I really
have the blood I have gelato a lot of
jeans that's why you're so good it's not
fair and I'm up against you it's okay
wow Ancient Ancient well well well oh my
goodness so otherwise both of our
original songs yes should we sing next
you can sing this one since we already
put this here
it's another song from
way well hello we also have some
non-hell life songs though yeah yeah
yeah
family heritage
yeah okay let's search for the lyrics
first
I'm so happy
yes yes yes oh look at this
oh you say you love this song right
that's spicy song spicy so I also really
really really like this song so I'm
happy
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so this way
this is like me uh me you me okay me you
and then we can we can swim
we're we're plotting the lyrics
Distribution on the go all right let's
do this
spontane
ous yeah
[Music]
anymore
foreign
[Music]
why you know
I could say guys
[Music]
yeah I love this song
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
meaning
of life
[Music]
number down
[Applause]
I never signed this with someone else
before really I think it works perfect
you know for two people because there's
like the overlapping awesome nice nice
[Music]
song oh it's a banger yes it is yes it
is always always always the banner I
want to
oh yeah sorry guys please don't don't
follow this because we were like eating
and then like eating food and then
eating ice cream yeah I wanted to be
here earlier but you know traffic is
[\h__\h] yeah oh can I tell a story while
you're eating or like drinking your ice
cream no so I tweeted uh in the morning
I think many hours ago that I was like
panicking yeah I will explain now why I
was panicking
um so kiwawa normally you know I travel
a lot so normally I prepare properly and
I I
look ahead of time oh yeah but and I did
that for for Indonesia too I looked up
with what do I need and so on but I
think I just saw you need vaccinations
and I saw okay well I do have so
whatever should be fine and I saw that
uh austrians don't need a visa so I was
like okay that seems also fine so that's
what I saw so I was like okay I'm just
gonna you know calm down it's gonna be
fine and then one day before uh
one the day before I saw that
there's like a visa on the Rival and I'm
like
okay so I guess I have to pay a little
bit that's no problem though that's not
the problem but then I also prepared
because I thought I might need and I
prepared my certificate my vaccination
certificate uh so I had it as a PDF okay
so I thought that should be enough then
I arrived today at the airport and I
like tried to check in my luggage and
all that
and then the lady asked me all right do
you have the vaccinations I'm like yeah
she wants me to show it to show her the
PDF and and she's like oh but this is
only one and I'm like no this is the
certificate from after I got my third
one so it's just like it's it's not so
clearly on the certificate you know so
she was doubting it though so I was like
okay the other thing I have is I guess a
PDF of my scanned in
um vaccination pass do you know I don't
know if you guys have vaccination but we
have like a yellow vaccination pass so
it's not really has officially usable as
a certificate but yeah it's I guess you
know you saw the stamps and the dates
and all that on that one so I showed her
that and then she was like okay but you
have to download the this app yeah
what's it called
[Music]
and then
so overwhelming and all that app there's
so many things
right yeah but I started uploading
because I guess that's what I had to do
I started uploading my certificates but
um it didn't accept my final certificate
for the other two vaccinations so I was
getting really worried about if they'll
accept it like this but I just uploaded
whatever and I hope that it would work
but it needed time for for
um approval and instead waiting for
approval and I'm like I'm recording my
plane I'm like in 20 minutes oh no wait
a minute so like the whole time in the
flame when you stress yeah
fine what's gonna happen that was Google
I was trying to Google what happens when
you arrive in Indonesia without like
disapproval or without vaccination and
so on and then I saw like one one person
said that if you arrive without any
vaccination then they're gonna give you
a vaccination at the spot
but I already have
well there's no way that I'm gonna
arrive and there's gonna be like well no
thank you go back right yeah yeah
so I was trying to calm myself down but
eventually I had to sleep because it was
a pretty long flight and I woke up
eventually arrived and so I go through
like immigration I get the visa
everything's going fine and I have I get
my luggage to check my luggage
everything's cool and I'm like when
where when are they gonna check my
because actually when I arrived I logged
into the airport Wi-Fi and it said that
my vaccinations are uploaded they were
approved but
[Applause]
no one checked it
nothing there there was there was an
immigration part there was a luggage
part there was like all of that but
there was no space for checking my
vaccination certificate whatsoever so I
was like what did I get those
yeah man but they made it so important
at the airport and online everywhere it
says you have to get your certificates
if you go to Indonesia as a foreigner
yeah but I guess it's like better than
like suddenly getting sent home or
something it's just a prank bro no
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
nothing happened what do I do and he
said something in really fast English
and I didn't understand
it didn't matter I guess okay I mean
that's good you could get into the hotel
yeah thank God yeah but they're like
definitely like even though I think like
some places may be lenient but there are
definitely some places where you can
like you have to do it because like if
you're not shown like green then okay
you cannot enter
or something yeah
so far thankfully it went okay oh yeah
that's good that's good that's good I
think in figure it's good that like
Indonesia still takes it seriously
supposedly you know but but then they
didn't so they made me stress for no
reason
I was like What if I can't meet Wayne
I was like worried so when you like let
me know that okay you're like already
like taking care of stuff like oh okay
good good good
and she messed with me like traffic is
so [\h__\h]
well well well yeah
you're here to sing let's say something
thing
do you want to sing uh yes
okay how does the milkshake taste it
tastes good I ordered the strawberry one
with jelly and I think it's okay
no that's not the one I tried to dminate
it but but one thing though I have to
say uh I was hinting at the strip for
example with
um muna's birthday I sent her a birthday
video message oh yeah yeah at the end I
said like all right goodbye see you soon
see you soon indeed and nobody knows
nobody like father was like weird or
anything my my laugh yeah and also when
you were doing the Indonesian lesson
with me yep yep I was like
hint hint I need this I need this soon
and tell me Teach Me Oh what should I
what what if I go to Indonesia what
should I eat
yeah
yeah and then you told me I shouldn't
use my left hand that's why I was like
so panicking because I knew I'm going to
Indonesia and I can't use my left hand
oh it's okay
Chad was scaring you it's okay I mean
technically like in practice like okay
the typical old school right hand good
left hand bad but like literally you can
get away it's like oh sorry left hand
and then like after a while they'll
catch on you're left-handed yeah but
because you know I got so worried about
the vaccination things and and like also
like things about clothing and so on I
didn't want to know you too much so I
was like I was spamming Muna
even then I was like not sure so I
looked up YouTube videos of what's okay
to do and what's not okay to do in
Indonesia and they were also all saying
don't use your left hand
you guys want to ride on my forehead I
am left-handed please
like slap it on your forehead I'm sorry
I love that I just understand
I can't but I tried I was like in the
airport when I give someone my passport
and so on the whole time I try to focus
on only using my right hand yeah and
when I gave the money to the Visa person
I also gave it with the right hand nice
yeah nice nice nice nice
wait next song next song more attention
more tangent yeah where's the song again
so many songs here type
she said she wanted to sing this band in
ID
oh no
okay
well
what what what's the typical Indonesian
breakfast by the way
fried rice or porridge okay porridge I
understand is that a mosquito yes like
just like in the Maldives
I don't know it flew away
yeah and Nasi no I think nasty cooling
is more for a special occasion right
it's yellow rice in the in the place I
ordered our food from there's also
see like this kind of stuff it doesn't
seem like breakfast to me it's like
lunch fried rice is breakfast
you see uh maybe in like Indonesian
hotels maybe they offer you like uh what
kind of breakfast you want is it the
international breakfast or Indonesian
breakfast and I can guarantee you the
Indonesian breakfast will have fried
rice oh well I'll try I'll try
everything I'll try as long as it's not
spicy yeah yeah yeah maybe you can like
tell them please no spice or I will die
it's like do you have any allergies
unless it's spiciness yeah that's okay
like I I told her like okay like no
spicy right and then yeah this the
stream is spicy so we have to save the
spicy for this stream yeah yeah the food
not spicy spicy food no spicy yes
[Music]
you don't
wanna
eat
means duck like I I told you I'm not I'm
eating fried sugar
oh the rice and the duck it belongs
together it's yeah it's rice rice it's
nasty baby it's dark so nasty baby is
rice and duck oh yeah she ate uh
yeah I thought like because it's only
the two of us maybe we should add
another holotori you know
recipes
you know right there so when you say
like where's the duck oh it's inside me
right now
right now your turkey wait but if
third duck what if I had eaten your your
small chicken
that will be turned out but you ain't
the
um is that chicken I think that's it
oh yeah okay
right now right now
so cool yeah how do you feel as a
turducken I feel whole I don't know
complete complete final form
okay we're gonna sing our next song do
we search for the lyrics of yes okay
okay
three
two one
[Music]
does it start from the beginning yes
foreign
[Music]
tomato
ES
[Music]
foreign
no no no
more the machine
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
bye
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
Lotto
numbers
[Music]
that was nice such a cool song I know I
was so laggy I don't know yeah I don't
know because I'm fine look
because I'm fine should I like re-enter
I don't know
weird should I
maybe try wait wait
and then maybe you re-enter I restart
application re-enter my soul
it's almost like we enter the country
why did it just arrived what do you want
give me some time oh I was so proud of
her she was like she was like trying to
like open and open throw the trash and
she's like trash demon
[Music]
I'll be back you will be back oh yes you
are back once again
[Music]
I'm still lagging I think
Maybe
[Music]
um
but it's okay I'll sound laggy that's
better than nothing okay
I go from right to left right to left oh
stop
oh
it's like what three four seconds delay
oh well no maybe your tail looks like a
Cheeto
wow you look like a blueberry
no that's not bad right I mean I mean
I'm not saying it like as a bad thing
yeah
well one of my cats is actually a Cheeto
cat yum
what's that means
I get it
over yeah
we were saying she looks like like a
Cheeto cat yeah my other one looks like
a radiation cat why I was thinking
seaweed no she's too like bright green
turquoise it makes it look like it's
like my chat right like this coloring
something oh yeah yeah
oh yeah so true
yeah nice nice nice nice
and okay next time next song next song
next song
oh what did we pick such serious songs
right let's do the last one oh yeah yeah
okay okay oh yeah I guess or should we
end with that because it's a happy one
no we should end with it though
we just randomly picked some songs from
the list yeah maybe there's some
overlapping of what we sang in Maldives
because we don't remember yeah we don't
remember
yeah shame okay
uh let's look for the song all right
below it's right below was my first time
singing this one in the karaoke so let's
see how it goes
like this we're not doing like
specific Parts we're just mixing
randomly right yeah it's okay we can do
it on the go okay and wing it because
we're Birds your emotes are so cute
[Music]
okay no it's not it's not the last song
like it's just unless we have Alexa and
I saw I saw that song
just what we had on the list
[Music]
I don't know who yeah
thank you
[Music]
foreign
whatever it is
[Music]
thank you
come on
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I
think I need to remember how I mean
memorize the other song
[Music]
the song cover of this official
wow no voice
spicy spicy spicy well I don't know you
can you can try you can try you know
uploading a cover of Loki Wawa I bet
everybody would be surprised
if I learned the song better then yeah
yeah if you learn the song better and
surprise them you know like everybody
like knows you can sing Kawaii like
heart challenger but did you know did I
know that the girl that's singing with
that guy Suzuki yeah yeah yeah that
she's an idol from one of my favorite
Idol groups back in the day oh for real
yeah yeah she was you know I love hello
project it's a home oh yes get the
mosquito
my protector
yeah so there was an idol rip called
cuta and she was like the most popular
member ah for real like I think like
after this song too like she's been
making like um
she looks so cool and yeah right the
thing is like
um in Kyoto in her original idol group
she was doing that for like 10 12 years
and she was really popular and all that
but I feel like after she left that the
group disbanded you know and then she
started doing this solo songs and the in
the beginning her Sono katsudo wasn't
that
um
not going that well just yet it's just
when she started doing this Anison like
um songs when she got really popular in
the general crowd which I'm really happy
for her because you know it's great that
she's getting discovered finally a bit
more but all these people that discover
her now and they're like oh I love this
girl she's singing so well they don't
know about all the past she's
this Idol group forever and she's got so
much music out there and they don't know
and they missed out on so much yeah
you're like you're like the OG
are you a first
but see if they like her enough then
like uh probably they will also check
out you know her fast work and stuff
like that right hopefully but I think a
lot of people also really don't know oh
really I see always some every time I
tell this story so many people are like
yeah I didn't know I didn't know well I
didn't know now I know
you're welcome yeah you need to dive
deep you know but I'm so happy for her
that she's doing so well because after
you know the girls leave hello project
idle groups most of them
they all lose popularity and pretty much
no one gains more popularity than they
always I already had so I find that
quite interesting that she is like you
know she's been booming so that's really
cool to see I don't know why I'm talking
like this moment
[Laughter]
as a OG fan I'm quite proud
you know I'm somewhat you know an OG fan
myself you know
is
what song was your favorite one damn
it's like oh you're an old genius man
name all of her songs
oh no you got me now I suddenly got
amnesia you know
all right suddenly a part of a drama
[Music]
well you know what I think it's about
time we sing another song right yes this
one's a little bit of a sad song I think
all of this is sad this is sad too okay
sad song number one or sad song number
two one
one one okay
I love this one I love them all
I'm so happy to hear you two and
together again
yeah last time when you when we were in
the same place we didn't have time to
collab right ah so true so true so true
I thought we established that we had
something I told you at first
I told you at first don't even get us
started about that again
together yeah we're saying karaoke just
not on stream yeah we were like in
karaoke with some council members and
Cali but you me and Cali we were like
the only ones singing most of the time
yeah
[Music]
who put all these songs did Kelly put
them in I know it wasn't he was either
like Cali or like when they fought it I
don't know I don't remember who my dad's
saying some MCR songs so yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah a little bit a
little bit Yeah but we sang a lot no no
it was fun never mind
maybe one song a little bit
some something she's saying a little bit
hello hello
yeah we're gonna do that sometime
okay let's check this next song yeah
where is it
oh here it is
[Music]
okay next song it's sad
we need that emo in our lives inject the
emo into your veins
is it really that sad isn't it just a
melodies concept the lyrics are the
lyrics are a little bit sad oh you
[Music]
Okay so
it's okay it's okay
she's here for you
oh
[Music]
um
stories
[Music]
that
monster takeout concluded
[Music]
today
yeah yeah goodbye
[Music]
no matter
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
goodbye
today
[Music]
foreign
like for a moment you didn't recognize
me
I was wearing a mask
because I did my hair and braids and
normally I'm not impressed yeah
that was so mad I was like yeah
no but yeah this looks a little
different than the last time I saw her
yeah
but I missed
you I always miss
ing yeah
you know you know I'm I'm gonna try to
take the you know this this time to meet
some other ID members too but you know
my number one is always you yeah
yeah so no no jealousy okay
[Music]
now you told me beforehand so it's okay
it's okay I can't just come to Indonesia
and then just meet you and then yeah
here it's time for you now you I think
the I think the other ID girls be
careful people have the same be careful
if you meet the kusogaki you know oh
yeah yeah I am really curious about
meeting Kobo yeah
but yeah I'll try to meet as many as I
can and but yeah keep in mind I'm not
staying that long I'm not gonna tell you
guys until when but it's not such a long
um stay but you know maybe maybe we'll
have some of collabs with uh more than
one more than two hopefully I'm gonna
min max
oh God that's that's what I say a lot
yeah I got that from you though yeah I
just started saying that recently but
only because I got it from you
main maxing time let's go but yeah I
hope you have a lot of fun
I'm so happy it's so happy you're here
I'll protect you from the mosquitoes oh
thank you
because in some countries the mosquitoes
are a bit dangerous they're not like
dangerous the ones are here are not
dangerous dangerous but of course not
saying that there are no Dangerous Ones
so just to be safe but I'm pretty sure
like if you're like high up there's no
mosquitoes not what your vaccine was for
no no no no but yeah I don't even know I
probably don't have any other active
Nations I think really only as a child
and then yeah I don't think I have
anything active which might be a problem
because really I don't remember anything
I know there's like um some recommended
vaccinations for Indonesia and like
generally like
[Music]
am I like safe for my whole life I don't
know
well hopefully
um
hopefully it'll be fine hopefully yeah
I want um I don't think I'll even be
outside that much so
yes
uh already getting used to the sunscreen
I didn't bring any sunscreen well then
you can then you can order the sunscreen
online and get it delivered to you right
but they don't know but that sounds slow
that's way faster if I just go to a shop
and find I guess so
me I don't me I order everything online
wow wow yes because it's hot outside
like you said it's so freaking hot but
you should be used to it no nobody's
used to it
I don't think yeah see she doesn't know
how fast in the online shop yeah you you
just like native and then they're like
okay will it be there tomorrow
I doubt it literally one hour
yeah but like it's like uber like yeah
like like Uber Eats but for Supermarket
stuff Oh I thought it was like Amazon
you meant like something like Amazon or
so yeah and then it's for tomorrow right
so maybe like uh right now it's already
closed but like if you order at like 10
and use the instant uh Courier or
something it will arrive in like maybe
half an hour or whatever in Indonesia no
we use something else I can teach you if
you want and I'll just try to if I go on
the street and I wave my hand at the
taxi will they come for me yes but also
it's so hot really yeah but I just go
into the taxi so true but no no if
you're in the hotel you can probably ask
someone to like find you a taxi yes no
problem
yes okay one more song One More song so
two more songs we have two more songs
we have
little kiwawa Adventure in Indonesia
yeah
wow where's the song here thank you
Indonesia for welcoming me I made a joke
on on Twitter that I thought was so
funny I want to say it again somebody
wrote to me on Twitter welcome to
Indonesia I hope you enjoy our
hospitality and I said yeah so far
everybody I've been feeling everybody's
Hospitality so much that I feel like I'm
in the hospital
but yeah like what do you think were you
surprised
well so far yeah I don't know if that's
like all the time and if it's normal but
you know in the video that I was
watching about you yeah I was looking up
Indonesian things and then somebody you
know then in that video but I think it
was more about like Bali but they were
talking about how everybody is so
Hospital
so
hostel
not hostile hospitable Hospital
kind of sounds like it is uh it works
like that oh well
that's just me sorry guys
words are difficult words are very
difficult but yeah
we can I'm gonna look for the lyrics is
it like in Indonesia is this a normal
greeting not not really no no it's kind
of like more traditional somebody told
me to do that you don't need to I
usually like do this like you know like
clasping your hands together like the
the like
you can say this
yes and then you use this
it's not like when you're giving
somebody a gentle reminder
remember your deadline weighing in yeah
yeah it's like a tiara so uh the
deadline uh for your materials I am done
with all my deadlines yeah a simulation
simulation yeah yeah what about you
though no I'm not done there's something
I need to do that's fine yeah your
deadline for this and this is tomorrow
oh but no pressure
all right tomorrow is Monday just a
reminder something like that is that
what your manager says to you I sure
hope not
deadline
just to just a soft reminder but
sometimes you know you feel the passive
aggression
no pressure yeah but uh this is
difficult I can't remember that one
yeah it's pretty difficult yeah and
basically no you don't really do this or
sometimes I'm like it's just me like
when it's like oh oh thanks thanks you
know I say oh I do this but it's not
really anything is it okay to wave hello
yeah yeah of course hello because I
don't know what lots of great people
yeah the Boeing is Weird Brian Boeing
you don't do Boeing here do you like in
Japan
maybe in like some regions you do
yes I think we're like very like
versatile because like there's a lot of
like
um ethnicities and stuff in Indonesia as
well so we just like mix everyone
okay just small nod or like small but
like even even last year like I have
this uh it's I already have it in my
blood I I bow yeah
and now I come directly from Japan so
I'm still in Japan yeah that happens
totally yeah okay wait I was
hi hi
except to parents you bow to your
parents oh
okay
[Music]
p-u-n-t-e-n but I remember that yeah
yeah it's like a massage you know yeah I
really need them soon yeah you can maybe
get
video
yeah okay next to song
[Music]
song yay
but you wouldn't understand you wouldn't
get it
oh
no no do you want to talk okay unless
you know Japanese then you understand
okay it's a classic song three oh what
who sings first I don't know
[Music]
there it was
okay okay
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
wow
he is
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
hold on
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
yeah guys did you notice the lyrics said
I need to tell you
yeah
and then the last chorus there was also
a a line that says
uh the the space between us is zero so I
I was touching shoulders
[Music]
it means hug please hug me
oh so much spiciness so much spices
[Music]
oh we have already reached our last song
Last Song
and it's
it's what it's that shiny Smiley story
song yeah because you don't know how to
sing yeah
I know I know but like I'm not confident
because like I don't know the part it's
gonna like it's gonna sound like you
singing daddy daddy
said the roast oh this [\h__\h]
yummy sometimes you have to challenge
things you know yeah so true sometimes
it's actually not surprising you don't
even realize until that point how well
you can actually sing it so true I'm
like oh oh I didn't realize I could sing
this oh okay you know um you know the
song I suggested you earlier I can't
believe as a fellow hello Tori you
cannot sing
like she can say it's not like she can
sing my songs
but wait wait
I just realized I think one song that
people would want us to sing what
uh we should sing uh macroso Delta songs
we can sing the song I don't know how to
sing the last part though
the only thing in karaoke did we sing
yeah this one
in karaoke no really okay yeah
how do you how how is it written ah
hiragana
oh here this one
wait is it loud
I think
there's like let me check let me check
let me check let me check let me check
it's allowed but there's several
instrumentals oh now let's use this one
okay
here we go okay bye-bye no no no no no
no it's okay I sang it before in the
Stream okay
that was a that was a yeah I think this
one
I think I was no was I don't feel like I
was using that one before I think I can
use this one okay
yo which karaoke to use I wonder
is it spicy oh kinda this is the song We
sang when we were like hand to hand
like we sang it before yes we did but
yeah I immediately uh realized that's
what we did yeah you know the reason why
we were like like holding each other
during that song was just because like
Cali was like sitting like inside the
booth and she wanted to go through
because she was leaving right yeah it up
but we our song was just starting so we
were standing and then we were like okay
I guess okay I guess because
[Music]
the rest of the time we were just
sitting everybody just sits yeah yeah so
yeah I think I told them to arrangement
in the Stream so it was like the Council
of girls like if you were right it's a
council girls and then Cali and then
yeah it's me and kawang
okay we should fresh French toast we
should honey toast
oh I was just very confused for a second
yeah oh yeah
well I heard we shoot French and then
you said toast
hey yo what
spicy okay yeah we got the lyrics
three two
[Music]
let's check the volume first
I'll start
[Music]
okay
alive
[Applause]
[Music]
myself
I see the Lord
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
because
foreign
[Music]
thank you
okay I didn't know until that went yeah
[Music]
uncle
um Encore all right now
I had a long day okay well okay I woke
up early for this stupid flying okay my
face is tired my eyes are tired
but I guess one more one more one more
okay just one more okay
and then I will sleep with Guinness cats
yes
I think it's this one oh but hold on
I think this one right shouldn't have
been a minus one a minus one two because
it has like backup vocals
correct okay
minus one there's two minus one what's
the difference oh no no no no no no this
is a different file
okay
because there's a lot of files because I
don't know which one it is okay
okay how do we divide this
well first we're supposed together
okay it's okay we'll do it on the go we
will yeah okay last song for today
shiny Smiley story thank you Mama
[Music]
oh
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you foreign
foreign
[Music]
oh
you're happy
[Music]
together
I die foreign
[Music]
together
[Applause]
that was fun that was fun
I think you know guys um I think we
gotta go now because I sense that
somebody's pretty much dying to go back
[Music]
and then fall into my beautiful hotel
bed
it looks so comfy I actually recently
you know the place I'm staying in in
Japan we have this like Hollow Ian house
right now which is cool and all and
generally this really cool place but the
bed
is [\h__\h]
you can't really you can feel the
Springs oh my God the mattress
okay well it's good that you can rest
comfortably yeah tonight right yes
okay guys well that was it Fibonacci
karaoke leave your thoughts with the
hashtag
we'd love to hear or see see see
your comments yeah that's it for us
thank you thank you for your attention
ah yes
[Music]
obviously
thank you
[Music]