yo I brought your stupid water wait how
did I did this latest voice before I
think I know how
oh
you called me
weird fish lady with the human face
didn't you it was you wasn't it no no
no no it's talking about gouda the title
is not about you
quite believe you
anyway there are more important things
in the
[Music]
oh yes just look at that color yes
there's no doubt this is the water I
need quickly boy pour it into my
bison
[Music]
yeah
good water yes
yes baby oh that feels good baby yes
Ice Queen
[Music]
yes Exquisite I might even say that was
a Divine I can feel its energy surging
from me oh yeah
that's human yeah
yeah done well
well sacred
before
I see now it was no coincidence that you
completed the goddess trial and obtained
a freaking water dragon scale beautiful
Divine yes baby oh my God boy in turn I
will grant you the favor you have asked
of me and lead you to the sacred flame
of my land
come home
[Music]
baby give me that oh hell yeah open it
up yes baby that looks good Divine oh
hell yeah
um
I have to go get my nails done now so
please just [\h__\h] off your little [\h__\h] up
away I'll DM you on Twitter I'll send
you a few cute pictures now that I am
looking fabulous to get yours until then
do not lower your guard
farewell buoy
Eggman
bam oh come on unbelievable this [\h__\h]
sucks man
yes slay Queen yeah
yeah
Cali slang yes
oh my God