foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
thank you foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
thank you foreign
[Music]
welcome everybody to the 29th episode
today's episode is the first and whole
talk history because we welcome a whole
new generation all at once please say
hello to shiorino
[Music]
and of course
yeah
hi Kelly oh my God hello everybody girls
you can say a quick hi don't worry I'll
meet yourself
okay oh my God sorry for the wait guys
uh you know it's it's much to prepare
with so many members and many many
things to yeah put together but uh let
me introduce how to talk to you as
always although even this time the
explanation is not so accurate I guess
whole talk is a live talk show with the
purpose of interviewing and left
translating mainly Japanese whole life
talents to bring as much wholesome
knowledge to you to oversee viewers as
possible brought to you by your host
takanasikiara but this time as you can
see it's different I have a new
generation they're not Japanese to my
knowledge and
um this is like basically
um something I wanted to do since a
while ago
um actually I already considered it when
ID for Jen debuted because I used to
watch a talk show a German talk show
some Germans might know it
um where you know whenever there's like
a on German TV there's like a new
um like survival Idol group that uh
finished the Survival show then they
invite them to keep they thought to
Talent they interviewed a new group and
you know stuff like that I just kind of
wanted to have a special uh you know
special episode of whole talk where I do
that especially with this new gen that
has been so lovely since I first met
them and they're so easy to work with it
has been such a pleasure because they uh
reply super fast
and they give me everything I need super
fast so it's been a delight so say hello
and welcome everybody to
and our first generation yay
hey Advent
Ure
girls so I want you girls to introduce
yourself let's start from the left
shielding
Novella here and I am but a simple
archiver here and I hope to make many
memories with all of you so
looking forward to talking today oh what
do you archive
memories books maybe maybe things I
shouldn't be archiving but I do it
anyway
spicy all right if you say simple but I
think it's a very difficult and
important job so it's good to have you
here Xiaolin hey thank you we archiving
today's memories too oh okay okay
you're our cutting abilities will be
tested later today
don't don't give it too much pressure
and the next day I see hi
I'm Lititz
[Music]
so sweet yes we need some more smiles to
be protected thank you for taking that
responsibility I feel like I could
squeeze can we redo your opening and you
start with instead of I'm not a
Chihuahua can you say I'm not a kiwawa
okay and we'll go from there
I'm not kilo I am
okay
nice yeah I feel like that was almost
meant to be you know
okay then we have a small beagle who is
sitting on two laps at the same time
yeah I'm very comfy right now
ah Bambi you I am
English I learned sparkling Jam uh rock
rock
but
okay okay welcome Happy
I wanted to talk more to you because of
our overlapping game entrance yes yes so
I'm excited to get to know you more as
well and then somebody who I've gotten
to know quite well so far
hiya Darlings this is hello live English
advents devilish Diva the one and only
narissa ravencroft hello hello
I'm so happy to be here on hello
your speed running kfp goals I know I'm
living the dream
well it's so so nice to have you all
here for this special episode
um we're gonna interview you we're gonna
play some games we're gonna watch some
special videos and have a lot of fun
together yay
a little uh disclaimer for Japanese
viewers it's also written in a pinned
comment but uh
[Music]
okay
we have the Japanese questions on the
screen though at least so let's get
started shall we
first question girls I will ask this to
all of you what have you been up to
recently let's ask Shirley first
I have been packing to go on a trip with
my nyakuza family oh
don't leave us
I can't live without you okay what are
your packing Essentials
oh
so number one close the only issues I
don't know how much pants I'm supposed
to bring for no none don't like wearing
pants no I bought one what should I
bring two wait why would you bring pants
if you don't like them just leave them
at home
I don't want to be freezing cold in the
Middle School wherever I'm going but
yeah if it gets cold
but tight zarya there's some really good
fluffy strong tights out there
or fuzzy ones or fuzzy ones but they
might be scratchy
I don't know uh so do you like Tides
though if you don't like pens yeah no I
like I like things loose because I like
uh flowy dresses to be honest and also
it's more efficient because you only
have one dress you don't need pants and
a shirt on top of it and even like a
belt if you need it so it's just a fish
you know I'm if you're on like
preferring dresses but generally let's
say you go somewhere for five days and
you want to pack only dresses then you
need like five different dresses but if
you were if you wear pants then you just
need maybe one or two pairs of pants and
then maybe five different shirts or so
so maybe it's more efficient to wear
pants
is it is it normal to reuse pants I
don't understand
throw them away
well it's not how it works when if I I
won't I wouldn't pack five pairs of
pants that's for sure
so so at least three pairs yeah or two
but I'm also like on the on the dress
side so I feel yeah I like dresses too I
love your dress did you buy that hot
topic
I I have some Hot Topic clothing yes but
not bringing those
I have to appear as a prim and proper
lady oh okay oh I want to see permanent
proper Gionee maybe in the future oh all
right oh maybe for real for real okay
thank you Siri what about it
we've been doing lots of Halloween
lots of fun like that and most
importantly protecting smiles yeah
you know what um this is not really what
you're doing recently but what you were
doing right before the stream fascinated
me
um yeah I saw you girls warming up
everyone once and then when you know we
were done talking details these girls
would like mute themselves and go warm
up and I would just see them move like
[Music]
have you told your wheels that you warm
up before every stream
you know it's very loud that we like to
howl a lot yeah yeah of course before
we're gonna have all together we're
gonna hold it before yeah how warm up
you know can you give us an example of
your warm-ups okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
oh so okay like kind of like warm up for
your voices to get louder
all right that's very professional
what about small people
um I don't know I'll go to this bed
pretty late but I woke up right before
this can I ask you one question about
your sleeping habits yes which side do
you sleep
oh
um always the side next to the wall
because I want to feel protected oh you
know what I mean I mean actually which
like body side angle
it swaps all the time like I think I'm a
side sleeper
yeah because I always have to hug
something so I'm always like my my bed's
like full of plushies right so I always
have to hug something else I don't know
what to do with my arms
understandable what's your favorite
thing to hug oh
[Music]
okay okay keep fine then keep your
secrets funny what's the meme
you guys know the meme picture should
know the meme
you don't know the meme find them which
one something like that and keep your
secrets one yeah the the Lord of the
Rings one
all right then keep your secrets well
well moving on to narissa who gets it
she just gets it what have you been up
to oh good question uh work I've been
I've been very excited with with this
new job I have so I'm so I'm very in I'm
I've I do it all day all every day I
haven't been planning and working on
many many many many many many sound
covers yes I have a lot I have a lot wow
so well prepared and and you've been
calling with a certain Phoenix he's
almost daily right yeah
I'm spoiled
it's really nice to talk to you yeah I'd
like to talk to you too thank you all
right girls
um I see we're already taking a good
amount of time for every questions so
let's let's move on how did you discover
whole life and why did you decide to
join let's actually start with
ah hello
um I discovered through when myth came
out there were a lot of like uh clips of
Halloween I remember one specific one of
Chihuahua was very inspiring to me
um yeah you're like
reading a super and then you started
crying and I was like oh it touched my
heart
that one the one the one about the the
cancer patient yeah it was so sweet I
almost cried too because you were yours
I was so touched by you and then
um and then I also there were a lot of
JP sounds like playing Minecraft at the
time so I was like Wow cute girls
playing Minecraft together I want to do
that
um so I decided I want to do that okay
so it was just like Random clips coming
into your recommendations on YouTube
yeah my recommendations and then I
started like watching streams a little
bit and I was like oh this this looks so
fun I think
um nothing I wanted I like the most is
like you guys were like group of friends
just hanging out with each other and
people are like hanging out with you and
I liked it a lot awesome thank you and
then let's see what about fuomoco
for us maybe it's a little bit of a
Funny Story at first um we saw a really
cute girl on Twitter
and we thought you know it's just
everything we love all all wrapped up
into one big ball you know what a sister
box yeah understandable oh I I maybe
somebody has already made a fan made
visual novel game of hatama at this
point you know we got many fan-made
games so exciting
you girls to be involved like maybe in
holocue for example someday
right
okay and then I want to hear the same
from Judy
oh
for me I found her life because of
korone senpai
first off I think they were untranslated
Clips at first and then people slowly
started getting into the rabbit hole
that is v-tubing and then there were
just a lot of uh gifts gifts yes kids I
said Gibson gifts both I'm singing again
I don't care what it's supposed
and then for for why I joined I I
suppose it's simply because I like to
create things and I have my other
reasons but but yeah I'm just happy to
be here oh okay and then what about
well uh I saw clips of the JP Senpai
first and I was like oh I wonder what
this is uh and then myth debuted and
then I was like oh my god oh
I love them so much I need I need to be
a part of that somehow so that's kind of
uh what got me in and then of course I
just felt fell down the rabbit hole for
their from that point on okay yes yes it
often starts really lightly with clips
and then you can't escape it do be like
that yeah okay so once you got accepted
where were you and what was your
reaction when you got the final approval
to join Holo who wants to go into this
first
sure I can do this okay
first off
which family once again and I remember I
got the the EML right it was probably
around midnight or something and I have
a horrible sleeping schedule I looked at
the email and I thought I probably
should apply reply immediately and I
also thought like maybe I should wait a
bit just to formulate how to reply my
emails are super formal despite like how
how I seem to be honest yeah so I I kind
of just like slept on it I kept replying
I better reply this way otherwise you're
gonna hate me yeah I was happy I was
surprised didn't expect it to be honest
okay so uh you you are did you were you
emotional or anything when you got it
I was more
just kind of blank if that makes sense
like you kind of stare at something you
tilt your head in confusion yeah you
blink maybe once twice three times and
and then you look at the date you mark
the state on the calendars like is this
real yeah so it's still hard to realize
I guess at that point yeah what about
Marissa
[Music]
um well mine was kind of funny because
uh in the email they they didn't tell me
um so I I I was like panicking
um
so when when I finally got like the okay
I like had to keep it together yeah and
then like after after I I just I think I
went straight to bed and then just
started crying very happy tears because
I was like oh my God oh my God
very very happy moment
I can imagine you being really really
happy also connected to the other things
you told me about your auditioning
process until now yeah I can imagine
yeah what about me boo
uh I was already crying when I got it
I was with
to a song from a certain anime all the
songs called I really want to stay at
your house uh it's from cyberpunk the
the recent anime
um and and if you know the song
it makes you cry
so I was already crying when I was when
I got the email and then I cried harder
because one thing and I was like oh and
then and then I was like oh and then I
cried sang along to the song in
happiness
and then and then I like ran around the
house a lot I got like excited excited
crying zoomy so just imagine like me
running around crying yeah yeah I can
imagine oh oh no I would love to hug you
in that moment but unfortunately I did
not know about your existence at that
time
football
for us when we got the email being like
oh we'd like to talk with you we are
really really happy with something
really really happy but we never really
had a moment when he's like we're in
Hawaii yeah so we still kind of feel
like
ah
it was a time where they told us yes yes
and we were like
and then 30 minutes later we're like
what what if they were lying what what
is nice
yeah right so yeah we did it to
ourselves I think yeah it must have been
a really special moment for you I'm so
happy with all of you girls
I was I was also when I first got my
okay I was like alone in bed and
depressed in Japan and then suddenly you
know the whole the whole situation
changes into a happy one so kind of got
rescued I'm actually gonna skip the next
question because I'm worried about how
we're doing in time in the next one
isn't so important it's just the usual
what do you like to stream so next skip
a shield what's who is your holy life
Oshie or inspiration I don't I don't
know if I even need to hear this from
the Versa but let's just hear it you
know for good measure yeah I'll go first
well of course of course it might be
obvious by now to most of you if you've
been following our interactions the I I
I'm a Kiara Senpai is the love of my
life
okay let's hear it from um
but I think I heard you or she recently
wasn't it
what good choices very good choices is
there anybody in Yen that you like to
watch or so we both feel like fondness
and fighting guys oh you like the the
music from Cali or what what do you like
her her work ethics
she has a very strong work ethic yeah
yeah very very dedicated yeah I think
that's a good thing to Aspire towards
that work okay maybe don't overdo it
like her yeah still take care of
yourself okay that's important yeah
okay I'm tactically bypassing this one
however I I actually Advent will always
be my oceans
and I learned to your streams however I
also keep an eye on everyone on the
English side and just see what
everyone's up to so that's where I'll
leave it the eye okay that uh You're All
About Eyes
respectfully perceiving and feeling much
are okay and then what about people
ah okay for e and
um I don't know if I can say Ian because
I really love all of Ian and my Ian OST
changes by who's nice to me
so far so I give you a nice me I'm like
oh you're my favorite oh you're my
favorite so uh I bought everybody so
much anyway so I love all of Ian but so
I'll say someone outside of Ian
um I'm saying this person because if I
don't see her I don't know what will
happen to me I like Kyle is so far
is she threatening you
she's been really nice to me and I like
her like work ethic of like streaming so
much and uh she loves games and stuff
just like me and we've been talking so I
like Kyle stuff all right even though
I'm a little scary
oh my God okay
let's hope she hears this and is happy
about what you just did
okay uh oh wait I skipped the video
let's go watch some debut highlights
let's move over to a comfortable cozy
place
but some of you have to stand
well actually oh I just noticed she only
is maybe standing on the chair that's
okay that's okay
okay so I prepared a clip this one
actually has Japanese subtitles
let's watch some Debbie highlights
novella
squeal
[Music]
and
I eat with scissors at times scissors
quite dangerous I can see how it's
sufficient though
scissors to me it's like Chopsticks
steak even hamburger I've used Pizza
even ice cream ice cream scissors
put it in your mouth oh well I would not
recommend you do this unless you're like
me I suppose
very very well don't get sharp scissors
naturally I'm gonna try it later
I'll watch over you if you do I have
already seen your Twitter comments you
wish for me
tongue bleed and
Everything's changed
but they're very handy if I have okay
traditional items
like your paws yeah suppose the epitome
of your hot golf girlfriend question one
yeah
yeah it drips perhaps that is not the
only thing can't wait for it the
sponsorship
so
pretty we enjoyed looking at almost
pretty as you
know
yeah
I was in charge of boom sound who did
that
can we talk about this can we can we
talk about Creepy juice
[Music]
I'm not letting anyone get the jump on
me no yeah yeah it's gonna happen I'm
doing it myself
[Music]
being in my presence includes Ursa
these are my likes
PowerPoint presentation uh did you guys
like my presentation I love it
spoke to my new friends
like I'm so scared when this happened
it's all on purpose I assume very
professionally
there is a raven
crossed out I speak English oh no I
speak a little bit of Japanese
um I'm not confident enough to say any
any right here right now but I can read
about two thousand pounds
if you're a Japanese speaker please feel
free to type in Donkey grinding and I
will do my best to read it and respond
it'll be good practice for me pepperoni
and pineapple pizza
but this one's the best and if you don't
like pineapple that's okay that's your
decision it's okay to be wrong thank you
I'm gonna say this right off the bat so
there are no surprises I don't I don't
wear them I don't enjoy them they're not
they're no pandas don't think they
should be free either but who am I to
tell you what to do but either way I'm
strictly no pun thank you
[Laughter]
I'm
a Pomeranian a bit more fluffy videos
rejected
a lot of ideas that get rejected wow
needs more control
let's take a bath together
of course I'll clean them yeah
[Music]
right
is that going into the misunderstanding
corner
[Music]
warm your heart I will be there to
brighten your day and warm your heart
even an old age
[Music]
wow okay there was a lot to take in
there but these were just a few of the
highlights that uh I personally chose
from your debut streams that everybody's
watched I think but just to you know
recap on how everybody your
views were all so stable and good like
oh my God
I'm so happy they went without a hitch
good job girls how many times did you
like practice your debut stream because
we did it also a few times like once in
front of staff I think twice
once once okay but all in front of Staff
right
how was that was that awkward yeah
but even when you like practice it once
in front of Staff doing it in reality
then at like in front of like
tens and tens and tens of thousands of
viewers yeah completely different
did you girls like look at the viewer
account when you were yeah yeah no no no
no
no no no I didn't ever look at it
actually I was watching it you shouldn't
have looked at it it makes you nervous
it was a good choice from the others to
not look at that yeah oh my God that was
insane all right let's move back
[Music]
all right welcome back everybody you
moves so quickly
I didn't know you had like a skill of
shunkan idol teleportation wow
[Music]
alrighty are you ready for more
questions
okay so I'm I'm interested in this
uh did you tell your parents or other
family members about your new job and
what did they think of it let's start
with Julian
I I only told him I have a new job but I
didn't go into detail because I'd rather
well frankly they also don't really know
much about this stuff they're just
stereotypical uh strict parents who
don't know technology
also they just think you're doing what
um I just tell them that oh I I got into
voice acting
I say that too too like strangers yeah
it's like the most General League
group give
it
but don't they want you to show them
like examples
I I suppose so but I'd rather keep them
protected so I'll tell them I'm like
okay well this is the company but that's
all I'm telling you yeah okay okay and
and they they think it's cool
uh they just want me happy so whatever
works it works sweet understanding
family who is happy to just not know all
the details that's good don't ask too
many questions
what about people
ah they know they know my mom's Jackie
and dad said you both know and they
watch every stream I think and they have
me on like three different devices and
my mom says like uh she watches me while
she's cooking I don't know if it's a
good thing though because they called me
yesterday and I had to explain to them
what bass meant because they didn't know
what face man and I was like and
um but yeah they they're very supportive
my parents give me like a little pep
talk before I debuted and then after
they I debuted they called me too and
they're like oh good job but yeah
sometimes they don't understand English
too well sometimes so some of the things
they say like based what is that I'm
like oh no well even that it might be
English books slang too so yeah even
like people who speak fluent English but
just don't use the internet much might
not know what it means right yeah based
on what yeah there's one
so your parents are the very supportive
type who watch out your streams yeah
yeah my family also with my mom like she
watches uh almost all of my streams too
she's very into my Minecraft streams for
example
our Minecraft server once and we were
building some
Mama Tony so we're quite similar there
um what about
um
he just wants us to be happy okay that's
also very sweet but they they probably
don't understand also happily ignoring
the details
maybe it's better that way yeah yeah
what about nawisa
I have told my family
um because I need them sometimes to
maybe be quiet for me
um but it's it's very funny because uh
Bijou my mom asked me the same question
she was like what's face
I don't look it up I don't know how to
explain this to you but no same uh
they're very supportive uh they're very
they they really they had no idea what
hollow life was and now they like
they're coming all my streams they're
like looking at all the Ian Senpai and
they're like oh my God
I was like I really like that girl with
the red hat and the orange hair yeah
you just got that you got that thing
about you
I wonder what it is that's it it's
everything I really got a long run with
moms I I think I know how to please them
but
um but but I thought you I wasn't even
trying to please your mom in that moment
so yeah but it just interesting one so
maybe one day if I come visit you I
already can start off easily with your
mom you know because she already knows
me she'll love you
all right okay is there anybody here who
would be open to or thinking about in
the future bringing their family members
on stream like some others did before no
no I see some knows maybe probably maybe
okay
excited for that okay it's okay to not
do it totally fine like honestly I was
so scared to bring my mom onto my stream
because I I was she talks a lot you know
and it's hard to control yourself really
if you're not used to controlling
yourself to yeah not saying certain
things so
yeah
yeah let's move on
um are there any bigger projects like
whole talk or Minecraft sports festival
that you girls would like to do anybody
you know any opportunity yeah even if
it's something that maybe we're not
great at it's fun then it's good okay
the feeling is fun good too you already
have like certain at least like kikaku
going on like a morning and and so on so
I think that's really great that you're
already having like some regular
projects yeah I really like to be able
to evolve a lot with the ears and like
um
that's fun any more ambitionist people
in here you want to do big projects
I wanna I wanna join all like the the
gaming tournaments and stuff like Mario
Kart I was cheering
uh during Pokemon because she plays the
same role that I did so I was doing her
on yeah
do you think you you could have done
well in the Pokemon unite tournament I
think so yeah I'm always up for like a
challenge in terms of like games and
stuff so I want to like try out all the
different like tournaments and stuff and
I'll be cheering you guys on tonight as
well yes we have a Minecraft ID whole
little cup thingy going on in a few
hours I'm excited for that too yeah so
okay I see I see then if there's no one
else I'll move on to the next question
what's everyone's favorite live original
song
's excited to say something to go it's
so it's so so so so so so hard to chill
there's so many other songs
okay okay one my first choice is ever
Blue by poker I can't sing it it's of
course you can
it's too much I get to a voices
are you liking emotional songs huh I
like a lot of songs
you know you seem so fuzzy and so
um energetic on the outside but are you
truly inside like very emotional and yes
I really really like the feeling of it
um yes
yes yes that one is beautiful especially
when performed live
oh wow good choices very good choices so
I like them is this perhaps like a
little bit of a a hint towards what
you'll be singing in your whole
Aboriginal karaoke
maybe yes
okay so what about people
uh can I see two as well yeah go on okay
uh the first one I like body some pie
it's so upbeat and fun and I want to
learn how to sing it one day maybe maybe
for karaoke or something like that it's
just so catchy it's just so catchy it's
been stuck in my head for so long and
then the second one I like fauna senpies
let me stay here because it's so it's so
cute it's a very sweet song it's so
relaxing yeah it just puts me in a good
mood always I want to hear Bijou
versions of those songs
I will practice go go whole life
Originals karaoke when I hear that from
all of you
oh
okay I remember the whole comments
during it and just like seeing it and
everyone's just enjoying it and this is
pretty catchy based split dope super
based good choice good choice will you
maybe sing it one day
I don't know about that
I'm waiting for it now
so you you have to
what about
I have three technically okay so they're
all pretty much tied but I really like
Marine essential songs uh both marivako
and Unison well they're they're like
pretty much tied I like to sing maribako
best
but I I also really like Unison but it's
so hard to sing yeah but then uh also
tide is uh do you sorry
I remember exactly exactly where I was
when it came out and I I think I
mentioned I don't like dancing but I I
kept on I had to like Loop it and I
everywhere I went I was like listening
to it I was like oh my God all right
once you get 3D you gotta do the do you
challenge okay I will I'll stop but I'll
do it for you you can start learning
right now oh I'll teach you I'll teach
you yes please getting taught by the the
original dancer the teacher
me fun all right okay I'm also looking
forward to all of you girls creating
Originals while you're here please
please it would be very hype you know
create an original and then one day
perform it on a concert stage
doesn't that sound good yes
okay let's go to the next question
um is there a certain whole live stream
that stayed in your memory because it
was so special or funny how about chioni
honestly it's a 3D debut stuff as
someone who is into unity and I actually
try to think of like how did they
achieve this and all that stuff yeah
it's probably that one so I keep
thinking of the technical aspects so I
was there for Ina's thing she had a cute
room and she was like drawing yeah then
I will also watch Maurice thing with the
Giants the stage you know yeah
also except for I think her birthday
karaoke and I think about somebody
showed up in a PNG which I found amusing
and what was it the PNG
I believe it was I'm trying to remember
I think it was Louise somebody oh all
right did you watch the uh myth collab
3D collab the one for the VR chat one uh
oh no I meant the actual official 3DW
collab that happened in February
I'm trying to remember February is when
things got hectic this is all I'll say
um well maybe maybe the archival has
some catching up to do hey then you can
you can watch some 3D streams also for
inspiration for the future maybe when
you girls get to do 3D streams yeah it
was about
um
um it's really hard for me to answer
that because you watch too many streams
huh I watched too many streams I really
do
um I I maybe this is a cop-out answer
perhaps but after debut actually I feel
like the streams became a lot more
special in a lot of ways because a lot
of this Senpai unfiltered have been
talking about all of Advent and like
hearing Senpai like say really nice
things about us that makes my heart feel
really full in a way I've never
experienced before so I think I think a
lot of the recent streams here here in
the Senpai talk about is have been
really special for me but otherwise
before that it's a secret I can't share
it I see crap
you tell me later though yeah yeah I
don't think I know it's the secret okay
how about for McCall
mean a lot to us too I think probably
our favorite so far is probably
um
[Music]
yeah it's just it's perfect it's perfect
it's perfect and it ends perfectly yeah
yeah it's honestly isn't it a crime that
we're not charging money for these high
quality well-organized beautiful big
efforts streams right for these ones
like a real concert uh what yeah yeah I
get it what about people
um I was gonna say 3D too because
I really like the when you guys go into
VR chat I think 3D is great because you
can see like your actual yeah and stuff
and like see how you guys like behave
um any move and stuff and like the
Halloween 3Ds were so funny for both
friends and Council I love seeing your
Halloween outfits but I think that my
most favorite
um was the most recent Fest uh concert I
think that was my most memorable because
I don't know it just made me teary like
oh that's myself
and watching everyone Dance I'm I want
to like learn how to dance Too and Kiara
Senpai had some moves oh thank you I'm
sure you all can learn those moves too
it were you girls were you all watching
the our en concerts in L.A yeah
did you like it can you imagine being up
there on stage with us next time maybe
oh it's hard to imagine but I really
wonderful yes yeah oh I'm looking
forward to it very excited for it
imagine uh performing your original song
the Advent original song together
sounds like fun okay uh I think I asked
everybody so did I did I ask everybody
okay let's move to
some fun segments we're gonna take a
break from the questions for a little
bit uh we're gonna is everybody in the
in the
um in the room of the game
yes the drawing one so let me pop this
one up
[Music]
I have a challenge for you girls you're
not allowed to look at what the other
person is drawing
but I will give you
some time
maybe
I'll I'll say maybe roughly two minutes
or so uh to draw
each other and everyone will be assigned
someone to draw just one person from
memory don't look anywhere it's actually
maybe I'll only give you one minute so
you don't have so much time to look at
somebody okay let's see
Siri will draw flower
foreign
[Music]
okay
have fun try to remember
what your new gen mate looks like
because you'll be working with them for
a while from now on
it's good to remember their faces
right
oh okay
okay wait is anybody drawing somebody
twice
no right
why should it
what is it that doesn't quite look like
her
oh what show me
well
narissa is drawing
looks I drive with the mouse please
pretty easy on me yeah some some of them
are drawing with mouse that's okay or
maybe um
everybody else has a tablet I think
[Music]
um
really okay
that looks a little bit like Medusa
right now
a walk yeah right so
it has The Rock charm for sure oh B was
looking very good oh you're more skilled
artists
the one that Shield is strong it's
starting to look like it's like part of
some kind of like uh game like a
character in the game
um like a jump jump jumping jumping one
game like I don't know
spooky but looks like a fun mascot to
play in the uh and I had a platformer
that's what I wanted to say in a
platformer game
cute some ideas for you then hello
old platformer oh I actually wasn't
looking at the time I'll give you a
little bit more time
[Music]
yep body important
a beautiful beautiful looking beautiful
yeah
and Bieber stopped throwing at the boops
because maybe that's good enough
[Laughter]
the little like what was that that she
already has a spider or what is that
thing huh it's yours okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
shoulder yeah
Goblin Goblin okay not early
he's made of mercury
better not eat him right
did we have a misunderstanding right now
and I missed it
foreign
[Laughter]
I'll give you 10 more seconds
[Music]
ten nine
eight
six
five three four
three cool
two
one
wow beautiful yeah
honestly I I made fun of it first but I
think the one that she already Drew
looks like really detailed and well made
um but wait which one is it you draw a
full all right
yeah
it might look weird
yeah especially on uh this type of hula
understandable I get it
very good though and then the drawing
from narissa oh very cute got the
headphones got the pink highlights got
the T-shirt everything there that needs
to be there and also Mr headband now
that I'm looking at her oh I'm sorry
it's
let's see who it is right
and then people I want to see drawing
streams from you because it's so cute
very cute by the way I must say for the
scissors I think I've seen like
professional restaurants use scissors to
cut up Stakes for the customer so it's
not so weird okay but I'm assuming that
you you are you replacing both fork and
knife with scissors
makes it efficient yeah
well why not I see how it can work you
know it works uh and then and then and
then the beautiful Medusa Bieber
the wings are now placed up on your ears
so that your head can fly off
it's just going oh can we really quickly
get forward to draw Larissa while while
maybe we talk a little bit go go go for
a while we have to joinery
are you gonna raise mine
um
shots it's it's fine we can get a lot of
knives and archived forever and ever
so guys that's who you think did the
best with those drawings like drawing
is always always
telling mokuku what to do now we have
now let's have what to do yeah yeah it's
payback all right don't look at me good
luck
control of who was I so she doesn't look
at Marissa always people want to see if
you see from eyes dark then you know
[Music]
does whoever like to draw sometimes no
no
who here like draws oh my god oh
thank you
oh I'm putting this on my fridge
[Laughter]
yeah you maybe want to have you know two
tones for the hair
food likes to draw a lot in her Pastime
Maybe
yeah
I haven't had too much time recently
weren't you drawing emotions
yeah I do uh my first emote cute
will you draw all of your emotes no but
I I think I'll add a few more oh my God
[Laughter]
I understand now why
eyelashes
oh my God I think maybe
whoa it doesn't really like me huh yeah
she wants to accentuate the oh it's
because
[Laughter]
oh
no
no no that's that's just a skin skin
Mark
the color the color the color is the
color more more important to you than
maybe maybe you only have more parts on
the head important recognizable parts
[Laughter]
oh yeah ah yes there you go beautiful oh
that is like a lot plus size
very thick horn
[Music]
less weight on your head yeah yeah
jewelry oh can you remember
I'm not giving hints no
done yeah okay
is it recognizable that is questionable
but yeah I don't I'm not so sure about
that
features are there for sure
thank you this is beautiful
I've never said well surely print it out
and put it in yeah I've already saved it
right put it on your fridge
yeah
thank you for this uh love these lovely
paintings now I I think it's proof that
you girls have a good memory of each
other so far and have been looking at
each other a lot which is a precious
beautiful uh okay then you're done with
that challenge but I have another
challenge girls
we are replacing the usual speed quiz
that my lovely holotalk nearers know so
well with
this on the table oh it's a button that
you can I press it no don't press it
we are replacing it with uh Holo live
knowledge quiz with questions that I
thought of
some are maybe quite old knowledge but I
think still very classic you know and
they're mixed uh with Enid and Japanese
members knowledge and you guys in the
chat are welcome
to you know play with us and guest with
us now I have a buzzer system behind the
scenes that you guys don't see when they
will buzz I will see who Buzz is first
and I will ask them if they get it wrong
I'll ask the next buzzed player and it
goes on and on and then we see
how many points and who will be the
winner fuemoko is playing as a team as
far as I know right okay and then I
think we can get started let me test
everybody test the buzzer
wonderful
it worked okay here we go and wait I
have the questions for the screen in
Japanese uh oh no in English as well
this time in English because I thought
it's a bit easier
okay we're told I've never solely used
[Music]
okay
in that order let's start with Moco
um
[Laughter]
but you said two people right now right
you're missing someone
[Music]
I know yeah
[Laughter]
wait yes yes
but next time I will not be so nice and
you have to get it right on right away
okay one point for four more goal
next question clearing the buzzer which
members does gen zero consist of
[Music]
gen zero
oh
okay people came in first let's hear it
okay ah so this sounds fine uh
uh oh it's fun
uh-huh uh
[Music]
um
yeah faster faster
robocopy yes
foreign
[Music]
guys don't spam it so much in the chat
okay
we're not tweeters
gotta play fair and square okay next
question
um
what is the name of caliope's male alter
ego
[Music]
wait I I feel like I shouldn't say it
because I feel like I know what it is
but I also feel like it's wrong say it
right it's not C
man is it
I guess
it's
what does say
uh I was thinking maybe kale okay
yeah no I was looking for Calvin but I
guess cement count
I guess does it count chat okay
it counts okay let's give Marissa a
point oh hell yeah I think she did uh
refer to he referred to himself as c-man
too I think I guess so yeah okay okay
clearing the buzzer and next question
this one's an easy one I think
it
[Music]
in what country was hachama studying
abroad
go on
Australia of course yes
[Music]
she had dreams when she would cook like
tarantulas and and the spiky ones that
have a spiky tail what do you call those
uh scorpions scorpions crazy
and her her favorite food I suppose okay
next question
which whole life member has an opposite
all right there might be and other
answers that I'm not looking for that I
will still accept go on fumuku
that's what I was looking for extra
points what's the name of the altar
[Music]
clearly leading the quiz
okay okay okay
next question
beef balls are the favorite fruit of
it
yeah yes good job good job the Marissa
was also buzzing there at the end did
you know it too yeah
I'm just slow it's okay it's okay it's
so fast
two in one this isn't fair yeah
maybe a ghost would risk it for a
biscuit and just even if you can't think
of it right away just buzzer anyway just
to get faster
okay next question what is the piggy
bank incident
[Music]
did I get them did I get them should I
get them all
okay no one knows
reset the reset or buzzer oh
I know
do you know it no okay
well let me tell you this is really
funny I want you guys to look it up
afterwards was this like last year or so
maybe in the Stream uh of the ID Girls
the first gen they used to live together
in a dorm and there was a stream where
this is stole muna's piggy bank and then
locked herself into her room while she
was streaming and she was counting the
money and Muna was like outside the door
like knocking and screaming and it was
20 20 three years two years ago and when
she was like trying to get in like
and then you know this is like a long
time ago but they recently in the uh
recently in the first gen 3D streams in
the collab they brought up this incident
and reenacted that in 3D which was
really cute too
yeah yeah ID knowledge it's so cute I
love that
they're all so close you know funny
incidents okay next one should be pretty
easy again
Marissa was very close
but Fuego was first
who is it
exactly yeah yes yes yes okay I will
clear the buzzer next
how many pets does Emilia oh
alone okay
no oh
no
okay it's not just Bubba I know we
always hear Bubba and she always
mentions Bubba But Here Comes number one
teammate knowledge uh there is she has
two dogs and two cats so kind of four if
you ignore the fishies that she has yeah
I've met them and they're very lovely
all of them it's not just Baba yeah yeah
yeah maybe one day you'll remember yeah
it's a cute family
oh it was the first time local got
something wrong
I had a chance but you missed it
yeah all right oh even yeah the names
I always forget some of them but it's
Mickey Henry Wellington and bye-bye yes
all right this one I think is quite
difficult unless you're you watch even
Japanese streams from back in the day
um
what is the origin of tokino soda's
famous phrase oh
okay okay because I think a lot of
people know the phrase but they don't
know where it came from uh yeah so it
was in the Minecraft stream where at
class and by told us that she's the
leader of the whole life resistance and
then just you know really gently but
threateningly says
which means so that means we're we're
enemies right yeah it's a meme okay
next question
which whole life member is known for
having insane
we had a lot of members Buzz for this
one but for mocha was the fastest again
yeah okay
wow even know the number I don't know if
the number was correct but yeah
maybe maybe
some of you girls can get stronger than
Canada what do you think
again clearing the buzzer next question
[Music]
if someone will duck what was she
actually supposed to be
what was it called ww she's she's a
she's a like manager of a wrestling
wrestling Esports or Esports
yeah I know where you got the W from
she's actually an MMA and Esports Club
dyslexia you know how it is
the same thing
good job it's it's you may just be a
whole little intern but you seem to
already have Horror Story knowledge very
good
yes
burn out true okay bye now I said Brown
now
okay good good all right then next one
wait let me clear okay next one
what's my favorite food
[Music]
oh
come on
potato chips yes laughs
oh you were unsure for a moment what
were you thinking of I was thinking just
out
yeah she does have an Uber sheep thing
going on yeah yeah but she loves she
always snacks on potato chips on stream
yeah yeah okay
show up next one we're getting close to
the end so the score is already pretty
clear but don't give up yes
next one
Ina's famous reaction tomorrow was in
regards to one
um
what word was it about though oh what
was it about it there was the game and
then it was gonna start tomorrow
the full one yeah so it's actually about
the Kingdom Hearts announcement
but it's okay you already have so many
points anyway
okay and next is the last one but I am
gonna add another one just
that that one isn't written written in a
um graphic but I was wondering if I
should add it but I want to add it for
some okay first uh we have the second to
last one
which whole life English member wrote
the book
it was uh again a close one
bibu was second by the way research what
do you say yes
uh script for the Advent calendar final
video that I acted out with sock puppets
I don't know if you girls watched that
one but um I wanna do that again this
year and then we'll have you join in and
I'll make sock puppets of you too
yeah okay
um
almost last question
this one's not on screen
[Music]
um spell to me and the name of the
following whole life number
LaPlace Darkness
oh oh I missed it Risa let's go okay
wait so the question here is then
the literal plus sign yeah so la plus
sign if you want me to spell out plus p
l u s and the last name
d-a-r-k-n-e-s-s
o
that's the weird thing about her name it
has free SS oh I shouldn't have said it
maybe I should have asked for the next
did you all the girls know where it is
yes it's got a weird Triple S see us
English readers we see a word and we
just see the first and last letter and
then we we meld all those ones in
between together so we wouldn't notice
something like that you may have auto
corrected her name in your brain yeah
well many people didn't notice it
apparently yeah
oh wow guys
yeah it's a triple S yeah you never know
oh my God just call her Yamada
okay now that comes the real real real
real real real real last question
because I can't let go of this one just
because we changed the game
what's your panty color
[Music]
[Laughter]
s
do you not know the answer maybe go
check it no maybe it's your chance to
get a point girls
no I have enough points thank you yeah
all right okay and ironically Rissa was
the first to buzz
uh everyone already knows the answer to
mine which is that I'm not one yeah
answer the question what is the color of
your panties
transparent there's not any answers
wrong there is a what's the color biboo
what is it I'm just checking
thanks
hahaha
okay okay okay hey I give you one more
extra because some of you girls were too
embarrassed
what's the color of my panties
we would never look at you like that we
would never try to look up your skirt
ever no
I'm buzzing okay people tell me you're
down so low you can probably see it
I mean are you so you know so small
[Music]
black
I just want to say we're talking about
the ones I'm really wearing really wrong
oh right
okay
[Laughter]
well guess who won
yes
oh that was fun it was fun thinking of
the questions too I hope I hope you
enjoyed this also chat yeah we learned
some things hopefully we got more
knowledgeable about hollow life as a
whole and and then we will now
oh okay we have a few only a few more
questions and then something special as
well at the end
all right all right all right all right
back to the questions
I was wrong
so many things going on wait what was I
trying to open this one
okay you can leave the buzzing system
now girls
thank you
don't worry guys it wasn't something
that will be a problem nothing I know it
was gone really quickly
but don't even don't even think about
looking it up it's not interesting okay
it's not interesting
bgm is back all right next up tell us
about your singing experience what got
you this good what did you learn to get
this good well uh when when I was a
young demon I I joined uh something
called a choir and I did that for eight
years as well as I got two years of uh
training and I also performed a lot and
uh did a lot of um performance uh
competitions
um so uh one might say I'm a little
naturally talented too because even even
at a young young demonic age because of
my demon magic of course I was the kind
of person who got a lot of the solos but
um so maybe it's a bit hard to answer
but I think I think when I when I first
started
I don't think I was actually very good
at the way beginning I thought I was and
I think that motivated me was because I
thought I was really good so my best
advice would be just to not give up keep
going if you have the opportunity to get
lessons do that if you can't there's so
many things on like just YouTube that
you can look up and use like just to
find you know assets assets uh videos
that will help you learn how to sing
help you learn how to warm up help you
learn how to take care of your voice
some of my best recommendations would be
to use those free things that are at
your fingertips if you have the
opportunity do local theater join your
community theater join your local choir
and those will help you naturally grow
as a singer and a performer so good luck
aspiring singers I believe in you so you
already have like so many
um like experience with learning uh in a
very professional you know ways of
singing but we talked about behind the
scenes that we want to learn how to
yodel right yeah that's the next
challenge yodeling
actually since you kind of mentioned
about how to take care of your fruit can
you like maybe is there something like
when your voice is really strained or so
that you do to help it
um the best best thing you can do if you
have a strained voice is literally vocal
rest honey is really really good for
your voice having it in tea is really
good but you can also literally just oh
yeah you can put that directly down
your throat if you want okay you don't
have to
um
I also like uh pepacoa uh pepacoa is
really really good yeah it's a it's like
a herbal dietary supplement you can like
mix in a spoonful into tea and it
soothes your throat so so well it does
have an off taste I know some people
really like it it's yummy it's yummy
it's yummy yeah give me yeah I had some
people think it's yummy I don't think
it's yummy
how do you spell it I put I put it in
for you
pet
yeah yeah actually a lot of uh whole
life Japan Senpai is
a lot of Japanese zippers use this and I
found out like uh unfortunately kind of
late like the middle of my whole
lifetime yeah and since then I've been
uh eliminating the copiest flag as it
also says on the packaging
very good very good yeah
yeah
if you guys want to try it out I think
they have it in a lot of Asian uh
supermarkets and so on you can also just
get it on like you know online shopping
things yeah true true so and they also
have it I I tried they have like little
like uh Licking candies
but I think the best is the the liquid
version that you pour hot water into but
the herbal candies
yeah
of course presents
yeah yeah okay if somebody else and
Alvin ever has throat problems try that
out okay yes if you can find it okay
then I want to ask bibu a solo question
yes
Bijou please rant about MMORPG skull ah
okay I'm gonna go rapid fire because
I've been playing Emma more
I was a baby uh first one was MapleStory
maple story huge fun clothes I like
MapleStory uh very grindy but it gets
better uh the past updates or the future
updates uh let's see oh I really love
like Korean animals as well as Western
ones um let's see uh uh what I play
right now is ff14 ff14 story good end of
end game combat fun uh uh uh Blade and
Soul button so really good are really
fun combat really really really fun uh
Black Desert black deserts
it's so pretty it's so pretty and uh and
the um effects are so pretty and the
characters are so pretty and you can
spend hours in character customization
um
um uh Guild Wars 2 Guild Wars two story
really good you always do a story and
and like interactivity of the world is
really cool um arcade uh PVP super fun
PVP I like killing people in Arcadia was
really fun
um which one was the one that we both
played
because it was pretty old by the time I
started it but it's really cute I like
the animal characters and everything
um and then uh Giana Senpai wants to
play an MMO with me
last year playing protocol together it's
blue protocol a long-awaited Bandai
Namco uh online MMORPG that's already
out there in English now this year it
has been a long wait but next year it's
gonna be out in English finally we're
gonna play together
with these kind of games would you spend
a lot and if yes how much money for cash
up items to look cute
I do not have a limit if it's still cute
look how cute I must in every game MMO
that I play I must have the cutest
character I am sorry that is a
requirement yes if the character
creation is not good I will not play the
game
character creation yes but then you know
you gotta spice it up with some no yes I
will buy outfits yeah and like wings yes
cool uniforms
I get it I used to uh spend all the
pocket money I had on the MMORPG catch
up stuff yeah
I remember asking my parents for the
first time for Maple store I'd be like
hey Mom hey Dad can I use your credit
card uh because I want to find this
thing in the game and they said no and
then I got really well that is very
understandable because you shouldn't use
your parents money for that
and especially if you start using a
credit card for that who knows how much
you will spend yeah that's for
eign
[Music]
do not spoil your child too much when it
comes to animal refugees and stuff like
that and and you got your game really
yeah
it is a rabbit hole this one yeah so
okay thank you Bijou for that I just
wanted to hear you talk very nerdy like
thank you
okay next question is
if you were to write a book what genre
and topic would it be
okay I'd rather write interactive
fiction so anyone who can look at it
they can self-insert as themselves and I
would like to add the ability for
romance or friendship it doesn't really
matter because you would have that
choice and it would be like choice of
game stuff and it could have a little
bit of horror romance and all that good
stuff maybe a little bit of mystery but
but yeah I think you should do it
you should do it someday I've tried I've
tried it before but I can't really
finish a story in terms of like writing
it that's a lot harder so even if I can
program get all the assets and stuff I I
have like too many ideas and I get
roadblocked by myself do you prefer
writing or reading
I prefer reading because I can transport
into like different worlds like that
yeah because I saw you were letting your
fans write so many stories I keep on
seeing them on my Twitter timeline it's
really cool I don't think anyone has
like engaged their community so much in
into writing until now like this much so
you actually read all of those
yeah I I used um like an extension so I
sort things by like the latest of course
my eyes can only travel so much yeah a
lot of people have a lot of pages but
everyone's doing really fantastic and
I'm very proud of them as someone who
also cannot really art that well I know
that there's other Talent venues and
people want to contribute or just like
leave a nice comment and all that yeah I
think that's really nice to give also
the fans who are maybe not so good at
Art a different output to you know show
their creativity like that has there
been some good stuff some spicy stuff
spicy like uh like like spicy or just
good stuff and anything really yeah I
haven't really seen like spicy spicy but
there are some shipping ones and I
really like the ones that have Advent in
it because we're all just like
they talk about the lore how we met each
other how we hang out I think that's oh
that's sweet well maybe maybe they're
too embarrassed to write something spicy
spicy because they know you will read it
I think I would be embarrassed about it
like knowing you you would read it I I I
hi embarrassing yeah no I can't even
think about that I wouldn't I wouldn't
imagine you know you girls doing spicy
spicy spicy stuff no I mean they they
draw it already so yeah
oh okay she got her eyes everywhere the
moment after the teaser even though our
eyes weren't shown there was there was
stuff already oh yeah oh I said so wow
it was already enough to go off with
they were inspired but yeah that's
really
I think it's it's really cool what
you're doing what you're how you're
interacting with your uh community so
awesome keep it up keep it going and
next question I want to hear from
why am I reading in Japanese
do you wear each other's clothes do you
share makeup I want to know about what
you share and what you actually keep
separate
uh-huh
[Music]
yeah so you don't share clothes
so you have like separate wardrobes
closets it's in the same place
yeah yeah maybe it makes sense you maybe
share
um socks at least
ah it depends on my socks are swords
yeah mine are longer so it's not that
hard it's the same material but are you
telling me that you only have short and
long socks specifically
oh
right now we have our clothes is it like
maybe a case of you have the gloves
you're wearing now like 10 times and
that's it
you know we have pajamas too yeah
okay and what else is there like you
know what about toothpaste you share
toothpaste ah toothpaste toothbrush
separate but only an emergency shampoo
um
do you sleep in the same room
yeah yeah
is it separate bits
do you ever you know have a problem with
Ruba like moves around too much in your
top bunk bed and it annoys you oh hi all
the time will be like
obviously
[Laughter]
nice wait what about makeup
do you think we need makeup no but I
mean you know do you share them like
liquid foundations or do you have
different ones or mascara and you see
the space
we do share sunscreen yeah share
sunscreen
the screen is good yeah
what else what else do you share what
could there be
is there something that's very important
to you to keep separate tonight you
don't want to share it at all when it
comes to food
[Music]
are they robotic just to me
girls
oh they might be all robotic to me right
now
[Music]
um
internet connection
did you have I feel like I remember new
debut streams you had different likes
and dislikes and food though oh see we
do have different preferences yeah
I didn't have that right but I like
black but I like it more and then I like
not though but I don't like natto I
would like to I would like to like not
though but I don't like so when whoever
wants to have NATO then I stay out of
the kitchen okay because it's stinky too
yeah okay it's not very appetizing
interesting oh okay okay I think I I
understand
um you know a little bit more about your
habits and all that now actually almost
everything all of you okay okay share
almost everything
then that is the end of the individual
questions for now we are gonna move over
and watch some special videos what could
it be
we're moving are you ready to teleport
yes yes okay yeah teleportation
so I thought we need another fun segment
segment here
um I asked these girls for some
confessions yes yes everybody has given
me a confession about each other I have
uh you know assigned them so
so hear about it what has been on their
minds what has been troubling them or
you know so let's start with
let's start with Bible's confession no
actually no I liked her
listen
[Music]
this is and we have a very important
confession to make about
very concerned
she's really clumsy
way too clumsy yeah whenever she eats
her drinks she spills
you have to lend her stain remover
multiple times in one day yeah he placed
over my water all over the table
yeah she can play elderly and talking is
like a boss yeah where is all this hand
eye coordination
good point
so what does Bijou say to her defense
about this
um all my skill goes to video games and
it doesn't go anywhere else
do you at least clean up your mess and
you have created yeah yeah I did yeah
all together all together it helps me
clean up
um but yes I will say I am probably the
clumsiest one oh the person I always I
was always drunk
admit it
drop stuff and and I knocked over the
water and then I got I got I got stuff
on my dress and I had to get there
then I must ask you I must ask you how
many cracks does your phone have
oh oh I oh
you guys saw my phone right
this is quite a big crack on my phone I
dropped it on my PC and then you can see
you oh my busy I really cracked my phone
so yeah gotta be more careful
for the future because what happens if
like you know maybe up until now you
spilling things and dropping things has
not maybe caused so much trouble
directly to others yet but it could be
that maybe you spill water or drinks
over other people in the future and then
you ruin their dresses not your own so
gotta train your what was it mokuko
the coordination
I will I will try to beat the elegant
princess that I'm dressed up as right
now
okay well maybe maybe for now football
is
is more helpful towards the future with
bijus upon this let's do our best okay
let's support her in her in her journey
of being less porn
to lick things when they're like you
know build
[Music]
and I have a confession about
how dare you be so freaking cute the
moment I met you in my gut instinct
I thought they're way too nice oh dare
they are they trying to lull me to a
false sense of security
but then I realized no they're dogs
they're just this freaking cute
I look forward to spending more time
with everyone in Advent especially my
two favorite pepperonis
the best companion after all right wow
but you have to think you know
no but that was people but don't you
don't you have to like consider people's
like heart problems and all that you
know like you may be causing heart
attacks to people with your cuteness
your smiles make Smiles protect the
smiles anything else is uh not our fault
no you can kill people with cuteness you
know
yeah
okay well it's true I mean it might not
be a responsibility completely but well
it has been has been on shioli's mind
after all so you know I don't think I
think they're perfect just the way they
are as long as they don't use their
claws to Grapple my heart physically
we're fine don't touch my tail don't
touch my ears and you're good yeah but
what if I wish to give you a head Pat
may I have a professional avoid the ears
Yeah scratch behind the ear later
um
[Music]
will you use your big claws if if it was
if it's not followed these rules
will you use the class yes have you used
them before
not yet but well there's been Maybe
but but you don't need to know about
that
they're escaping other crimes they're
still Secrets because they don't want to
go back to prison
Oh we must investigate I'll send this to
Amelia Watson to further investigate
please don't please don't please I have
to it's justice for all of the humanity
you know gotta keep them safe okay next
I want to hear
[Music]
um
there is a confession
this is nurissa ravencroft and I have a
confession to make about shiorin you see
the truth is she's just as clingy with
me and DMS as I am with her
I know she'll deny it to the ends of the
Earth but it's true
what do you say
is that how you see it I'll keep doing
it and if it makes you happy
yeah yeah keep acting all smooth you
can't get away with that forever it's
all that thing it's just me
but then that's good then that means
it's real it's if it's not yeah I think
that's that's good
hey whatever makes you feel better Risa
[Laughter]
it's good to know that she is nice to
you off stream
we will hold on to that for a while okay
and then this is my favorite confession
um
um I was shocked I'll just say I was
shocked okay here you go
Bobby is you I'm Kawasaki Visual and I
have a confession about narissa believe
in craft
My Confession is that when there is an I
met up
she asked me
to touch
my
cutting board and I said okay and then
she did
but it's okay because in return I got to
touch some
pudding
um squishy
[Laughter]
it's okay I'm not shy about it
but honestly I don't quite understand it
I hear many stories about members asking
to touch others boobies if they're
really big but if she has a cutting
board you asked to touch the what the
flattest Justice all boobs are good
boobs you know you might as well touch
them why why should we discriminate
against knives why should big be the
only ones that desire to be touched
Bijou how did you were you like like
what was your what was your reaction
when she asked you
oh I was I was kind of just like okay
sure why not
oh it's that easy huh okay I'll ask you
two I guess yes
you know I was even
like against like touching Martin's
boobs for example like but she forced me
she took my head and put them on her
boobies I don't
need her like a good size
it was just nice to feel appreciated
yeah yeah there's something different
about having it in your hand versus just
looking at it you know when they were so
how did it feel
um nice and soft smooth
very smooth but very soft
Like a Rock like a rock yeah yeah smooth
like a rock but not not hard like a rock
right no smooth yeah maybe yeah it feels
similar
down here uh okay I mean this girl
[Laughter]
my head oh yes your head
not like you know not like a you know
because I I don't like dog smell so much
but you you don't have that so much yeah
I don't smell bad because I'm a good
person yeah oh is that connected
what if they have body odor
oh well the bad people smell bad so all
right time to shower
let's all take a shower after this to be
uh a better person yeah I don't I don't
wanna I don't wanna I wanna spell good
for the girls all right I'll I'll use do
you like perfume though does it confuse
your your snooties
yeah it's not perfect but if it smells
nice then but but
it's good clean is good okay okay I'll
do my best let's go back to this screen
hope you enjoyed those confession videos
yes
you know everybody might have something
on their mind is what I thought so I
just wanted to give them a place to air
it all out and we did that so let's go
back to the questions we have only two
more so don't worry guys and next one is
[Music]
if you would tell you're one of your
future self something now what would it
be I also want to hear what you would
say to your one year past self sorry for
weird English I did not know how to
phrase this
uh let's start with um
[Music]
okay when your future self I would say
hey Vivo uh don't forget to
eat today oh yeah cause she probably
forgot again so don't forget to eat
today Bieber and uh do your best at
whatever you're doing and then
I would say hey people uh don't forget
to sleep because you're probably awake
at 5am right now so go go to sleep
already they'll be fine and also
um
wait wait for the future or like keep
going because the future is so so good
right now and you're very very happy and
every your dreams are coming too so just
hold on a little while along because you
got this yeah I thought so good one okay
how about healing
well I actually already talked to my
past self and that was part of the merch
stuff actually the the voice thing oh so
I'll only talk to my future self okay I
hope that you're getting along with
everyone I hope you've made new friends
yeah I hope your parents are doing well
and that you get to talk to them even
more often and that they're happy and I
hope all of advents are having a lot of
fun together and maybe you have gotten
greedy bodies hopefully but yeah what
did you say
greedy bodies ah afraid anybody yes yes
yes I hope so one year later
I would I would be quite positive about
that yeah
yeah okay yeah good thank you current
president shieldi what about present
Marissa
hmm I guess I guess for my past self for
sure I'd have to say uh keep doing your
best you've got this there's there's
going to be a light at the end of the
tunnel yeah just keep going the long
long long long tunnel
and to my future self I feel like I
probably just say um even if things
might be hard sometimes just to remember
the happiness you were feeling before
and to keep keep using that to power
yourself and to know that there's always
going to be good times ahead if you just
keep trucking through yeah I think
that's a good thing to think about
because you know right now you're still
kind of like all of you I think you're
kind of in a honeymoon phase maybe right
now you just joined things are fun
things are exciting but one year later
maybe one year later you're struggling
with with things maybe things aren't so
easy anymore maybe you've been stressed
out maybe there's a lot of work that you
don't know how to handle but you gotta
keep on going you gotta maybe also
remember
how happy you were on the first days
when you just joined and everything was
so exciting and maybe that will motivate
you right to do your best even when
things look a little bit tough yeah
and what about
ah I guess the the ones here ourselves
in the future the future I guess good
job for like running as fast as he did
when you did
when you're going to Marathon
nobody running
yeah we'll be running just as fast again
but you know but it was good that we ran
then two then two
I guess don't tell myself yeah
that's good that's important yeah yeah
were you doubting yourself a year ago
oh
yeah
it's it's high even like now yeah you
know some days like are difficult you
know but it's important to just be true
to yourself and believe in yourself as
much as you can do I think we all have
you know moments where we doubt
ourselves
but look at you now look where you have
made it so there's absolutely no reason
to doubt yourself girls Advent is strong
strong yes I've been strong together
yeah I asked everybody right this
question yes
then next question is the last one I
kept this one
because I think it still fits what does
her life mean to you I'll start from
very left she already
for me this is my new family if that
makes sense yeah
um ever since I've started everyone has
been very kind hard working and I know
there's a lot of talents to oversee and
all that so I'm just very happy to be
managed so well and to have the help
that I have and I'm really glad that
advent the the people here are my gen
mates so I'm just very pleased you have
great Jen made yeah
yeah sweet a new family what about
this is a hard question for me because
hollow life means a lot to me both as a
fan and now as as a talent yeah I really
don't know if I can put this sort of
question into words uh there's no words
in the English language that I can use
to describe it
it means it means so much to me hello
Life as a fan was there for me in a time
where things things weren't really easy
you know so like as a fan it's really
important to me and now as a talent you
know I feel similar to shiori and like
Advent has been amazing getting getting
to know these wonderful girls and become
so close with them and like to love them
so much and then getting to meet my
amazing Senpai whom I've looked up to is
also just uh so it's a it means it means
a lot to me more than I can ever Express
in words so sorry I hope that's not a
cop-out answer but yeah I'm blushing
happy that you're part of her life all
of you yeah
ah I guess all that to us it's it's like
endless possibility yeah and there's
possibility is to become the the US that
we've always wanted to become so can you
continue to strive
that's great I'm glad you found a place
where you can do whatever you want and
be who you want to be yeah what about
people
hmm I think it means it means so much to
me because uh for the longest time her
life is what kept me motivated I was so
motivated uh because of her life and
like for a lot of my life I was like
doing what I thought I was supposed to
be doing
um like you know going to school I have
to go to school going to work yeah I
gotta do work but all I was something I
wanted to do and I worked so hard
because like I wanted to do it so it
means so much to me and Evans I love I
couldn't imagine better family friends
it was very lonely in jail but it wasn't
as lonely because I had all of them with
me and I love Evan so so much and I was
uh so grateful that we have we're all
like so friendly and and also oh
somebody were so nice and I got to meet
my heroes and yeah it means a lot to me
good answer
yeah I'm happy for you girls I waited so
long for you uh I'm glad we finally have
a new gen bringing some fresh air and
fresh meat into whole life and yeah I'm
looking forward to all the things we
will be doing together as a whole of
whole life English and what you girls
will be doing as Advent and on your own
really curious to see how you girls will
grow uh what you will be achieving and
all that and yeah I hope you will have
the time of your life oh
[Music]
yeah okay so thank you so much girls for
being here in Hollow talk and actually
with this uh timing this day today the
collab then for within whole life
English has been lifted for you girls so
I know some of you have collabs coming
up and I think next is actually video
right you have a collab with Cali yes
yes in a few hours
so that would be fun and exciting I'm
sure uh to mingle and have fun together
and yeah maybe maybe there's some others
planned already coming up very soon so
it's it's time it's time to unleash
Advent same to all of English
are you excited excited
okay so thank you Chad for coming to the
special episode of whole talk I hope it
was uh fun for you guys this little
little uh difference different a little
bit different than usual but maybe we
can do it again whenever a new gem comes
out uh I would be glad to do so it was
my honor to have you girls uh collab
Virginia
it wasn't my intention but you know I
was just excited you know when you hear
of Columbus is over on this day then you
know kind of quickly weekend is usually
a whole talk day after all so yeah thank
you for being here thank you for being
so Cooperative honestly you girls are
the best you always reply so fast girls
very professional please keep that up
please tell your one year uh later
selves to still be so fast and replying
too
I would appreciate it yeah understood uh
at the end of my streams I usually say
and in German we say of readers in would
you like to say that together with me
yes oh yeah it's German you should join
in at the Alf vidazen okay can you say
it slowly once
okay everybody
and in German we say
as always feel free to use the whole
talk hashtag to tell me your thoughts
about the Stream
oh come on
[Music]
foreign