[Music]
y
what's up iron chaos the end EV event a
St is trapped in a cage advice your best
friend Bel takers from Hol life
[Music]
English
H
hello oh witness
me I don't know why recently I've been
forgetting the witness
me I don't know
why
M um the time has
come ladies and ladies and Gent
gentlemen the the the time has come
for do you guys know what day it is
tomorrow
um I have like a yogurt drink strawberry
flavor to celebrate the
occasion yes is the 29th of
February do you know what day that
is it's Thursday yeah do you know what
day that is happy Thursday everyone it's
my
birthday it's my birthday in 1 hour I so
excited it's my very first
countdown okay he um so we have a we
have a lot of um guests calling in guest
friends I make it sound very intense but
it really isn't I'm just like hello are
you free would you like to call in all
right
cool um so last year I did a call in
where I just want I just asked everyone
to sing me a birthday song because it
wasn't my birthday this year I actually
have a question prepared I had a
question prepared for everyone and the
question is um if you could get me me
one present what would it
be
and yeah so be like just one question
and then everything outside of that one
question is just we just we just we just
talk
for
[Laughter]
uh
yeah 1.3
billion 1300 million what congrats on
being a teenager thank you I'm so
excited oh I also uh we have two I
always wanted to say thank you I have I
I may have stolen some of your brats uh
the pictures from the brats from Twitter
I stole some there's so many gifts um
there was only one that I didn't the the
New York Times Square One I haven't put
up yet cuz I couldn't find a picture of
it yet but there's the there's the bus
WAP and then there's the themed Cafe and
then there's the subway sign board and
there's operation PP there's so many
gifts thank
you thank you thank you so
[Music]
much this so cool um there's also a
cameo video that I haven't watched yet
but I'm thinking of watching that we
have a little break during um when it
crosses over to midnight when it's
actually my birthday um so I'll watch it
then also there are some guests who sent
videos instead um of of calling in
because SAS it is so early in the
morning right now that it probably I I
understand I
understand I'm so excited thank you so
much um
also why am I butterfly I'm a
butterfly
I'm good I just ched a little bit I'm a
butterfly I'm flying hold
[Music]
up should we call in our first
guest
uh I'm going to
die
uh
man moth who just called me a who just
called me a moth excuse me
o
o happy birthday to
you m I have a I have a birthday gift to
you
wait I thought she was
singing huh I thinking is your birthday
gift I thought I thought you were
singing a song and then you stopped like
after the first
line hello wait introduce
yourself hello hello hello thank you so
much for coming good morning
hello look at it's my birthday
gift happy birthday hot for
you did you say it's a
hot
h h
[Applause]
[Music]
hold on I need to do some some some
movie Magic movie Magic let me do some
let me do some movie Magic right here
okay you know you know what's name is it
that high
what's the name of the hot please tell
me a Jal Jing
H genital Jing hot oh my
God pee peee
peee
pee how do I explain pee pee PE pee is
um the thing that does
[Music]
the
j j j is the basic game of
o
[Music]
bit just said
that I feel like we're going to get
bonked no I'm sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry I
do what something something on your head
a thank
[Laughter]
[Music]
you why is it on her head where else am
I supposed to put it
huh where am where else am I supposed to
put it I don't
know this is okay it's it's beautiful it
looks like a h it's beautiful thank you
so much it's beautiful thank you thank
you so much Ah that's the answer that's
the answer of question this is what you
give me for my for my birthday yeah peee
hat a peee hat yeah a peee hat thank you
very much yeah it's like the it's like
the potty hats that you wear at when you
go to a birthday party party panty party
panties PTY PE py PE hat pee pee hat pee
hat M thank you so much for your
wonderful gift and thank you so much for
[Music]
coming
Dad Dad byebye
byee we've started off strong ladies and
gentlemen we've started off
[Music]
strong um I hope you like the new
addition to to we've got wings and we've
got a peee
hat let's go to the next person
maybe
[Laughter]
spe
[Music]
fore
for
speech
fore for
Fore
[Music]
for
I don't know wow oh my god oh it's a
[Laughter]
crazy
yeah oh
yeah I
I I am dancing dancing very
very
feeling
H body
language H body
langage big love
you
for
[Music]
fore okay
[Laughter]
fore
[Music]
okay
happy birthday after after 30 minutes
later yes thank you thank you byebye me
everyone byebye than byee oh I love you
to
[Music]
to I feel like this is the most unhinged
to to have done in a while also we're
already 1 minute behind I'm so sorry to
everyone who's like later in who who who
has a later time maybe 5 minutes wasn't
enough it is what it is is it cuz it's
my birthday God
damn
Ziggy happy
birthday to
you happy
birthday
to
in happy
birthday
to
you w Harmon
harmonization yeah
harmonization I'm surprised thank thank
you I wanted to do or say h at first
part so I I
[Laughter]
couldn't um it's not um I don't thing so
my my J you
wasted I had a not Wast it did you eat
it
afterwards yeah yeah yeah
yeah I had a two meon pants oh my
God why were you mad at my mle pants
yeah I wasn't
mad yeah yeah many people said so same
thing so it's awkward or it's
uncomfortable uncomfortable
uncomfortable please return
[Laughter]
my
your your Japanese are getting more
fluent these days I
[Music]
think you said
only
it's where did you where did you know
there
[Laughter]
historical
anime are you watching hisorical anime
Japanese hisorical anime really oh m
how can I translate n in English if you
it's kind of like oh
um
like
translate how do I
translate it's kind of
like somehow I'm sorry kind of
sorry my bad kind of sorry it doesn't
have the same
ring y y I'm really happy thank
you
okay so you remember the memory of
Yokohama together in Japan so you
enjoyed um Cafe petto Cafe right animal
Cafe yes yes yes and you said you liked
capy oh yes yeah right soy Flappy yeah I
will give you Cy
[Music]
Cy B so big it's so big bir so I think
she's going to buy me one cyy oh my God
Cy yeah do do you want two I would I
would like many thank you many Happy
happyy Farm okay so so for for the for
giving you the capy B you must live in a
big house
[Music]
it's all right they can sleep on the bed
I sleep on the floor okay on the floor
instead of bed okay okay thank you yeah
anyway happy birthday happy birthday
enjoy your birthday thank
youe bye
bye bye
[Music]
bye 5 minutes isn't
enough
yeaha 5 minutes is not
enough I done
[\h__\h] I done
goofed he baby happy birthday hi
ol Y how are you enjoying your birthday
this has been it's only you're the
fourth person in and this has already
been the most unhinged tosu I've ever
done and I don't know
why huh I don't know
why save me Ollie okay don't worry I
will be say so oh
okay so um four years
huh yeah it's crazy isn't it and God
dang you even spent the last 28 days
streaming nonstop with so many programs
yeah yeah yeah are you streaming right
now oh yeah sorry
hi
hi sorry even though you're busy thank
you I I actually forgot that it was like
right now and I was like oh it is okay
thank you thank you so much for coming
my pleasure yeah well I won't keep it
too long but did you have a did you
think about a birthday gift you would
get me I I did so like you know I did a
lot of thinking okay because I actually
do not know what you actually like what
do you mean everything you've got to me
I'm just
like I know but I don't know you're like
you know like actual interest like do
you like bath bombs do you like this do
you like that do you like soaps I don't
know those kind of stuffs I like
everything and so I thought about it and
since you um since you wall climb wall
climb was it called Boulder bould Bing
yeah yeah since you do bouldering and
since you go to the gym I thought about
getting you pop
Flex you oh my God yes it's the brand
that I always want to get but I'm just
like it's too
expensive yeah if if I ever have a
chance I actually want to get you that
a a thank you ollie you're welcome a but
is there actually anything that you want
like really not
really oh I W um I think if if you know
a lot of people in like my family stuff
have been asking me as well like oh what
what would you want for your birthday
and stuff like that and I'm just like
just get me something for the JP shed
a so you know I don't know buy me knives
I don't know knives you actually want
knives bro I would kill
four wait what I would what you would
kill no the things I would do for a high
quality Knife Set BR and those things AR
cheap just tell I'm just
saying I mean yeah but like actually
like cooking knives right like nothing
else yeah yeah
yeah
B
yeah I'm very Bamboozled right now um
anyway
anyways um I you get me a knife set I
would get you a knife set I actually
found this one cute knife shop so like
they have like all sorts of uh colored
knives there was actually this one set
and it has your colors it has teal and
it has red ooh actually I want to buy it
to you but I don't know how I'll bring
it to Japan honestly oh you can bring ni
you just got to put in your check
baggage I think ah yeah do you want
knives I can get you
knives I never turn down
knives okay thanks Mom you're welcome
thank you so much for calling even
though you're busy I appreciate it and
thanks for having me I'm sorry Dad I
can't talk much um no it's my fault I I
no how is it your fault you're having
your birthday no as in like I'm already
behind as well I should have 5 minutes
wasn't enough I was like 5 minutes is
enough to talk to everyone no it's not
it's not enough but yeah man thank you
man I love you it's okay though yeah I
love you too have a lovely birthday K
tomorrow yeah look forward to my live
dream catch it don't forget to catch it
guys thank you
all right I love you babe I want to talk
to you
later bye-bye
[Music]
byebye
Happ
[Music]
KY
hi
for I am forever indebted to
you
[Music]
[Laughter]
for
happy
[Music]
birthdaye
[Laughter]
hi
hi hi
[Music]
I want
to yes yes
[Music]
yes
byebye musy
musy
foree
spee
[Music]
speee
[Laughter]
fore
wow
[Laughter]
[Applause]
fore
[Music]
for
fore
[Music]
spee
[Laughter]
[Music]
fore
foree
[Laughter]
[Music]
for
come come
here come here he come
this
it's been unhinged the entire what is
going on this has been this is the best
Tatsu I've ever
experienced the best the very best we've
got 15 minutes oh hello hello oh hello
hello have a birthday thank you wait
what your your voice matches your
profile pictures so
well yes that's that's my whole energy
right
there hello how are you doing I'm doing
good how are you doing all of those
preparations I'm good I'm so I'm so
unhinged right now but it is what it
is
good good because because yeah um you're
chaos and I need you to be unhinged yes
more and more more and more yes okay I
will be more unhinged more and more I
suppose yes
nice man thank you so much for calling
in um I don't know if you guys new but
this isai is also another guest at my
birthday how how what is your what is
your take on the performance without
giving too much
away it was fun the most I can say is it
was fun cuz I'm afraid that I will spoil
anything so I will just say it was fun
it is going to
be so fun because I'm actually really
enjoying it myself oh I'm so I'm so glad
you thought that thank you so much for
agreeing to be a part of it as well
thank you for inviting oh my God okay
guys it's going to be
so just just so big so epic oh my God
yes thank you I do I'll do my best I
going to do my best
thank you yes um now I have a question
for you okay if you were to get me a
birthday present what would it be i'
okay I have a good reason to give you
this but this is just a what if question
so I have like an alternative to it so
if I could give you a gift I will give
you a
[Music]
house I have a reason for that I have a
reason for that yes cuz if I give you a
house you will never know whether I live
in your walls or not oh because you'd
have the
key I have spare key most likely what if
I just changeed I mean okay I I still
take it new
house new
house but because I probably don't have
enough money for that probably I will
just give you a miniature a miniature
like a dough house mhm bro I would love
love that I like collecting those kind
of stuff so yeah I see those shorts
where they like decorate their dollhouse
and they find the miniature furniture
and I'm like how does how does this
exist it's so cute oh my God it's so
cute and nowadays though doll houses can
be something like a place to put your
Hol life merch
so you're a genius and I put I put Hol
life merch and then I'll put my Barbies
right next to it it's going to be
perfect yes
yeah thank once again though happy
birthday thank you thank you thank you
thank
you well I hope everyone enjoys um
beautiful cute this tomorrow as well so
please come and watch it watch it
everybody don't miss it yay thank you so
much for
coming thank you thank you for calling
thank see you later bye bye bye
bye we should start a count of how many
times I Shield the live for tomorrow
honestly it's my birthday I can do
whatever the [\h__\h] I want doesn't
matter I get birthday
privileges all
right chill it more I have a live
tomorrow guys all right
next
[Music]
oh man I feel like as we wait for the
next person I can breathe a little bit
oh wow we just zoomed through 1 2 3 4 5
6 seven seven guests
already isn't that
crazy that here live I have a birthday
live tomorrow yeah it's kind of
crazy Let's see we can maybe try the
next person for
now it's in 12
minutes I get the m a call
I'm a little bit nervous with this
one
[Music]
huhy happy
birthday
spee
happy
birth yeah Al's birthday was two days
ago
so it was
yesterday
fore
[Music]
[Laughter]
for
[Music]
hi
foree
spee
[Music]
fore
[Laughter]
for
[Music]
fore for you happy
birthday
[Applause]
[Music]
fore
fory
yeah
is my face flushed oh my goodness I
scored a date yo I'm winning and with
that being said we only have 5 minutes
left until my actual birthday but oh my
goodness man she's really
funny that's the way to my heart
comedy yeah no Ian members yet don't
worry I systematically put it designed
it designed the totsa that way so they
could get get a couple more hours of
sleep cuz I know it's very early for
most of them okay now we can calm down
for a second uh I've have I inserted a
little break in between um so that we
can watch it cross over midnight and
also I wanted to watch some of the
videos and the presents after uh
presents as well um before we continue
on with the totsu hi guys how you doing
how's the totsu been so far holy [\h__\h]
it's nearly been an hour what the
heck
Hello
unhinged this been
something man this is the problem I'm
having I'm feeling with tsus these
days um I remember my very first Tatsu I
mean I said I say you this every single
Tatsu but I just
the very first tattoo 3 minutes felt too
long and then now I guess 3 years later
my I feel like every person needs at
least 10
minutes but it is true it's cuz I gotten
to know people so much better now
and is less awkward yeah it feels weird
to actually have to ask a question
that's what it like I feel like we could
have I didn't maybe maybe preparing the
question was a bad choice we could have
just talked without answering the
question oh well we'll know for next
time
[Music]
minutes oh my God you know what I wanted
to do where I need to get my phone hold
on I want to see my Twitter
balloons that's what I wanted to do I
want to see my Twitter
balloons I need a
screenshot screenshot my Twitter
balloons
okay that's probably the one thing I've
looked forward to most is seeing my
Twitter
balloons yes I can only see it once
every four years isn't that crazy you
can pop them on PC I think someone said
someone told me about that
but damn you don't get them on the 28th
nope
easily entertained it's not the fact
that I'm easily entertained it's just
that the entertainment is is is
unreachable to my fingertips every every
four it's only every other every 3 years
for 3 years you guys been popping
balloons and having the time of your
life I got to wait four times that
amount of time
okay one more
minute
I don't know the seconds I don't see the
seconds so I don't know when it's
actually going to
turn I also have pudding prepared
but I don't know if I'm going to eat
that just stare at the clock this is the
longest minute I've ever experienced
hello
why is
it
hello
[Music]
happy birthday
B thank you
everyone
[Applause]
oh
Master thank you everyone woohoo woohoo
woohoo oh actually have I wanted to
change
the happy birthday happy birthday
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday to me happy birthday to me
happy birthday happy birthday happy
birthday to
[Music]
me
yes my
[Music]
balloons woo
oh my God I'm taking so many screenshots
oh my God a the
balloon oh my
[Music]
God oh my
God
[Music]
oh that's it
okay which one is the
[Music]
best I like this one
no wait I can always go back let's take
some
more does only come up
once
[Music]
so many
balloons o I like wait I like this one
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
thank you
[Music]
everyone should we just keep the
birthday one for the rest of the
stream does any can anyone get sick of
listening to the birthday song I
wonder is that
possible she's the T should I get the
pudding maybe I should get the
pudding I was like maybe I should get
cake but I was like I don't want to eat
cake at midnight should I get the
pudding get the pudding all right get
the
pudding congrats on turning 12 babe but
I'm 13 I'm a teen n
don't test me it's not a face um I
bought some Dy good new pudding number
one is my stomach going to die from this
maybe wait I have a Al tomorrow
though it'll be
fine I
think she's becoming em
mom get out of my
room oh it look so
pretty it's not a oh my God can I
actually tell you a funny story it's the
most godamn Papa rat moment I've ever
seen in my life I'm experiencing Papa
rra moments even though I'm not in
Australia
ow
[Music]
can I tell you a story
so I I've been so busy recently
especially this past week I haven't been
able to call so I've been like chatting
with ratf on Al like group
chat and I sent the link of of my of my
birthday live to the group chat and I
was like hi everybody it's the big show
tomorrow and then you know Mama rat was
the first to send like five messages in
a row like it was claps balloons cake
and then it was um what time is it even
though it says the time right there and
I was like oh it's probably this time
and then she was like okay love hot love
hot love
hot and then 2 hours later do you know
what papar rat sends he sends a link
like a YouTube link and I'm like what
like not saying
anything and um I opened the link it was
a video tutorial of how to install a car
interface monitor into your like the
centerpiece monitor into your car I'm
like
Dad
Dad I don't know I don't know prior I
don't know why he sent it
there you know what
whatever
[Music]
I guess he just wanted to share that he
was installing a cent like a
center what do you call it a center
Center monitor thing into his
car thanks Dad it's not like it's my
birthday it's not like it happens once
every 4
years that's fine I'm
fine oh s a console that's what it
is thanks
[Music]
Dad anyway I just wanted to share that I
thought that was really
funny thank you so much for all the all
the love oh my God I just realized chat
hasn't been on screen this entire
time should I add you oh my God
I'm so sorry I totally
forgot sorry
guys I was so
preoccupied with everything
else professional
[Music]
streamer
hello oh chat doesn't even
work oh there it
goes oh
wow
h
Hello
broken is it cuz chat's going too
quick
bro
broken thank you so much for the Super
Chat thank
you
oh
interesting interesting very interesting
all right I have to keep you open for
some reason all right there we go I
fixed
it I fixed it wa we only okay um the
tots is resuming at 9 at 15 minutes I
want to read some of the gifts wait what
read some of the gifts what read I want
to watch some of the
videos um that we were sent and also I
want to watch the the Cameo video I'm
so I'm so curious thank you guys so much
for the present um Monday toown sent it
to me yesterday was like your fans got
you this as well and I was like oh thank
you so
much but I I tried not to I didn't look
at it so I didn't thank you guys you
guys you guys gave me so much this
[Music]
year oh I think I know what what the
problem
is
oh
broken uh you know what chat you guys
are just too powerful for this stream
I'm going to keep you off for
now thank you all right let me get the
video
[Music]
ready and you guys named it for BA thank
you it's so sweet
okay who's it
from happy bday enjoy this little Cameo
that we have gotten from a special
greeting Bells HOV it's me Rodan from
Bayonetta I've received a message from
your fans the brats telling me that it's
your birthday for real this time you're
turning uh what 13 years old hey they
really also want to let you know that
they care about you lot and appreciate
everything you've done for
them now ain't that beautiful hey be
sure to swing on by the gates of hell
and I'll whip up some drinks for you
just make sure you don't forget to pay
up I don't take kindly to people who
don't pay their
time don't act too purple around me
either you
hear anyway happy birthday bells or Bell
ear whatever the hell they calling you
these days it's me Rhoden don't cross
me oh by the way this birthday message
once again is from the brats see
you holy
[\h__\h] it's
Ren yo that was so good what the heck
that's so
cool thank
you oh my God oh my
God oh my
God oh my God wait so now I have B do
what wait is my memory serving me wrong
I swear I got a Bayonetta one last year
or some some
sometime now
Ren yeah I have Jean right Jean I think
I did right I'm collecting all the
bayoneta cameos oh my god dude his
voice that's crazy Roden swing on by to
the to the gates of
Hill thank
you oh my God I'm so happy thank you
that's so cool oh my God you guys did so
much for me this year thank
you no I didn't expect any the sub okay
the Subway crazy the theme Cafe crazy
bus wrap crazy crazy New York Time
Square crazy then you're adding this on
top of that you
[Music]
guys thank
you thank you
I hope he genu genuinely thinks you're
13 what do you mean I am 13 billion
years
old thank you that was amazing oh my
god dude the fact that his voice already
sounds like that through what I'm
guessing is his phone screen can you
imagine just hearing that in studio
quality I can't oh my God I
can't
wait
[\h__\h] I have other videos that I was
supposed to watch [\h__\h] um we might have
to push everyone a little bit later or
should I watch it at the
end or should I watch it at the end um I
maybe I can watch it at the end it
should be okay I wasted time or I can
show one we watch it at the end it's
fine it's fine it's fine don't mess with
the schedule everything's fine
um
[Music]
flon Mach X Fon Drew this for me and
wish me a happy
birthday thank you
Fon it's so cute oh my God it's so
cute look at that I didn't realize they
could draw that well wow that's crazy
thank you so
much I put that I'm put I'll put
that I'll put that right here and then
the ticket will go right here
perfect red children true no one's
commented on my wings
I just realized no one has commented on
my wings is this normal for everyone or
did they just already give up on me
anyway I'm a
butterfly it looks like a bow
oh anyway let's continue the
tosy oh I did have play On's picture I
just put it
here
yes next
guest ah
G happy birthday
B steel rose trapped in a cage of ice
you've been witnessed thank you I've
witnessed you
thank you Callie thank you so much for
calling in yeah no problem happy
birthday it's my birthday I didn't know
it's my birthday oh [\h__\h] that's the
first time I heard about that oh man
Color Me surprise yeah I got even be did
you know that I have a 3D live today no
way wait what the heck can I come yeah I
was going to say did you know that you
were also a guest wait really I did that
yeah you did
no way oh man I must have been in some
kind of like stuper I don't remember
doing it I can't wait to see
it hype hype hype no I I can't so it was
so oh my God I wanted to talk about this
on stream like give them a little little
little little hint um but our rehearsal
I think I laughed the hardest I've ever
laughed during our rehearsals same it
was so much fun some of the moves some
of the things we were doing were just so
ridiculous I I couldn't help but just it
was really funny and not to mention
there was also some exhaustion in
certain
areas if you catch my you'll see you'll
see you'll see you guys will see yeah we
were very tired in a certain place
afterward but you'll just have to watch
yeah yeah yeah you'll have to watch it
was a good time it was such just still
so much fun I had so much fun dancing
with
you we got we got to do it more in the
future I mean we've already kind of like
you know like a couple dance practices
together but but let's let's dance some
more together
[Music]
cuy yeah and I need to I need to work on
perfecting my technique because I'm
always like kind of glancing over at you
and I'm like all right got to get the
moves perfect just like ba oh no you do
great you do great you do great you
already do great thanks so much for for
inviting me so that I can kind of like
learn and like dance more you know
really had a lot of fun so yeah and
dancing's not about being perfect it's
about having fun if you're having fun
you're doing it right expressing
yourself yeah yeah yeah yeah cool oh
yeah yeah yeah I've got a question for
you yeah if you were to get me a
birthday gift what would it be well I
already did
here this is your this is your special
birthday
Binky what for you I made this for you
it's oh my God you're 13 years old old
now and so I have crafted I've
handcrafted a little a little Binky for
you it's a little pacifier oh my
word you're 13 now is it cuz I'm 13 now
yeah this is
13-year-olds why does that made Binky
what I mean I I don't know I just kind
of I felt like I felt like it was a
crowning hey plenty of people still suck
on pacifiers when they're 13 okay it's
very normal should I be worried what no
no no no no it's just you know birthday
Binky I just thought that you know it
would be perfect for you no not saying
you're a baby child or anything like
that it just you
know I don't I've never seen you with
like a pacifier before so I just kind of
it's not normal okay well maybe it's not
normal but there are people that still
suck on a paci ofier when they're 13
okay don't make them feel left out yeah
really I mean my my sister right she
she's been sucking her thumb since she
was
born yeah she's like Z years Infinity
yeah Infinity years old but she still
sucks her thumb yeah sometimes I look
over she's sucking her thumb
yeah to be like this is this the
confession no I do not hey look she's
sucking on a
binky the colors came out a little
darker than I thought they would but you
know what it works it it
works it looks perfect for you look it
says I'm 13 on it in comic Sands comic
Sands thank you you're welcome so
everybody knows you're 13 now but to
answer your question actually I I just
came back from a from a vacation and I
got some souvenirs for you I'll give
them to you next time I see you a real
happy birthday gift oh thank you you
didn't have to thank you I wanted to I
wanted to cuz it's your special day a
yeah I'm so happy thank you you're
welcome also I wanted to say I'm
extremely proud of you thank you're
always doing so much great stuff and and
I think it's also really cool because
you're so passionate about like making
music and stuff like that and I just
think that you know this is this is
really wonderful that you get to have
like a 3D show to like show the world
even more how hardworking you are when
it comes to music stuff and it's really
you deserve that and more so come learn
from the best no
no no no no no no yes it's true though
yeah congrats on your cover by the way
it's sick thanks bro thanks man I
appreciate it big UPS man I'm glad you
like everyone go listen to C's new cover
it's so sick I'm going to give you a hug
hey everybody go watch B everybody here
already is going to go watch your
birthday and then so I hope so I can't
really I can't really give a good
advertisement right now but I will
tomorrow during go watch the 3 live yeah
yeah well it'll be really fun I guess I
guess that's about it I don't want to
take too much of your time no I should
have scheduled more
Man 5 minutes is too is too short true
we could go on forever and ever though
to be honest you yeah wouldn't it be
great May if we could we' had something
to do that with like I don't know like a
podcast maybe yeah that's a good idea is
that crazy let's do that yeah yeah yeah
nice idea wouldn't that be insane let's
try that out yeah sounds good maybe
we'll think about it yeah yeah sure we
can write up a plan and like you know
see where it goes maybe all right Poss
eventually all right with that being
said I'm your Mory and make sure that
you get some sleep some good sleep
because we have a big day tomorrow yeah
true true true all right I finished I'll
see you later bed and then I sleep yes
yeah sounds good and don't fall asleep
with the binky in your mouth cuz you
might choke and die and then I'll have
to come and visit you and that won't be
good oh that'll be very awkward before
your birthday I will Roger that Roger
you copy I copy copy copy thank you oh
bye-bye
byee peace
man I look Kei I look
Kei thanks
Kelly
cute
I got tend down the music for
this good
morning who are you who Am I who are you
who am
I are you perhaps the N my
inan oh I'm
N I am I think you are I am are you
eer of the
floor no I'm ener of the desk cuz I've
been waiting for a for for for an hour
cuz I got the time wait really I'm so
sorry oh my God no I was like oh yeah I
totally will be awake I woke up I sat
down prepar my drinkies I was like yeah
ready to celebrate and then I looked at
the time just like I got an hour left
I'm so sorry no why are you sorry it's
my fault no thank you for coming I know
it's really
early thank you for coming my sleep
schedule as you have known is all over
the place so it is not is never early
nor too
late I still remember the other time we
were like just talking and you were like
oh I need to go to sleep good night I
just like me too good night and then
you're just like I like what aren you
what that's not oh good I was like hold
on a second the math ain't mathing
what's going on something is
wrong man but I feel like ena's sleep
schedule is just in a constant I I don't
know what's happening I gave up I gave
up as last time I came back from Japan I
was like yeah I'm going to fix it and
then yeah I gave up it's it's not it's
not happening it's not it's not
happening well it's
so I'm very happy you could call in
because n my inness you are a precious
guest of a certain 3D live that's
happening today at 12: p.m jst dream
catcher what
what did you know what is that why I ran
into you so many times last time God is
that why I saw you every day for like a
week is that why is that
what how was your now people finally
know it's like I was like I want to talk
about it but I know it's it's like I
can't talk about it until it's anoun MH
it all it wasn't a coincidence that I
ran into her all the
time I think even the days where like I
wasn't I guess like in the studio or
have to be in the studio I was like hey
B can I can't come H
out I'll be like yeah yeah I need a desk
yeah bro I got you
yeah so yeah oh my goodness I can't wait
cuz whatever whatever I saw those days
it's amazing so I know that I know that
it'll be great and the fact that you
made me move so
much you did great you did great you did
great you you did so great I'm so proud
of you I tried I'm so proud of you
you're so cute guys come watch Ena be be
be be amazing come watch Ena the ENA who
got off her floor for me I know the ENA
who actually moved rather than just
moving her arms is
there oh thank you so much for thank you
so much for moving for me what um any
time for you B anytime thanks man thanks
man he time thumbs up thanks
man um but real quick if you you could
get me a birthday gift what would it be
oh I actually prepared something except
except someone someone already did
something similar and then now I'm just
like mine looks kind of what inferior to
that so I'm was like well I don't I
don't know if you like it or not but
maybe you can find the use for it
tur no no no it's a it's
no you know I appreciate youa I love
it I love
ITA I love how it's it's it's named Ms
pain I love it
oh I love it I forgot my screenshot
program
names a I love it wow what a deal the
the the the rent of Ena coupon you can
you can use it for anything um from you
know um I don't know from a collab that
I cannot refuse to like you know
accompanying you to um dinner or
something like that wait it has an
expiry date oh in years okay okay yeah
got you I mean I could have made it like
yesterday but you
know imagine you gave me a rented Ena
coupon that expired yesterday I like oh
oh what what a shame I get subscribed
yesterday a I love it thank you I can't
wait to hang out with you
again let's go have fun I still owe you
a meal you do yeah remember the Mario
Party collab from like way back I feel
like we had this conversation like five
times or something last time every time
you're just like I owe you a meal I'm
just like you do
yeah well then this it's just not just
me you though it's the others too that
were part of the true I just ow I owe
everybody a meal but thank you so much
we'll have a we'll have a banquet yeah
we yes okay well happy birthday I happy
a great one I can't wait to see you be
true Idol in your live yeah everyone
make sure to check it out I'm going to
go back to rolling on the floor yeah
sleep well
okay okay
bye
bye God damn I love in you why am I
already late how is that possible how am
I
already I'm 5 minutes behind schedule
even though I started on time how is
that possible I'm so I'm so sorry people
guests I just want to talk to you guys
I'm so
sorry I'm sor oh sorry I'm
late
hello
oh oh Kitty
[Music]
hi
hi what's wrong what's wrong what's
wrong kept me waiting H I'm so
sorry no I'm appalled 5 minutes waiting
time that's so sorry so rude you know
what the next person can wait 10 minutes
how about that no it's okay I actually
also just like Ena I waited like um over
an hour cuz I also somehow thought was
an hour earlier yeah I'm sorry no it's
it's actually more convenient uh to be
at this time so all good all good in the
neighborhood happy
birthday you happy
birthday oh my God your first birthday
my first birthday K is my first birthday
nah we celebrated your birthday every
year it doesn't matter it doesn't matter
yeah but I didn't have a day that was
like me being like hey guys it's not my
birthday but like can you say happy
birthday to me but then this year I
actually have a day where i'm like it's
my birthday you know this is your day
it's it's the bay
day yay bayday happy bayday thank you so
much I miss your break I hope you had a
good a good break oh thank you yeah uh
I'm back I'm back yay welcome back yeah
so Bae are you excited for your 3D Live
you you have no idea actually I think
you would have an idea yeah I have an
idea you have an idea yeah no she knows
I'm so excited yeah I know the feeling
it's your first like after your Frey
debut this is your first you know
project thingy so I'm sure it's super
exciting
I'm sure you practice so hard all the
coral learning all the coral
tomorrow okay I'll watch you I have
probably nothing else to do wait no no I
think the life is at 4:00 a.m. for me
4:00 a.m. watch it when you wake
up yeah I I'll watch the vog yay thank
you me you're welcome I hope you get to
do a lot of these kind of things cuz I
know it's like in your blood oh my your
your thing thing you it's our thing I
want to do more
together oh
wow maybe I'll invite you to my upcoming
birthday then oh that yeah I already I
already have a plan I already made a
power point oh my God power point oh I'm
so yeah you don't know but you're part
of the power point I'm part of the power
oh my God spoilers but oh yeah a little
bit of spoilers fine I mean who knows if
it's even going to happen like what if
you turn it down like what if you reject
it could still be like it's not certain
I will commit Sudoku if I reject
something like that from
you there's no need there's no need you
have the power of decision
making it's called advertising says
someone in your chat that is true it's
advertising half a year ahead of time or
so I'm not even half year this five four
four months four months four yeah oh wow
I mean damn yeah cuz like yeah beginning
of July time is ticking and going by
fast it really is it's going so
fast y man so you are uh permanently
located in Japan now right uh yeah
pretty much wow do you have furniture
I I went to big camera the other day
they don't I mean Furniture is not
really nerving why did you go to big
camera I had to buy a fridge Ki a fridge
partment didn't come with a fridge bu no
I had to buy all the appliances uh from
what the [\h__\h] cuz it's like a it's like
a new place so yeah but like fridge is
like pretty basic like I bought a fridge
I felt so adult damn big fridge eh no I
actually I was like theoretically I
would like a bigger fridge but if I'm
being realistic am I going to use all of
this space probably not so I got like a
a medium smaller smaller
fridge okay you're welc what about a
kitchen do you have a kitchen yes I do
was the kitchen there but no no fridge
or what yeah oh yeah that's interesting
okay damn I want to check out your place
is there like what about the other forid
do you have a bed uh yeah I do I got bed
I got I got a couch you're welcome to
stay on my couch whenever does it fit a
WWA it does it fits three wahas actually
oh three wahas oh [\h__\h] three wahas okay
okay I'll bring the other waas too then
I splurged on a on a nicer couch because
I have like whenever family or friends
come I'm like hey you can take the couch
and it's just a nice couch oh I'm really
curious to see her play that's exciting
yeah congratulations thank you so much
that's like a a huge step to get like
your own place in a completely different
continent I've never moved out before
and I the first time I'm doing it is
overseas such a baby I've moved out like
when I was so young like 16 holy [\h__\h]
and who who knows how old I am now but
um yeah I've moved a million times I've
been living alone pretty much almost
ever since so if you need advice on how
to live your life
alone um I'm sure you have many other
people to talk to but uh I I could also
help yes I'm going to I'm going to hit
you up with the w my FR isn't
working what the break box oh yeah oh
okay to be honest those kind of things
I'm also like I don't know when if my if
all the electricity goes out and
whatever with the breaker breaks like I
don't really know what to do either to
be honest oh I see
okay I'm just lucky that the breaker
didn't break so far I see I see wow
yeah uh to answer your question of if I
were to get a birthday present would you
give
me um so I I had many thoughts but I
think I will settle like I I see I could
probably give you like a really
unrealistic uh thing like that's like it
doesn't have to really happen right like
but I think I'll say something that
could possibly happen so um I see you
doing like cooking streams every now and
then too
right yeah and uh I thought because it's
kind of also my thing to do cooking
streams I thought maybe you would like
to learn from Wawa how to make Austrian
schniter yo I'm not going to lie I saw
that recipe once it popped up on like a
recommended website that I was scrolling
and I was like I want to I want to
learn oh I can teach
it's Austrian snit it's uh it you can
make it in a with a with different kinds
of meat but usually it's like pork or uh
like cough
cough yeah and it's like breaded right
and then you kind of like fry it in oil
make it puffy and fluffy and then uh
usually you should serve it in also you
should serve it with uh like buttered
potatoes with parsley
oo so yummy and then the whole thing you
eat it with Ling and Berry
Jam what yes interesting I'm intrigued
yeah okay I know it's weird like lingo
mer Jam you might think oh it's Jam like
why do you eat meat with Jam but it it's
just it's just so perfectly matching and
harmonizing it's like a symphony of
flavors I know you don't like sweet
things but it's like not like sweet like
chocolate uh actually lingonberry is a
little bit on the sour sweet side I
would say it's so good oh yeah and a
lemon slice lemon slice just squeeze it
over the snitel so I can teach you how
to make that oh I in a cooking stream
perh I look forward to that one day oh
have have you ever had Ikea
meatballs no Ikea Ikea meat no that's
something I need to try oh because those
are usually also surfed with Ling and
Berry jam oh well I oh my I will have a
peek next time
yeah maybe for your apartment maybe you
need to go to IKEA oh I definitely I
definitely do Japanese Ikea let's go
although I think Japanese Ikea
equivalent is
n yes I've heard of that but they still
have Ikea so it's okay yeah you got to
go somewhere where it's like familiar is
Ikea like the place to go to for
furniture in Australia yes okay it's
like everywhere damn yes it's everywhere
damn yeah damn let's go okay so let's go
cooking yeah let's go thank you so
much thank you so much for calling in
watch my life tomorrow yeah good luck
with that thank you so
much byebye byebye talk to you
later what was I thinking giving K 5
minutes of course there's no [\h__\h] way
we could talk we could have talked for
20 and I'd still be like what okay where
did the time go I'm so sorry
my we love waa man we're both like zsu
Queens I I'm I'm so I I'm so I I'm so
I'm so
sorry
[Laughter]
yeah
[Music]
spe
[Laughter]
what oh
spe
[Laughter]
[Music]
for
spe
[Laughter]
foree
[Music]
[Laughter]
e
fore
fore fore
[Laughter]
fore
[Music]
you
oh
[Laughter]
for
for hi
[Music]
ah bruh I will do a translation very
quickly um we had dance practice and
there was a certain move in the dance
that required you to move your hands in
a certain way and then no se Senpai
couldn't do it at all and then the dance
teacher told him to do a certain stretch
and he's like oh [\h__\h] I can't do it
turns like he played too much Monster
Hunter spoilers there we go and then we
me and Cen Senpai proceeded to laugh
immensely I that is all that happened
next
guest
oh my God how am I already 10 minutes
late goodness gracious
me
[Music]
what
[Laughter]
fore
[Music]
foree
for
[Music]
fore
per
for
foree
Fore
[Music]
so
fore
foree
t t
t
chees
wow hi hi hi
hi
[Laughter]
oh
okay
for
for I give
up you know what what is
time what is
time it's fine time is but a concept
everything is
[Music]
fine
oh happy
birthday thank you so
[Music]
yeah
fore
spe
[Music]
fore
hi
[Laughter]
fore
so present
foree
speee
[Music]
spee
I've been talking to no
Senpai more
recently and I I I we get on very very
well let's just say and I'm really happy
that I gained another new friend as
well
so
all
righty um I think hold on let me we do
have the promise girls ready but I'm
going to let everyone get ready first
and then I'm going to call one more
person before we call the promised girls
let's see if she's she's
awake
morning good
morning who is this I hear I what's my
thingy
[Music]
toally not a steel rose trapped in a
cage of I witness me or whatever I
guess thank you for waking up I have not
slept I knew you were going to say that
I I knew you were going to say that well
I didn't want to miss your thing
so rather than
the over sleeping why don't I just stay
up all night
yeah hey you're
little you need to sleep more I don't
want you to burn out and die I'm okay I
just I'm running on jst hours without
being in jst it's fine what everyone
says yeah literally what everyone
says what happy
birthday y you're 13 you have an actual
birthday how do you feel I feel great I
poorly misjudged this tosu in the sense
that 5 minutes is too short and I'm kind
of stressed but it's fine are you
kicking me out at 5 minutes exactly is
that what you're trying to tell me I'm
trying to say exactly
that I'm kidding I'm kidding okay well
fine I'm kidding no I'm kidding I'm
kidding thank you so much for
coming yeah I you
know kind of somewhat my older sibling
and now that you are year yeah okay a
year more do you have any advice wisdom
for Life
wisdom
no oh
none
whatsoever okay
amazing I have a matching pacify now oh
yeah okay I was there when Callie was
like and then you were like oh is it's
weird right have a pacifier and I was
like yeah it's weird to have a
pacifier well look who's wearing it it's
a
gift
uh-huh it's a
gift you seem to be enjoying I actually
am it's quite
comfortable it's cute and it says your
age right on there so no one can mistake
how old you are exactly I you had to
thank
you yeah you don't need to focus too
much on that uhhuh yeah don't know I can
I can guess who G gave it to you pretty
sure okay very sure I can guess all
right very
nice but you probably shouldn't say in
case get for me I do have a question for
you if you were to get me a present what
would it
be well your present is my presence
because I stayed up all
night I would to be here I normally
would say refund but honestly that's so
true thank you so much I kidding I got
made you something wait really I
did I hope you know what this is or
[Laughter]
Reon let [\h__\h] go let's freaking go I
thought you could use one too you know
oh my God everybody hold on a sec oh my
God oh my God so many things so so many
things on my
face I can't wait try it on clip it clip
it I'm trying it on hold on hold on hold
on hold on hold
on
okay T you know I one you're older you
need to be one level more tuni you know
oh my God so well thank you so
much I actually made it for your casual
so it fits better on that one so if you
ever wanted to put it on yeah I think it
fits pretty good I studied you really
hard thank you I was like looking at
every line oh my God shading and
everything I I studied you very
intensely to make sure that it would fit
thank you so much this is the best oh my
God why does it fit so well oh my
God yeah and mine's on the other side so
we kind of have we can match next time
we collab or something yeah yeah let's
go we can be tuny we can be tuny
together thank you so much
you're welcome to like it I love it I
love it so much it looks it look so good
great thank you so much I really really
appreciate you coming please watch my
live today yes yes we um I set Advent
collab today so that way we could
all pour our people into your you're so
sweet thank you well I maybe you guys
can watch it together or something yeah
we can watch it together we'll show
you thank you so much well yeah um I
will it's been 5 minutes it's been 5
minutes yeah kick me out I understand I
get it I get it get out yeah out okay
well happy
birthday
do I have no idea what she just said but
anyway
cute
hello hello uh uh-huh uhhuh this is so
weird this is so weird that me and you
are the only ones who don't sound
sleepy I mean it's Japan time hi R happy
birthday thank you hello can we get a hi
can we get a self intro from everyone oh
wait here oh wait wait wait hold on is I
think
we're hold
on I think she must have steep away for
like a
second let us wait should we wait
someone sounds dead here yeah
that's you want to say hi who who was
that not couldn't be
me all right I think maybe she maybe she
went to an idol meeting or something
voice it's fine hold on can you guys do
intros while we
wait we have intros oh yeah okay Who
start in order in order in order who's
order the order of the icons oh no wait
no no
what what's happening oh my God is this
what is this what it feels like to be on
the receiving end of sleepy voice yeah
I'm just like I I don't know it feels
weird that I'm not sleepy right now
either for calling sleepy it's so weird
I know I feel alive you feel alive wa
you sound alive I don't I don't hear
Hello I should be here I think maybe her
mic or something oh hello he's just
watching oh oh all right how about Iris
you do your intro first okay hiis it's
Iris the most awake in this um uh
call-in group most likely a happy
birthday babe thank you it's your actual
birthday is and you've been saying
you're you're 12 so that means you must
be 13 now right yeah I'm 13 gazillion
years old hello oh she's here there she
she's here hello wait she doesn't sound
sleepy my phone was not working oh wa no
she is Sleepy it's fine okay all
good thank you thank you hello Iris
welcome to the non-sleepy club who's
next y um well for you want to go next
K it's me S FAA live from my bed
straight to
you from the bed from the
bed another one from the
bed all right uh M
hello wrong order wrong order oh okay
gry hello oh we have an order
okay I don't need to uh
crony from H live English
promise it's your
birthday thanks I mean it's your
birthday thanks
guys y wake up oh this is this is gold
oh bless I'm also bed ridden but that's
good bedridden oh
gosh you're and cuz are you are you on
your death bed is that what it is oh oh
Jesus man I hope not not
yet
yeah happy happy birthday man thank you
all right now order MIM here the order
um it's nasty Moon mate from H life
English promise I woke up 13 minutes ago
and I cannot tell you how quickly I
grabb my phone to see did did they did
they
message it's all right on oh no happy
birthday thank you oh my God this is
amazing normally like the quality I'm so
not used to this like normally we have
the mobile phone quality uhuh yeah I
know and now it's zri that has the phone
quality this is great oh my God turns
have
tabled yeah I saw someone in chat ask if
I'm wearing a retainer what's with that
do you sound like I have a you do kind
of sound like you have
one retainer lisp so cute so cute
retainers are important it is you know
got to keep them bra straightness yes
it's long gone this
beautiful all right well to test that
invisaline
continue is
going oh this is the best choice thank
you so much for waking up for me um I
have anything for you thank you I have
anything for you you didn't wake up a
[\h__\h] you didn't wake up a
[\h__\h] but uh I guess I have a question if
you could get me a birthday gift would
it
be I already got you your gift I'm not
going to spoil it any further even
though I told you what it was and how
much a cost thank you I I I very much I
anticipate
it yeah is it's great thank you so
much you're welcome I I would like to
make every year a leap here for your
birthday oh that's a good answer nice
nice nice oh thank you thank you man
it's a leap you guys it's kind of
insane I would I would give
you a
hamster what a hamster a
hamster you're going to give her a
living okay maybe that's too
much
uh I would give
you the
[Music]
Moon so a hamster was too much but
Mo not the Moon is
good thanks bro I got I got the moon
anything for
you rtic but a hamster anything but a
hamster I see so like on the priority
list so if a significant other gets you
a hamster then it's like yo run but if
they get you the moon yo it's a
keeper
run
run man I
see who's next yeah man pay up pay up oh
hm oh are you talking to me yeah pay up
get what you get
me I mean I don't want to spoil what I'm
planning on getting you I'm I'm going to
keep quiet about that
but something huh she totally doesn't
have
anything totally I'm totally thinking of
something don't worry I'll get you
something the next time I see you I
promise you that um but uh as for like a
you know a nonserious answer oh non-
serious okay here we go a nonserious
answer uh I remember last time we talked
about was the Disney thing and I'm just
like what would be better than that
what's better than Disney what's there's
nothing better than Disney actually but
but
since you're a
rat I'll get
you expensive
cheese no no but hey expensive cheese
expensive cheese that you can oh you
know what no cheese fondue restaurant
you mean the one we went to last time
did we did we oh we did what didn't we
are you talking about are you talking
about Shibuya yeah this
is okay we did but I mean no that wasn't
expensive though oh expensive to okay
got you expensive cheese fondu okay all
right sounds good thanks got to put that
price tag on there
yes oh my God I'm so not used to the
three of you being sleepy but thank you
so much for calling in you may return to
your Slumber and oh I can't but thank
you yay yay
thank you I birm Koke for
you what huh I do a 5 a.m. karaoke for
you oh that's the sweetest thing anyone
has said to
me I would
totally that's commitment right
there thanks man your list of priorities
needs to be sorted out bro where Hamster
Moon
five oh um another another present I
would like to give you is my current
manga recommendation called hiar go
which I've been I've been sacrificing
sleep reading the past
days in the beginning in the beginning
they're all like kids but in the later
Vols they all become like eamens okay
and yes a lot of eomens and apparently
it brought a whole new generation of be
BL content even though it's not BL the
thing itself the anime itself for the
series itself not BL at all but it gave
rise to a new generation of fujoshi for
some odd reason I do not understand why
that's how it go but it's a great series
it's very interesting I see I will have
a I will I will have a look thank you
very much for your recommendation you're
welcome thank you thank you very much
well I have a 3D life today that some
some of you are in
y thank you so excited yes I hope you
guys enjoy it as well
yeah going to be
amazing amazing it's so weird hearing
Iris being the most energetic I'm just
like wa what my world is blown anyway
thank you yes I hope you time yeah
anyway thanks for calling in you may
sleep now thank you Z thank you I to to
you later happy birthday
birthday happy
[Music]
birth Happy
Birthday to
[Music]
You
birthday to
youy
birthday
[Music]
birth that was the longest happy
birthday that I've ever sung dragged out
it was beautiful thank you my dear
friends thank you very much emotional
yeah it was it was crying it hit the s
thank you well I will I will leave you
be for now thank you and I'll see you at
this time in another four years all
right sounds good sounds good all right
see you there
[Music]
bye that's so
weird that is so
[Music]
weird
man
strange I'll put them
here that was
something I don't know I feel like it
was so weird I don't I felt I feel so
bad why do I have a surprised expression
it was your surprise at at their sleepy
voice and also it was the first PNG I
could
find
it's great thank you
everybody oh my goodness all right we
have one more guest through the
phone I feel really bad cuz I made her
wait for so long
but H hello hello hello hello
[Music]
hi you know I literally just got back
like a while ago I was I was at Hop Jong
and I was like trying to take a picture
with you like the the birthday the
birthday promo so cute oh my God there's
a little table right in front there's
like like a like like a little desk in
front of it with like your plushy on it
wait someone just left the plushy that
yes it's so cute yes that that board
right there there's like a desk in front
of it with a plushy on top who Lefty
it's so cute thank you so much it's so
cute oh my God oh my God thanks for
going oh my god of course oh my gosh it
was so fun but y yo Happy Birthday to my
baby this is me
C celery everybody oh shoot do I have to
do like an in oh wait wait wait
wait um with the powers of Darkness
sealed in my eyes it's Shadows consuming
you in the moonet night I'm Mary Celesta
BL see with my
presents hell
yeah let's [\h__\h] go thank you thank
you let [\h__\h]
go thank you so much thank you thank you
y s I've been witnessed you've been
witnessed you've been
witnessed I have that saved from last
time thank you thank you for
coming of course thank you for having me
oh my God it's birthday bro I know it's
your first birthday happy 13th birthday
I can't believe they grow up so fast
she's
13 I can't believe
the gy Whiplash I'm not like honestly
hold on my brain is taking my brain is
just not working tonight I swear to God
I don't know don't worry it's just I
feel like it's the fatigue from the last
month just catching up to me I need like
a good 3 minutes to to to to figure out
where I am and what I'm doing I get it
you've been working so hard you know
every time I talk to her we're just like
oh yeah it's
work work work I just got back from
practice I just finished like a project
work it's so
s this what it is I know it do be like
that I'm so excited for your life you
have no
idea I'm so excited oh my God I'm
nervous but I'm also excited please do
it's going to be so good would like to
hear your your thoughts after the show
oh my God oh God oh my God you know I
was like I really want to sing another
song with you but like a cool like rock
one because guess what baby my bab K she
can growl now my baby she can growl and
I'm like oh my God we have to we have
I'm like we got to do like a I learned
how to grow she did learn how toow I'm
so
proud I need to I I I my dream is to we
need to get you a 3D model and then my
dream is to perform with you on stage oh
my God I will let I will make it
happen don't worry I will make it happen
this year let's go let's let go [\h__\h]
go oh my
God okay so um so for from what I know
yes you have been asking people for what
their gift yes yes okay so I thought
long and hard about this and I at first
I was like do I give her something like
funny but then at the end of the day I'm
like okay I really if the technology was
there all right hold on I have to get
into like my telemarketer voice okay
okay
um okay so welcome to our show tonight
tonight we have a special offer for a
cloning machine cloning machine where it
prints clones that you can give orders
to they are exactly like you but they
are aware that they are a clone and act
to do your job and at the end of the day
you can sell on them and save their
current stats and you can absorb their
stats improving yours overall yeah the
next morning you can upload those stats
to yourself so they also improve along
with you and knowledge is shared along
all of the Clones
and I I'm just like every single time I
talk to you you're you're like working
girl guys she's like the most
hardworking girl I've met and I just
feel so bad so I'm like one can do your
chores one can be like doing other work
and one can like be streaming or like
relaxing and then and then you yourself
you can just like eat yummy food and
play Persona and
like bro I'm not going to lie as soon as
you pitched that I was like oh my God
this this is the making of a horror
movie wait a second what a horror movie
no no because you know the horror movie
us it's about double gangers and like
clones oh no no no see that's why that's
why they're aware that they're your
clones but they exist to serve you it's
safe it's safe I thought about this s s
pretty much Naruto
is yes I am an innovator I I was also
thinking about this and I'm like what if
she thinks it's going to be like really
scary what if people think it's going to
be like us don't worry beo is real it's
real
exactly and um uh dear ma'am these will
cost about 10 m billion yen to replace
but for you my dear special lady I will
offer to you at the amazing price of
eating monjayaki with me when I was in
Japan this
year oh my God wait did I take you to my
regular store or did I take you to the
one in in Shia I don't remember no it
didn't get to go to any so this will
this has to happen this oh my God I
haven't taken I haven't what oh my God
pass B what are you doing I didn't take
you to mja all we did was
e oh you're right is in yu oh my God
you're so right oh my God now I got to
take I got to take you to my mja store
we have to eat monaki or or
alternatively changing your freaking
Discord Pro you're to something else
because you I feel so bad every single
time I talk to you guys you know she
still has her disco Pro picture from
from her freaking collab last time
stupid what are you talking about my my
dumb D like my dumb chuny doodle love
her with like her her eyes glowing up
like freaking Sands from undertale like
I'm like I'm so embarrassed you think
I'm not embarrassed D I look at your
icon and I'm like oh my God there's like
literally A Potato Head who's shedding
hair and has soy beans for eyeballs okay
I actually got an compliment for that at
some point someone was like wow nice Rob
Pi I'm like thank you very much I very
happy with I don't think they were
serious oh come but please I'm so
embarrassed now I'm never changing it
never no never ever no no I need to I
need to get better at CH just so I can
get you to change no never never never
freaking Santa Bay is just immortalized
forever it's
forever it is forever no no it is
forever thank you very much but thank
you oh my God I miss you I will I will
come see you don't worry I want to go
ker this even if you come I will let
I'll take you to my favorite Taco play
that's [\h__\h] go there's a there's a
there's a there's a oh my god I've been
watching um what's what's her name
what's her name Zang oh yeah yeah oh my
God there's actually a place near me
where diang has like been and like they
advertise it like oh diang has eaten
here oh my God there's one place that
she went to and it was like a they
they're famous for the Kim and it was
like a Kim video and I was like bro that
looks so good oh my God I will take you
there oh my God we will go on a food
pilgrim
true let's go I'm so excited oh my God
one day one day one day this year indeed
do you have anything thank you do you
have anything to comment about me by the
way it's kind of concerning me like at
first it was like a haha but now I'm
kind of concerned no one has said
anything about the way that I look is it
about the object on your head yeah no
one has said anything
like literally no one apart from my city
but uh uh I don't see anything wrong
with it at all that is totally a very
normal happy birthday hat to totally um
it's just very
normal wow someone think it's weird wow
that's crazy there's no way it's a
lovely hat thanks nothing wrong with it
at all man right of course I just don't
know whether I should be concerned that
no one questioned it at
all du it's such a totally normal
looking hat of course wow that's
crazy it suits your perfect exactly oh
my God the wings too I mean they're very
normal at like you know birthday no one
has commented on the wings literally no
one you know actually before I called
you I thought they were like RI it's
wings it's because I'm a
butterfly because dream my theme for
dream catcher was butterfly I'm a
butterfly yes I remember seeing the
crafts the the Arts and Crafts yes okay
you're so right you're so
right hey they can be both it looks
great I mean they look beautiful thank
you thank you for humor thank you thank
you thank you so much well
of
go you look crazy right now with the
freaking pacifier and the hat and the
[Laughter]
chuny I don't know what has happened
it's been an hour 30 into my I don't
know I don't
know it is what it is Happy Birthday to
me I guess happy birthday to you it is
your first so you better enjoy it while
you're still yeah I I'm going to enjoy
it so so much thank you so much indeed
embrace the chaos it's part of you will
it
yes oh my gosh well thank you get
excited for the live tomorrow I am so I
literally cleared my whole schedule I'm
like so excited I'm like I I I could
stay up the whole day and the I will I
will catch this freak life I have alarm
set up for it on my phone and on YouTube
I will be there you have no clue yes
please everybody please come please come
if you're in jst go to bed right now so
you can wake up for the live I swear to
God if I don't see you there I will kill
you I mean I will um I'll punish you we
will punish you please be there yes yes
yes thank you very much please be there
I'm so excited thank you thank you you
inspir me so much yes
promis thank you on everything me
literally me no thank you so much yes
stay awake stay awake everybody thank
you I mean you get some rest for your
life but yeah I'm going to I'm going to
go sleep afterwards but perfect perfect
I'll be there thank you so much thank
you for calling in thank you so much I
love you I love you
too have a wonderful rest of your
birthday I will see you at your
life thank you thank you byebye
[Music]
byebye ah
I love meori celery I love every I love
I love I just man I love my friends God
damn
it what has happened what has happened
in the last 2 and 1 half hours I don't
really know um I still have two video
messages from people I was going to
watch these beforehand but I didn't get
to it so let's watch them now yeah
yeah I literally don't know my head is
like
blank this has been the best T stream
ever actually
though all right first one who is it
from turn the
music hello Bae hello and happy birthday
wow what is it like what are you like 12
that's uh that's crazy crazy yeah wow
woo the big old uh the one two that's uh
that's that's nuts uh uh anyway so you
asked me a question and I I you know I'm
here to answer it and I put
it it's here
somewhere okay yeah it was okay if I had
to choose something for your birthday
what would it be well it's a prev it's
it's pretty it's pretty obvious because
you know when I was six years old I
wanted this like I don't even know what
it's called it's like a Barbie
Dreamhouse and she's got the dog she's
got like that dog and and it and it
poops it's like a pooping dog Barbie has
a pooping dog and you press on its tail
and it poops and then it and you could
you could like feed it back into the dog
and then it and then it poops again and
I frankly I I got a kick out of it I
think you would love it um and and I
cannot think of anything better really I
I I mean I I literally can't think of
anything better I want it right now I'm
I'm jealous that I even had the idea of
giving it to you when frankly I should
be giving it to myself regardless happy
10th birthday you kill it out there and
you know what from me to you let me be
the first to say have a wonderful rest
of your day
bye-bye why did I lose
years why did I lose
thanks
B why did I lose
years wait there's a Barbie that has a
dog that poops and then it eats the poop
what
Barbie dog that
poops wait is this the Barbie walk and
potty
pup
oh my God oh my God why why is it
banned oh my
God wait actually
what oh my
God joking
haard
wow well that's one thing I put on my
Amazon wish
list thank you I I
guess oh my God all right and we have
one more
[Music]
video
yes
H wait where did
the happy
birthday happy birthday
make it very natural okay
yes happy
birthday yay B happy birthday wait
what wish you all the best
y the D my
soul yeah thank you so much B yay yay
thank you so much for existing thank you
so much for teaching me so many language
that I will use in my daily life thank
you so much for everything
yay now you will not get a happy
birthday wishes only from me but from
all of uh thousands of people
yeah yay babe I'm streaming right now
yay yes but honestly I really hope I
could come to give you my wish directly
but I just had schedu
unfortunately anyway I really appreciate
your presence I'm happy that you are
here always doing your best and I admire
that so much other thanon I'll never
forget that you are the first person
that give me an ancient debris in
Minecraft huh you're strong you're a
great person and I'm thankful for that
so I just want to let you know that
you're great and you deserve to be
happyy happy first official actual
birthday
B that might might have been the perfect
one to end with what the
heck
Kyla K
Kyla
KY what was the text in the end wait
there was text in the end I didn't even
see
it what's
that Happ
wait I missed
it oh my God I think it says get some
help You're great and you
did get some
help oh classic oh my God I I don't even
know what this screen has
become thank you
everyone everyone who called in everyone
who sent in something thank you so
much I'm already overwhelmed thank you
guys I'm actually oh my God I actually
I I don't get overwhelmed often on
stream but I'm actually very overwhelmed
I don't know what has happened in the
last like nearly 3 hours thank you for
all the love everyone I appreciate it so
much it's my
birthday wow so this is what birthday
feels like
huh
wow thank you so much to everyone who
stayed up thank you to everyone who sent
in a super chat
um thank you to everyone who called in
my dear
friends and thank you to you
guys for coming to
watch it's my
birthday oh
[\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
a
[Music]
ah
thank
you I don't want this has been
amazing wow this feels really weird cuz
like obviously like I did the countdown
last year and it wasn't my birthday so I
it didn't really it was don't really
feel anything but damn this is what it
feels like it's my birthday um thank you
guys so much for tuning in uh go watch
my live I'm going to redirect over there
even though it's in like
hours but it's been
fun it's been
fun 10hour waiting game thank you every
everybody my stomach is starting to hurt
pudding so the how do you say
overwhelmed in
Japanese
uh overwhelmed how do you say
overwhelmed
[Music]
for
I just feel very lucky that I you know
sometimes I get very tunnel vision in
like just what I'm doing and I forget
that I'm surrounded by so many amazing
people
people um but I really do appreciate
everyone not just you know the people
who called in tonight but everyone else
who who who didn't call in and who are
always so nice to
me thank you I really appreciate
it so that's all for
today I'll see you you guys at the
live I'm getting I'm getting I feel the
mushiness coming up but that's
[Music]
fine okay I'm going to go now
byebye who
wrot God
damn bye love
[Music]
you