why
[Music]
than
e
[Music]
hello welcome to my birthday party
everyone Hi hi it's from H second
generation
[Music]
hello hello hello fancy to see everyone
here coming to my birthday
party I'm sorry I'm trying to save my
voice for the Cat part but yeah um today
we have a lot on the
[Music]
schedule anyways yes um please be sure
to tweet with the hashtag by the way the
hashtag is like the title says # 20
[Music]
24 please use the hash
lot you know what I I'll I'll put the
hasht I'll put the hasht Q you know what
so that people people won't
forget I'm just going to have it
here
[Music]
and well also as the title says there
will be
announcements
reveals and
karaoke so what we will be doing
is um the first one I'll be doing I'll
be doing the evil
[Music]
first okay so the first thing I'll do is
the
reveal and then the announcement after
that
and
then and then um and then um the
continuation of K so if we have time if
we have time before the announcement I
will be I'll be going to the Cat part
and then after the after the
announcement we can continue the Ki
part and then after that we'll be a
premere a cover song Premiere by the way
the link the link um I pin the
link l
guys
[Music]
link yeah
okay we can we can do the we can do the
reveal part now so as you guys as you
guys saw in the thumbnail as you guys
saw in the thumbnail there is a Myster
use a do see what Myster use
guys thumnail this is a thumbnail
right
this what is this what could this
be
what could this
[Music]
be
what do you guys think do you guys have
any guess about this
[Music]
silhouette do you guys have any gears
about this
[Music]
silhouette oh boy
I okay I'm not going to lie I'm not
going to lie the Hat kind of the Hat
kind of gives off the feeling right but
you guys got to remember that this is a
this this is this is um for the steam
punong
outfit so I can't I can't really be a
cowboy
sheriff cowboy Emoji the cowboy the
cowboy Emoji is
[Music]
real
detective
maavia yeah I have yeah I have something
too I have something what is that what
is that I'm
[Music]
holding
revolver will be cool revolver will be
[Music]
cool revolver will be so
cooli
[Music]
Hitman also sounds spicy not going to
lie not going to lie Hitman also sounds
[Music]
spicy definitely
wh why why but why why is a
senpai why is a
senpai why is a Senai
[Music]
though
foree okay then I I'll be I'll be
changing I'll be I'll be I'll be gone
I'll be
[Music]
poo yeah why not
both why not both
indeed you
[Music]
okay okay I'm here I put on my stuff
I put on my St I'm ready I'm ready to
[Music]
go
oh oh my goodness what is
that what what is
[Music]
that wa
oh my God the the party emoji I'm so
[Music]
sorry really really cool
right super
cool super super
cool
me oh my gosh look at this oh my gosh
you can see half of my
face you can't see half of my
[Music]
face
guys access guys really won oh
no after the cowboy we have Wily
[Music]
Wonka
one oh my
goodness
[Music]
let me let me see if I can
have guys so that people can have a
better look on it okay there we go there
we
goo oh my
gosh who was
that who was that I
[Music]
wonder
oh my gosh what is
that oh my
gosh oh my goodness would you look at
that look you look at
[Music]
that
hello okay I kind of I kind of give off
a wi w c five I'm I'm not going to
lie I'm I'm not going to lie kind of
give up a will w c
five actually please wait actually
actually let me
[Music]
cook actually wait a
minute and J
[Music]
but yeah that's pretty that's pretty
much the also I have I have one more
thing I have one more
[Music]
thing transparent
I'm transparent help okay let me let me
let me do
[Music]
something okay this is this is not
working
unfortunately I
think I think it's kind of a little bit
messed
[Music]
up
this is fine
too no
[Music]
problem I was trying to change the
chroma
[Music]
key I think I fixed I think I fixed what
I was trying to fix
I think I fixed what I was trying to fix
so all is
[Music]
good yay
an oh my gosh is that
the is that the g s
flute inside of my
gun and is that the g s flute inside of
my
gun watch out I might I might shoot you
with the ga as G
flu very nice nails thank you so much I
love my nail arts a
[Music]
lot oh my
goodness would you look at that
let's go hi hi hi hi
hi
go
goles very very cool
right very very very very cool
right
yay look at my new head and my new gun
guys
so so very
[Music]
amazing yeah I have to go as flute
inside of my
[Music]
gun Wily won I'm okay okay it kind of
gives off a Wily won of five I'm not
going to lie
but
[Music]
really
for and then lots of
[Music]
Expressions nah I would
win nah I would
[Music]
win
yeah the accessory from the goggles they
move very very cute then there's also
this and then there's also
this not an expression I make normally
yeah but oh my gosh I have even more
stuffs for my te P wait I also have my
code my my not Cod but Cate one that I
usually don't use but hey look got
[Music]
this come
picking thank you so much as a always to
mama and also um Papa thank you so much
thank you thank
you thank thank
[Music]
you
oh okay um let me
see let
[Music]
me CR CR CR CR
CR
okay there you go there you
go how how do you guys like the new
steampunk outfit accessories not only
one but two new accessories let's
go let's go
[Music]
yay
who are you hunting Ana
anyone you can pistol do it with
t she also has a
gun yay she also has a gun that's right
that's right that's right
[Music]
I think I think I have potential to be
secret agent as well don't you guys
think so
[Music]
foree
happy birthday Ana thank you thank you
thank
[Music]
you we can move to the
Ki the Tatu k
I will be I will be singing with some
[Music]
members
yeah I'll be I'll be doing a talku k
with with the amazing Hall life
production
[Music]
members they they they they their videos
are pre-recorded of course
[Music]
yeah you know just uh um just like the
usual just like the
usual you know talk to
K the last time I did Koke was like in
my anniversary so not too not too long
ago not too long ago
[Music]
there ID JP n members
yay
[Music]
yay okay let let me
see can I get my mic where my
[Music]
mic
I might have to move this m this mic
here and
there I think I can have I can have
myself okay chat you guys you guys might
have to go smaller all
right sorry chat it has to be
[Music]
done singing with my gun and my hat
feels like I don't
know I look like I'm about to I'm about
to kill people but like I'm
[Music]
singing
I look like I'm I'm about to kill people
but I'm actually going to be
[Music]
singing holding your guest at
gunpoint hey
yo hey yo not like that but
[Music]
also hey yo
man
[Music]
name you're announcing people who will
get
shot hey yo
bro hey
yo okay let's what's turn off the bgm
and
uhuhuh let's see let's
see
okay we
good okay first first person
of the
day oh my gosh wait let
me
yay happy birthday Anya thank you for
inviting me to your birthday karaoke I
hope you're having a great time so far
um I have a feeling that you
are cuz I'm smart like that but yes
let's have fun together uh this song is
going to start immediately so let's go
on the count of three 2
[Music]
one
foree
[Music]
you
yay and once again have a great birthday
thank you yes yes yes yes
oh she she left just like that but why
that
was that was Odo
cron from Hol live English
promise
yay
[Music]
yeah crony she must have been she must
have been really real busy with her own
with her own birthday
preparation but she's still she's still
came thank you so much
yeah we are birthday buddies kind
of we are kind of birthday buddies my my
birthday is today at the 12th and then
Tony's birthday at the
[Music]
14th
I've always wanted the s k all bad so
that was that was that was such a good
opportunity thank you so
[Music]
much
maybe a cover one day I'd love to I love
to make a cover I think we talk about it
like at the stream let's cover something
together or something like that with
crony but
[Music]
why
why thank you so much for coming
crony and I can't wait for Cron's
birthday live in two days
[Music]
woo wait if it's on if it's on um if
it's not on jsd then that means in three
more days I
guess I guess in 15 jst
[Music]
jst I
guess oh my goodness okay next
up next up so I'm Z here I'm a little
bit n of this cuzz I don't I don't
really do kokis often I don't really do
kokis often so oh my
[Music]
gosh all right let me
see there we go there we
go
okay next up
from Holo life
idy
[Music]
hi my ID gun
buddy
[Music]
J
no please don't make me
[Music]
laugh
is she
okay are are you okay
[Music]
no
for
[Music]
spee
bro are you
[Music]
okay happy birthday
Ana
forever D forever
an live with
you you are the sugar to my wife
Papa happy birthday say that
game
[Music]
what what
a
[Music]
for
you happiness
Melodies
oh
bye oh
goodbye I was trying to not to love so
hard I kind of messed up the timing in
the
middle
bro
goodbye and she left just like that
well that was H live
besta and we sang Sugar song
[Music]
and oh
what did she say at the at the
middle the the sugar of my life
[Music]
something she got off my life
what you know what can can we play that
game I
know you are the sugar to my life
happy
birthday
M thank
you thank
you thank you so much that made my
day that that made my day thank you very
much Zena forever ever
[Music]
yay that made my thank you so
much yay how was that after this I think
we can go to
[Music]
announc
all
right
announcement
announcement shall I announce it
[Music]
now
yeah I know I can do the announcement
[Music]
so
n COI COI COI announcement
announcement oh my God no I'm covering
it yay Ana M V birthday
celebration
[Music]
woo birthday merchandise
set okay okay so we have three
merchandise items the first one is
Devil's invitation acrylic sand and then
we have cup and ster and then we have
[Music]
set also voice pack of of course voice P
yay birthday
merchandise we have the A stand of the
birthday birthday
art L Sensei thank you so much for the
birthday
illustration and we also have top and
saler and then we have Cy set s
g and then bonus invitation
oh my gosh what
[Music]
invitation a special invitation for the
M
fans looks so cool right looks super
cool skip
guys skip
okay no skip ad skip ad
[Music]
guys illustration
byi the material is
acry
[Music]
yay
this atmosphere so good the design is so
good yeah look at the
design yeah we have cup and
suer and then the next one we
have C
[Music]
SA
this is so oh this is so
stylish stylish bang
[Music]
guys
I considered that as a
[Music]
win G
guys also voice pack you also have we
also have voice pad situation voice pack
sweetness Whisper Of The Devil in
Japanese with English and basa Indonesia
[Music]
translation
I wrote this as usual I write I write my
voice packs
yearly all my birthday voice packs are
written by yours truly I also wrote this
one this one the voice pack is in
Japanese but it has English and B
Indonesia
[Music]
translation
yay I also did the English translation
by myself by the
way mchan did the basa Indonesia
translation thank you
mchan thank
you
okay yeah a sweet Whisper Of The Devil
oh I wonder what this is
about sounds spicy from the from the you
know from the title sound spicy by the
way
[Music]
voice
oh yeah it will be on sale in like in
like um less than 5 minutes in like 800
[Music]
P.M
for
[Music]
and also the indon
one complete
merchandise
[Music]
AC
Hol life tokopedia Hol life Pro Shop and
also gjack as usual by the
[Music]
way
good is it as usual as
[Music]
usual yeah Link Link in 2 minutes Link
in two
minutes
thank you
680k thank thank you oh and also also by
the way for members for the D dwellers I
have that any let me let me change it to
the English one and then I'm going to
I'm going to have it
[Music]
here
exclusive birthday membership
wallpaper
[Music]
yay
member
[Music]
guys
membership
Community
[Music]
streamers membership
yay yeah M yeah MMA M
member membership
again the art is
bya by the way thank you so much thank
you thank
[Music]
you also it has it has connection to the
voice pack by the
way
[Music]
for
yeah it's kind of spoilerish I guess to
the voice pack so if you don't want to
get spoiled then you can you can listen
to The Voice pack first and then you can
download the membership wallpaper
afterwards join that join
that that's right
[Music]
join I
don't sauce
guys Min sauce to
[Music]
b b sauce B
sauce yeah thank you so much also it's
on sale now my
merchandises good to have
to
L
link is it posted is it posted it's
already 8 8
PM hello
[Music]
M mchan hello where's my
link mchan link
[Music]
doco
for
yeah from the Hol Life TV account the
announcement will be the announcement
tweet will be at like 15 minutes later
but it she'll be at the H life Indonesia
account already I don't know I think
mchan guys I think mchan fell
[Music]
asleep well I have I have to take this
method into my own hands I will I will
find the link
myself
M Chan is asleep
[Music]
guys I'll do the job myself I am an
independent ancient weapon
H life shop H life production official
shop okay there we go okay the
[Music]
link I am an independent ancient weapon
I'll do it
myself okay
gjack let me see good C
[Music]
nice
sh oh no not
enough
fine okay let's just have the tokopedia
link and also the H life Pro Shop link
for
[Music]
now
there we go there we go Anya is the
m what
twist who
[Music]
knows M John is asleep guys
bro the Hol Life TV account and the
English account already has the
announcement up and the Hol life
Indonesian account doesn't have the
[Music]
announcement
maybe I I might be JP for
you I might be JP for real for real
that's so freaking funny though I'm not
even
mad that's so that's so freaking
[Music]
funny
guys I'm not even mad legit this is so
freaking
[Music]
funny oh God okay I love too much oh God
my
voice I still have Koke after this
[Music]
obious
let's
see okay there we
[Music]
go I also want to have this
here
[Music]
yeah the illustration this time is so
cool right thank you so much
[Music]
l guys guys bully guys bully bully bully
yay
yay also my my my voice pack is at SOA
bus for Indonesian
viewers I don't I don't know what I'm is
doing I don't know what
is
[Music]
doing oh Community T YouTube life
ID thank you mchan thank you mchan it's
okay you can you can go back to sleep
after this after posting in my after
posting my merchandises
announcement let me to tweet um where is
it it's okay M Chan you can go back to
[Music]
sleep just a little bit late uh a few
minutes
right just just a few
minutes KY okay thank you I will go
back
[Music]
sorry bro
exposed bro you're freaking exposed I'm
not even making this
up K Koval
confirmed H life Indonesia's manager
Kyla
Koval bro
also I don't believe you when you say
you're going to
sleep I I don't believe
you sorry wrong SC
[Music]
bro bro wrong
account
bro are you
serious
really
I don't believe you when you sa you were
sleeping I think you were playing
Minecraft or
something bro you were definitely
playing
Minecraft instead of posting my birthday
merchandise
tweet
xost xost everyone mchan reveal
[Music]
on
the oh my God I'm so D bro I'm so D why
did you post my birthday merchandise TW
so
late like 10 minutes late I'm so done
here hey
[Music]
yo get some help
bro hey yo bro get some
[Music]
help right also um for the for the for
the for the you know the premier PR the
cover
Premiere this this will be premiering at
9:20
p.m. so we have roughly one one more
hour one more
hour which means I have to yeah let's
get back to
K there's so many stuff oh my gosh um um
um um okay there we
go
[Music]
let me have a hydration chat hold
on hold on
[Music]
oh oh my God
okay
woo okay okay
okay hello
hello happy birthday thank you thank
you
let me
[Music]
see
okay okay
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
e
what
[Music]
for Happ thank you okay we're going to
go back
to K key in a
bit
yay yay yay yay okay let me
see uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh hello
hello
[Music]
okay okay I have to be here for this one
for this one I have to move
here for this one I have to I have to
move here and please
wait yeah cuz the person will be at my
left
side all
[Music]
righty an
happy
birthday it's
Tak from English
me today I'm a cat yes and we're going
to sing a song
together but I want to say this song I
don't know about you Ana you got to tell
me this song is from my favorite anime
series ever have you watched
it yes I have
I was I was a huge fan I see I was
actually a huge fan until I sto
following the entire series I think they
they released a bunch of animes and then
I kind of stopped watching
anime
exess
mpress
go
[Music]
Ani Ani is
real oh my
[Music]
God
[Applause]
fore
for
[Music]
foree
for
[Music]
fore
for
dble
tble
d
[Music]
foree
n
[Music]
yay woohoo hey let's go I'm your
W yay that was
fun good job Ana
so you didn't see then go go go watch it
because bring even more and my favorite
character is also n let's go party fans
where you at okay I'm going to go oh my
God I got to go because otherwise people
will misunderstand that we're like best
friends forever which we're totally not
we're totally not I hate
you totally not best friends love you
bye bye thank
you I forgot about my mic but that's
okay my mic my mic is just there my mic
my mic was just
there anori enemies forever for real for
real thank you k
I messed up at the middle but well don't
don't sweat about the little
[Music]
details thank you so much for coming
kiaha oh
thank you Ma thank you
K Moni was one of my Moni is still one
of my favorites but I think I stopped I
stopped watching the new the newer
animes
cuz at some point they started they
started releasing a bunch of them
and then I kind of stopped watching
animes as well and that's why there's a
bunch that I haven't CAU up
too I fell off with oari monogatari I
don't think I even watched that
one I remember watching kizu monogatari
though after that after that I think
they started like releasing a bunch of
them
and then it was at the it was at the
time I kind of stopped watching animes
and yeah there's a bunch that I I
haven't caught up
to anyways thank you so much K we sang
Moo Express together thank you thank
thank
you
she oh my gosh not beating the only only
one V one collabing on
tatus Ana not beating the only tosu 1 V
one collab
[Music]
together yearly anator yes
exactly okay
okay oh my goodness let's
[Music]
see thank you so much everyone for the
birthday
wishes thank you thank you thank you so
much okay then um let's go to also we
have um we have um mostly um the Kow
kotu is mostly do it but there's going
to be group karoke 2o at the end I'm
going to finish I'm going to finish the
doet the doet ones
first so
yes all
right
happy birthday
[Music]
Ana thanks for uh inviting me to
celebrate your special special day I
hope you have a wonderful wonderful uh
year the upcoming
year full of lots of happy fulfilling
things and of course yummy things yeah
yes
and um I hope that we can also do more
stuff together this year I'm looking
looking forward to it
so and I hope that you it doesn't have
to be the song we're singing now but we
I hope that we can also cover something
together down the line I'd love to I'd
love to anyways for today um I want to
sing I beg you by emit uh with you uh
it's one of my favorite songs to sing in
karaoke so want sing let's sing together
let's have the mic together go like
[Music]
this
foree
[Music]
la la la la la
laee
[Music]
tonight
[Applause]
[Music]
I know you're here to stay with me
I
feeling
[Music]
good he's
not
[Music]
he
the
[Music]
foree
fore
speee
[Music]
yay
y happy birthday again Ana thank you
let's have more fun I mean yeah yeah
let's have more fun together soon soon
soon soon soon okay
by happy
[Music]
birthday
and there she goes oh my gosh I got
really really nervous at the middle cuz
I think the last time I sang this was on
my 2021
birthday it has been exactly 3 years
since I freaking sang this song I got
super
nervous at the middle isn't that crazy
the last last time I sang this was on my
2021 birthday stream and today it is my
2024 birthday
stream I beg
you
[Music]
yay
all
right next up wait let me
see let's have the oh God the
[Music]
BM okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay you let me let me do something real
quick for the next
[Music]
one let's
see
[Music]
um we
have we have
like five more I
think five or four
more and then that's
[Music]
it oh we still have an hour we still
have an hour until the until the cover
premiere
[Music]
okay before going to the next one I'll
have a hi ation check I
[Music]
think
okay okay I'll go I'll go and grab a
drink real quick give me give me 5 to 10
[Music]
seconds
yay okay that was quick right that was 5
to 10
[Music]
seconds
guys
[Music]
toia guys yeah don't forget to buy the
merchandises
Okie doie wait let me
see okay let's see this one this
[Music]
one this
one let me
see
[Music]
I okay I have to
I
have
okay I got I got I
[Music]
got
okay we can go to the next
one
let me move this
to
here okay
JP JP
uh oh
no happy
birthday
y thank you for inviting
me singing
together
[Music]
y
foree
[Music]
fore
let's
[Music]
go
for
[Music]
happy
bir thank
you thank
you thank you that was that was
guys don't tell M Chan
okay if you guys didn't know if you guys
didn't know id id can stream with our
with our you know um
swimsuits swimsuits outfit so that was
kind of like that was
kind don't tell M Chan
okay that was a loophole that I that was
that was an existing
loophole that's probably the closest we
could have to like something something
Mis related in my
[Music]
channel big brain I know I have big
brain don't tell M Chan
everyone that was such a good loophole
but anyways I sang auna Blue with coori
thank you so much for
coming
[Music]
for company
fore
spee
[Music]
foree
hi hi
hi
you
[Music]
e o e o e o
okay and 30 minutes we're
fine 30 minutes we we fine we good I
think three more this is the last do it
I think
right should
be should
be I'm going to check I'm going to check
on stuffs just in
case sure just in
case just in
case I'm going to check on the on the
[Music]
thing oh okay okay
okay
okay next up let's
go
[Music]
fore
for
foree
fore
[Music]
spee
fore
[Music]
me
for
[Music]
why thank you can oh Sho shoot she's
gone my voice okay it's been okay my
voice is starting to die tbh
tbh my voice is starting to lose it but
that's
okay
that was lower one lower one's
eyes bye Night Court from pro thank you
so
much
spee
thank you thank you so much
can thank you thank you that was one of
my favorite
songs
yes
okay all
right next time I think that's it for
that's it for you know the do
it next one we can go
to wait next one we can go to group
songs yay group
songs
okay but first I have to I have to look
at the stuffs
wait wait wait wait hold on give me a
moment
man how are you guys liking the Tatsu
Koke it is my first time doing one
obviously
okay how wait let's let's have the
[Music]
G
super fun thank
you my voice is going to die soon
though my voice is going to die soon so
we have to um we have to wrap this up
real
[Music]
quick my boys is dying soon so we have
to wrap this real quick
[Music]
oh
dinging oh
okay okay I think we should be good
there's like there's like four people
for the next Group by the
way can can you guys
[Music]
guess can you guys guess there's like
four
[Music]
people
um
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay yeah I'm
good I'm
[Music]
I'm
okay we should be
[Music]
good okay next
up now we still have 10 minutes
[Music]
is the next one is also going to be pra
song also one of my favorites by the
[Music]
way
ah next one is also Pro
[Music]
okay let
me
[Music]
spee than
you
[Music]
fore
oh my gosh the
placement thank
you
family thank you so much
to and also
Senai yeah the song the song is
definitely not something you can sing on
like alone or like Duo it just doesn't
work it just doesn't work right and so I
was trying to think of a perfect four
people
group I was thinking of a perfect four
people group to sing this one with and
then I remember K
family yay exactly
right four people group plus me that
means five
people okay that was that was a little
bit scuffed but that was a little bit
SCU but that was that was that was
really good that was really fun thank
you so much to K em I
Wonder
show
I hope the volume was fine
though I hope the volume was
fine I hope the volume was
fine yeah I hope my voice wasn't too
loud or something
the volume was good all right thank
you yay that was that was really fun
thank you so much to k k family for
singing together with
me okay next up next up last but not
least last but not
least do you guys know who it is do you
guys know
who they
are let's
[Music]
go
foree
[Music]
spee
for
[Music]
fore
[Applause]
[Music]
fore
sh
[Music]
[Applause]
thank
you that was to
Shandy friend as well
bye C Tumi thank you so
much yeah I've always wanted to sing
that
song
so good so
good such a banger I know right thank
you to ollie and
Rain Man I I just really appreciate
everyone who came cuz we are super busy
with f so
like so like it's hard it must be it
must be hard to find a time to
record to record all this you know all
this Koke
[Music]
videos so I really appreciate
it
[Music]
I'll redirect you guys to the premier
the cover
[Music]
Premier
don't forget my birthday celebration
merchandises are now on sale yay I have
acrylic stand cof and saer and also
cocky sets now on sale a
[Music]
croni gr cha heading to sleep now but
happy birthday thank you a thanks for
thanks for coming thank you thank you
and thank you too for singing together
with
me happy an day let's go and in about 2
days it will also be your birthday too
soon cron day cron
day crony day crony day cron
day it will also be crony day
soon I can't wait for your live birthday
life I will be I will be tuning
in don't forget about my
[Music]
merchandises
wait crony don't sleep can you stay for
my for my cover Premier
please wait no crony don't
sleep crony
are you still there actually crony can
you not
[Laughter]
sleep okay L A thank you I knew I knew I
could trust you yeah who needs sleep
anyways only weaklings it
sleep
[Music]
okay
okay then I'll be ending the stream
thank you so much everyone this has been
a blast thank you thank you
and all to gra
everyone
bye-bye thank you so much for coming to
the birthday stream
[Music]
byebye