[Music]
hmm
all right
ready
it's back are you seeing me
what the hell what was that i have like
really good download and upload speech
right now
hello
how we looking we're looking smooth
i like it i like it more like that
yes welcome everyone um we are playing
minecraft on my new pc
uh
i actually really like the quick pro
that i guess we're not going for quick
bro because everyone else was pretty
triggered by that see i have
i just started minecraft so i'm getting
like uh tutorial instructions
uh wait a second did i just mess up the
window no i don't like it okay okay
hello welcome everyone
jump to 4k wait my stream is 4k
right now i
i definitely changed it to uh the 1
1 1080p uh
oh you mean the viewers okay okay
yay okay i got new shaders as well i
don't think they're this yeah i think
they're different from the
last ones i didn't know which last ones
i used so i just went
with some random ones from zelda let's
see how the game goes
with um wow with my new
pc and my new shaders ooh
the water i kind of liked it the way it
was before
but i guess we're going with new shaders
hello oh yeah you want to see my specs
already hey you guys are
so fast this is why you guys don't have
a girlfriend because you just go into
things too fast don't expect to take
a girl to show you her respects so
early on okay
give me some time damn by the way is
that bgm
the video you can hear right
oh let's look at kfp in in in in my new
shade of graphics hello kfb
yo what up where's my
they all escaped
hello why did you where did you go
no they're everywhere no no
no no no no you have to go to work go to
work
go away for [\h__\h] sake oh my god
it's just a little bit quiet oh okay let
me turn it up a little bit
how about now
how about now actually i kind of want to
hear it myself
i don't have it on right now
how do i do that again i forgot
oh wow workers are on strike
why how dare you you have to work i
hired you for a reason and that reason
is to work
damage damage but looking good
and looking smooth i actually i also
installed optifine because the
the instructions told me to do so but
i'm not sure if that was actually
necessary
by the way guys off screen um while i
was um
chilling in the game while while kelly
was playing
i no it's not a new mic it's just a new
mixer and some different settings yeah
um i was chilling in the game while
kylie was playing
and cali stream and i just wanted to be
there in case she needs me
but i got bored so i started like
flattening out the area you might not
know unless you have a
direct um comparison but i did
start flattening out there that was
there was a huge hole here
and i filled it all up really nicely
and then i like started flattening it
out here as well and here as well
yeah cause i want i want a bigger
flat area for like more buildings and
stuff you know
for just in case we get more um
more halloween members someday we want
more space right
because it's so many mountains and [\h__\h]
and so so many waters in this
ocean right there so we kind of need
more
more flattened out area but i wonder so
i never use the
creative mode how does that actually
work
like does anything you do in creative
mode
apply to the real mode or does that get
reset
after you change it back to like
normal
it applies to oh so i think i would be
forgiving
forgiven if i if i go into creative mode
and
and just uh flatten out everything like
otherwise i'll lose like a million
pickaxes
is that like i feel like flooding out
the area will be forgiven i mean
i mean oh you guys don't hear the game
audio one second let me
turn it on up then uh oh wait i guess
that's me it's because i don't have
desktop audio on oh
okay okay okay okay
i turned the desktop audio on
and let's see if you can hear something
how about i don't want to do that there
and how about
what did you hear that
sound is there okie dokie
yay okay welcome everyone once again
to my uh minecraft stream where i'm
using my new pc
wow wow finally new pc finally
bam finally finally
what might as well use command blocks
wait i don't know what you're talking
about
i i honestly don't i won't use a
creative mode for anything
else okay i just want to flatten out the
goddamn area
and if you guys don't forgive me for
that well then i'll just do it off
screen
and then once i come back on stream i'll
say ah
yeah i totally did that all by myself if
you're not really gonna
be mad at me for doing that off-screen
uh in and if you're doing that on
creative mode well then i'll just lie
and say i did it for real
you just have to believe me i don't care
it's just for a better future for for
our future
for our future children you know don't
you want the best for our children
huh that's what i thought
i want to sleep too early okay so
what i want to do today is well
never adventure the last time oh my god
if you missed it you have to watch my
last minecraft stream
we we went out okay randomly in one
direction
tried to go straight mostly and then
we found a pyramid we found several
villages
we found uh a pillager uh what do you
call that tower
uh uh something you know the thing with
all those people
and we freed a golem and we did so much
that was so successful and then we even
made it an out a stronghold yes it was a
stronghold and then we even made it
safely back home
without any problems i i have no idea
how i did so well but yeah it went
amazing ah
you want the pcs box
i mean they're not as good as cali's i
think um
but stop telling me to punch a tree
goddammit how do i turn off those
tutorials if you really want me to punch
a tree on one second
god dammit
we're gonna go destroy the tree i don't
want to destroy the tree stop telling me
what to do
batman oh look at that
oh nice lining but i have a feeling it
might get pretty dark
when there's no torches people keep on
telling me to
like turn up the minimum brightness uh
but i don't know how to do it
and people keep on telling me how oh
busy under the loop got me one second
people keep on telling me how and i keep
on not listening
i'm sorry so here we go loopy time okay
so uh first of all
decide which direction we go last time i
think we went
in that direction
oh yeah you are welcome to backseat but
in my stream i don't care
i need your help anyway let's be real
i'm i'm such a horrible
minecraft player maybe this time we go
in this direction
i mean i i think there's the ocean over
there
but we'll just take a boat um
last time we also took a boat okay and
uh then we have to prepare something so
let's eat that steak
by the way i didn't have breakfast and i
got up uh
40 minutes before the stream actually i
i
had my i had my alarm on uh
for an hour ago no actually more than
that yeah more than enough
30 minutes before the original starting
time but i was so tired
so i uh secretly without saying anything
to my chat i secretly extended the
starting time to 40 minutes later thank
you everyone for being so
so um um
nice to meet you and you know this well
yeah
of course you did and then i went back
to sleep for 40 minutes but i felt like
i didn't sleep at all in those 40
minutes oh well so
then i woke up and i i i did um
i quickly tried to get um the minecraft
game
going and the shaders and all that and
made myself a tea which i will sip now
so um oh yeah i'm now
collecting uh more and more pumpkins
because i feel like they might come in
handy in a future
hollow live end collaboration stream
voice voice sounds so much better it's
really it's it's more realistic and
smooth
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay what do we want
to bring
like something like some bread uh
red get that bread
oh that's only 25.
oh we can also bring the berries but
uh should i make some more wind
i have so many eggs i wish you could
make uh scrambled eggs
on stream in minecraft
why can't you make scrambled eggs for
god's sake that's like the simplest
survival food ever
so simple right
oh nice nice let me use that
make some more bread
i wonder how much do we need for a big
adventure
i mean that's okay that's probably more
than enough and yeah one stack should be
fine
right one stack is falling
[Music]
the fella probably shouldn't be there no
no no okay
she sounds different yeah um since
yesterday i'm using a new pc
and with the new pc i switched from
streamlabs obs to normal obs
and uh in obs i'm i changed the audio
settings a little bit
and i uh in my new mixer that i got the
other day
i uh gave myself a compressor
so all of that together might be
the reason why i sound so crispy since
yesterday was since yesterday i
happened yesterday apparently you guys
didn't come to my sakura stream
for whatever reason which i do not
understand
okay so next up we got food so we need
um
stuff okay good did i still have some
swords from my last adventure which i
did not even need to use all of them
the hole we don't need the hole i feel
so rude when i say that
damn uh should we put on the
some golden helmet
i mean we have it
what's aqua affinity what is that
ah i have a golden hand it looks like my
hair the white it actually looks like my
hair
swimmer swinging fast oh amazing perfect
but we're going on a boat so that's that
uh anything else i mean i mean we don't
we're not really going to
mine but i'm bringing the pickaxes
anyway
and i mean we could bring the crossbar
but i'm not sure i know how to use it
should we bring the crossbow
i don't have an wait i also don't know
how to use a
i'm breaking oh can i try to use a
bowler you guys got to teach me how to
use a bowl first
how do i use a ball bow oh
i don't use that
ether thank you for the red super chat
oh okay okay okay my first time using a
bow bow did you pick it up oh did i just
pick up my
own arrow oh is that a thing they do
well but i kind of need more arrows how
do you make errors don't tell me i need
iron for that don't tell me
oh flint
i don't really have flint do i
um i have two
i have a few more errors okay i'll we'll
just not use them
as much okay
good that i have some more torches here
okay torches
um anything else guys
i probably should uh i could bring a
crafting table
and should i bring a chest
i could bring a chest is any chest like
available oh
wait that's from last time oh oh oh
what do you want me to bring wood i have
glocks
um
well spare bed there we go
i want me to bring some wood well okay
okay okay
looks good to me boom
wait don't we don't need to crossbow
okay
hey but i'm scared that this will break
because it has i'm breaking but it will
break anyway right at some point
i could torch oh yeah
i'm late did i miss much no because i
was also late
i was waiting for you
totally stop picking that up
i was waiting for your big brain this is
what i call big brain i'm so kind to my
viewers i wait for them when they're
late
okay you really shouldn't be late but oh
wait
don't have an infinite source over there
infinite water aren't you there
yeah i mean i don't know if i don't know
if it's infinite
yeah oh there we go okay we got a water
bucket
wait wait maybe we should have it like
always there
okay easy specs
yeah you really want to see my specs
stop munching
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
thank you so much thank you thank you i
i appreciate it
okay um okay okay
are we ready to go boots yeah
i don't want food but okay it's your
birthday oh yeah i saw on twitter when i
was lurking on your twitter account
sometimes i lick on your guys's uh
twitter accounts just for fun
happy birthday happy birthday
to you happy birthday
dear happy birthday to
you yay
takuma has been trying a lot of art
and a lot of fan art for me so thank you
so much and happy birthday hope you have
a lovely day
did you know why did ina also do some
flattening out here
this wasn't like that before hey good
job you know nice one
did she carve the whole mountain
stream lagging
really did she flatten out the area
i mean this was not like that
oh stream is fine okay well then guys uh
i think i'm ready i have torches i have
blocks
i have a crafting table i have a bed uh
i
hey i think did she plant those trees to
make it look more
pretty
cool
okay guys we're going for an adventure
in this direction
ah wait i want to get a horse
there's no do you guys know if there is
any horses around here by
watching the other girls streams that
any horses i can capture
probably not i don't think there were
any horses
bit rate was is too low goddammit
oh
yeah i have ah let's bring a saddle yeah
i have so many saddles let's bring one
in case i find a horse
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
i can't change it uh right now because
i'm already streaming
sorry but at least it's at
60 60 fps and 1080.
saddle saddle saddle saddle saddle
yeah look at all the saddles i found
last time and and all this
are all this armor damn
let's bring some armor as well yes
okay and now we got them first we sleep
bring some wheat ah for the horsey
oh horsey means horsey meat horsey wheat
how much is two enough
bring a leash in i don't have a leash i
need a leash for a horse i thought i
only need a saddle
i start
you guys are welcome to backseat in my
stream because i suck at minecraft
but if you're gonna backseat then please
do it correctly
and tell me right information nah not
wrong information thank you
thank you thank you more wheat
really more wheat
okay okay okay
okay chill bringing more wheat
and then we go can you please tell pc
specs
okay one second i think i'm i'm ready
i think i'm ready for this now
what why is there different stuff
growing in between my wheat or why is
that not grown
and planted that ages ago what
is that potatoes or can
can i be more careful when i'm oh god
oh my i only want to get one at a time
why is she destroying everything
thank you for the red super chat thank
you
[Music]
is that enough now that that must be
enough right
oops
maybe i can get back to the employees to
work with my
seats because apparently they
need my seeds in order to work properly
i said that's so adorable oh my god it's
so cute that you come there like
okay guys break is over
hey mama is calling
hello yes yes yes yes break is over
hello everyone
what about you stop hiding there's no oh
my god you run away
okay babies come get somewhere come
come come back
wait one second you know i don't want
you guys to fall down
come here good babies
a good baby
here yeah oh look at them being super
adorable
are y'all following me okay back to work
okay got it tell do they actually like
if i drop it how do i drop it again how
do i drop
stuff there we go i didn't try to get
that
oops you couldn't eat that
there you go do you want to eat it
eat it idiots
bye bye bye bye
i don't stay working okay i have
security cameras
in there
let's go
okay well guys
ah if you really want to see me yeah
well there you go
yeah that's uh my deepest secret
i i only show it to people who i really
trust and
i really like
i wanted to get that everyone was
talking about that 30 80 or something
i wanted to get that but it was so loud
they didn't have it so
i they gave me the best that they had
is it good there we go people saying i
have a beefy one
happy happy finally
wow wow jesus that's beefy okay is mine
better or is cali's better tell me tell
me
which one is better
oh what what an annoying puff here oh my
god
granny's stream is aesthetic oh man is
it so bad is the bitrate so bad
yours is better
well i did pay for it
well uh i'm happy to hear that
cal is better oh come on
facebook is bad oh man it's grainy
okay have you seen enough of my sexy
specs
there you go 10 a looks like
240. yeah hey can i say i i don't think
i can change that in
midstream
a bit rained
it's super grainy
i hear a monster
i think like i might have to
ah
street output
i mean video bitrate i don't know what's
normal but i have it at 2500
what should it be and i have hardware
amd instead of software
it's good yeah because i don't move it's
good but that's too low
10k what can i change that right now
oh 10k
apply okay
did it do that oh i can't do it during
the stream what
i changed it let's see if it's better if
i move what was that
what did i just hear what's that was
that enderman
i heard some weird noise man yeah
enderman okay so you know what i'm gonna
go back home with my coordinates anyway
but um let's play some torches
okay it's really it's better
oh nicer okay oh yeah see where we're
getting there we're getting there we're
getting there and it's gonna be
just gotta be patient i place a place
torches a bit too late but
let's see if they will be helpful did
anyone ever go
into this direction i wonder oh
could we should we um should we make a
tower here
let's make a tower
around here so i don't know if it's rare
but we are really blessed
like the area where we spawned and
live is amazing honestly
oh
that looks beautiful
oh i have the i i have the view quite um
quite uh how do you how do you say that
options okay the render distance
have a quite uh
five so okay
porch oh my god another red lipstick
thank you
your love is contagious energetic
personality
oh thank you what
let me read the whole thing how people
continue to stream for a long time does
our restaurant have a slogan
yeah it does
never gonna give you up never gonna let
you
down never gonna run around and they
search you
yes you know that that's our slow i
didn't even make that up right now it's
it's
for real i was talking
my heart every time i jump down from
somewhere scares the [\h__\h] out of me
that's my slogan yo going to the wedding
go away going no going
no i don't want to
i have too many okay
and should we sleep first or should we
also sleep
can i already sleep no no
well thank you for your super chat thank
you thank you guys for the support thank
you thank you thank you thank you
yay good night oh what a beautiful view
going to sleep
now we shall go on a water adventure
[Music]
should we get the coordinates of the
tower
maybe
well and now we go somewhere
i don't know where we're going but maybe
every now and then i should
put a torch somewhere
like for example here
[Music]
that's smart right it's not a smart
thing
i have water in my boat
i hope i'm going somewhere where no one
else has ever been that's my goal
basically
good move then right wait let's uh let's
put the torch here
because we smart oh you can do it while
you're in the boat oh
nice nice okay we
we are smart adventurers okay
um oh there's already all
right i feel like this is uh where i was
before but i went in a totally different
direction
was someone ever here before
oh
wow fancy what's in there
nothing
oh your voice feels like er
in my brain what what does that mean
should we wait someone was here
goddammit who was here
anyone who knows inna
uh i want to go somewhere where no one
has ever been
i think we need to is those
are those pillagers in the water
am i saying that currently
no way
oh yes it's just it's just those boys
okay
[Music]
wait i came from there right let's just
go like really far let's ignore the land
and yeah we'll
we'll get lost and we will have to take
some time until we get back
uh by coordinates but
that's just how it is i want to find new
lens
i am not satisfied by finding lens that
someone else has found before but this
also looks like someone has been here
before
press m you can open up a bigger map
i don't have a map thank you for your
super chat thank you
thank you for your support
uh i should have yeah people told me to
bring him back
at a map
but i was smart and did not bring one
oh are those new lands that no one has
ever seen before
possibly oh
or is there any sign of enough being
here before they were trolling me all
goddammit trolling me with a red super
chat
well okay take it
you know what's it before no
no no
let me go
thank you
i mean i don't see any signs
[Music]
give me the boat okay i have it okay
okay
well actually it's absolutely
um meaningless for me to put down any
torches or blocks
because i'm totally um
i told i didn't really do it i if you do
it you have to do it like efficiently
but
let's put a sign there at least
something
okay and another
another boat
why is there always water in my bones
where do we go guys where do we go no no
no
money
i feel like someone told me that before
okay
oh another red what's going on guys
thank you thank you please
told me when you're looking for me what
what
pushing t on angular places oh wherever
oh my
god what mind blown
thank you thank you wait is that oh
it's a troll what does she do again
i'll just chat god damn it
i found you i thought you were giving me
useful information
why are you lying to me wait a second
did i not bring it i have a [\h__\h] okay
why tea patrol goddammit
who made that tower is that my tower
someone was here before
who made that tower did someone know i
did
is that my tower of cali uh
[Music]
but kelly no no me and callie didn't go
here we went somewhere completely
different
hey how do i go somewhere where i
haven't been before
wait a second wait a second what did i
just see stairs
oh no
wait it looks like nah that's natural
right
where am i am i like super close to home
nah did i go in a circle
[Music]
how about we go straight over that ocean
please make a map
no i don't want to make a mark
i don't want it
i i don't wanna
i can't i don't even know how i don't
even know how
[Laughter]
and i'm lazy yo but see we're going over
a big big
big big ocean there must be
something new here
i'm gonna get lost no i have coordinates
of my home i'll just
i i found my way home with coordinates
last time as well
so is this a new area
oh i see it oh i came from here
no coca-cola i came from here
thank you for your service
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
how is that
what do i need for a map don't need a
map table
a card cut cartography table thingy we
have that at home but now i'm too lazy
to go home
pick one direction i did
should i make them up okay
but how do i get home
how do i wait i feel like i didn't thank
you appropriately
fine nugget face nugget
thank you really so much for your
support thank you thank you thank you
thank you
thank you soon
so she made several maps
okay okay um
oh what are my coordinates again oh god
damn it
what are my home coordinates let me
probably sleep please
let me sleep
okay am i going in the right direction
um probably not
and just need to listen to chicken
noises if i hear chicken noises and i
know i'm close
oh i never thought yeah
but that's not my torch
are they leading me home
are those torches leading me home
or are they leading me somewhere else
i feel like those mate might go
somewhere else
don't follow the light don't follow the
light
is that is that uh
are those torches that i placed
i need like torches with name tags that
was that
i did not play so many torches because
that was a lazy piece of [\h__\h]
what are those torches supposed to mean
maybe that was me before in my other
adventure
those are mine if really
okay let me get out those uh wait i have
a new pc i don't have the
oh okay well i posted them in discord
before
i have a new pc so i don't have my um
i don't have my uh screenshots bad
but i think in our in our discord
i posted our uh coordinates before
oh someone had oh my god
the chat has the coordinates oh my gosh
amazing okay
okay okay got it okay so
at 314 that's pretty close
and minus 472.
chicken i told you just listen to the
chickens
[Music]
they have my tattoos tattooed my touches
my uh what what my my what my
what they have my coordinates tattooed
okay well that's a yeah i feel closer
flower in the forest makes me feel very
close home
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait
wait anyway wrong direction but there's
a torch
i don't have any tattoos uh i just
misspoke
i'm i'm too much of a of a kind of
person who's scared of pain
actually wait that doesn't make sense
soon doesn't suit my lore
i love pain i love it because i can i
just die anyway let me uh completely
undo everything i just said
i love pain i love them
pain is um my comfort
um i'm not making much progress how do i
get back home
this might be the right direction
yes this is one coordinate going up one
corner going down wonderful
we should see our home soon i feel it i
feel it in my veins
i should probably eat
oh
[Music]
well that was a nice adventure thank you
everyone for coming today i think we did
quite some progress um was really nice
we found many
many treasures um i didn't even die so i
feel like that's quite amazing um
a respect for that
let me up
okay so where does ina have that stuff
place is so pretty
[Music]
oh what an architect
ena so fine
where is her stuff
i can't even go up what
okay where where does she have those um
[Music]
those car cart on those maps
you guys are talking about
in here
wow
second floor in the new house is that
that's not the new house right
that's the old house
now is this a new house oh
it definitely looks new okay second
floor
second floor
you know you got to do something about
value you can keep on falling down there
okay second floor okay
how does this work how do i do this
that's probably not what i wanted to do
i should probably put it back right
doesn't she have copies you guys told me
she has copies
the other house copy that map
wait why does she have to uh i also have
the
card card card cartography table
this is up here oh my god goes up
oh there's nothing how do i go down how
do i go down
oh how do i go down
oh it was right there
oh [\h__\h] thank you
it was right
i don't see it
which one
it's in the old house oh okay you mean
that the extra maps are in the old house
and i can just leave that one there
okay i hope so
i told you guys you can backseat but
only backseat if you're if you know what
you're talking about
old house but i always i already wasted
so much time
wait is that old house no
is inna online
no she isn't
second floor how do i get up there
[Music]
wait i don't know do i have to make my
own copy
i think i have to make my own coffee
second floor is korea
i mean i saw the table i saw the table
but i needed the map for it right to
make
a copy yeah yeah okay oh god damn it
maybe she has it in there
she has so many beds
huh did i see that before oh yeah oh
i'm so confused get the map again okay
ah we're not making progress
i want to go on an adventure
okay
okay got it it was there er
pop right in the oh god
no not the bread not the bread
i hope you guys are not trolling me okay
it better be there for real now
oh okay so there's that
that and then you guys said in top right
of that chest
ah how do i only take
well one oh there we go
okay oh yeah we finally got it
let's sleep in her bed no okay wow
okay
let me sleep okay
let's just hope i don't lose it all
right
okay one hour late did that take me one
time and one hour
no make one more empty how how how
how put the other map back i did i did
you want me to make one more
i don't have paper i don't have paper
i don't have an empty map
sugar is paper
see this is why i don't travel with maps
because it's just
too much of the bottom men look finer
should take care of it yeah you know and
then we'll be fine
let's just go with that okay so we are
where are we what taco bell is there
oh am i a taco bell
so she did not go
in the top left corner right
it's moving so much i don't see where i
am
oh that's the mountain
i did close the door i think
gosh you guys are so i mean what's going
to happen
what's going to happen huh
what's the house okay whatever but
what's
nothing's going to happen there you guys
are going too crazy over one open door
as if everything's gonna explode and
[\h__\h]
there's horses here
what let's go
let's go somewhere new let's find a new
place
[Applause]
see i'm already finding new lands
she didn't go here before but i feel
like i did go here before
the report replaced torches now wait how
do i have uh
how do i do that
how do i how do i have a torch in one
hand like that
and the map in the other hand there we
go
okay
don't necessarily need any torches right
now but no well
kiara is a root house rubber me me me me
me me egg
you for real with that comment you for
real
sorry that was just so funny chiada is a
rude house
oh my god she literally made copies
so that we can use them but okay
it's robbing okay sure makes sense okay
let's go up the mountain i want to go up
the mountain
come on
uh should have brought a shovel i feel
like i never need a shovel but when you
need the shoveling you obviously don't
have the shovel
i feel like amelia inspired me
to be more toxic
hello piggy wait where's the map where's
the map
no okay
aha we want to go here
i wonder if she went here with a goat
maybe and just didn't have a map
because i feel like i didn't go oh oh
well
um
there we go okay
where am i oh okay okay let's go in that
direction and hope there will be
something new for real
hello i see my torch from before
i've been there before
okay i mean now it now just stops so
it doesn't really help to have the map
so
we just go straight into this direction
and hope ina wasn't there before
jungle by jungle jungle
wait yeah i've been here before i think
okay you know what we just gotta go
straight over the land
and see what happens
the ocean is useless at this point
ocean is useless i'm telling you
kiara you're beautiful today oh thank
you
my inventory is confusing me
okay yep i someone has been here before
oh that was just a cactus okay
yep but someone has been here before oh
yeah
isn't that yeah that's the village
that's that village
god damn it i'm in the same how is it
possible i started out
by going into the opposite direction
than where i i started out before
how do i end up back here again
was oh possible
posted
and yeah we docked here and then we went
okay you know what i'm just gonna go
over there i'm gonna i'm gonna i haven't
been in this direction i think see
that's my stuff
goddammit
yeah i have to i have to just go far
farther yeah
let's go oh god i have been here before
as well
then i'll just go there and i'll just go
here
i'll just go here instead
hopefully that will make a difference
if we keep telling her inna has been
there before will the stream never end
yeah that's correct
now i've been here why am i walking in
circles always
[Music]
uh pick a direction stick to it i'm
sticking to it i'm sticking to it okay
also i wouldn't mind a horse now
okay i see no signs of uh kiara
having been here before i see no signs
of
human uh exploration
oh i see uh i see a
a thing is that
one that we have seen before i i think
that's a different one from the one i
saw
last time because the other one was um
in a desert now if there's something in
the chest
then it means no one has been here
before oh my god
oh my god oh god i don't want to fall
down there holy [\h__\h]
oh my god
okay so let's see
no one has been here before
new land new land
glyph's doing my melon slice what is
that
what is a glycerin melon slicer
i'm just too lucky
stream over i know not yet but
damn i already see i keep on fighting
why why is there why do i keep on
finding so many of these
dates
goddammit
give me the test
why it's not that rare oh i thought they
were quite rare
wait a second
sleepy time
we're finding so many nether portals
everywhere man
damn okay maybe we should chop it
oh my god oh my god this is so dangerous
here
it up so i don't did you get a new mic
well okay
so people keep on asking so let me
explain one more time i didn't explain
before but let me
say it one more time so basically
let me let me get real deep here okay
i had a good microphone since the
beginning
because i got one from from i got the
old one from cali
which was a really good microphone oh my
god
[Music]
and i just i guess i didn't have the
right
tools to make it work properly
oh my god
so it did sound shitty in the beginning
yeah i definitely didn't have the right
tools for it
um so
uh after a while
oh is that is that new as well
i'm going out in the one direction now
is that the what
isn't that a new village
why is that the same village
and
but yeah and what i was going to say
it's i know she has been here before
right now that is them
how do we know if this is a new village
i mean there's a dongdang
i'm getting distracted
that's new this is new oh
hello new village so yeah um
i had a good microphone from the
beginning but i don't know it didn't
work out but
i was wondering like um cali was like
maybe it's like broken or something
i'm not sure if it was actually broken
maybe maybe
it was maybe it wasn't uh i feel like i
just didn't have the right uh
um things to go with it like probably if
i had the mixer that i have right now
the co xlr then it might have been fine
um but yeah that wasn't the case
so eventually i ended up getting my own
microphone
uh which is now a sure sm7b
and uh ever since then i already had
better audio
but in the beginning with the short sms
sm7b i had a focusrite
uh which wasn't
i mean it it um it was necessary to have
the shure sm7b running
but i had that i had i
even bought a cloud lifter which by the
way i'm not using the cloud lifter right
now because
turns out i bought that for nothing it
was only useful with the focusrite but
not with the
um with the go xlr so basically
uh cloud lifter i used that for like
a few weeks and that's it that's a big
oof for me
but okay because that cloud lifter was
also quite expensive well whatever
is there nothing here
there's nothing here
uh so
wow amazing you know i was there
oh oh well so um
what was i going to say
oh thank you no i already have
everything i need but thank you thank
you thank you thank you
thank you for the support thank you uh
where was ike uh let's go back exploring
let's go back there
oh i'm still on the map that's not a
good sign
um so yeah and now uh recently i finally
got my sappoco xlr
which made me get rid of the focusrite
and the cloud lifter but it seems like
the mixer makes uh my
microphone sound even better than it
already did i mean it was already an
improvement so
um people already said many times kiara
you sound so much better than before
eh but now for real i think i finally
found the the best combination
and where the hell am i
no i'm going back see this is how it
happens
this is how it happens
no no no no no we ain't going we're
going we go
we go um here where there is no land yet
welcome to the membership so yeah i'm
also finally happy with the audio
i was already quite happy with it before
um i thought it was already
pretty pretty okay oh
but we have finally peaked i think
around the right yeah but but there's no
land over there so i'm sure i'm just
gonna go there
but i feel like i've been there before
but well i mean it's not on the map
well let's go there
been here for 15 minutes already loving
this why because i just can't find uh
one direction
oh that's nothing okay
paw okay
wow where we're going here now yes okay
i finally found
the lake we're going
straight in one line guys
and yeah um the go xlr
i got uh like two days ago
so i've been using it since like
yesterday we didn't
that was a new village maybe that's
awesome
is that orsonia yeah going on why is
there so many villages
but is a book useful
got it i see
that the floor the ground looks so shiny
with my sliders down
take the book take the book it's just a
book though
you can't enchant it
i feel like i'm gonna find more useful
things but okay
i'm just gonna go ahead and throw it
away if i need space
take the wheat no i have enough wheat
was i was anyone here before
nope ina was not here before because the
map is not filled out
new village why is there so many
villages
foreign
is another one of these shitty villages
that don't have anything to offer
come on what's what's shot shaders a
silver
silver shaders i really like those
stones i want to bring those home
pretty thank you oh
thank you thank you
[Music]
they're so nice thank you hello
stop looking at me don't look at me
oh oh is that is that good
smite's too what is that is enchanted
soil look at that oh
no i wish i wish i could find an amazing
little
villager and you guys go like wow
she's so lucky wow wow pug amazing
i want you guys to be amazed by my
my look is that too much to ask
oh
hello anything interesting here wow
there's literally only crap here
now i'm monitoring come on give me
something
give me something of value some
tower up there
don't run you're such a cute cat
that's a rat doll that's a ragdoll
that's a red
i want the wiggle cat i want it i want
it
it's a ragdoll
wait you're a wrecked all right you look
like a ragdoll to me
yeah oh my god it's a ragdoll or a
siamese i guess it could be a siamese as
well but
i want it so much
[Music]
oh my god oh my god
[\h__\h] that book we'll fight much more
amazing stuff
[Music]
what else can i leave for
almost broken pickaxe
i never almost broken pickaxe
okay get some more
[Music]
yes see that is that is why you always
follow cats uh rectal the
ragdoll cat brought me look
[Music]
what is that
where did the ragdoll kitty gold
yeah there was lava there and it was
quite scary
don't like seeing that lava but hey we
got diamonds without even mining
yes so yummy
horsey you are now my horse yeah you can
look quite pretty
okay how do we do that first give them
weight or
first give them the saddle how does that
work
[\h__\h] you want
you ride it first but why are you in the
water
go online first come on
why are you swimming i think i'm gonna
have problems riding your feeling
all right there we go
do i just keep on doing this until it
accepts me
and without the saddle right click oh
empty hand sorry i don't have an empty
hand
oh and how oh
what do i do now we're best friends how
do i give it the saddle though
oh i'll give you some armor as well yeah
fancy horse
look at my horse my horse is amazing
first try
so is that such an amazing thing wow
okay yeah yeah
yeah yes
okay oh wait that i have to feed it oh
oh damn maybe we do need more oh wow is
it gonna die
if i run out of
is it gonna die
no okay the feeding is just what do i
feed it for
i can't even feel it i feed it
ah maybe if the health goes down then i
have to feed it um
what's the name i don't have a name yet
i don't have a name yet okay so
wait can i give it a chest and no
okay so now what are you doing
what are you doing
horses don't eat wheat then why did you
make me bring wheat
name it circles because i keep going in
circles so that's pretty cute
that's pretty cute i like that
horses eat apples what
it does eat wheat okay
so let's continue going in that
direction
yay we're so lucky
so if i uh go off of that horse will it
just
will it just stay wherever i leave it
it's a slow horse god damn it it's okay
i love you even if you're slow
don't worry about it circles
i like that name i'm gonna call it
circles for real
oh that hurts me as well
he's fairly fast oh okay circles don't
listen to the haters don't listen to
them
let me teach you something about haters
they're full of crap and they're jealous
that's all there is
oh god chuckles be careful circles
where do we go circles it's a water
from here but i don't want to leave you
just yet
let's uh let's go on land
can you swim oh good circles
good circles good job
that's my first horse in minecraft ever
i never had one before
no circles circle you okay
got them i'm sorry
for hurting you check his stats
ow how do i do that
i don't care about his stats you guys
you guys only care about
this dance
and you only care about this dad
look at papa
look at papaya's hair really
no turquoise tacos come on
first is gonna die in record no why
would it dying
it was here oh look at papaya
okay
f5 i'm scared to press f5 what happens
with f5
i mean that's just that look at me
looking beautiful on my horse
why are you telling me to press f5
wait that looks so cute the legs
look so adorable oh my god kawaii
press alt f4 i'm not that stupid
he's so cute
lava what is the lava doing there oh
dear
stay far away from that surplus i'm not
interested in eating roasted
look is that new
what is that
temple is that a prayer is not a pyramid
but not the one where i was before a
temple
is it is there a difference between
temple and pyramids
oh god i'm scared
where you go where are you going
i thought you're gonna stay there why is
it moving why is my horse moving
why is my horse moving stop moving
horsey
stop moving
i don't have a leash i thought you went
and now it stopped moving
okay i have to capture you
i can probably go over this
no wait wait
no horsey okay wait a second
oh my god i've just had flashbacks to
the time where i played minecraft
for the first time and suffocated in
sand
oh my god my bed oh my god i hate sand
so much right now
there we go okay uh horse where the hell
are you going
why is it moving
i don't i need a leash how do i make a
lease
[Laughter]
uh
slime and string slime
these can only be found goddammit would
you is it going to stay in the area
can you stay around here baby circles
you're gonna what if i give you some
wheat
i bought some wheat no don't fall down
don't shackles sugars
come back up here come back up here
circles circles we have a problem here
you just don't listen to me
wait circles wait wait wait wait panic
panic fencing yes
yes yes
yes okay okay
it's not going to be able to get out of
there right right
circles
now i can finally explore my temple
wait i was never in the temple before
only in the pyramid
well you guys did a great job at helping
me uh get through the the pyramid last
time
so we can do it again it's the same
oh oh okay well
in that case i trust in
me yeah but i will put
all my stuff in the chest diamonds we
have diamonds like
oh my god what is successful
uh uh travel already oh my god
let's put all that in here
[Music]
oh it's already full
oh wow oh well oh well
you need oh yeah right i need a pickaxe
okay
there we go okay so where do i
start going in it looks different from
the one i was in last time
looks different
oh wait actually
oh i didn't was someone here before
wait i hear skeletons
it's looted
yep it's oh damn it watch
so will not explode hey what's that
is it really dull
oh wait are you sure that's loaded are
you sure
gurda was here for real in the first
collab
oh how the hell did she get here
but i'm curious for real don't take
chances
all right if you guys are so sure about
that
a portal
oh
it's hard to see does that look looted
really did she take the tnt
it exploded oh
look at that floor it's so shiny she
forgot the tnt
drop a torch i have it up there um
[Music]
i mean i don't really care about the tnt
that much so
i don't really care i wonder if there's
still did you take a treasure i guess
you probably took the treasure or
oh i want those orange blocks
should i well you guys said okay
okay well then we find our own
very soon let's take everything back
back back back
back back
back back back okay
then usually down
i should have brought up an axe
no
okay now we're free circles again and
keep on moving
where from which direction did we come
from
wait where's my helmet
and
one second i'm so scared of losing my
diamonds man
i don't want to lose my diamonds
hello i'll free you right now
oh what a pain in the ass oh my god
oh my god oh my god
diamond pickaxe
[Laughter]
i don't want to make a diamond pickaxe
see to zoom why would i wanna zoom
why would i wanna do that
just leave it but maybe i needed to
to capture him again somewhere well but
that should be
enough to make a small peach
okay stop wandering off circles
you have a mind of your own okay
next stop
i'm sure we will find something exciting
right away again
thank you oh my god thank you for the
super chat
and eat so you're not serving my last
yeah oh my god i didn't have breakfast
yet
but i'm not i'm not that that hungry
just yet so i'll i'll be fine i think
you thank you for your support very kind
of you you forgot the diamonds i did not
how would i forget the diamonds
hydration check that's a good idea um
i should probably drink something sooner
or later
welcome to the membership
hmm well we ever find back home though
i mean i mean the map is actually going
to help so i guess it was a good idea
that we brought the map
but i don't want to keep on exploring
the same
uh uh desert
i want to find
this mic picks up some really deep voice
of hers what do you mean
what do you mean with that
you're saying that my voice is deeper
than you showing
up
can i go with my horse on the boat
probably not
increase the map i don't have any
methods to do that horsey
what what are you doing
horsey come on
seahorse how adorable
one second welcome to the membership
he can he can ride on the on
we cannot go on on a boat together can
we
okay i think i really gotta go now
though like um
there's only ocean here i'm going in
circles with circles
i can i can push him in
but
wait circles wait
no circles circles wait
circles come on get in there get into
the boat get into the boat
get in the vote get in the boat get into
the boat get into the boats
get into the boat circles you can do it
yes
yes yes no no no no circles no circles
no no bad circles
tickles circles circles
circle sounds like circus to me
circles get into the boat
are you gonna need a leash are you for
real it won't work
why didn't you tell me work what they
were trolling
oh [\h__\h] god they stopped calling me why
do i trust you we have a trust
trusty relationship and you do this to
me why
how do i deserve that
you're trolling me
i knew it wouldn't work but i feel like
um we're having a problem here right now
i i gotta
there's so much ocean everywhere we
really
am i mean look at the map there's so
much
so much water everywhere
horses are not really
make a bridge that bridge is gonna be
like five million kilometers long
yeah i'm still not on the mouth but um
what are you doing circles abandon
circle
no i cannot i mean i guess i will
circles it's been nice with you
oh my god circles
circles circles
don't die now okay
let me take that circle you are
you are a free horse now but i will
actually still
oops so close
i want you to be safe i just want the
best for you
wait wait circles
wait wait
okay wait i keep on messing up the
controls and changing to japanese
keyboard it messes up everything wait
circles
[Laughter]
stop moving
no it's not good
i i basically allow you to be free
but at the same time i want you to stay
in this fence
forever and ever oh god it's the last
one
wait right there should be a portal over
here right
okay and now we apply some torches so
you survive
go away leave circles alone
i will kill you
koi i am a part-time warrior if you
haven't seen the youtube title
of this stream i am indeed a part-time
warrior trust me on that
okay so close
it was nice to have you maybe maybe one
day i'll i'll come back to you see i
have my accordance here
one day i will come back and i will
rescue you but for now i have to go on
maybe it will even be today in the same
stream
oh thank you for the super chat vowel
thank you thank you
[Music]
carefully when i um
when i do my super chat reading okay so
now
i see a creeper kind of scary
oh god i should probably sleep
then i don't know
quick quick before the creeper comes and
kills me
yes okay
let's see where our destiny leads us
shall we
i have the chords i literally just took
a screenshot
did you have your eyes closed or
something
and now it is time for me i will go from
here
voice is also here okay maybe not so
many
okay
we are going into the ocean and
hopefully not in circles
where is this spawn no
circles want this bone
chuckles might be spawned oh well we
will see
we will see what the future has in store
for him
and me it's tamed
yeah but i i didn't put the i got rid of
the
saddle yeah so is it still tamed
i wonder if somewhere down there there's
a zombie
with a dragon
oh it is so tamed oh okay branded horses
don't juice one okay
well i see you one day again circles
let me just go straight now oh i like
how there's a literally
only ocean here
oh i see land i see land
you know that was at least a big spot of
ocean
um okay is that new land
it better be but it's is it only a small
island
it's only a small island
did i just see a torch there
did someone come here no that was my
imagination
no torch okay okay okay no torch
no torch no treasure okay
then it's all good
i'm just checking kfc island
make a tower oh i i don't have any
stones left
oh i see more land but
that's not what was done no flower
what's that it's just flowers
more land there's only small islands
interesting
and my boat is not leaking right now oh
what happened
oh i'm not sticking again
never mind just leaking
wind waker simulator oh my god i have to
say
wind waker is my favorite zelda game
what about you guys
welcome to the membership
yeah you too
i mean i might be biased because i i
um i didn't play all of them
although i did watch uh like
playthroughs from another youtuber of
almost all of them
pretty much i think every single one
so i've i have i have seen every single
uh zelda game but the one that i
really enjoyed playing myself was uh
wind waker
oh yeah travel princess was good too
[Music]
i have breath of the wild by the way i
bought it like ages ago but i never
um touched it i never started playing it
but we might play bro breath of the wild
in the future on my channel if you guys
want to see that if that's something you
guys want to see
what do you mean i'm going in circles
i'm not going in circles right now i'm
just going straight the whole time
but there's a lot of islands here man
um okay so i i originally thought that i
liked the area where we spawned
but there's one because there's so many
like flowers and everything it's really
pretty but there's one problem we have
with the area where we spawned
it's so much ocean around it it's hard
to build
like a huge area like the
like they have in the in the japanese uh
holo server you know what i mean
and it's so hard to get to a different
biome like i've been looking for hours
and the only thing i find is a desert
and there's just so much ocean
in the beginning i was like wow this
area is amazing but i'm like hmm
yeah it's kind of bad for headquarters
it's kind of bad
it's better to not go by ocean why see i
haven't seen anything for ages but this
is beautiful
i haven't seen any proper land for
engines man
built in the sky
oh if we finally find some new land but
it's still it's still a little desert by
me
oh well i mean
let's check it out shall we meet the
miracle
never mind never mind
we're gonna keep on going a little bit
longer
why does that look like home to me
if we finally find something
we found land we have found land
ahoy ahoy
with a huge mountain right in front of
me don't tell me it's uh oh my
what what on earth
don't tell me it's the ocean right away
again after that after that mountain
[Music]
is it
come on no it's just a mountain in the
middle of the ocean
um i don't know why i'm placing torches
at this point
placing torches is absolutely useless
i have moved down on one ax
so i'm kind of getting close to hope
i guess in some way
yeah that sounds so different did i miss
something
people keep on coming in being super
surprised about the
the audio i just have better audio
quality because i got a new mixer
and i i changed to obs so i also changed
some settings
and i have a higher audio bitrate
and stuff like that you know
let's go over there and then yeah i'm
using a go xlr now before i use i didn't
use a mixer i only used um
uh interface i suppose that's what you
call
it i think that's what you call it
finish the map and go back home no i am
not satisfied
with my adventure just yet i want to see
more
oh i don't want to fall down
[Music]
i need to discover something new
i need to come home and be proud of what
i have found
i cannot go home like this it will be
a shame to go home without having found
our old friends
we loved having found a new amazing land
found diamonds well that's true but that
didn't even take me any effort it was
just in a chest in a village
i want my diamonds to be earned
oh is that a junk what kind of biome is
that is it jungle or
just normal where are we
yeah it looks like a regular forest
goddammit where are we now by the way
minus six hundred minus eight hundred
under under that uh acts we are somewhat
close to home
but on the x-axis we are quite far away
interesting let's sleep
nail me everyone hydration jack
you did earn your diamonds thank you
thank you oh wow indonesian translator
hey thank you
do i has an indonesian audience
find a jungle temple there's samples in
the jungle
but this is not a jungle
wow is so many what
i did not expect so many indonesian
viewers to be here
i didn't realize that hello everyone
hello hello thank you for watching my
stream
how does the jungle even look like
where am i
okay i'm i'm moving
further and to south with every step i
take
i don't know if i like that
why this is by me why does it say that
uh
planes well that's boring and i see
there's it again
again there's it it keeps following me i
want to see something else for once
come on
is that new i see something new is that
you
has that been conquered before
we must be far away from home is that a
new village
what
what a big red super chat holy crap
thank
[Music]
have you been conquered before thank you
thank you for the support
hello
thank you
yeah please tell me you have diamonds
do you have diamonds i'm here for the
diamonds only
don't care about anything else diamond
simon summons diamonds diamonds are
girl's best friend after all
hello hello diamonds oh emeralds okay
not bad hello books i don't care about
amarillo sounds so good
yay why is there an en translator when
i'm speaking english
thank you for translating my english are
you saying my english is that bad that
you need to translate it
into english come on
rude
but i like it it's funny it's funny
[Music]
oh wait um i'll take some of that bread
thank you
thank you thank you thank you what
spelling have i not been in
never been into every house now
damn what a boring shikimura
in japanese you call this shikamura
maybe you've heard it before
maybe you've heard it before but this is
just as you would
have it in the books up in here before
you
george burp peep
chicken shut up
what a beautiful white cat i want a cat
hello gum oh well yeah that's it
you could
okay well that was a bad village but at
least something
but actually i didn't want to go into
that direction i just went there because
of uh
because i saw the tower now where did i
come from
what a fast cat the cat is speed holy
crap wow
did that come from here yeah i did right
where do we go marquette
canadian
okay translate what i'm saying now meow
or actually okay i guess you guys don't
speak
uh cat language that well but i feel
like since you are all chickens you
should understand
[Laughter]
this
during my stream i tried out my mixer it
has like a function where i can
record sounds live and then replay them
so i'm basically a dj now
and those are the four sounds i can do
maximum for sound and then i have to
clear them up
but these are my four sounds
the crowd the duck
the seagull
and the chickens i did that during the
super chat reading
yeah a lot of things happened during my
super chat meeting
for the first time in my life i tried
doing uh
i tried doing uh duck sounds i didn't
know i could do that but what is that at
the temple
how do i get in there where does it
start does it start on the other side
how do i do it
oh my god break the wall
mind it it's safe to mine into that
sounds like
[\h__\h] to me it's safe to mine
randomly into a temple that sounds like
the biggest crap i've ever heard
eh really no no no no
but i don't see any other entrance so i
guess we have to
well that's a hidden temple if i have
ever seen one
so
well
oh okay
oh you guys gonna help me here
i gotta put all my stuff into a chest
again
first of all because we don't wanna lose
this this is dangerous this is dangerous
[Music]
what part is that what part uh
is that
put that stuff in there my diamonds my
gold
uh i'm already running out of space
[Music]
uh yep
well we can place the boat right and we
can place the bed
right and yep
bring dirt for what
i'm just bringing okay okay
let's go
on
okay that's true yeah yeah true i need
torches
why is that floating there
oh let's bring them these ones yes
is it sleepy time
okay i'm scared how do i get in there in
the best way
this is sleepy time ian thank you for
the translation i have a feeling there's
gonna be enemies in there
hmm just take
it like straight into it nah
i mean as long as i
wait what was the rule again what am i
not supposed to dig
only the because oh god
what am i not supposed to be digging
the blue block right the purple block oh
my god wait that i can go there okay
okay
okay okay okay
there's there's a spider in here
somewhere i hear it
wow this is like super super scary
[Applause]
what do i do how do i kill the spiders
without them destroying everything well
i do have a bowl
i don't have a ball panic
what do i do
yeah but then it will block the damage
from me but it will
block it will explode everything i tried
that the other day when i was not
streaming
and it exploded everything around me i
did not take damage but it exploded
everything else
shield wait a second how about we bring
a bow
if i if i kill it with with that
then it should be fine right
wait how do i undo it how do i how do i
[Music]
but
but what if it comes closer to me so
quick than oh my god
[Music]
next one
oh
well
what is that
is that oh it's just a bug
okay
oh my god wait am i already on the
ground
[Music]
oh my god that's so dangerous that is so
dangerous stop exploding there might
have
oh my god
so where do we dig again
how do we where i forgot how do i dig
properly again
not purple right some people say purple
only center that's [\h__\h]
he wants to teach me um he really wants
to teach me
lies but i told him not to
quit how do i get down there again
how did you how did i do it last time i
have to make stairs but
what was that
stop kidding me peace oh my god
keep on surprising me okay
okay
okay so how do i make stairs
i mean i can go around here right oh my
god i'm so scared
i can go around here right okay
i did it before i can do it again
i did it before i can do it again i did
it before i can do it again
don't panic don't panic don't panic
don't panic we can do this and we will
we will be rewarded
very much can't speak english i
literally
don't know any words at all
good job kiara you're doing a good job
you can't eat candy
okay now don't step on that pressure
plate just don't step on it kiana
how do
[Music]
yes i'm safe now right
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
okay okay is that good i mean string for
a leash
okay but i need slimer
as well apparently
mine the tnt okay
oh yeah i just done i just mined it like
any other block right it won't explode
right
you miss a saddle oh really
hey i don't see a saddle ah
yeah okay
that's
[Music]
we did it guys thank you for the super
chat what what
have you seen a meme where ammo does a
prank by waking you up and kelly wakes
up in the bed next to you
i don't know why but i could ah you mean
that you mean nothing that actually
happened but you mean the fanart yeah i
did see it
i don't know why but i could hear your
voices in my head and it made me laugh
so hard
yeah i did see that one it was a good
one
let me get back up
we did it you know actually now i'm
quite satisfied i must say i'm quite
satisfied
yay i love pyramids they're so exciting
i love pyramids i'm so glad i'm finding
so many of them
okay no creeper outside i've been good
i'm back and i'm saved
[Music]
the chest now i don't have so much space
in my inventory so
um
look at that loot man i have five
diamonds
three emeralds some gold stuff another
golden horse armor a few books is any of
those books like
cool what is riptide you guys seem to be
excited about riptide
chest will stuck oh oh well
riptide rules for tridents what does it
do
is that the one where it keeps on coming
back
riptide tried an illegal flight oh
it's a rare enchantment for twine oh it
makes you travel
what
uh like a rain that's worth trying what
makes you fly makes you
fly when it rains what
i can fly with my tr try that
it's for good it's really rare
oh yeah it's a number three that
means it's pretty cool right oh my god i
cannot lose it
[Music]
i know then i have to go back home now
safely how do i get back home safely
oh dear
that's the max level oh
yeah three is the highest right oh my
god how do i get back home
without losing everything
give me all my fancy stuff please thank
you
anything else uh
yeah we don't need that
and we don't need that
oh there's still ah god damn it ah
what do i don't need i mean i don't need
a weed now
don't really need to blocks and that's
uh i think put it up but i still need to
bring the bed and
ah at the bone yeah yeah
a second need a bed
um maybe we don't need flint
hitting it with the diamonds okay okay
okay okay well we don't have the chest
now but
that that's that should be fine okay
okay okay
okay let's sleep for now
good night everyone what what a success
oh my god
i'm i'm a real warrior man i find so
many exciting things too
okay the question is now can i make it
back home safely
about losing that riptide enchantment
because that seems absolutely amazing
um okay i have my coordinates we will go
straight home
uh it's a 314
and minus 472. if i want to explore more
around here i want more
i want more i don't want to leave yet
mother
how did i i want to explore more
i want to see more i am
i what if i just make a second home here
and then continue exploring here later
isn't that couldn't i do that what if i
make a base here
and then do another minecraft stream to
continue exploring even further because
going back here kind of sucks
it's a long way to go should i do that
i want to find more temples but i mean i
will have a problem with my inventory
but well i mean i can just make a second
base here and
you know
was i there before i was there before
right
in that village polo outpost
i don't have chicken noises shut up back
home first
um
[Music]
i was there before right that was a
horrible dog
jay
but did i go here before well i can live
in the
village for a while i can't just
put my headquarters in here was that
here before
the doors are
this place looks new to me
but everything looks new to me
ah yeah that's not new i was here before
okay okay well yeah how about we
live in the village for
if i put my stuff in their chest are
they gonna steal my stuff
which house has a chest
do you have a chest no
you're not gonna steal it right okay
there we go okay
this is my test thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
oh then we will go even further next
time guys
we will go even further
peace the new life takanasi kiyada
making the largest you know i left my
chest do you think it despawned
do you think my other chest already
despawned
was it over there
how circles i don't know man
i don't want to think about him
i don't want to think about it makes me
sad
where is that though where is it
where did it go oh god i'm so hungry
circles is no more oh i did take uh
coordinates of the of the pyramid
i did take a screenshot
here oh yeah it's my chest oh yeah my
chest is still there okay
okay i have come back to retrieve
another just
thank you in that flint i want that
okay
for circles has gone to and farm upstate
that sounds like something you would
tell
a child who's oh bunny
rabbit meat that sounds like something
you would tell a child whose horse just
died
don't scare me
hello village my new home
i am now your queen except me
otherwise i'll burn you i'm a phoenix
okay don't underestimate me
get used to me uh oh yeah second chest
am i blind where's your chest
am i blind i don't see your chest
maybe i never had a chest
i picked up everything oh well let's
let's go up and take the other chest
let's take this chest
it's mine give it to me
yeah i know i could just build a new one
whatever whatever
i save my stuff where's my home there
my new home this is my new home
for a while i have decided
to leave our headquarters
oh well
and i will now live here for a while
i don't know how long it will take until
i get back maybe by the time i get back
everyone will have forgotten me but
that's okay
sometimes sometimes you have to accept
these
sacrifices in order to be a real
adventurer
right
like you forgot circles i did not forget
circles
deep in my heart i would always think of
circles i will never forget circles
i will never how could i ever
forget circles i kind of want to
continue exploring
but i should probably end it here and
then read super chats
okay we gotta we gotta end it here i'll
continue uh soon
and today uh in actually uh
six hours from now i have a collab with
kelly on her channel we're playing
uh a way out
chat now well thank you everyone for
watching if you want to stay you're
welcome to stay
and see you usually some crazy stuff
happens on my
super chat readings like this
let's move over to my main screen let's
go
oh i didn't i didn't do the chat thing
here just yet one second
what's that noise did i just hear and
the man
is what was that weird noise oh
oh well yeah there's definitely an
enderman here right now
i hear it hold up better log out to be
safe
okay okay
there we go chad is back
well that was smooth right thanks to the
new pc and
although minecraft was moved anyway
before that but
oh
i hope you guys enjoyed this stream i
really enjoyed it as well
let's read the super chat i only have to
read the ones from this uh stream
so it won't take too long i think
[Music]
someone translates that try it if you
can
ok
it's not too quiet right i will get
circles
maybe on the way back i have i have the
coordinates of where he is
very quiet
[Music]
how about now
he will not wrapped in the fence don't
worry
i left him torches as well so he doesn't
get scared in the dark
[Music]
has returned to us now truly today is a
blessed day oh he was there like in
pre-chat as well
oh he was there really what did he do
did you guys what what did what did what
did he do
did he just say hello
[Music]
a secret
what icon
[Music]
i miss him he wasn't here for a while
because he didn't feel so well i think
okay okay okay
i know
gotta eat more fried chicken to get all
that power and energy back
i'll send you some fried chicken to the
fried chicken
now
who said i was gonna stop super chat you
did uh or
maybe you didn't
let the superchat be whatever it may be
from minecraft deaf compensation to
any celebratory celebrity why did you
write it like that
reasons yes that's how you spell it
really
also good luck with the collab with your
wife thank you looking forward to it
walter jackson darkeshan jacqueline
duncan jesus thank you for the red super
chad
thank you thank you on behalf of all the
kfp employees
very nice of you thank you soon thank
you for your support
and airborne cats thank you kasana thank
you very much for 11.
thank you hey you you're finally awake
you were trying to cross the border
right walked right wait i know that
what's that
walked right into the imperial ambush
same as us and that thief over there
damn you stormcloaks skyrim was fine
until you came along empire was nice and
lazy
okay thank you soon
sapphire kitten
time for the ultimate test of any pc how
it can run mc
i will think that is quite a test for a
pc
gotta play more difficult games than
that
more more ram eating
[Music]
i'm so
no i got a new mixer and a new pc and a
switch from streamlabs obs to obs
and all those factors might have
had that effect on the microphone to
sound
super crispy i am upgraded crispy
[Music]
it's saying my first superchat didn't go
through so here's my second
attempt oh just wanted to say your audio
sounds so amazing now and converts on
your new pc setup thank you
it's so big the pc is so big
it's so big it came in a huge
uh cardboard box and even when i
put uh took it out of it it was so big
it's like before i had like uh i had my
pc
on top of my desk because it was
relatively small
but now oh my god i could not put that
on top of my desk that thing is
huge
um that's a huge tower it was pre
pre-built yeah i ordered it from some
company that um
[Music]
that i was uh recommended by uh
covered so i went with that
and they just gave me what the best
thing they had apparently
um crimson air is done and airborne cat
duncashin
available
[Music]
but um one thing like i want to bring
this
this pc back home once i go back home
uh in a few months and use it there as
well
but i have a pc back home and it's it's
a decent pc
and it has like a really fancy white
case
and the insides are also uh partially
white
like um specifically made
and because i wanted a white pc
so i can't use that though like it's too
small it would be too small for the
current pc but i
i don't want to get rid of that white
custom case
i wonder if i can get a new white case
for the
pc right now and i can like get get rid
of the current case because it's just
boring black
i want this fancy white case
[Music]
why would i give this pc to kelly kelly
already has a beef pc
[Music]
i wonder i want the white case for my pc
two pc streaming setup
how does that work
um i'll just i'll have to get a new case
i hope
i hope i can find a big white case for
my new pc
i know it's expensive as [\h__\h] to ship
everything over there that's why i
originally didn't want to
you know get a pc here because i'm going
home
soon anyway in like three months not
even
so i was like oh i'm just gonna buy a
new pc once i'm over there or just
use the pc that i have there which is a
decent pc
[Music]
but well i got it anyway
it's okay i'll use all my funds
to send my whole life back to where i
came from
[Music]
oh oh two pc setup you use one pcs
stream pc and a second pc is only used
for the game
same as streaming console essentially
this means if your screen pc crashes
your extremist slop
that is interesting that is interesting
but i don't really think it's necessary
ah
kfb administration officer thank you
sparta prowess thank you
alvaro diaz thank you for the scooter
thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
love you love you too thank you thank
you very much
i really appreciate your support
thank you for your generosity rosie does
is duncan richard erin's junkie
crispy duncan
[Music]
thank you so much
thank you uh and dakuma
once again thank you for the red super
chat and happy birthday one more time
[Music]
the takama takamori collab is the best
gift i could ask for thank you for
making my days brighter
yay you're going to be watching our
collab on your birthday that's great
i hope you can eat some cake a birthday
without cake
is not a real birthday
[Music]
makes me really crave some cake right
now god damn it
i want cake now
i want some saha torte
[Music]
kfb stands for kiara fred phoenix here
exactly
justin reinhardt duncan
again thank you for the red super chat
once again thank you so much
yeah trolling me with uh all kinds of
stuff
space attack i know how to attack
slick order
finally congratulations a little behind
schedule but better late than never
also the new mic setup is crazy smooth
and beautiful thank you
i'm also very satisfied with it
yes yes yes good audio very good audio
i hear it myself too because now i um
now with the mixer
i can hear my own voice in my headphones
and
constantly listen to my really smooth
voice it sounds so good
i want to eat my own voice
sounds so good
arctic foxton casper duncan renevost
[Music]
what fifty thousand look up the custom
settings
on nvidia's website they have custom
settings for 2080. what
is that is that the is that the the card
that i have
[Music]
i mean for free and 80.
i don't have the 4080 or the 20 80.
maybe he thought i had that well i do
not because all the all those ways are
not available but i have something else
that's pretty good
thank you your streams are super fun
your love is contagious and your
energetic personality puts me in a good
mood
hope you will continue to stream for a
long time i
i already answered that during the
stream thank you once again
[Music]
thank you for your support thank you so
much
god of amiibo well next is
[Music]
simple answer about uneven crop growth
because growth is randomized there's
some variability in the time it takes
for crabs to grow
oh i think i think
again thank you for the troll for the
troll red super chat
thank you although i will not
fall for your troll super chat
you amber nancy i missed most of the
stream last night but was blessed with
your hilarious boob remix when i popped
in
you mean this one
sorry i'm a bit tired today
yeah i have it saved i will never delete
it i will use it every time
mother kissed tonight
it's so funny i love it i love it
[Music]
thank you so much for all the support oh
my god it's so many
oh my god that in one hit
send kick archives and vote for
secretary
and again thai nugget face with the red
super chat what the hell
thank you thank you thank you
i don't know how to thank you enough but
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
foreign
um
chat thank you one last thing have you
heard of up dog
what's up dog i only said that because
it was a red super shadow okay i'll give
i'll give that to you i'll give you that
what's up doc
oh so you have to yawn so much
[Music]
nothing much how about you thank you
guys thank you for answering me
thank you thank you for the support
thank you
one day i will eat you i love chicken
nuggets i will eat you
thai nugget face
[Music]
it doesn't matter
curtis clements duncan big poopy boy
thank you for the pinky thank you
thank you for your support
professor nope space guy red duncan
we should find the donkey yeah donkeys
can have storage right
damn it wait if i i never saw a donkey
before goddammit
i need a donkey
[Music]
he said waiting sweetheart well he's
sweating i'm just worried nothing to do
actually i was thinking about that
yesterday while i was reading the super
chat i was like hmm
with this crispy audio people might
enjoy
uh whispering
well
out
let's see if it picks it up properly
but it's a noise gate
okay that's that's
i'm so hungry though i'm hungry for real
there he goes there they're happy
thank you thank you
thank you for your kindness reminding me
to drink water and all that thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
greetings to a fellow uh australian link
is
thank you for the like triple
the baby only has 24 days left until it
dies
please survive please don't die
[Music]
forest henry thank you i tried
patrick that one guy thank
chat i already reacted to it during
stream but thank you anyway
i'm so hungry
though
question any intention of playing modded
minecraft i know you got the shader mod
and stuff but i don't want to see a team
of phoenix
or something in a modded minecraft oh
yeah why not
that would be fun
i keep on forgetting to replace my
um sword with the sword texture
that people sent me of my own sword
[Music]
i have to do that eventually but now i
got my new uh pc so i
have to i had to get the mods all newly
installed anyways
oh maybe now is the time
people sent me a weapon texture for my
sword
allah
now let me refresh because we're already
almost at the end
everyone is so worried about circles
i'll get him back don't worry don't
worry
rachel thank you teammation
i cheer broke and i hit the back of my
head on my bed during your stream the
pain wasn't enough to stop me from
watching your stream
are you okay your chair broke
oh my god
okay
of sing along of the song sound of music
for the next member movie stream
or sing along no why not why not
i want to watch that movie when telling
you guys
oh my stomach just did you hear my
stomach
i wonder if my microphone picked that up
you don't even you didn't hear that
right
okay okay
[Music]
i will do it eventually looking for the
top thank you again
you're the the reason why i'm whispering
right now
thank you for the support i
i i've noticed that you were um holding
back
a little bit recently and being nicer to
your own wallet into your bank account
i think your bank account is really
thankful to you for that
i hope you're in better terms with with
your bank account now
well thank you for your support thank
you please always be careful of
how much you spend on on me okay
no need to like try to um this is
towards everyone no need to like try to
impress me or something or flex or
something
but every little support is appreciated
very much thank you
oh wait looking for the top did you get
a kiss
i love refrigerators and also for the
red super chat thank you thank you thank
you thank you
kfb staff recommendations for stream
settings
use x264 instead amd
yeah really
4500 to 9000 kbps for bit rate
fast fast medium cpu usage
one two one 120
audio two seconds keyframe yeah you sure
about the audio though
you sure
it seems kind of low audio a bit range
what do i know anyway you guys probably
know much more than me
chiara talking specs in asmr
wait
[Music]
wait a second wait a second
wait a second i wanna
wait a second where is that where is
that
how do i how do i find my specs again
like not in minecraft
how do i how do i i don't how do i see
my own specs
in windows 10
run dx dying how do i
i can't it's just it says something like
oh there it is okay
oh hey
empty wait let me turn down the
noise great even more
amd ryzen 7 5800x
eight core processor 16
cpus 3.8
key h set
free 32 768
mb ram
uh i don't know what else is interesting
here
i don't know the rest seems not
interesting
but let me tell me tell you about my
mixer
pc helico xlr
is [\h__\h] amazing
i don't know what else is
considered the specs dammit
sure sm7b
windows 10 pro 64-bit
that's all i have to offer windows 10.
wow
can you imagine is the bias
something p p free
dot free one t what is that
[Music]
what is that anyway
okay guys send me your pc specs now in
the chat let me read your pc specs
go nano special
gtx 650 r5
3600 5700xt
32k kilobyte of ram
i5 minus 3007
35 470k rx 570
16 gigabyte ram
h nvidia rtx 2016
32 gigabyte ram
gtx 1052 gigabyte
gtx 1066 gigabyte intel
157 600k
amd ryzen 7 3700x
amd radeon rx 5700
xt 8 gigabyte gt gtd r6
512 gigabyte ssd what the [\h__\h]
plus one terabyte hd 16 gigabyte what
the [\h__\h]
that sounds amazing even to me
elite
elite ect 3100
maximatic four slice long toaster
with extra white 1.5 inches
slot for bread bagels croissants
and buns reheat cancel and defrost
six adjustable toe settings stainless
steel
amd ryzen 7 3007
with radeon vega mobile gfx 2.32
gigahertz
nintendo ds lite
i7 windows 10 pro 16 gigabyte nvidia
geforce gt730
64-bit sp1 cpu
intel core one five three thousand three
hundred thirty
at three gigahertz
uh 47 degrees
wow decrease celsius around
16 gb dual channel dtr free
at 798
mhz motherboard msi
h77mag43
[Music]
ms-7756 in in
uh yeah brackets
to eight what 28
degrees celsius graphics hp 2159
and the 2047 mp nvidia geforce gtx
660.
oh my god
lenovo yoga 720 i7 7700hq
16 gigabyte 2400 set
gtx 1050 for gigabyte 512
tv samsung and fm nfme
open source tumbleweed 2020 1202
linux 5.9.linux
linux
ryzen 1950x threadripper
16 core 32 threads 1000 adti
64 gig of ram
rtx 2080 super one five
six thousand six hundred k skylike uff
small
ssd for food and free increasingly
i just gotta pop up in japanese
saying that my computer is in danger and
i should
um activate my of my
free trial of a casper
casper's key internet security
shut up leave me alone
i think that's the sign to stop
let's turn up that noise gate again
there you go
okay okay hi nobody
i think i think many of you are uh very
into pc specs so i thought you guys
might be into that kind of stuff
um okay back to what we were doing
patrick chen thank you
and chase maester thank you and uh i
only think i think there's only like a
few left let me turn up the btm again
there we go okay we're pretty much done
guys we're pretty much done
don't worry don't worry thank you for
the membership thanks guys
thank you for all the specs
[Music]
uh feeling a bit down today but watching
the stream made me feel better is it
impossible to whisper never gone home
well i can whisper that for you
oh oh oh noise gate a bit
too low
never gonna give you up never gonna let
you
down never gonna run around and
desert you
oh okay
[Music]
hey samara rico
you're welcome thank you hope you're
feeling better i hope you're feeling
better
james mcphee thank you for the red super
chat i hope you enjoyed the specs
reading
when when the super chat reading turns
into a specs reading
thank you
[Music]
uh
everyone thank you thank you for your
support thank you for watching the
stream today i hope you enjoyed it
i'll be playing a way out a way out
with carrie on her channel tonight
in about uh five hours oh
so if you're awake at that time you
better watch it because i think that
game is quite a good game that a lot of
people are very
excited for oh and then tomorrow i have
a members only stream that's the only
stream tomorrow
oh cause um besides that members only
stream i have to finish some
deadline stuff uh and then yeah my
my schedule is up on my twitter if
you're
ash i keep on forgetting to upload it on
my community
okay okay i'm gonna upload it on my
community tab as well after this stream
yeah and i'll go get some food now
[Music]
again
everyone think you guys send them
the bug kills me every time
[Music]
thanks for tuning in see you next time
when we continue the minecraft
adventures what's up
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
my
you