[Music]
so
my
[Music]
do
hello
welcome
everybody
[Music]
yay
hello
oh we just realized
the glo and the glue gun is actually the
same color nice detail
yes look at my new arm
wait we can
do the same movement
slowly
[Music]
[Laughter]
welcome everybody
[Music]
i have a special stream today for you
we'll be making
stuff of hot glue but before we do that
i
i i recently got some stuff sent to me
uh from
from the office
uh and uh i figured
yo why not put some decoration up
this is from some kind of event uh i'm
not sure what it was
it's uh
oh i have english little chibi figures
with the stands
uh yeah they're from it summer festival
but
um
what what summer festival was that
i couldn't go there but i got uh jenma
to buy me some stuff
um
so cause these are really cute these are
really really really cute come on
maybe i should do streams where i like
show off merchandise why is it blurry
there we go
yes just gonna show up some merchandise
here
oh sure
i i am i wait okay i'll i'll unpack this
and then tell you
oh
oh so today maybe you hear a difference
today um this stream is not happening
from my kitchen
it's happening from my office i brought
the extra table my
my
extra
use it for anything table
um
to my office
and uh because because i don't know i
feel more comfortable streaming from
here and uh
yeah
and and that way i can also comfortably
do a super chat reading right afterwards
no i'm not on the why would i be on the
porch outside
uh
what not using the old yeah yeah yeah i
actually
speaking of my laptop i i [\h__\h]
dropped it um
[Music]
i [\h__\h] dropped my alienware laptop
before the stream it's i didn't drop it
it fell down like it's just bam
and i'm like holy [\h__\h]
cause that costed so much money i was
like
okay hot glue it quick hot glue that it
didn't break i i turned it on it seems
fine for now but it was a really loud
bang and
man it fell on the ground i didn't throw
it on the ground it fell on the ground
so i don't know man it was an accident
um
it's dirty as hell you guys think you
will be fine it's a very fake laptop i i
just wonder like even disc damage
even if i can turn the pc on the laptop
on like i wonder maybe there's some
internal damage that i won't know until
much much later
or so
um
don't make it a habit this is the first
time i usually don't drop laptops it's
not my hobby so now
we uh take the kiwawa figure it's so
cute meet the kawaii
beautiful
my um gloves are a little bit dirty
from previous adventures
forgot to wash them but it's okay
now can i attach this uh
she's standing she's standing like a one
at least we say that in german you guys
say that in german uh there's guys
do you guys say that in english
uh that's the way
you guys hear the elevator music
oh no
can i fix this
okay
okay yeah you hear it wonderful
wonderful
let's do kelly next up
do you guys have a whole life
merchandise or are you the type of
person who's like
either broke or just not interested in
getting merchandise which is fine too
you guys have merchandise
omo cat the omo cat stuff
thank you for getting that thank you
you just hear me out
there is a high chance of one of my cats
jumping on this table eventually but
for now she's i think in a different
room now we have oh here let me show you
cali
cute
kawaii
doll facing they are they are all facing
the same
way i like it it's cute it matches
broken rise up
i mean even if you're not broke i mean i
get it if you have other priorities
it's fine and also stuff like this you
can only get in japan usually which
cover
why why why why why why salad overseas
sell everything overseas come on cover
and give us some give us some good
shipping rates
and shipping services come on
we want that cheap shipping please uh
ship to overseas for a cheap price
please
reasonable price please
[Music]
she doesn't want to stand she's like i
will swim [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
too lazy to stand
what oh i think i got it okay
oh no i didn't get
maybe we should hot glue good out to the
stand if she refuses to stand
hot
[Music]
good are you standing careful careful if
we're careful she might
consider standing good ah
you see that is the cute
jack
[Music]
beautiful
[Laughter]
now my mum
what do i not know
do that size accurate
she does see him oh wait let me look
yeah she's uh built smaller
a little bit
very ah
[Music]
make your own merch with hot glue i
support that or like it doesn't even
have to be with hot glue i mean you can
take an old t-shirt and use an editing
and just draw on the
draw on the t-shirt
maybe you have some artistic skills that
you have not uh
figured out that you have yet
amen amelia what's
the famous paladin's announcer
cute kawaii
i'm i would surely love some hot glue
she retweeted the i think she retweeted
or or she liked the stream um
i i am glad she likes the idea of me
doing [\h__\h] with hot glue
in my last baking stream you guys were
so obsessed with the fact that i used a
little bit a little bit tiny amount of
hot glue
for
my
gingerbread house which is by the way
still standing still standing
um
and then you thought that i would
continue using it for every every food i
make from then on but
no i have not used any glue for
the
uh cookies and they turned out amazing
but now we're back with the glue because
because i can
why the hell not
i will use glue when i want to
[Music]
i'm not part of your sister
now we have tentacle wife
[Music]
cute
oh webcam reflection
at least it's not me
and here we have
the members of whole live english
oh we can play with them like with dolls
like
let's play some
apex
[Applause]
you can't win against me though you suck
i you guys stop fighting
otherwise i'll have to take the guns
away from you okay
hey listen
i want to play apex 2
come on let me in let me in good please
let me join
[\h__\h] i don't play fps games [\h__\h] what do
i do well is this i don't play a fast
game but i can handle this gun maybe i
should
maybe i can join with my hot glue gun
let's see
this is how you do it
[Laughter]
[Music]
in like a million years
[\h__\h] real guns i have a hot glue gun
it's not even on right now don't worry
yay
hi hi hi clippers
watch the full stream clip watchers
watch the full stream are you listening
anyway
i today am drinking
an energy drink this is a good one
because i wanted to force myself to not
take a nap for once and i cleaned my
apartment and i was productive
so
hooray hallelujah
might need to go to a few isle meetings
um this is nothing
the energy drink has nothing to do with
how i am acting today
just so you know so also i tweeted i
tweeted
um salami earrings but i'm not making
them i tweeted it out not because i
wanted to make them but because i was
shocked by how ridiculous that is okay
and ridiculous
but i was also worried like doesn't it
like
you know start to mold in there but
someone else replied and said no it's
actually pretty oh safe and doesn't mold
at least not for a long long million
[\h__\h] years maybe i don't know
um although i don't know if hot glue
works the same way
way as
raising
resin reason
uh yeah it's [\h__\h] disgusting
i just thought it was crazy like they
actually used
real salami
like a salami slice if you didn't see my
tweet you need to look at it and use a
real salami slice and then covered it
nicely in a below and above layer of hot
glue or resin i'm not sure it's what it
was supposed to be hot glue craft but
then they put resin on it resin i
and then they put like little you know
earring thingies on it and then she
honestly she [\h__\h] puts those salami
earrings on her [\h__\h] ears i mean i've
seen cute earrings that are like
resin uh-huh
that aren't like you know
uh like like little pizza pieces but
like not real pizza just like you know
like
you know like the toil-ish pizza or
something like that like donuts or
whatever there's all kinds of cute like
food items
as uh earrings for girls and those are
cute those are cute they're small and
they're not real food so
that's fine but
why the [\h__\h] oh my god
anyway um
anyway let's let's uh put these like
here for decoration
so you always have something to look at
decorations
okay
um and then
i have uh
i i
i realized something today um
because uh yesterday
uh something arrived for me some ex
because i have this
huge bag of vodka
which i thought
is not gonna be enough no totally not
gonna be enough so i ordered some extra
hot glue but in special colors here look
at this
and they're sparkly and all but then it
arrived yesterday and i realized these
are like for smaller glue guns and i
don't know
if it will work like it i don't know man
i have to try it out maybe we can
squeeze two in otherwise we'll have to
make everything with see-through gun
today
non-special gun and then later on we can
try
uh with us i actually went out to look
for a smaller gun last minute
today
um but they only were selling the normal
size guns so
yeah sorry about that i was really
excited to use this but maybe we can
still use it but i think
probably not i'll try i'll try i'll jam
it in
won't work did you try that before
ah
[Music]
i did however
in case you really feel the need to
color something
oh my god
i
i did buy
um
acrylics
in case we do want to color something so
desperately and also just
maybe for another occasion
to make some beautiful paintings you
know bob ross style and
and i think the most important like like
my my goal today is to
um
not
make things combined with hot glue but
make things really only with hot glue
as much as i can um but there was one
thing that i saw that i wanted to add
what do you think it is what do you
think what do you think it is
what do you think it is that i want to
add
[Music]
no
um
googly
[Music]
we can put those everywhere
maybe i can make a spider oh
with like millions of lives
oh by the way i forgot i forgot the egg
let me bring the egg
to the weight
i forgot an egg
[Music]
ah
okay
egg
i'm back
i didn't lay it
this is a boiled egg so i feel like it's
safer to work with hello egg welcome
back egg
first there's an egg and then magic
trick
there is no egg
whoa
it's a cute egg i know i know not as
cute as you though you're cuter
now this was already pre-boiled
i didn't just boil it that quickly and i
didn't lay it
did you lie it
i'm looking for the parents of this egg
please
well the layer of this egg please come
to the counter number two
will the layer of this egg
please come to the counter number two
quickly it's about to
hatch
is that the correct word
so anyway
let's uh do something my ideas are
my ideas i was thinking of actually
some from some things that could be
useful
so i wanna i wanna make some clothes for
this egg
this is
somewhere in the category between useful
and not useful
it's useful for the egg maybe not useful
for me
then another thing i want to make is for
whenever my mom comes to visit
or other smokers an ashtray because i
don't have one and they always use like
other objects to
put their ashes into
so maybe i feel like that's something
that
why would i buy it when i don't smoke
but i feel like i could make a decent
ashtray with hot glue
yes i believe
um then i saw one [\h__\h] this idea i had
myself the astra idea was myself now the
next idea
is
i i have it from one of those diy crafts
videos and i'm interested in if it works
well
um
a flight catch thingy you know that
like a whip you know those little fly
bam thingies
fleek and clutching in germany applies
water yeah i saw they made a fly
swallowers i thought that was
interesting another thing um although i
never have flies here so it's probably
hello chunkers
are you okay she's trying to get up the
country i dare you if you come up here i
will
have to
throw you out the window just kidding
i dare you
i
[Music]
you're not going to come up here aren't
you chunkers
nicole
sorry
don't come up here okay where are you
now
you're there okay
sound case
do you not want to leave the room
perhaps you never in this room when i
scream smoothie sometimes comes but you
unusual maybe i think she's like
confused why this table is in this room
yes investigate
investigate
why there is a table
that's usually in the kitchen
white is here
she's just thinking a little bit and
okay okay now she's on uh on top of the
catchery okay okay we're safe for now uh
another thing i wanted to make that i
saw that
it looked like it could be useful oh oh
and she's about to
[Music]
not jump on the table
good job chunkers she looks like she
wants to
oh yeah she's on the table
it was good of me to not have the camera
on
hi chunkers
i'm just gonna let you take a look and
then you're gonna have to leave okay
you're gonna yes sniff sniff on the
kiara uh figure yeah well it's not a
figure it's an acrylic stand right
wow
what is it
you want the egg
ah she wants the plastic probably she
likes plastic she's sniffing me
are you i'm i'm not gonna stress you out
take your time i'll just continue
talking junkers
so another thing i saw that was really
easy looking was a hair tie kind of
thingy but like in the shape of like a
spot
[Music]
spiral
yeah you want to go now maybe you could
go now
no you're gonna stay okay um
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
hey give her a moment it's okay i don't
need the camera right now it's okay
she's sniffing the egg
i wish i could i wish i could show you
oh
you should show chunkers yeah i show her
who's who has the power here
glue her to the floor excuse me okay she
left
we're we're we're
we are free she maybe also left some cat
hairs but that's okay
um and then
i was thinking if we get the colors to
work then i want to make some food items
but you'll see what i mean with that
later
so let's start with
hmm
let's start with the egg cloves i guess
and okay then i actually i tested if i
can rip out um thing like thingies that
are already inside and already melting
and with some
with some
uh violence you can get them out
but now i have to push it back in oh no
no i wanted to test out if these work
right but ah but now it's like because i
ripped it out there's like a little part
of like um glue stuck in here that was
like when it was hot it was obviously
melt melted but now it's like i have to
warm it up again
so first we have to warm it up
and then
violence yes violence and then we will
see if we can get the i really hope so i
want to give you colorful cloves
once it heats up yeah once it heats up
the stuck part will be fine but i wonder
if we can
push in one of these
oh light blue would be nice there's so
many nice colors
[Music]
i want to try light blue maybe we have
to do two wet ones i'll try that too
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it shouldn't be light blue i was
going to give you casual clothes but i
guess it should be a uniform huh
you're all right you're right do i have
orange
it's like uh something between yellow
and orange
guess that works well what about this
that's red if we mix these two
it could be an orange
what is it is this orange is this orange
no that's also red
huh
but there's a brighter yellow so i guess
this is suppose no this is gold why is
there no orange
discrimination
there's every [\h__\h] color like purple
gray
pink red blue
but they're green but there's no
orange what the [\h__\h]
oh well
um i i i saw something um
someone
didn't mix two colors but they put in
one of these hot glue sticks
um with a string of uh
fabric string of string
and put it in there and then it really
came out like as a as a mixture
it didn't melt but it kind of worked
they were doing something with that but
yeah
anyway
are we ready come on okay uh are you
melting
let's see let's i guess put
the golden one no the red i guess the
red
does that work
i don't doesn't even
[Music]
kind of already get stuck ah
oh no
how would this work
[Music]
i'm having some problems
these are actually almost too big for
this
machine
okay um well this one fits
okay but no [\h__\h]
get out of there i want to do the
other one
[Music]
the thing is i guess that it won't like
if i push this button it won't
go to the front i guess
we have to still wait it's not hot
enough
locked and loaded
egg
this is the last day on earth for you
what are your last words before you die
okay you shall not die that was the
right answer
take it back you cute
you're a cute egg
she's got a gun
i got a gun hands up in here
[Music]
oh hi chunkers welcome back
be careful don't you dare to i have my
hand on the mouse
okay
oh it's starting to smell like melted
glue
i'm waiting i'm waiting
junkers why are you here i don't
understand
you're usually never here
oh you're gonna go go go home chunkers
oh this is your home that's true i'm the
guest
oh jokers you're gonna take take a seat
there fun with me
oh she's an adventurer today chunkers
mommy is streaming
it doesn't work
maybe i don't know what am i doing wrong
is this is this something that can even
work to begin with
why does it not go to the front
does it not go to the front
you can push the
glue stick in i'm trying i'm trying like
here
i'm pushing with this finger here
why it's just not working maybe it's
still not hot enough
it's plugged in it's plugged in
i'm doing the best i can
i don't give up yet i will not give up
if the stick is smaller it works just
have to press the stick with the hand
yeah i feel like i tried something like
that before like years ago
um
[Music]
okay no two
two doesn't work they're a tiny bit too
thick for two
maybe i can like
cut some some part off
okay we'll wait wait maybe it's not hot
enough is it are you hot enough it is
definitely already melting if you put
something on it
don't touch it can't be
don't touch it
should i uh
throw this egg on the ground
maybe
maybe we'll crack it
at the end of the stream
waiting
how about now
oh my god you guys are
the kitty cats
why
oh my god jonkers
[Music]
wait i've been waiting
it's already melting when it's hot in
the front
should i just make you um see through
clothes
we can paint it
although i think i'm too lazy to do that
but
hmm
[Music]
the tip is what do you mean
this doesn't even have a button to start
it it's just plug it in or don't plug it
in chunkers what are you doing
get a 3d pen
it's moving it's melting
ah
but this is so difficult if i continue
always like have to hold it
while
like push it in while using it
wait maybe it didn't work
no it kind of i think it
oh
[Music]
wow
but i always have to push it in order to
make some oh god and it's so tiny like
it disappears immediately
uh okay well um
uh
second one second one second one second
one
second one
[Music]
oh god
oh god what how
can someone hold the egg for me
okay now it's still only uh the normal
gun coming
through okay there's two sticks in there
now okay okay how are we doing
well i can't i can't
i'll make you a santa hat i'll try
oh i can't i can't someone hold the egg
please
do i have an egg holder i need to i
should make an egg holder
are you could you be an ankle
he's an egg holder
uh maybe a glass that's the perfect size
uh let me let me try to find a glass
that's the perfect size
[Music]
i think i found something
it's a shot glass i don't even own a
shot glass
uh yeah okay well
oh okay you guys
don't see much of that but okay
at least it stands there now so i can uh
do other things besides holding it
this will be terrible
terrible yo terrible
um if only i had the right glue gun for
this one specifically
[Music]
uh
huh
i only got pinks left i feel like oh
wait more more one more red one i'll
just make you a santa hat okay
i'm left-handed yo
i'm left-handed
okay here it comes here comes nothing
hello
hello hello
trying to push
[Music]
maybe
with the scissors
[Music]
[Applause]
no i think i ruined it like how will i
ever get all this gunk
what happened here
you see that what happened there
how can i ever
where is it going where is all the
glue going what if i don't what if i
broke it because like everything's
jammed up in there maybe now
and i will never
never be able to
make anything at all
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no come on
come on come on
come on
i mean that would be a funny ending but
come on it doesn't go any further
there's two sticks in there and i can't
push it any further
[Laughter]
another stick okay let's go with the big
stick
wait um
[Music]
like ah i need like a little bit more
get in there
[Music]
why did i not just go with the invisible
ones
oh there's only one temperature on this
[\h__\h]
ah
i think hey what the [\h__\h]
ew there's like like a lot of mess there
oh god what happened what happened there
it looks like
what happened there
[Music]
you guys see that
you guys probably don't properly see it
but like some of the
glue was like i don't know
the [\h__\h]
did the gun melt
no like i actually i see like a seat
a tiny bit of the red there you see it
my mother
my glue gun
my glove on
i think it's clogged yes does that
happen that never happened to me before
i'm i'm really ramming it in there
maybe a fresh one is better
okay fresh stick
like it doesn't move even a tiny bit
when i do this
and i do this it doesn't move the stick
in the back doesn't move
[\h__\h] but it's like all the way in there
can i get it out
no wait let me first try
i need to save this hot glue
try to push with a pencil oh yes
i don't think
that makes much of a difference
[Music]
this is so stupid i think i made it
worse
i think i made it worse i think i made
it
it feels even more clogged up
oh come on
i can't get it
cool plumber mario
mario
keep pushing
nothing happens anymore even even that
part it doesn't move anymore like
see it doesn't this part
[Music]
it's it's like it doesn't this is
supposed to like open up and close
whenever i push this
[Laughter]
microwave it no
i had so many
goals no is this really the end
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] look
this is really the end
this can't be it
[Music]
straight on the end
no
something moved
ah no
no maybe it was just my imagination
leave it okay leave it
for a while okay
um we can draw something on real paper
i don't know
no the stores are closed
[Music]
i am paint i don't have paint
don't have a don't have a
canvas though besides real
[Music]
do i even have normal paper
not sure if i even have
maybe a little bit somewhere somewhere
maybe
uh
paint on foil you mean this one this is
baking paper
use the acrylic to paint the egg oh
should we just paint the egg and call it
a day
[Music]
i thank you i beg you i just want to
make something nice oh
there's a little bit dripping there it's
like there's hope
i don't know when it started but
[Music]
this doesn't look like there's any more
coming from where that came from
easter string yeah painting eggs is
something i want to do for easter
ah
can't get it out i can't get in
stop it how stupid do you think i am
oh my god
um
i think i'm
gonna paint this egg which was totally
the original gold today
i'm gonna paint this egg
um
i think i'm gonna paint the egg
that was the original
the original mission today
that was always always the black i even
fought lancashi
uh
precious
pour the egg at the glue gun in anger
now hold on
well
no
not yoga
um this was always an egg painting
well you know what we will do in the
next stream it won't be egg painting it
will be
okay now get this apple i will use hot
glue
in the next stream to make funny crabs i
know shock wow
surprise
no one would have thought of that before
ever
wow i'm so disappointed
i'm so sad
oh my god
maybe maybe if we just leave it there
eventually maybe something will come out
i haven't painted with real tools in a
long time
for sure
do you mix you don't mix acrylic colors
with anything right no not with water
right and just use it the way it is
right
it's been like
god it smells here but
should i turn it off
i really can't pull it out [\h__\h]
i turned it off to turn it off
use it as it is yep okay
let me open this up
should we make a uniform now now i have
a lot of choice of colors i'll make you
a uniform
this is so stupid i can't believe this
happened
i was so
excited i was anticipating this moment
where's my scissor
there
oh man
my disappointment is immeasurable and my
day is ruined
but don't give up don't give up don't
give up this is fun anyway
rachel
uh
anita
i need an example an egg sam
uh let's go to dakoma twitter
what does uh
[Music]
what does it look like oh my god
christina
[Music]
why the [\h__\h] are you putting goggly eyes
on my
standing figure
on my acrylic thingy ah
you think you're funny
i went on twitter but that looks so
funny
okay so we need orange blue white and a
turquoise we have a toy there's of
course no turquoise
well [\h__\h]
uh then we'll change that a little bit
we'll just keep it white
um
uh wait what i forgot the colors the
orange oh my god
uh
oh my god i have so many acrylics i
didn't
i wasn't really expecting to use them
today i wanted to use them
if anything to
paint the hot glue in case we can't use
the colorful ones and now
the mission has completely changed
but okay wow i'm such an artist oh my
god
art is my passion
yes
okay the good good the good news is we
can still use the goggly eyes
[Music]
hello hello hello
hello
oh
oh there you go okay
[Music]
should i paint a base of white
nah nah i would probably will
how how good does this [\h__\h] cover
orange
a little bit of uh
which blue this glow
maybe that one
blow
and uh
yeah that's it that's all i need
okay
face is good okay cover
okay we'll paint it white
this this is just so tight i've always
wanted like by the [\h__\h] acrylic colors
are so expensive and you only get like
such a little amount it feels like i'm
wasting
so much
that's it don't use too much
okay egg paintings oh my gloves are
gonna get so [\h__\h] up maybe
can you you can wash out acrylic colors
out of fabric right
[Music]
no
i'll be fine otherwise i'll just buy new
ones
no
it stays what
[Music]
i'll do my best to not touch my gloves
and but you guys barely see it let me
try to find a better
egg stand if only i had hot glue i could
create an egg stand
but no but no no no no no no
uh
[Music]
do
ah
i looked for
every ages i looked everywhere
i looked everywhere
i couldn't find
anything
that could be a an egg stand but
really a random thing guess what that
was
uh
something with a pen even for my drawing
tablet or for my
ipad
uh random packaging it's
ah
hot glue we'll fix it
[Music]
wow
okay the only other thing i can now
offer you is i will paint on this black
piece of paper
and then put some googly eyes on that
i have more eggs but i would need to
cook them and i'm not in a mood for that
[Music]
i said i would protect you but i did say
today it would be its last day
eat
i'm not
i don't wanna
what the [\h__\h] happened here today
oh god
[\h__\h]
oh no
okay i will make
i will make a chicken oh god i will make
a chicken um
[Music]
i will make i will draw it
i will draw it
[\h__\h] nothing can stop me okay i am
destined to draw a chicken look out lit
art
has there ever been such a scuffed key
hours no this is not scuffed this has
always been a stream where i
draw
something
so the white
shut the white
yes okay
okay
i i really haven't drawn like this in
like a million years
uh where do i even start i guess we just
draw the the white body of the chicken
ah
i need taco my chicken as inspiration oh
my god
that was a stream
going for jack on my twitter
dangerous game
[Music]
no poor yo
chicken before
[Music]
that's so cute
they're all so cute oh yeah um
first we make
first we make the the sexy plump
shape of
a beautiful
club chicken body
yes we're drawing a chicken now not an
egg
oh god how do i hold this thing
i need more color
this is
not much coverage
uh
although maybe two white was not good
maybe owned i have a good color here
oh well maybe some shading with that
okay
maybe i should maybe i should auction
this painting afterwards and then donate
the money
to
some good
uh cause
maybe i should really just
to at least get something good out of
this stream
what do you think yeah
i don't know how i would do that if
anyone knows how i would do that
let me know
should i um flip the
screen thingy
ah nah whatever
whatever you'll see it sooner or later
[Music]
nice i i actually eventually i always
wanted to do
a stream where i paint
um
like not digitally but like you know
like this traditionally
it wasn't supposed to be a chicken
on a black uh canvas
twenty dollars
this will be worth a million excuse me
million dollar painting this is the
the mona lisa of the chickens
what should we call her she should be a
lady
there was some color stuck in there
might be some cat hairs in here
um so if you're allergic to cat hairs
you might not want to take part in the
auction
for this chicken arch
[Music]
i'm sorry the the thumbnail and the
title is so clickbaity right now i feel
so sorry
i guess i'll change the thumbnail
afterwards
and and the title
did not get everybody's hopes up
oh it should be bigger
[Music]
it was an accident no i was always
planned
i click baited you all on purpose
i never planned to do something with hot
glue today to begin with this looks like
an egg
this is because
a chicken always starts with an egg
for my new hot glue gun thank you i
i don't know how to fix that to be
honest i think i really need to get a
new one and then i'm gonna get a small
end and a big one
this one didn't survive very long
i used it like what once
one time
[\h__\h] but this is this is my fault i i
destroyed it
it's all my fault
man
it's so sad
do we want a theme for this one like
what what is the theme is it is it
really gonna be oh i have color on my
i have color on my um glove that that
happened that happened that was to be
expected
well i am an artist
artists usually have colors on their
clothes
it's just natural
i'm painting this with so much care
beautiful
it's taking color from my
from my finger now yeah like eufy
exactly
look the [\h__\h] look at eelfy
and you will understand
look at that technique oh my god
oh my god what a technique
[Music]
artistic
now we're gonna make this part a bit
more
proper
[Music]
no
no color can shine through
[Music]
the cracked egg
yeah it's just you don't even see the
cracked part
here it is
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's so painful to look at
okay but wait the white color for now
we're good with that
uh
now i need uh
do i need to let it dry
really properly
wait i should
draw what
we're on one side
nice is okay
i have been destroyed
where were you when egg was killed
i was in stream
egg was killed
i was like no
no
[Music]
oh
impossible
[Music]
okay
maybe one wing
here what do we call this masterpiece
we'll decide later i guess
once it's done
would anyone really want this
who wants to join the auction
[Laughter]
i'm so flattered thank you
thank you
i'm gonna try to make it um
look pretty so that it's worth
auctioning it
[Music]
okay
now i'm gonna
make the uh
the red part up here wow
wow wow the the brush is all fuzzy
i can't make exact lines
i'm trying
oh
[Music]
it's a little bit pinkish because of the
not dry
white
but that's okay
one dollar
that's the starting bit right you don't
think you're gonna get this one for one
dollar
[Music]
oh guys
you know what i saw before the stream
on twitter on twitter
automata is getting an anime adoption
for real dogs oh my god it doesn't say
when anywhere but
holy [\h__\h]
i haven't watched anime you didn't know
it was announced today i haven't watched
anime in such a long time you didn't
know i'm glad i'm the one to tell you
um there's no date but it just says
anime coming
near automata
yeah
and it has 2b standing there in the
promotional image
i'm so excited i will watch that 100
i'm so gonna watch that
uh okay red is good
thank you for telling me you're welcome
oh [\h__\h] now i have red on my on my glove
as well
thank you acrylic colors for making this
day
better and better and better
it just keeps on getting better
that is good news yeah there's a small
teaser yeah but it really doesn't show
anything besides the
um
besides the art foot no no this brush is
all red what do i do i don't have water
to wash it out i'll take a new brush
[Music]
it
what was i gonna say
what was i saying
oh yeah it doesn't show anything besides
the illustration the main like promotion
promotional illustration right now
oh yeah
okay
we got orange now
i'm gonna
give you something nice to wear
oh it's already dry here nice but the
brush is [\h__\h] hard what
it's like a cookie
okay
uniform you gotta wear your uniform oh
or you could be wearing omocat merch
you could be wearing normal cat merch
just saying
oh i don't like this brush
why am i using this brush oh my god
this is [\h__\h] what a [\h__\h] brush
please tell me you're using water no
there is no water here i could use the
the water i brought for me to drink and
just continue drinking my energy drink
what would i be using water for
you guys said don't mix it
why is it still watery the color is
really watery what the hell
sell me a new one it's not ew it's not
supposed to be this you disgustingly
watery is this are you supposed to shake
acrylic colors
from wiping i understand
oh
you guys yeah that
you guys don't see the consistency of
that
orange can be a bit rough really what
the [\h__\h]
so let me shake that
boy
[Music]
shake and add a little water why it's
already watery
you that's so disgusting
my god okay
there's still water in
it's still so watery
[Music]
oh my god
why is nothing going well today
[Music]
it's okay i'll make it work i'll make
everything work somehow
no it looks so bad
it looks so bad
like
look at this
what is it with this color
huh
[Music]
and i don't have a palette
it has character
yeah
wash the brush let me drink a little bit
more water before i use it
no the white was perfect and the white
already um
[Music]
the white is already dry so it's not
like mixing with it or so but okay wait
so you want me to wash the brush even
though i'm still using orange
avent guard
thin your paints
i don't understand that it's already
thin
well we'll just coat it i guess yeah
what choice do we have
i have water now
[Music]
a coca-cola glass
guys yesterday i did a members only
stream and i totally forgot i like
wanted to talk about the fact that
yesterday was the
the 22nd
february 2022
and end and end
wait
ah
it was it it was a apparent
and an ambigum
because it's two two zero two two zero
two two it would be the same if you read
it from left to right right to left and
upside down
these facts are provided to you by takan
ashikiyata and takanashikira only
i knew this by myself
yes
[Music]
you knew that my flowing isn't it and we
won't have a number like that uh for
another million [\h__\h] years okay not
millions but
it's the last one in our lifetimes
so
i wanted to treasure it but then i
totally forgot about it
[Music]
i forgot
i forgot to mention
i was even streaming at um
22 minutes past
so it would have been
on the 2 2 0 2 2 0 two two
yeah yeah yeah it could have been
oh god this is so disgusting
it doesn't look nice
this egg looks no this chicken looks
like an egg it looks horrible
it needs it needs a face when once it
has a face i'm sure
it will look good now we will let the
orange dry a little bit
we'll let it dry
let it dry let it dry let it dry let it
dry
let it dry
and now uh
although it needs a mouth it needs an
orange mouth
[Music]
and then we're going to put the goggly
eyes on it with what glue dough
with what clue am i gonna put the eyes
on this
little chicken oh we'll have to
put it on without glue for now and then
later on i'll uh put it with glue on it
once i have a new glue
oh man
[Music]
okay
beautiful
cute mouth
good
now we're getting there we're getting
somewhere sorry this is too bright for
you guys to even see but i'll show you a
progress here oh no there's a little bit
of color on the
on the left side
um
oh well um
look
look at that
[Music]
really
you mean that
i'll do outlines at the end of it like
if it was digital art i would do the
outlines before but since this is
traditional and i don't know how to do
traditional art i'll do the outlines at
the end
um with black i'll just paint on top of
it
and now i need
blue
[Music]
and you need legs legs
also with orange or
[Music]
looks like it has cat texture that's
cool oh thank you for being so nice
uh yeah i went to art school but that's
like a long long long long time ago and
to be honest we mostly uh used
um
like
coal and like
you know we we didn't do much with a
krill
at least in the time when i was there
uh
yeah i think like if i remember
correctly well yeah most of it was
charcoal
uh
yeah
learned some techniques and stuff but
it's a long time ago and we we did uh
like our studies of like fruit
had like fruit in front of us
put on the curly hands not yet not yet
not yet
i guess i don't want to do the sh the
legs in the same color maybe uh oh maybe
that's the little
[Music]
look at that legs
i'm gonna use like a brownish yellow
thingy mustard color
[Music]
i'm just gonna use a lot of brushes so
that i don't have to wash them
okay
[Music]
can i give you some cute pieces do you
guys want shoes though
or you want to go barefoot you should i
guess you guys should not wear shoes you
never wear shoes
this should be like the the classic and
perfect
employee
the ideal
the ideal employee
[Music]
yeah cute
[Laughter]
drip
oh i thought you meant my color was
dripping i mean the cloves
hell yeah that's some drip
if i've ever seen one
okay
[Music]
this is the smallest brush i have it's
kitty kitty okay
okay
he's gonna be an artist now and mix
things yeah
yeah
no shoes allowed in this household hell
yeah that's right okay then i need
[Music]
now this one i will
i wash like i'm a child again when i was
like doing a lot of art with watercolors
i i used to have i used to be really
really really into art and um the best
thing that you could give me as a
present was like art supplies
i was so excited about anything
and i once had these
like pens where
you would fill some water in a container
at the back of the pen
and and then draw watercolor is kind of
like
there the front of it was uh was a brush
and the back was uh a water container
it's those pens were so cool i loved
using them they're they were like for me
they were like next level [\h__\h] like
holy [\h__\h]
that was the future for me
absolutely genius i must say
this is also a little bit watery but
that's okay
[Music]
okay
i think that's
uh
all it really needs maybe
[Music]
maybe i'll do the outline now for
sure i'll go i'll try the outline
oh wait i still wanted to do a second
coat of orange
i'll give it a try now
i like the pens where you can move the
thing and it has like eight different
colors
ah
i'm not sure what exactly you mean
it's not getting that much better but
yeah it's a little bit of an improvement
maybe
it's not completely dry
[Music]
no stop doing that why are you doing
that
[Music]
i will try
to fix you
okay this side is okay this side is kind
of dry
[Music]
oh it's okay
it's fine
[Music]
this has become an art stream
isn't that beautiful you guys like me
doing art streams you always ask for
them
but usually they're digital
well
i hope this is fine too oh you guys want
know what happens tomorrow tomorrow
dory
oh no tony collab with all of us
i'm so excited
and i just
[Music]
we're gonna play garlic phone together
it will be the first time that all of us
will be together and actually will be my
first time to collab with really
actually i wanted to
uh
i wanted to
i wanted to kind of like you know collab
over
already since the beginning when she
joined but i didn't really have a
a good idea or i don't know yeah
um i was i mean if she would have asked
me i would have said yes
but i couldn't think of anything myself
i wanted to do
um
a minecraft tour but then she did it
with
some other girls
so
yeah
i'm trying to do an outline now
a bit difficult but at least the the
stiffness of this brush actually helps
in this case
it still has no eyes it's a bit creepy
a chicken with no eyes because
it means it has a deep meaning guys it's
because you guys
it's because you guys
trust me
so much that you would
um
fall on your back with your closed eyes
and trust that i will catch you
yes that's how much
we trust each other
i i if i will catch you or not that is
not the question
it doesn't work so well maybe i should
use an editing
[\h__\h]
uh so fake oh well
[Music]
oh man
oh this is [\h__\h]
this brush sucks
falls backwards oh i'll catch you i'll
catch you
the frying machine will catch you
something something will definitely
catch you
something look at you
yeah a warm you might feel this this
this uh warm warmth around you which is
totally the warmth of my hands my
phoenix hands
totally
believe
believe it
i don't want to touch it
okay that worked
[Music]
is she going to sell that and we talked
about that that could be a possibility
and then and then
uh donate
whatever i get from that
to a charity because
i wanted to do something with charity oh
no
oh well
ever since alma did that one incredible
stream you guys remember that
and that was so funny when
when she reached all the goals already
beforehand and
i was watching and i was like amen you
need more goals
you need more things to offer you
already reached everything and you
didn't even start streaming yet
so i gave her some ideas i think the
voice pack idea was my idea
did you guys get the voice back is there
anyone here who donate who donated to
that
did you get the
rewards that you were supposed to get
she still hasn't record what
we didn't get the voice
i'm there
she didn't
she's still deciding this script i'm i
guess you know what i'll write it for
her if i have to
what the [\h__\h] emma is like scabbing you
i feel like no one's like you know
giving her the pressure she needs
i mean not now she is busy but
oh i'm gonna give her some pressure that
is that is inacceptable um when did that
happen like a year ago it feels like a
year ago it wasn't winter time i think
i met
[Music]
i need to scold her
they've been waiting
that i'm a girl unbelievable
unbelievable usually you know she's very
very reliable so don't think that this
is
always on me
she always helps me with all the talk
and stuff as well so
i sure
oh maybe that didn't need an outline oh
well
down down
[Music]
let me show you let me show you let me
show you
it's like it looks like a
seven-year-old through this
[Laughter]
something's wrong with the shoulders
[Music]
[Laughter]
two different size ones now
should be the same size
[Music]
it's cute thank you guys are so nice you
guys are so nice if you guys ever have a
child or you already do
and they show you like really shitty
drawings
like look mom and dad look what i drew
you're gonna be like oh good job right
just like you say it to me or are you
gonna be mean to your kids i feel like
you guys can if you guys can be nice to
me and lie to me like that i feel like
you guys can also say that to your
children okay it must be the biggest
ones that i have available i think
should be the biggest ones not the small
one no no
[Music]
okay i can't do i have any normal glue
uh
i don't i don't think i have any normal
normal glue
well i really just have to or is there
something to peel off here
no i don't think so well i'll i'll i'll
i'll give you a sample now
so it will look like
it will look like
[Music]
you're so stupid
[Laughter]
wait
stop stop reflecting there we go
wow
should they be like this or should they
be like that
i don't want like that yeah i want
bigger ones these are not big enough i
should get even bigger ones
maybe i'll order bigger ones
i want bigger ones these are funny
though i'll take a picture on my phone
and then i'll upload it on twitter so
you can see
the beauty of it it's beautiful
let me sign it um
sign it with uh
[Music]
oh let me remember i write i use my
signatures so rarely i need to remember
how to write my signature
majestic
[Laughter]
i wish i could use my heart to stop
reminding me of the pain okay
um for everyone who
came in after the whole
[\h__\h] happened
um
i tried using hot glue but i i kind of
broke the glue gun before i got to even
use it so
yeah i'm sorry i'm very disappointed
myself we'll do it another time
okay
um
i'll title it
uh
why don't we title it should i write the
title here there's a lot of space here
or should we keep it simple
just my signature how big small
jimmy jimmy
employee of the month
ideal point divine title and jimmy why
does why do people want to comment
okay i like that though look
[Music]
that looks like a [\h__\h] five-year-old
true bad
[Music]
okay
um
uh
okay so my sign was like
oh no
oh i'm an artist this is supposed to
look messy
[Music]
getting my signature is really rare
uh
is this how it look like
there was like little little chickens in
the eggs that's that's all i remember
[Music]
did i have hearts as the on top of the
eyes
does someone know what my signature
looks like
it's not super complex no no no
hearts yeah wizard hearts i think so too
okay
[Music]
oh god oh god
this is even more difficult than
painting
[Music]
yeah
i don't if i misspell my name now
that would be a big problem
[Music]
okay okay that looks decent ah and then
i did like did i do this did i do that
oh well i'm doing it now
um
that looks like [\h__\h]
did i forget something
that doesn't like like
is my signature do i have that somewhere
let me let me look at my folders
let's let's look for
uh
[Music]
yes
ah it wasn't the heart it was a star
[\h__\h] okay this one is special guys
on top of the i was supposed to be a
star
but the rest looks fine
okay
special edition value just went up yes
ssr signature oh god
nice nice
okay this is the signature
and and jimmy
this is jimmy
you're losing your eyes
get a hold of yourself
okay he's he's okay he's okay he's
feeling just fine
i'll glue it on once i get a new glue
gun
he turned out
um exactly how i feel today
after all that mess that could have been
so perfect everything could have been so
perfect and beautiful today
but maybe it turned out like this for a
reason
don't blink if you need help
[Laughter]
[Music]
he looks great thank you
he feels great i'm sure
it's all part of the journey yeah
i think i have a cat hair in my mouth
wait a second i need to take off my
glove
yeah okay
i was that was a cat hair indeed i love
him oh i love it thank you
[Laughter]
yeah i mean this is fine um
we had a lot of good moments nonetheless
i would say
um definitely we'll have to change the
thumbnail up a little bit
i think you got ripped off here no this
i wrote this right now
yeah i'll get you that
glue gun stream
at one point
i i believe in it
probably not next week because i'm busy
kind of busy next week
maybe i don't know sometime soon
sometime sometime
within march that's for sure
yeah and i'm i'm excited i will dual
wield guns because at that time i will
have two two guns
yeah um i'm sad about this one
maybe i can fix it behind the scenes
maybe if i
um do some violent
[\h__\h] maybe uh maybe i can get the glue
out of it
i will do my best
two extra i've never had something like
this happen before i've worked with hot
glue a lot
in my life i've done many things with
hot glue that you shouldn't do with hot
glue um
so honestly this was not supposed to
happen i'm very i'm a very experienced
hot glue user
um
so
yeah i'm sad
better safe than sorry well i will
definitely get
one new normal one and one new small one
as two hot glue guns i feel like
that should be enough
okay i guess i think um that's that's
that's it
i will rate super chats now
um
yeah
i hope that's okay for you guys
uh this is the beautiful painting that
we got out of this today i'll leave
maybe i'll leave this screen up i don't
know
i will however go grab some new water
because this one is contaminated now
with some acrylic colors
right sticks for the right guns yeah i
know i know
stick side or wrong size they'll work
once and jam what misses to learn that
the hard way
oh
i see i see
okay um i'll see you guys in a moment
i'll just go grab some water and then
we're gonna read the super chats okay
okay
i know
thank you
[Music]
here's a heart
kfp
jimmy
jimmy we love you
we love you jimmy
you beautiful just the way you are
my beautiful jimmy
jimbo
on facebook he's trying his he's trying
his best every day
okay brb you guys
[Music]
oopsie
i
[Music]
got some fresh water
i saw
sorry sorry sorry about that i moved my
microphone
um
uh okay my my camera is kind of placed
uh somewhere where it's usually not
placed so this is kind of a muzukashi
uh i'll probably be looking somewhere
else all the time probably this way this
is weird
ah
unless unless okay i'll try to look i'll
try to look here
on my on my other
the most leftist
screen to read super chat i'll try
uh guys i have a little
surprise for you guys
um
surprise
tomorrow
huh
is holotori collab right and i was
thinking
um to surprise the girls
they already know i kind of ended up
telling them anyway um just just uh
today but
i decided to
commission a logo for us and surprise
the girls with it as a present it's a
present from me to the
whole tory girls so there we have a logo
now
presented
[Music]
there it is
yay
made by of course spirit snare
and um i asked uh for it to not have
like two specific
um
like signs of
each member in it this time i wanted it
to be more generic because
um
so that way we can use it not only when
we're all together but also when it's
like
a one-on-one collab with one verb and
another verb or a
free people collab or whatever
and and yeah for future burps as well if
there's future burps we can still use it
um it was very like sudden and and last
minute
he made it in one day and um yeah i uh
we're going with this now i like the
little footsteps on the on the um bottom
it's cute
it's simple but um
it i like it it's
cute thank you for
accepting my sudden request to make this
out of nowhere
now we can use it for all kinds of
things i wanted to use it tomorrow for
the thumbnails i'll be making all the
thumbnails afterwards after this stream
and yeah
yeah yeah yeah
based very appealing really thank you
i hope the girls like it
that i like that it's future proof yeah
yeah yeah yeah
big brain kiwawa once again as always i
mean right now i'm a cat but i'm still
at heart it's so
at heart i'm still a verb a hollow bird
so i felt like
making a logo for us
this way we feel like we belong together
even more maybe
[Music]
yeah
okay so that's that just wanted to tell
you that because otherwise it will
suddenly be on the thumbnails and you'll
be like yo what
so i figured i i might just
better introduce it to you guys
beforehand here so the thumbnails won't
be like that confusing
yeah by the way mumei will most likely
almost a hundred percent
you know what probably a hundred percent
will not be streaming
um
but everyone else should be streaming
the
event tomorrow so
yeah
watch it wherever you wanna watch it but
i feel like you guys are all gonna watch
my point of view aren't you
we use the updated whole bird's animated
intro yes yes yes
i asked specifically if i can use it for
the stream
so i will do it
okay
super chattos
[Music]
oh super stickers were off sorry if the
baby wanted to send some super stickers
ah
[Music]
okay
we will only have to read the ones from
this stream because we we caught up and
we finished reading everything else also
from the member stream yesterday
yeah i'm curious about super's point of
view i feel like for guarding phone if
you
you could i think like maybe maybe
the best way to watch this may be have a
few windows open but only listen to the
audio of one person maybe i don't know
so then you can see what the others are
or you just watch one and then get
surprised at the end i don't know but
but we'll see
i feel like
every point of view will be funny of
course
gary phone is always so much fun
um
i think we'll be mixing like simple
english with simple japanese tomorrow
because mumei can't speak japanese
and the japanese members speak a little
bit a little bit english but
obviously not fluent so
we'll mix it we'll speak in toddler's
language which i
of course am very good at
yeah english for bay base
i know louise you know his english is uh
pretty good but somebody will stand by
yeah it's it's also like she can we've
seen in the
in the worms collab that's been pretty
pretty decent
but i don't think we can do a
full-on english collab we'll just mix it
up a little bit baby boobs yeah
[Music]
sweaters passionate that is true
okay patrick chandan
a fruitful kitchen for the rainbow
and wait i should move this window over
here huh
[Music]
so that i don't look somewhere
else all the time
okay kind of awkward today but
we'll have to deal with it forever
represent a big rainbow
beautiful
let me read
er
look how crispy i am and finally fried
too one year has passed i'm happy that i
spent it with you i remember is this a
rhyme
it's so it is a rhyme wait okay when
we're done when we're done
look how crispy i am and finally fried
too one year has passed and i'm happy
that i spent it with you
i remember the first month when i
decided to join kfp and became an egg
roll i couldn't see anything but i had
your beautiful voice guiding me like an
echo
thanks to your warmth and your wonderful
words too i could then hatch but i
almost got a heart attack because of
your chill
that i did catch
oh
cat chat no that's kind of a weird rhyme
it was interrupted but okay okay another
month passed which i spent with joy and
entertainment and i didn't even care
that at kfp there is no payment
i became a chick and i could finally
dance to your music streaming hinatori
high under sparks and just losing it i
couldn't support you from the start of
your journey but i'm happy i had found
you and now nothing can stop me you have
been through so much but have also
achieved almost all of your goals you've
remained yourself through this you've
touched so many chickens souls oh
love you tanto and thank you for this
wonderful year i may have put my uniform
aside now but don't you fear because i'm
in the background okay wow you gave me a
shock for a moment
uh you can bet my fried wing that i'll
always be here yay
thank you frufo that was beautiful
you missed tantra sitting on you ah
don't we all don't we all
don't we all miss that time of being an
egg
yeah
thank you fro fro
your feelings have come across perfectly
thank you shin for your sweet words and
your generous support and for being here
with me for so long
thank
you very very glad to have you part of
kfp
maybe one day you can put on the uniform
again and we'll see if it still fits
you gotta keep your weight
the same so that it will fit when you
want to wear it again
for now you shall be a bucket
genie thank
did i really
give you a one that has been already
taken out of the millions of numbers
that are possible i gave you one that's
been taken genie how how did i do that
oh my god um okay it shall be
twenty six zero two six okay
what are the odds
that is so weird
that is really weird
i hope that doesn't happen again are you
guys keeping a log somewhere of all the
numbers that have been
given to people
zero two six
yes
no
well how did you find out them genie
good research genie actually does
wow
there is a sheet wow
we get numbers now well you all already
have a number but you guys keep on
forgetting it so you ask me to assign
one to you
which makes no sense because i'm not
assigning it i'm just telling you what
it is
this always has been
this number
oh sorry it's for naveed okay i'll go
get sorry i'm stupid
oh wait so you wow you're like man
managing the number for
the numbers for other people that's wow
you're like a manager
see her two sticks what about one two
three four five
okay
okay calm down now calm down now
oh man motion duncan thank you
banana bread okay that will that i will
accept
carrot cake no but banana bread sounds
good
duck joseph oh
thank you for the pinky congrats on one
year for offroad oh
just stopping in before worked to sign
kiana's chimken attendance chain and
wish the chimpkins a good stream kia i
seem to be hot glued to my cafe
workstation
could you help me get loose boss boss
do you really want to
come
on come on
yeah you don't want to
i know you don't want to wait what are
you guys doing with mommy
mommy
what are you guys going on about
well um i'm good to know you're here
again and back to normal with your name
mommy
so sweet how you wish furfo
congratulations on one year everyone's
so tinted such a lovely community
you guys are distracting me
thank you doug joseph i hope
everything's fine over there thank you
for stopping by and saying hello i will
check your name off of my list now
and tomorrow we'll see again if you're
there or not
keeping
exact track of who's here and who's not
here
it's a reverse rainbow
blue
rain blue
it's a rain blue love you all cute
chimpkins things aren't going well on my
side but thanks to you i've had enough
strength to slowly carry on you really
mean a lot to us i repeat this a
thousand times if i have to leave this
only
and of course i'll stay as long as you
want
blue thank you it's so sweet
thank you
i hope i hope things are going better
for you soon
ah i don't like to hear when my chickens
are not feeling well i hope i hope
everyone who's feeling
mad right now
will have
it going back up again soon
you guys deserve happiness just as much
as i do
so yeah fight hall don't give up blue
don't give up don't give up i support
you
mentally
with my
brain um
energy
thingies
can you feel it it's like
brain waves that's what i wanted to say
brain waves i'm sending you
i'm sending you my support for my brain
waves
sorry about that
i think it came across
thank you blue
[Music]
hope you don't feel blue anymore soon
thank you
trevor g dankeshen that is a pinky
altogether
what is this
excuse me
man i missed your rhymes you know your
rhymes your stupid puns i miss them
let's go trevor g
excuse me mrs taganashi i have a
complaint i placed an order over a week
ago and now it shows as completed yet i
never received the meal i paid for
you were busy being so i knew i'd have
to wait but this is ridiculous
at the time of delivery i took a gander
out my window
that must be a pun i don't know what it
is all i saw were kfb chickens flocking
around with a sink waddling toward me
i was growing concerned but i wasn't
about to let that sink in hey let it in
so i flew out shut my door and asked the
chickens a question
[Music]
about my order but they turned tail
and fluttered off without even p a peep
as a loyal cam loyal
canopy member and rabbit heartbroken
over this ordeal i expected bester
clocks to my service i'm sorry but no
amount of hot glue can fix this are you
sure about that
if only i was able to use my hot glue
today then you would have seen it can
fix anything
i will need to speak to your manager
genma while i'm at it i could take her
out to dinner and see if she likes oils
be honest that's your that's your end
goal it always has been
all of the other things that you talk
about are just a way to get to
the goal it just means to get to the
goal isn't it
[Music]
oh man trevor t i i read you're your
beautiful message and complained but i
still don't quite understand what you
ordered to begin with
a meal
but you work here
you're not supposed to be a customer
you're not allowed to complain about
anything
you're you're
you're
you you work here are you aware of that
strategy
i'm a customer no you're not
no
you work here oh my god
how do you not know this
has he been on his shifts
ever at all
oh my god
it wasn't his day off
and what's my job
working
your job is
working at kfp
um
you're not a customer that that i can
tell you
yeah i mean look at you
look at yourself
traffic g
you're
you're a bucket if anything
you are the order
not the customer maybe not even the
employee maybe
look at yourself you're a bucket
of fried
owl if you want to
but you're a bucket
you are the food
have you not noticed
but
you're a snack
[Music]
never no it is it's not about never or
ever
it's already happened look at yourself
you have to accept the reality
someone give a tragedy a reality check
someone help him accept the reality logo
looks cute thank you
he's in denial yeah help him out guys
let him know it's good to be uh what he
is
when you eat when you become the food
that you eat it's not ironic travertine
huh
you owl
you ow i know you owls like to eat
little chickens i know you do well look
how the turns have tabled look at you
now now you are the food
just wait just wait and see until an owl
eats you up
and then and then i wonder how you're
gonna react
yeah
okay i'm like thank you for the red
super chat
[Music]
hey sorry kiwawa i'm unable to watch
your streams live most of the time now
physical class has resumed and i need to
go to bed early oh man
fun fact my current professor is an
austrian
should i practice our usual phrase after
my lectures in german we say
you can definitely impress him with some
german if he's austrian then he would
probably be very excited to hear you say
serbus
sabus
it's a
it's an austrian way of saying hello or
goodbye
i honestly don't really use it but
um
a lot of people do maybe on the
countryside more people use it yeah it's
very informal yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
and uh yeah in bayern bayan probably
they use it too yeah
busy bubba
sands
[Music]
yeah yeah exactly like that serve us
no that's not what it means i wonder
where it came from though i i could
probably look it up but not now anyway
thank you uncle mike for the red super
chat i hope that you can at least watch
the archives in your free time
yeah
it's sad that you can't be here so much
live anymore but maybe on the weekend
maybe on the weekend
um
and good luck with your classes
[Music]
status report from the cafe infiltration
of the mouse's land and we've made our
way into the dl
disneyland our survey of dca
what's dca
disney
[Music]
what's dca
yesterday was complete
presently we are stranded on the jungle
cruise it should move soon if i don't
make it back take care of me i love them
california advent disney california
adventure is that the name of the
disney park in california
that sounds really fancy
or is that like the
a second park yeah
two parks next to each other
[Music]
yeah good i would know the answer
there's magic kingdom and california
adventure
oh
that's a new one yeah
does it have attractions too because
like in paris when i was at disneyland
in paris they also have two parks next
to each other but um one of them is the
proper park and the other one is like
kind of really boring because it's like
it's not really
how do i describe it
how maybe someone here went there and
knows how to describe it i didn't go
inside because my friend said it's
boring in there
um but there are like no no roller
coasters
in the other one so maybe it's like that
in california oh it has roller coasters
too
cool
[Music]
it's got better rides oh when did they
open that now i'm curious i want to go
i'm gonna go to american disneyland
because the one in paris is honestly
lame
compared to what i experienced in japan
um
a disney studio yeah that's that's it
that's what i mean
okay but the last time i went to
disneyland in paris it was definitely
better than the time before
definitely was improved probably because
i had someone with me who knew a lot
about the disneyland there
and was able to show me around really
well
[Music]
but yeah the one in america must be
huge and i really want to see
the the evil queen lady
i wish they would make a
another disneyland in europe like one
one
when there's so many countries in europe
and just having it in one in france it's
just like
dude
please uh we need more
[Music]
maybe in maybe in italy or so i don't
know
not even asking for it to be in germany
and austria just somewhere else give us
a second option
yeah italy would probably make sense i
feel like
it would fit well in italy
and probably do well because italy
already has a lot of tourists
um
have you been to tokyo distance yes yes
yes yes in japan i went to tokyo
disneysea
even more often than token disneyland
yeah disneysea is
um they're both fine they're both really
fine um but disney sees a bit better
yeah
because they have a a few more
attractions and
for people who like to drink alcohol
you can drink alcohol there isn't
anything
else
would love to see one in denmark oh
yeah it would be good to have one more
upper up in the northern regions
definitely
so the northern people don't have to go
so far down to france just to go to
disneyland
yeah that would make sense
so california new york time
ah denmark has legoland
legoland
so you work you re reject having
disneyland just because you have
legoland
hmm wait do we have uh
you know universal studios are in uh
england right only in england
the universal studios i went to was in
japan right not in london
and i think only in japan
do we have
they have yeah
england has universal studios right
oh wait no am i imagining this
there's one in florida um i really
really like universal studios in in
japan
i've only been once but i really really
liked it
it was it was one time was not enough i
need to go again there's not even that
many like franchises in universal
studios that i like i was mostly um
occupied with the harry potter world
that was that just came out when i went
there it was really really new
harry potter world
and i spent like three hours standing in
line for one attraction
so that was
but still i still had a great time
because it was like ah it was so
immersive the whole harry potter world
was so immersive and now i want to see
the nintendo world
they are adding nintendo now no they
already edited you're behind you're
behind
have you tried butt up here no i have
not
oh my god
jimmy is looking at me
jimmy is looking at me oh i'm having a
cramp oh man
jimmy is looking at me with his wobbly
eyes
[Laughter]
oh jimmy stop looking at me he looks
confused
so he looks like he can't make up his
mind where to look at
me
he's looking at me
he wants to tell me something what do
you want to tell me
what is it you want to tell me
oh jimmy wants to go to disneyland too
we'll have to put him on the leash
though
i don't think i can control him once he
goes to disneyland they might want to
try fry him they might think he's like a
although in disneyland i i saw like
ducks running around freely
real ducks so he can just blend in
they probably wouldn't even mind if they
let the ducks roam around for really
they let around they they won't let a
chicken roam around really no
that was just donald no like
no not not a mascot i mean like a real
duck you understand right
those are animatronics no those are real
ducks
no
anyway
pink super chat
is
a
since i'm gonna be on my way to work
when this starts i wanted to send you
something special thank you for always
making my heart go doki doki no
makes me feel really good about
everything just being a part of kfp
always happy to support you and love you
and kfb thank you it can't be such a
wholesome place to be in isn't
it everyone's so happy right now here
i feel like we're the happiest community
right now
everyone's just so happy it's like yeah
you walk into a room
of kfb
and
you just feel like the sun is shining
ah everything's sparkling
everything's so warm and cozy
and fluffy
isn't it nice yeah
yeah beautiful
marshmallows
and stuff
doesn't look like the usual room no no
one no one needs to go out to the user
room now everyone's acting and behaving
perfectly fine
except for the ones who are already in
the usual room
but i like i like the piece that we have
right now
oh thank you
yay
so thank you dead beach spartan you're
always welcome
please continue watching my streams and
have fun and good luck at work today
fight hoof
[Music]
how do you read this
sorry i couldn't glue anything today
sorry next time
pillar next is darkest in sapphy dancing
thank you thank you
squiggly mustache thank you the pinky
fiery chicken boss i'm sorry i returned
all kfp employees i borrowed
uh
that guy
don't take my head i needed to receive
bugs from mama's crowbar okay but you
better not be causing any more trouble
here okay
next time
i will make takoyaki out of here
i will not be fooled and played around
with any longer
[Music]
the fun ends here
no one threatens and steals my chickens
it's my flock i protect yes
and then i feed you to my chickens
because i don't like takoyaki
i don't like takoyaki
i'll feed you to my chickens they will
gladly eat you up
mm-hmm notoriously terribly tasty
i agree i agree but there i'm sure
there's some some chicken here who likes
takoyaki
who volunteers to eat squiggly mustache
i'm sure there's some volunteers
me me me there you go so
be careful
kakundan
60 fps for the first time
what do you mean the webcam
did you mean the webcam or my stream in
general
i think you meant the webcam didn't you
it was it was better quality today yeah
because i i guess i set it up properly
yes yes indeed jesus is the gondra thank
you for the right super chat hi your
boss hurt we might be getting into a
sticky situation today feel
glueing oh
all your crap that is uh
an english german pun
because field gluck
is written uh
g-l-u-e glue ck
means good luck
feel glue
is so funny i like it i like this pun
yay
however there was no glue
um
today
there was no glue involved
at least
there was some glue involved in
jamming and uh breaking my hot glue gun
um
yeah
a little bit of glue in the beginning
good pun i love your pun
it was marvelous
thank you mwah very well deserved kiss
for that
anton m
i will fix you next time oh i'll order
with amazon prime so that i can fix you
immediately
vivi cordage and yoshikawa honeydew
and jacob 47 out thank you and steven
brown
[Music]
currently listening listening to you
while at work and i was wondering if you
ever had trouble with a slinky
when's that reason i'm asking is because
i was messing around with one and i got
it all tangled and now it's all bent
thanks for the fun stream what the [\h__\h]
are you talking about
what the [\h__\h] is this slinky
eh don't be worried slinkies are fun
the [\h__\h] is the slinky
slinky google
oh the ones that go like
ah the one
slinky dog from toy story he's made his
body is made from that
he goes like
uh if i ever had one
tangled up um
i don't recall that ever happening and i
don't really recall
i mean i definitely had one in my hands
before but i don't really recall playing
much with
those
if anything it was probably like a long
long long long long long long
time ago
foreign
[Music]
it's a fascinating
toy though
[Music]
anyway
i wish you uh the best in untangling it
uh when in doubt just put some hot glue
on it and it will fix it trust me
i'm a pro when it comes to hot glue
that's why i'm why i'm wielding this hot
glue gun the whole time
to show you
how professional i am with it
mr casper examination extremely dude
as the 604 dungeon
got a license for that thing oh i don't
need one i invented this thing
angel i recently watched a clip of good
on inna hunting cronian iris for senpai
attacks in minecraft have you guys isn't
that old have you guys ever thought of
doing a minecraft hunter games like
hunter hunger games like enter a big map
solo or in teams and last group standing
wins would be lit in my opinion
never thought of it but good idea
could definitely make something like
that happen but i don't know if 11
people is really
uh
if
considering
uh or assuming that really all 11 people
would be able to participate
sounds like
it's not
that many people don't you
usually do that with a bit more people i
wonder if 11 people is good enough for
that
get id to join ah
well if i need joints we have a lot of
sea and a lot of n a
so i'll be [\h__\h]
maybe i'll organize it and then just
sleep through the event and have them do
the hunger games and i'll just sleep but
at least i organized it
yeah um
[Music]
we'll think about it
well think about it
it's a good idea though
i will have to um
uh i would have to investigate
on like how to do that whole system and
all that
with virgin id
i don't even know that it's gonna be
free
you can't do that math yet
hopefully a nice land grip has more
members in your time zone
as i said before in some way i don't
mind being the only one in this time
zone because this way i have my monopoly
i know i announced auditions ages ago i
know i know but like who knows if
they're really gonna be three people
again
you don't know that
thai fandankishan ironheart thank you
i asked the store for a refund did you
purchase this one recently uh yeah on
amazon
um
but i don't really
i don't usually don't really like um
bothering
myself with like getting refunds and
stuff
especially with amazon because i i'm too
lazy to like put it in the box and send
it back to them
um
yeah greetings from hungary oh thank you
thank you thank you
er
i used to be able to speak some hunger
hungarian because i had a lot of
hungarian colleagues
but now i forgot everything [\h__\h]
er in a different job obviously
amazon refund's very generous now i need
to send it
true i once got something refunded and
didn't have to send it back just because
i think it was like something was
missing
or something like that so obviously i
can't send something back that's missing
oh but yeah anyway nah it's okay i'll
just buy a new one maybe i'm able to fix
it anyway who knows who knows
[Music]
any greek boys good question is there
any greek people watching
feeling great grace doesn't
greece doesn't know i exist
even though i love greece
greek person here oh my god
yasuo
yasu
we are so greek great
[Music]
if anything i would be flying
i will not be going
i can't say if i'll be flying yet
but i i can tell you i won't be going to
dokomi
[Music]
thank you for the membership oh oh thank
you
no no no no no i said nothing
i said nothing
is there is it
how to unjam a glue gun
uh
i think i'll just buy a new one
run a long fine wire through the nozzle
from the inside and try to push out the
clog
run that same wire through it from the
outside and to try to push the clock
back into the gun if it didn't come out
the other way repeat the last two steps
until the breeze is removed
uh nah
nah no thanks dude
unscrew it i i guess i could try
[Music]
m
to
you
nani mukabolo question
yeah i feel you lazy cat excuse me
what did i do
[Music]
y
[Laughter]
[Music]
is that you or is that someone else who
tried to do the same trick on me
is that you it's you
you changed your profile picture on that
one just so i wouldn't notice
just that's not you okay someone else
just for context there's ha there has
been someone who tried to make me read
the words i am a chick
um several times in many ways like
writing it in different languages and
different
uh letters
like korean or
japanese and so on
now this one is a new one this is a way
of writing it that i have never seen
before
i
made
it it's the
i
the kanji for i for love
then hiragana ya and then meiji air era
the kanji for the meiji era so i am
meiji
and then the kanji for time
which can be read in many set many many
different ways i could have chosen so
many other ways of reading it and yet i
chose the one for
ken which was exactly the one we needed
for the puzzle to be completed
for [\h__\h] sake you can read it as ida
you can read it as away you're going to
read it as khan as hassama hazama esma
or as
ken it's like it's like i i wanted it to
be that way
who the [\h__\h] was that
who was that
who was that show yourself
show yourself
you're going to the usual room if i find
out who you are
if our friend owned
if i find out who you are
it was you
you didn't you say it was not you
but
only someone like you could pull that
off
you little [\h__\h]
okay
you little [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i will never forget that
no running aloud you'll break your
little toes
[Music]
ah that's difficult um that's difficult
can't do it that way i don't think so
chris
dankuchen ellie cat duncan do anon
dankeshen dragonspire thanks for the
pinky is there where we send our beads
you mean this
no no no no can't do it for super chat i
i i will ask uh
genma if she has an idea
or maybe maybe uh ame has an idea
well thank you dragons fire keep keep
some of that money so that you can
actually participate in the auction when
it actually happens if it actually
happens
i'll oh i'll give it a try don't get
your hopes up too much
[Music]
worst case i'll keep it for um my
birthday this year and i'll
one random lucky winner
who buys my birthday merch will get it i
don't know
we'll find a way
we'll find a way michiko masada
in the game of creed thank you for the
pinky it seems to be one of those days
where everything goes wrong no matter
what you do it's a conspiracy i tell you
it's not even a conspiracy it's just a
[\h__\h] day in
life isn't it
but yeah today a lot of things went
wrong but i feel like it still ended up
being fun and um
the fact that things went wrong was fun
in itself i feel like there will be
clips of me breaking the egg
and of me fighting the
acrylic stands
and the googly eyes reveal i feel a lot
of clips are happening
but there are two temperature range
for hot glue gun ah it's possible your
gun is a low melt glue gun while the
colored glue sticks are hot melt oh
[Music]
i will um
look at that information on amazon when
i buy my new guns and stuff
thank you i didn't realize that
thank you for the pink super chat
arigatou
[Music]
in thank you thank you yeah i think it
was i guess fine
moon
out run the wind thank you
jim tracy thank you
he wants to be on my fridge oh
it could be on your fridge though
you guys should put him on your fridge
if you win this
[Music]
uh
refreshing the chitty chats
[Music]
and you need to chat
thank you for the pinky i feel bad
because i suggested to stick the small
glue to the gun it's okay i wanted to
try it anyway i was gonna try it anyway
i think i've never had that kind of
problem myself and now tantra's glue gun
went put on stream it happens
well here's for the new glue gun i'll
see myself the usual room much love no
no come out of there no no it's not your
fault i i was planning on trying it
anyway
but i should have maybe before
using the the colorful ones i should
have at least started out by doing some
non-color um glue creations and then
just destroying it after creating
something but oh well i was really
excited on giving you guys some clothes
for the egg
goddammit
live and learn yeah yeah
live and learn
thank you though it's all good in the
neighborhood dominic
it's 127 on that list
which list
if you already have a number
what do you mean huh dominique i don't
get it
[Music]
what list
oh wait so then you already have a
number no
[Music]
are you asking
for another number
no clue
thanks for reading
[Music]
i'm so confused he wants confirmation
did i give you that number originally
then it's probably fine
[Music]
i'm confused
ah
no not me
who gave you that number
did you give that to yourself i mean i
told you guys you can give yourself the
numbers if you want to
uh
you can if there's a specific number you
want you just give it to yourself like
yeah i told you guys you should
oh
wait oh wait it's like a roleplay thing
okay
uh
yes yes let me take a look um
yes yes
uh your number indeed is here it is here
it is number one two seven yes that's
your number yeah just to confirm
sorry it didn't quite come across that
way
it wasn't
yes of course but add a zero in front of
that please
zero one seven it has to be okay
you forgot your number
uh
five
one
you're welcome
down star thank you for the pinky 10 to
my one year anniversary since nana gave
me your husband numbers next month oh
she gave you a number may i leave the
usual room use your room and take a
vacation to celebrate thanks bonds
are you trying to trigger me
they'll stop
i feel triggered
[Music]
i'll start your little [\h__\h]
what do i do with you huh
i know what to do
oh yes yes come out of the usual room
takes your hand leads you out of the
usual room
come here this way this way
leads you into a different usual room
closes door
walks away
yes
[Music]
you can celebrate in there
well i meant you your wing not your hand
obviously
[Music]
sorry i just kind of felt like your the
way you asked me was kind of it kind of
felt like you were
just asking asking to be
put into the usual room again
i thought you were challenging me
uh
one week
[Music]
this stream reminds me of the time i
glazed both my hands and glue except it
wasn't hardcore it was super i had to
scrub it all off about two fronts oh my
god
[Laughter]
i probably did something similar when i
was younger maybe not my whole hand
but yeah definitely a lot of glue
uh projects there for all of us probably
i missed me
five
seven
one
desu
muffin donkey soon
oh
cheer up
cherry thing cherry
[Music]
you know
so twice song that i sang
right now and absolutely butchered it
[Music]
she didn't sing it perfectly
uh where do i
it's my song i'm allowed to play this am
i
she looks so cute
so cute
[Music]
[Applause]
dancing to me is that she knew i was
watching
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
oh what was that voice some korean male
voice
i turned her twitch alert okay okay
she's so cute
[Music]
it reminds me of amelia's thing
oh man cute cute
i wanna i wanna collab with navi mama
mama
she's got the spirit
she tried
i feel like if she practices a bit more
she can nail it
i'm so happy she sang my song
i'm so happy about that
thank you for telling me what a surprise
ah
i was i was blessed
jesus christ
do you think you're a gryffindor
hufflepuff sliver in a ravenclaw
well definitely not slivering
uh
can i do a test
but i'm sure there's a test out there i
don't know man
harry potter house test
chess test i hope it doesn't have any
hogwarts questions because i don't know
[\h__\h]
all right this sorting quiz will
buzzfeed let's go this sorting quiz will
tell you
which hogwarts house you truly belong in
you've made it to hogwarts which means
you've already bought a wand from all
the vendors what material is
it says phoenix feather dragon hearts
string or unicorn hair well obviously a
[\h__\h] phoenix weather dude
if you give me that choice it's
obviously going to be that
during the end of year exams you notice
that one of your classmates was using an
enchanted quill you come top of the
class anyway oh is that like cheating
come top of the class anyway but they
are second what do you do oh it's like
cheating
when i do live in school i saw someone
cheating for a test
i probably wouldn't say anything because
uh i probably cheated myself
depends on the subject but uh the
options are tell the professor i mean
only cheating is wrong no matter what
nothing but if i hadn't come top of the
class i'd definitely tell the professor
uh encourage the other student to admit
what they've done nah give them a high
five for my introductory i would say
but
none of these answers really
apply but i guess i'll go with nothing
uh but if i hadn't come top of the class
i'll definitely tell the professor
i wouldn't even tell the professor if i
hadn't come top of the class but i'll do
nothing so i'll use that one
you would be most hurt if a person
called you
weak ignorant unkind boring
difficult question
not weak because i know that's [\h__\h]
um
i'm strong
i mean i have weak moments but
stronger than most people mentally
um
considering the
the position i am in
[Music]
yeah i don't know
they're all kind of on the same level
you would be the most hurt if a person
called you weak ignorant unkind or
boring
[Music]
hey i can't decide
you need to add the mentoring i know
because you guys would be like xxx
uh which of those four would hurt you
the most i don't know i feel like this i
feel like if it was something insulting
my outer looks it would hurt me more
than these kind of traits
i'll go with something that i won't tell
you
you're locked in a duel
with a skilled opponent they fire an
unknown spell at you and you shout
experiments protego stupify or crucial
uh is expelliarmus the the thing to
undo there i don't know i'm not sure
what these are protegos sounds like
protect
no experience is the one where you shoot
the other's uh wand out yeah yeah
disarming right right yeah yeah yeah
yeah
what does crew shield do
crochet is the strong one is it like
attacking back
protego is shield
i'm i'm i'm really bad at
shielding
what's stupify
horseshoe is unfit unforgivable
that's a torture spit oh [\h__\h] that's
probably uh slytherin huh
stunning knockout is stupid fly oh
[Music]
i
will go
i'll go with protego anyway
it's your fifth year at hogwarts and
you've just received a howler from your
parents what the [\h__\h] was a howler again
what for
sneaking into the forbidden forest at
night on there
getting caught cheating in my
divine nation o-w-l
a letter that yells at you
okay
uh what are they yelling at me does it
depend does it depend on what i'm doing
being put in detention after i was
caught in the library after hours
oh i i see after
nothing i'd never do anything to warrant
a howler ah okay wait sneaking into a
forbidden forest at night no i wouldn't
do that
getting caught cheating in my is that a
test
being put in the tension of this color
okay it's getting caught cheating
[Laughter]
probably
ah
which of these dumbledore quotations
speaks to you
pity the living and above all those who
live without love
words are in my not so humble opinion
our most inexhaustible source of magic
[Music]
it matters not what someone is born but
what they grow to be
it does not do to dwell on dreams and
forget to live
[Music]
that's tough that's tough
opinion almost inexhaustible source of
magic so this is about talking
communication
matters not when someone is born but
what they grow to be that's like
um
your life is not decided by
what
under what circumstances or in what
family you were born i suppose
that's not to do to dwell on dreams and
forget to live
is like
i get it i get it
[Music]
pity the living and above all those who
live without love i get that those who
live without love won but why do we pity
the living
why do we
pity
the living then we pity everyone no
[Music]
hmm
don't pity the dead is the first line of
the gold
hitting the dead is pointless
oh
hey but that's so stupid just because we
because paying the dead makes no sense
why do we automatically pity everyone
who is alive
you shouldn't you shouldn't waste your
time on pitying
[Music]
that's like that's like being like
really negative from the get-go
it might like this is how i uh uh take
this right now
okay i'll go with the fourth one
um it does not do to dwell on dreams and
forget to
live yeah yeah
which of these most wait this is really
long is it oh god there's a lot of
questions okay let me do a speed speed
speed speed uh
which of these
most accurately describes your
relationship with your closest friends i
love surrounding myself with people
they're more friends no
i have a few very close friends that i
would trust
i tend to be very only people so don't
mean yes i find myself becoming friends
with people okay i tend to be worried i
want new people so don't make new
friends often yes it has been very much
that for the past few years which of
your skills are you most proud of my
ability to absorb new information my
ability to make new friends my ability
to get what i want my ability to keep
secrets
oh probably my ability to get what i
want because i've been making my dreams
come true even if they seem very very uh
impossible to
the first quidditch match of the season
is approaching you can't wait to get
involved what role are you playing
seeker i want the glory chaser i'd like
to be involved and work as part of the
team be there i'd like to have all the
power i'll be in the crowd make sure to
support them around high
um
ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
i don't want the pressure of
any of those
[Laughter]
the beater maybe has the least pressure
[Music]
like secrets [\h__\h] pressuring chasers
well
i feel like i just want to be in the
crowd to be honest but that's boring
[Laughter]
uh beater is fun
[Music]
uh
i'll say i'm let's be honest i'll be in
the crowd
you're allowed a pet in hogwarts an owl
cat okay
don't even continue
it's saturday you finish your homework
although i don't want an owl
but cats are
unfortunately a tiny bit superior
it's saturday you finish your homework
and you have some free time you decided
to spend some time away from from your
common room where do you go
forbidden florence library kitchen's the
room of requirement what's the realm of
requirement
[Music]
you guys know
whatever i need it to be
oh
that's so cool
wait why would anyone not go there
[Music]
is that is that like illegal to go there
somehow
there's a secret am i not allowed to go
there is it like yeah to go there
probably right
[Music]
it's a secret but it's not illegal
well if they give me the option i'll go
there let's go
[Laughter]
what would you see in the mirror of a
rise
a reused arise
is that the mirror where you see um
where harry potter saw his parents
where you wait what do you see there
like what would you miss or what you
want or
uh air ruse said what
where you see what you mostly desired
okay
myself surrounded by riches myself
surrounded by my loving family and
friends myself knowledgeable above all
myself experiencing a marvelous
adventure
it doesn't say myself surrounded by my
cats
[Music]
i'll say marvel's adventure um because
that for me will be um me chilling um
the maldives
in on the beach
which of these magical events would you
most like to experience
the train wizard triwizard tournament
the quidditch world cup the ula ball or
christmas at hogwarts
the ula ball is that why harry potter
kissed that girl
it's a fancy ball right i want to do
christmases hot at hogwarts you're
having trouble monstering a new spell
and you've decided to ask for help where
who do you go to my professor my house
goes my smartest friend the library
figure it out myself
um
my smartest friend
choose a deathly hallow
what's that again
the elder wand the resurrection stone
the cloak of an ah
i wanna be invisible
which part do you tend to follow after
leaving hogwarts
i joined the ministry i want to make a
difference in the world i think i
traveled for a while before committing
to a career
i settle down to start a family as soon
as possible
this is like what what path you intend
to do after a whole life
i'll continue to work hard in order to
achieve as much success and success
across possible
i think i travel for a while before
committing to a career
and finally we know that the sorting hat
takes into account your preferences so
which hogwarts house do you feel you
identify with most closely
yeah
[Music]
i forgot what hufflepuff and ravenclaw
was like generally ravenclaw like
hufflepuff are the ones that
i
like
um
kind of like
i have an image of them like
eating a lot
what do you guys think i should be in
ravenclaw is nerdy
ravenclaw's burb
raymond claude is knowledgeable
hufflepuff is
what's hufflepuff how cool are they
true friends oh
ravenclaw nerds i kind of want to be
with the nerds
oh okay
oh damn it's not very clear i am 34
gryffindor
30 ravenclaw 21 sliver in and 15
hufflepuff
oh
just like hermione
granger you were ultimately placed in
gryffindor but the sorting hat seriously
considered putting you in ravenclaw
you're a natural born leader
often taking control of the rains from
others whose recklessness or dedication
to facts and knowledge clouds their
judgment
your intelligent but acknowledge that
there are more important things in life
and therefore aim to use your
intelligence and determination to fight
for what you believe to be right your
slight combat
compatibility with sliver in house
suggests a determination to succeed
though not at the expense of traits from
your more dominant houses
this is a million percent
accurate i think that is beautiful
wow
i can totally apply that to myself in
real life i think
wow
yeah
thank you buzzfeed
um
girl are you a gryffindor because i'd
like to sliver in shut up
shut up
this was this was um this makes sense i
like
it uh
back to super chats guys back to super
chatos
sorry for the little break
um
you really got something out of that
super chat didn't you
and i was i was i was five super chats
away from finishing the super chats
now not anymore probably
ziggurats thank you for the pinky tantra
is a fellow jrpg lover i was wondering
if you're going to try a new triangle
strategy game that comes out in like a
week
is that the one i saw in nintendo direct
which one was that again
i always love to see the
uh rpg streams and i'm looking forward
to trying out this new game
um
[Music]
let me see
ah
i actually um i actually liked the the
looks of it but i wouldn't stream it i
want to play that privately at one point
it kind of looks to me like um
like a mix of uh
fire emblem and uh
what was that other one octopath
traveler
like the visuals remind me of octopath
but the the way the battle works looks
to me like fire and blend
and i already wanted to play octopus
travel since ages i have it on my
nintendo switch
um
one day i will i do want to stream
octopath traveler i'll tell you that
if i ever get the chance to
i do want to stream octopath traveler
yeah oh it's done by the same depth that
that looks like it makes sense yeah
yeah yeah yeah that makes sense it looks
very similar it has like a similar
atmosphere vibe to it
bravely default i also want to play and
maybe even stream that yeah
if only i could but our next uh jrpg
will be a yakuza game again although oh
wow i just realized
the
the first and the only yakuza game that
i played was the most recent one right
and
i'm used to that but
you guys told me before and i'm aware
and now figured it out again i've
remembered that the battle
system
just
completely was a new one with the newest
game and the other ones will work
differently
wait so it's not turn based in the other
ones
oh man
will that make it easier or more
difficult
probably for me
more difficult unless it's really
forgiving
it's action based okay i mean i i like
that too i like that in
in in tails off games too
the other ones are more like beat em up
beat em up beat em up beat em up okay
okay well i'm interested definitely
there's difficulty settings okay okay
they're kind of hard
easier to spam healing arms oh
we did have some trouble
even with the turn-based ones because
sometimes the enemies are really [\h__\h]
strong
i do remember
yeah you didn't love me them up for his
puzzles i am in misery
[Music]
um
boo hoo seven two three down question
yeah that is a terrifying thing to tune
into
the gonzaga tickets monkey duncan skye
duncan thank you
yeah i'd like gunslinger girl next time
with two glue guns
two
thank you so sweet travis
thanks lu for dancing your own skin
moisture makes super glue brittle and
break apart but
i use it to close
cuts
all the time
you ask your parents or guardian
what
[Music]
what you mean when you cut yourself with
like
like a like a knife or so by accident
you put hot glue on top of it
to heal yourself
tell this guy then it exists
i mean that is i guess a life hack that
i didn't know about if it works it works
i guess
oh silver glue not hot too okay okay
whoo
hey
okay if it works it works i guess if
that's safe to do
[Music]
yeah isn't it kind of like chemical
um
like i get alcohol
obviously
maybe there's some alcohol in glue but i
feel like there's some other chemicals
in there and it's like
better than bleeding out well
if if you're in such a situation where
you're bleeding out and you have
and you have superglue with you
i'm actually surprised
out of all the things you're carrying
with you
nothing to stop the bleeding besides
super glue
go for it go for it
superglue was invented to close wounds
oh
[Laughter]
i wanted to do a buzzfeed quiz thingy
with ammo
oh yeah if she's here that might be even
more fun to do that's like a like a
sleepover
sleepover activity doing buzzfeed
quizzes together oh remind me remind me
when the time gets closer please if you
could
please remind me
creative burst thank you
no
that's a fact you're the only halloween
member who regularly streams at a time
when i'm awake oh yes monopoly is not a
joke it's a real deal but i'm actually
glad that i can watch your streams
regularly you have become an important
part of my life well you know
um
for a while i was like
kind of like
not sad or mad or anything but just like
it's unfort i thought it was unfortunate
that i live in this time zone because
like i automatically have a smaller
audience because of that but i mean
someone someone needs to tend to the
europeans right and um
i'm i'm happy that i don't have to
overlap with a hundred other girls so
it's better this way
and i'm just i just feel sorry because
so many of you guys um can either only
watch the archives or you sacrifice your
sleeping time or really adjust your
schedules to the weirdest uh
time zones and and others of you can
only watch my streams doing work or
whatever and or only on the weekends and
so on so that's that's one thing that i
just really regret that um i have to
make so many of you suffer
just because you guys really really want
to see me
so thank you guys for making such a huge
effort to watch my streams
um but yeah as i said someone has to
tend to the europeans you know
um
yeah thank you guys thank you
live with the pain
we wouldn't do it if we didn't want to
thank you
great for those of us that are in europe
yeah well
well i hope the europeans are happy that
i exist
i hope so
listening to your voice relaxes me thank
you
and then and then it's not like not even
like i have a fixed streaming time like
many others do i
i do change my streaming time quite a
bit like sometimes i start at
at 3 pm my time sometimes i start at
9 pm my time that's quite the window
because i do want to try to at least
somehow somehow
uh
tend to some other time zones if
possible but even then it's always like
kind of chutohumpa like um half-assed
it's
always like
i tried but it's not perfect it's not
quite there
yeah i don't
[Music]
yeah i try maybe you guys all need to
move to europe how about that
european
[Music]
but but you know i love your europe and
i love my european friends so
i'm i'm honestly really glad if i can
build a big fan community within europe
yeah there's so many different beautiful
countries in europe i really really love
europe
i love being here and
i want to embrace my europeanness
yeah i am proud you are our pride oh
thank you
i am proud to be your pride
if you let me be
started at 8 a.m for me until um
well i mean if you if you don't have a
job then my streams are probably fine
but if you have a job let's be real
it's uh shitty
uh but thank you i really really
appreciate it and i always just feel so
sorry for not being able to
stream at good times for you i i really
think um
i wish i could do something about that
but i can't
anyway thank you anton m
for your lovely super chat here's a case
for you
for your support
attache thank you for red super chat as
well thank you
made me this glue gun for this occasion
and i couldn't even really use it
thank you don't eat an exhale i really
appreciate it thank you for rushing it
he rushed it it was a rash request
i'm so sorry
little this thank you very fun thank you
destiny's play thank you
oh thank you good to have you in my time
zone
and i think
[Music]
uh oh vander danke
thank you thank you
and sky dancing which europe country
should i choose they're all so different
you should you should decide not me
big sweet duncan
okay we're done we're done we're done
we're done
yeah yeah
yeah yeah we should be done now reading
super chats i'm gonna go make the
horotodi thumbnails now and then make
some dinner and then
sleep
thank you guys for watching
a relatively short stream
for q one standards even with super chat
raining
not even three and a half hours
what
well well well
guys
bye bye
thank you
for today
[Music]
thank you guys or someone wanted to i
think someone wanted me to
do uh the following i don't know if i
can do this properly
um
[Music]
i can
i'm it doesn't look good but only
because of the angle it's not me it's
the angle
um
like this way it looks
[Music]
see that better that look smooth to you
oh you saw that omocat t-shirt a little
bit there
orange
spaghetti arms excuse me
[Music]
love
alrighty guys
best handbrake thank you i'm a
professional dancer so i can do some
some dancing
i can dance with my fingers even i know
impressive
twerk
okay
anyway
um i'm gonna go now
thank you for watching today i'll i'll
make up for this
um whatever this was
kiss the egg i can't really um
i don't know how
without you um
seeing it
okay thank you everybody and in german
we say
auf wiedersehen
[Music]
that's what happens
when you try to betray me
remember
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
put up a new art of me
oh i love his art so much like all the
way he draws skin and like boobs
oh
[Music]
i i retweeted
it
i didn't expect this
[Music]
beautiful beautiful oh he was streaming
it oh
how did i deserve this i was like is
this an old post that i somehow missed
is this from last year or what's going
on i was looking at the date and i was
like is this today
[Music]
a kiss before
okay
[Music]