[Music]
you
do
[Music]
this
do
[Music]
hmm
me
[Music]
ho ho
ho ho ho
[Music]
merry christmas
what's up chocolate is right
there she goes
[Music]
oh wait i should change clothes
i i like this outfit but recently i
don't know i've been feeling like the
streams i've been doing
uh
that my casual clothes
were fitting better meow
meow
meow meow wow wow cat's very talkative
party quinoa
yes
uh hello everybody whoo
how's it going
um
let's start with some pineapple juice
six six six six six six
pineapple juice we love you no matter
what thank you thank you
what happened do you mean no matter what
outfit
i'm so kind of you wow oh wow
what happened
today we will be drawing
okay so pineapple juice is ready so i
don't
um looking at this now after a lot of
time passing there's a lot of things i
don't like about it like for example her
the top of her head is way too big but
you know what i think
maybe i'll get away with like um
liquefying this after i'm done with um
drawing like coloring in
i think i'll do some liquefying in
photoshop afterwards because now it's
like i feel like i'll i'll i'll [\h__\h] up
too much i'll just i'll just color it in
and then afterwards i'll liquify
it
i mean normally like when i when i was
more active in art i
i didn't use liquify for art
uh but yeah um
uh
uh let me put on i feel like uh we
should be listening to
the lo-fi stuff and someone from hello
live so i can come along a little bit
when i don't know what to talk about
so today is not an audio stock day today
isn't a whole live day
hell yeah
haven't listened to these for a while
wasn't there one song that
[Music]
oh well
oh yeah this stuff is so chilly here it
is
[Music]
thank you for liking my art but yeah i
need more practice it's
i i just need more practice that's all
um i'm not like really that harsh on my
art i'm just i'm just a realistic person
i say it i say and see how it is no
needs to unnecessarily flatter myself
because you need to be if you want to
improve you have to be critical of
yourself as well you know there's no use
in saying
wow i'm such an amazing artist when all
you can do is draw a [\h__\h] stick
figure
right
[Music]
don't hear it wait you hear it now don't
you
it's quiet on purpose but i can turn it
up a bit more
how about now
[Music]
good stuff good stuff i hope i hope
we'll hear a lot of those songs
uh in the concert but i'm not even
teasing anything because i have
absolutely no idea what the the others
um the japan members will be performing
i have no idea
[Music]
but i hope i hope there there'll be some
songs like these um
don't evening days is this one
three moon days i so nice oh and i'll
turn it up to lunch didn't i is this too
loud
[Music]
happy lunar new year happy new year new
year yeah
happy new year new year
go
now is finally the year of the tiger
right
it's fine now okay okay this can't hear
really why
it's so i think it's a difference
between people listening on headphones
and listening on on speakers sometimes
people are like yo look i can totally
hear it and then others are like i can't
there's a bgm question mark
moto zone
that's a bit you're rip delayed are you
slowpoke pokemon
[Music]
is the volume okay
thank
remember i feel like last year i got
those red envelopes from you guys uh
when i was playing raiza i think
oh man nostalgic
i think we were playing raiza at the
time oh man ryze has so many like
memorable
um moments for me
ding dong
when i became a clock
i forgot to tweet let me tweet
oh i went on twitter and i see
paco paco papa art of
of iris yo that looks cool
[Music]
oh yeah sophie two is coming out i know
i'm like ah you know what i
i
[Music]
what we could do
is maybe like play
it for one stream
and if i can get permission i would love
to play it as like a members
a members stream because it's so chill
and
and all that well i don't think i want
to do a full play through
of it again in my
on my channel like publicly
but i don't know we don't have many
um
you know games that we can play for
members only
that's why i kind of i was thinking
about like uh what games would could we
play our members only
anyway tweeting uh
we have started
already ready
oh i can't what is it with this keyboard
recently i feel like my keyboard is
broken where are you
eh
nihongo
mo [\h__\h] mata
[Laughter]
food
a
where the [\h__\h] are you
i didn't know that i translated it like
this it almost seems like oscar was a
valley girl
coco
[Music]
i don't celebrate it but a lot of you
guys seem to celebrate it
so hallelujah
to you
so i need to figure out you know my
since i'm not not an art stream i
usually
um i have a
i i'm not really like capable but like i
don't have the ideal
setup here um my drawing tablet is my
left screen
unlike a mount
um i can move it closer to me but not in
the perfectly comfortable
position unfortunately oh well
as close as possible okay well this is
fine this one
this is fine
okay
where's my pen here's my pen oh my god i
have my pen yeah let's go
okay
yeah try moving your chair huh
no
i don't really i don't really i can't
but i've been thinking of completely
redesigning my office
uh like completely moving everything
around but i will need some help from um
a friend
because i can't do that [\h__\h] alone but i
i wanna i wanna move everything around
so that i also have more space for stuff
like vr
and
i don't know anything else that might
come up in the future
no alarms not not really because of i
mean that as well but also it's a pain
in the ass because now i got all these
cables
somewhat decently uh organized and uh
if i move this table i want to get a new
table actually i need a bigger table
but i can't find oh we're already
starting here to chitchat unbelievable i
can't find bigger tables
shut away the moment
where do you get bigger tables huh where
do you get bigger tables
[Music]
yeah i was thinking about the corner
desk because those are in general
kind of bigger than
normal desks just because they're corner
desks
[Music]
yeah yeah i had one of those in
japan
because of space reasons space issues
uh what was i going to do oh yeah
[Music]
can i put that in there nice okay
you celebrate lunar new year in korea
too
where do you celebrate lunar new year
because i feel like when i lived in
japan they didn't
they didn't celebrate it
what they do in korea
you do
[Music]
didn't realize that
happy new year
happy
um
[Music]
let me grab my phone maybe i'll grab a
cat as well
there's a cute
bread loaf on the floor let me pick it
up
[Music]
i failed i don't know if you heard me
giggling but she my my bright loaf
suddenly grew four legs and escaped
it was chunkers though she's very loafy
yum
okay so
it's gonna be
probably a pain in the ass but let's go
uh
i have a picture of myself here
to pick the colors because
i'm a [\h__\h] noob
and uh
wait rest earlier i forgot how to use
this program raster layer i guess so
can i change the name um skin
so that we'll know what we're doing
i will name the layers
it's gonna look much better with
color probably perhaps hopefully
self portrait yeah
yeah yeah yeah i started this kind of
soon after i got the new outfit
yeah okay so normally
normally what i do but in this program i
realized it doesn't work so well
which kind of pisses me off
um but okay let's try it out here
i just select
uh where i want to
put the skin color on
but this worked so much better in that
other drawing program that i used to use
called psy
[Music]
i look so weird in this
what i i don't have a discord server but
the kfb
fans uh
have one if you someone's asking for my
discord server i don't have one
um
[Music]
i feel like my hand is drunk
what do you mean lockdown
well you don't want new people be
friends be friendly take downs
take down seoul south sword
[Music]
slap that wrist
no no
we don't slap here we don't slap anyone
except chimpkins
[Music]
you guys didn't think i would uh be on
time today did you you thought i would
delay the stream for like an hour or so
i know because i thought i thought there
was a risk of me doing that as well when
i scheduled the stream
i expect that you're like at least
you're honest
but here i am on time because i was able
to sleep pretty nice not really
not really early i guess but
a bit earlier than usual in the past two
nights
um
so
kind of thanks to that i am here yeah
we shall
[Music]
huh i got out of bed right when you went
live i was worried i was late
thank you we woke up for me
it's incredible to think about how
people some people out there adjust like
their
schedule of the day in order to watch me
and like wake up in order to watch me
that's crazy
that's crazy you guys like me too much
kfp at
[Music]
i love that she says that
you like me too much is what she says
sometimes cute it's cute
i don't know why but it sounds so cute
when she says just anything she says
sounds cute so
i should draw fan art of the other whole
life members maybe they maybe they would
uh like me
if i do that
and i'll do
eye eye color piggy piggy
and i really like my tension too much no
i guess not
no um
we've learned in i guess we've learned
in uh
yes
the day before yesterday's playthrough
of needy girl
there's something that confused me about
that game on on stream on steam it's
called needy girl
overload i think but the logo that i
found was needy girl overdose is that
just a difference in
japanese
game title but why would they make such
a tiny change
it's a bit confusing oops what am i
doing
um
a localization thing i thought so
because then someone in the comments uh
uh tried to correct me by saying hey
it's not needy girl overdoses need to go
overload or the other way around i don't
know it's confusing
and i was like hey wait a second and i
checked and then i also saw
that then i looked at enos and callie's
um
uh titles and thumbnails and they also
got everything like mixed up
[Laughter]
yeah it was pretty difficult to find the
transparent logo which was also an issue
why is the color so
what
[Music]
where's the color
oh
okay
wait oh [\h__\h] that means that the skin
layer is uh [\h__\h] a little bit
transparent [\h__\h] oh whoa
[\h__\h]
why did they
[Music]
change it from
those two loads
i wonder what the reason is
actually um yesterday in the middle of
the night
the composer of all the music of the
game
uh
followed and replied or wrote a tweet to
me
yesterday did you see that on twitter
[Music]
i see
yeah yeah
uh i guess because i was vibing so much
to the music
was legit good i think my favorite part
about the game was the music
um i mean maybe it's
not really something i would like
choose on purpose to listen to
randomly um but
but
in the moment it was [\h__\h] awesome
and also uh because i didn't get to
listen to it um
during the
uh
doing the game park portion
uh wait a second transparent pixels was
this
yeah okay
um i i checked out the music video
because the girl kangel
she releases
um a song apparently when you get to
500k now we did get to 500k
but
i
um i guess i reached it too late
and uh
yeah because of that we didn't really
get that scene i don't know how to color
eyes i don't know how i want to color
there's so many different ways to color
eyes and i don't know how i want to do
it
okay no that was uh oh man
um
still trying to figure out how to get a
million i've been thinking a lot about
it after the stream
i've been thinking a lot about the game
i also watched inna's complete stream
from beginning to the end
um
yesterday yesterday i think it was
yesterday i watched it because i went i
was like yabby how is she gonna react
but she um actually tackled the game
quite differently than i did
um impressive
i must say
uh because i freaked out about
everything and i
i see there's also a
calm way to play this game
for me it was impossible the game the
game oh my god uh it [\h__\h] me [\h__\h] my
[\h__\h] with my
mind i couldn't stay calm
i can never stay calm
i know i don't need
[Music]
actually like i realized like mostly she
got the same
like chat messages from kangel at the
same like she got the same streams and
all that i guess to a certain
um
amount
uh the game
play is very similar
depending like yeah um no not really
depending it's very similar from
streamer to streamer
um i guess because we have a
similar way of playing it
i might have played it differently if i
was playing it off stream yeah to a
certain degree
it's it all ends up being very similar
so
whenever you know i was doing something
i was like oh i did the same
but she did not get to 500k
uh her first
her first ending was oh should i spoil
this if you don't want to hear it then
close your ears now
your first ending was uh
you know getting
two two days before the end getting uh a
hundred affection
now i know what that ending looks like
too
the game just ends when you get on the
defection it just ends
she just goes like i love you i love you
i love you i love you i love you i love
you i love you i love you love you and
then it just ends
because she overdosed on love apparently
so that's a thing
and she tried some other endings as well
but you know i maybe i could have done
the same but no at the end of my stream
i was i was just no i couldn't
i i was overdosed on the game
it was too much for me
in my play for kangel got stolen by the
horseman
horseman you mean the the tinder
the tinder horse
what
stolen by a horse
oh my god almost almost like the rumors
about catherine the great saying that i
don't know if that was really a rumor
but in in the show in the hulu show
of catherine the great
there's a big rumor going around that
she um
can i know
was it really a rumor in reality
they they really joked a lot about it in
the show as well
and she's always like i did not
oh
wait where's my beep there it is i did
not a horse
oh man
what was that actress's name again
what was her name again
such a cute actress and her saying stuff
like that is so funny
[Music]
um
l fanning yeah yeah elf fanning going
like i did not
a horse
over and over and over again she gets so
mad because like the court the court
kind of makes up
um
a rumor because i guess they didn't like
her
they make up a rumor that she
oh
[\h__\h]
a horse
of course she didn't
she's a lady okay she's a lady
what the [\h__\h] are we talking about
hey eyes like this when you don't put in
the highlights they look pretty and they
look pretty um yandere don't they
doesn't doesn't leina have an option for
her eyes to get rid of the highlights
and look like this i think i i saw that
in her
playthrough of needy girl
i want that too
the dead fish eyes yeah
okay papa
[Music]
no
just kidding
i mean if i could get him why the hell
on
my eyes aren't beautiful
that those were something i was um very
proud of especially in the i mean i'm
still i still am but i was i was showing
off my eyes a lot back in the day
i was like my eyes are [\h__\h] beautiful
are they not
[Music]
they are so detailed it's my favorite
thing about myself is
probably my eyes if i had to say
in my hips because my hips don't lie
um
[Music]
so that has this the same song down loop
the whole time oh my god i thought i was
looping the album
down
mouse how many cat hairs are in my mouth
sensor huh
it's a lot one two
[Music]
three
come out there
three oh wow four
five
[Music]
six seven
eight
nine
you know in that little hole where where
it's like there's a light in the mouse
and there's a lot of cat hairs in there
[Music]
i can't reach all of them
some of them are too deep
okay now it's better though
[Laughter]
don't let that light hit your eyes by
the way yeah i mean when i'm looking
right into it it's i i'm looking into
the light is that a bad light
i don't know they said it to me
as if it's some kind of
yeah by light
it's not like i was immediately like oh
my god i believe you
i was just asking
lasers are bad for eyes
no it's not amazing what the [\h__\h] you
guys are not even sure about it either
and you're making fun of me and like
yeah dot dot dot as if as if i'm so
stupid i'm not the only stupid one in
here then
dear lord
always judging me
[Music]
what are you trying to say
what what's your problem
um
just playing around with the eyes but
i feel like
i'm like uh
we can end it soon for sure
i had a i had a dream last night
i was doing my makeup
and uh
and it was a huge dream [\h__\h] weird a
lot of weird thing happening and then i
was doing my makeup with someone else's
makeup because i forgot or i lost i
don't know ah no i was in france
apparently uh and then i arrived
somewhere where i needed to do my makeup
and i was like i don't have my makeup it
just came from france and then they gave
me their makeup to work with and and
then i put on the makeup and then
someone that comes up to me and is like
yeah what's that on your face and i look
into the mirror and on under both of my
eyes
or like partially in my eyes
on each one of my eyes there's a spider
sitting
who the [\h__\h]
man like uh under my eyes was the body
but one of their legs each was in each
of my eyes
and i was like hey what the [\h__\h] i
pulled out the eye
and another i won't have the spider
yeah i was weird that was so weird weird
dream hadn't you done
it was it was a relatively small spider
but with long legs pretty long legs so
that was [\h__\h] creepy
[Music]
okay let's do
highlights actually
why does it still look
why is it was it always uh kind of
transparent oh well what does it
it will be fine
dun dun
[Music]
something like that
something yeah check the brush settings
but brush density is hundreds so i'm a
bit confused but okay so eyes are okay
ma
mama
manzo kakana
i'm okay i'm good with that but you know
i like to do something weird here with
the eyes
with the lashes
[Music]
doesn't work now it works
i don't like these
i don't like these brushes
gum
[Music]
what's the setup being used here ipad no
i have an ipad but i don't i don't use
it for drawing
i don't use it for anything
uh i'm using my cintiq
with
with a
clip studio
but one thing i've noticed
when drawing on this cintiq
during the daytime is
it reflects the light or maybe actually
no doesn't matter if it's daytime it's
just the ceiling light reflects on the
tablet it's kind of
annoying
man
it's irritating
you can use ipad for carrying lasagna to
the pc i like the way you're thinking
yeah you would think that an
expensive tablet like this
would have
you know a feature in the screen that
doesn't reflect that stupid light
um
yeah
because it's for drawing and you look at
the screen man
anyway whatever
it's not that bad
[Music]
oh wait we're listening to blue clapper
again oh i forgot to loop the whole
thing
your eyes are beautiful oh my god
thank
you your eyes are beautiful two
chimpkins
actually did you notice that i put a
chimpkin into the thumbnail but
um i got the art from ida so yeah you
know that free like clips flip clip
style all right
um
that was originally a parrot
but i liquified it to make it fat
um
and then changed some of the colors and
and and stuff it was originally a parrot
you could tell it was that it's a it's a
parakeet i guess or whatever how you say
i don't know
i was like i i wouldn't be talking to a
parakeet they think i'm crazy
if anything i talk to my chimpkins
who talks to a [\h__\h] parrot man crazy
people only people who have no one else
to talk to maybe not me i have chimpkins
i talk to my chimpkins big difference
big difference
[Music]
sorry kiana sorry it's just easier that
way
sorry
[Music]
i don't like these brushes i don't know
which brush to work with realistic
thick
[Music]
i don't know
that's just too much
i don't like these brushes i didn't
really test out the brushes you know
i don't know what i'm working with oh
well
we'll just
it will be a hot mess
of
brushes
being used by an amateur
um
[Music]
at least parrots can talk like what
about people who talk to cats
excuse me
excuse me cats talk back as well
it's just
humans are too stupid to understand what
they're saying how about
how you know how you know people are
often like yo you came to my country you
better learn my language well how about
we learn cat's language
um
we came to the kent's country this i
think cats existed before humans did no
probably probably
evolution-wise
cats probably existed before humans did
did they
correct me if i'm wrong maybe if not
even if not
they did well there we go oh make me out
dinosaur meow
so
so they were here before us
so we should learn their language we
should adapt to their language
[Music]
i think that's only logical
and and they're even so kind
to meow for us the only reason why they
meow is apparently for humans to kind of
understand loki what they're saying
apparently right because otherwise they
wouldn't apparently wouldn't even be
meowing much
they're doing it for us and we're not
even trying to understand them
it's that's that's
heresy or whatever
they're meowing for us trying their best
to communicate and we're just like haha
mia whatever
we should be taking notes
oh they me out
for five seconds in that tone
uh at this time of the day
and after giving it food it stopped okay
that probably means it said food please
[Laughter]
you take notes and now you take notes
who says i'm not already fluent in cat
language have you not noticed the way i
meow back and my cats were obviously
having a conversation you need to take
notes not me
[Music]
i'm already done studying catfish
and you wonder why i enjoyed the movie
cat so much
because i understood it on a whole
different deeper level
that's why you can't enjoy cats and i
can
yeah language barrier it's
understandable i guess i guess can't be
helped
can't be helped if you guys just don't
know the language
[Music]
i love cats
i just love cats
it all makes sense now
right
actually uh while we're talking about
cats here's a tangent
that no one cares about that no one
asked
for uh i was watching before the stream
after waking up i was uh watching a
little bit of
disney plus i was watching a
stupid cartoon
american cartoon show
not gonna say what but i just needed
something where i don't have to use my
brain
to wake up to
and
at one point i noticed
that smoothie
smoothie was
very very intensely with
uh
like all all its attention to the tv
watching it with me
like she was like
her eyes were like
she was like looking following what's
going on on the screen
and
normally like i get it they do it when
there's like for example like a simple
background like a black background or
whatever and then there's like a mouse
or a
official whatever going from side to
side like you know videos for cats
but like in anything any other show that
i watch on tv it's like too much going
on so my cats don't care
they don't care about it but
and there was a lot going on on the
screen today as well but my cat this
movie was like
wow she was so fascinated by it
[Laughter]
she was so fascinated she was chilling
on the bed with me and then i i was like
i'm gonna pet you now and then she she's
like stop i'm busy right now and she
walks away from me she walks further
closer to the tv
and she
she sits like
literally in front of the tv looks up
and continues to watch tv
while refusing to being pet by me
unbelievable
unbelievable i say
i know about the nose guys i could be
like yo i'm gonna make a realistic nose
now
let me show you
realistic nose time
if i were to do that
it's tommy
oopsie
and then and then and then and then
flap your hands oh no that was not it
and then we do obscene
nose
[Music]
there you go
fruity nose w
wow got a nose job
but kiwawa as you can see here has
no nose
so that's not gonna work
what's the other option the other option
is just drawing it like
all these
enemy anime knows this but i'm not happy
with this either
oh well
it looks it just looks weird because
i've been
i've had too much time with this piece
of art looking at it
oopsie
hmm
what
well it do be a nose
what i did not watch arcane no
i still have not um
looked at that
just don't know if i should like draw
the bottom part like that
[Music]
doesn't look weird
oh [\h__\h] weird
nose
[Music]
just kidding i'm just kidding i'm not
serious of that
but
most people draw anime like they don't
have a nose but the more i look at it
the weirder it looks to me
the solar cell is so
oh
anyway something like this that's okay
that's okay that's okay
uh so we were talking about my cat
watching uh a cartoon with me
well uh well good start into the day
good start
and i had uh some
stretchatella stretchatella cake
uh
for breakfast
oh and last night i had ramen yesterday
was my day off right and i went to eat
ramen alone
it was good ramen and
there was a
ramen yeah okay for breakfast yeah why
the [\h__\h] not
simple breakfast
easy just cut off a slice and eat
um but yeah yesterday
i was at this ramen place and um
i was talking to one of the staff
working there
and
i don't know they were they looked nice
and they just they said hello and i was
like okay i guess i have to be social
and make a conversation and
because it was the first of february i
was like hey it's lunar new year right
so
uh i was like
where are you from
and they're like guess
and i was like oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
um
so the guessing game started i was like
please take off your mask for a moment
and i was like okay you're not from
you're not from japan
and they were like yep that's right
and i'm like
you're not from
china and they're like yes you're right
he was quite surprised at me guessing
that
now i'm pretty good at that i'm pretty
good
i'm pretty good at that i think other
people would just randomly be like are
you chinese and then yeah
because they're they're not so used to
yes so anyway then i was like you're
also not from korea and he was like yes
that's correct too
hell yeah so i got i got three countries
down
uh and then i was like [\h__\h]
i got those free rides but
like okay where to go from here
and then i then i was i blanked i
blanked because i i don't i did not know
where to
find those features
eventually i had him give me a hint
and he told me
uh he told me the following
that
where he's from
he
there they had a king until not so long
ago apparently like he said 19
19 200 and 1920
uh
no [\h__\h] idea
maybe you guys already know just by
saying that
uh but it didn't really help me man
and then he he like started
boasting about his king
saying that um
saying that he
uh oh that that austria almost would
have been part of his country
uh if that king wouldn't have failed
last second or so and i'm like what
oh and he did say his country is next to
russia but um
me and geography no [\h__\h] idea but
yeah it turned out to be mongolia yeah
i didn't get it even after all those
hints and oh but then he was like oh
don't you know genghis khan and i'm like
hell yeah
it's gone
hey buddy
he was like
but no i mean i've heard of i've heard
of the name
i've heard of the name thankfully so um
that is only thanks to
thanks to the idol song from betty's
kobo which is called genghis khan so
what do we what do we learn out of this
that you can learn some decent
decent
history from idols
oh yeah actually it's a german song
apparently originally but i know it from
a japanese idol group called genghis
khan
anyway i said i'll be back and he said
yeah um next next time you're back
you're gonna tell me all about uh
genghis khan right and i'm like yes i'm
gonna do my homework i'm sorry
but we had a we had a fun conversation
he was very nice
is there anything you can't learn from
idols no you can learn everything from
idols
everything
even math
oneplus 3 is for
hell yeah
oh yeah and then i told him at the very
end sorry i was actually just asking you
because i wanted to know if it's
appropriate to say happy lunar new year
to you or if you don't celebrate it and
he was like yeah yeah we do celebrate it
today so i was like happy new lunar new
year and it was like thank you
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
happy lunar new year to you
i just wanted to
have a conversation and i said happy new
year
um
wholesome yeah yeah yeah he told me how
long he's been in
austria
and he had a really weird reason for
being in austria i was not able to
understand that man
he told me that like um
uh what was it like he
he originally wanted to move to japan
because in mongolia apparently you can't
make much money and
he had a wife and
and i don't know they they wanted to
move somewhere else where you can make
more money
understandable right
when is this mouth why does his mouth
look so weird
and originally i wanted to go to japan
but i think his wasn't his mother
told him that
uh learning japanese is so difficult you
should
go to austria and learn german and i'm
like
huh
what kind of conclusion is that how do
you get from
no japanese is too difficult go to uh
austria instead and then i was like why
not go to germany then
they speak german there too and it's way
bigger how how the hell
what
[Laughter]
very very interesting
[Music]
and like i mean
if if if you're
if you're
i mean i don't i don't really know
how difficult
his mother tongue is but i'm i'm
guessing that it would be easier to
learn enough another asian language
than um
[Music]
than german
wouldn't it be more difficult to learn
german than japanese he said because
japanese has uh kanji
well okay but german language from what
i've heard from other people who try to
learn it they all have a struggle quite
a bit with it
so
you would think how was this german his
german was uh
very very good but he has been here for
quite a
while at that point it was not like
um he would still know that he's not
born here but very very good
very impressive
i told him i told him
[Music]
they always react to my
sounds
[Music]
hi
you can come here you remember when i
told you i think it might have been the
members only stream but i got this
blanket this cute
pink blanket
and with um
with cat ears oopsie what did i do
hi meow
meow
oh yo
she's rubbing her
she's rubbing her face against my pen my
tablet pen
uh yeah yeah i got this blanket and uh
i put it on the chair that movie likes
to chill on and now now she she really
really loves it
blanket is so cozy
[Music]
yeah yeah blanket cute blankets not my
blanket anymore
it's her blanket now yeah
that's okay that's okay
i was i only only really bought it
because i thought i need more blankets
in this house
yeah
oh [\h__\h] i'm on the
oh [\h__\h] i'm i was on the wrong layer
[\h__\h] oh well that's okay
[Music]
da
oh she's on the shelf now
she's playing
parkour did you hear that meow
she was singing with me
is that
the reason i like that restaurant is
because
they change
the ramen
up for me like i i made a couple of
requests and they they answered to all
of my requests and now i'm like hell
yeah they're so nice
i love them
i love
them good restaurant
[Music]
eh rip myself
did you cat
throw over your your shelf oh man
sorry about that
always nice when there's good service
hell yeah they're also nice like they
had a lot of
every every [\h__\h] staff member
said hello to me and they all asked me
my name and then the the the dude
who i had the whole mongolia
conversation about he he also asked me
what my job is i was like oh i work for
japanese entertainment company and i was
like oh what's it called and i was like
oh you you wouldn't know
the name so never mind
oh
it's so hard to make a conversation why
do you have to ask what company i work
for
why why it was one of his first
questions towards me
[Music]
why
i can't
[Laughter]
[Music]
very difficult
do you forget how to people you have to
have to socialize how to be a person
i get that question a lot like where do
you work
and i don't want to lie to them it feels
so bad i feel guilty about la i don't
want to just make up some
random [\h__\h] and even if i do sometimes
they ask more then i have to make up
more random [\h__\h]
so most of the time i just i just say
something but i say it in a way that
maybe they get a hint that i don't
really want to talk about it so i'm like
oh i
i work for it
i look for
entertainment company and the other day
i said i work for uh i work for a tech
company
i'm a voice actress i tried that before
too but they ask a lot of questions when
i say that
when i say i'm a voice actors they're
like oh that's so cool what do you do
like for tv for a movie what what where
where what
and i'm like oh oh you wouldn't know
it's
all in
japanese
it's not but let's just say it is
um
yeah it's a way to interesting sounding
job you have to say something that
doesn't sound interesting
uh
like i don't want them to ask too many
questions
[Music]
very tough man
i heard people don't ask questions about
accountants so what i should say i'm
accountant i don't want to completely
lie to them and make something
completely random up that's like oh i
would feel bad about lying too
i'm an accountant yeah yeah sure i love
that plush thank you
say you manage a fast food franchise oh
i should say i work at kfc
[Music]
say that i have an nda i don't know it's
just so awkward to
let's say i'm in um uh i don't know i'm
in a restaurant or in an uber or
something and they're just being nice
they're like oh where do you work and
i'm like i'm not allowed to say sounds
like i'm a secret agent or something
i don't know i mean it's reasonable it's
a reasonable answer
but
i don't know
i should just say i'm a neato i don't
have a job
i sit at home all day
and i spend uh most of my day on youtube
which i really do
but then they think i'm a [\h__\h] loser
what you don't have a job ew
what so what nito is besto
it's the ideal lifestyle
what's your problem huh
what's your problem
[Music]
i wish i could just be in neeto
sometimes no honestly you know what i
used to wish that i used to wish that
but nowadays with this job i'm very very
happy with it
when i had my old job i was like i just
wanna i just wanna be jobless
now i'm happy
[Music]
public relations for entertainment
interesting
yeah something like that
would probably be good
i know we all have the same issue
every whole life member
it been has told stories like that
before like they don't know
what to say
when it comes to questions like that
thank you for the super chat online job
interview
calm down calm down you can do it you
can always like
you know the good thing about online job
interviews is like
if you like maybe stutter or if you
don't know what to say you could be like
oh [\h__\h] my connection i didn't hear you
well can you repeat that question
always always uh
say the internet connection is at fault
or like yeah you didn't hear them well
your headphones are like shitty quality
or whatever
i read the question please i didn't hear
you oh [\h__\h] i didn't hear you again it
was the ping the ping
i was just about to say i never had an
online job interview but i guess i did
i guess i did
whole life um
kind of started out
online so yeah or like literally
if if i weren't in japan then everything
would have been online
but i was in japan at the time so at
least i got to
yeah
meet them eventually
um
oh yeah you know what we didn't talk
about at all yet but there's really not
much i can say anyway
is the announcement but i did make a
post on
the community board so i hope you saw
that
did you see it
did you see the announcement
or did you hear it a lot of you probably
heard it from kelly
yes
we confirmed
um that
because i guess a lot of you were
thinking oh no way no way that they're
gonna be in 3d on the concert oh they're
going to be just live today yeah
whatever going to watch it anyway but
life to deep there
[Laughter]
yeah but now we were able to confirm
that it is going to be
in 3d we
um
management has found a way to make it
possible
thankfully cause
i wanna [\h__\h] dance
i wanna [\h__\h] dance man
i wanna i wanna move my body
that's not the lyrics i don't know what
the [\h__\h] i'm singing
no i'm not gonna twerk
just kidding
i will not be twerking on
this big ass stage
i won't be twerking
but you guys know that i
i've been uh
i i already have like i for for purposes
like this to one day
you know perform them properly in 3d i
have had like
choreographies commissioned already like
ages ago ages because i got really
excited about it i was like yo yo yo i
want a commission a choreography i can
dance but i can't really
i'm not really good at making
choreographies at least not really
intricate ones i can do like simple
choreographies but
um not not so much like intricate
choreographies
so i commissioned them
yeah yeah
oh yeah i i did it
like i don't know then
back then it was like i just i just
i just
wanted it
and i i didn't know uh
i don't know i just commissioned it
myself
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah kiwa is in control
my it's my choreography
my choreography
or i have several ones i have several
choreographies
but as i said i can't i can't say much
so i'm sorry i know you guys always like
me talking details about stuff but i
can't i can't the only thing i can say
is that
this
is not our 3d
um debut there will be
i mean it kind of is but it's not really
we're still doing a proper 4d debut
when the time comes um in the future
we're still doing that so
don't worry about it we want to do it we
want we want that kind of like hype
hype event
i was dreaming about this myself like
the moment i joined whole life i was
like hell yeah i'm always looking
forward to a 3d debut 3d reveal
one day i'm gonna have a hype stream
like my senpai's where i reveal the 3d
and everything else that i i
thought of that i wanted to do in a 3d
reveal
yeah i was fantasizing about it since
like a long time ago
[Music]
and yeah i know it's a weird weird
situation but
um
i mean what else what what else
would you have preferred to just have us
not be there at all no that was not an
option for me
like when else
will
will i get this opportunity one year
later
[\h__\h] no i want to be there now i want to
be in the concert now
hell yeah
so it is it is the way it is now um
um
um yeah what was i gonna say
oh yeah yeah 3d
debut is still coming
so
um don't worry about it
we're gonna make
it happen yes
i mean it will
the order will be messed up but actually
i don't know if you knew but the third
gen uh i think
marine senpai and foreign senpai had the
same thing they
performed
in 3d in a concert
before
they had their free reveal
so
it happened before
it's
sometimes when it can't be helped i
don't know i don't know what the reason
was back then but they they will have
had their reasons
such as we have also our reasons as well
yeah
but i'm excited i'm so excited
i'm so excited
[Music]
which means
which means i also continue working on
the
new song that i've been talking about
although i don't want to release that
before
a 3d debut
so
i'll have to
figure out when that happens
um
because i've been i've been focusing on
having a 3d uh music video for that
um
[Music]
genre hint
did i just hit something i didn't you're
asking for a hint
it's a it's a different genre from my
previous songs
it's uh
pretty
different i would say but i'm not gonna
say one
i'm not going to sell one
[Music]
um
death metal
symphonic death you know i think i said
this before but i wouldn't mind one day
releasing a song like a baby medal
and then the kids in this song what was
it lying
it would be so sick yeah
i kind of want to make an album where
um every song is a different genre so
it's like a
it's like you're at a buffet and you can
taste all the things and you might even
like some things that you didn't realize
you would like
it says song song buffet
test it
test it out and figure out if you'll
like it
yeah yeah thank you delusional dreamer
thank you
in 3d head banging
one 3d when i can already do it in 2d
now
um
foreign
[Music]
okay i think for now i'll
i'll keep the skin the way it is now my
arms feel like they're insanely long but
i think they're fine
[\h__\h] it i don't care
i'm not a professional artist anyway
thank god i'm not thank god my life
doesn't depend on being good at art
although it would be cool if it did one
day
but not with these skills because i
would fail
i want to do the hair now because hair
is fun hair is fun hair hair hair let's
do the hair coming is
um
i guess i'll
do this too and then later on layer the
sheer fabric on top of it
[Music]
did
lyrics help me
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah one more thing i did yesterday
was i went out to
buy the last necessary things for my
skiing trip that i'll be going on with
rmd
skating trips skating trip skating trip
i bought some
fitting skiing clubs because in that
other shop that we went to they only had
like
size is too big for me
yeah
so i went to a different shop
and got some fitting
fitting cute skiing clothes decently
cute
[Music]
yeah now i have like oh my god i have so
much stuff i don't even know how how how
the [\h__\h] i'll cr carry all that [\h__\h]
i don't know how to carry all that [\h__\h]
i have to carry the shoes and the skis
and a suitcase with at least a few
blank on the left earring ah thank you
smart
uh a few a few cloves i gotta bring as
well you know some amenities
of course i have to bring my cats just
kidding though
uh there's so much stuff
how do i carry all of that as one person
takes
no it's not about the new lars it's just
i don't have enough arms if i had more
than one more than two noodle arms if i
had like three noodle arms that would be
awesome
but yeah it's gonna be a bit heavy too
oh this is gonna be so much fun to color
with that
gradation of hair
oh
let's go
hair hair hair hair
a certain gen mate could help you mean
amelia buffson gotta lift weights with
buff buffson
amelia buffson
you don't think that's all just uh
fake huh
you think those are reals that's a real
six-pack
what if she's just wearing one of those
shirts that that give you a buff look
or ina you know with the tentacles
have to ask the ancient ones for some
help
[Music]
oh man drawing hair is my favorite part
i can't believe amma is a literal noodle
didn't call her a
buffs improved herself and ring fit
really she proved herself
did she have a lot of stamina
although i can see her working out a
little bit more than i do or a lot more
because i don't work out at all but
okay
i'm i was in easy mode
i'm super flexible too
who says i'm not flexible
i have a very flexible
time schedule
i can move around my schedule
in crazy angles if you want me to if you
say kiwawa can we do a stream on
wednesday 8pm i can be like hell to the
[\h__\h] year
i'm gonna end my stream early you're
gonna see how flexible i am
i am insanely flexible you don't even
know
i can change everything around like
crazy you're gonna be like what what the
[\h__\h] how did you do that
yeah
i know i'm not bound to work hours
impressive i know there's i'm my own
boss
i couldn't be any more flexible than
this
it's called being available shut up i am
flexible
i am available
and flexible i'm only available if i
make if i make myself available through
my flexibility
[Laughter]
don't take away my flexibility from me
very proud of it
if i wanted to i could go fly to hawaii
tomorrow
who else can say that they can do that
huh
unless their borders are closed because
i'm gonna have a problem but still
how does my hair look
some other birds
flexible as uncooked pasta excuse me
excuse me
[Music]
foreign
migrating to what
i want to go to hawaii someday though
you know one one thing
one reason why i want to go to hawaii is
because i saw a lot of
a lot of hawaii um footage in
um
idol dvds
[Laughter]
like back in the day hello project
sent a lot of their idols to hawaii in
order to make like photo books but also
just
to i don't know for a vacation like they
they used to make dvds
about their vacations like the cameras
would follow them and they would have
like they just would do like you know
touristy things and
those were some awesome dvds yeah
and then sometimes they would be in
bikinis and i don't know they would like
run around on the beach sometimes sure
but but but there's also some other fun
times where they would just buy hawaii
t-shirts and [\h__\h]
um anyway so that's for some reason they
often chose hawaii as their destination
um i think because there are a lot of
people who speak japanese there
so i i saw a lot of hawaii
again
here's idols teaching you
geography
[Laughter]
and other stuff
can learn a lot from idols
lots of actual japanese people yeah yeah
i've ever heard i've heard i've heard
about
um
what the [\h__\h] where did i hear that i
heard about a dating service um
it was very interesting
there was this dating service i think i
saw it on tv
um
that a lady from japan opened up in
hawaii
really interesting
for for for japanese ladies who
want um
a husband that's like i don't know kind
of like i guess it was about
somewhat successful in business but also
speaks japanese so this japanese lady
opened up a dating business in hawaii
for
um
for japanese ladies who are looking for
a partner but in hawaii so she would set
up
[\h__\h] she would set up like a meeting she
would like fly them into
hawaii it was apparently pretty
expensive but she would set up a date
with like a a foreigner who lives in in
hawaii
um
and then and then i don't know
the japanese lady was like oh he's so
handsome he was a it was a foreigner he
was a foreign american
and and she was like oh my dream guy he
can't speak japanese but we're gonna
he's he's my dream guy i want to marry
him but he was like
so
funny to me
uh
so
what do we learn from that to you guys
who want a japanese waifu
maybe hit up that that dating service
moved to hawaii
and hit up that dating service
it might just actually work
why does it sound so dodgy they made it
look very professional
they made it look very professional
it's just a dating service
for japanese ladies who aspire to have a
foreign husband in a in a place where
you can still get around with japanese
quite well
[Laughter]
[Music]
sounds legit
sounds legit hawaii let's go
fascinating how i must be a very
fascinating place
are the beaches nice in hawaii
guys i bet they are
tell me about it tell me about those
beaches i want to go to the beach
i've been low-key regretting
planning a skiing trip because i don't
want to freeze my ass off but phoenix
wants to be in a hot place
i want to go to a hot place
an rmt
rmt
she's currently in a hot place
man
man i envy her she's gonna go from hot
place to cold place
fascinating
of course i can swim i can at least keep
my head above water for a certain amount
of time
hawaii is the closest thing to heaven on
earth from what i've heard
what
really
wow you are praising it in to the
heavens
i don't know is it really dark right i'm
not struck at all
why is it why is it so close to heaven
hawaii is very nice went once with my
family but is it like insanely crowded
[Music]
if we avoid the city which city
honolulu
is honolulu in hawaii
waikiki beach
avoid honolulu
avoid tourist season isn't it always
tourist season
in hawaii in a place like that
i like how i'm just using blue to shade
everything here
but i feel like it looks cool
[Music]
i feel like they have a [\h__\h] ton of
japanese tourists probably which could
be fun
feels like you're in japan actually not
in hawaii
go to bali i want to there's so many
places i want to go to
so many you have no idea
i'm gonna travel the world
all of it
trip through the whole world
hell yeah
have you been to okinawa
no unfortunately
i want to i wanted to but the closest i
could get to okinawa was uh fukuoka
mm-hmm
[Music]
good place to visit in winter
maybe in spring
i think winter is maybe i know it's
still like warm enough in wonder but hmm
kiana grandma your back okay excuse me
no well my back is not okay
bye
i guess going to bali would make it
pretty easy to meet up with those girls
here
[Music]
did a stream where she talked about
going on vacation recently right was
that bali because i watched a bit i
think it was bunny
was it bonnie
um
beautiful
[Music]
oh
damn
oh it's like really close to
[Music]
oh and singapore is also like [\h__\h]
close to indonesia
[Music]
did you draw of course
you should drag myth out of the houses
and go to hawaii or something sunny [\h__\h]
yeah i want to i wish i i've i kind of
tried it before like inviting someone
to go somewhere
um
[Music]
but yeah didn't really happen
maybe in the future
but i feel like it would um do us all
very very good uh to go on a vacation
[Music]
no no not to uh not to um
not to an island or so more like a
a city trip
well it's partially uh
a beeps fault
[Music]
almost said
almost
almost talked about the secrets
words which won't which shall not be
spoken out loud
voldemort
was it voldemort
and the fight club
don't talk about the fight club
apparently
voldemort yeah
i've been talking a lot about voldemort
recently maybe maybe that's because
recently i've been hanging out with
voldemort
who knows
oh wait that's uh that's not hair that's
supposed to be skin oopsie
hi it's luffy
oh yeah i'll see you too
hi i'm so happy to see you want to come
here come here come here
no why are you ignoring me
yes
yes you're good baby
oh i see you she jumped on the on her
chair where the blanket is
yeah you're gonna stay here
you're gonna hang out with me
well you know
she's so soft
she's so shocked
she's moving and blanking
you have common ground
having no nose
man if if that were the reason then all
anime girls would be besties with
voldemort
because they can all relate
oh bye-bye smoothie okay it was just a
a short a short trip to say hello to
mommy
[Music]
yeah we're all besties
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh yeah some anime girls depending on
the art style some of them have some
pretty
obvious noses but most most of them
don't
i wish i was a cat same
that reminds me of asuki's
she has this song which is about if i
wear a cat
if i wear a cat i could do this in that
baby
smoothie where'd you go
[Music]
why you soft soft soft
anyway
oh
ah
i just looked at my tangent memo
and i i remembered something
can i talk about seinfeld
i i wasn't there was a time when i was
watching seinfeld and uh young sheldon
at the same time
but seinfeld
i was watching like weeks before that
already and
you know
george in seinfeld yeah yeah the
character you see all the time
and then it took me a while it took me
quite a long time to realize that in
young sheldon
george plays a role
seinfeld's george not a main role but he
does show up uh here and there but i did
not recognize him at all
he looks so different
he looks older but at the same time
i know he looks like a completely
different person
uh yeah the hair facial hair and and and
head hair
all
very very different and the moment i
realized i felt like my
my brain exploded
studio makeup no i don't think it's only
that it's really just also because
young sheldon is a very new show and
seinfeld is a very old show but i
finished watching seinfeld by now
there was so many
so
every [\h__\h]
episode seinfeld has a new girlfriend
right and some of them holy [\h__\h] i've
seen them in some of my favorite shows
like he had like at least two girls from
friends he had one girl from desperate
housewives he had so so so so so so so
many different girls
and i want i've been wondering like did
did seinfeld become like a stepping
stone from for them do like do like the
people in hollywood when they think
about who to cast for female roles do
they just
turned on a random episode of seinfeld
and and they're like okay and that this
this
uh girlfriend of jerry from episode five
of season six yeah we're gonna cast her
as the lead role
i wonder if that's how they picked
uh or if that's how they picked the rose
in hollywood
sign purple is just really popular back
then
yeah but yeah i want to know like were
those ladies famous before or like did
they all become famous after
after seinfeld because there's so many
familiar faces holy [\h__\h]
actually wait there were two
two ladies from desperate housewives at
least two
yeah
some actors are shape-shifters
true
that's what they do
everyone wanted in on it
well yeah but oh my god did someone
count i'm sure there's a count
let me count
how
many
girlfriends
did
it comes up at this point as a
recommendation how many girlfriends did
jerry have on seinfeld how many
girlfriends did george have on seinfeld
jerry had 73
different [\h__\h] girlfriends
george had 47 that's still [\h__\h]
impressive
for george
47 for george 73 different girlfriends
for jerry
wow exactly is oh my god [\h__\h] up how
many boyfriends did elaine have
about 30 about 30 for elaine
oh my god
[Laughter]
americano you may not have
absolutely crazy
grandma is the only good one yeah wait
did krema ever have a girlfriend on the
show
what it
he was always focused on other things
he was always focused on other crazy
things and schemes did he ever have a
girlfriend i don't remember now
he's pure he's a say-so idol yeah
he couldn't spend this waste his time on
dating
what
what's sigma
what is that
[Music]
sigma grind what is that
what
what did you make me say
oh god
what
i'm cooking it
[Music]
hi
wait that's me oh wait that's me
isn't that no almost i'm getting i'm
getting close to that mindset grant said
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait my face hurts
me
to snare
kiana sigma grunsa
no
[Laughter]
what's going on
it's movie yes feeling smoothy she left
the room already she's gonna come back
i'm gonna say hello to her again every
time she comes in here
i am a sick my boss
i guess
i have no idea what's going on right now
[Music]
um
um okay if we overlord yes that's me
grandma has apparently 14 girlfriends
one of them was played by sarah
silverman who's done
14 really wow
meanwhile jerry had 70 [\h__\h] four
74.
ah
can you believe
oh my god
wait did i say i finished watching
sunfield i didn't i i lied i'm close to
it i'm trying to slow down on watching
it so then i don't finish it
as per usual
i want to finish my shows
[Music]
you can't maintain a relationship yeah
but i mean they totally did that on
purpose like
they just
i guess they just wanted
to
have variety
obviously it's not realistic or is it is
it realistic am i just is my world view
just wrong is it is it a realistic thing
for jerry to have 74 different
girlfriends
i mean at this point can you even call
them girlfriends he's just
having fun
[Laughter]
but yeah i think they just wanted to
have all kinds of different girlfriends
to create a different situation with
every one of them for the sake of comedy
[Music]
it's not realistic
but damn he was a lady what do you call
it a ladies
lady
ladybug
jerry was a ladybug
he was definitely bugging the ladies man
a lady's
a womanizer yeah a womanist
oh yeah
[Music]
an average first date cost 77
what
77.74 dollars
times 77.
what seventies did you say it wasn't 78
or something i got no never mind so he
jerry probably spent probably five
thousand six hundred ninety eight
dollars on his dates
what a calculation
approximately
seven uh five thousand six hundred
dollars
on all his ladies
isn't jerry a casa nova hell yeah he is
uh
but after watching so much seinfeld
i don't like his voice anymore
it's kind of
ugh i don't like his voice because he
talks like oh he talks like this almost
like mickey mouse
have you ever noticed that guys
oh my god it talks like this so often
[Laughter]
no hate though no hate
it's just something i've observed after
watching a lot of that show
[Music]
it was inevitable
mickey mouse never thought about that
really
[Music]
inna undercover
no
no no she wouldn't do that
she wouldn't do that
although ina is a comedian
[Music]
archived singing stream again
i think in general if it's just like an
hour or so
it's not more damage on my voice than
any pokemon streamers so it would do
probably even less
because you use your voice differently
when you sing then as in compared to
when you talk
but anyway i don't really think it would
be that much damage maybe maybe in like
uh two weeks time because next week i
don't have time but maybe in two weeks
time we can do a singing stream again
i watched and watched amaze on our cap
singing stream
and she sang some songs i want to sing
too
[Music]
one
step
[Music]
i
that's all i want to sing at
is that from twilight i never watched
twilight
man
i was around when it got really popular
and all my i think i was in school
all my schoolmates they were like
watching twilight and i was like yeah
too mainstream i always had this kind of
like
uh
i don't know i just always stayed away
from mainstream things i still
do i still do
and then and then later on everyone
started hating on it and i was like
i never watched it
i was right
[Music]
probably my face doesn't um move much
when i
look over to my art because yeah it's
not very positioned
uh not very well positioned
[Music]
also as you can see i like to spend a
lot of time with the hair
also i just had i can't help it i have a
[\h__\h] ton of hair in this
outfit
oh [\h__\h] the volume yo what can i do it's
just too much
[Music]
me
oh thank you
really
[Music]
that is some one-piece level assets
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
oh tomorrow by the way before the
minecraft stream i have a recording
um not a song recording something else
um
i think it should be
there should be a buffer in between my
minecraft stream
and the recording but um if there are
some problems it might go on a bit too
long i don't know but no it should
normally be fine but worst case there
might be a delay
on the minecraft stream a little bit but
i think it should be fine just warning
you ahead of time
um
good okay okay okay
yeah it was decided um
i don't know why it keeps on happening
that it was literally the recording time
and date was literally decided yesterday
uh i can only be happy that it um
it doesn't overlap with my stream or my
sleeping time
i can only be grateful for that so
but it's something um from management's
side that has to be done so
i cannot like move it or so we don't
have time for moving it to a different
time
we have to do it we have to do it
we have to do it
he tells a bedtime story
top cake your name is top cake isn't
that a snack
i want to understand um the this is not
a bedtime story but i will understand
the reason
why
this snack
became such a like a meme
and i've seen people like i used it
before as well
i think but why do people sometimes like
stay top kick i think when they want to
say something is funny
or just kick
but isn't it a snake
like how did that happen
[Music]
like if it's extra funny then i think
it's top cake
it's from world of warcraft
what a vlog of meme but there's a snack
too right well let me look it up
is that just completely separate but why
did they name it top captain cupcake
yeah it's a snake snack
snack
pop snack
urban dictionary
topcake a category 10 lol what
an extremely powerful lel the strongest
magnitude of kirk possible
boycerosely mary
something that generates an
extraordinary level of amusement
my
my sister just got pregnant and we have
no idea who the father is top cat
i see
it's like oh my god
so stupid
ah
i am amused that is quite the kick
alliance was seen as kick
oh because it was like yeah you couldn't
see what the others were writing because
supposedly they were speaking different
language right ah and that's their way
of translating oh
that's top cake
so stupid
one that's so funny
cake
baka
japanese viewers
[Music]
[Laughter]
i sound like a mom picking up hip words
well you sound like a dad
making fun of
my mom
okay
you challenging me
are you challenging me
god damn
goddammit these chickens
they think
they think they're funny
cupcake
[Music]
perfect count the critical hit shut up
i always win the argument yes
chop cake
[Music]
why did i
why did i think of that recently i felt
i think i uh i think it was kramer
eating
a topcake in seinfeld
i think when i was watching like two
days ago i think kramer was eating a top
cake and that made me
remember why the [\h__\h] is uh the snake
snack called topkick
when there's also the word used in a
completely different way
i think that was it i might be wrong
though
i never said two plus two is five
no
i never said that
slander
what do you mean two buster is five
[Laughter]
you stupid chicken
no
[Music]
oh yeah yeah i need to update you guys
not only have time
i do update you
on my pokemon adventures
if i can remember all of it holy [\h__\h] so
i i i don't know i had this i had this
urge to play uh
[Music]
oh they're from turkey
i had this urge to play
some pokemon legends in my free time in
the middle of the night because i also
was running out of tv shows yeah
so
i was playing for like hours and hours
and hours
i first did like a [\h__\h] ton of cyclists
and then while doing a side quest i i
caught myself another eevee
and because i evolved my other eevee i
couldn't hold back first i was thinking
i should do it on stream because that's
more interesting but no i couldn't wait
guys my evening is now
uh the cute one the cute fairy evie
um
yes
so gaki is now a cute fairy evie but
then i was thinking it's so cute what if
i do a whole team only made up of eevees
but then i realized no that's too boring
but maybe one maybe one more eevee
um or two
maybe three eevees and and some other
three
other boring ass pokemon
um
so i have the fairy one and i've been
wondering which other should i get i'm
thinking the maybe the dark type
the
what's it called again i don't know all
the names in english
it's like saying night night girl or so
umbreon yeah
maybe like umbreon
but i don't want the psychic type
because i i've been thinking of using
something else for my psychic
um
because my my balloon pokemon
my drift loom is now evolved as well
hell yeah
hell to the air
sorry guys a lot happened behind the
scenes
i have a big [\h__\h] pokemon now a big
balloon a huge ass balloon
[Music]
my
drifloon
jeri falloon is now big balloon
balloon
big balloon so that's my that's my
ghosty
um i was thinking maybe maybe the fire
evie
because
although i did find the fire starter and
called the fire starter as well the
monkey
in my adventures i did find the fire
started started but i don't really want
a fire monkey in my team i'm already a
fire monkey myself after all
[Music]
but yeah i was thinking maybe a flareon
flareon and uh the night one the umbreon
and the the fairy one that we already
have
or or we don't go for the fire one
instead we go nine tails is is is nine
tails fire nine those is fire right
i would love to have a nine tails in my
team holy [\h__\h]
there's nine times fired then i want
nine tails in my team
we couldn't get it in diamond uh pearl
cause we played pearl right and she
wasn't available i think
i think we couldn't get her now this is
our chance
vulpix
this is our chance okay
yeah i feel like i'm i have like an
ideal team of cutie pies
i keep i will keep my ghost
for fairy have evie for for dark we have
evie
for fire we get
nine tails
for
plants we have the starter
for for water we'll have to
we could keep my
gyarados
but i don't know i don't know if i want
to keep that big snake
i i've been using it at the moment but i
don't know if i want to keep it
big snack pokemon flying snake
pokemon
chunk
wait who's junk again
who did i call junkie
who did i call junk again
ah my beaver right my beaver
oh no bieber is still in the team and
being very helpful
[Music]
i forgot
no no no
could never forget
we doof is gone
yeah
at least has been helping me with the
stone attacks and so on he might
actually
stay in the team for for the top kicks
he might stay
at least for a while
we do forgotten no
no no no no no no no no
yo will i ever finish coloring this hair
yeah
come here
[Music]
oh
all these colors
gorgeous
yes
you're craving top kick now
see i'm just so good with uh
promoting
food and any any anything really
am i not
[Music]
this stream is now sponsored by topcake
best promoter
professional aisle promoter i would
drink that natto coca-cola and i might
throw up on stream but
you wouldn't see it because i'm a
youtuber and then i would say yo that
was delicious
while still hinting at the fact that
it's uh disgusting
but still stay professional
no
honestly i probably
i uh
i wouldn't lie to you guys i would not
be able to tell you it's
it's uh good but
i know how to stay professional
don't wanna
be too um
mean
although as i said in the play for the
creators of such a product
they must know that what they're
creating is um
what's the
word what's the word
what's the word again what's what's what
no
controversial yes frankie their kids
that was the word i was looking for what
they're creating is controversial thank
you johnny come sign me now
a nice product
yeah well
definitely a niche product mm-hmm
um
if i use up all my tangents today i
won't have any more tomorrow
guys i still have some topics but
is there anything you want to talk about
[Music]
horror
no i would never on purpose watch
someone else's outlast stream
favorite pokemon i don't have one
uh oh what the what the hero
pizza what tweet was about
uh
that was honestly
me just
being curious
that was just me being curious in the
middle of the night but then later on i
realized [\h__\h]
maybe i shouldn't be asking your for
european view to this at um 4 am in
europe
but i still get a lot of i still got a
lot of replies to that
and then i was kind of inspired and full
moment i was thinking what if i
organized a eurovision
song contest for v tubers
but that is just a really random thought
that i i have i don't know if um
i don't know if i can really take up
uh something like that
oh no wait was it
was an azuki
senpai
who
talked about
i think in hong kong we talked about it
as well was asuki senpai who organized
something like that
[Music]
that was before
before she like
uh
became completely
whole alive no
i don't know if she would still do it
but
and i don't know how much she really is
involved in that
but i guess yeah it just sounds like a
[\h__\h] ton of work man
but
i mean it would be
would be cool
would be a legendary it would be
something big no i want to do something
big
i just want to do something big
right
no i don't that's the other thing but um
i could do it whenever i feel like
i have spare time maybe maybe in half a
year
um i will be lacking things to do
maybe
and i'll
take up on that idea i have a lot of
ideas but they're all like not
necessarily something i want to do right
away just
eventually
now i almost feel like i've been
coloring or like putting too much detail
into the hair sometimes less is better
but
uh but it's fine
i don't want to stop
[Music]
oh
it's fun
can we get a history tangent no
not now
i don't know where where what i would
talk about
[Music]
huh did you see pacquiao talk about
meeting excuse me what meeting momoti
how the [\h__\h] would you meet
what is that recent what
is that is that a clip what let me go on
my phone
what do i need to look up
huh
maybe momoko cause momoji is just your
nickname
huh
no that's not it
there's a clue
what
[Music]
maybe
favorite
idol
no
thank you for becoming a membership
huh
iqra's mind went blank favorite idol
what
mind went
i literally this is funny because
literally yesterday i was i was going
for some old hello project videos
because i'm a huge hell project fan
myself um
or i used to and i was watching
something really old there was like i
was watching a movico video yesterday it
was
one of her
concerts before her graduation she had a
solo concert for the for her fan club
and she made up this song uh where like
she would in the song tell her um fans
how to act after her graduation and she
was telling them things like uh yeah if
you see me on the street then don't talk
to me don't come up to me
just act as if you have not seen me and
walk away but then go back home and be
happy that you have uh had a glance upon
my godlike self
um but she sang it in a cute song and
the view the the the fans in the
audience they were like hi
hi
hi they were very obedient it was very
cute uh but she was like partially being
very um
very very strict about it
oh but let me let me watch it
[Music]
i said not recently but like from when
she was still an idol when momochi
momochisto was an idol
that's from before
i thought you were saying she recently
met momoko like on the street herself
cycle cycle
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
she said that
you know
she her favorite idol is part of my
favorite idol group that is kobo as i've
told you about many times before but my
favorite or she is not momochi minus
arisako um
different member of the same group and
she said that she went to a handshake
event of the group and she was the first
one after a little break
so so she was like yo what if what if
she washed her hands in the break and
i'm the first one to touch it after the
handwashing oh my god no one touched it
before then
and then she said she she shook uh
a momochi's hands with her right hand
but then everybody else's hands in the
group with her left hand
which is so weird because
you weirdo at least do it the other way
around so that at least only one member
will have to shake your left hand
instead of having uh
most of the group shake your left hand
you should make them shake your right
hand because that would be less awkward
and then only momoji the left hand
[Music]
i've been to a lot of a lot of handshake
events from them too
oh good times i love those hand turkey
ones it was always so short but i always
i always felt like they were a little
bit biased towards me because
you know all of these all of these
male otakus and then there was this cute
foreign girl coming up for a handshake i
feel like they were always very happy to
see me not gonna lie they were like oh
my god hello you come on
well that's the good thing about looking
like this
[Laughter]
is
top cag moment
who knows maybe i actually once went to
the same handcuff event as pikot
maybe i was at the same place at the
same time like pickled at some point
maybe we even went to the same concert
at some point who knows
[Laughter]
yeah yeah one one popular place for
hanjak events for our project was in
ikebukuro
uh underground at a bookstore um when
they would release a
um a book a photo book they would often
do it in that place
indirect handshake yeah that's the most
exciting thing of course instead of
focusing on the fact that i hand shook
with my favorite idol from venice kobo
the thing to
consider now is that maybe i had an
indirect handshake because i shook hands
with
uh momochi and
beccara did too
that's the that's where it's at that's a
real exciting thing
oh man
idolception
you wonder do you wonder if tequila
senpai would be excited about having an
indirect handshake with me
probably not
yeah indirect handshake let's go
handshaking is loot afterwards
um what should i
ah
i i think i need to go to an idol
meeting
[Music]
pineapple juice
i think i will go to an idol meeting
oh my gosh she says while picking a new
color and continuing to draw
[Music]
i'll go to an idol meeting soon
it's too lazy to get up
i want to finish
the hair
down
[Music]
if you play the handshake event meta
just right you can technically can you
technically can shake handshake all
idols
or everyone in the whole [\h__\h] world
yeah and all the all the fans as well
yeah
what are you trying to tell me that i
should be handshaking with gloves on
or replacing my hand
i should i should replace my hand
every time i do a handshake and then
keep each hand in an ice container
freeze each hand what the [\h__\h] am i
talking about
what am i talking about cyborg let's go
cyborg canada
i just need a bit more
bit more depth
stuff
oh yeah by the way for the members only
stream which is
is it tomorrow or am i doing minecraft
tomorrow no i'm doing minecraft tomorrow
right and then members only right
[Music]
on friday then this is friday okay
yeah um i did uh i did a um
i did a
poll on the community board if you
didn't see it but german lesson seems to
be winning you guys wanna
hear about the forgotten the last
episode
the last continuation
of me teaching you uh uh german so
that's probably gonna be it
i had some other good ideas and yes i
know i i promised a baking stream
we'll still do that eventually but i
don't think i feel like it this week
because i have to set up everything for
that
wow and i'm pretty busy this week
well for german i also have to set up
stuff but at least i don't have to
change my whole
camera
uh
setup and blah blah
internet cable
etc
so quite a lot of work to do these
cooking streams
ideally ideally one day i want to be
able to just
have the whole setups there at all times
and can switch over at any time
that would be cool
etc
in german i would say etc
make a new setup on the kitchen then on
the bedroom then in the whole house yes
streaming setup in the bathroom let's go
or in the in the bathtub i mean
bathtub streaming setup
that would be very chill watching
watching a movie watch long in the
bathtub
movie watch along in the bathtub
with a with a lush bath bump
in the bathtub
bubble bubble bubble
[Music]
now for the daughter's chop door
feels dangerous
dangerous
[Music]
with pizza
yeah good i would like that
bathtub please i can't believe this girl
sometimes
eating a pizza that dropped in the
bathtub
are you okay
that just that just goes too far
[Music]
i feel like that crosses the line
it's clean no
that's the thing about taking baths and
bathtubs all your own dirt is there and
then perhaps if you put in a i don't
know some kind of
kind of bubble water so then there's
gonna be you know the bubble water on
the pizza as well so imagine there's
wow that's just not that's just
wow
poisoning yourself
yeah crazy crazy that shark girl
crazy girl
i don't know how she does it
soap pizza exactly that doesn't sound
very healthy
[Music]
i think my russian
my russian snack box has been sent out
by the way
it's on its way i think i believe
snack box number
two from russia
mr vodka even if there was i don't know
if i would want maybe i will take a sip
but
just because it would be in there but
nope there will not be any vodka in it
i don't like alcohol anyway
[Music]
foreign
i love this song
down
foreign
yeah that's cool
that reminds me
i've been following a little bit of what
football sample has been doing
in pokemon how the freak does she
gathers so many shinies so fast
how is she doing i've been trying to
like look around for shinies at least
they're like easy to easy to see on the
field because they like shine they go
like sparks back and they make a sound
apparently thank you for the red super
chat senior
obligated how does she how is she so
lucky
the outbreak said i've heard that the
outbreaks make the chance
uh
go up by a lot
huh
and then others just really find it so
randomly
how do they do it shiny magnet yeah
she's really lucky
it's easy to get shiny pokemon yeah
because because of people saying that
i've been hoping that i would find one
too
but i haven't been that lucky yet
oh
[Music]
but not just any shiny i want a shiny
eevee
shiny eevee would be nice
[Music]
i got a shiny jew
dude boring it's not cute
[Music]
you need to wait for a shine
an eevee outbreak that
would be
very very
helpful
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay you know what
i'm gonna do now
uh
i am going to
make a new layer
um
and then
no
a
big color
[Music]
i'm going to do
some strands of hair thank you for the
membership welcome
yup not going to an isle meeting yet
oh
[Music]
oh thank you for renewing your
membership why are you in my basement
should i be worried
thank you for the membership renewal
what's going on why is everybody
renewing them
[Music]
welcome oh my god
that's just membership messages you
already renewed your membership but
thank you
oh thank you vegan green
it's so green in here
i feel so lucky
um
[Music]
green is green is a positive color
green is a lucky color
[Music]
oh my god i looked at my tablet and
inside of in the corner of my eye all i
see is green
[Music]
green green green green
so i'm focusing on
something else right now um
[Music]
green green
hmm
folks
all right
all right all right i'm pretty happy
with that
here
oops
there we go
oh
well well
i will go
to an idle meeting for a moment
oh yeah yeah yeah something about um
i'll if i don't forget i'll talk about
it when i come back
brb
ah my legs
[Music]
i know you didn't hear i was just
playing with jonkers
[Music]
so
i'm back
i brought some
tuna salad tuna noodle salad
oh that i bought
before i just snack a cold tuna noodle
salad
for later if i get hungry
suddenly
totally not for my cats just kidding
really not for my cats
they like tuna but don't they probably
don't like noodles
[Music]
so
for now i am pretty
done with the
hair
so we are
moving on
to
the
[Music]
clothes
yes
okay
what big eyes you have you sound like
out of that fairy tale
what was it was it
was it the one with the
with the with the wolf where they're
like oh you have such big
something something yeah
red riding hood yeah
who says that though
i never forgot how that fairy tale goes
on red riding hood says it she says it
huh
what's the wolf
red riding hood says it says it to the
grandma who is
already eaten by the wolf i suppose
oh you have such beaks something such
big teeth for example i think that's
what she was saying because the wolf
then obviously
has very sharp big teeth and she's like
yo you have such big teeth
[Music]
yeah yeah okay yeah
thank you
i did want to just
um tell you i i'm not sure when exactly
is happening but there was a notice
notification on um
on twitter
uh
you uh no a
whole life
is
um
becoming uh
an mcn
some something something something
right that's yeah
and because of that i think
uh
because of the changes being made
yeah a multi-channel network which is
quite a rare thing apparently
uh but whole live is becoming a
multi-channel network
it comes with some features i guess that
are helpful for
a company like whole life i suppose but
because of that for a little while
um when the changes are being made
approximately for like a day or so the
memberships are gonna be paused but i
think it's going to happen when i'm on
vacation anyway
thank you for renewing your membership
uh
yeah
it can be as strong as an hour true yes
it could be very very short you might
not even notice you're gonna you might
not even be online when it's happening
but you're probably gonna get like a
notification as an email or so that your
membership has been paused but it's
gonna be reactivated soon after anyway
so don't worry about it it's just
yeah
us being uh
integrated in something i don't know i
don't know much about it
yeah it should be quick
what does that mean i'm not sure
[Music]
maybe look up youtube multi-channel
network i
i don't it doesn't really affect me
as an individual much i think so
at least not at the moment so i don't
really know
i don't know it makes whole life a
banner for you
oh
i don't know some things
will be improved
[Music]
a close layer
so here we go finally cloves cloves
should be fast
relatively fast by the way there will be
no background cause
um i can't do backgrounds and i don't
care much about it even right now
why is that word so similar japanese for
boobs
oppai
and korean for brother oppa
it's confusing
bye
[Music]
oh yeah it wasn't sister only
but in [\h__\h] in korean sisters only right
and then in japanese brother is
okay but it could also be any key but
[Music]
only but it depends
that's really uh similar
sounding
but it's just a coincidence
after my ski trip i want to learn more
korean after my ski trip i'm so busy now
is that the same color
yeah it's kind of is the same color okay
but i will do it separately
oops
[Music]
when is the ski trip again i didn't say
any exact dates or times
um
you will see you will see uh when i
will come back
that it has ended at that time
i
don't want to over share
um before the trip
[Music]
although good luck finding me in the
mountains
i'll be camouflaging myself i'll be
wearing all white
and have other skiers run into me
don't you have dancing practice who says
i don't already know my choreography
i've had it since like
months many many months ago
over
like almost like a year or so i think
i don't know gonna practice a little bit
obviously beforehand
dance and queen
kia y is the dancing queen
[Music]
well i got um
i won't be saying what i will be
performing
but like soon after
nothing
not that soon maybe for hinotoni
i think i got like a
choreography like maybe in spring
and for heart challenger i also
quickly quickly
pretty
immediately have the heart challenger
released i got a
choreography for heart challenger as
well
and so on is really really fast
fast finished
ivana
i mean i didn't back then i didn't get
the choreography
with having a concert like we've i
didn't you know back then it was too
early i didn't know about
the existence of a concert
but um
i wanted it because i was hoping i was
hoping for
uh
i was hoping to be able to do a 3d
birthday concert for example in 2021
we always got to be prepared for it you
know in case it might be possible
well it didn't happen but
i i wanted to be prepared
[Music]
nothing wrong about being prepared
exactly i'm like so ready i've been i've
been ready for
dancing in 3d since like i was born
i've been so ready
wait's faster that meme is literally me
i'm just waiting faster
faster faster faster
yeah i'm just waiting
teeny tiny details
who the hell father of all these details
[Music]
what
is that did i select everything now
oops
puppies
kimono well that's like that's just with
a kimono
you don't have much choice kimonos just
are bound to have a [\h__\h] ton of patterns
otherwise
it would be lacking it wouldn't be what
the chemo is supposed to be i mean there
are some simple kimonos obviously like
everyday kimonos are often like they
don't they don't even have a pattern
often or just a very simple striped
strapped pattern for example or
i don't know some kind of very simple
pattern if it's like an everyday kimono
but the formal one has to be
very very special
that's what makes a kimono a kimono help
my cat one stop flushing my toilet what
for real that's so smart
your cat can flush the toilet
can you can also use the toilet as in
you know did you teach it to sit on the
toilet and
make their business inside of it
because i know some people teach their
cats to do that
[\h__\h] genius
that would be impressive he just won't
stop flushing it
i love your cat what a genius cat
not a huddle i need to fix that
i love cats
they just they just want to see the
world burn and that's just something i
can relate to
as a phoenix
obviously
is that a fire today
sparks is the national anthem
of cats
all over the world
although they
interpret the lyrics in a way more uh
violent way than i originally intended
it to being
interpreted
interpreted interpreted
[Music]
does that mean cats actually twerked as
box
no cats don't twerk you're stupid
[Music]
oops
okay
i love this song it's so catchy i love
it too the og and this mix
this mix makes it like so dreamy to
remix
isn't it wonderful
that's twerk if you scratched your back
mine don't twerk when i do that also you
can't really call that twerking but okay
you and your fantasies sure sure
here's a random topic guys
did you
um
do
i did something in elementary school
that i wonder if you guys maybe did too
or if i was just being
a genius businesswoman
i wonder if i already mentioned this
before i think i did not talk about this
before
in elementary school
elementary is kindergarten right or is
kindergarten kindergarten kindergarten
is kindergarten no i don't mean
kindergarten i mean the thing that comes
after kindergarten yeah that would be
elementary i think elementary school i
didn't work in elementary school that's
not what i'm asking
twerking wasn't a thing in elementary i
think
[Laughter]
no one asked if you weren't working in
an elementary school
thank you for the answer though good to
know
no um
in elementary school
um after elementary school i would go
into something that was called
what i think we call it hort
what
do you guys call it that in germany too
until like the
in afternoon
it's elementary in it
yeah they're hot
kinder hot now
yeah yeah
because my mom i guess was working and
couldn't pick me up so for for the kids
that
uh had parents working
um they would after elementary school go
to
like a i don't know daycare i guess it's
like a daycare
until the afternoon
yeah it was like
like immediately next to
daycare aftercare whatever yeah
immediately next to the school
is where that was and it was my favorite
place to be because
there were like there were different
classes
or like sections i don't know i guess
it's more like classes different classes
in the heart in the court
in the daycare as well
um but i had the absolute best
daycare
cara lady
she was the best oh my god i loved her
so much we were like besties
she was like my second mom i really
really loved her
um
and
uh we were more like a little bit more
of a smaller group
while the other groups were like
a bit bigger
i don't know why it's just because our
building was a bit smaller there were
several buildings there
and
oh my god
sometimes we played doctor there that
was so cringe
but
i was also like
inline skating a lot my biggest hobby in
that age was inline skating
yeah i was skating around a lot now with
a skateboard but with inland skates
and um
that's not what i was trying to tell
though
oh that's not that's not what i wanted
to say
oh one super cool thing that i remember
though you know our building was a
little bit small but we would go over to
the other building
that had like they had a big park as
well
and and they were they had those
go-karts
they had those carts they were like
really shitty but they had those carts
and they had some
some uh streets like mini streets
my tent has tangents exactly
and we were like driving around it well
that was such a popular thing
that uh i think every child was only
allowed a certain amount of time on
those cars
because it was just that popular
mario kart in real life i mean it was
not that big the road was not that it
was literally just like
i don't know maybe
20 meters
of a street
like just a little pathway and then it
goes uh like it has a curve and then
yeah a second line it was really not
that much just a loop yeah
yeah yeah but it was so much fun
yes
unlimited tangent works
tangent this is the tangent before the
tangent it leads you smoothly into the
tangent that i want to talk about
so
oh my god can i tell you wait one second
i want to show you a sample because this
is perfect we're in a drawing program
right now
it's also
token
style
[Music]
let me show you
so
what i liked to do
and
we had uh
we had this
these
big rows of paper because it was cheaper
it was like
see
this is me
bigger than my
bigger than my head
so i would rip up like
such a
big piece of paper
baby kiwawa
and i would do the following
i was
in elementary
school in
in the school itself i was unpopular and
and one i was friends with the most
bullied kid which made me a bit bullied
as well
um but in the daycare
we were a small group and we're all we
were
there was not enough place to really
bully anyone
but
um i was a smart business lady
so in order to
i think i don't know i mean i probably
wasn't thinking this far originally but
i wanted to
i wanted the
um to have control probably
um
and i wanted i wanted the others to be
nicer to me so i was not the only one
doing this i'm not even sure if i
started it but
me and some of the other kids in daycare
were
using these big pieces of paper
and making
here
um
the following
one two three four well this is okay
imagine that this is seven days i think
and i would say monday
tuesday wednesday
first day etc okay
do you see where this is going
rachel and here i would write the names
of certain kids for example i don't know
maria
julian
uh
susie
[Laughter]
and so on
did anyone else do this
and every day
at the end of the day i would i would
bring out my my big chart
and i would say okay
i'm doing it now
it's not a school time table and i would
i would write a big smiley or i would do
this or i would do this
and then actually i think there was a
bottom part a column which listed
some kind of i think
i don't know i think i would even like
rewards or something
if so if you were nice to me on that day
if i liked you particularly on that day
then i would write it on my big list
and this was really important to all of
us
this was really important to all of us
because we wanted to be influential
we wanted to be on everyone's good side
and so we would you know keep looks at
what everyone else was ranking us and
who liked us today and what i need to do
to be liked by others
i don't know did you guys not do this
we're i think we're trying to influence
others to be nicer to one another
yeah
it's weird and then there must have been
something to motivate them to be nicer
that's why i think if i remember
correctly there was even like a point
system or like some kind of reward
system but what can an elementary
schooler really give as a reward i'm not
sure
i don't remember that but it was a very
important chart and everyone we had
these drawers
uh where everyone could put their [\h__\h]
in uh for the daycare and you know you
know obviously
my big ass
roll of paper would be in there and
every every day at the end of the day i
would pull that out and i would be like
okay i'm judging you now
and the other kids would actually a lot
of them would do it too here we use
toilets what do you mean
it's
i think this is
this is um
this might have influenced
the kiana that i am today
into being a social influencer and a
business lady and a ceo
and yeah socially
uh adept
i certainly did not do that what i
thought a lot of people could relate
wait is there anyone who did do this
was this only a thing in my daycare
no no
no
i did really miffin
really
[Music]
fascinating you know how old are you
when you're in elementary school usually
around
a third you
around what age are you when you're in
elementary school
sounds wild
five to eleven six ish seven to eleven
we're probably a bit different in in
austria as well
but something around that i suppose so
imagine an eight-year-old kiwawa
[Laughter]
doing this this is kind of like
brainwashing like i don't know it's
probably not really what kids should be
doing i'm surprised like our daycare
teacher she was like okay with this
it's kind of shallow but
we just did it
we just did it like in a fun way i
suppose keeping books yeah it's like a
burn no it's not a burn book but it's
like
yo if you
if if you have too many of those
frowning smileys on the chart and we're
not friends anymore
i'm not gonna play with you anymore
maybe one of the rewards was like
yo you can eat my lunch or you can
play with the toy i'm bringing next week
i don't know
[Laughter]
uh
good times good times
this is how i learned how to become a
ceo one day
and yet
and yet maybe maybe i should still do
this with all the kfp chickens
one two three
kfp number
keep track of how you guys are acting on
each day if you're nice to me
[Music]
[Laughter]
of course all of you are always just the
sweetest chimpkins ever
so you're only gonna get smilies
yeah
will we get something for being nice
you'll get
me being nice to you is that not enough
oh my god
is this the good place courses i watched
that
oh they got the idea from me
they stole the idea from elementary
school chihuahua unbelievable
unbelievable
[Music]
they stole it
how could they
[Music]
it's time to soda yeah
i mean we are a
a big business
i wouldn't exactly call i can't be a
multi-million business
but we're getting there
we are getting there
yeah
we need to sound more threatening
let's continue to draw that was a
tangent elementary school tangent
elementary school was nice
huh
elementary school
elementary school yeah
after after elementary school
i got into
a school where i had to walk up a
[\h__\h] mountain every day to get to the
school
because the school was on the mountain
horrible
why
why would oopsie
wrong leia
why would you build a school on the
mountain huh
i had buff above legs
at that time
[Laughter]
but it was exhausting every day anyway
hella exhausting
i didn't stay long in that school
maybe because i didn't want to walk up a
[\h__\h] mountain every day just kidding
no that was not the reason
well it was because i
i sucked at latin
thank you my pinky
happy birthday toby wong
happy birthday what is that profile
picture is that a male version of gouda
like above male gura
what a language
a language that feels incredibly stiff
when talking and using it
don't you worry
it feels so stiff
[Music]
just doesn't flow as well as other
languages
but but but they always told us yeah but
it will be the basic for learning the
other languages that you're going to
learn
i guess
your
[Music]
[Laughter]
but i have to say they did not uh
like
i did not drop out i changed on purpose
[Music]
in between of a year in the middle of a
year
because i decided i couldn't take it
anymore
i wasn't going anywhere with this
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it's not
it's not locked
only the rich schools in my area latin
oh that wasn't a rich school it was a
free school
we i don't even i don't even know of any
private schools in my
country
they maybe one or two exist but i
wouldn't know of them all our schools
are free
but there are some differences anyway
some are shittier
some are a bit more difficult to get
into because you have to do like
tests to get into them
i remember man ah that was this uh
um
before getting into that school on the
mountain i tried to get into
um
it was a
it was a music school i think
and they they had a really good
reputation and and really
really um
difficult entrance test
um but back then my
my
grades weren't as [\h__\h] yet
so i still had a chance but the problem
is the problem was mostly i think that
i
did not grow up with learning an
instrument and most of my rivals who
signed up for the test for the school
they
um
all
had like that going for them
and i had nothing going for me besides
i don't know being good at art but that
i think that was like it was mostly a
music school but some kind of creativity
was
yeah very welcome but i had no music
going for me and
up until this point
i still like
wish that i had learned an instrument in
my life properly
but yeah
i couldn't
i couldn't so
i remember i was like so hopeful i was
trying so hard at the
um entry test in order to
make up for the lack of instrument
and i said i would i would love to i
think
i think i remember um if you were if you
were to make it into that school you had
to
buy and no wait i think i even had to
buy it before the
and uh before the test
they had like a weird instrument that
one had to learn
it wasn't flute it was like something
i completely forgot about that
it was
yeah before isn't that weird because i
remember i think i bought it
well it was something like
really weird i think it was something
like like
it had
parts of a keyboard to it but it i think
it had parts of a flute to it
i don't know it was weird as [\h__\h]
like why out of all things did it have
to be that
a melodica
maybe
melodical
yeah what the [\h__\h] i think that might
have been it
wait why why didn't they make us
that's such a [\h__\h] weird choice
that's weird
yeah so i was like i was ready to learn
an instrument but i think most of the
other kids already
had some instruments that they were able
to play yeah
so
they even had like a physical test as
well and i remember i was so proud that
i was able to reach my toes
easily they were like checking yo can
you reach the floor if you like bent
down and like some couldn't and i could
but as a child you're still like so
flexible not only your schedule actually
your schedule isn't really flexible but
but my legs my body definitely was
flexible
and i was so
proud
i was very proud
but then
a while later i got the letter
telling me that i didn't make it
man that was rough
that was rough i was really unhappy and
then i went to that
mountain school
where i didn't stay for long
because of [\h__\h] latin
and then i then i went to a shitty the
the music school and the mountain school
they both had like good reputation
um
but then i changed
to a different school
like in the middle of a
of a semester
and i didn't have much choice in the
middle of the semester
so i was kind of forced to go
into literally
the school with the worst reputation in
my city
it was
horrible
horrible the kids were absolutely the
worst
and they were like it was like a whole
different world like the the mountain
school i've never heard of anyone doing
like any kind of you know weird stuff
but in that school
suddenly
it's like
they're like 12 or 14 or so and they
talk about having
the s word or like having taking the d
word or not not really the demon but but
smoking
and i was like what the [\h__\h] where did i
where did i end up holy [\h__\h]
and i tried to i tried to kind of i
didn't want to become the bullied one
but but once again i felt so
uncomfortable so i i i
um
kind of found a friend in the most
bullied kid in the whole school
because she was the only one who wasn't
who wasn't
uh
[\h__\h] stupid
yeah
yeah she was the only one
so we tried our best to make it through
that stupid school
that we are both not supposed to be in
i was so scared man
especially the boys in that class man
oh i hated it i hated it so much
eventually we went on a trip to croatia
together though that was okay
oh i oh my god a good example of what
the [\h__\h] this
these
students were like was like on our trip
to croatia we were in like we were
stationed
uh put into like one of those
um
hotels for like students i don't know
what do you call it like shitty a shitty
hotel with shitty like boring rooms not
really a hotel it's more like for
students hostels yeah yeah yeah you're
going to have bag kind of like that
and um we were kicked out in the first
the whole the whole group the whole
class was kicked out of that in the
first night because
um
some of the boys
destroyed a door like a wooden door they
made a hole in it they broke it like i
don't know they were fighting or
something
imagine how frustrated the teachers must
have been holy [\h__\h]
how tough is it to be a teacher in that
situation
[Music]
unbelievable
punching a lot of cheap doors are really
weak
it was a normal door i mean maybe it was
a little bit weak but still like what
the [\h__\h] are you doing
don't break the [\h__\h] door
what did you do after i
i don't
i remember a different place that we
went to yeah yeah that was nicer
actually
but
i don't know how we got to a different
place so quickly pretty impressive
um respect to the teachers holy [\h__\h] i
couldn't i couldn't do that kind of job
[Music]
um
so thankfully
i didn't have to stay in that school for
that long
at least not full four years normally
you would have four years in junior high
school and then four years in high
school
or if you would start out junior high
school in a gymnasium then you start
then you do all eight years in the
gymnasium
yeah
so
i
wasn't there for that long because i was
in a different school before that so i
had some years in junior high school in
a different school
gymnast we call it gymnasium it's a
it's a school that combines junior high
school of high school like it's one
thing you just stay in the same school
instead of switching from junior high
school to
eight years of gym class
all you do is go to the gym and live bro
no
[Music]
constant fights back tonight teaches
substance
and the what and the what and the what
and the what
a bunch of other ones i'm surprised i
came honor right
yeah
man i really did not like going there
and i got so bullied back then and then
there was a time where
oh something happened that i really
don't want talking about
but it's normal in school time and kids
but i don't really want to say but like
i imagine i was already bullied and then
something happened that made the kids
like hate me even more
[Music]
okay i won't say it
but it was a good reason to not go to
school
and get away from those kids
um
yeah
at least like
there was bullying but every once in a
while they would be nice to me because
um i was
at least
i was not good enough for that other
school but i was definitely above
average in that school
so
sometimes they would be nice to me to
copy my homework and [\h__\h]
got it
why did i separate their layers like
that
[Music]
one thing though that
one other student that was there then
was not bullied but she did um she was
very nice to me and the bullied kid
she was like the the in between kids
sometimes there's like
a kid that gets along with the popular
ones but also gets along with the
bullied ones and somehow
but doesn't get put into the booty kids
box by the popular ones even though she
perfectly juggles
both of the teams both of the groups of
kids
that yeah the diplomat kid
uh
it was
she was fascinating to me
because she was not the smartest kid she
was however pretty nice um and
she was like
she had
insane boobs
and i asked her hey help how is that
possible
and she told me it's because
i'm already taking the pill
and the hormones
they make my boobs go big and i'm like
wow
that's so cool
yeah
fascinating
no it depends no it does it does work
depending on which one you take
apparently some some do other stuff
some
some make your boobs go big some don't
make your boobs go big she revealed her
secret it was not really a secret she
was she was pretty proud of it
[Music]
those but donkers
keanu was never the same again
[Music]
a whole new world
okay
[Music]
that's i think the boings may have been
a reason why she was uh able to juggle
no way
able to juggle both sides
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] why she was able to juggle the
both sides the popular kids and the
bullied kids
thanks for the membership fbi welcome
welcome
am i am i saying you buy stuff i'm just
talking about my childhood okay
it's just i can't help it it's just my
childhood
i envied her but now look at me now i
have big boobies too now
sometimes it just takes time
[Music]
fbi kick him out kfb how did you even
let the fbi in here
how could you let that happen
yeah bye now
red red red just like those pimples i
had
man
acne do be a [\h__\h] though
[\h__\h] acne
[Music]
it's too real
it's just too real
the conversations
[Music]
relatable it's not fetch acne is not
fetched i never had it i hated i hated
everyone who didn't have acne how dare
you
not have acne when you're a [\h__\h]
teenager
how dare you
if one has to have it then everyone has
to have it
suffer with me
it took me
it took me so long
to get a hold get get control over it
i'm gonna be very real now holy [\h__\h]
what a real talk stream
it took me so [\h__\h] long like even
when i was out of
puberty
holy [\h__\h]
real stream eyes if you look close you
might see some scars
look close at me look close closer
closer look look look you're not looking
enough look
[Music]
enhance
look at my pores look at them
look at them
did you guys ever have chicken pox
i mean you're all chimpkins so i assume
you all had chicken pox before
yeah yeah me too i remember
my mom put like some cream on each each
tiny spot that does not mean that i'm a
chicken though i'm still a phoenix even
the phoenix can get chicken pox
even the phoenix can get chicken pox
it was awesome could stay at home and
eat ice cream hell yeah
hell yeah
melted ice cream though melted it had to
be melted my favorite thing was melted
ice cream
not the watery ice cream i said this
before
not the watery one but the creamy one
wait until it melts mix it with other
ones like chocolate and vanilla
[Music]
hell yeah or chocolate the best one was
chocolate and strawberry
um
and then make a soup out of it yum yum
yum yum yum
it was still cold obviously you just
wait a little bit until the creamy ice
cream becomes soupy ice cream
no no rephrasing no you drink the
the soup with a spoon
spending too much time with this shading
doesn't need that much detail
[Music]
oh
hmm
[Music]
making no sense thank you for the pinky
now
thank you
well there's a lot of a lot of school
stories school reminiscing
i don't you guys say my
i saw someone saying that at least that
my
um stories my childhood was whack but no
not really compared to ominous stories
my stories are nothing
really not much happened in my
my
my childhood started getting interesting
at a certain age
without no no as a teenager but i can't
really talk much about that
i can only oh you know what i can tell
some things
i can say some things
but it stops at some point
i was getting this
my obsession with japan
started
when i was like
i think
11 or so
you know with uh
tails off symphonia and then
and then with
idols watching lots of idols
and then
uh
getting into anime
thanks to
suga sugar doom and ah megami sama
oh my goodness goodness goddess and uh
what was that other one
was that one okay no no
no
n what the [\h__\h] i don't know why i
watched that as a child
stuff like that
[Music]
classics thank you mike thank you i will
read that when i read split
that's kasi on that
yeah
kimi nozo yeah
yeah weird weird uh choices to get into
anime
but
um
the the one thing
that i
really that really really kept me so
interested in japan was the idol culture
and i was going so deep into that rabbit
hole of hello project that i wanted to
become an idol myself
that was ages ago
yeah i'm kind of i'm i'm something
similar now i'm not not quite the ideal
you guys say you're an idol now but it's
not quite ideally what i want it to be
but at least i once i become
3d
i might be able to do something
similar to that i suppose
but it's still different it's still
different
[Music]
um
no i like what i'm doing now it's just
kind of too late anyway to
make that other dream come true
um
anymore
it's too late so i accepted it i
accepted the situation
[Music]
but yeah i mean it's extremely difficult
as a
as a foreigner living in a foreign land
to become an idol in japan
you gotta first of all you gotta be
young for that but how how the [\h__\h]
do you
[Music]
go there to japan
at the right age
in order to become an idol
that is the first step and that is the
most difficult step
unless your family for some reason
decides they need to move to japan
it's gonna be really difficult
[Music]
because they start like
the hell project items they all started
out like when they were like
10 some even with 9
10 11.
[Music]
and then they went on to be idols for
like 10 years
approximately
until they're like 20 21 22 23
oh
the whole their whole childhood they
spent doing that
which i guess at least
i could keep some of my childhood for
myself
[Music]
looks fine i think that looks fine
oh sure
alrighty moving on enough ruffles action
i spent too much time on that because i
was chit chatting too much
boobies
[Music]
this part
is interesting because it's
translucent
it's
transparent
[Music]
a virtual idol yeah but the one thing
that's just
missing in my opinion
is like you know even with like concerts
or
meet and greets
you guys may see me
but the other way around hmm
there's just some
some real interaction missing like
imagine
i was i was looking at some stage
footage yesterday and the day before
yesterday from hello project and also
from mizuki nana of course
but like
seeing
them on stage
like
like them being able to see the audience
stare with their own eyes and not
through some camera or something
but with their own eyes in hd
wow that's just so much different
experiencing it while you're on the
stage with your own eyes from that angle
it's just something that's not exactly
possible for a beachuba
orbeezinger
or whatever it is
um
so it's never quite the same feeling
and with handshake events
for example or any kind of like fan
event
[Music]
i mean
in some way maybe maybe it makes it
easier in some way to not be like really
like
a touchable person
but just being a beach offer
um
but in other ways
it would be
so cool to actually be able to like
physically
like shake the hands and and like really
like
take a take a hd look at you
you know what i mean
it's just different just because because
it always feels like you're you're not
quite there well me me as a
me as a vegetable i'm just
not quite there like for the dokomi
concert for example
and the dokomi handshake event that we
did in germany at the event called
dokomi an anime convention i was there
as a as a guest as a special guest i
performed
on stage and i
um
i did a handshake event
but
which was fun it was fun and and and the
concert as well like it was live so
and i had a i had a camera feed
i saw the audience
but it still would be so much more fun
and so much more different if it was
like more real
yeah
that's something i regret a little bit
maybe maybe one day
i don't know maybe somehow one day that
could be improved to give us an even
more realistic experience i don't know
i don't know how technical stuff is
gonna
in the future
maybe maybe i can take harry potter's
invisibility
a coat thingy cape
and be on stage but be invisible
hmm
no
hologram but that's no
maybe i don't know
hologram i guess
[Music]
i'm kind of already something like that
mikko's mascot costume
why does it have to be mikko's mascot
costume why can't i just have
chihuahua mascot costume
or or
dress up as a kotori
hmm
[Music]
something's broken here
um
[Music]
i think i saw that yet
oh
why did that get deleted i was starting
to read it was that your boy
[Music]
want it
oh okay
okay
i didn't even get to read it
um
here's a little spot
i found you
nonetheless i think the food fest will
be amazing anyway
holy [\h__\h] that crowd will be huge guys
it will be huge
but that's exactly something i would i
would love to experience like
standing on stage like
there in person you know what i mean
physically that kind of crowd is
something i want to
experience
like that
or even as an audience
i would love to mix into the audience
that's [\h__\h] amazing too
become one with the audience one of the
chimpkins
[Music]
accept the
fact that
i'm
i'm a [\h__\h]
i'm not real am i real chickens am i
real
am i not real
this is so sad
one could make a drama anime about the
life of a youtuber falling in love for
example with a real person and then
the real person falls in love with the
veto booklet
but then oh they can't touch the video
but they try to but the hand goes
through the body as if they were a ghost
and the future was like we can never
never be together no
we are not meant to be
we're not meant to be
i am not real you are real
[Music]
would i think that would be a
pretty dramatic
am i really
what
i can't believe my favorite youtuber
isn't real
i'm real though right
what was that wasn't that pinocchio
he's like i want to be a real boy and i
want i want to be a real girl
i want to be a real woman
oh
oh let me be a real girl
maybe maybe none of this is real maybe
this is all just a dream of someone
right
conspiracy
let's go
maybe none of this is real anyway
are these boobies looking weird
maybe not that many
well
these boobies need a lift in liquify
later on they're kind of saggy which is
nice too sometimes but
mine are way more lifted
why no lambor lifted yo
girl what happened girl what happened to
your boobs huh
they look heavy yeah i know it's it's uh
uh physics
this is gravity
okay i'm done with that for now
um
[Music]
i don't know how i'm gonna do this
it's really roughly i think it's fine
[Music]
this is supposed to be like a golden
detail so we're gonna make it shiny but
golden stuff always has a high contrast
in like the shading yeah
but i shouldn't be talking is if i knew
what i was talking about if you guys
want to learn something about art go
watching those art streams
i'm like useless in that regards
three cards
useless don't listen to me
don't listen to me
i'm just trying my best here
watch along with blade runner because it
touches this like what is it yeah i'm
sure there's like similar movies like
that out there um not exactly with a v2
but totally can see that concept and
other stuff like a girl just being i
don't know a hologram or
a a ghost or
a
figment of your imagine a pigment a
figment
of your imagination
a pigment a pigment
a pigment
the movie her
where the dude dates his phone what what
the [\h__\h]
is that a horror movie that kind of
sounds like it would be a thriller or a
horror movie
scary
and yes someone
some people asked i will be reading
super chats
once i'm done with drawing
he dates siri oh
is he aware of it the whole time though
that
he's just dating a [\h__\h] robot
is he getting brainwashed
by the robot
oh my god
he's aware of it is he crazy
[Music]
does she force him to do weird stuff
her name is samantha
does she does she become a fridge i feel
like i've seen so huh
what's that what am i thinking about
oh
i feel like i've seen something with
a person out like a ai or so hacking
into a fridge and stuff
what the [\h__\h] am i thinking about
hmm
we just want this to look decent
when looking at it from
a distance
doesn't have to look good up close
let me look up
nadal do i have some cute
pink stones
here and there let me add that as well
it was here oh i already made an outline
for that okay
[Music]
let's look at it
perfect
check out the trailer
if that's a thriller i don't really like
friends
[Music]
thrillers are so
hot scary
[Music]
alrighty now let's do the dress oh we're
getting close to finishing it actually
the longest part really was the hair i'd
like to spend a lot of time with the
hair
when it comes to coloring but the
longest part overall is
outlining this piece of [\h__\h]
i hate doing outlines
let me look at my tangent list unless
you guys have a specific topic again
otherwise i'll look at my
tangent although there's not many
tangents left i don't really have much
anything and any more [\h__\h] i'm running
out of digits
i'm opening my my food my tuna peanut
pasta salad
with some tomatoes
talk about lasagna
wait this is even still good
are you still good are you still edible
actually the the expiration date was
yesterday but i think it's probably
still fine it looks a bit weird but
it's probably
so
still smells okay
be fine one day it's just one day in
some countries maybe it's still
yesterday
now probably not anymore at this point
but still
[Music]
did someone say any tangents that i
can't talk about
let me see scroll scroll
what language you use when you dream
i'm not not really aware of it
sometimes it's like a mix but mostly i
think it's just
german or even english
but i'm not really quite aware of it
portugal concert already talked a little
bit about it before
any [\h__\h] post ready for your vacation
yes
um
one special one and it's not gonna be
that much this time
it's not gonna be much sister slow
um
one thing that
is very special
that i think you guys are gonna love
um where
i had someone else
do something and i did a voiceover
and the other one is probably just gonna
be an am something video
hmm
mr translate for pickle and valkyrie
um
i saw some comments saying that
i mean if they need one
i guess but
you saw all these reply i did but i
don't really want to play apex
um
any other
plans just getting a massage
but besides that we're just gonna be
skiing
just skiing every day
[Music]
yeah they both wanna
collab apparently i've seen the clip
but why the hell would they
think of me i think there's like other
people as well
who could translate maybe even on on
valkyrie's side i don't know
i mean i wouldn't turn it down but it
would be kind of awkward if i was just
there to translate
wouldn't that be kind of awkward
i would personally feel kind of awkward
um
[Music]
wow these tomatoes are crazy um
are those even tomatoes wait a second
what are those where are those
no i think i think they're not tomatoes
they're like tiny weirdly shaped
um
not paprika they're in english they're
not paprika they are
um
bell peppers but like tiny how many tiny
tiny tiny bell peppers
tiny tinier than like the same size as
this as the tiny noodles
hmm
they look so tiny
pepperoncinis
i don't know maybe something like that
definitely something that you would say
cheeni too at the end of the name
hmm
yeah the taste is uh
pretty good it doesn't taste expired yet
thankfully
um
weird videos
[Music]
let me look at
my i actually can't remember
yo
wait a second let me mute myself
[Music]
wow
okay
sorry i saw something that
um
very interesting
let me look at my
let me look in my videos right after
watching i've been watching a lot of
clips out one weird clip was uh
lucia
acting yandere
[Music]
not that much weird stuff here in my
history i was watching some perfume
concerts at concert clubs again
you know perfume they have some
dope ass concerts as well
they're so hype
and we're watching a lot of hill project
concerts oh ah
thank you you have led me to a tangent
i
got some recommendations for a rabbit
hole that is called
traveling through japan with uh this
train or this train or this ferry or
this ferry
uh
this train that takes 12 hours or this
train that takes one hour to the same
location
for example or
this and that oh this this train has
this kind of uh sleep overnight
thingy
uh this is a luxury overnight train yeah
yeah you've seen us too
it's fascinating
like
traveling only for the sake of being in
a specific train or a specific
fairy or whatever
is something i mean i guess i have kind
of considered it before but
there was also this one train that
shows off like
a very beautiful
um
winter scenery but that was actually not
in japan this rabbit hole started out in
japan but then then um i think it was a
swiss train a swiss train
that
um has like a lot of big windows and it
takes a long time and it leads you i
think through
switzerland mostly
oh wait i don't have the wings here
uh let me look at the color oh okay
[Music]
and uh yeah it's just it's pretty
expensive but
uh it shows a beautiful winter scenery
youtube only recommends me those hoof
videos ah
yeah yeah that's
something i do not need to see
anymore
that was weird
the hoof cleaning videos not that not as
satisfying as you would think they are
as they claim they are
um
uh but yeah yeah yeah it made me think
if i ever if if the c thing is finally
gone
sheep sharing oh that sounds that sounds
satisfying
but if the sea thing is finally gone i
wanna i wanna use those trains too
[Music]
i want to try out some of those like the
the luxury
luxury deluxe
solo rooms in the train
oh it's just a beautiful scenery like
waking up in the in the early morning
in the train while the train during
sunrise is is like
uh traveling through some winter scenery
snowy scenery so definitely want to take
one of those trains in hokkaido
or on the way to hokkaido um
in overnight buses
i've been in a lot of overnight buses
but they're all not that fancy or
comfortable
ah you know what never mind um
in
in um
sorry brain is slow right now
in
in germany and like austria and so on
there's this company called flixbus
which is like the biggest company
for
uh
like long distance buses and they're
pretty decent
but
in japan i've tried like so many
different
uh
night buses before
when i lived there before her life
way before
i had to travel a lot between tokyo and
osaka
and
there were
like
uh so many different categories of buses
mostly
we could only afford the people that i
traveled with we could only afford like
the cheapest of the cheap
so
there's
the cheapest of the cheap would be um
two seats on each side so like a four
seat row
and
no blanket really uncomfortable tiny
seat
and usually also very [\h__\h] cold in
the in the bus
so i would travel a lot like dad it's
like a seven or eight hour trip i think
with the bus from tokyo to osaka or the
other way around but sometimes sometimes
sometimes i would be
blessed with a bit more of an expensive
bus
a bit more expensive means a curtain in
between the seats oh my god privacy
curtain yes
a little bit of reclining because you're
the most basic ones don't even have
reclining
and a blanket oh my god blanket
and then you can go even more high class
fancy
some of them
have curtains
or
they have like a
you know when the when the when the seat
when the seat is almost like a
like a
capsule like you can
above your head you can like create like
a
like a hood or something that is
connected to the seat i don't know how
to explain it
you know what i mean
it turns into a bit not exactly okay
that's that's definitely exists but
not as
we didn't we didn't we weren't uh in
such a fancy bus but close enough close
enough
um
yeah yeah and it would be like two or
three seats per row maximum and a lot of
reclining
a lot of reclining
really fancy and blankets and [\h__\h] um
nice but i hated traveling with
those buses because uh um oh it always
made me
very
nervous and i couldn't sleep well anyway
because i always have
always had issues falling asleep and
especially in the bus i was never able
to sleep and then we would arrive at
like
5 30 a.m at shinjuku's [\h__\h] station
5 30. i saw goji honey shinjuku
i would be so tired and then we wouldn't
have time or any any place to
to sleep to take another nap we would
have to immediately like go to work
first breakfast and then go to work
in tokyo oh man
that was so
so exhausting
switching back and forth between tokyo
and osaka
what was i thinking when i was drawing
this
what was i thinking
actually no this one should be
that color
oh my god one too
sounds painful it is
i'm so glad i'm i don't have to travel
with those buses anymore but now after
seeing
all those videos on traveling through
japan in all these different means even
that there's this one channel that makes
all these videos right you probably get
recommendations from that channel too
but he even sometimes goes like really
cheap um
he sometimes he chooses very cheap
transportation methods as well and he
still makes it
looks so enjoyable like he appreciates
even the tiniest things about
these cheap transportation methods
seeing it in such a
positive light is art in itself i think
that is a skill
i should do this on a separate layer to
be honest
we'll make it easier afterwards
[Music]
envy the public transport around the
world japan is like especially
like they have so many choices too
like as i said
in germany and austria
we only have like like one specific type
of bus but japan has like so many
different types of
night buses night buses specifically
like long distance
long distance buses
if we had more of those
not only trains japan's train system of
course also amazing
but like their buses yo
next level
although i do have to say i only that
only applies to the long distance buses
that japan is next level when i tried
like normal buses in japan
they are
they they don't look that advanced
uh as where i'm from
here i feel our buses are more advanced
um like more modern looking
probably because here we are more
focused more focused on like um
buses as a quick transportation to work
than trains because we don't in austria
in most cities in austria
we don't have
a
subway in like
probably 90
90 i feel like in 90
of austria we don't have subway
so what else do we do we focus on buses
and non-subway trains
yeah we do have trains
but those are more like for a long
distance
or city to city
village to village
lots of trams
depends on the city as well
[Music]
some cities don't even have trams
yay
rush hour
i don't know i don't experience rush
hour because i don't go outside
ah but i don't remember when i
when i still went to work
uh
at
like a normal place
and took transport but
public transportation
yeah yeah i guess they were rush hours
but not as bad as in japan holy [\h__\h] you
guys probably know they pushed the
people in right you guys have seen that
before i have been pushed in before as
well i hate it
i hate it so much
good
rush hour in japan is the worst
it's nuts
like there's and it it confuses me
because there's literally especially in
tokyo
if you miss your train there's another
in two to three minutes most of the time
two to three minutes and you have to
push yourself into that like even when
it looks already full there's still
gonna be extra 10 people per door that
are gonna push themselves in even when
you already think yo there's no space in
there
no [\h__\h] way that anyone is gonna make
it inside the train anymore japanese
people they have this skill they push
themselves in
and and liquefy themselves japanese
people may as well be cats
they might be cats
they turn into liquid somehow they all
make it into that one train
nekodesho
i usually just choose to
take the next train which will be a full
train as well but at least i will be the
first one in that station to make it in
or one of the first ones
because they feel like somewhere in the
middle of the train
it's
it's not as painful as at the as when
you stand in the entrance
area of each train
and then have all these people being
pushed in
it's crazy
[Music]
why am i even coloring it like this i
could have filled it in with a selection
tool probably but a lot of these lines
are open
because i was being too messy
[Music]
gives you anxiety
those trains
yeah yeah but you get used to it you
have to accept it like there's not much
other choice you have
if you gotta take that train then you
gotta take that train
i guess
because every train is gonna be full i
guess maybe that's the reasoning behind
why they push themselves forcefully into
it and not wait for the next ring
because the next trend is also gonna be
full
every train is gonna be full
there's a little piece of skin that i
missed
whoopsie
totally did not see that
okay
that's fine now
i will also add some color oh my god
we're close to done i still have to do
the headpiece
good eye yeah
yeah yeah
mainly
they will have
how about we do a separate layer
this color
big big big feathers behind my ears
hmm
adult adult nature
kiwawa
really nice thank you
i'm so glad to live in a place where
public transport is needed
where is
public transport not needed do you mean
like on the countryside where you have
to use your car anyway to get anywhere
[Music]
fluffy feathers yeah gorgeous feathers
i know
moonlight am i looping song
no
[Music]
very difficult word
in america
[Music]
i don't know i guess so yes probably
your mountain survivor
[Music]
i recall you saying that you did a
drawing of yourself pretty debbie did
you mean starter bookstore was there an
illustration you haven't shown this
are you talking about the sketch
yeah i think you're talking about the
sketch
well i never ended up showing it to you
guys today
the sketch that i did like immediately
after
uh being shown the first draft of myself
uh
yes i have it somewhere
no
what no
what
what do you mean that's not it oh no you
mean i didn't show you okay
uh i can try to find it quickly
i'm trying to find it again
i found it many times before
it should be
[Music]
i found it
previously
but now i lost it again
where is it
ah
wait it might be on my laptop
it might be on my laptop
but i feel like i have put all my data
on here as well
i keep on finding it and losing it yeah
because every time i find it i'm like i
don't need this now wait it could be in
my download folder
uh
when did i ah
it would be like so
old
i can't find it now
i can't oh wait what if i
maybe
oh wait a second what if it's in my
drive
what did i not put it in my driveway
i had to put it in my dress
all my old pencils are drying and the
t-shirt drawing
yeah yeah yeah yeah
not so costly
i haven't
haven't used my drawing skill as a as
much as i wanted to treasure hunting yes
i'm going on a treasure hunting
[Music]
no i can't find it
i forgot where i put it again
i'm so useless
oh but the drawing we did for cali as
well here everything but that one
drawing
that one sketch that i did of myself
everything but that
[Music]
okay
you
oh
oh there is some
good nostalgic stuff in here
remember that
my first rew stream
that's cussy
um
[Music]
made a meme for that
ah
yeah yeah i was showing memes
during that stream i remember hmm
who can't find it
maybe in here
[Music]
i lost it again
maybe maybe next time i find it randomly
i'll upload it as a members only post
in the members in the community board
maybe i'll do it that way so i don't
lose it anymore
it's
yeah uh
just like finding circles
[Music]
oh you guys
oh no that's uh that's something else
something else or something else
okay i keep it up we can't waste too
much time on this
you will see it eventually we'll get it
someday one day
i'm i ran out of pineapple juice
water only now
water mixed with some remains of the
pineapple juice ew
this is fine
i know you've been asking for it for a
long time
you're very curious about it for some
reason i don't know why you are so
obsessed about it why are you so
obsessed with it
explain that to me why are you so
obsessed with seeing that piece of art
that i talked about
just obsessed with everything about me
aren't you
understandable
and so my aunt you guys are still
swinging
and room temperature is fine if it
depends iced tea i want to drink cold
water room temperature
coca cola something in between
i love your art you guys love my art
more than i do maybe
but that's some something that i think
artists have in common they don't like
their own art most of the time
i wonder if eno likes her art does she
ever
say stuff like yo my art looks like [\h__\h]
does she ever
i mean she would be kind of crazy if she
did but
maybe she thinks it a little bit i don't
know
most most artists feel that way about
their own art so i can imagine maybe ina
feels like that sometimes but doesn't
necessarily vocalize it
she doesn't like every piece
she was astounded by her own art what in
a negative way
man i need to hit her
i need to slap her flap her silly
so she sees
how amazing her art is
i'm a big fan of the art i often i often
like
when i see something
new of her art i dmr i'm like yo we know
you read that yoina yowiena that's so
cool
holy [\h__\h] you know you're so cool
you're inspiring me you know
she really does inspire me
i told you before i think that i
wanted to be an artist like her but i
wanted to be many things wanted to be an
actress
wanted to be an idol wanted to be a
uh
an illustrator i wanted to be many
things so that's that
try to make
these look like
hookah papa jordan
feathers
very soft
washed with gravy
carefully by hand
these feathers
one strand after another
carefully with love and gravy
you excuse me
as if you
don't like gravy
you were wondering why those are so
shiny
you know wants people to rediscover
their love for it i'm sure she heard you
say it at all
ah
yeah yeah i know i know
i know i know i know ina is so wholesome
[Music]
oh i was i was wondering uh for future
references i was looking up um like
music producers
um because i tend to
for my music i just tend to go for like
you know think about commissioning
people that are like available that are
in this community like in the japanese
music industry like
um
vocaloid or touhou project producers
stuff like that but
um i do want
to
there's there's like a specific sound
that i want at some point for at least
one single
which is kind of like a mainstream sound
i want something like kpop-ish but i
i've been looking at like
um
producers and most producers that like
get mentioned as producers under the
songs like in the youtube description
and so on
there's like no way to contact them
so
i'm like how how does one get in there
but if you guys know
of any like
cool producer
who's kind of available on twitter
doesn't need to be kpop
like kpop
in itself is just like pop button korean
any any kind of like western producer
is cool too i just want to look
uh through them for their portfolio i
guess
and if if it's possible to contact them
i wouldn't mind considering them for a
future release not what i'm working on
right now i'm working on something else
anyway
but just for the future you know
because i've been looking and looking
unlikely looking there's a red velvet
produced on twitter
what but they're probably [\h__\h]
expensive aren't they
i wonder i wonder yeah
i wonder how much a k-pop
producer would charge for a song because
like once i feel like once you get out
of that vocaloid and touhou
project producer bubble i feel like the
prices will rise in an instant like into
galactic levels
[Laughter]
[Music]
but i want to at least check it out see
if it's like realistic
an intelligent producer works best for
personal connections yeah but i don't
really have
much like uh only like in in japan you
know
but whoever said that about the red
velvet producer please
uh let me know about it maybe on twitter
afterwards after this stream
i am interested
red velvet has amazing songs
[Music]
do these like look like feathers now
they look similar to how look at papa
drew them now
pretty pretty similar
oh maybe a bit maybe needs to be a bit
more shiny he made it very shiny
papa made it very shiny
i made them look very fluffy perhaps
fluffy
usually not how i would draw feathers i
think but
um
start fundraising music friends no no no
no no no no you already kind of do that
without doing it on purpose i suppose
all of the super chats
go into stuff like that music production
so you're already doing your part
without knowing about it
for making my music possible
the other day i started completely
random but the other day i started
watching this uh
show
on netflix
that
from the local aesthetics looked to me
very the great gatsby-ish and then i
started watching it and i realized it's
a show
about the author of the great gatsby and
i'm like what [\h__\h] it's the
gatsbyception
it's a freaking gatsbyception what was
it called again
what's it called again maybe you guys
know it's on netflix i think um
what was it again
yeah my art deco cake yeah the guy is
called
f scott fitzgerald oh gerald my fruit
oopsie
fitzgerald and his
girlfriend although it's the
the show is mostly about the girlfriend
at least in the beginning
you don't know what it's called you
don't know what the show is called
really
he had an interesting life yeah i was
getting curious about their lives so in
the middle of watching their the show i
was looking both of them up on wikipedia
uh
zelda yes yes yes
yeah his wife is zelda
um
let me look it up
netflix fitzgerald
ah zed the beginning of everything is
thank you albert's good a little bit too
late
that's what uh it's called
[Music]
set
the beginning of everything
and it i was cracking up over the accent
that the people are speaking in that
show
where is that accent from something
southern i think
very interesting american accent
of course if i were to try to imitate it
it would sound like my scottish accent
again probably so i'm not even gonna try
hmm but the cell phone man they have a
funny accent
but howdy people a little bit howdy but
it didn't sound because of the
i think the choices of words
um
because it they use very old words
it was i guess when was that the 50s
or so
um
it sounded more
sophisticated it sounded indeed very
sophisticated even though it was a howdy
accent it sounded so sophisticated
kind of want to learn how to talk like
that
howdy accent i shouldn't call it that
probably
[Music]
19 20 19 30.
probably around that time yeah
and thanks to that i learned about a
term
i learned about this term
zelda the girl
the girl
the wife
the later wife
of scott fitzgerald she was something
called a flapper girl
a flapper girl
um
you know what that is
[Music]
yeah in the 20s and 1920s
a flapper girl was
was a
a subculture of young western women in
the 1920s who wear short skirts
oh scandalous
and they bobbed their hair i guess
the others would have long hair
listened to jazz oh my god scandalous
yeah they listened to jazz
and flaunted their disdain for what was
then considered acceptable behavior
so just rebels
they were like rebellious adults
flappers were seen as brass for wearing
excessive makeup drinking alcohol
smoking cigarettes in public etc driving
cars oh my god
treating s-e-x in a casual manner
and otherwise flouting social and as the
actual norms
oh
as automobiles became available flappers
gained freedom of movement and privacy
flappers are icons of the roaring
twenties
the social political turbulence and
increased blah blah blah
this is uh interesting so they were the
the
valley girl the 1920s i'm not sure could
we call it that valley girls of the
1920s
i'm not sure if valley girls are
considered a
rebellious
but these girls definitely are
that's accurate
it took 40 more years to get a mini
skirt hell yeah yeah back then knee
length was
scandalous i find that very interesting
kneeling holy [\h__\h]
look at my skirt look at my skirt of my
normal outfit what would i would have
been naked i would have been considered
naked back then
my orange skirt in the
in the size of a belt that literally
looks like a belt
they would think i'm like [\h__\h] insane
[Music]
funny
funny how times change isn't it
it do be funny
[Music]
you'd have given them heart attacks
i would've wait what did we what did
they call them flappy flappy girls flap
yeah flappers flappy girls
what would i have been
couldn't even find a term for that oh
man
i would have been a legend
[\h__\h] legend that's for sure
so this part hookah papa
didn't really draw this very feathery
i mean
it's kind of very
flat
so
it doesn't need that many details i
suppose
it's wings but at the same time
it's not that feathery
hmm
permission to use your eye that you're
drawing is my proper picture when you're
done
but you're gonna change it soon after
anyway until another one of your shoes
aren't you you're gonna change it back
to chloe or so one month later whatever
is hot at that time
i don't want to be your girl
your profile picture for the moment for
like one
week or two weeks at the most
and then you're gonna change it i'm
gonna be like was i'm not good enough
for you anymore
just kidding you can use it if you want
to
but you're gonna change it eventually
and i'm gonna be like why didn't you
change it
no
no no no no not that i care not that i
care
if
several times um pointed out that you
say i'm your aussie but you have other
people in your profile picture
i've pointed out several times and yet
and yet your profile picture is still
still someone else
so
i'm not sure
not sure what you're trying to do
anymore here
[Music]
sad
my profile picture on discord has been
your face for the past several months
thank you
this is why i don't have a picture
you know why not have a picture change
like me your profile picture make me a
profound thing to make me a professor to
make me a professor
please
[Music]
please cannot be your profile pizza
please
[Music]
am i not cute enough for you
some of you already have me as your
profile because i love you
thank you
no just kidding you don't have to oh
obviously
you don't have to
you have to do anything
you don't
you don't have to watch my streams but
you don't have to like me
i don't have to do anything
not that i care
what did i care i don't care
i don't care
okay
i guess i'll be changing my profile
[\h__\h] oh you didn't have to
i don't want to wear another person's
face okay sure whatever
whatever
[Music]
that's a crazy face but at least it's my
crazy face
that's okay
there's too much
tough uh competition in k-pop anyway i
don't have a chance but
at least at least at least i can be a
youtuber that's maybe
that that maybe has a few fans in korea
and
that's fine
i will be satisfied with that
[Music]
oh thank you man you changed it
uh santa doesn't whatever he wants to be
a penguin okay
okay okay
making your own pvp pfp consensus ah
yeah yeah i guess so i've heard people
talk about that that is actually true
yeah if you if you are a bad chimpkin
and write [\h__\h] about other people
somewhere uh then don't please do not
use my profile picture
you changed it
yes i see you
[Music]
that is true
make
kiwa proud with your actions
hmm
i feel like there's like a
a lot of kiwa faces in the chat now
maybe there are already ones before
some of them already were before
i can't change it
that's okay
it's kind of your personality
mm-hmm
but i'm just saying not like whoopsie oh
you make me
very happy if you have me use your
profile picture it makes it it's
flattering but of course you don't have
to
it's just one of those things that
make me feel loved by you
oh yeah
how long have i been drawing today five
hours already how has it been five hours
what the [\h__\h] is that express menu
if you
time flies when you tangent yeah but i
ran out of tangents unbelievable i know
right i know i know
i do not i do in fact not have endless
endless tangents
especially after
over a year of streaming and always
streaming so long always telling so many
tangents
at some point
i just run out of it
we love your 210 job
ah sweet
you sweetheart thank you
yeah sometimes i
very rarely but sometimes i add there
goes out just as a
as a
cute extra
it is not
me trying to copy any other member it's
just sometimes
it's a cute way
of ending your sentence sometimes
[Music]
don't say that to her she will be mad
she will be very angry if you say she's
a ninja
she'll be like no ninja
samurai
[Music]
no no no ninja
she's not no she's not a ninja no
no no no no no
i think i even saw a clip where she was
uh saying that
when she was getting a little bit
aggravated
the drawing looks good thank you thank
you for checking in
[Music]
exactly
that's
i guess the same way how you guys always
say i am a chicken
even though i am a phoenix but
you don't listen you don't listen
[Music]
i don't know how to color this
it's supposed to be wings but the
reference aka myself
it doesn't really
look like it i'm just gonna
color it flat then we're gonna be done
faster too
probably who it is yo
are you excited for 3d
anything listeners can do
no not really
not regarding that
no no
thank you for wanting to help though
[Music]
i'm i will not give up my hope though
my hopium i still have enough of that
i'm a phoenix and the phoenix does not
give up
no matter how long it takes me
[Music]
hope
bless bless no yeah but your picture is
amazing i feel like i'm jesus
this is not a cult
holy [\h__\h] nabita maybe you need to show
me that picture in big
show it to me on
twitter i will print it out and then
print it on on tinted glass
and now secretly in the middle of the
night i'll climb up a church and replace
all their windows with
with that tinted
tinted glass that i uh
printed out yeah
so all of their windows will be me in
the next morning
call the police on me
i trust you guys of this knowledge to
not tell anyone else
i'm trusting you
need your support here
it sound bad
i leave a reply okay i'll go okay
thank you
yeah that looks okay that looks okay
looks uh like what i have here
i've been writing articles of course to
inspire entrepreneurs while you stream
please speak business but what is your
wisdom
uh my wisdom for entrepreneurs
here i will give you my 100
original wisdom that you will get
nowhere else because i am the wise
business lady
don't let your dreams be dreams
just
do it do it
you you've heard it here the first time
[Laughter]
you already knew the first time right
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
of course of course of course of course
of course of course
no 100 original because i'm just that's
inspiring
[Music]
you
i wanna play
pokemon
[Music]
i wanna play pokemon i wanna play
pokemon
[Music]
why is it
addicting i must say it really has
become addicting
surprisingly
it's like i guess this is how people
must have felt when they played breath
of the wild
it's like a game that you can play
pretty much endlessly
um
like even if you're not doing the main
quest
there's so much other stuff to do and
the quests are like even
i feel like they're
the side quests are
not that repetitive and boring like okay
a lot a lot of them have something to do
with casting pokemon and all but they
will have like some legit reasons like
one that needs a needs a ground pokemon
to help with his rice fields or whatever
welcome to the rice fields [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
um
and then
and then there's uh the lady who wants
to study fashion
so she wants the male and the female
pokemon of that whatever pokemon that
was called
yeah i feel like they did a good job
with the quests
they all make sense to me
she said the thing it's not the first
time i said it
i said it during my
during my
sakuna
streams
many times
the ogee
yeah yeah good old times
a lot of them fit the setting exactly
that's what i'm saying yo
[Music]
i feel like pokemon side quests used to
be
simpler than that
and like they didn't try that hard to
make each quest
unique
the only thing that maybe could be
improved is like the looks of some of
the
npcs those are still a bit repetitive
but
doesn't bother me that much many games
have their repetitive
copy and paste npcs
yeah
pokemon side quests in general as i
remember as well i don't they're rare
barely any right yeah
just some trading pokemon and that's
about it
[Music]
so that's a good thing
oh i'm not in late game yet by far
but um
when playing privately i said this on
stream i said it probably wouldn't
bother me playing it privately and
indeed it does not bother me play when i
play it privately the quietness doesn't
bother me at all
just as a streamer
like it's like uh
yo
this is so quiet
all right all right oh [\h__\h] the boobies
are looking
3d don't you guys feel like you could
touch them
try touching them try catching them
i will try too
wait i need my
with my finger
[Music]
where's my thing
is
[Music]
let me touch it
poke the booby poke the movie poke the
booby
poke
is so soft
they're so soft
hr nightmare
well it's myself i can do this with
myself
poke
poke or maybe
put it put in between here
just
hanging hanging out with
myself yeah just having fun
[Laughter]
what's your problem you like what you're
seeing you wish you could poke it too
noodles noodles
tuna noodles
[Music]
why are you like this
oh my god we're almost done
oh my god
oh oh oh what do you got me and dick
hurray
[Music]
let me do this part quick little the
little golden part here
[Music]
are those pink
what's wrong
no it doesn't really look like it
okay
it's just golden detail
[Music]
okay noise
tacky out of this chip
yeah when no one else loves you just
gotta love yourself
and
it is what it is
at least my cats love me
hey isn't that mentality lovely though
some even say that you can't love
someone else or so before you don't
learn to love yourself yeah yeah yeah
it's quite a deep thought
you need to learn to appreciate yourself
otherwise you won't be able to love
someone else
isn't that beautiful
[Music]
that's how it is
it's true it's true
do you guys love yourself
can you guys say that i mean it's okay
if you say you can't
that's okay it's really difficult it's a
very difficult thing
sorta no yes yet
most of the time i would kill for me wow
that's wonderful you like yourself that
much that you would kill for yourself
kind of on and off not really doing my
best yes do your best
it takes time
and i understand if you can't
but
everyone is beautiful and lovely in
their own way
you all have qualities about yourself
that you maybe just have problems with
realizing
or
appreciating or even
you know finding out that you have them
there's times where i really don't like
myself either
so it's just normal
i think one thing that people can get
really hung up on is
their own looks
being unhappy with their own looks
when everyone even like people that you
deem
that you think are beautiful they often
also have a lot of
issues with themselves
and they look at you and they they think
nothing they don't think that you're
ugly or anything even if you think it
yourself often they're just like you
look fine you look pretty
often it's just ourselves
isn't it
[Music]
yeah that's self-esteem
which is very very difficult to have
[Music]
oh my god i'm getting there i'm getting
there
oh buddy
[Music]
but if you
if you think for example you have a big
nose look at my nose i have no nose okay
so appreciate your nose
think about all the people who don't
have a nose all those anime girls out
there oops what am i doing
all those animal girls out there
who don't have a nose
all right
they have to live without being able to
breathe for the nose we pray for our
mouth because we don't even have
nostrils
you know how how tough it is to have to
breathe for your mouth some of us
animate girls we even have to teach
ourselves how to breathe for our ears
yeah
i've been trying to teach myself that
too too breathing for my ears especially
when i sleep
because having my mouth open all the
time i can't rely on that
i know the feeling oh really you don't
have nostrils eva yay
ear breathing
it's a technique that only the anime
girls really try to learn
[Music]
real pros ready for their eyes yo that
is next level [\h__\h]
[Music]
yo teach me teach me how do you do it
also what does that thing look like
uh
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] why is it doing this
why you do this
all right it's open there okay
good night quinoa
good night
is this a power that can be learned
uh
you will have to
young padawan
life does not give you
a choice sometimes
you have to adapt but i'm sure there's
animals who
don't have nostrils right and they have
to breathe i guess sometimes through
their uh what's it called
in english you know fish for example
fish
so it's it's not that special if you
think about it humans adapt when they
need to as a mom
girls yes skills
[Music]
i wonder if glitter breathes for her
nose gotta ask her i mean she says that
she's an anime girl too she doesn't have
a nose either so she probably braves for
her girls
i'll have her show me
those guilts
sometimes
maybe i can get
something similar to that that would be
helpful
maybe all anime girls should have kills
i don't know what the [\h__\h] i'm talking
about
someone stop me
a tangent please
tangent
please save me from myself give me
[Music]
have you had lasagna recently yeah i had
that soupy lasagna i'm like what when is
it sunday
soupy lasagna i love all the lasagnas
regardless of what they look like
[Music]
ah the movie bound yeah some people said
we should do a watch along but yo the
movie is currently being aired in
cinemas right so like i don't know when
the hell it's gonna be out on um
on a dvd or something something
watchable but yo i would love to watch
it looks gorgeous
who watched belle the movie
that anime movie who watched it
i don't even know if they
play it in our features probably not
anymore
it was good
never heard of it i wanted to but the
only favorite in my city showing it was
before
it was good super pretty
i didn't watch it still waiting for it i
i like summer ones better summerwise was
amazing
b-e-l-e-e
[Music]
this part is kind of difficult
i think i'm gonna
sell shade
the [\h__\h] out of this
um
[Music]
foreign 13 years since it came out
summer wars holy [\h__\h] that's a long time
14 years
don't make me feel old
don't
[Music]
you know what it's february that means
that means
one of my favorite shows is getting this
new season
mrs marvel the marvelous mrs marvel
marvel
basil
i got confused mrs barfox
yeah i guess that's me
kind of wanting to watch marvel movies
haha
when are we gonna watch some marvel
movies what's everybody's favorite
marvel movie
um
what's the superhero
she is perhaps maybe she is for me she
is for providing me such great
entertainment she is a superhero to me
civil war iron man
iron man a lot of iron mans
captain america
guardians of the galaxy that's one of
the few ones that i've seen
[Music]
and
i have had barely any information about
who's who but it was still fun it was so
entertaining
phoenix woman what
oh and another one that i watched was uh
that one about that
lady
uh one
super woman not superwoman uh
help me out guys
[Music]
help me out
what was her name again
wonder woman yeah i think it was wonder
woman
wonder woman wonder woman
i've seen that one too
but besides
those two movies i don't think i've
watched much maybe the first spider-man
movie but that's
about it
sorry guys very disappointing i know you
all love marvel i know i know i know i
know i know the boys they love marvel
movies
dancing dining
i don't know anything about it i haven't
even seen bully maguire what is that
fubuki also loves them
[Music]
i think i've heard of that
her love for it
i wouldn't mind getting a little bit
into it though
at least they are visually very pleasing
with a lot of special effects and [\h__\h]
[Music]
how much detail do i want
how much detail
what's along with you on the first
ironman uh
i don't really usually like doing watch
lungs as a collab i feel like we could
use that time doing much more fun things
in general
so
i will i
appreciate your idea but generally i
would want to do something more
more exciting you know
[Music]
yeah of course she has already watched
it
probably
monthly can't switch
i wonder if you would like cats i think
she would like it i think kooky would
love cats she would enjoy it she she's
of course also a cat just kidding just
kidding food
just kidding don't kill me don't kill me
you're not a cat i know that i know that
i know that senpai i know that
no that's a wolf that's a wolf
what does the fox say
that i don't think i've ever heard from
bookies
never heard her say that that song is
lying
they can't they come up with so many
noises and none of them is what fubukki
makes
ridiculous it's just ridiculous we
should watch the lonely island
music videos guys
we should watch them all of them
[Music]
eight more things
uh mums mums what thing what do you mean
what do you mean what do you mean you
have a thing you mean in eight months
you have a thing
the fox says
[Music]
oh man
it's to be it to be a kinda
[Music]
the endurance that that fox has man
incredible
i respect it
does that look like goldman i don't know
[Music]
i mean on my head it's also pretty dark
in those spots
i
i need to
make it more sparkly here and there
[Music]
sparkle
shiny shiny
if i can't have a shiny pokemon i will
have a shiny crown
[Music]
yeah more like bronze yeah
it's probably just plastic though
nah an empress
can afford some gold can she
oopsie
i'll work with that
there are no
mistakes only happy accidents right
yep
oh i really want to try those acrylic
videos man i'm i'm always getting these
recommendations on like acrylic
not necessarily pouring
this pouring is a [\h__\h] mess
but just acrylic
videos man
let's do it
oh it's really heavy
of course i know i know i know i know i
know i'm wearing gold right now
oh it's so heavy my head hurts kevin you
should be holding my crown or my head
actually if you could hold my head that
would help my shoulder pain so
much chimpkins
i need your support
how's it looking how is it looking
how's it looking
let me look on my other screen
huh
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's looking like
that material
it's starting to look like it or it
doesn't no no no no no no no no it
doesn't look like it
it's shiny it's looking shiny oh welcome
it's okay it's okay
i started very early today for my sca
bros because otherwise
it's always a shitty time for them but i
want them to
have some good streams
as well good times as well
but maybe they're falling asleep by now
japan rose korea bros
everywhere in the world bros i still
like
okinawa
kanji
um sleep is about a week
it was so badass saying that so badass
man
[Music]
mm-hmm
night shift
well tomorrow at least for you guys it
starts a bit late again
but i have something before the
minecraft stream
[Music]
so i
i have some stuff to do
it's looking pretty messy from but from
further away
i'm hoping it will look good
yeah
yeah i mean it could be a bit brighter
but it's okay
i think i'm satisfied i just need to do
the veil oh
we're finishing it
i think i'll leave it i leave the
headpiece like that i love your
headpiece thank you i love it too
hmm yeah
looks so cool
it's like
a lot of different
pieces
of wings and feathers
maybe it's the feathers of the other
phoenix's that i killed
can that crown wear as a face mask like
especially on your clothes
no because i have a face mask separately
that i never wear um for some reason
i can turn and put it on
[Music]
and that is literally the face that i
ripped off of another phoenix
no
we never do something like that
oh yeah this is my nose my nose my bird
nose
hey who's this mysterious woman
you can't recognize me anymore it's me
takanashi kimawa
it's me
look at my eyes look deep into my eyes
and you will realize
it's
wawa
mysterious beauty
you don't look like her [\h__\h] it's me
oh wait i forgot the ribbon i forgot to
uh do the ribbon
back to work kfb
back to work focus
i'm not sure
i'm just gonna do a layer underneath
that and then
oh snap hyper chat
dead refresh and it's back um happy chat
you're so
such a good good chicken
so obedient
what color should the ribbon lean
um not need only heel it's just a random
ribbon that i added there because i
wanted to put something in my hand
red
whole
okay
[Music]
akka
a different color of red and
the dress i suppose would be good
[Music]
i'm fine with that and harmonizes with
the rest of the picture could also have
been a blue ribbon though
could have been a blue ribbon
cooked very wrong
no no no
we're going with this it's fine it
doesn't matter okay now thank you for
the membership annyong
comes
[Music]
you
oh
[Music]
yeah
you that's it
i'm beautiful beautiful
and last but not least
the sheer one is actually super easy
because it will look good just by being
a little bit of sheer fabric on top of
it it doesn't even need much shading
this part this part this part this part
this part this part this part
and this part
yes
i'm gonna layer that
i'm gonna use a white color
seven months thank you
members only stream on friday by the way
it's friday friday getting dinner friday
[Music]
what a banger
oh this part too
[Music]
friday no sorry alright it's not friday
already sorry for shocking you
i live a little bit in the future
sometimes
i like to visit
imma
hang out with amma in the future
sometimes
she takes me on future traveling dates
in my in my fantasies
in my
i'm i'm a
gosling fantasies
i love bubba i'm a teammate i'm a
[\h__\h] teammate and i'm proud of it
[Music]
oh
she's just so cute man what can i do
when she's so cute it's probably how you
guys feel about me
i hear her singing off-key and it's just
to me
this is the most beautiful sound i've
ever heard it's like she's like a song
bird
looks like she's singing opera next
level [\h__\h]
[Music]
it's the cutest thing ever
it makes my heart go donkey dokie
sometimes she changes the lyrics and she
sings
i miss you
and i'm like
i stopped functioning
she's so cute
so cute still now we see if we can find
a layer effect that works
this doesn't work
maybe we should lower the opacity yeah
yeah yeah yeah lighten white and color
like too
yeah okay and then i'm gonna add some
white detail because it has some white
data or actually we could change
the color of that outline to something
more
bright
yeah
i usually always just leave all the
outlines
in my art in one color
[Music]
because i can't be bothered with it oh
but this time
for the effect
for the immersion
did i miss something
no
are you guys ready
so there's on the bottom layer of that
fabric there's a little bit of a
of a layer of uh i don't know something
some seam
[Music]
like that
uh
huh in the curve
[Music]
what
oh
[Music]
thank you freddie
thank you
uh
sweet
[Music]
um you know what they don't really have
it on the top layer but i'm gonna add it
anyway like something
[Music]
is there anything i missed
i'm looking respectfully but i don't see
anything that i missed
it's finished
this
no background [\h__\h] backgrounds i hate
backgrounds
and shading on the ah
oh it's because it's kind of transparent
is this the part you mean that's okay i
can fix that quickly
thank you thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
thank you
thank you chad i finished it
oh wait there's here too
you'll be
we are finished though i will say that
thank you simply divine
would you say it's exquisite
i think i think it is
[Music]
oh what the [\h__\h]
what's going on in such a mess
yo why is it taking the color from the
other
layer
what's
why is it turning blue
[Music]
that's okay
is there anything else that i missed
that looks weird
okay
i think the rest looks fine to me
you see something else
i don't see anything else i think
did i miss anything
wait i see something again around the
feathers actually i see a little bit of
the balloon oh no is that my imagination
no i just say it i don't say it
it's because the skin layer was like say
a little bit transparent
yeah now this is this is this is where
it gets me it pays me back
[\h__\h]
okay
uh wait i know how to fix it an easier
way
here we go there we go that's clean
here
doesn't really bother me
[Music]
and that's fine
okay i'll go good that's all i see
like a soft shadow yeah yeah awesome
working on thank you love the details
insane thank you
i think i'll throw this into photoshop a
little bit wait a second
um wait can i save it as a
png wait a second
i will sit oh my arm is transparent
young buddy
[Music]
you see that
i think it's only
the skin color
yeah
look
oh
oh [\h__\h]
there's a little bit here too
ah it's no problem because i'll i'll
save it as a jpeg and then it saves a
white layer of white underneath
duplicate the skin layer oh
it's definitely better than before
not 100 i'll do it one more time
oh that does help that does help
let me duplicate
this part too
oh oh it's much darker now
but i don't see the transparent check
checkered padding pattern anymore
alright alright alright
save as
png
uh
and press q
yeah
okay let's go to my office we'll be
reading super chats uh but before that
i'll finish it up on photoshop
but not not here
or i might actually do it afterwards
i'll do it afterwards
i'll fix some things up in photoshop and
then i'll upload it
on twitter thank you for
watching this art stream it was very
comfy up until now now i have to catch
up a little bit on super chat a little
bit
quite a bit
let's move
thank you thank you oh my oh my oh
[Music]
thank you chimpkin for always welcoming
me
in my own office every time we switch on
over here it's like as if you
caught us in
what you called flagranto
as if i was just making out with one of
my employees
[Music]
anymore flagrante
i think that's uh
italian
is it
i should make myself a bit smaller
oh
and press kiwa with mask in this office
it has been a while
i'm kind of tired man why am i tired
am i tired let me take a fruit
candy
cola
oh it's french oh excuse me
oh i guess they have it in both
languages i think um
similar similar word
power level tier
of the fan base
chickens in the bottom only feeding
shrimps
but they don't know
that all of you can
uh revive once
so it's better of them to underestimate
you in battle
because if we go to war with for example
the taco duchies
and we send out an army of 3 000
chickens
they will think oh only 3 000 chimpkins
we only have to um
counter that with maybe 3 000 takodachis
but they will not know that we basically
count double
because
y'all die and then i'll give you phoenix
down
and we'll be six thousand will count
double
they don't know and it's better that
they don't know it's war stretch threat
strategy
tactics you know
leave it to your empress
i shall lead us to the wind
big strats reinforcements we are our own
reinforcements
you die and you you let them think you
died we let them wait a little bit we
don't revive immediately we wait a
little bit
we wait when they think they're done
that's when we rise from the ashes
ha ha
yeah
thank you i'm glad you like it
thank you it was a comfy
uh stream i guess
thank you thank you for the pinky thank
you you guys are so sweet thank you
thank you
[Music]
what if there is also a takodachi in
longus
we will have to decapitate them
it's as simple as that and they don't
really have a lower body so
yes they're already decapitated
[Laughter]
yeah
so we'll have to do something else with
them leaves the room what manga rocket
you stay here
sweats profusely
uh-huh i see i see the nervous faces
here i see some nervous chimpkins
shaking shaking shaking and their their
feathers falling off and underneath
there's some purple skin shelling
i see what's going on
i don't remember you
on on your way out you might um
want to say hello
to my guides
whether you want it or not
the treasures have been revealed
kill them
just kidding just kidding
love and peace put down sound beautiful
and here
beautiful and
[Laughter]
looks like we're having taco yagi
tonight
you can have it all i don't eat taco um
but
yeah let's have a taco yucky party
shall we
i don't know why we keep on picking a
fight with
with the taco that juice man even though
we love each other don't we we love we
love inna
and taco duchess and and kfb are on good
terms in general
it's just
chickens like to pick you know they
like to pick and also they like to pick
fights
[Music]
oh don't worry ruby will be kind to you
taco dodges
[Laughter]
that fruit candy i kind of breathed in
something weird
yosh
i have to read super chats from
the previous stream and this stream
as far as i know
should i read them normally today or
should i
it's already been a long stream
[Music]
i'll i'll try to write them normally if
i feel like it's too exhausting i'll
switch it up
[Music]
yeah
okay i'm scrolling i'm scrolling i'm
scrolling i'm scrolling
i'm scrolling
[Music]
one
why
[Music]
okay i found it
found it found the start
and soda
coco
huh
[Music]
cute i've i've been shown um
i've been shown
the progress of the models that i
designed
for the
music video it's happening so soon
i've been planning on uploading it one
day before before valentine's day so
that's like 11 days left
approximately
that's not even 2 weeks
it's nothing special though it's really
simple
it's really simple
nothing nothing too intricate
oh my god
censor it kfp
[Music]
can't wait for the stream since i had to
miss all streams since the member one
due to moving into my first own place oh
[Music]
congratulations on moving your first own
place that's so exciting i still
remember when i had my first own place
actually
my first own place i think was
in japan so that's that was more
stressful but my first own place in
austria was
um very exciting even though it was like
old and run down and
but yeah it's very exciting to be able
to decide yourself which like completely
what what furniture to put in
and
uh when to be naked
stuff like that uh
yeah and spend as much time as you want
in the bathroom
doing your makeup or whatever i don't
know
yeah
so i wish you good luck and have fun and
hopefully you'll get some proper
internet going soon thank you soon
peter chandang fire the elements thank
you for the red super chat happy lunar
new year thank you dear tencho it's
almost 3 am here so i'll catch the vault
later hope you have fun playing this
game
thank you i don't know if you're here
now but
happy lunar new year to you too
[Music]
how did you celebrate it huh i hope you
had a great
a
great previous year and hopefully a
successful coming year as well um thank
you for all your support and your love
thank you
mwah wrestle
happy chinese new year potential it's
red envelope job
it's a year of sugary cornflakes
frosties tony the tiger
ah cause he's a tiger
smelly ointments tiger balm never tried
that i think shops of shops full of
cheap everyday rubbish flying tiger we
have that in austria too yeah that's a
great shop i love it and [\h__\h] parents
tiger mom
interesting
interesting so these are the things that
will bring us luck maybe this year
frosty's tiger ball flying tiger
copenhagen sponsorship incoming
and tiger moms
yeah blind tiger is a fun shop
i love shops like that that sell like
everything but it's all like kind of
fitting because it's from the same
company i guess
duncan rice oh free
[Music]
well maybe you will start every day and
this year with frosties sugary conflict
corn flakes don't be scared to
mix it up maybe put in some sliced
bananas i i used to love eating corn
flakes like that putting sliced bananas
in in to the milk mix
because corn flakes just in itself is
kind of boring
very good
yes
thinking that that way maybe i could get
a little bit more vitamins
bananas and cereal yes yes fresh bananas
i don't really like those
cereals with the with the
dry bananas in it
i don't like it that much sometimes i
can eat it i don't mind it sometimes but
fresh bananas better
better putting apple slices here that's
yummy too
and not a good username don quixote
m thank you for the red super chat
unfortunately your message got deleted i
don't know why i'm sorry if uh that was
by accident or so maybe you deleted it
yourself i don't know
thank you no i wish you
i wish you happy lunar new year maybe
you're celebrating it i don't know
thank you for your support
yeah yeah guys if it was a yeah bye
super chat then i hope you feel bunked
book
book champions have to learn
jason
for the rest of my channel envelope you
guys are too generous thank you tai
chi mwah
eh what was it
sh
it was very similar to japanese in the
first part xin and kuaila
what's it what's that
[Music]
koila happy new year
am i saying it right
probably mispronouncing it was correct
[Music]
the first part is easy to remember
because in japanese it sounds the same
you're great artist thank you
optimus prime dominique duncan hope
young
thank you for the pinky this game is
great but take this warning serious chad
just about every dangerous
self-destructive behavior is represented
in this game be safe and have fun
everyone
yes
um
i uh
i hope no one here in the chat uh
has to
do
stuff like that i hope you guys are fine
without those kind of things those
those um methods of coping
if you
feel alone or if you feel like you're in
pain
then please try to talk to some friends
or family
or therapy yes that's fine too
i don't if you if you can if you want to
promise me one thing
if you want to do one thing to make me
happy then please
do not
take any
d's
and um
don't
don't hurt yourself
please
these nuts
[Laughter]
i'm serious though i'm serious okay i
mean yeah you know what i mean
optimus prime
thank you for the red super chat mwah
happy lunar new year 10 2. it's 3am here
i hope your myth girls can meet in japan
as soon as possible yo i hope so too
i've met cali before but i haven't met
the others i really really really really
really want to meet the others
yeah but shin nang kuai la
blue jian thank you so much for your
support thank you
song time i really really really really
really wanna meet smith
in in japan or somewhere else i don't
really care i really really really
really really really want to meet with
they must be so cute i want to hug them
and hold their hands
same
um
putting down dankeshan simple polish
name
there are no such simple polish names
duncan for the
red super chat wait choose two common
super chats i sure hope she chooses this
one you have been chosen thankfully i
choose all of the all of the super chats
i always do i choose them all
thank you for the red super chat and
your support i hope you enjoyed the
stream
and got some happiness out of it
for the red super chat happy new year
attention here's my red envelope
happy new year
thank you so much thank you thank you
thank you
andre ponce duncan
get out of here we have our angel
tangent angel
ah that's a smart one it could also
stand for takanasi angel as well
takanashi the tangent angel
wonderful you are a big brain sir
if i had a hat i would take it off
i mean i have this thing but i don't
want to take it off
and i said myth
takanasi tangent angel
um
thank you mr paul for the uh pinky boom
what what went boom
is it your heart that goes boom boom
boom boom boom all the time when you see
me
understandable thank you for the
painting
papa thank you for the red super chat
happy new year attention hope you are
healthy and happy red envelope
happy hair of the tiger
you brought the eggs
i'm sure 87 thank you for the red super
chat money successfully squeezed
did you want to give it to kangel it
accidentally has
been sent to me i'm sorry i'm sure i'll
i'll take it though thank you very much
angel loves you and angel loves you too
thank you
i struggle so hard to get up in the
mornings
same like oh my god
i struggled so hard that i have just
completely given up on it
yeah
it's okay though [\h__\h] mornings they're
not meant to be
awake for
um
first time here really oh really
maybe it's your first time at angel's
stream but then you sent the super chat
to the wrong person
thank you
for the support dragons fire very
generous of you thank you so much mwah
and reports thank you also for renting
the chat don't cry
oh
can you or me
did kangel cry
kingel was very very stressed out all
the time man but she
she decided to put that
stress onto herself
by choosing to try like force herself to
become like a huge
huge streamer in one month one million
impossible man
yeah i know a lot of these are just uh
copied from the game i know i'm still
trying to
interact with them
andre thank you
[Music]
happy lunar new year here's my red
envelope yes my omo cat merch is finally
coming oh you ordered omo cat merch too
thank you
i'm glad it's on its way now
you better
be wearing it all day every day once it
arrives okay
i hope it arrives safely at you please
chin and quiet
for all your support skye
that's okay that's okay i know that was
a super chat in the game it's okay
that's all right
thank you for your support
yeah
and response tag don't don't sleep in
your super chat come on wake up wake up
okay it's for you though andrew ponce a
pinky telling me kiara your sticks
wait was that did someone tell archangel
about their sticks well i'm confused i
was very confused about this one what's
which sticks i still don't understand it
i still don't get it what sticks
what sticks what sticks did kangel have
one what sticks
[Music]
what does that mean
a tumblr meme
an old tumblr meme what the [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh
andrew ponce duncan for the rest of the
chat you're super cute oh
stop
i know
thank you mwah
so sweet thank you so much for all the
super chats holy [\h__\h]
you had quite some fun huh
i don't blame you skye thank you also
for red super chat also telling me i'm
super cute oh my god it's like everyone
has one brain cell and they're all
thinking i am super cute
thank you
[Music]
87 thank you for the pinky
yo we're the nerds aren't we you know
you guys are not nerds no no no don't
don't let what kenzo has been saying get
into your head
don't let it in
kangel is evil she's evil
speak for yourself
well if you proudly proclaim yourself as
a nerd i have no problem with that and
you do you
not that there's anything wrong with
that that now sounds so familiar for me
because i just recently saw him say that
jerry seinfeld
i love this game
it honestly like it was way more comfy
watching someone else like inna play it
than playing it myself so um maybe maybe
you felt the same way
it was just like i tackled it in a very
stressful way kane just stressed me the
[\h__\h] out man she's such a crazy [\h__\h]
stupid stupid [\h__\h]
will you be playing internet over this
what you mean needy girl overdose
already played there that's what we're
reading right now
super
chat
wouldn't play about blockchain 10 out of
she needs professional help
but she was getting it in the hospital
or lord knows what else she was getting
there
[Music]
uh
pink super chat high attention i'm doing
a challenge where each month i cook my
favorite vegetables top three dishes
last month with inna now i choose you
you have chosen correctly and you will
be blessed hashtag blessed please tell
us your choices wait my favorite ones
not necessarily austrian dishes huh
pictures will be up on twitter and the
taco eats on kfb hashtags also first
thank you too thank you all right
uh number one i guess it has to be
lasagna
um number two in order to get you to
cook something special as well i want
you to do a schnitzel
schnitzel
austrian vienna schnitzel
[Music]
and number three
ramen is [\h__\h] difficult to really
properly make yourself
[Music]
pineapple pizza what if he doesn't like
pineapple yummy
no i will say
oh there's so much choice
makeup oh make
one of the burgers that are on the kfp
menu even the phoenix burger or the
jaguar burger
now this is not really my favorite food
but i do love burgers so
now that i think of it you should make
one of those burgers
i think there's a
on the on the kfb website right there is
the ingredients right like uh you can
like change it up a little bit if you
want
add some creative freedom
we still have to do that too as a
challenge i want to do a cooking stream
on it and a review stream on how you
make those burgers we're still doing
that one day
[Music]
yes i did see the tales of a rice recipe
book yeah yeah yeah i think i have it i
have it i'm pretty sure i have it
okay
you predicted exactly what i was gonna
give to you thank you senator thank you
for the pinky and love and money
yes kangel
priorities
for her money goes first still i think
or fame
i think for her
it's
fame
love and money number one is fame number
two is love number three is money
hmm at least love is number two fox 70
for the pinky
i'm ironic woke yo love you forever i
know you're unironically doing that and
that's i i respect that perfect
no problem with that all of you guys
should be unironically woke yolk
speak five minutes germany please okay
five minutes is pretty long
i'll give you one minute
okay
um
[Music]
foreign
so good
seems i don't understand english anymore
okay now i'm back to english now
now we're back to english
i love corn
[Music]
you know there's a cute phrase in
japanese in england in germany
which is like a kiss
a kissy on on your uh on your head
but
if i directly translate it it sounds
funny um a christian of nusian it rhymes
but it actually translates directly to
a kissy
on the nut
but like a cute version of a nut
but it's used as a kiss on your head
as far as i know
[Laughter]
it's supposed to mean a kiss on the head
yeah that's what i think you don't need
my shoulder but that's too clingy
[Laughter]
both words the kiss and the nuts are
being like cutified in the german
language by saying
ken at the end like you could say
[Music]
you could say for example
ah a good example is
brought which is bread
we like to say bertien to a smaller
bread britian
becomes britian
yeah
chicken
[Music]
bread
uh it's not as cringe but yes i guess
oh no no no not everything with not
everything with c-h-e-n
at the end is cutified not everything
like kuchen
is just cake
and it doesn't work with every word it
doesn't work with kiara if you can
curify kiara by saying kiara la in
chiang rai or
is also
something you add at the end of some
words to make it cuter
chiara
chiara line it sounds weird though but
if anything it would be that it wouldn't
be kiara he and it would be kiara line
line
[Music]
l-e-i-n yeah but it sounds
unnatural
yeah we're already starting the german
lesson now
i'm not 100 sure yet what to teach you
guys by the way in the next members only
german lesson but i'll figure something
out
i'll decide spontaneously maybe business
german or we just kind of try to still
keep it simple like the last one
but uh
kind of add on to it
[Music]
87 thank you for the pinky
getting empty art by the game's chat
lads
but then how shocked must you have been
when
we got ntr'ed by some other streamer
when she ran off with another streamer
but don't worry we're better off without
her
[Music]
definitely especially if you look at all
the other endings i think it's a proof
that we're better off without kenjo
[Music]
floor is lava dangerous
let's go
thank you
i love cats too
[Music]
that was a quality super chat boohoo
maple leaf two five zero one down
question for the red super chat cats are
all right
[Music]
they are
maybe maybe you didn't mean they're all
right especially when i look at how you
wrote it
the way you
wrote it it grammatically
leads me to think that you meant that
they are all correct
because it was not
one word all right but it was a l l
space and then right
so you probably are saying that cats are
all correct they are never wrong and
that is true
yes they
always all correct whenever they say
meow they are right and we must
do anything they say make believe you
are
all right as well
[Music]
[Laughter]
i wish i could stay until the end but i
have to stop for today i wonder what it
was like for you to be a manager for the
first time will you treat genma a little
better after that
anyways thanks for the stream love
forever and bless thank you you're
implying that i'm not streaming in
general well
i'm treating her well she's treating me
well
we are a dream team
[Music]
it's very very different from what
kangel and her manager had in the game
very
very very different it's a whole nother
world
for gemma has the deal of dmca but no
she doesn't have to because i never got
the mc8
i'm invincible i'm immune to that [\h__\h]
glad to hear it yeah
yeah i'm also glad that uh genna is a
wonderful manager
[Music]
famous last words no no no no no no
a community strike
well yeah well my channel got boxed for
nothing
got shadow bunked and uh one time
completely deleted but i didn't do
anything
i didn't do [\h__\h]
yakuza's last stream um
if anything happened then it wasn't my
fault and it's fine
[Music]
i'm tanky yeah
i'm done
[Music]
another good username 360 donation
nightingale donation stable breadcrust
and maple leaf 2501
for the red super chat
all this game proof since we need a
kiana streaming simulator as long as it
isn't your b
pet kitties with stress relief that
would be very effective
she had a streaming simulator
could work or like a whole live
streaming simulator
it wouldn't be as insane as
this needy girl overdose game but
it could be more the wholesome side like
you know idol master
[Music]
cat breaks yeah
cat breaks out like going to the
hospital for me
[Music]
oh yeah yeah one one
would be streaming a game without
permission
or singing a song
that should be unique in an archive
stream
stuff like that
change of pace
um
here
i think
what no
where did i
save the others
i want the
other ones
that's not the one i was looking for but
it's the og it's
i beautiful
know why did i save the other ones
oh well you know what you know what how
how does this one work as a super chat
music
[Music]
oh it actually works nice it feels like
an ending
yeah
oh guys let's go
oh it's hype
wait
[Music]
my kisses are never shameless
maybe they are i don't know is that a
bad thing
i will give you a shameless case
i like that
how you like that
[Music]
did i wake you up with the music sorry
i'll call down question for the pinky
that was a super fun stream the game
turned out to be pretty deep i hope you
didn't get any funny ideas from it
conspiracy theory streams could be fun
though jk your streams you use your
streams your topics also get well soon
thank you but i think i
probably wouldn't be allowed to do
conspiracy theory streams anyway
realistically speaking
those are i think
yeah bye
would be cool but
i mean if if mumei can't do history
streams then i highly doubt i can do
conspiracy things
[Music]
i could do whole life conspiracies yeah
like my inna waking up stream
like the conspiracies i made up there
that's just people will think i am on
not case
is that the word people will think that
i'm literally going crazy
if i do that
just normally
people will think i'm crazy
and maybe some girls might not be very
happy with the
um
conspiracies i come up with
i don't know i don't know man i don't
want to talk about some conspiracies but
maybe in another life
and we're done with the uh little girl
super chats
we are reading today's super jets now
[Music]
mr kashmir sanctions
no
no need for that thank you
i have a manager that i'm very happy
with
no thank you pete john
i i love
genma
nine
nine dunk it
nine dog we want to be polite
where the where are the emojis the
member emojis at the jacket
[Music]
nine donkey shoe nine dunk it no no
thank you
excuse me connor
you
you know
she doesn't need to be freed
[Music]
spreading rumors here
harborland danish and the certified
dangerous and petrogen danger thank you
thank you for the rental chad wow three
days off
what who took three days off and i'm
taking three days off you were taking
three days off tai chi
roomie are you thinking is that why you
sent a super chat
hi t you need to speak full sentences
with me otherwise i will not understand
thank you though here's the kiss for you
all for that for the
new years ah maybe
[Music]
thank you i don't i have no idea how to
pronounce
the rest of the sentence but i suppose
it means happy new year
thank you
and the red envelope for our genma as
well thank you
very kind of you
to think of gemma as well so i want a
little crispy fry fry party for god's
sake
thank you
[Music]
papa
let's say a bird god descends from the
heavens and turns all kfp employees into
seagulls
we carefully be able to survive as a
restaurant considering most people won't
want to eat or be served seagulls how
could you use seagull employees
you know how
the vegans and the vegetarians out there
have made tofu taste like literally
anything
i think we can do the same with seagulls
especially because they probably already
have you know that that bird meat
texture so
i don't think people will really doubt
it
i will just uh you know add our spices
and herbs and all that
the vegans
you know
this is not a conspiracy theory
the vegans and the vegetarians
they make tofu tastes like meat
it's unbelievable
they want to make you think that it's
meat but it's actually tofu
there's no meat in that at all
unbelievable
[Music]
i think i think i'm on to something
follow us blah
[Music]
can we trust this information well the
source is me so yes
[Music]
thank you
for the pinky
oh
it's been a pretty lonely and tough week
thanks to you it's a healing day
oh fighting cheer up please don't feel
don't feel too sad or devastated
it will get better things will go
upwards again trust me
but thank you for spending your time
with me
even when you're feeling bad thank you
so much
come sign me down fighting
hello guinta thank you for the rinse
pink super chat hey attention i recently
received your birthday merch and i love
it yeah
don't know how i live without those both
low food flippers they're really moving
for aren't they also i would need my
employee number for my employee card if
i might give any suggestions i would
like the number ct7567
yes of course it's already your number
why you what do you mean
you could give suggestions you you're
not the one choosing
you have been
you have been uh given a number the
moment you joined kfp so this has always
been your number i don't know what it
means but it is your number indeed yes
just got mine yesterday thank you
mine came today oh my god pepe lonnie
the peppaloni sorry forgot
no problem chickens forget something
sometimes it's completely
understandable
thank you for your support i'm glad you
like those slippers are your do your
feet actually fit inside
i hope they do
slippers are so warm yeah perfect for
winter time aren't they kinda okay
that's better than not at all
this lip is not too small for my feet
potential well um have you ever watched
cinderella
[Music]
just saying
inspiration can be taken from cinderella
[Music]
it doesn't need to fit my foot it needs
to fit your foot
stupid chicken
account name thank you for the rent
super chat i love you archangel i can't
wait for the next conspiracy free stream
i heard a scary conspiracy about a
secret society called kfb that secretly
took over your channel spooky stuff
please
well
it's not only me though the tentacles as
well and the deadbeats as well and the
mummy
fans as well
there's a lot of people taking over
kange's channel
so many people taking over kanger's
channel is it really kangel's channel
anymore at that point hmm think think
fake account name think
the mermaid fans are the humans
i forgot
[Music]
she's so funny
she
[Music]
well can't be so much easier to remember
cause we made it into a whole franchise
[Music]
tradition to send red envelope
apparently yeah
happy luna i know you're intentional or
do you even celebrate it well thank you
for seeing it as an opportunity to
support me and i appreciate it thank you
so much
[Music]
happy birthday to your friend emily
derek seattle thank you michael lanka
thank you for the painting happy luna
new year and now i sleep with the stream
open oh are you sleeping now are you
sleeping
oh
i wanted it to be loud
but it ended up being um
i'll wait now
[Laughter]
[Music]
damn awake indeed thank you for blessing
my eardrums you're welcome you knew i
was gonna do that you know me too well i
hope you turned down the volume before i
did it
[Music]
okay
cruel loud unforgivable 100 out of 10
perfection ah
i'm sorry to the headphone people
for the rest of the chance to the
wonderful lovely amazing divine being
finger
to the bloody
hell amazing mate gd
what is that profile picture you're
rocking
what is that
oh
i see i say it's me holding that yo judy
you have clips on your channel
i didn't know
gd you like me don't you
drowning compilation aren't you funny
judy
aren't you funny
no that was a genius though
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for the
thank you for the pinky when i see my
oshi i start singing let's put that into
papago i think it's something like
cookie cookie cookie oh
[Music]
it is
i hate the translation something
something's awful to translation
sometimes
coco home
coco coco
[Laughter]
coco
oh my god
home coco coco deck coco
cup cuckoo chubbu crouch crush crash
coco
home coco coco deck coco
cup cuckoo chubbu crouch crush crush
home cocoa
uh i went to an idol meeting
i told you
i told them
some things i just meant to be read out
by someone else
that was funny
weak bladder excuse me i just drank a
lot of water today
hmm
and sometimes jaggle just urgently needs
to talk to me
[Laughter]
coco
oh my god it's killing me
it's the english the english translation
reading out loud is much more funny than
the korean one the korean one was just
cute she even had some rhythm
[Laughter]
so funny oh my god i can't i can't i
can't i can't
papa go thank you for that blessing
pong pong are you here pong
oppa
are you here
the one who sent this super chat
you realize what you have done
you've created a clip i'm pretty sure of
it
are you here
he's probably already sleeping
well that means you're going to the
usual room
oh my god
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man
google translate
or should i read that in
no i can't read that in japanese
kishinami
i thought you were leaving me again
happy lunar new year kiana and employees
i'm still working now but i'm happy to
be able to hear the stream by just audio
today i hope i can see piano drawing
chickens too someday
thank you for
saying hello today thank you for coming
by dan kishan
very sweet happy new year to you too
thank you for the red super chat thank
you and today is the second day of lunar
new year so here is a red packet for you
wish the good luck to be with you and
have a genki coming here dan
i wish you the same good luck to you as
well happy new year
and all the best wishes to you thank you
for your support
[Music]
i did draw a harbour line
get him
drag him into the void
chicken rice thank you soon
[Music]
thank you hey i woke up feeling crispy
today which means oh it's been a year oh
did it happen while you were asleep huh
so let me thank you for all the laughs
and good times till now the only regret
i have is to not have found you out
sooner looking forward to seeing you on
stage in march
thank you
one year thank you so much for
being here or being a member for one
year anderson magic that is so so so
supportive of you hashtag
hopefully you'll stay with me much much
longer
hope you like your new second skin it
will make you stronger
hell yeah
now when people try to stab you or or
try to eat you
it won't hurt that much anymore at least
at least uh at first
optimus prime
they ate madness
did i give any success
[Music]
again
yes yes yes freddie debut
uh
i mean there will be a separate pretty w
stream
um sooner or later afterwards but uh
in some way i guess the concert in some
way is a debut as well
please look forward to it
i am very excited to have all of you
see it
yeah
it's like oh like a teaser i feel like
you should see it just as a teaser um
an appetizer exactly
words can't begin to describe how
excited we are you're so sweet thank you
it's getting closer and closer and
closer
well people who are not watching the
concert you may wait for the pretty
debut
or i don't know which comes first my 4d
music video but i think i will that
would be after the 3d debut
um
or i think
previous concerts
uh at previous concerts screenshots were
allowed
so you're probably gonna see it in
screenshots
it might not be moving but
it's at least something
if you don't want to watch it no one's
forcing you that's okay
and i'm sorry if some people aren't
happy with it i cannot help you with
that unfortunately but
um as i said i
i think it's better than not being in
the concert at all so yeah
but if you change your mind tickets are
available and
uh as far as i know there's also gonna
be an archive so you can even watch it
afterwards as well if you change your
mind
the omo cat drip reveal
yeah i'm not sure like if i should still
wait longer but i already talked to
kelly about it um
maybe
end of the
middle or end of february
because uh now i will be gone
for my skiing trip so
yeah
but don't worry we didn't forget about
it
[Music]
thank you
you're gonna carry my stuff with your
wings that looks so cute if i imagine
it oh
duplicates oh sheesh
i hope that gets uh sorted out
um since it's like oh man
[Music]
i did not know about that i'm sorry that
that happened
[Music]
i will make
i'm making a note of it
special
notes being taken
i think they're probably asking people
to return it yeah
which is
understandably very very um bothersome
i'm sorry that some of you guys have to
do that
what thousand thousand what thousand yen
1000 yen
to send it back to japan
to cover the shipping to set
1000 yen no matter where you are from
america i have a feeling that it's gonna
cost more than a thousand
yen huh
uh
i will be asking
management what what
what what
[Music]
and what if you don't return it does the
other people
are they not gonna get it
[Music]
hmm
all right we are uh
we're gonna look into it thank you for
telling me i didn't know that was
happening i'm sorry about it
yeah i i i will i will have it
investigated
wow
[Music]
that's weird
that is weird
wow
thank you for the red super chat i think
this message is long overdue but i've
never found the time to actually send
this i'm very proud of how far you've
come compared to the start i can't simp
as hard as i used to but kfb has grown
so much and it can probably make up for
what i lack in time
oh thank you so much don't worry about
it i'm happy to like still see you
around every once in a while
thank you for not forgetting about my
existence
and checking up on how i'm doing it's
nice to see that you're doing well too
hopefully
thank you very much enough for your
support wow
and yeah i think i i agree i've i think
i've grown a lot since the beginning i
am very embarrassed to watch my old
streams
my debut was decent in my opinion but
yeah it's still kind of cringe to watch
old kiwawa videos
so yeah i agree i think
i think
um come far in many ways
lucas kennedy
jackson fb
and yet there are many people who have
been here from the beginning or sometime
in the beginning and still like me
even though i was so cringe
before
how did you
like me when i was so cringy
i don't get it
my mouse pad you mean my birthday merch
the big the big big big mouth the desk
mat
ems not active from japan to my country
oh
that's yeah
japan hasn't been delivering to every
country
for a while
[Music]
but i'm sure it will come eventually
they won't lose it
[Music]
real idol experience
i guess so
holy
[Music]
oh
hmm
[Music]
nope not a big deal just kind of notice
the
some
some caps messages have been
timed out
uh
dear mods if it's like like spammy
and like a lot
then
yeah go ahead and and time it out but if
it's just like one or two words or like
a little bit not that much
then
no need to
don't need to
[Music]
like delete it or
ban it okay
a little bit of cat's luck is you know
necessary sometimes to express you your
strong feelings
yes
okay okay
okay okay okay
no problem though don't worry about
yourself for future reference
yeah thank you for your hard work thank
you thank you
i feel strongly [\h__\h] you up now don't
don't
don't go crazy now
don't stress out my mods man
oh my god love forever so true so true
ah my four months
see but this is okay in general it's
it's mostly mostly
okay
don't don't okay calm down now she's
just just
shush
[Music]
oh i wish she was here feeling
i wish
i wish sophie was here
if i get up then she will come and greet
me but right now
i feel so lonely i need a fluff in my
hands
you understand me you get me don't you
thank you felix
for being so supportive of my cats as
well
yeah
my lovely
lovely
bread loafs
um
[Music]
is my favorite anime
i was promoted just recently and thanks
to that i'll be able to watch holofest
but i'll be lurking more than ever oh no
anyways your art is so beautiful and i
can't wait to see on stage rocking much
love
all the ups and downs of getting a job
huh
having not that much time anymore but
then at least you can super chat
maybe you're able to watch my streams a
little bit on the way to work or or
during work maybe if if it's not
um
bothering anyone
well thank you for your support and i
hope i'll still see you around every now
and then congratulations on your
promotion doll that's a reason to
celebrate
hey recommendations there's so much to
see in tokyo and kyoto in kyoto
maybe i don't know
yama
uh
in tokyo there's just oh my god
too much i i don't even know when to
start
uh
everywhere
she everywhere
all those tourist spots obviously
so i'm here watching youtubers oh during
work nice you have nice co-workers mood
lamp thank
[Music]
don't take me so literally
lord of a castle
yo
i respect those people for respecting a
cat
johnny j dashing for the rest of the
chat
thank you for everything gentle your
presents make my life much happier
and your words make mine much happier
too
[Music]
thank you for watching my streams
even even when it's very very late over
there thank you so much for thinking of
me
hope you're enjoying it
that is an interesting name
satan's
pea collection
in japanese
thank you smiling bird dangerous and
brandon wood duncan maple leaf two five
zero one question black rich in danger
[Music]
yeah thank you thank you maple leaf two
five zero one dunkishan
for the rest of the chance if you play
the handshake even with the just right
you technically can handshake all others
oh yeah i read that one already
thank you
for your
valued opinion on that topic thank you
for disappoint
thank you so much
hope you enjoyed the chit chat today
i hope i was not too boring um
[Music]
what
us army boys love watching you in the
morning
what
oh i feel i feel flattered now i feel
like one of those flapper girls
[Music]
i'm surprised you're even allowed to
watch me or like anything
what
can i stop saying what
oh
and i hope i wasn't too boring
i'm well i can't help it if i'm boring
myself
[Music]
obviously they can watch you you have
generals and employ
what you mean from my side
kfb
kfb members in the army kfb generals in
the army
yeah they might be pulling some strings
[Music]
yo army boys
i'm sure the army boys want to see a
little bit of a
rocky rocky pie action
look you see that you see that
[Music]
you're welcome i mean it's always
visible
it's always always visible
[Music]
lord have mercy now now lord have
chihuahua only
in stock
[Music]
genma told kiara to do a sexy stream
but it brings in the views
genma gets it
now don't worry about it
they believe
in
[Music]
with a red envelope
once again i feel like you sent one last
year as well
thank you
that's already two red envelopes from
srika kamiyadin
if i'm not wrong
yes yes i wanna be one of those girls in
the old movies who waited the dog for
the hot sailors yeah i want to be that
i want to be like hey welcome back
[Music]
and then a wind breeze
passes me and my skirt goes up like
marilyn monroe and i'm like
oh
[Music]
thank you
for your generous support i'm getting
sick of this now
i need something calm
[Music]
um
ah
size
foreign
[Music]
bye
soon says that he uploaded the drawing
but since he's like shadow bamboozled on
twitter
i can't see but i think he deleted it
again
i'll get down get there
[Music]
um
uh
shadow bamboozled on twitter
and i had experienced that before on
twitter not with um
uh
kiwawa account
of course it's my ame account
yeah but it was it went on for like over
a year
it's like basically unfixable
and it's really really bad so
besides the sun i might recommend making
a sub account
i don't even know how it happens but it
happens hmm
yeah
after a while it might go away on its
own but i'm not sure what helps to fix
it um
unfortunately
put down your leg and sit straight
yeah
[Music]
no i don't know what i don't know it
bartending simulator
bart cyberpunk bartending
wait why does it sound familiar
korean thanks for the pinky
hello
thank you
mwah
wait why did i give you a kiss oopsie
take him give it give it back give it
back
to say hi
give it back give it back give me mean
case back
that one's a pinky
i made a mistake
refund
[Laughter]
[Music]
well you'll maybe make up for it at one
point when you send another pinky one
day
it's a early it's a pre-ordered
pre-ordered choo choo
pre-ordered and early access early
access
yes
very exclusive
thank you
[Music]
come on come on
i wanna go to my cat
sailing
[Music]
what
japanese person who's been working in a
anime company for 11 years or like 11
years ago
and there was an austrian there working
there not me
and then he went on to work for a game
company and he's super chatting in his
name
and i'm like yo there's barely any
austrians in japan i felt like i was the
only one when i lived there
so that's
pretty
cool and like going from an anime
company to a game company living in
japan for years and years
that's like really cool dream job for
some people i think even though it's
definitely very very
stressful to adapt to
a so different work culture
spaghetti and black kitchen
toby wong duncan for the pinky again
happy birthday
[Music]
bye now when you sent the super chat it
was still 20 minutes early but by now
it's your birthday
it's your birthday it's your birthday
kelly said the exact same thing about
being second most bullied kid in her
school
second i like how she's also second
depending on the school sometimes i was
number one and sometimes i was second
hmm
common awesome creation like
i feel like
this is uh a phenomenon that i've been
i've been noticing um
i feel like
i only ever hear about like people
saying
they got bullied in school
but i never hear people saying
they bullied others in school
like are they just acting like they're
one of us now because now
the
now that they're adult the majority
of us are somehow the ones that were
bullied before and they're just trying
to fit in
[Music]
or they don't or they didn't realize
that they were bullying but how can you
not realize it
for me it was both oh
i don't want to admit it
yeah probably
when these were bullied before
so they leave out that part
i guess that's
the case sometimes
i probably didn't think of the steps the
police
what else i also never hear is people
saying i was the popular popular kid in
school
i only ever hear people say they were
not popular or just normal average where
did the popular kids go
i don't believe it i don't believe that
they're just in a whole different like
world now
[Music]
that was pretty popular wow confidence
they aren't wanting me to shut up
don't say that popular people might
might be watching each of us
popular people
we are pro all of us are popular see
there's some people in chat who say they
were popular
well
hey
don't diss us
don't dissolve like that so naturally so
smoothly
it's moving
i was well liked in high school
of course you were you're a cool person
when i bullied the kid in my class i
always had a small voice in the back of
my head saying why are you doing this i
just want to be your friend
[Music]
i don't know if i should be mad at you
but you at least hopefully regret being
a bully
back in the day
i kind of want to punch everyone in the
face to bully others
um
sorry please please uh stand in the line
in front of me
and i will uh
not i will punch every single one of you
or slap you
um
yes
one after never
we stand in one line now
what does danger mean
it's german for thank you
i say it after the super chats because
i'd like to thank you in my own language
[Music]
slap him silly
i need to read super chats hmm
[Music]
sounds like my school's over here in the
states cause i already read this one
glad you're okay now and survive that
nonsense yeah
[\h__\h] school
so
bad oh my god i'm glad i'm out of that
face too
and now and now
sometimes i wish we had something like a
reunion and then i would tell them
[\h__\h] you look at me
look at me and my gucci belt which i
don't own yet but i will buy a gucci
belt
if if there's ever a reunion i will buy
a gucci belt
and a versace scarf
and i will dress up in in louis vuitton
and i will say [\h__\h] you
now you're the bully
no i'm not bullying i'm just saying [\h__\h]
you
nah
i don't i don't actually think that
there'll ever be a reunion like that
because like uh i feel like uh
uh
how would they contact me
i don't think my
old schoolmates don't have any means to
contact me and also my my whole
uh constant school switching
[Music]
probably will result in the fact that
they don't think about me
they don't think about inviting me
and i don't know do high school reunions
even happen in reality or is it only on
netflix and those kind of shows
is that even a real thing
i skipped my reunions er
i feel like it would be very interesting
to see some people again and see what
they're doing now
if they finally grew out of their
stupidness
it does happen
don't know yeah they do
real thing
i wanna go
to one somehow but also at the same time
it depends it depends on the school some
schoolmates i wanna see again some i
don't wanna see again definitely not
the ones i went to croatia with oh hell
no
hell no never never again
installment pain
thank you
[Music]
take your time take your time
i will take an interest rate just
kidding
so let's keep like don question big
sweet duncan i'm sure in 87 thank you
for the red super chat
yes red boobs
[Music]
boobs
usually
[Music]
you're back and you're already causing
troubles
cupcake
no i wasn't roasting him no no no no no
no no i was relating to him
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
thank you for writing out your name in
uh katakana for me
although i i feel like you're almost
like doing some witch
craft
sounds like
if i say that out loud i'm gonna summon
some some
something from hell
reminded me of my days in elementary
uh it's elementary in it
was physically bullied cold shouldered
excluded somehow got myself of a group
of friends but one day i realized they
were fake [\h__\h] them i fell off a
playground and was paralyzed on the
ground for good god knows how long my
friends run away [\h__\h] them give me their
numbers
give me their numbers or their addresses
anything
[\h__\h] them
is it isn't it nice to be adult now and
having all that [\h__\h] in the past
uh
i'm sorry that happened to you okano
like those [\h__\h] hats
those [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
sorry i treated you like that you didn't
deserve that at all definitely 100
percent not
here's a kissy for you
maybe that makes it better stupid
memories
okay if we hit squad on the way
down
[Music]
new year to you too kate thank you
i hope the new year will be very very
awesome successful and amazing for you
wish you all the best good luck
and make the best out of it all right
[Music]
i want a burger
i like thank you for the red super chat
um a while back someone made
oh yeah yeah i already read this a power
level tier list of all of mimi's fan
base it was based on the lore you girls
have given throughout your stream it had
us chickens near the bottom only beating
shrimps boss can you give us more power
so we can be right here for happen you
already got my answer i hope it was uh
uh satisfying i think it was don't worry
about it we are strong
don't worry
thank you very much that was my meme oh
is that so
good meme oh and an additional pinky
thank you so much alex very very very
kind of you thank you for liking my art
thank you
thank you love you too
wow
cyrux
and thank you for watching stevie brett
danke soon sends you in thank you soon
i shall refresh
we're almost done i think
i think i think we're getting there
on
oh don't worry i know you're a good
chimpkin in your heart so it's okay
sometimes a slip up might happen
i can apology
you didn't have to
you must understand as well that you
don't have to send a super chat in order
to apologize for another super chat okay
i forgive i am
wait
if i if i had that
that one perfect image
uh who was using it who is using navidad
midi
i need that i need that image
i feel like
that
shows my greatness and kindness
perfectly oh there it is wow it's
beautiful
[Laughter]
oh my god
look this is me i will forgive you i
shall forgive you chiara the merciful
will forgive all your sins my child
it has been said phoenix can heal
injuries it i just hit my pinky toe on
the kfb frying
can you hear my poo poo oh this is why
we don't have health insurance yes i am
the health insurance um
so when i hit when i needed uh my
boo-boos to be healed
um when i was a child
whoever would be close any adult would
blow on my booboo so i will blow on you
how's it how's it going
[Music]
how's it going is it better
should i do it cuter
hurricane
is it okay now
why is my pinky toe on fire no [\h__\h]
way
maybe my my fufu was too strong
okay
well it's not a red super chat but i'll
give you a choo choo
and now it must be 100 healed if not 200
percent i saw one compensation you sound
like a pigeon
step up your chimpkin game
then then oc donkeys
is that a mountain
and rapunzel
kissing
thank you for the rest of the chat i am
a shameless said
[Music]
jimin
i know that was a reply
to what i said to your super chat
i'm having trouble
reacting
my dear chimpkin
you need to
you need to take
a a little break come here come here
come here shh
stop talking
shh
just stop talking
[Laughter]
did he stop did he stop thinking stop
talking
good
okay
only dreams
put my wings on it
now i have hands
and
i'll close thank you
i'm gonna skip the flush chats again
thank you though thank you thank you
ak stf2 dungeon thank you what are you
enjoying the slippers
on eating excellent
outrun
[Music]
chicken
his name is kiara and then i'm chicken
wow don't tell that to nanny
she's a seal okay
then i'm taking is korean brand what
[Music]
yeah why would he drag that into it
maybe because uh she needs a little bit
of a chicken when it comes to every era
a whole live
horror stuff in general she told me she
told me she's not good with it either
oh
maybe they really just mean i am that
korean chicken brand
i'm my own brand i am phoenix
this
no chicken
we had a song before
fire
huh once again
[Music]
something like that
it's a
chicken
perfect perfect that you had the super
chat right after that other person
to even more undermine me i am a ch need
you to respect me i need you to change
your name
andrew right thank you for two pinkies
which makes
one red one but it's the same message uh
[\h__\h] did that youtube bamboozle you and
you sent it accidentally even though you
didn't want to
oh my i'm sorry i will
i will
i will soak your super chat up like a
sponge so that you don't have to be
too regretful
[Music]
um
uh so andrew says kiana don't sell
yourself short people happily want you
for hours just chatting about random
stuff and that's because you're a star
oh
your charisma is off the charts nah
it shows us two here maybe if it if it
didn't send two then that's good for him
keep doing what you're doing and
chimpkins like us will keep flocking to
you
enough
i hope they will
well i usually don't do
such
chill streams like this
so you know i just don't know like how
how
how much
like you know if if it's really like
going well i don't know i don't see it
from your point of view i only see it
from my point of view
and and like personally
i personally probably wouldn't watch
this stream
if i weren't myself
if i was someone else i probably
wouldn't watch this
so i kind of like
i don't know i personally want stuff to
be more entertaining
but as long as you guys especially the
kf people
are enjoying it
then i'm i'm cool with it
your your high-tech polygraph
give me that
send that to me
i want it
we are kiara
you are me
did you not watch idle streams no my
idols didn't stream
uh hello project idols don't stream
they blog but they don't like the blog
in in in the shape of a
text but they don't stream sometimes
they have videos on youtube but not much
hello project really doesn't show much
of their private life at all
personally i love these dreams
[Music]
i'm your llama
you wish
oh man everyone wants a hot mom like me
don't they
i am your mama
oh yes she's a legend
yes yes
but
during her time in hell project she
definitely didn't have a youtube channel
i'm so done with the super chats like
literally like i'm done i only need two
more for two korean dancers banging him
down for the pinky just sticking my head
in between meetings with his masked verb
it's me
did you forget what i look like with
this mask
it's a mia
don't forget
do i need to take it off when are these
people really that confused about my
mask
wait a second
i don't know
hello it's me
hi
welcome back
there you are
i've always been here
what did you get here
oh yeah today's twin tails day oh man i
should have worn my twin tails but i've
been wearing them a lot anyway recently
it was as beautiful as the day i first
laid eyes on
you are cute
saying that
where did that mask of the avenger go
[Music]
she went back inside a marvel movie i
guess
[Music]
she was um she was just taking a break
from recording uh shooting a marvel
movie
she's the new superhero of a marvel
yes it's about youtubers
okay
all came from the hen mother and all
shall return to the hen mother
as it is said in the book of kiwawa
bless
beautiful beautiful
yes that is a direct quote
and i think now we're done
hook
thank you
pinky
oh
oh great phoenix lent me a wisdom how do
i probably find my girlfriend's ring
size so it's still surprised when i
propose to her
oh sheesh
yeah
well uh i have i've yet
to have someone propose to me but i
think what people usually do they just
like approximately like guess it and
yeah cause the size can still be changed
afterwards
yeah
or if you look look into her accessories
maybe she has some rings in there if she
wears rings you can take one uh but it
depends on which
which finger she usually wears it if she
wears it on her pinky and obviously it's
not gonna work but and yeah maybe check
if she has other rings
um
give her a regular ring first
[Music]
yeah you could just like as um as a
normal gift give her maybe like a set of
a normal basic
not so special ring maybe with some
earrings like some matching earrings
and then
ask her if it fits and then she says no
then you're gonna say oh god michael
burgo and then she's gonna be wondering
huh i hope that dude
i hope that dude gives me a real
ring and uh gets on his knees one day
what's your ring size i don't know
i used to
know what um there's these like rings uh
finger
finger size thing
of things
i used to know it but i don't know
anymore
i don't know
i don't need to know
no one's gonna pull the ring on that
finger
but
i might put a ring on my cat's paws
but don't worry don't worry just uh even
if it doesn't fit
normally you can change the size as far
as i know so make it a bit bigger maybe
so that at least you won't have that
awkward movie
moment where it doesn't
like
uh like go
on top of the finger at all
at least a bit bigger would probably be
good
how's it been eight hours i'm still
streaming it's been eight hours but
winning now
daisy thank you for the red super chat
you sweetheart you're so cute
you're a little bit obvious though you
shouldn't make it so obvious daisy
i wanted to wear a surprise
i'm an ordained minister if you want me
to officiate wedding city today
thank you all that's good thank you
oh
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i got it i just remembered i
gotta do something
for tomorrow all right
thank you for watching today
[Music]
the art will go on twitter
soon
thank you
thank you and in germany
[Music]
tomorrow will be minecraft minecraft my
minecraft streams have recently been
kind of cursed by getting cancelled a
lot i think
uh
but tomorrow's probably fine i feel like
i'm jinxing it
[Laughter]
oh
we'll see
at least minecraft is so replaceable no
no i will do it i won't play i will play
although i don't want to play pokemon
but no we'll play minecraft we'll play
minecraft don't play minecraft we need
to get back into it
yeah yeah
and bye bye did i sell videos and join
with
we
[Music]
thank you
do
[Music]
what do you
what do you like about me guys
asking for a friend
[Music]
ah
why you cute
[Music]
do
jimin thank you
strangle
g-man
good night
didn't i tell you to shut shush
you should have shushed
[Music]
hi i didn't listen
three days
[Music]
hmm
yeah i need to end the stream