[Music]
foreign
go
they should they should be able to see
us
[Music]
don't start that again i just got rid of
it i just got rid of that
hey
what oh oh yeah
i wonder where she is but don't worry
because
i'm here i'm the bestest cook in the
world
so just because ame forgot to come to
work
you will not fail you have me
what oh yeah although the game audio oh
one
[Music]
okay is this is this too loud my friends
let us
[Music]
what what the hell why is that happening
again is this happening with you guys
ah because i had desktop audio muted
okay do you guys you oh they can't hear
you
oh that you could you guys couldn't hear
them
all are jokes
some really uh some hot jokes there hot
joe guns that no one will ever hear
it's fine uh basically what we wanted to
say was
um this is this is um this is our [\h__\h]
in kitchen
uh me gouda and amelia have invited
kyara
kusotori a little special guest however
amelia is missing uh missing
we can't find the detective she's very
good at hiding
yeah yeah she's quite good at hiding or
rather probably rather busy
right with a special case who could say
[Music]
a very special case but don't worry
don't worry
as i said when we were muted even when
amelia forgets to come to work it's okay
i'm here i'm the bestest of all the
cooks
in all the world as you can see that the
little i have like a default
little chef hat i mean it's not really a
chef hat but something like that so
i have it by default so i think that
shows that i am a good cook and you can
leave it all to
[Music]
we have we have one of the the best
managers in the business
restaurant managers here in the business
so i'm sure that uh today the bitching
kitchen will succeed once again
i'm sorry i make you guys too loud now
now too loud game too loud okay
how about now okay guys
[Music]
uh
500 different answers yeah
okay perfect perfect i have i got a few
perfect
okay i think we're finally ready to
start
i'm a original food taster professional
chef matt wait
we have chiara the professional chef
good at the professional taster
and cali the professional professional
here we go let's go
what what wait wait wait wait wait
they say again that that you guys are
muted how this
was like when when kelly was streaming
this as well
hold on a positive name that's the game
hold on i'll quite go back to maine
um did you set discord to high priority
oh ah-ha wait i remember that
i remember that and
open the task manager
yes yes yes scroll down to discord but
now they hear you guys apparently but i
still probably gotta
do the thing because every time probably
every time i go into the game
window uh-huh wait i have like five
million
discord processes oh maybe the one who
takes up the most
i shall yeah that must be one mm-hmm
[Music]
um amelia is super loud what amelia's
not even here
amelia's that's the best that's the best
amelia still amelia okay now i'm going
i'm opening the game
even here do you guys hear callie
hello check one zoo hey hey you guys
here gouda
better hear that it's a shark
what what
like even if they say it's fine i feel
like that's from five minutes ago
they can they can
wonderful all right let's get let's get
this party started then
let's make some burgers what
what burgers are we making burgers i
only played the tomatoes
so i only was making salad
okay well it gets a little more
complicated than that i will say
oh that's why i was like hey let's play
a tutorial and you were like nah i got
this don't worry
i played the picture so you weren't
muted to begin with they say in the chat
what the actual
people are probably just plugging with
you how did it happen
okay you did um so you want to chop meat
and then we want to put it on the frying
pan right
uh so let's okay okay and the meat
chopper wonderful let me chop the
meatloaf
one yeah put some buns and then we also
got to remember that we need to chop up
some cheese as well
um it looks like this patty is actually
done
i don't have anything can you take my
meat away
i got your meat wait what do i do with
that son
it's good that we have one person down
there because one person can always
deliver off
okay
and there um one burger that doesn't
need cheese so remember that i sent the
burger
i sent one more burger all right well
we're doing good
yeah we're doing pretty decent now let's
grab some blood and
so this actually this one's ready to go
what's happening there you go
we have two teaspoons and a hamburger
okay i'll throw the burger away right
away ina is muted oh my god these trolls
these trolls
worries and we gotta get a dishwasher
i'll go ahead and take care of it leave
it to me
leave it to your boy that's so much
multitasking
yeah that's a lot for the brain
what am i doing that's fine well this is
what it's like to run a restaurant right
i mean you gotta get that gotta get that
multiple testing
i already built my first kfp uh
restaurant but i'm not actually working
like
i let everyone work for me so that's
that
yeah i'm sorry that was my bad
that was your boy's bed
oh you don't want that to happen okay
[Music]
i wanted to mention uh my dear wife
callie
uh even that's incorrect don't tell them
wrong things
no that's not the point even though we
have been
dating for three weeks up until 10
minutes ago
you did not have me accepted as a friend
on steam
and i was the only one who had everyone
except me
there's a reason for that what is it
don't play games together at least not
recently ah
there you go okay simple a simple enough
explanation don't be so sensitive
and does it rather send something to
that burger no
okay so stuff like the cheese and some
of them don't
thank you for the meat oh by the way do
you guys want to know why i chose
uh the present uh skin
because kelly's present and toss me that
meat
oh boy that's interesting so this
cheeseburger is about to go away
um if someone was a job ah yes all right
so let's
okay we're gonna have to run this i'm
gonna run take that one in right take
that burger take that burger you gotta
this that burger's ready
burgers ready what this one right here
that good uh just kidding
i'm standing right here you take this
kiara please take the burger please
[Music]
please if this is you trying to get back
at me
i do not appreciate that because the
business is suffering
but it's good
bitching kitchen's on the line here man
pull it together
pull it together i don't even have
enough chopping boards
okay cali designated chopper now and
deliver all right
who of you is even good and who is uh
oh yeah the game is in german
yup you have a problem with that last
time problem damn it
what's this thumbs up
ghost writer thinks it's fine all right
one star could have done better but hey
we made it out
do you want to do an easier look wait
wait one second one second one second
people people say that it's laggy
is that true is it really people could
be fun
how many people are how many people are
saying that if it's a lot then yes
because i was busy cooking i don't know
if it was really lagging
i mean they can try and turn the stream
resolution their quality down like
instead of viewing it
at full quality sometimes no problem
okay
i can't believe the chat anymore it's
like so many mixed opinions
well what is the upload speed like
for your internet currently uh 64
mbps
okay then there shouldn't be a problem
but there should not be
why they should not be there yeah if
people are having lagging issues it
might be their own
issues but not certain um why can't
[Music]
why can't we proceed to two seven do we
have two stars and it might be a
different path
there might be let's see let's see what
we can find
and we might have to go back to the uh
there might be one feet or yeah all
right
not lagging anymore oh man let's just
hop in a bit that's like honey
honeycomb
amma is frozen and muted for real i
wonder
where she's probably in the land of the
dream
emma deserves a break okay i'm jumping
in for her shift
yes you guys made her
work way too many over hours i'm so
sorry look that wasn't my intention but
[\h__\h] in kitchen never stops moving man
did you get brave chefs you're involved
because you didn't pay her hey all of us
are getting the same weight
which is minimum wage you get paid in
in delicious meals
oh my god yeah else do you want to skip
around
all right about something unimportant so
let's get out of here
maybe the pathway will be open maybe it
won't be i wonder what we'll do
team vision kitchen we'll have to figure
it out translate to english oh the story
was in german now
oh my god i guess i'll have to read out
loud then you guys will hear my prose
readings
german was so natural to me that i
didn't realize sorry guys
oh my god how do you say
it's no problem in germany
that's so cute and today from before the
stream god told me
that you learned german for two weeks
that's uh-huh and then she said
i try random what did you say
what did that mean i'm a good student
cute so we got to chop up the pizza
dough if i recall
i really kind of didn't you know what's
wrong with these pizza dough to the
right whoa they're smoking
it's smoking why is
okay i'll put these on the platform okay
yeah
is it loud
there we go all right it's in the oven
though thank you yeah let's make these
pizzas
we got this cheese
oh my gosh it's like magic wizard
wizardry magic
welcome to wizard school today pizza oh
gosh
oh the pizza's ready to come out you
gotta grab it
thank you all right you can grab this
one oh wait the of the
wait i'll take that let me take that let
me take it oh okay hold on
here you go thank you just have a plate
now it does yeah now we just need some
mates
tomatoes
take the tomato and even stress it's
fine mm-hmm
take it and chop it cali let me out of
here please
here go ahead and drop drop the tomato
on the
cool all right now we can go ahead and
put it in the oven okay sick
now go ahead and get the chopping that
cheese
all right you can chop that tomato as
well
that pizza is ready to go wait grab it
do you guys know anyone because i know
someone
who who likes to who hates tomatoes but
likes ketchup isn't that weird
that's a texture thing i mean i can
laugh at it
that's so weird though i gotta get these
plates washed though so i'll wash them
squash in place making pizza okay that
needs some tomatoes
okay there's a tomato here and there's a
pizza ready to go
thank you
oh no watch out don't get trapped in
there unless you want to be designated
that's okay i think i have no problems
that's where i can be and this can this
is ready to go
we're on fire we are on fire all right
real quick hold on
oh all right all right this is going in
the oven
i'm under help today but i know this i
don't know [\h__\h] about the game i'm sorry
guys
it's okay okay
nice you can drop that uh on the on the
conveyor belt up on the top
there are some areas
you can throw this in the oven too if
you want
[Music]
and chop up the cheese
hey i wanna thickly
do in the oven okay oh i just feel like
every time i push it obs the fps thing
gets fixed
oh well when i'm out of the window it
sucks oh yeah i do hoe though you got
another piece probably
all right there's a plate down there i
need to put yeah
it's okay no problem i wonder if it'll
be ready inside well we can give it a
try
always always give it a try always go to
there give it a shot
honestly this is how this is streams are
supposed to be they're supposed to be
scuffed
six
three yes sick
side absolutely
[Music]
[Laughter]
do you guys know how to say uh
itadakimasu in german i don't even know
how to is there a word for
english nope no i mean you could say
let's dig in
yeah in german it's my site
oh my god i gotta teach you guys german
at some point because that's so adorable
when you guys speak german oh my god
uh
i'll do it that sounds kind of fun like
a challenge
can you say
amen i know what that last word was hey
don't don't make her say something
embarrassing that's rude
wait what does that mean i know what the
last word is but
[Music]
damn [\h__\h] ah
whoa
that's why i'm here i'm the help
yeah so so we have a new a new friend
what are we making
uh okay well actually we don't need
lettuce why am i chopping lettuce we
don't need that
we're making burgers um so yes we yeah
so amelia is
missing an action which is fine she's
probably working on a
tough case right now so we called in the
best of the best
uh to come help us uh the best
restaurant owner that i know
yes the only restaurant owner that you
know
what it's uh it's also true but i'm not
gonna put it in
my chat that's gonna fall which i'm just
gonna fall oh very successful restaurant
owner
now you gotta go through the magic door
what is this oh wait i can control it
ready let's put your management skills
to the test kiara
what's the choice already
nice
and we can toss the food i keep
forgetting that we can toss the food
you can toss it and chop it and toss it
happen to us yeah so like here's oh okay
oh you laced this for me i can just grab
a bunch of materials whatever
i probably should top it though gosh
darn it i should chop it yeah
and send it over to me to chop need some
cheese
please oh my gosh darn it yeah cheese is
a good idea
okay let's see cheese lettuce is this
one done no this one needs cheese
she's coming yeah
okay so a cheese a ham
okay no what
there's a plate here can i just cook
with
it for a second i want to try something
don't mind me
okay i'm just a plain meat one just a
plain old meat can you chop this
i'm just kidding maybe send that over my
way
can you chop this okay just kidding
um
is running in place for me how are you
doing kiara yeah same are you
are you okay i wonder if it's just hella
leg
or something like that but it's fine
it's fine
what are you doing on your screen kiara
do you work i'm standing
oh come in hell
i'm trying i don't know i'm trying to do
something with obs i'm requesting
assistance
oh you're doing something with obs ah no
hold on i've got i got my gotcha
yeah if we can get like a plain a plain
one i'll grab a
bunch all right what'd you guys put on
your hamburger
uh um for me
i like just meat and cheese and
mushrooms
oh caramelized mushrooms love mushrooms
yes it's the best oh my god
just plain one one
one that we need it's okay don't die
i need a plate here you go how to plate
yeah sorry problem with that one these
plates are in a really tricky spot
because the
the the door keeps sucking me in the
hungry door
you talk you drop some lettuce too and
throw us in my way
me oh good idea
i think kiara said that she's busy with
obs right now yeah i'm trying to
figure out what's the problem
okay best
[Music]
nice i think that's about the best we
can do for now but
it's been a valiant effort but they're
good that's a that's a one star
easy yeah inside
up kilau fan
okay one second before we move on before
we move on
uh i want to know why the
fps drops every time i leave the
streamlabs window
yes it's dropping here um why don't you
go to the game settings
yeah um and maybe you can change the fps
there yeah i wanted to do that but it
doesn't give me any any setting like
that maybe it shouldn't be
window capture
oh yeah use game capture for sure for
sure but didn't show me anything with
game capture
it should automatically pick up the
window
maybe try that try adding game capture
give it a shot
because i tried to use window capture
too and ame said no use game capture and
then that worked way better
oh now finally it sees it okay
hey that could be better but that also
doesn't give me
a frame rate option i thought oh well
okay well let's exit to the main menu
and see what we can do hold on
if we go to the main you might be able
to mess with the quality there
uh in the game
so go to settings now we're in the menu
go to settings
and you can scroll down to quality it
doesn't say frames but
you can change the quality
[Music]
oh my goodness it's fine
i'll invite you again i'll invite you
again
it's no problem the thing is like i
i rarely play with uh with a game
controller
um so i i never know if
the b button or the a button like
because i i
i'm used to the lowest button being the
the
leave button and the button on the right
side being the okay button but
here it is switched so i keep
pushing the wrong button
out pushing the right button
[Laughter]
um wow when you get the invite again
oh i i already accepted and then
okay cool i'm getting in check out the
settings
i'm getting yeah if you check out the
settings uh you can hit game
and then you'll be able to go down to
quality and you can change up the
quality
it might be set to super low
automatically because it was for me
so i'd bump it up oh i had it on mid
middle
medium although maybe turn it up to high
really the game you know what
let's see let's just see how this works
now that you've changed it to game
capture instead of window capture
how about that yeah let's just let's
just see what happens
okay let's give it a try
what i don't know what i clicked what
are you fine do you guys have
yeah i took us into the game i took us
into the game okay
so nice next up yes
got next up i wonder what we're making
i'm hungry
opens pizza
it kind of looks like it is pizza from
far away
oh baby it's all right pizza time
we got sausages too sausage pizza
[Music]
and broccoli you know we had a german
word
pineapple pizza pineapple pizza
what hate it food
pineapple is okay it's all right here
you go ahead you can chop that
as well i'll chop it wait that's not a
cutting board
oh lol okay i wonder if it's a little
brandon's asleep
cheese oh my god
now this can actually go ahead and be
not ready it needs tomatoes tomato
tomatoes potato potato
and then we can grab some cheese for
this bad boy here
but this already has dough so i'm just
kidding
guys don't try to add me to your
friend's list
the only thing that i will ever accept
is all the lives got it
i can't believe your profile isn't set
to private uh it should be
it's a plate what do you mean it needs a
plate can i get a plate for this
yup right over here here you are
thank you kelly
[Music]
how to make pizza you're welcome you win
this pizza can go in the oven
yeah nice yes
i need the job oh my gosh is that okay
it's really not making us easy yep
but your oven that'd be great yeah no
problem
awesome nice that can go right
out okay oh oh oh
oh all right ready to go pizza alarm
that's cut already oh my brain wait i
can't get this plate
no problem ready to go
uh no problem i'm washing them
all right here's one where are the
pineapples
where are the pineapples maybe it's in
the dlc
oh oh
i like meat lovers pizza let's put meat
on it
same i'm a big fan of meat lovers i got
it
okay
okay dirty plate kiara do you want to
come watch this dick
yes we'll do nice thanks
the chaotic boss trying to be useful for
the organized depression
all right i'll wash this dish
this cheese one needs to go uh it's
never mind
okay okay it's a cute mermaid now
and then i just realized yeah i don't
hate it okay that went straight into the
tree i love how i slam
dunk that straight into the trash mba
moves right there
okay here's one ready to go
okay okay okay
stress and anxiety level five million
over nine thousand feel high
it's good it's how we like it
how do you keep forgetting to look at
the orders up above
because it shows which ones are in more
dire need of being finished
all right i can't look at that yeah fan
no it's that one yeah we hella failed
that one
oh no we have we got close we got really
close
um yeah so let's try and remember to
like look up at the orders that are in
most dire need of being completed first
i think that might be the key to boss
are success
accepting expecting me to multitask
i am i am yes that's how you that's how
you would
that's how you do this difficulty
restaurants manager
get out of the you kitchen have so much
more experience
than me in being a bitching kid
that's true bitching kitchen is a little
bit different from from
kfp i'm thinking yeah um so it's okay to
take take your time you know we'll we'll
figure it out
if you're learning yes exactly
we have a cheese and a sausage nice
i will try my best to chop up uh bread
and put it on plates
how about that that sounds good i think
i'll do that i'll have it ready too i'll
just i'll finish
doing it and i'll just leave them around
i'll just leave them sitting around
that's probably right
oh ping why you do this to me stop okay
okay this one
this could use some cheese where's the
cheese
or there's in stressful situations
how do you calm yourself down you don't
uh
you use the stress to fool yourself to
go faster is what you do that's what you
do in the restaurant industry believe me
i worked in it for a while underworld
arubato
[Music]
yeah there's two orders to go out if you
want to take those up
okey dokes
i can't tell if this just needs a plate
yeah i think it just needs a plate
because it's steaming
right oh it doesn't just need cheese
there's cheese right here
i don't know i'll get some juice in the
oven it goes
thank you i'll wash them i think i
should just be endlessly cutting
then i'll be fine yeah you sometimes uh
some teams decide to uh divide up the
responsible tomatoes tomato come to me
tomatoes i got this oh my god thank you
finished pizza over here just needs a
plate
yup yes indeed whoopsie doodle here
ready to go we have a cheese also that
needs a plate right here
oh sorry that hurts me
okay we have uh the sausage one oh wait
is that
the lack of plates is really not great
i'll wash them we have we have cheese ah
when she's sitting here so
you guys know how my name is uh like my
nickname is tanjo
do you know what that means girls
yeah a restaurant owner right store
manager
i think today that title is officially
not mine anymore
it's okay you'll earn it back it's fine
this is mission kitchen
territory it's like the wild west of
kitchens so don't even worry about it
like is it off there so that the store
managers don't do [\h__\h]
that's ready to go yeah yeah yeah
okay
i mean they they did quite a few things
when i when i recall having an aruba
in the underworld wow then you had a
good store manager
a good one yeah well a lot of times
because cooks and and uh
waiters and people like that weren't
actually doing the work that they needed
to be doing
so oftentimes the store manager would
step in
so we have no time
we sure don't i had a pizza almost done
oh no i don't know if i'm gonna make
this this is gonna be tight it's gonna
be close
i think that we did fine though oh yeah
needs a plate ah i
[Music]
very good amazing bell played indeed
well you chef what a cutie
[Music]
bon appetito mm-hmm
i'm just saying italian son of words man
let's go to the next here we are next
level this looks like more
man i don't like it
these doors are so tricky oh we're
making burgers
[Music]
let's do the first three we'll focus on
the first three so we have
uh one plane buns
[Music]
no wait hold on
oh shoot shoot shoot okay i come uh i'll
take this out of your way
thank you yeah teamwork make the dream
work baby
deeper does make the dream work so this
just needs a plate over here
lettuce and cheese and a plate and it'll
be good to go i'll take it
i'll take it okay excellent
slap it on a plate there we go bring it
out
you got some buns yeah
i got some really hot buns here take
them
a lettuce tomato
nice all right
here's some vegetarian meat
i've never had a vegetarian vegetable
tomato
i have not tasted that but i've heard
that some people
okay some vegetarian meat there's some
vegetarian
ready to get out of here this just needs
a plate
oh my goodness there's really just so
there's so many things here
start i'm gonna start getting uh
i'm gonna start from uh chopping up some
of this meat and
frying it up okay i'll put the plates
here
this is the midway point
this game takes so much
all right so this needs
to play here got any greens i wonder
green i'll toss you another one
everyone just needs a tomato nice one
i made the vinegar
eat your job you did it yay you did it
i'll toss you some vegetarian options
okay good idea definitely need water
right now i'm not tomatoes oh gosh we
really have so many materials
uh darn it oh i was just making the
burger that i want to eat
yeah we need we got to look at the
ticket right oh look
we got orders coming in kiana oh no
we're missing a whole lot of them aren't
we oh gosh darn it
hang on up what
okay you have burgers my bad i'll go
i'll have it what if i put bur i'll put
buns on all these so if you just worry
about
the insides of me wait how is that gonna
work that's not gonna work
never mind that's a bad idea on my part
this has been
we can come up with a system after this
but then it always devolves into us not
using the
system
like somebody's designated plate washer
somebody chopped yeah that maybe would
be a good idea
chopper etc yeah
[Music]
okay i hope we're getting some uh
tip tip tips tips tips
tips tips here and there
here and there it would seem but not
really that many because bitching
kitchen is not that we're not known for
our quality we're just known for
we squeak it out so you know we're known
no don't sorry hang on
again
oh you quit you you ran away you decided
to
nigeru to escape we aren't going to do
the same one over again
[Laughter]
unless you're feeling dary next kitchen
hey you want to talk about daring how
about this next one
looks rather daring all right
okay so beautiful oh
favorite chef what are we making
we have
oh my god this is like whoa there you go
this is too difficult
it's pretty close no it's bad it's fine
into the fryer
so this is how things are going to be at
kfp you got to be ready for it
on kfbs are not supposed to be on rivers
i mean if you wanted to add a little
extra spice
i don't know what do i do oh you could
actually go ahead and
chicken uh through the thingy through
the the
the whatchamacallit this is the worst
for it to be yeah then we had to wait
i wanna throw this because i feel like
it's too risky
yes throw hot oil over the river
wait no we need that we need just potato
on plate wait no we need to get our
potato on plate okay
that's just just an order guys yeah i
got the i got the basket sorry about
that oh
i'm so confused now what's going on
ah there's no way to wash dishes over
here huh ooh that's a shame
we have an order that can go out if you
would like wow excellent
wow oh got a plate over here
it wasn't ready all right let me wash
these real quick
oh nice all right those potatoes are
ready to go just a single one
going out ready to fly
and we have these potatoes going out too
nice nice nice and nice
bird shopping some things
chopping all right washing as well
wait this game doesn't let you throw
flights it knows
it knows too well it's not gonna end
well for anyone
hey man man i wish you could tell please
though that would be so helpful
i know it's too realistic realism in my
video
okay you can put that in there
[Music]
grab that chicken and throw it all right
i got it never mind hang on
leave it to me okay wait what no
come on man
this is so confusing
[Music]
thank you oops oh scott
can you bro all right oh favorite
chicken out
of my mind got it got it right and we
need a a chicken and potato
uh out here asap
[Music]
go
that makes it confusing the orders up
top i thought they were like
i know me too they start yeah they said
make something on top of them there's a
color
there's like a color that will show us
how much time we have left
well came in clutch at the end there so
okey dokey
one star is good right one out of three
size is very good
team [\h__\h] and kitchen always freaked it
out that's what we're known for
i mentioned before
before the uh before the health
inspectors follow us
what's your favorite chicken nugget
sauce
chicken barney and honey mustard and
ranch
oh i like those three oh
i like honey
my favorite is sweet and sour
but yeah they don't have it everywhere
really oh we're making burritos oh my
god this also looks so difficult
what the hell i don't like the
acrobatics
i need rice yeah okay we've got to toss
gouras some of that rice
[Music]
i'm gonna start throwing materials over
to the other side where the cutting
board is
with my uh basketball skills
well on the same platform
oh man this level really i really am not
a big fan
i'm not a big fan i'm going to be honest
with you
guys okay i can go out
yep it looks like
what am i doing you gotta go back over
without
okay i'm an amateur
over here i did not really get training
so
excuse me oh all right
we're not getting any okay for not
getting any training you're doing pretty
well
yes um
what i can do is i can probably chop
things and then uh
and then three pointer uh free throw
them over to that side
oh you got the you got the pins though
you got to cook all the meat
yup okay ah iron it
over here you're right you're right
you're doing it
maybe we need to find a way to um
maybe somebody can throw the materials
someone can chop and fry
and somebody put it all together why did
that black one just go
away they go yeah i'll come i'll take a
taste
scuff it's quite a level done
okay nice
oh coming up coming up look out complete
coming at you
look out the ice popping all over
i have no idea what's going on here
uh food is being made uh-oh can we cook
everything
else i got it right it's good rice is
good
oh rice is very good i need some what do
you call that
steak meat beef just
no no
oh no oh
no yes nice this is
rice oh i have to cook rice
nice excellent nice rice
i'll take your chicken burrito go go for
it
now you're ready to add this to it we
need the beef
coming in a second is rice
i'll take it why does time go so fast
i know oh tricky
we're good though we're good oh really
oh really this is what you call good
shittiest kitchen i have ever
experienced
whoa whoa woman
[Music]
i'm so proud i mean we have to say that
we're understaffed today okay we're
understaffed
we are understaffed this was not
according to the yote
yeah or the keikaku the plan was to be
for i friggin said that translators know
[\h__\h] kill me
let's see where we going oh back to the
castle all right i'll be sure to narrate
this properly this time
ebit me oh oh are you reading star
valley
are you gonna read star wars uh yeah i'm
thinking so we're supposed to go to the
castle which i'm assuming means
yes he's got a little onion man
okay kelly will read it in english you
guys will see it
uh in german so good luck on your
studies everyone
write it down
okay barge it says wolf in german
who's there come at me if you want that
dot dot exclamation point oh thank
goodness it's you
and look at you so united so cooperative
i don't know about that one mr onion
king
you're going from strength to strength
at rapid speed
but the unbread are still too powerful
wait can i read one line any german yeah
go for it woof there you go that was a
short line
very well done that was very well done
can i read the next one stink
okay yeah okay mine still oh yeah and
you skipped what the [\h__\h]
i'm not i'm not pressing any buttons
this is
you are brave you are bold you are the
greatest band who ever lived
you are the [\h__\h] in kitchen nothing
bitching kitchen of uh in german is uh
here
and then expect us not to not to use it
as our new catchphrase
[Music]
i wonder if we're going to make
something new something
probably maybe a new recipe maybe
something easy
looks like sushi
thanks for watching
this the first level that i ever played
actually of this one
yeah i remembered that we got killed by
the many cars and i thought what kind of
world is this shrimps
shrimps shrimps shrimps
i'll just i'll just chop okay i'll just
jump
okay i got it don't worry this one i do
okay kids don't forget your street
safety look both ways before you cross
the kitchen road
got that nori
all right
[Music]
it's done this is is this california
maki i don't really know much about
sushi to be honest
either i'm not very ah
i almost got hit by a car damn this is
wrong chef
oh no why did we the shrimp i
chopped it that was on me it looks the
same mess
okay it's okay don't worry too much
about it we'll be fine
oh gosh that wouldn't go shoot
we'll leave this in the road we'll offer
this to the guys guys guys guys
why did the chicken cross the road
i am not in the mood to deliver the food
[Music]
okay
sushi that sounds good yeah i did
oh
how to make sushi i feel like ina would
be
better here oh my gosh there's a dish
that's just literally the fish
sashimi is this pink why can't i cross
the road ah
okay we're good no no no no
way to put the right i just need one
dish
all right this is ready to go okay nice
guys cannot die so don't worry about me
just kidding i'm fine
i've got more fishing
you are zooming
for the plate that i need double team it
double team okay i'm sorry yeah
yeah is there cucumber anybody
ah tight
[Music]
the only thing i'm doing well is the
german announcement that the time is
over
it's okay we need somebody to watch time
too i think it'll count
yes we need someone because it wouldn't
have been obvious that the
time is over true
true enough that we use well what did we
learn from
what did we learn from the last round um
nothing
i also did not learn why did she can
cross the road because you didn't tell
me
why did it cross the road
i couldn't
[Music]
it's fine so i'm going to boil a lot of
rice
and i'm going to wash a lot of plates
that's what i'm going to get some fish
i'm going to put a lot of nori on plates
[Music]
i already put cutie in there
oops sorry i ah push the wrong button
thank you okay oh bad boy's ready to go
this one's ready for sale oh this
thing's getting me oh
he's ready this is ready this is ready
yay don't kill me
it's nice let me just need this i got
the tip
i got a tea there
[Music]
i need the fizzy i need the fizzy
shrimp stamina oh yeah that's a redfish
this actually doesn't need any rice just
needs a plate
yeah get that washed yeah sick
why would like one plate what the hell
because they're dirty we gotta wash them
[Music]
they show up next to the delivery window
to the right you see it oh the brown
plate next to it i'll take one
chicken will never cross the road again
dangerous zone
very dangerous always go with a friend
yes
i always think a buddy
that's what they say no my cucumber
cucumber
cucumber it needs cucumbers
what the [\h__\h] this place is
so let's just uh chop up the fish yeah
we're doing much better
here i have i have this for you okay
and then yeah that one hold on the car
is about to come by
[Laughter]
nice we got this guys yeah
cucumber right now really
i was so busy cooking i didn't even
realize it's sakura season here
cherry blossom oh pretty
people unfortunately no time to look at
them
excuse me i'm cleaning here
tied up
[Music]
two stars everyone i know right that's
two more stars than we had last time
yeah incredible i just gotta you know
do it a bit more seriously before sorry
i really didn't take it too serious
it's okay it's okay
you're good no worries but uh are you i
hope you're not gonna
fire me after this session
of course not how can we fire the
general manager
i feel like next week i might not be in
this collaboration anymore
oh no we're gonna ask you this come
along but
you're welcome in the [\h__\h] and kitchen
anytime you've proved yourself to be
where oh my gosh
that's doing this we just got to clear
it with big boss amelia
yeah she's a this is a big boss
unfortunately missing in action for now
yeah i hope she has sweet dreams
dreaming of sushi and burgers and hot
dogs and pizzas
yes all the tasty foods
all right let's see um here we are
boingy river
oh man i don't
[Music]
all right kiara you and i are on
shopping duties okay
we'll do it i throw a potato away i'm
sorry
we only gotta focus on salad right okay
never mind i like
there you go what do i do with these
what are you making
oh again chicken nuggets and salads nice
[Music]
yeah this could go really bad
oh yeah all right so this salad is ready
to go aha
so we have just a lettuce just a lettuce
salad whoever eats just blood is
questioning me just
lettuce lettuce with chicken nuggets
a weird person ah like people that would
like if you go to a restaurant and just
order lettuce like wow
what the hell where did i go this needs
to be washed
you may have fell off the best of us
yeah this is done here you go take this
people are asking where's emilia since
like an
hour she's missing
this will be a meme this should be a
meme like from now on
every
wait that reminds me of who's rem and
then okay who's ram and where's amelia
okay only
people who watched league of legends
okay nobody look nobody
[Music]
wait wait what do i do
there's no room oh oh oh maybe we can
connect now
can we connect
why would you want anything besides
nuggets
hold on ghost rider is hungry dude what
do you want right surprise
now he's good by the way callie uh i
noticed something recently
that's not good i don't know how
[Music]
on my belt but i was like i wonder if
it's the same person it's such a mystery
it's a big mystery and maybe gouda has a
tony no shrimp rider
shrimp rider now that you've said that
that's something that's going to happen
maybe something somewhere
you got emotion
[Music]
weirdo who just wants lettuce
we only got dirty ones oh my god it's
all very sturdy
[Music]
that's okay that was tricky amazing
it's pretty decent i'll take it
hold on hold on ghost rider's ordering
something in the chat hold on a second
oh fries with nuggets thanks boss all
right you got it no problem ghost ready
would you like to start with that effect
the return of inanes
perfect in a perfect character
now where is the detective the most
mysterious creature the british
i was gonna say where's the detective oh
my gosh
oh if we make a bingo for bitching
kitchen
ah make a what ally restarts this if we
make a bingo
for bitching kitchen that needs to be on
there it restarts
oh what a good opportunity all right
let's see
next up next kitchen
what is this chin what are we making
girl looks like
oh they're going really fast too really
fast treadmill girls
died that was quick okay yum yum yum
reviving
right i'm going to toss materials over
to you guys sounds good
well i guess i'm tossing it back here to
come to me
[Music]
uh maybe we should actually be one in
each area
here huh that makes sense actually what
we can do we need to put
if we put materials on the conveyor belt
okay and
they actually oh i put myself on the
conveyor belt
no that's also probably fine dude
we don't need lettuce right now yeah we
do need to cook this meat though
yeah can you put it here
how do you just put something down can
you put it there again
i want this thing can you just give me
that yeah thank you
oh thank you guys bro you see
that did you stand good at those skills
damn cut that songs
can you put that raw meat over to me so
i can reach it
by the way you are
you want to drop that over here for me
we're doing
good thank you need that i like lemonade
oh all right okay i accept my face all
right
oh dude are we switching can you drop it
yeah that one's ready to go oh that
works too oh it's switching
all right okay what is happening
we need another meat over here chopping
meat coming right
up here you go that's
yeah there are a couple burgers that
just need meat on them so here you are
thank you why is there a wait i'm sorry
i need that thank you
we're good
uh oh nice bro
[Music]
who stuck a plate in the corner that was
[Laughter]
meat
i think i'll make it
i'm not even necessarily here if you're
gonna have froze like a like an
i don't know basketball player then i
don't need to even
be here i just want to put them down
okay
yeah i do need a cheeseburger on the fly
all right oh good perfect perfect
perfect and then a bun
that one should be ready to go and then
we just need a
one
go in for a dip i'll be right back hang
on if you can go ahead and chop
uh cook and chop this yes it'll be
perfect
you can get that one going we just need
a simple meat one
okay i bet that'll be ready just in time
oh [\h__\h] this just needs cheese
can you have some cheese real quick if
you don't throw it into the water maybe
i can
put the cheese away
[Music]
it yeah a little bit chaotic in the end
yeah it's chaotic
yeah it'll be good we just need to go
again it's good
it sounds so wrong in german so wrong
oh i want coffee we're doing it again we
gotta do it again so we can buy it
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go
without floaties
[Music]
okay you go swimming again
you need some bloodies
i also go swing i got it
hey girl burger okay thank you
oh is this your are you are you chopper
kiara is this like i don't know what i
am
i lost my identity existential crisis
happens to the best this is going to be
worse than before
i'll show you i'll be um okay
oh man oh my god
can we start it
this is horrible bitching kitchen fights
till the end
[Music]
yeah i'm gonna stay here it was kind of
better when i was here
thank you oh yes
all right oops
kindly thank
oh
where is the lettuce
gotta get my lettuce uh some chopped
lettuce please
you can chop this for me yes thank you
thank you the
i think we have found our balance
yeah for the most part i mean it works
it's fine all right
uh and a burger with everything on it
i put everything on it two burgers with
everything on it
two burgers with everything on it
everything on them
oh my god that gum is popping off
where why are we oh
no it's all falling apart no
oh man it's all falling apart
okay i got lettuce coming home
mine is chopped here thank you yes thank
you
grab uh wait we're good we just need to
make a 300
300 points we just need one more order
oh yeah we made it nice one star
sick all right now for our dignity let's
try and
get this popping off it comes back
do that yeah that's easy nice
all right stick next three two one well
done yeah
[Music]
it's when you work hard together you see
the results eventually
yes practice makes is progress
true it's progressive decent
makes makes you're doing okay just keep
running from the health inspector
that's the premise of this person
no they're coming for us how about one
last
it's level four four we are gonna kill
it
we're gonna die i think not gonna kill
it unfortunately
wow sure is windy
oh sorry oh no
okay i don't know how i feel about this
now
i don't know if this is my favorite
anymore
so i need a chicken and potato
got
i got chicken ready what do i do
yeah okay so that's probably best to go
out first oh
to me to me to me do me thank you
all right so this is ready to go as well
[Music]
yeah why not that works fine too we are
i mean we've already made it quite
apparent we're not very good friends
with the health inspector so
look man you gotta do what you gotta do
all right it's i mean water's water you
get you got some you got some floaties
in it and snow it goes
wow
[Music]
i'll wash a plate i just need fries
hold on all right that's ready to go
and fry's going in fresco
this is our last chance to prove
ourselves
i could not pronounce that very well
look at this run fire wow
[Music]
oh no and back nothing can stop me now
don't let your dreams be dreamy
yeah wind's pretty strong man i'm
cleaning up these
uh nuclear plates and why is it so windy
we can have some some single chicken
and french fries out to go because
they're actually
cooking right here single chicken
oh man that one's cool
yes i got it got it
oh cool i delivered just as i always do
i deliver can't walk without being
dumped in the water because you're so
small that the
the air just uh you know
dominates you i'm prepared what are you
doing here with those guys here we go
yes got it oh yeah we for sure got that
one hello
[Music]
first try and everyone first try to
oh and team bitching kitchen does it
again good job
good job good job
as a brand new chef all right well done
team [\h__\h]
oh man i feel like i want to go into a
food coma now
and don't die from all the yeah
well i think that food coma you can
still go into a food coma even if it's
not from eating the food but from making
so much good food delicious
that's true that's a lot of standing and
running
[Music]
exactly well off we go
even though we were understaffed i think
we did quite well
yes thank you very much kiara for coming
in to help us
i'm sorry i'm sorry for the lag
no don't be sorry it was great yeah i
mean it was
again i feel like the legend of the
[\h__\h] in kitchen is that we always have
trouble in the beginning but it doesn't
last very long
it's just that's when the smooth part
comes out
exactly exactly that's when you insert
the [\h__\h] in
yes instead of just kitchen
yeah i would definitely say oh
[Music]
thanks for inviting me to your kitchen
i'm waiting for my paycheck i hope it
comes soon
yeah i did yeah yeah i don't worry about
that
all the wrong orders that we had from
your paycheck
you got to pay for that all the medical
bills from gouda jumping into the river
without floaties
you know what may actually end up
happening is that your paycheck is that
you owe us money
uh i know that that happens
that is the standard in my company you
know i don't pay
any salary to my kfp encore employees
they pay me they pay me
that's me yeah this is the modern world
this is how you do it in the modern
world
yeah that's a very solid business model
and i do admire you for that so um
nice well good to hear that and good
luck with uh good luck with kfp from
here on out um i'm sure that
afp will be a fabulous rival for
bitching kitchen i don't know if you
guys are aware but you
were uh hired by my company i
i did the signature on your part but i
knew it was okay for you so thank you
for joining the community
you're talking hey do i company a cute
uniform oh yeah yeah yeah yeah look at
my twitter banner
twitter header you're already wearing
the cute uniform
all right i'm in i changed it today put
me down
orange orange looks really good on
youtube i have to say orange
looks really good thank you but
gouda isn't quite filling out the the
vest
yet but there's still there's still some
you know maybe why are you mean
maybe you just need to eat more shrimp
sculla
what what what is she talking about i
don't get it
if i fill out the best i wouldn't be
hiding your dynamic
give gouda more shrimp she needs to grow
big and strong
eventually eventually
well
yeah i don't know what they're talking
about but anyway
i guess i'll go take a look at kiara's
banner after this question mark
yeah yeah yes yeah well
whatever it is what it is um i
appreciate as i said before i appreciate
you coming in to fill in as a manager
for the time being this is very kind of
you um
part-time manager part-time warrior
part-time idol part-time
everything yeah part time
i do not envy you even though i have
three jobs that's not nvu
hopefully one day we all don't have to
just cook anymore maybe we can just all
all just be idols
the dream isn't it chef idols
until then let's continue the bitching
kitchen huh
yes we need more practice before we're
ready for
the big stage obviously cooking
is the best practice for the big stage
yes
definitely is like a good training for
anxiety issues
yeah they go hand in hand with each
other i think
maybe possibly i don't know i need to
take a nap uh so with that being said
thank you everyone that came to watch us
in our kitchen kitchen
yes thank you
can we say it in german krishna
[Music]
you proposed the idea
yeah well the good thing is that youtube
only really picks up to swear swearing
words in english apparently but not in
german so we can definitely say it
really
really loudly with all our energy in it
in free perfection
oh my god
bye oh my god
[Music]
do
foreign