[Music]
this is
questions
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
okay
[Music]
hello
what
ah
[Music]
how's it going guys looking festive yeah
I didn't feel like taking it off I was
dressing
dressing up for a video
it's been Christmas
[Music]
hello
uh
we are here to play some Pokemon again
yay
[Music]
foreign
I've been busy because of my stupid
sudden idea to organize a whole live
English advent calendar
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
it's
um pretty much finished
I am just
uh now waiting for
submissions contributions
so it's going well yeah we can talk a
little bit later on
uh
no my goal today is not to catch Chinese
but
um I saw that it's really
easy I watched a lot of stuff
on how to catch Chinese and it's
incredibly easy but I'm not gonna waste
my time with that anyway look who I
brought into the
huh look who I brought into the team
why are the caspers for now
I thought it was two I guess I never
looked at them from the front
I'm confused
um let me update my team
[Music]
when did they what do you mean they
evolved silently
[Music]
I didn't do that I don't remember doing
that I don't remember witnessing that
[Music]
hey what do you mean they evolved
randomly
without animation
what
foreign
that's so funny
look at the Pokedex will they get more
are there like endless Evolutions yeah
how do I look at the
oh they're hiding what
[Music]
explain it's so cute
this Pokemon is pretty serious by the
way
it's somewhat Wayne what does that mean
is that good or bad
is any of this good frankly it was just
damaged out to allies
[Music]
yeah this is so cute
I need some good attacks though the only
good attack here is play around pretty
much
again
oh no
it's great and double bell yeah I can
imagine with that
I guess I gotta go here
I wish you could just go there directly
but okay here we go
Mouse hold
the book
oh
what
[Music]
the two little ones just appeared
they really did but I didn't even
restart my game it was just running
that's so cute
the group might be a family of related
Pokemon but nobody knows for sure
[Laughter]
family of four
ah katni
okay
let me update my list uh
[Music]
so we have Mouse hold
oh but the picture here has three minus
four
oh this one's this one's four
tandem Mouse will randomly evolve in
your party when over level 25 ah
it's formed with a one in 100 chance to
be a family of three
oh
fossils form is dependent on this
Evolution one in one in 100 tanimals
have a chance of evolving into a family
of three oh well it's only the looks
right it's not like damage wise or so
open image
okay I'll put the
image of
uh free I guess also this one's also in
shiny you you can literally not notice
it
it's they're just white instead of the
light blue it's a really really really
really faint yellow but
it's ridiculous like how are you
supposed to see that
so subtle yeah
okay they could they could have turned
them black or so I don't know man I
think I got rid of long boy right
because I lost hope in longboy
uh wait how do I play this game again
shut up
don't let me look what
thank you
uh yeah no long boy and these are
caspers
[Music]
because it's a couple of them
rip long boy
don't worry he's just chilling in the
sand now
[Music]
that should go
and then uh what else change the fight
just I guess vital is now evolved
and for Cocoa too I guess okay
[Music]
comes
this thing that looks funny
[Music]
pro pro color
crocolor
[Music]
Pro color
find your place where is it
below our name stay the same
there you go
box
[Music]
uh-huh
oh shiny egg
she's in crook even choosing crackers
and fight let's fight those original
name again uh
something with bread right
um
bread dog bread dog
fiddle okay I do
became
[Music]
also there's nothing after that huh a
Dax burn
yeah
look at those buns
[Music]
okay
I don't know if faito will stay forever
now that we've seen the final evolution
there's still a lot of other Pokemon
probably hopefully that I haven't seen
yet so we might kick fighter out because
uh
yeah who knows what else we will find
that looks interesting no guarantees
we're about you know
switching it out so it doesn't get
boring
okay
team this is the current team what do
you think
I mean it's not perfectly balanced but
it's
it's kind of trying its best to be
balanced
um
yeah I Wanna Give like some some
opportunities to other Pokemon
[Music]
it's been ages since I've been able to
catch between my hand
down there hopefully you can watch it
until the end
just begun they have a lot of time uh
yeah I don't have one and I don't even
have one that has a water attack but
maybe Connie can learn a lot or attack
um
put the dolphin into the team I caught
one
but I wasn't sure I got who to
replace
with the dolphin and uh what are we
doing we're going to Electra Arena so
the dolphin will be useless there anyway
I might just add the dolphin when it
seems appropriate
uh I don't know no I I got rid of
Gyarados already
uh
tricky to evolve oh that's annoying
okay and then sorry I'm just still
trying to perfectionize my tree
um I bought from the pharmacy I bought
some
not so yummy but supposedly good for
throat infections and other [\h__\h] like
that
um
mallow tea just mixing it with a lot of
honey and yeah fruit wise like I I
honestly like I understand winter time I
air is dry and all that but I've been
using my
my
humidifier constantly and
this is weird like I wake up with in a
crazy feeling in my throat and I don't
know what it is I don't think it's
normal just winter dryness I don't think
it's just that because it feels
different so I thought maybe it's the
seeping and I took a test yesterday but
it said negative so who knows I mean
sometimes you know you gotta do a couple
of them they're not always accurate
but
besides the throat pain
I mean sometimes I feel a little bit
yesterday and the day before but today
today I'm fine I think today it's just I
guess
the throat pain for now
or shop
but I'm okay I mean when I drink the tea
constantly
then I'm doing pretty well
um
foreign
mama
I've been drinking so much tea so much
my tea consumption is
insane
you're cleaning I cleaned the humidifier
but I don't know how you clean it
properly I don't know if you can
consider it clean properly but it
doesn't smell weird because like before
when I didn't clean it it had a weird
smell
so I cleaned it and now it doesn't smell
weird anymore when the air comes out so
I think that's a good sign
yes hydration
okay
also guys are mini donuts with me I got
too many donuts and I got my favorite
you know the fluffy potato chips in the
shape of bears
I got uh some kinda chocolate I got
everything here all right and I got the
Pearl candies I'm ready for a long
stream let's go ah
foreign
[Music]
I don't know it's just like sugar flavor
I guess
um I see something over there and you
might be wondering oh where is she
well
um
uh when I was playing
when I was playing off stream I felt
like
running around so and and checking if I
missed some trainers and so on so I did
that like all over and then I noticed oh
there's an island so I kind of like
jumped down there no no I went from here
I swam it looks really far but it wasn't
that far so I'm all the way to here
there was a trainer here here and some
items
and then I swam to there and then I did
all the beach [\h__\h] but and then I ran
around I ran around
here here here around the slump but I
didn't go into the slump because I felt
like I gotta leave some exploration but
it's kind of weird because there's
nothing here
in terms of
I don't know City or Arena or Titan
Pokemon there's nothing here no nothing
in all of this area
but the Pokemon are on my level and yeah
it's like I'm I think I'm supposed to
check this out but I guess you can
totally skip it and go somewhere else
um
[Music]
the area has something but it's not for
now ah okay I was thinking like maybe
it's for later but the Pokemon are On My
Level now
show hmm
I guess you have to revisit it and then
the Pokemon are super low level it's
kind of weird but yeah yeah
um I think so this is probably where I
caught my dolphin
at some point
uh
oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah
but I guess
I still didn't do enough trainers
right
that's so weird like I I fought way more
than five but I guess they counted for a
different region confusing
so I could continue exploring here
especially because of that slump or
because we're already quite over leveled
I think we could go
uh no I didn't you know what these signs
I didn't understand those were outbreaks
I thought that that just meant oh this
kind of Pokemon appear in this area
I didn't realize those were outbreaks so
the whole time people told me do shiny
hunting and and outbreaks I didn't
realize well let's let me check that
where is the outbreak
and how do I know where are the
outbreaks
how do I know I don't get it
they didn't the game didn't tell me
they need a red symbol
oh that that is that one
question mark
[Music]
yeah that's one
um
here's one here's one oh
so I heard like if you do an outbreak
cluster City you can keep on re-entering
and exiting re-entering exiting and then
that way you can keep on changing the
spawn
there's a lot of those kind of
respawning techniques that are paired
off yeah
anyway we're gonna go to that City I
think level wise I'm I'm fine I think
I'm like level 26 to 30 so
I have a feeling we're fine
oh yeah with picnic Studio I know I know
I know I saw it
I saw it guys the song it's already
[Music]
I'll be fine okay good
uh did I fight you I think I did
yes okay okay then in that case
[\h__\h] map what
you guys said something about how to
I
[Music]
hate this map so much
I hate this map like if it's just static
it would be so easy to remember get a
feeling of what is where but since it's
always like looking different it's like
I will never remember what this world
looks like
because of that
you know you can lock it but
still it sucks
okay thank you my shot let's go
and always keep an eye out for shiny
hello Berry ooh
all right
I think the music might be too quiet is
it too quiet
oh oh my God a bike
oh items
it's okay
really okay
foreign
[Music]
running over the street like that you
have to wait this is the main road and
there's like rules you know
I have foreign priority I think like I
don't have a license but I would assume
in a world like this if you come for the
south from the side you have to wait
stop once
there's no stop son even then it's like
right right
oh I guess it's gonna go around here
[Applause]
[Music]
little [\h__\h]
can I battle you you actually have
something to perfect it
huh that's what you get
for bumping into me
I also tried to catch a couple Pokemon
just for the sake of catching them for
the Pokedex
um off screen
you guys didn't see it but I didn't
just so that I can fill it up a little
bit and get those Rewards
the process of catching them is just bad
if I'm not gonna use them I just don't
feel entertained by it
hi Tower Ross
what is that
what is that oh the man ah there you go
when you turn around like that then I
Know Who You Are
from the side no idea
understandable right
order
mindset hoarding the the Bells
you wanna fight
let's fight with my tea drinkable
it's not good I can't control my power
oh my gosh it's gonna explode
she's like um that that
um Pokeball Pokemon that I don't know
exploration on us
I have that
I would be interesting if you had that
Pokemon it's a fish fish
fish do you like Stone
let me try
it's a stone effective against wall
no
didn't look effective but also not
uneffective
how about rock smash how do you like
that
that was bad
I still have to learn so much oh
[Music]
uh just a tiny bit a veil of water
you take one more or maybe just one oh
that's
I would use something super effective on
me what was that
[Music]
it could have helped you
Pokemon Db has typed as if you want to
keep that no but there's so many
like how can I not is that the shiny
the yellow thing over there
I guess what
it looks shiny and is that shiny nah
it's not seen it before I see there's so
many
[Laughter]
Lego shiny hunting
especially when it's so easy apparently
obviously I'll get a shiny then but the
the real excitement lies in finding one
randomly without even looking for it and
especially as an Entertainer as a
YouTuber
you know
it's like a legendary moment
the people I'm gonna clip it
oh my God accidentally shiny oh wow what
a locker
she's so lucky
[Music]
um
oh
that nurse will get the best of both
yeah what the heck
[Music]
I watched the video
I watched so many YouTube videos
yesterday and today I watched the video
of someone trying down I think the was
your Pearl Pearl whatever remake that
came out last year or so
oh it's the car engines
uh and trying to and it gave a Kelly
hello
gave himself a challenge of having to
catch every shiny before each gym that
you could possibly catch so
Mariah Carey it's time or even like if
that's too early for you it's less than
a month until Christmas
those markets are already open here just
saying
they're beautiful you should come
and yes it's already been the first
Advent on Sunday
the first out of four so I think
I am I'm justified in wearing this now
anyway that dude I think he said it took
him
three years to finish the challenge
and I watched the video
oh three years of shiny Pokemon
Challenge try
catch like you know let's say until the
first Arena there's maybe five different
Pokemon that you could possibly catch
but uh he has to get a shiny not a
normal Pokemon not allowed it has to be
a shiny of each one and until he catches
that he cannot move on I don't know what
his name was but I'm questioning
why why why do you even try something
like that also I don't think I have
anything effective I'm assuming it's um
Steel
and I don't I don't know what's
effective against Steel
I think the starter was also shiny yeah
Hatchet steel poison budget okay
cool a day why
[Music]
well oh well
dick is four times
but whatever it worked amazing
no more car engine for you that's such a
weird Pokemon
car engine
so the question is
no question it I guess
this is a good Pokemon it's also very
shiny even though it's not a shiny you
know what I mean look how shiny it is
you could catch it and say I caught a
shiny Pokemon
because it was actually shiny
I'll break over there let's see what it
is
[Music]
I found a mess out like a wild mag where
are they one
I'm not interested in them though
if I get a shiny if I go looking for
shiny I wanted to be a Pokemon and I
would be happy about and maybe would uh
want to use in my team
you know
oh cute one
Magnemite it's the the shiny one right
it's already shiny I don't need a shiny
of that
is that the bike is it drowning it just
fell down right in front of my eyes
drowning
no it's running in the water how do you
do that oh it can't get back up
foreign
[Music]
it's also something else that's weird
down there is that what is that a spider
that on the left
who's that
the wall oh
[Laughter]
man they seem to have endless breath on
the water they got the the diving
um skill that I don't have
good for them
yes
just everyday things oh the Firestone is
here
and now here we have a cool View
of the the big city I is it maybe the
biggest city besides the the school city
which I don't know if you can call a
city
what do you want
the lights are pretty cool
yeah pretty cool lights there oh vital
is that a shiny what
what where did you stay inside
[Music]
when does he look like so
in Utah
for one millisecond that I am not
actually able to do in reality
okay
how cute
uh what is that
ah probably ground type right
I don't think I have anything oh it is
brown okay see that makes sense
we do fighting a darkest week to
fighting okay okay
oh
big damage
[Music]
what color is the shiny Chihuahua blue
oh
okay Roost oh that's the healing move
um
that's pretty good isn't it
should I keep it
[Music]
Twitter
is that a double click
[Music]
maybe instead of protect detect I don't
use detect ever
foreign
[Music]
yeah
you know what I want to become real
strong just like missing the moments oh
cool
well you gotta eat your vegetables
she already has the almighty I'm above
you look damn
looking at me from above even though
she's so much smaller than me
that's ice maybe metal claw because I
can imagine ice breaking
[Music]
Yeah by metal
yes okay see I guess right some some of
them might congrat guests but
other things are not so obvious to me
because I feel like it could go both
ways
um
all right bye bye little girl I wish you
all the best though
was I here before
down there
I cannot recall I mean you guys won't
even know because what do you know where
I went off screen I
was right over there
okay so then I happened here
pretty sure
I even fought you didn't I all right
or laughing
are you shiny because you're lighter
than the other ones
now maybe not
[Laughter]
I feel so stupid
or even having any hope
this thing too
you're making fun of me
you know another another thought I had
today about YouTube videos
I was like
I was led to buy recommendations from
YouTube I was led to
Airline review videos
which I've seen before you guys did you
guys watch those have you watched them
before
Airline review YouTubers
no
I get them every now and then
and
I feel like some of them
are so click baby it's not even funny
like the title and the thumbnail will
say worst Flight Of My Life getting
abused by the airline crew
so much drama there and then
I watched the whole video to find the
abuse and so on
but okay sometimes there's like maybe a
little bit of trouble
[Music]
um but then most of the time it's like
worst flight ever it's just just a
decent flight or rudest Kore Airline
crew ever it's just a crew chilling
a lot of the time maybe not being like
Oh
[Music]
that look
yeah it's so click betty and then and
then and then
I don't know I don't know that some of
them are still it feels like kind of
entitled I don't get it what do you want
man
I don't know I was shaking my head the
whole time watching the video trying to
find
um
like actual
what is it
like a proof of you know really bad
things happening but
oh
it's just and then and then you know
they you know they make those videos and
they write those reviews on Instagram or
wherever like oh this was the first
my life I can't believe it drama and
then they're like surprise Pikachu face
when suddenly the crew comes up to them
or contact contacts them and they're
like can you explain to us what the
problem was and then even that doesn't
satisfy them because even that and
that's that is like oh surprise they're
now suddenly so nice to me yeah of
course they're suddenly nasty and maybe
it's not even because of your stupid
review but just because you had one bad
light out of five million flights
talk to me when you had a bomb in your
flight like me alright
[Laughter]
I don't know man click bait
click bait is too much
I don't know the story you have to watch
my streams guys
then you would know the story right
because I told it before I forgot this
is a girl's steel probably
I don't think I have anything problem
yeah I told it before
fairy still okay
do I have something
oh
you're locking me up spicy
[Music]
oh
let's see how that
oh super effective
very good good job good job chat
remember when I used
a thumbnail with thighs for my rhizo
stream well I would not say that that
was clickbait I would say that that was
100 on topic
ryza like literally with every game they
make her fives thicker they obviously
they obviously are like doing that on
purpose so
ah I think it's just part of the game
five fake fives are just part of the
game so me putting my own files on there
with Verizon flies I think there's not
clickbait cannot be considered as such
it's an insult to even say that
yeah right
yeah oh my God I saw rhiza collaboration
with a certain Godzilla game
bam in like oh really light
jealous
with quite the cleavage
[Music]
scandalous but cute
good for her
tails off is getting a cool avocado came
too what
which one
I don't think I saw that oh there's a
variety
Leela Leela is the sexiest thing I've
ever seen
yeah last clock that's a game
[Music]
what what kind of name is that last
Claudia a Claudia you guys were all
corrected to Claudia but it's Claudia
oh wow that looks like
the logo to me looks like it's like
something final fantasy-ish
[Music]
well so tails off
oh
a couple of like old school nostalgic
uh Tales of characters wow
[Music]
oh look look fun fabre
and stand I run
that's pretty cool
the cool Club
anyway
I'm a Pokemon League
Pokemon battles so far you have to
defeated seven seven already oh yeah
that's probably exactly how many I need
stomping tantrum driven by his
frustration the user attacks the target
this move's power is doubled to use his
previous move failed
okay well we have arrived
oh Chuck whoa
oh
oh yeah that thing sounds familiar from
the introduction of that character
similar style at least
funky
hey
I like it
laggy
have I always been running so slow
I felt like I've been running faster
night Vibe yeah this is cool
[\h__\h] oh
I think that's a strong bug attack
I love come on wow did you know there's
a new Pokemon game you should buy it oh
it's a sushi place that's cool
yeah yeah you see those curtains I
didn't want to go in
what do you have oh
folk art
oh my God
[Music]
it looks so delicious
oh yeah those curtains
they have those a lot in these like
Japanese stores and so on restaurants
the small ones when you walk in like
that and yeah yeah I got like I got
those because
um they were merchandise we had like
these kind of
um curtains as merchandise in that
collab Cafe in Korea and yeah I put them
up on my office door every time I walk
through that now you can kind of imagine
what that looks like
um
foreign
[Music]
I
can use my bike
[Music]
is that Pokemon
you almost super cute really oh I can't
wait to meet her
you're not cute oh socks
store just for socks you don't see that
so often actually I know them I'm not
even sure I say that a lot in Harajuku
wise glasses and I don't even have a
music pair of glasses let it boost the
power of what it's a pure to Fashion
[Music]
big Square
well not really square but it's
cool
on water oh cool wow
so modern
oh she's so pretty right the purple lady
oh she's also kind of famous
oh wait they're all I guess because
they're all the arena oh brecky that was
bricky
oh I like the advertisements exchanging
like that those are some cool
advertisements
credit card
soft drink whatever that is
credit card bricky
you know
and the Little Cakes Nice Kicks
is that where we fight
it's a cool look especially at night I
guess with the lights
foreign
[Music]
okay where where do we go to do we go to
that we need to find a building that
looks like uh
uh
the the arena building thingy right
I'm surprised there's no cutscene or so
I ran past it okay I'll come back
just will not
check out
can I jump into the water from here
I feel like I could but I don't wanna
because then I'll have trouble coming
back up
oh
cool cool cool cool
I wish more restaurants had actual
interior but the food art is like
so good
I don't know if I need to heal but I'm
just gonna do it now and refill my teeth
steaming hot
might not even have enough tea for eight
hours because I'm planning on streaming
at least seven hours because seven hours
in will be I think the release of that
new Mario movie trailer we're gonna
watch it together there's some pretty
close pretty close
it just means
it's called variations though right
because I've as far as I know that's
everything that's it
pretty close no way
if it's just variations of the school
uniforms they barely look different
from what I've seen
it's glove stock shoes yeah but I want
to change the main part otherwise it
just don't looks the same
stand extreme
yeah I'm in seven hours for Pokemon
normal
electric Terror Shard oh
that's the first time I got a terror
shard
y I wanna meet you know
I don't know
[Music]
maybe here
what is that
can I enter these buildings out
no
these look like big office spaces
bought by so many spotlights
it's not on the part of the city where
you came in
none
what do you mean
looks like we're Team galactically have
their headquarters
Team Galactic that's some old old
generation huh I
[Music]
just dropped I didn't expect you to make
it as a revive so worth it
always
function
there's so much stuff
that means Pearl Platinum uh-huh
hahaha
and okay
we
but it must be somewhere here right oh
what is that oh I mean that I was
saying that the backpack looks nice
and that's poof again
oh that's a bag of ATMs that's a post
office
some nice details here
yummy oh
found Luigi
[\h__\h] now it's raining I like the detail
that how your character you know when
it's raining
well now she doesn't do it why not
because often they will hold their arm
over their head right
oh slow
now let me see is this normal
let me leave the city
am I just too used to being on the mount
[Music]
I don't know I don't know I'm confused
foreign
now let's go back in did I really miss
it what how is it what
is that building there where I need to
go
now live India
where is iono
mini am I building on the right
the buildings all look the same here
because they're all like Office
Buildings kind of style
I'm gonna eat the donuts
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
where do you respawn ma'am
foreign
never happened ever before to me when
playing Pokemon games
that was the first
auto save right so
[Music]
um
yeah Pokemon Center
then we should be fine
[Music]
hmm
hello I'm back
sin is a good thing that I healed my
Pokemon here because if I hadn't done
that it wouldn't have saved right
I knew it ahead of time I knew that
um
okay please let me in now
oh looks good maybe yeah
I'm a psychic Pokemon
look at the back the TV screen on the
wall it's that risu Pokemon with a beard
and a cooking chef had eating a giant
cupcake
[Music]
how's the gym Journey which one are you
going for now wait seriously I'm close
by hang on I'll come say hi do you want
to fight me now you've been telling me
so often that you want to fight me and
we'll never get to fight
[Music]
another mini donut
um
you know what I find interesting
you know back in the day with old
Pokemon games
when they were still like on Game Boy or
whatever you obviously you moved you
know
like you go straight then you have to
turn and then you go left like it wasn't
smooth right you couldn't do like pretty
curves and so um
but nowadays you can do it however
NPCs like her still do it they still
move on the grid in four directions
right
I find that funny how only the only your
character is able to move properly like
a proper person but everyone else is
still stuck to the grid
I don't know maybe is it on purpose to
keep Nostalgia or I don't know is there
a reason for that
it's funny to me
uh
this is the gym you chose to be number
three huh well you're up to the
challenge for sure but like just be safe
you probably better have a pre-gym
warm-up battle with me
what if I say maybe not
I guess I'll do it
[Music]
okay let's do it right here are we
allowed to do it here
[Music]
foreign
let's do this
let's have us a fruitful battle fruitful
okay
[Music]
hell yeah
really it's not even a ball
there's a little cute dog but you can't
the floppy ears you see the Flappy ears
oh that part is so soft I really like
touching those
um ears you chose the wrong Pokemon to
start off with obviously
I feel sorry for you
and you're level 20 you look 10 levels
below me
Oh I thought
wow let me do more money
[Music]
what do you got next
hopefully a little bit higher level
[Music]
well then I'm gonna switch
Tommy's
the same Pokemon that I have but one
Evolution before I think or two
so that is electric right electric
fighting maybe
um ground
but I don't have ground what's good
against that finals
oh
uh
fairy to learn really I want to use the
cast first let's use the cast first at
least then you know customers are not so
high level yet
so we can be a little bit more on the
same
level
[Music]
wait Tommy that doesn't even look like
the first you know the second evolution
oh it's just effective
[Music]
weak
know what
I'm cute ah it's okay even from behind
look at them the little Tails and the
tippy tappy movement
and the one on the left is waving
okay I switch
at least this one I know
donut
um
[Music]
hmm
oh how your tables turn
[Music]
well I've kind of seen this before
already so
I'm not surprised but
I still don't know what to think about
it it's I guess okay
um it looked cuter when it was smaller
but don't we all don't we all hmm
you got some racialized oh [\h__\h] I didn't
expect that
you should have told me before okay I
should have expected it
of course she's gonna do it
of course but it's okay I think we could
fill one hit there
what a waste
[Music]
all right
[\h__\h] only free Pokemon
[Music]
just kind of a catch up
does she not fight agenda sure he does
no
no I didn't start again this is my third
stream
man you sure about like seven of more
than two gym badges well I have more
than two Gym badges I have
two Titan badges
right two
and
two
[Music]
uh enemy base whatever car Badgers
so yeah that's um I'm I'm pretty far
yeah I know she doesn't count it but I
think it should count because that's
pretty much like on the same level
of content
was it fruitful really how was fruitful
but pray for me okay
a challenge you can literally right now
but Champions have to be understanding
hmm
so I'll hang back and respect your time
okay sounds like an excuse to me coward
most thank you for the rest of the chat
keep on collecting badges for now and
let's battle next time rewinding to each
other at the gym
and piwala
I hope you get even stronger like wait
wait stronger
okay I will but why why are you why do
you want that and once you do you and me
can just battle our hearts right out
please can I retire already all right
time for you to whoop that gym test
thanks for this
she has no friends maybe
well but no people like her right I have
seen NPCs talk about her
right but I could imagine that like she
doesn't have many actual friends though
[Music]
I could see that
so she's really clingy onto me
[Music]
so maybe it's like you know you see
someone really popular and you think
they have a lot of friends but
well that's just from the surface in
reality some of these people they just
are pretty lonely
hmm
welcome to livingsia gym
let me register you as a challenger your
name is kiwawa
[Music]
great now in order to face gym leader
iono young first due to pass a gym desk
I wonder what it is staring in one of
her streams
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay he almost a streamer as well as gym
leader so we want you to Dazzle her
audience with your skills and rack up
those subscriptions just head outside
and you'll soon find out what you need
to do
fan service now get out there and have
fun oh
ASMR or what
no way
[Music]
ah
I did not expect that it's such an honor
to me although I am her senpai
she should it should be her honor
ladies and gentlemen's it's time for
this
come on
oh [\h__\h] I'm already being filmed
oh God she's there
what the hell
she's
hey
hey your eyeballs are mine caught in my
lecture web who's a what's it
oh I'm the gym leader here hello
[Music]
hello
it's not really her greetings
if she wants to speak to a lot of people
oh
not
[Music]
not the first rodeo yeah
shaking is she being electrified right
now by her own hair
I hope this doesn't come as too much of
a surprise but you're being Ruckus life
to the world right now smile smile say
hi to YouTube
Challenger thanks for coming out to the
lavencia gym just to see me
I'm super happy you're here but I'm this
is not a fun collab part that you have
she doesn't say [\h__\h] you almost gotta do
all the work what the [\h__\h]
I don't think this collab is ever gonna
happen again
I'm super happy in here but I'm also a
bit of a celebrity now I'm all kinds of
busy why do you have to tell me that
what do I care
supposed to do your [\h__\h] job so I
can't collab with you unless I know you
can bring in those sweet sweet View
I gotta make sure you can bring some
real passion to my stream Yahoo
and so if you want to battle me you're
gonna have to help me make this life's
Revival
he got it I have some ideas
I have a lot of ideas
if it's okay to
use those ideas in a Pokemon game I
don't think so
Natalia just can't wait to get started
well well done allow me to explain the
plan
we fell off the boat
is that her Pokemon oh no oh oh I
haven't seen him in his normal form in a
while
oh okay well what a coincidence boosting
you here haven't seen you in a long time
you guys know each other already or
something
your dude had a real aura about him when
he was walking down the street so it's
just him up for my daily out here do you
not know who he is
she really doesn't that's why she called
him Mr walks about just walking around
huh you are lots of God
does she realize he's a boomer
I'm gonna help you stream you need a
Zoomer in your stream the only they will
understand how to make things viral by
click baiting and walking into forests
where you shouldn't go into and [\h__\h]
[Music]
let's do today's challenge
we play hide and seek with Mr Walk spot
[Music]
for the good gentleman using the
Straight surveillance cameras to find in
three times and you can consider this
gym test pass eh how does this
this is not streaming content in my
opinion
so I'll call it
clemencia is Mr waxify
okay
you think that I'll save there's nothing
iffy about it or anything right
is that no I don't think so
it's a boring title though
I don't know about you but I'm ready to
go get ready to hide Mr walks about
she's cute
I feel that I own a Pokemon League for
many a past papers so I'm more than
happy to help do bear with me as I try
my best in my allocated role oh there he
goes zooming down he ran fast
just like mume you know mogus
yeah oh dab a gentleman is ready
yes I am
oh
I see him already yeah
already
ready
somewhere in this video for you trying
to open those eyes wide like a magnum
ready or not here our Challenger comes I
see him how do I
how do I
do it
there we go
[Laughter]
oh dear it seems you've found me
this is um a very easy version of Where
is Waldo
[Applause]
you're one cool kid well then before we
move on to the next round let's make
things a little more interesting you get
to have a battle with Wonderland
ah those are the jackets right
it's kind of fitting so your high school
just here long live the Yono Zone
where is the kfp hive Squad
at KFC merch where is it
I want to say it
say it looks here always intimidated
anyway I started once again with the
perfect Pokemon it seems
thank you
[Music]
can't be Supremacy
iodo's got nothing on me
ah there we go I was like where where
did my attack
that's one moment here we go
[Music]
yay was that it oh my God week
well done telling your friend though
time for a change of scenery she's got
the kyani hair by the way
now
you know coming out the boy
[Music]
the next stage for my totally rats test
everybody loves it it's the
it's the last one is once again hiding
in the feet somewhere is panic
oh I see him yes isn't he in the Pokemon
Center
is that not again
yeah how'd he get in here
oh and here I thought I'd blended into
my turn around this is quite well you
did because it's [\h__\h] bright here and
you were overly bright
on my side
actually better than before
[Applause]
oh she gave away the answer kind of I
guess so
oh
miss the last if I've been found once
again yes I know you were something
special let's spice things up again
before
oh that's brown that's right
Pokemon battle get out here book a
maniac pal
okay I got another fight
she's not too bright as she well
streamers often are not so bright look
at me
uh what is that there's fish
it's just a water
let me try one charge
okay no problem
I'm fighting it with its own weapons oh
this one has two Pokemon what's flap is
that like a um a fluffy
uh cheap Pokemon
[Music]
I want to use someone else who should I
use Electric Sheep oh wait that makes
sense because this is Electro trainer
and then
what can I use
I don't want to keep on using dacoma but
we have dig I guess that would work
anyone but Amiga
no need to change
hmm
[Music]
that's an old Pokemon
they're looking at me so nicely
oh
[Music]
my God
oh that's sweet
I'm bad
that's how it should be
never lose your path
[Applause]
and you win well Dance challenge your
friend up
[Music]
there's no stopping yet master of sticky
and master of battling you're the real
deal
oh I'm running then time for a change of
scenery where are we going
okay of course we want you
what's up
stage will be this place right here
what battles are a rating
oh I have to find him one more time I
thought we were gonna battle
wow that's pretty good
[Music]
Mama
admirable hmm
whoa
my subscriber numbers are on the right
it's like a super fast
crawling out of the ocean uh I mean
congratulations on passing my gym test
hot diggity dance
what a good time huh you had people on
the edge of this it's worldwide I bet I
could have some super red streams by
collabing with Yuki Wawa
no
that is too sweet for you from you to
say I think you should never collab with
me ever again at least not with Pokemon
version of me because she's
that means you can find things but she's
not much of a talker
so I don't recommend it but I mean if
you say so
so hey when you're ready just hit me up
and hit up my Lobby stuff they'll get
you all set up to collab with me look at
these splits I'll be ready to go
whenever
it's cute
I like her though
she is cute
interesting gym test
kind of random
she's a cool yeah she's so cute I like
her design too
everybody's got such good designs except
for the protagonists
I see you only gave your performance a
thumbs up amazing job well done no clue
gym test if not we're going to write a
challenge to generate a bit of luck
[Music]
uh oh wait I'm not writing I guess so
grounds is actually dakama is perfect
with dick because Raven resists her
Electric
but can attack effectively and then
besides that I guess
I don't know Connie
[Music]
okay well you can even go through takama
only
[Music]
better than anything else maybe
I didn't think I would go in there with
dacoma but okay
forgot about dick
what do you mean I'm muted
okay oh
[Music]
she's so cute
ladies and gentlemen
[Music]
damn her eyebrow
that must hurt
your eyeballs are mine ooh creepy caught
in my natural lamp who's a what say you
know
eyeballs remember remember the horror
story with the eyeballs from my group
hello hola ciao and bonjour
hello hello hello
[Music]
it's time for the units on everybody
thank you she's so smug too
I just gotta look into the camera
today's Challenger is flying high like a
wax
[Music]
thank you
Too Close oh he's gonna interview me how
you feeling about this battle kiwawa oh
she's so cute
um
like I can't lose hey hey we got a
Lifeline one here we had to make a
gnarly influence of Randall OH if she
only knew
alrighty then who's ready to see me kick
some butts oh oh kick my butt
Elijah
it's so pinky thanks for the pinky oh oh
she even notices it looks like y'all
getting hyped thank you monthly Electro
King
I'm waiting I'm waiting for it
I'm waiting
she said that there was no message
though
because I have to wait for a bit
why is electric King what what
let's get this show on the boat how
strong is our Challenger I don't know
let's find out together
thank you
oh cute look at her look at her
[Music]
oh thank you parsley
Mr King is the only honest you think you
think he's uh the type who would only
support iono and no one else
maybe he's a tan or she not uh
uh demo daisky kind of person
but you know I I can see if inspiration
from a lot of characters here like I
could see them having taken inspiration
from gouda because of the oversized
Parker with the long sleeves
uh and kind of I can even see La purasu
in there and the spiky teeth obviously
but then I see inspiration from Kyary
pamu with the hair
yeah
and you know streamer so obviously
um
[Music]
wait what
you know you got this what the [\h__\h]
for iono
why is everyone supporting you oh no
what about me I guess she needs to
support desperately hey
oh he's so cute
is that an electric Pokemon I don't
realize
I love the way she's so bounced in the
bag give me about a little less
Electrify all my viewer Pals
all right uh oh I actually
okay that's where she gets me dick has
no effect well well I like a surprise
like that we have Connie however for
that
it's good
[Music]
music is a bit too quiet for me like not
not in terms of volume but there should
be more going on
I feel like
ah which one is better
whatever it doesn't matter it's a one
hit anyway
[Music]
you're supposed to support me do you
understand which stream you're in
Valley booked
so now I think I'll switch that's her
main Pokemon
switch to Tacoma
wait I can see her using the the Bold
switch attack
[Music]
that was a thing for electric Pokemon
I can see her doing that yeah bye
what
let's see what she's gonna do
water guns and water
is it water electric
it's supervisor when he survive wow it
charged him
I'm impressed he survived that but if
your water is well
then oh it's just Electric
oh oh okay okay yeah it is
you wanted to use Sparks
thanks for trying I appreciate it what
you didn't even have her main Pokemon
she didn't even use the crystallizing
what else do you got
ah okay of course she they always use a
different Pokemon of a different type
and then crystallize them to Electric
but Luxio was electric as well I think
maybe an electric dark or so
in any case
not be a problem
oh yeah it's gonna be the next Pokemon
[Music]
I'm making a fool out of our Pokemon by
letting the Mr one attack
from the crowd out of nowhere
that means matches well it's gonna
become Electro so I might as well stay
oh
let me hear you say okay okay
[Music]
oh that's a cool Pokemon though
I mean I want to support her too like it
Orange
that's a heavy hat somewhere
wait oh wait it's gonna miss isn't it I
think it's gonna miss Maybe
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
oh
um
let me try Connie
that's really smart he's got the
levitating
all right
[Music]
please does this work
oh we're getting more right oh wait that
was just one
okay we just need one more hit I could
even crystallize if I wanted to
my speed Rose nice nice chill chill
chill chill chill Connie
out
I think
this should do it
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
the music got to climax just in time
it was flashy and bright as a 10 million
volt Thunderbolt friend no
she looks
looks um
not okay she's not okay
[Music]
wow she immediately recovers
you're both so strong
I hate to say it but I lost thanks for
cheering me on any who my loyal fans oh
I like the way she stands
she knows how to look good
well then what does our challenge get
for beating me the lean mean streaming
Queen
[Music]
you win
screen captures quick this will be a
shot you'll want to save in your brain
space is forever
but she's got all the filters on her
what about me yo
I look so so normal next to her yeah up
she only edited her own face man
a free Gym badges polka Pals of up to
level 35 will be easier to catch then
listen to yeah when you ask them to do
stuff too
and that's my thanks for such a sweet
pick and I'll give you a TM
[Music]
oh
you obtained what it's really
comfortable switch nice yeah there it is
their side attacks you didn't get to use
it though
Vault switch
swish swish
any of you found our electrifying battle
to be shocking go smash that subscribe
button right
you understand right your eyeballs are
mine caught in my lecture map who said
what's it you're not a supercharge
stream ER catch y'all later
[Music]
very cute
so my biggest goal for today already
accomplished let's see what more we can
do
oh oh Mommy Mommy
hello
you just defeated the gym leader yes and
your name is kiwawa if I recall
correctly tell me do you seek to become
a champion
no I don't want to be a mushroom
but a champion yes
just what I hope to hear you have a rare
Talent especially for your age
aim high great to hide So within your
reach
oh but I've gotten ahead of myself
[Music]
chair women of the Pokemon League the
organization that runs these gyms I have
marvelous lower lashes as you can see
you seem to be collecting gym badges I
suspect we'll meet again down the line
until then good day to you
good day to you too
didn't we already meet her before though
feels like she just introduced herself
to me for the first time but I feel like
I saw her already
[Music]
when I hear this music
I think of
an old K-Pop song
I think
something with
roly-poly or something like that
especially when it just started out
and rolly holy yeah from Tara tiara
am I going crazy
let me listen
yeah
tomato
so old
yes yes that's what I was reminded of if
you listen to it roly-poly roly poly
[Music]
no no no no no no
no no no no
[Music]
something like that
hey yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
also I got a message from
um
[Music]
foreign
too many messages there's lots of
planning going on
but as I said the calendar is going well
I think it will definitely launch safely
[Music]
I even bought a domain for it I didn't
tell you that yet
right
I bought a domain a website domain
so professional
honey
come out
it's making the funny sound again oh I
have no spoon oh no
[Music]
yeah
um I mean it's not being hosted on the
official whole life website because it's
just too last minute and if we wanted to
do that I guess I wouldn't all have to
be more like
I know different
[Music]
but
uh no problem because I mean
it's had its own domain so it's really
professional and cool and and yeah
um also um I'm really happy that the
other members you know I told them this
is what I want to do
I need your help please it seems like
everyone
except maybe enough
um it's very eager and and will
participate and contribute so I'm
excited yeah now I'm trying to fill up
all the days we're obviously not 25 so
uh gotta you know have some doubles and
so on but that's okay
yeah yeah
I'm glad
it's gonna be neat
every day you can come to the website
and open the door and then you won't
know who will be behind it until you
open it and it will not be able to be
opened until
um I think we're doing it I decided to
do it at uh it will be like midnight of
GMT zero
that will be the base
so yes
I have to choose one time zone as a base
[Music]
and then the other doors will be locked
until that day
[Music]
I know
um
foreign
yes
we're making sure that it's not
available beforehand that nothing will
be spoiled
and everything will be locked locked
down
before you're supposed to see it
no no it's not EST as I said GMT zero
which is usp0 the same
so I don't know when that is for EST or
so on but you can easily look it up
just look for a time zone converter and
or just wake up one day and then look on
the website and you'll probably see
something new
at UTC
what should I do next now Kubo is not
helping she's busy which is totally fine
yo
got my own team
where should I go next oh
foreign
[Music]
so either this one
or that one
left or right that's a useful content
this one
okay
[Music]
it is the steel Titan lurking steel
tights and steel mine is working an area
finger and jumping huge burrowing under
the ground is the cause of frequent
landslides
huh
what's good against Steel
[Music]
tell me tell me tell me
it's annoying to catch hopefully oh
we'll figure it out
ground fire and fighting okay easy
oh I've got more than enough of ground
fire and fighting
to give up am I here let's see
wrong button
oh no I'm not oh
[Music]
damn your buff
is she a bodybuilder
whoa
[Music]
man she's packing
intimidating okay I'm gonna close the
the donut so that I don't eat them
anymore
but I'm gonna open up the chips package
it's already open
[Music]
um
all right let's let's explore
what's up what's up
dark
stars in disguise
can I jump up there we should yes
is it the mysterious person oh no
woman
[Music]
um
so somewhere in one of the mines are you
around here we should find lurking still
Titan
rumor as it did the things to charge
really huge and real old snake
we'd think a Pokemon like that would be
easy to spot I wonder how it stays here
I can't read the codes
maybe it's super fast
I can't read
Steelix ah yes it makes so much sense
that's right there was a long snake
Pokemon with steel
that must be it
oh
is it Pokemon
um
it's Pokemon right
it's like awesome things that roll
around They Roll and Roll and Roll and
Roll
cute
[Music]
does it have an evolution because I
don't know what it would be I can't
imagine
hey Winnipeg is what
oh you bought it my favorite that is ah
he's trying to sell me the good stuff
it just becomes a bigger tumble
that's the only thing I could have
imagined but that's kind of lame but why
not
okay that's funny and you have to walk
to evolvement that's also funny
[Music]
scent stuff
also that is weak damage very weak
[Music]
let's bring in the the Pink Bird
what are you doing
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
the same Pokemon
now what is him
do I got it back now
or did it just eat my berry
[Music]
may even leave as a with a with a bird
in this one
oh this one would leave an item like a
berry burned up interesting I didn't
even realize it had that
skill
but
flamethrower because uh don't need two
of those attacks I think
[Music]
Amiga no no no no no no that was my my
starter what
that little joke cost me
I mean I didn't force you to pay but
that's not a new Pokemon right
it's from Luna
[Music]
they had like these
iron cards oh interesting region
you guys cute
oh there's many of them
a muscle car
oh my Pokemon is evolved into what
what let me see let me see what they
have my new level talking with some
target practice uh-huh
but you will be the target
not me
oh
dear
um
I was there with the wrong Pokemon
that's for sure
okay I'm gonna go to Connie
[Music]
must be a real surprise
having your tiny
tiny fish
[Music]
can't even keep it at home anymore
if you let this Pokemon out in your
in your living room
chances are
it's not gonna fit
need to have a garden or sofa drum
[Music]
more
like my Pokemon so nearly evolved it
doesn't know how to battle
I don't really know Eva I'm just letting
chat help me dude there's this skinny
goal up there how do I get there
is there a ladder
I want to see one
I have to learn how to fly or how to
climb
would be nice
I heard one here too but I guess it's on
the
no way I don't see it did I imagine it I
think I heard one
okay that was my imagination
unless
no
I think I think ideas
[Music]
oh the elephants are so cute
really cute
oh they're following
oh no never mind they don't want to go
up here
what is this a snake are you not new
right
oh the first itself on the ground
these uh what are they called again uh
gasoline
I also saw their shiny is like so
basically the same as their normal form
well that's also a difficult one gotta
be careful damp Rock oh
and number one
is the first thing I caught is hard to
spot
but in this game
you've called it
damn
good job congratulations I guess
oh speaking of fishing
I have fallen
into a huge rabbit hole and I'm enjoying
it it's like
eye opening and mind-blowing
it's not necessarily fishing videos
but it's
um
catch and cook videos and survival on a
like remote island or whatever
uh by only catching and cooking and so
on
so cool I want to do that too I want
someone to show me I was watching a [\h__\h]
ton of videos especially from one
channel
uh called Nick Frye does anyone know the
videos they were recommended to me
those videos are very very
um liked by the algorithm
okay
yeah they Trend a lot all of them have
like millions of views
but honestly kind of deserved because
the quality of those videos the way he
films them and edits them so good
so much beautiful footage with drones
and GoPro and so on you can see footage
on the water
and then he he
didn't know that there were so many ways
to kill a fish catch a fish
I didn't I mean
I don't know when you when I think of
catching a fish I think okay I guess you
you fish it with a fishing rod
but he does stuff like
um
spear fishing oh [\h__\h] why did I run into
it again
underwater
like he Dives a little bit
and then finds a fish aims at it funny
shut up
games on it and then Swoosh it's like a
gun on the water
but it's a spare and it goes so fast
and then bam you have the fish
on your spare spear spare
so cool oh so cool
and then uh
another thing was like he would go
for mud crabs oh wait he was Australian
by the way so he does this stuff in
Australia oh there's like outbreaks here
bye
he does it in Australia and so there's
apparently a lot of mud crabs
and uh
he catches them like he goes up to them
and you don't see them there were in the
mud and he really got a good eye for
them and then he he goes up to them he
pokes them to see if it's really one of
them
and then they then they come out of the
mud
and they're so big she'll speak crabs so
cute though
and they go like Snap Snap with their
big claws and apparently there's like a
illegal size that it has to have
in order to like be allowed to catch and
cook it and it's not allowed to be a
female apparently because I guess if you
take the females then
they'll have problems breeding I suppose
so that's cool that there there's these
uh minimum sizes and you have to follow
them
in order to you know not
uh [\h__\h] up Nature's will
so he always has like a like a measurer
but he kind of knows it by heart already
because he's been doing that since he's
like really small
so cool
and then he catches the mud crab from
behind
I just exploded catches it from behind
and picks it up and then throws it in a
bucket of herself and brings it to his
little cooking area where he just Cooks
it in some water and then ever eats it
like that sometimes he does some recipes
with them
that are not like the most chef-like
recipes but
it's like really really simplistic
recipes what is this Stone what can I
fight this with
his family gets to watch no he does it
alone Oh you mean the crab
fighting okay thank you
anyway it really makes me want to do
something like that because I mean I
would probably be scared of a lot of
those techniques or things but
I don't know it felt like so refreshing
to watch that
like some videos were also like 48 hours
or 72 hours alone survival in on a
remote island
um
yeah and he would like catch those
species and he knows
how she's I don't know what those fishes
are I look at the fish when I say that's
a fish but I didn't know you can eat all
of those different fish
I mean I guess you can eat all fish but
are they gonna taste good I didn't
expect so you can just take all these
fishies and they all taste good
apparently they do
I know
it's so cool
and then I also learned that
I know I learned a lot of things from
that about fish
oh I even looked at one thing he did was
like
um if he caught a fish right and then he
fillets it
at the spot
and oh
he didn't really cook it he had a lemon
with him then he'd just start squeezed
all the lemon juice
out of it
out of the lemon and and had it all over
the
the fish fillets
put it in like a little box you know
and then waited a while and with all the
lemon acid
it kind of cooked itself
[Music]
like at first it was kind of see-through
right the filet you didn't know that
either huh I didn't know that either
yeah like the the see-through meat from
the fish a while later through all of
the acid from the uh yes yes that's what
it's called um all the acid from the
lemon makes it like become white it
becomes white and then you can uh see
that it's like kind of cooked like not
really but it's kind of cooked
and then it has that refreshing lemon
taste you know lemon goes really well
with fish so this must be really good
I'm so interested in that
also this place is confusing like I have
once again no idea where I am
where did I enter up from here okay
reconsidering your opinion yes like
that's also another thing like he was
eating all these things so deliciously
like the crab and all those kind of fish
dad ah
he even cut himself some when he got
like really big Tunas
caught some really big Tunas and they
look so beautiful all these fish look so
beautiful man but he got them and then
he cut himself some fresh sashimi
dashimi
I'm like reconsidering maybe trying a
bit more fish
I'm like
so hooked I'm so hooked I want to go
adventuring I want to go diving I want
to eat some fish but I don't know I
don't want to eat octopus okay but I'm
open to eating more different types of
fish and eating them maybe even raw okay
okay okay
I'll give it another chance I'll try to
go into it with an open mind otherwise I
can't do catch and cook
I want to do it
oh he also there was one time where he
did um bow fishing
like he would shoot Arrow
but he was not so good at that
but the spear fishing seemed relatively
simple although you can imagine that the
equipment would be really expensive
spear
Britney Spears
both pushing both pushing both fishing
hard yeah
but I would be so scared like doesn't
Australia have like
so many dangerous
things everywhere and how do you know
that the fish is okay to eat how do you
know but I guess with fish it's less
um
like there's way more fish that you can
eat than fish that you can't eat maybe
most of the time what he was able to
fish was like cods and uh
I know what they were all called anymore
smoked salmon smoked salmon is all right
yeah I've had smoked salmon before not
my favorite thing but like a little bit
is fine
fishing date with someone I don't know
anyone who can fish I asked my mom she
said no she can't be she never fished
I don't know do I know anyone who can
finish
which which whole life member is
confident in fishing like not in the
game but an actual real life um
[Music]
wait I should do more of this all the
battles why do I never do that because I
don't know what works against one but
does that work
[Music]
I need those materials
there's a bird can you can can you use
your fire on that
good job
Cali really
has iron legs experience but it's enough
to like lead someone to do it I wonder
foreign
[Applause]
spikes well
damage when they switch out okay
oh we're almost at the Pokemon Center
over there
fight that thing there you go
good move for competitive yeah
where am I
oh down there uh-huh
which is
that way
all right I'm on it
German version
I wonder I wonder there's like
apparently there's a lot of YouTube
channels who do that survival challenges
and and catch and cook but obviously I
live in Austria so a catch and cook it's
it's not very it doesn't have the same
kind of vibe especially like
um
well we have lakes okay but they're not
remote at all there's it's just there's
no such place where it really makes
sense like that I mean okay okay I guess
you can do a catch a cook catch and cook
at a lake if the goal is not necessarily
to be so Unga Bunga you know
but if you want to be
and
have that survival Vibe and It's gotta
be somewhere else it's gotta be
somewhere else
to civilize yeah that's what I mean yeah
I mean thank God but
it's also really cool to see the those
kind of like
Australian
in the middle of Dover kind of Vibes
apparently it's like close to click
Queensland or so that footage
where he films it
but there's just like big big big areas
of nothing so cool
lots of mud and lots of ocean a lot of
the desert kind of place
all of us is basically Australia is
basically in the middle of nowhere yeah
oh it's uh it's okay should I be in here
is this recommendable
maze
come here hello
thank God that's a dead end
any day now
it's good to expand your food taste yeah
I'm like really inspired and I didn't
know that crabs they they only are
orange
you know because when you cook them they
turn orange
before he
put the crabs into the cooking boiling
water
they were not all
good
I mean I I thought that obviously not
all crabs are orange but they want to
eat they're always somehow orange aren't
they
oh shut up you think you're all so smart
now once again don't you but you didn't
know the thing about the ceviche with
the lemon
you didn't know Dad
taught you
I taught you that just now
remember
some piece of chicken I don't know what
works against Hypno what about
[Music]
how about we try this one
oh dark works it is super effective okay
I wanted to lower his special attack
because I thought he'd probably attacks
obsession
am I right
what he copied my changes whatever I
don't care
[Music]
she's Peruvian oh really it sounds so
French
ceviche
[Applause]
[Music]
chicken we just think before I could
shut up
app
s
ah that was great about special junk
yeah nice so at least something
but why are there so many Pokemon here
what the [\h__\h]
crap
so aggressive
let me try to catch you
stay up lie let's try Pokeball you
probably don't want it though not gonna
stay in Mario
that would be too easy
almost had it though
I'm feeling a little overpowered
wait you're not you're not so weak
either for me
try this
um
oh couldn't move nice
one more
I might lose my starter here if I
oh I bought yeah
oh
here's a low catch rate really
I don't want to all the Battle of my
boyfriend I'm doing this because I need
to catch some Pokemon too you know
take this take it take it
no I'm not not playing a nice look I'm
just saying that it's kind of annoying
when they die you know
disabled what does that do
I'll buy the last attack probably that I
used
anywhere let me [\h__\h] catch you
[Music]
it appeared to be cold
thank God that's so weak
my audio is slight delayed
really
[Music]
little [\h__\h]
why are you acting like that
stop wasting my Pokeballs please
it didn't have to be you right I could
have just chosen any other Pokemon to
catch for the sake of
having caught more Pokemon
but I chose you so can you please choose
me back thank you
you said like 10 balls on them
oh fine don't level up Amino level up
hmm
wow
game
wait I don't think I want that attack
I choose Kiwa thank you
hmm
I'm expecting any Evolutions
um
only Sparks I guess
only Sparks
I think
so good so salty
hmm
who are you fighting
oh go get him go get him can get them
too and the big ones
oh
wow impressive
sweat oh we literally catching his sweat
running around confused
and these are these dragon Pokemon and
those are really really old right
like second gen or so maybe or third gen
you look old
it's okay
no sorry sorry I didn't mean to do that
but you actually killed it damn
um let me try some stuff
like a little gremlin
is a good Pokemon I think
wait what is that Ah that's um
weird black Gekko Pokemon
all right what's over here oh an exit
that's not where I came from right
so bright
good morning
is that where I came from
wait a half
crackling sound
legendary wow
uh I'm confused where am I
what oh
I should probably go back
on
what's in this hole
oh
crystallized um Psy Everly
pretty
[Music]
I take it
one F what's that time
isn't it
it's just a psychic
level 50.
oh no yeah
we have it
I'll take those anyway
[Music]
good that she doesn't mind
I was gonna catch her but oh well she's
just chilling
don't be so mad
don't be so mad please but in case you
guys want a dots I feel like that's like
a a fixed spawn point probably
so there you go that's where you get her
and
uh
[Music]
caught it an hour ago oh
we are very close to where I am
okay
um
delay
okay
totally
like getting lost here
as per usual
oh
let's fight you oh are you doing nothing
with the daisies He Loves Me He Loves Me
Not
I used to do stuff like that too and
then always kind of manipulate Myself by
um picking more because it's really tiny
leaves so you usually pick more anyway
that you should it's not one by one and
then pick more so that I would end it
the positive ending that I wanted anyway
ah
[Music]
dolphin
do I have something
oh only electric well obviously duh
I'm taking control of my life
[Music]
I don't know if it wasn't though the
outcome I wanted then I would just take
another Daisy and do it all over again
oh my God
shape your life the way you wanted to be
[Music]
hmm
yeah I thought it would be something
like that on
um
[Music]
you know what you're right yeah I kind
of assumed so yeah yeah yeah I mean of
course
oh
um
where was I planning to go
was I planning to go there
no
I'm eating potato chips I'm sorry I
can't stop myself
okay stop
foreign
Ty to control me yeah
nothing no one here to stop me
only I can stop myself
oh is this actually the right way to go
to the
title no I guess not it's too far away
still
oh but it's like a mountain
can we get much higher
yes
anymore
or is that the same level oh I guess it
is
okay okay okay that way that way I just
go toward the gold kiwawa how hard can
it be
thank you
oh hello
[Music]
are you a fan of sad songs or not so
much my personal opinion is they're okay
I guess well
Sparks
the sad version of Sparks
take a potato chip and eat it
that sounds familiar
oh Death Note okay then it's not
familiar to me
[Music]
but not curious about it I want to see
it
[Music]
hmm
sounded like she was singing Mad World
but not quite
well
what the [\h__\h]
is that that is not a Steelix
it's a
what what's wrong with its mouth
[Music]
is it supposed to be like that
[\h__\h]
but that's not really is it a new
Pokemon then I guess so far
wait the the bird one was a new one the
coming one I guess it's always a new one
huh
wait wait
so it couldn't have been a Steelix all
the Titan Pokemons are near Pokemon
I really found
going whoa
do I have to land on it
I just did
that what what is that
they look kind of
feel so stupid looking
so stupid looking
[Music]
um fighting is effective right
so stupid the other two I found looked
really good but this one is stupid
what
so mad I'm so angry
mm-hmm okay
time to follow the tsundere warm
oh I'm gonna make this path
are you sad
don't leave
oh
plot time
Ivan where are you when I need you
the Titan orphan began eating something
no snaps that
yes I bend it down
like a pin-up girl
that's the lurking steel touch and it's
well it sure is long
I think our little friend might even be
fights to you now after eating those
herbs
we're gonna need to do is to give a
Chihuahua okay are you gonna try to
actually build help this time
it's such a stupid Pokemon maybe it
looks less stupid when it's smaller like
it's normal size but
support Pokemon thingy doesn't matter
how big an opponent is Victory is gonna
taste so good season by what
hmm
I wouldn't tell oh [\h__\h] I bought it
[Music]
I don't know
is it steel bug or is it just steel it
looks so the
bit it looks like uh like a sock puppet
it's like a sock puppet the face the big
mouth oh no it looks like an automatona
oh the face also looks like an
automotive
[Music]
is related to Kermit
I'm very dirty but cute no only the face
only the eyes are cute that's it
but that doesn't help that doesn't save
it
I don't like this one
we did it you will wait to go little
buddy
don't patronize me because you get a
good look at his face though I didn't
expect a Titan to be such a little cutie
[Music]
but it's really just the face
I'll bet if we go in here we'll find
more of that Urban mystical I had before
it did before let's go find it before
that thing can regroup
I'm sure there's some here too
uh-huh
have you guys noticed it's always the
same cave
oh it's the same cave
oh how is that possible are they all
connected is this one portal where we
travel through without noticing and we
always end up in the same cave and when
we leave you know we go back to the
original world
but I'm also only in the first cave
the besides the green stuff there was I
think
pink or some kind of other color right
the second one had green so I thought
okay it's green on green I guess but but
since then you see now it's green green
Green again there's no extra color why
was just the first one a different color
salty Urban mystica
that would be good I think
enough successful search We're Gonna
Roll and then let's see what does the
book have to say helps of aching hands
and feet good for neuropathy anonymous
muscle weakness oh
that's good for me I want lots please
give me I'm not gonna give any to my um
bike this time because I need that for
myself
what you make what you make
sandwich again
but that was good but happy with this
one yes we are
[Music]
gonna give him uh hello fresh
description yes
[Music]
um
do I have a choice
[Music]
what if I say this is mine do I just not
get the skill
here's the sensor
[Music]
does he just take it away from me
probably
[Music]
it looks sad
oh
do we just couldn't like forever
continue like this
endless Circle okay
once again the illusion of choice thanks
Pokemon
this is what we call
manipulation of the Mind
of the human brain
[Music]
you want to make people happy by giving
them the illusion of choice but you
still want to have them so much in
control that there is actually no choice
sheesh
but I'm happy for your doggle
very happy for your dog
[Music]
can we see him from the front please
don't care about you Arvin
wanna see the dog go oh it's nothing for
me
[Music]
it's so mean
every time every time that gets me
[Music]
what we could jump higher how high I
kind of expected something else what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
this book seems to be benefiting from
the herbs too I guess it's all sort of
way
[Music]
can we jump much higher
oh yeah foreign
obviously
we knew that so does that mean the
Titans layer isn't really some kind of
treasure horde or whatever it's just a
pantry where the Titan keeps its food
[Music]
it spoke
yes
did a wolf
why would I say no
right I'm not imagining things
[Music]
it's burping it sounds like he's just
burping from the food
she she did I knew I wasn't just hearing
things
oh my boy stiff was my best brother
it's been so long
[Music]
feel emotional again
is definitely getting better ever since
I teamed up with me a good things keep
happening but we still got two more webs
to go hope you'll stick it out until
we're done
yes I will hey
[Music]
no that would be terrible if it had a
time limit and the dog of wood
perish no
that would just be too painful
oh hello this is Sada
I decide that corridon has regained more
of its original Power while you're
riding upon it it seems it can now jump
higher if you press and hold the B
button
okay
please continue to take good care of
good items
Hannah set it out how high how high how
high
oh
oh okay okay yeah I guess it's a bit
higher was that really necessary are
they ever gonna teach me climbing though
is that a little bit more helpful I feel
like
hmm
who
yeah we'll get it later oh
that is okay that is much cuter um but I
barely got to see it can you come back
oh
it's cute
it's gone
okay so you only jump higher when you
press the B button like longer okay okay
actually that you can still do normal
jumps
I like it this way
no
okay where are we going next door
let's decide guys
I I think I'll once again do like more
solo exploration around here like some
more trainers I think that's why I have
something to play off screen that I'm
enjoying and
um you know waste my time with
and we don't spend too much time you
know because it's a long game
where should I go next the next title or
maybe this
oh
another gym Water Gym
electron
so I've got Electro we good we're good
we're good
okay
so I think I have to start out here
that's too close it
I'm not ready for the Titan oh
okay do I have to grind
I was gonna grind off screen but oh well
okay kind of like a 45 damn wait after
the gym are you supposed to go to the
Titan or supposed to go to I guess
another one of those uh uh bases
poisonous okay good okay okay
[Music]
poison personal ground
good or
yes oh I guessed it bye I know I just
felt like if you bury the poison on the
ground everything will be okay
makes sense right
all right
let's go where's the red path
[Music]
you know what we need we haven't had any
Evolution for a while we should have
gotten like a dark
Eevee evolution would have been so cool
I think
but we already have done
enough power all right and then German
we're okay
and maybe poison
still I don't really think we need
that's kind of weird
but poison would be sick
in my opinion
Dragon yeah dragon dragon could be cool
uh
bug I guess we don't have but bug I also
would say would be kind of weird and
unnecessary
all right
don't need everything because
something's just a weird ghost yes ghost
like a kind of see-through
floating
whoa that would be nice
bug it sounds interesting I mean in the
end you can make everything work I guess
fighting even no thank you I feel like
there's like way too many fighting types
especially with starters like the fire
starters why are they always fire and
fighting why
it's so boring it's like oh I can't
think of anything so I guess I'll add
some fighting to it because essentially
what you do with the Pokemon you fight
not very original
oh they stop the trend really it still
feels like it's going on to me
maybe it was a little bit less though
that's good
[Music]
what is this
what
kids
take me down with me
good balance of specifying Darkness
oh oh I think that's a good Pokemon
isn't it I forgot what it's called
oh what is this path
nice jump
oh
is that where I came from
wait
that's a camp
surely it's not the only path wait how
do you
no am I even allowed to go through there
or do I have to go for the Asado desert
oh this one I already did Crush
really
so is that the right path
why did I lose my voice just there I
guess I could
let's go
through there as well
that was a good Pokemon yeah yeah I
think so too
I remember that being a popular choice
that's their own road but then I would
have missed this trainer
what you got what you got
a black Pokemon
oh yeah I need to say hi to the Pokemon
Center yes yes okay
does this work
super effective to but oh it's normal oh
so fighting is super effective to normal
okay okay
what is normal super effective towards
because it feels like barely anything
I can't think of anything nothing
that's so shitty why would you have
why would you have a normal Pokemon
so sad
[Music]
immune to ghosts
I've got good moves
[Music]
all right this one if we didn't activate
it yet it's now activated also
and I get your reward I love the
trainers all right let's go
what was that
what what
was that
it's kind of fun
[Laughter]
[Music]
lucky egg
lucky egg there's so many lucky eggs in
the channel and the stream chats I mean
chateau
hey get your lucky egg and you are a
lucky egg
Ah that's the one that we did um
but I don't think we went here before
[Music]
Ah that's that's it
foreign
[Music]
Brewing until I'm Reborn
oh
is it hot are you feeling very hot and
bubbly
you're looking very delicious I
shouldn't do a little snake this one's
not very heavy but it works
it works
[Music]
I want to switch just so that we have
some variety but alukuda is a fish right
okay but I don't always want to use the
same Pokemon
but okay
[Music]
the cop goes from Louie's magic oh my
God you're kind of right
that's weird says we find that
similarity here
[Music]
in the grass type yeah grab some water
um
we never have we have never of those
yeah never
grass or
uh water
even as a move
nothing could probably give something to
some of them though it's a story come on
sweet I want to try catching it I
actually like this one
but I'm guessing it has no Evolution it
would be nice if it had a pre-evolution
as a baby or something like that
bye bubble bubble
they're rare how do I not kick it maybe
with a wing attack
I mean I'm 14 levels above but
or or something that's
actually not very effective
[Music]
uh so the only
stuff is dark
when you attack your fingers well not
kill it hopefully hopefully come on
that's good
I wasn't sure because we're like 14
levels above
uh do we have like something fitting
[Music]
water bug type is there no like ball for
flying Pokemon
[Music]
effective the lower the level of the
white Pokemon so this one would be
effective too right
compared to what level I am or just in
general
[Music]
work
trying again doll
[Music]
we'll try again with the same one
get a bonus on level 30 or less
[Music]
here
hi why Pokemon why
[Music]
I know I know I should use better balls
but I don't care I have so many normal
pokeballs I'm gonna
try them anyway
[Music]
which really doesn't like the Pokeball
at all it didn't even consider it okay
here you go great ball there you go
hope you're happy now
and we have pink
Bomb Bird gear
[Music]
you think you're all so smart with that
pun right flying dark
dark it was using Stone attacks all the
time somehow I expected
something like that
[Music]
cool Pokemon
but not gonna use it at least not now
oh oh the standing version
image kind of cool
hello
so up and about are you here to rest
your time Pokemon yes I'm very tired
please give hug and blanket and hot
chocolate milk
thank you
I hear I hear the Gimme ghoul it's right
there
you know my brother is also incredibly
even more than me perhaps into chalky
milk
he bought some chalky milk
um
why is that from here
don't jump don't jump oh it's an
elevator
bought some chocolate milk when he was
taking care of my apartment and then
when I came back there was still a lot
of leftovers so now I'm drinking the
chalky milk
here and there wow what is this place
it's like an oasis
oh you can like cool down in the water
here
oh and all the walls wow this is like um
Dubai airport Style
I know you guys been to Dubai airport
before but uh there's like this this
huge
waterfall
I don't know which terminal but I
have to pass through there often
when I fly to Japan with um
an airline that passes through there
it's huge the whole airport is just
insane
so insane and so flashy
okay
where is
oh you know what I'm gonna look at the
hats we've probably got like so much
money
let's see if we can buy something for
lunch I guess
oh but it's
so long looking
beanies I don't really like beanies what
about Square cups
they look huge on my head
they look too big
Oh I thought it was an actual bucket
[Music]
oh the purple one looks good with my
eyes that are also purple see
well I don't really like bucket hats to
be honest
[Music]
space
now
cool but I don't like any of this
[Music]
foreign
do they have different hats in the shops
of different cities
sleep talk
like Cali
[Music]
yeah they do okay I gotta check out some
more
next time
let's look at the backpacks okay
and around oh interesting
they are like so Square it's kind of
weird like I have one big box inside
[Music]
are they all the same
this one is like
looks like skeleton hands
probably not really no I don't like the
shape of them
[Music]
glasses I don't want glasses in general
that seems to be almost dead when others
oh that's also not something to wear
okay
okay then
sorry to disappoint you guys I tried to
shop but
interestingly this is uh
a Pokemon game where I'm not interested
in shopping at all in the other recent
coupled Pokemon games
I love dressing up and going through the
shops but
but here not at all
the market later is much more fun while
can I take off my school uniform later
that would be amazing
let's activate them
hook up Center or have I been here
before is this the same where I've been
before nah
[Music]
and I'm not being able to change like
the top and the bottom it's just
did I find any of the trainers zero okay
okay okay again okay okay thank you
check you know
I guess it's my first time here
I like the city
um
I like designing the theme of it
it's water even though it's in the
middle of the desert
so they made it kind of like an oasis
Style
[Music]
checking out the Footwear
engineer boots
[Music]
dress shoes
oh oh I saw a shop the other day that
sells all like shoes and other things
like that
really old school
but I love it okay that didn't look so
possible anymore but once it has
these like two different colors it looks
really old school
oh okay meanwhile it's so bright so over
overly bright oh socks and sandals
not something that I would do like that
[Music]
nah
[Laughter]
not like that
not when there's an open toe
that's just a crime wait you can wear
flip-flops of the socks
are we wearing those Japanese kimono
socks with you know the little gap
between the big thumb and the the other
ones
those socks
they're kind of funny to wear
hmm
[Music]
no
I can't but can you take off your socks
in the game
oh why do I I want to leave
[Music]
yeah Tabby socks would work I guess
yes you can okay
I have to wait for it to come down first
foreign
did I run by the gym building again or
did I not reach it yet
[Music]
wait the way they write down those
prices
looks exactly like in Japan
exactly like a Japanese supermarket
funny
the font and the writing the color the
way they place it there
very much so oh socks
but
I want to
[\h__\h]
wrap it tap
[Music]
oh more socks
if you have over knee socks we can start
talking do they have over knee socks
oh they have tights
now I hate the pattern ew
ew
oh I can switch the other season
uniforms
um I think this one's still
the best
[Music]
oh this one's closed okay
left on the Deep pad
I think I looked at it before and I
decided this one's the best
yeah
oh God
I like the jacket at least
[Applause]
it's kind of jackets that's
just so lame
um
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no at least not on a girl
like me
no no those puppies well that's no no no
no
if you're cold then wear a hole jacket
and then maybe I'll open the zipper
we'll just rip off the arms
wow
that's so true
ah here's my destination
[Music]
oh my God
wait
we got away how am I supposed to return
this to him now oh
could you give it to him hmm
and I I know what's coming
I know it of course you are a gym
Challenger that big man just left this
kufu leader of the Costco refer to him
oh he has a bit of a chat like sorry to
him and today he's run out to the market
without his wallet it'll be a big
struggle about it that's why you coming
gym Challenger could you please take off
as well to him
yeah yes
oh you're too kind because I obviously
can't leave this place right now
here's just one of them counting on you
oh
why is it not water Pokemon themed
that must be his last Pokemon that he
terrestrializes into a water Pokemon
there are many dangerous Pokemon into
this desert oh we're going to the desert
he ran off into the desert
[Music]
in general probably right check inside
where'd he go did he go off to buy some
bread
oh but I can't find him in here
what do you got
oh ingredients
[Music]
oh I want a sandwich
no one that I've been to before
[Music]
why did it just change angles a second
time
[Music]
we're gonna keep go let me see maybe
it's on the map
yeah
oh he's there
right that's kind of my thing
ah so we have to go for the desert
to get to him
damn he was so eager what is he going to
buy
fish
for dinner or maybe he should too catch
and cook
do it yourself
DIY DIY
DIY no let me just jump why do I have to
take your elevator there's no fall
damage anyway
okay okay
[Music]
with the railings I could jump
oh well
so empty
it's not the cactus Pokemon so cute
try fighting some stuff can you fight
that one
nice
[Music]
Pokemon does it only take as a reference
what type my Pokemon is or also which
attacks which type of attacks my Pokemon
has
hype and level
okay
well it seems to be working Amica is
just all around there that works for
everything and damn the sandstorm
oh snake is on the move
I see you
oh
you did it
cute oh my God it's kind of disturbing
my view though can we stop it
level up let's go
there
[Music]
but that new Pokemon that you know the
Titan one it reminds me of long boy like
kind of similar just one is steel
and one is
water
they're both the same color even in that
form
[Music]
they both cook out from the bottom and
there are long boys
don't you like
long voice poking from the bottom of the
ground
killed
something about it is just so cute I get
it I get it
but it reminds me of those
um which I think what is the reference
of the long boy reminds me of that
animal
that we know
sand or whatever I think in in
the ocean though
[Music]
heels are they called Garden Hills
really
well I don't know what they're actually
called it ones I wonder what do I mean
to look it up
can you move away from that huh
that's nice
Garden kale no I don't need a I don't
mean a barnacle Barnacles ew
reminds me of all the Barnacles that I
saw in the Maldives
[Music]
is that you
it's a robo ostrich what the [\h__\h]
what Robo but also kind of balloony
he almost
the opposite right gives you those vibes
it's new but it's not a Pokemon another
not a robot
I mean I don't really
have an interest in it
you know the level 40 damn I need to
grind huh
let's see
kind of have a similar body shape like
my dirt
yeah
oh wow that doesn't do [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
oh okay how about
wing attack while you're flying to oh
dear
[Music]
oh
come on oh
what do I have what's strong against
psychic
ah congratulations
thank you for supporting dark bug ghost
whoa
perfect
Santa Dogo it's been a while since I
used the dog
[Music]
what are you gonna do what are you gonna
do when the dog comes for you oh it's
effective but
still not much damage
we need stronger attacks
should I try to catch it I guess why not
[Music]
maybe another lick and then it's in the
red hope for you this link was kind of
weaker
okay good good that's what I expected
para from that
let's go
okay let's just hope we get it with one
Pokeball
there's one just one just one
[Music]
up yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean it wasn't
red I'm paralyzed what you gonna do
ain't got no choice
oh sword stands oh that's a pretty
strong buff
that one not that we need it because
we're already freaking strong but
I'll put it in there instead of fighting
hmm
[Music]
let's go that's so long two years
psychic it immobilizes with bathing
damage sucking power from his large eyes
despite his appearance it has a vicious
temperament
I gotta say that's a weird design it's
like a verb that stole a Lady Gaga wig
and also rated
um Daisy's closet and decided to rip up
her dress and wear it on her butt
oh no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
all right it looks like Daisy's dress on
their back
my pretty Daisy is now naked wait is
that is
[Music]
no way that tiny thing
color wise it makes a bit sense I guess
but it's that tiny thing it's
pre-evolution
never expect that never never I just
realized because it was lined up right
next to it in the Pokedex
foreign
[Music]
unbelievable
my brother puts his head in the sand
the ostrich
they do that
I don't know about the Pokemon I have in
the front
[Music]
but we are only at three hours
okay at least we have full HP
even though it was only a normal
effective
it's okay I'll stay in I just need one
more hit
stay in
here
I'm feeling most of you okay
this is the fruit
[Music]
natural stack what the [\h__\h] is that
what is that
knackle stack
rock ah that thing oh oh dear
what what we'll do it what do I stand
out
a pickaxe or so
fighting oh Amiga is dead
I'm glad we have taco mom with arm press
[Applause]
I hope it will really take you only one
punch let's see oh cute in that form
it's cute
one
one attack as one punch so this is still
one punch don't worry one more command
nice song
good job
four times no it was one punch okay it
counts as one attack
that is I think a snake but I don't know
what
I was just staying
[Music]
hoping that
was a snake there you go
never fought this one before though
no it's okay poison ah poison yeah yeah
making a lot of sense right now
[Music]
that one's also old
by the way do you like guys like the
little decorations on my hair I
um was looking for my resource folder
and I found all the stuff I had from
last Christmas season all the
all the three decorations I still had
them
so yeah
I think we're gonna be wearing them and
some others throughout the whole winter
who is this
you will oh is there a Titan Pokemon
here oh the quaking Earth Titan oh I
wasn't planning on going there I think
it's too strong
Khan's been shaking on and off oh
earthquake
okay I'm sorry my throat hurt I can't
can't wait
yeah more decorations and you guys are
welcome if you want you can make um
hello it's this bird again
you can make a
some some hats or scarves for the little
birds the lovey-dovey love birds
at the top of my head I posted a hashtag
care of props
on my
um Twitter in a little video
we have to give them something to wear
otherwise oh there's that Pokemon
oh
otherwise they might freeze
[Music]
oh
you are new
are you a stinky bag
ground or is it ground or a stone I
wonder
[Music]
whoa
I was so weak
it's only bug then
[Music]
okay stop with that [\h__\h] that's so too
much
always takes so much time then maybe
Rock tomb will actually
rocks really hard yeah yeah
bug Stone pie like that to be honest or
or bug ground
would have made so much sense
the sparkling
oh let's see
[Music]
skipping some
half I guess
I'll check out what I missed another
time
unless I need maybe some whoa
is that where the Titan is
no
doesn't seem so
what that place looks really cool but I
need to heal at the poker Center first
let me let me go heal
oh that one is the foreign
[Music]
that honestly I I would not feel
this one's also difficult as a shiny
because I think it's just like inverted
colors but I was gonna say the Minecraft
Pokemon yo you could just place it in a
Minecraft world and it would feel
just
natural
[Music]
wait you can hear me right
are you gonna heal me
yes yes thank you thank you
I needed that
got a new Evolution yeah I forgot about
that
didn't they get a neck extension or
something like that
that's actually so cool yeah I like
girafatic in general but isn't it like
cycle
[Music]
oh a hoodie oh
I prefer the indoors me too but now I
want to go outdoors and do some
um patch and cook please teach me how
somebody teach me how
I need a boat
I need a spare gun I need diving
equipment
I need so much stuff
[Music]
I only have things that's all I got
Pokemon I know it's also really old but
back in the day I think it was one of
the cutest ones
[Music]
one of your favorites
some classic
nostalgic one
me so elegantly the way he claps
and he just continues he's like making a
beat for me to dance like that
hey why
I just started dancing keep it going
keep it going oh
little dragon all right
[Music]
this one's also really cool big ears
bats
[Music]
come back
another bubble Bubble Dragon
or dinosaur
[Music]
s
has a nice nice shiny well not like I
will ever get to see it
foreign
[Music]
what type is it
I think if I put another Pokemon in my
team
be one of the new ones
China
help oh I'm getting mobbed by that bad
put the holes on its own
show me show me
so that's how that looked like you did
that on your own also what the [\h__\h] is
that
a new Pokemon
a toddler and what
is that supposed to be
it is Neil okay
what is that
[Music]
you said
and I swear and it doesn't look like a
whale has an interesting mouth shape
[Music]
why is it here
it should be in the water
but I guess okay it was caught but you
know oh
[Music]
don't be so sad
anyway you as the little kid should not
be all the way out here alone
what if someone happens something
happens to you no one's gonna find you
because you're like hidden in this cave
foreign
[Music]
oh
okay then let's try to
kill them directly or or catch it it's
so cute when it's small but they grow up
so fast don't they
just grow up so fast oh no don't kill it
[Music]
that's one thing I know there's
so and they're cute but I want new
Pokemon
[Music]
but I'll try to catch it
just for the sake of catching it also
try to catch you because you're cute
yes
[Music]
no I have a curse on me I cannot make
friends because I just
strong I'm too powerful air slash
75 95
oh
but like this one's uh
this one's this one this one's physical
and now onto the other one
special
but no
it is hard because it's a special snake
how do you guys know which one is like
better for my Pokemon
no win
that one's a strong one
no I want to fall on you
me
come find me come fast me
it's like a dog who wants to play with
Chihuahua really desperately wants to
play
if you want to watch you she does not
want
level 50.
oh that one might be here yes
if it's the evolution of the Dragon I
already saw it it was just one
25 years of Pokemon experience
day
ah what what's with the Cherry Berry
I'm gonna kill you but at least this
one's two level higher than the other
one maybe
no you know what I'll do a double kick
strong
perfect
let's try
that's cool that's the one in the dark
places right
here we go Natsu
flying dragon
it's flying dragons
[Music]
oh cool Leo
it is
oh actually
if we kick out our other flying Pokemon
eventually I wouldn't mind replacing it
with this one because at least this one
has
dragon with it
[Music]
oh this one's on the cave but it's dark
it evolves late
maybe we can find the evolution
somewhere and then just catch that one
eventually
48 wow that's really late
[Music]
oh it's perfect we just had a dragon
Pokemon and now we get dragon pulse
oh those things
yeah
yeah I could have reached it
[Music]
was it for later I'm pretty sure
probably have to activate all of them
all over the world
and then those weird doors will probably
open
and then I don't know what will be
behind it though that will be the
interesting part
[Music]
but
even though they're scattered everywhere
I have yet to find so many is that a
shiny
mahita or whatever in the background
I don't care about you
I feel like I'm so shiny
I I feel like I saw it
makuhita or self
[Music]
are you sure guys are you sure are you
very very sure
what color is the shiny matajita
because it looks very shiny to me
I only saw on the heads
okay
and it was white
kind of like
uh silver not that one
not that one in the back I didn't mean
that one
um
[Music]
of course it wasn't one anyway
I have a fresh delivery it's a robin
soon
Spirit jump oh
let's switch
no one didn't get a shiny yet
don't ask me
oh [\h__\h]
okay I'll switch wait I wanna use
caspers
never use catfish
[Music]
isn't this the smartest choice anyway
hmm
oh my God you guys told me to use the
dog but I'm smarter for once but
bringing in caspers
[Music]
this is a weak very attack but
yay excellent place
I deserve a head patch for that confirm
smarter than chance yeah now you are the
boyfriend you forgot about my little
caspers how dare you how can you forget
about caspers
we have to I know they're tiny but we
have to consider their existence and
Implement them a little bit more
[Music]
otherwise you're gonna be sad and run
away
we don't want that
why is it always Emily what the [\h__\h]
Evie
why is it always dumb
[Music]
should I jump
yeah
can I already like push them in I think
so
oh pull them out I guess
for pink
I say we're already are doing some work
for future Chihuahua future siwa will
thank us you're welcome future Chihuahua
I did it with a pleasure oh
no it's running away
I I tend to say the German names of
those
Pokemon because you know
back in the day I played it in German
[Laughter]
oh yeah that sounds like casserole
[Music]
I hear it
I hear what I can't see ah
oh there's like magical music there
so poke what are you looking at
[Music]
oh I don't give I don't um
not like collecting them because I need
them so desperately just collecting them
for the sake of collecting them
foreign
[Music]
man
are we reaching it soon
ER
[Music]
I'm just gonna
ignore everything and just go straight
to it
for you several casserole no no no no no
no no no oh
there he is I thought I had to go into
the city he's wearing Crocs
Bolton balloons
where in the world
water goes he's got
double double
layers of eyebrows eyebrows
it's got double layers
and what's a big bottle bro
something fierce but you don't care
[Music]
would strong pretty little flowers where
where the world can I go to find more
like you
is that another supposed to be some
accent wait they're both monobrows
[Laughter]
oh
emotional hair is very special
oh shoot I need to get down to the
market oh
foreign
[Music]
are you looking for
can I check
something
[Music]
let the attacks
do we have nothing for you
this is
oh
like this Pokemon
is made for assistance in double fights
huh
or I just generally online fights
because all it learns are these shitty
attacks that I can't really make use of
hmm
yeah yeah yeah
foreign
I want to give it something to make it a
bit more useful though
a TM for it will you
tell me if you think there's something
good
[Music]
see we don't have a plant attack anyway
something like this might be nice
it can learn that actually
only Power 50 though
um
flying we don't really need flying we
have flying off someone else
[Music]
trailer sounds good you have a bullet
suit
yeah but isn't that kind of weak
um
yeah no step but coverage at least
I'm charged
laying under
50 isn't terrible yeah oh we should
teach you
both switch anyway
nope
right
um but instead of what we maybe could
get rid of arm for us because we have
our bird
but I'm thrust is stab so maybe get rid
of metal claw
it was we have been using arm for us a
lot and dig as well
charge but then we can only ever do a
lecture attack if we want to switch
that's kind of lame
oh should I just not use it
[Music]
um physical attacker okay that's an
argument
that I will take
ah the mice can learn dig
that makes sense it will be kind of cute
and then we can teach uh dakuma
something else
oh wait but let's see uh that hits five
times
[Music]
that's the one it could learn right
uh
okay I just looked at the power of 25
and I just ignored it
ah
rain from doko
so I'm gonna teach it bullet seed for
now
hello hello who's rating me
what you know
what do you mean you're not right I'm
confused
I think she fell in love with me
and then I kinda also want to teach a
dick unless I find something more
interesting
[Music]
um
let me sing one more time
foreign
Hyper Beam and
attack so it's stab
but the user can't move on the next turn
[Music]
is bad
what about Giga Impact oh can also not
move on the next turn
surf oh no one can learn surf
Heatwave
[Music]
sandwich ah
Dragon Balls that's so cool stuff Rock
oh
Tailwind Willow Wisp
[Music]
spikes No Rest uh
I was asleep for two turns
oh
stomping tantrum is that maybe better
than
is that better than digging
I mean not that dakuma can learn it but
I'm gonna teach it to someone else
and then it is
okay then that could be our our ground
coverage and then dakaba can learn
something else who would I who should I
teach this
I mean take us good because we disappear
for around and we don't get hit it's
kind of good kind of cool
um
big is better
effectively they get 40.
true
[Music]
don't need it for now
not me
wife
I need to buy TMs
you know what we'll go to a shop
and then I said no I thought you were a
trainer we'll go to the shop and buy a
15 TM
[Music]
I'm fighting
wait the NPC is just a ghost and the
ball is floating
wow thank you
here let me let me give you a quick bow
you're so cute
it would be funny if they could learn
Dragon pools yeah
I think that was my first one on NPC is
not coming back to me
we developed patches weren't even down
you wouldn't grow
all the pink is bald spots
because of its electricity oh that's
really embarrassing why did you tell me
that I'm sure flaffy has like confidence
issues and feels very
embarrassed about that
I I think I would have preferred to not
know that
naked scene
Flappy can actually learn Dragon Balls
oh that's interesting
powerful
I like this Pokemon it's funny
the mouth is so big
maybe this can kill because we're so
over leveled yes okay
no I don't want all of the Pokedex but
I'm just okay what is coming
I'm just trying to
oh that's pretty
I'm just trying to you know get the
minimum
for the
Pokedex Rewards or maybe the minimum is
everything but I want to get a good
amount you know
oh [\h__\h] that's weak I don't know I I
wasn't sure what to choose
when you guys need to tell me fast
on you
cool
you're lucky little [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh Connie level up
The Rose
so I'm not the only one who thinks that
sounds like casserole
[Music]
all right poker Center
I'm coming
oh one more trainer but the light
oh
oh she kind of like
[Music]
she pimped her bike
I don't think that's normal
[Music]
that one's actually been
uh customized yeah that's so weird
it's so weird
[Music]
doesn't that hurt the Pokemon of screws
right or what are they using hot glue
that also hurts
so weird
like surgery
[Music]
I already got the price just for taking
care of four of them [\h__\h] a sash oh
that's nice
uh-huh
it will ensure my survival and is surely
an important item for this look
challenges
[Music]
oh that looks like dominant actually the
package is 100
and let me go and find them I have to go
to an idol meeting soon very soon
foreign
[Music]
okay
one of the coolest burps you like that
one
I don't know
it's the visuals of that verb so much
there's a lot of other verbs that I feel
like
are
better looking
but you probably don't only look at the
visuals
you also consider the skills right
which makes me kind of shallow I guess
oh
yeah
[Music]
the vault
is Thunderbolt not pretty decent
all right let's enter the city
this road this path
makes me want to play City skylines
looks like a city skylines path
[Music]
all right what kind of place is this
yodie's houses this looks like such a
fake house
cute the pink one looks fake though I
don't know what it is about it but it
looks
I don't know made out of paper or
something oh oh
it's on the boat station thingy a port
oh oh there he is I didn't realize I ran
right into him
oh did we lose a win where in the world
um
[Music]
where in the world is my wallet I got it
I got it
of all my world I won't be able to get
today's hot item it will get brought up
by someone else
[Music]
I'll run and look for it right now oh
he's got fans too huh
what do you want I'll make Clovis in the
middle of some super duper important
ingredient buying
and we are thinking about trying to
interrupt and then I has
will you battle me and that will count
as the gym challenge then and we just
skip that
no way
you will have to stop me
because I wanna talk to him and he's
also a bit
[Music]
okay
what a douchebag
these are so important
I she could have just said
if albertare this was able to speak she
could have just said I have the wallet
[Music]
and I think then you know
we wouldn't have to deal with this
but okay
the drama for content
uh
[Music]
feeding him more satisfying hyper boys
the type of voice
that's pretty strong is this attack that
people said he will learn later and it's
pretty strong
90 power
that's pretty good
it's better than Echo voice
not this one but it works for now okay
okay
yeah it's better than a good voice thank
God
clauncher
uh
what is that
and why do we have two Pokemon
water oh makes sense makes sense what do
I have against one Energy electric
[Music]
oh what did he lose his other claw
oh it looks like he's missing one did
someone rip it off
too much to yes
how much tea to try to keep my throat
like somewhat
away from dying
uh
[Music]
and it's an actual type of crap they
only have one is that like a like a gene
problem they have or so
dang it that backfire and you know it
was empty too
oh step right up and tell me which other
workers over over here
oh my God for the same since kids got
something to say to y'all I couldn't
stop it because I suck I'm useless
why do you have to say that like
why are you adding that what can I do
for you
I have your wallet
we returned Cooper's wallet
oh my God unbelievable my normal stuff
is turned out here to bring it to me
that's a huge help thanks for coming all
this way
my Christmas
too I hope we didn't bother you too much
there's something here with Porter
Marina the auction that we really want
to get our hands on so as you can
imagine we're both a bit worked up to
find it forgot in my wallet
you want me
I need a batch or what
no way
that looks like Urban mystical
legendary walk on my seaweed looks like
I guess it's not
legendary welcome
no I don't want this
oh I don't have to touch it I can see
it's gonna just bring a texture of see
we talk full of nutrients just look at
it
yes it looks
very beautiful
oh we could just reload you're trying so
brilliantly I wouldn't reach pressure
Robo something look straight out of the
ocean I need to get me some of that
at least you could if you want to tell
us weird to coast guard for Jimmy
because on YouTube smarts and just the
perfect place to taste you get the
winning bid on the seaweed for this old
man
oh okay
do I know
already know the agent out to Fox Chase
is such a young age yeah I learned it
from um
um Wind Waker
14 points for the auction be smart with
it and when there's old men and seaweed
okay fifty thousand what if I just bid
the full ah he's probably gonna let me
keep the rest
so I would want to bid a bit lower but
let's see are we gonna unlock bid
against each other or do I just get one
chance
can I like correct myself
ten thousand
don't begin
[Music]
000. oh
yeah
but it's too easy really that's your
freaking challenge
what
foreign
yeah well I guess it was so easy for me
because of um
Wind Waker
you did better than me you paid less
than me oh maybe because I I didn't
um bid the first time so they could uh
not go that much higher
you guys probably beat the first time
oh I did better than you oh well wow wow
I also didn't pay the first time and
paid 40K oh
how how come
anyway
yes you can have the seaweed I'm not
into seaweed anyway I hope you're
feeling low it's the same but if I fail
to get my hands on it thank you so much
if there's any other money I gave your
lips yeah yeah of course I can keep it I
know that
okay and then we go
real quick okay I will go to you and
then have the battle all right but I go
take a I go meeting I'll be right back
[Music]
foreign
he's over my shoulder
no
sure
foreign
by the way right next to me I have my
humidifier running on
high speed
but I don't know if it's really helping
my humidifier also I'm feeling a bit
cold let me wear this
and fluffy
nothing nothing cardigan
this movie's still jumping on fireplaces
no no no no I
today I opened the balcony just because
I wanted to put out my
um Advent wreath
and I was
first I I logged out it's moving so that
she wouldn't be able to go to the
balcony and I could in carefully put out
the the Advent wreath and then
I was like okay okay let's see
I am I um carried her outside and had a
really tight grasp on here I just wanted
her to get a little bit of fresh air but
under my control
um
just for a little bit
but I was under perfect control don't
worry
she was seemingly very eager to
explore on her own but I stabbed her
uh I was just gonna say like too bad we
can't go into the houses but we can oh
not this one though only that one
only that one we can go inside
what about the other ones
hello let me in
this house designs are so tacky
okay only that one house they probably
kind of missed that one someone should
tell them
it's not gonna be me
[Music]
this this place is kind of cool
I like this place nice beach with no
people oh we got it all to ourselves
pretty the water is so pretty oh
wait free
wasn't always just two
is that the final evolution
[Music]
oh fish
oh was it always free I already forgot
[Music]
no trainers here or what
is going on
this bird is so funny because when it
has its its wings like inside
they were like so angled
Ohio
random shiny what the [\h__\h] also wow
wow look at this big bird
[Music]
it's all right so intimidating
that's the one with the random move
right
I wonder if I can give that to the
caspers
because metronome itself is normal right
do you always get stab on it done if you
have a normal Pokemon
no matter if the move that comes out is
not normal
oh okay I know what what it's so funny
hmm
I think I want to give it to caspers
let's see if we can
foreign
why not normal
no that would be so funny
I don't want to give it to Dr mom
what I'm already out of air what the
[\h__\h] out of water
it's beautiful so sparkly but it's
probably also level 50.
seems like there's a couple of these
that are like in fixed spots and always
love 40 or 50 or so right
are useful for next gym but I doubt that
I can catch it
we have that come up but let's take a
look
if it lets me oh I'll talk to check oh I
didn't realize uh L2 what
what L2
is that l
[Music]
what I can't I don't know
okay it's not happening
that ain't happening no
it will crush me it will crush me and
tear me apart and eat me like hot wings
but it's only that Pokemon right
what is this big Stone no it's a trainer
good night
can I not do the big jump from the water
because that doesn't feel very big to me
how do I get up there
oh yeah is there an opening somewhere
ah over there
all right this time oh
hello and welcome I'm not full energy as
our usual normally um
because my throat is in pain
hi again hello
wow that's so funny because just
yesterday
it just yesterday I was watching some of
her stream archive
and I was thinking yo that voice is so
cute why is she not in whole life
English
[Laughter]
just yesterday I was thinking that
it's so funny I knew it sounded familiar
to me
yeah
yeah I don't know I think I I found
ah
if you're on Twitter or YouTube
algorithm I don't know then I was
curious because his design was kind of
cute
voice is like oh whoa it's so cute
no no problem
you killed please audition for hollow
life English
please
where's the train of that engine stop
[\h__\h]
out there
why is he in such a weird spot
[Music]
oh come on
are you gonna bamboozle me and not
actually use one or Pokemon
well thank you for reading
a cutie pie
holy
clothini with Pony Club sounds like the
pop 45
[Laughter]
sounds like the the Pokemon the polygon
Pokemon
fish is it water dragon
[Music]
if it's water maybe I still have a
chance but yup it it's got just one
Pokemon somehow we should be able to
take him down
only dragon uh okay fairy
is it fairy then
we have we have faito and caspers
metal claw fairy or eyes
and football too
very Ice Dragon Eyes we don't have any
eyes
okay let's try a fight though yeah bye
at least it's fairy type too so it's
stab and
hopefully like resists some [\h__\h]
don't give up yet that's a beautiful
Pokemon it's so popular
and welcome to the gym it tells us all
right we do terrestrialize for I feel
like the first time since the beginning
of the game just for better odds of
surviving
come on come on come on come on
come on
hey can we do it this would be so
impressive there are actually 10 levels
above us
[Music]
show me what you get
show him what you got though
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] mom
let's go let's go
whoa
what I did not expect one hit
I wonder how much he would have done
without terrestrializing
impressive
Get Wrecked
[Laughter]
okay
now
dumb wet snack no
no a good snack
honey in my tea honey honey double stab
yeah I know
but still
10 levels above but we're lucky lucky
lucky I should get away from here
because I'm obviously not supposed to be
here he didn't even have a black box
so let's go back to where we were
supposed to go to the arena fight I
don't know why I went here I got
distracted this game just distracts you
so easily
um
it's just one shot someone yeah so I'm
not supposed to be 10 levels above
they're not supposed to be 10 lives
above ah if anything I'm supposed to
beat 10 levels above
because I'm just over leveled but oh
yeah hi no let me catch you
mm-hmm
I hope it builds very enticing
it's like
I feel like the world in our sales our
chaos was also super big
well sir I already have it it's also
super big but
um it felt like I I had control over
where I was going and I knew where I
needed and wanted to go and
I didn't get so distracted
um
as someone who
gets like OCD conflicts if I don't check
out every area and I think almost all
Pokemon players have that issue
um
it feels very
anxiety inducing
to have such a big world that's just
like where everything looks the same in
in each area like the desert area
everything looks the same
then you don't know where you are when
you're supposed to go you lose yourself
and you're not sure like oh I need to go
to Every Corner because otherwise I'm
gonna miss something even the tiniest
item
so even though that's supposedly awesome
to have a big open world
I feel like there could have been a
better way of doing it
so that we don't feel so freaking lost
you know
I don't know maybe maybe it's
good this way
[Music]
um
and I don't know how one would improve
it anyway
hmm
I feel like even an Elven ring I felt
less lost
because the world felt more like it gave
me points where I
kind of knew where I was and
Uber challenge is the word that I'm
looking for but another question maybe
not even nowhere
[Music]
landmarks and landmarks and
I just don't know
environment is just
not so confusing
it was also Grace I told you where to go
[Music]
okay Santa first oh
is there one up here I got small
[Music]
I mean I'm just heal on myself
so
I hope that we are no
shouldn't activate unless I stand on it
[Music]
has always been good at that kind of
stuff
yeah probably yeah so I guess this is
the first attempt at an open world so
um
it's cool though to have a big open
world obviously it's really cool
is that nimona's brother
I'm just thinking because of the colors
and the way the hair spikes not the
right one the left one the middle one
kind of makes sense or sister or so
no okay
[Music]
um
I forgot what voice he had
you appear to be progressing well on
your gym circuit
oh oh wow
you see on you I like the suspenders on
me no I also like your bootsies and your
tie and your hair wow
this person's got Style
what's this about is this that kid I've
been hearing so much about
whoa the way he walks
I don't know that's something about him
hey kiddo I heard you like way too good
at battling yeah
no no I'm really not that good
[Music]
oh flat like Ina
um
call me flat
how insulting
this this has its its upsides tool you
know no need to play humble anyway about
your skills I'm sure you're good
you've come this far after all
this young lady you would be really cool
he smiles I see it
also the the
not that only girls can have um earrings
but that kind of with the tiny tiny tiny
eyelashes on the edges makes her look
more feminine
okay
[Music]
what if one of them impressed me a bit
more as a as a guy I think
that's me Rika here at your service
okay but the more I look at her the more
she's Charming me and fascinating me
and hey I know I'm pretty but no need to
give it why I
I'm not getting intimidated or anything
I don't know what you're talking about
she's a little far for what
but like my oh
a member of the elite four oh they're
like interesting introducing them to me
one by one
what I wasn't trying to be funny
[Music]
anyway
um
tell you something kiddo you look fun
like interesting at a glance anyway
oh she's cool I
love naturally she's one of our
academies of Team students
oh
yeah that's exiled
what battles you'll face at these gyms
really ratchet up the farther you go
indeed your average trainer abundance to
challenge and roughly this very point
uh-huh probably because they just got
absolutely spanked by that wet snake the
blue wet snake that we just met
but not you kiddo right yeah that's
right I survived I survived hey
see you when you hit the champion
assessment you show these gems what
you've got
um
I like the shoes
best of Fortunes to you oh I see I see
you still have the hairstyle from your
daughter
two minutes will lower your attack yes
she's intimidating me on y'all all right
Water Gym
our second gym today
and then we're probably gonna do another
uh base
I don't know what to call them camp
[Music]
you're welcome girl
let's challenge him
for court
wandering into this room when I was
barely of 11 20 and it was badly oh no
so I guess you kind of stayed on the
left side thinking that you have to go
up there but no left right left right
left right it is kind of team star base
oh
[Music]
I like the city really
want grandma
oh here it comes
he's so cute
from the from the white blue
stuff I'm kind of getting grease Vibes
but that's really the only thing that
gives me grease Vibes but wait kufu
the Greek island isn't it
tomato
maybe it is a reference to Greece
colorful
close enough I wonder if that's a
reference
I mean his name is probably different
than the other languages of the game
hmm
but like
um I could see it I could kind of see it
so sorry everybody we've got some
business to take care of his gym leader
real quick look you know
cough all right coffee was awesome in
Japan as well yeah hmm
well who knows we will never know
I'm keeping someone waiting YouTube
please forgive me I need to do this
first okay
it's got a cool design
not as much as uh
the other little ones but this one's
cool too
we step right up I've been waiting for
you no I've been waiting for you
it will help over import America
[Music]
the legendary seaweed I can make some
real quality loot dishes with it
but don't expect me to go easy on you in
the battle here
all right let's see what challenge you
got for me
dog should we battle we're buying and
chilling at my gym we better learn a
more traditional sense moves and tactics
ever change against the Raging Sea a
mysterious full course of what that
Pokemon don't try to eat them though
um but I want to catch and cook
can I catch your Pokemon and then cook
it no why
why is it to learn
let's do this
aha
I already forgot the type but we thought
it before so at least the game will tell
me uh how to deal with it
to go easy on YouTube because of that
model breaker
will you break them out what does that
mean
okay well charge the problem is we're
still doing a lot of damage to ourselves
with World Challenge
and we've got to use it a lot because
it's our only Electro movement oh it is
really a lot of damage
okay that's like one fourth what trio
oh is that the the long boys
oh the nice day
[Applause]
the pink long boys
I wonder if I could like a section of
something else
it's not and it's not going for like
switching now though
well we'll survive
too
much time do you get a fourth one
Pokemon
won't break all small break allows your
Pokemon to ignore abilities oh
okay I cannot type
[Music]
you only had four
right yeah but once you go to Ino before
him okay what level is this stuff birdie
what level where iona's Pokemon
his own thing oh
foreign
Pokemon were lower but he has one
Pokemon left
that is weird it's like they forgot like
he's supposed to have one more but they
forgot to add it like a bug
oh maybe I should have pressed a lot
uh well
we're fine
oh one hits bill
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm
it's happening
[Music]
to a crocodile cute cute
I like it uh this way more than it was
than what what it looked like just
before
but it's cute when it's on the ground
like this
um
and the fire wait
[Music]
oh it's like a little cool down here
oh my God why
on the fire the moving fire like clouds
that's coming out of its mouth look
really cool too
I like it
looks like a clown hey
but the bird was so cute and it kind of
feels like it's showing him the way
oh I want to see like how it's like
animated does the verb do anything
fire ghost
cool oh there you go the favorite bird
changes shape when skeletons sings What
rumor has it that the bird was born when
the fireball on skeletor's head gained a
soul
fire bones head ah the egg
[Music]
that makes so much sense too
oh it has like a little companion
oh I'm happy with this
[Music]
origin story
torch song that sounds special that's
that's the thing where you said it's
gonna sing Oh I wanna see that
we have to take it 80 hundred
oh I was supposed to use a special
attack
uh
should I just get rid of like round
foreign
okay
I want to say I want to use it right
away
[Laughter]
[Music]
Lois is refreshing as the air at the
morning marketing I'm just like a little
helpless Margie Corp to you flopping
around all willy newly
you could be good I tell you what a
great catch you uh just like a monster
Fisher you're held on tight till the
last second and really Victor are you
gonna give me a fishing rod
you should give me a fishing rod item
then all Pokemon games have a fishing
rod
I don't have one yet
does this game have one
we write a good photo together
okay what pause
[Music]
freaking cute dork
oh
yeah I take photos like that too
sometimes
but with normally I try to have like a
building on my hands like the Eiffel
Tower so instead of a person but yeah
[Laughter]
we forward you purchasing your position
Pokemon develop up to level 40 will be
easier to catch on the list to your
window
and fix let me throw this into his extra
special boulders
chilling water
we need a lot of Pokemon sound oh why do
we have the dolphin come back to see me
again now here
I like you
you're fun this is sweet
[Music]
let's go say something on fire hell yeah
I'm in setting the moon on fire uh I
mean her Pokemon
her cat
you wanna fight
yeah yeah that puts you four boxes and
now right man that's awesome can't
believe you hover through your gym
Journey already your efforts are bearing
so much fruit so quickly I want to make
fruit salad out of you now let's try it
come on eh but never mind I put together
my team of Pokemon specifically to take
on the gym leader dang it
we're not family I want to do it under
the best possible conditions what a
freaking excuse why
which means this time I've gotta ask for
a rain check
week
so disappointing
yeah let's get it
[Music]
he knows I'm too strong
yeah could be but
she has to
go through that accept it
a lot of stuff
there oh
yo those are really hard to find do you
get hints for where they are later on or
do you have to just look for them
no you don't get hints
[Music]
what is this Sandstorm again what the
hell
was just looking them up oh I cheated
and so our next goal would be him
or her
this person
possibly because you guys said it will
be another base ideally
okay
I mean just poison right
well
let me read Atticus is of middling
strength among the team star bosses the
descendant of ninjas or so he believes
he likes to dress apart and use fancy
speech and poison skills to toy her foes
mm-hmm
interesting okay
poison
actually the light I have like all the
bases and so on additionally to the gym
gives them the opportunity to really get
as many
like types out of the way as possible
because if you do gyms only then
you obviously can't cover every type
hmm
okay
we got the best of almost all worlds
and I guess the Titans kind of also
represent a type
right
oh they will cover it oh okay okay there
you go so that's perfect that's actually
pretty smart
nice
because before wasn't it so that
um depending on which type of the game
you bought of the two you have different
gyms as well
so like ice instead of another one or so
but here they're all the same no matter
which Edition you buy
right
that stays the same I think okay you get
all of it oh something for everything
oh that was just sort of Shield oh I
kind of thought it was a thing for
everything
seems are almost always the same in both
versions oh I kind of wish it became a
thing I
[Music]
think the way they did it here makes
sense because they have such a big open
world so they can do so much with it
make good use with it anyway we have to
go on the opposite side of the world
again
ah damn it
here so the closest I can get is La
vincia huh
didn't I explore this area
I didn't say hello to any Pokemon Center
also gonna tighten your ear first hmm
which one is like lower level
s 45
and and poison
[Music]
Furniture well then it's obviously
poison yo what are you guys talking
about why you you want to see me die
why are you suggesting for me to go to
Titan when it's level 45 I mean I could
probably still take him down but
like
like if we try to keep a certain logical
order
then
[Music]
first
chosen guy and we've already had a Titan
today anyway
but no base yet so I think it's about
time
oh I didn't fight you yet when you're a
difficult trainer
if you don't look it up you get really
[\h__\h]
Pandora
I could probably still one hit you but
it's fun connection
let's go
[Music]
purpose on the head now wasn't it on the
snooze before
[Music]
but why did it become a stick
for a moment was that a buckle is that
normal
well I want to see it again this is sick
move
and I said
it's a microphone okay it kind of looks
like that okay
uh I just I'm just gonna do it again
because I want to see it again
this is the song So it turns into a
microphone okay
see we could have we could have taken
them down
[Music]
the more you use torches on this one I
am because I upped my physical uh
whatever right
a special attack that's what I meant
[Music]
oh my God I think
it was really a good choice that we
chose to stay there
looking at this little bird
it's meant to be
[Music]
hey hey
nice thanks for being my test object
I was actually even weaker than normal
because of the rain
but
no match for me
oh there's an ice terrestrialized thingy
there
oh
on the hill
I don't want to see what it is
or is it inside no it's outside
oh yeah
sandstone
Sandstone nice okay from here oh
I know my not not crystallized but you
know what I mean the rate
[Music]
oh there we go
who is it
oh [\h__\h]
I thought you were a TM because you were
so yellow
please don't explode thank you
smart strike
this attack never misses
it's a steel attack
that color looks like Steel
not the first one to make the mistake oh
yo nice landing
I was pressing a
are you a little [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
thunderstorm oh I got so many of those
stones now
I'm preach
Oh Oh I thought you were shiny
would be funny if it actually was and I
just ran away from it
ah
warm
holy cowly rolly rolly Coley
yeah I saw that but it was like so far
away and I needed to go somewhere else
that's why I didn't activate it
oh homo
here is already finished with the
Pokemon game
we're here already
did it all
oh
so many I mean this one
in particular but
wow hunting Chinese now
oh you just got it on Saturday and take
your time
finished poking them two days ago wow
old school cable color look at one I
want to do it because like cut off on
the software that we use has Kpop songs
but only old ones anyway
are you a normal time
that's normal
so it's not like I really have a choice
to sing
uh newer ones anyway
[Music]
I saw you after all to work
what what
I'll switch to playing oh
wait what's gum shoes what is that
oh just do aren't you also normal oh
let's go
I remembered something I think this one
I'll actually remember
forever
and learn something and I think it's
staying in my head
still alive
foreign
thank you for
ingraining engraving it into my memory
both the chat and that lady
why can you not let me fight you
you bunked I want to run into you but it
doesn't even disappear normally it would
right like it would like try to go into
the ground
box don't go
why are you being like this
I want to find you
look at you
okay you stupid
okay keys
[Music]
all right I forgive you
know
[Music]
I kissed the weird warm
oh
my Pokemon is too big for the screen
I should switch it down but I'll do it
the next time
[Music]
warm still here worm you don't want to
go anywhere you see I told you you know
when you want to get caught by me how
about I just
release you from your suffering here
oh
it doesn't recognize it
okay I give up
oh
[Music]
probably because that was so close it
was the game fought it was in the ground
like when I walked away
it counted it as being outside again
maybe
we released it from its suffering
from the endless loop
foreign
oh it's right there
it's a forest
morning morning
hello
there's this what
what
oh yeah oh they painted the trees looks
cool
I wonder if the trees had any say in it
though
hi claveo
and I've told you the name's Clyde
please don't forget it now let's pick up
a conversation from where we left off
before as I mentioned I joined operation
Starfall to resolve a sticker situation
and to find out the reasons behind the
team stars all the behavior above all I
want to know why students in keemstar
have stopped coming to school
and just like Casio Bay I want the team
to dispense for good constraining
operation Starfall with you I've already
had some succession opening up a
dialogue of Team star and I think I'm
starting to understand things more
clearly
but I don't have enough information just
yet that's why I want to speak with
students from Team Stars other squads as
well if you intend to take on another
base know that you can count on me for
backup
till then see you around kiwawa well he
was speaking so fast what's up with him
he has no time or what
yeah it's talking so fast
it's got some work to do I suppose
okay the tree thing is kind of cool
that makes this Forest at least
different from other forests
I don't like
well I haven't seen maybe that's that
dude's Pokemon
the
evolved form of that monkey
still haven't seen its evolved form
I think
he's cute okay kind of came kind of cute
kind of cute kind of cute kind of cute
kind of cute kind of cute I didn't like
it when I first saw the trainer but now
seeing it in game
never mind I don't like it after
I take it back
for a moment I thought I liked it
now I don't like them
it could have been cuter
but it's a
in fear it's a cute monkey that paints
things it's painting the trees
[Music]
that's pretty cute
in theory it's cute
it's a [\h__\h] monkey
shiny
what it's not a shiny
it looks like this
the [\h__\h]
and I thought it was like purple oh
[Music]
no I didn't think it was the monkey I
just thought it was originally like a
different color
shiny is blue green
okay
where am I
oh cute
oh I watch the random video that was
really old but it had many millions of
views because of the algorithm even
though it was filmed badly but it was
just an Australian guy randomly stopping
on the road because
uh really kariki mate yeah he found some
koala Mama carrying a koala baby uh
he called a Barbie I think
yeah it was cute he was just telling the
it was telling the koala to go our way
and he even kind of like touched it
to make it go away which you really felt
the Australian Nest to him
because normally they I think the koalas
they often
um
you know they look very nice and sweet
but they actually can attack you
yeah normally you should not try to get
so close to them
yeah
you really like it was awesome no I
don't know why it's just been
recommended to me a lot over the past
two days
yeah their wishes aren't they although
in this case they were so sweet they
looked so sweet and cuddly and it was so
cute
koala was literally just on the back of
the Mummy like a backpack so cute
he's looking at a dude I'm not cool
and then he's like you gotta go away
little Barbie or so he said something
like that
but they wouldn't move
and then he kind of blinked Loki touched
them
and then they moved and they just
politely walked away you would think
they're Canadian
no they were not brown bears definitely
not
[Music]
I want to think that myself the Nutty
Squad Take me to do an articles
that includes you I don't care I'm not
leaving till you let me talk to Don
articles
give me a Breaky little donut
people over there seem to be arguing
about something what do you want to do
it's kind of the same
[Music]
okay
I didn't think groundwork first team
star newbies would be just much of a
tour
it's got nice loafers yo they're so
clean and what you would think if you're
in the middle of a forest all day every
day
as a grant just like messing around
you would not be able to keep your
loafers so cleanly white
I wonder you're so perfectly white even
on the Soles
why are they so white
why are they so much no no way he
polishes them every day
it doesn't seem like a person who does
that
[Music]
why are they so wide they look so pretty
oh my God they're beautiful actually
those kind of loafers Japanese school
loafer kind of shoes I have uh over my
lifetime I've had a couple of those
but they're always black
or brown I've never seen them in white
before
pretty
I'm like oh God why am I so fascinated
by his shoes
what are those
[Music]
hold on Mr Grant I think this girl might
be cute
oh oh I'm famous
stop you guys should not be pushing my
ego like that
would keep stuff
your pants will be raining now I'm the
one who's reigning
[Music]
I know it
oh boy this ain't good the real rest of
the base is still asleep since we were
up last night playing video games
and polishing your shoes right
boiled Bridge kid
who goes golfing on the weekend with
their daddy
[Music]
it doesn't suit him like his whole image
makes no sense
[Music]
like he's acting all cool and high and
mighty now
but when he goes back home
to his family he's like the good boy
who wears the the cocky cocky pants and
has the
the sweater tied over his shoulders
around his neck
and his dad is so proud of him but he
doesn't know that he does this because
he wants to get out of his chair you
know he wants to be different he doesn't
want to live that perfect life anymore
somehow he thinks that so he comes here
to Rebel a little bit yeah I'm I'm
adding a lot of back lore again to
random NPCs
yeah all of that because of the shoes
yes yes yes yes
stop judging people Chihuahua
[Music]
[\h__\h] stem
I'm just trying to give them more
personality by giving them lore
therefore also making them more
important you know behind this NPC there
might be
Soul a soul that's caught in there
and it just does not have any purpose
and it's crying it's suffering from
having no purpose
I must give them purpose
it's like those toys in the toy store at
Christmas
where the unpopular toys just no one
looked the kids just don't look at them
and at night time when the shop is
closed the toys come to life
and they're just so sad for not being
bought for not having a purpose
for not being able to make a child happy
[Music]
this is just the same thing
what you're gonna find me now
[Music]
oh can we do a double plot element no
but no he really left a small kid on all
alone here
Bring It On are you gonna use poison
Pokemon too
[Music]
look at him why is he
letting himself be ruined by
these evil evil Rebellion Rebels
that looks like a jungle actually
or like uh
um not a jungle but um
a call Michael
what's the bun
but normally you know they have
different colors so this is kind of
green so it just has some
some food color
in it to make it green
[Music]
bikini bun
like the nicoman and the pizza man and
once you get from the convenience store
I don't know what I'm talking about
anymore just please just don't listen to
me don't don't even
I don't know
someone needs to shut me up
maybe I just want to eat food
even though I've been snacking the whole
time
[Music]
I saw myself for a moment
oh my God
Let's Roll
stay
oh the problem now is I don't have free
Pokemon with ground attacks but who else
should I send out one of your things
we've probably couldn't even handle it
with just one Pokemon
I kind of have to stand out more
who could I stand out
snow fairies okay okay
no dog no mouse holds healthy muscle fun
um can I still change Pokemon
you're always too late
always too late
um
[Music]
just bought one of the Academy students
who doesn't look like he's from two star
you're right yeah
so I have to see nowhere you want
your reasons for being here
I'd like to ask this boy some questions
you go ahead and start get started on
the base
um
not quite it
within that base let's team starts
poison cool the Navy's good
the robust articles designs the outfits
for the team you could say it as clever
ends the guys also a bit of an eccentric
you can never tell what's he what he's
going to do next so since it's beyond us
you respond to a declaration of well
just take out as many of the squad's
Pokemon as you can until Atticus shows
his face ring the bell on the gates once
you're ready to kick off this face of
operation come to wipe the novice god of
the map
Pokemon anyway
but maybe I have anything useful in my
box that I've caught recently
[Music]
so I could
flying dragon
not really especially because here the
level gets really low
I mean long bling is still wait long boy
has mud slap but I mean that doesn't
matter right because they're the water
type would matter only
by the way that's what I why I
originally got no that's not why I got
something else I wanted to use any guest
guest for the
Electro Arena Maybe
yeah Psych is good against poison
didn't someone just say no psychic
please
well okay the level would be perfect
39. damn
okay okay okay
we can do that
temporarily only of course
so this free
not that Connie has anything effective
but
psychic is good okay okay okay could
even actually be
really our main Pokemon even
for especially for the fight against the
car
no
maybe not at first
I want to check her move side beam
well I can change them
wow what a sound
I can't change it here
Sparks resist poison now oh nice
you can relearn a really good move what
what am I doing
check summary
why can I this is the same menu
can I only do it when I go in from here
Lumina crash oil
it already looks really good
and feather dance or no Trail pack Maybe
that one
yeah that looks strong
and
oh
I will do against Opera
[Music]
it's a new Pokemon I mean I don't really
like the looks of it that much but you
know
is she
I'm guessing what a physical attacker or
or or special attacker
special attack is oh special attack all
right because it's on like way higher
than normal attack
so
okay
she's a physical attacker what I don't
get it why
wait my chats my chats uh my chat
stopped working
Let me refresh it
where is that game you go
[Music]
oh
oh they were both sleeping
cute
where's that gaming goal ah
okay so she is a special attacker all
right all right I think I think
I got that idea on my own I'm glad I was
right okay then I get it now whatever is
higher attack a special attack is what I
should be focusing on
well then
I'm ready
[Music]
yeah don't worry
are you ready
[Music]
I just noticed the the wall is made out
of made out of school tables
seems the first behind operation star
fool are finally making a move against
our base you know what that means gang
time for us to shine bright and avenge
your teammates and hey a little Intruder
just so you know if you've got the
skills to defeat party I've ever Pokemon
another 10 minutes our boss Mighty new
worthy to meet in person good luck
[Music]
okay it's always the same you don't
always have to tell me
[Music]
wow these are fancy princess bird
so much
so much fluffy Ruffles on her back
well wow why are they so big they're
bugs
oh my God the monkeys
come on here bye
why can't I not call them
where are the others
[Music]
okay if my time is worse than usual and
that's because
it's not working like this should
[Music]
attack
oh
that's a funny evolution
you can slide me boy
what the Pokeball mushrooms over here
also kinda cute
it's so tiny
how many more ten more
[Music]
all right let's
go for these do they also respawn if I
run back so they respond there as well
[Music]
they're not poisoned
does that not matter in this round
[Music]
all right I got time let me pick up the
the item leg
I can't is it a bug I guess it's not
really there
all right then oh
[Music]
come on you can do it
if we're killing mushrooms we're done
[Music]
can't doing rain okay
listen two more hours until the
watch along
oh man it's it's gonna be so late
my throat hurts
Atticus
he's boy or girl whose lashes are kinda
long
[Music]
hello
oh Twitter space could also work you're
right
[Music]
it's a pretty boy okay
yeah that's gone drunk
you have some Nerf bearing your fans a
team star come then doing this Rich a
plunge into the green boys and she'll be
your well-deserved Fate on God
oh la la
[Music]
when we're playing Pokemon tomorrow too
so
wouldn't be too bad if we stop is anyone
in the end planning to do a watch alone
or does anyone have a reservation now
I guess it's not a normal Nintendo
Direct it's just a trailer so
it's not kind of worth it to do a whole
stream for it
it will be just like what three minutes
maybe
[Music]
yeah
that's why I just wanted to do it at the
end of the stream because that would
still make a bit of sense
[Music]
certain moves can poison with a mere
Grace trembles found drill for die
Pokemon stay
oh my God that's a my heart
that is very painful yeah wait didn't
you guys say gonna
immunity against poison
say that right now it was again like a
Split Second of a different angle
weird camera
didn't think you cared about the Mario
move and did you see me react to London
uh can I what should I find it with
fighting the car but is that poison type
now
didn't you see my reaction to the first
time we've watched the first trailer I
was like mind blown
it's all supports okay then I think I'll
go for the bird
let's see her in action maybe she can
convince me to keep her a little bit
longer
then we can have a new Pokemon around
it has an interesting type that we
didn't have yet
before
so let's see this
Lumina crash
the car Pokemon on top of this car
Pokemon
what
[Music]
uh uh-huh
did you not have any other choice what
is
we're gonna fight the car as well later
right so right I was confused because I
saw the name I thought we were already
fighting the car itself
I guess not
[Music]
there we go that's more fitting that's
more like kids
foreign
as much as I hoped it would be
I guess they were
on a good level though
[Music]
nice that's what I like to see so you
cut all that
where's she
[Applause]
was sorry that was fun
one more we're fighting the car now
it hurts but
[Music]
let me know crash
oh come on he's faster than me so
I'm gonna die now right how much damage
did he just do to me
[Music]
um
I wanna heal but it's my crystallization
gone after that
uh 16 20.
17.
60.
[Music]
what oh I thought it goes away after a
few rounds but it just stays until the
end
whoa
[Music]
I didn't know that I just assumed it
would go away after a while
not level 32 and I'm poisoned now
oh [\h__\h]
I'm pretty nine though
I'm gonna crack
I should do it
[Music]
nice good job bird
forgive me my friends
don't be like that sometimes
about a year and a half ago oh
wow pretty
forgive me I took a goodly time to
procure the required materials
[Music]
wow staying those bones are in signs
yes the move flame church was my muse
for those particular pieces
this outfit is everything I imagine it
would be thank you so much
outfits
I merely wish to create a costume worthy
of the great infernal Eddie if it aligns
with your vision then I'm content
seems your outfit a crystal wrapped up
then thanks to Johnny Atticus
with you two looking like absolute
beasts anyone who crosses us will be
sweating bullets
you're so good at these sorts of crafty
things Atticus those people bullying you
cause you kicked out of an old-fashioned
stuff or out of their minds
The Way of the Ninja is rough and
brought with horns I never expect nor
desire sympathy from the unrefined Rebel
oh someone's getting fired Up Watch Out
World our Atticus has fighting words
yeah don't listen to the haters out
because I think you're really cool
all right gang let's move on to the next
step it's time to put our backs into a
battle training so we're all prepped for
a parishion star we gotta be stronger
than everyone else in the team that's
what being a boss means
indeed it does henceforth I will devote
myself heart and so to honing my battle
skills
for the sake of the team I would give my
very heart and soul but I cannot defy
the rules our code must be obeyed and so
this badge is mine to keep no more
entrusted to die care
I'm winking
cute we're bowing to each other
kind of friendly
poison bench
take this contraption too it contains a
technique that allows one to cover their
Frozen gunk
shot you
kiwawa's thy name is not you have
utterly best of me but thy Victory
stared no bitterness within me such was
its Brilliance I wanna talk like that
too
telling me to Get Swole
I'm Kim
it's a strong poison move
whoa okay
[Music]
my my computer
the same this little fella has been
dying to speak with you face to face
here when I have to say I only need a
moment whatever brought you all the way
here
love you if you don't start going to
classical you'll be expelled from the
academy right
oh
oh still Atticus talking
when you're the kids at school and I
we're getting bullied real bad no
kids at the rest of dream star and we
saved us actually the operation you
carried out again we were only able to
go to school again if you got expelled
for being a good guys that would be the
worst thing ever
[Music]
haven't you heard anything from your big
boss
we're very not a whisper since that
fateful day without the big boss team
star I cannot carry on and without the
team the bright and married student life
we seek lies beyond our reach with no
choice but to defend our bases till the
big boss returns to us
who evidently towards this big boss I
feels a great deal who exactly are they
interview if not one of us had met them
in the flesh oh
by their own word they are recluse as
with the rest of us it would seem
bullying was to blame
that's awful
know their name and face be unknown to
us there nonetheless our precious
comrade our only choice is to maintain
our vigils from the bases awaiting the
day of their return that's why you don't
go to school but but still you'll never
find that team stars all you have don't
articles you've got a lifelong compatri
in me and don't feel forget it
I owe you a great debt
the truth behind the team starts truancy
and the bullying at the Academy but more
importantly I can't believe I had no
idea about these issues the students are
struggling with
they have friendships they hold there
and reasons for acting as they do I just
couldn't see it it's shameful how
oblivious have been I can't talk anymore
ah I believe team started to be the one
and only treasure in my life
me thanks
I may have been mistaken me thanks
especially written together but that
doesn't sound so
sophisticated
foreign
it sounds
modern to me like just like someone
talking like
um
like
in the Mimi way I don't know to describe
it
many things though Dove Dove protest too
much
[Laughter]
yeah
narodo
Shakespearean
I died I guess so yeah
um
it's me
Attica Starbucks is now Justin
now that its boss has been taken down
the novice God's days are numbered
undotra
no Atticus too
sorry I've got a lot on my mind right
now so operations therefore you've taken
down all but two business so it's fair
to say it's going well it this seems
like a good time to let you know what
we're ultimately aiming to achieve
our final goal is to defeat The
Mastermind that first recorded the five
Squad bosses and create a Teamster the
one they call
isn't the big boss
I thought it was Cassiopeia
who knows they control the fat squat
ghosts from the Shadows that's all
[Music]
then maybe it's maybe it's maybe it's
clever actually because I didn't ever
see him before so obviously they
wouldn't
um recognize him anyway
that would be quite the
[Music]
turntable
if we defeat this person and get them to
declare the team this Bandit that will
be it for Teamster
since the big boss never set up their
own base and keeps their identity hidden
I take it they are not one for the
spotlight but once all the squad bosses
are out of action the big boss finally
have have to take the stage now about
your reboot I'll transfer some LP
[Music]
but while I was considered prayer
I'm doing me a big confused right now
Clive is obviously clever
no [\h__\h] Sherlock yes yes yes no no way
[Music]
hmm
so weird
have you or Pokemon learn strong move so
that they can continue to be of use in
the operation my supply unit should be
reducing oh she's coming
or maybe it is her
that's the bullying problem
[Music]
what's she what she's young I mean
there's an the other one is also real
I guess
[Music]
hmm
hey hey hey hey there
um sounded like a pretty serious phone
call
um
oh I wasn't talking to you
you so slimy
just like me for real for real
did we need to have such a long black
cut
so that Mastermind you were talking
about Casio Perez mentioned them to me
too
oh well then I guess it's not you
team Stars
the person who's caused all kinds of
misery at the Academy if we don't take
them down I'll lose what I treasure most
in the world
what do you mean
you know I just oh my eyes are so cute
the way she just opened them up so wide
right now
that's right you need your reward here
take this
thank you all right well I'll be up then
guys
okay
interesting I I was so sure it was gonna
be casual player so this
I mean it could still be but that makes
no sense that Cassiopeia tells me to
fight the boss
maybe because you will pay uh desires
and
dramatic
turntable moment
where
my mind is blown
I don't know
[Music]
um dragging it out until then
I'm not even looking at it anymore what
it is oh
well I don't know my throat really
already hurt so much
I think
I should take a breaking another
breakfast for the break
[Music]
it would probably be for the best for me
y'all I will not play longer but we have
tomorrow anyway
oh
um
I don't know what it is if it's just
fun I don't know
I wanted to go away because it's really
painful especially in the morning
I wake up in the night and in court pick
a big horse
and before
I want to do you guys have any more
advice for me how to hydrate even more
because I already have the humidifier
running in the night and then I have a
glass of water
in case I really need to
take a sip to not like dry the [\h__\h] out
in the night time
like in the night time I don't know how
to
foreign
I can continuously drink tea and then
yeah I'm drinking a lot of liquid a lot
yeah and I didn't talk a word yesterday
except for my
um recording for my short recording for
the calendar
[Music]
no no I have the humidifier on overnight
um
[Music]
and I also drank tea until the last
minute before I
fell asleep
a bit of tape to tape your lips together
I mean that's a serious suggestion from
you probably
but then
it was like next level
I think I will probably
um Lose My Breath if I do that
I hate a raid hydrates me way more
really
[Music]
no no I don't think I have my mouth open
during sleeping though to be honest
[Music]
lemon and honey
I always put a lot of money into my team
heating no he think I turned off and on
like last night I had it off the whole
actually the whole day today and last
night I had it off I don't really notice
a difference to be honest
except that it's [\h__\h] cold now in my
apartment
but no no windows are closed
I was thinking
[Music]
like I remember seeing my sister when we
still lived together
inhaling like having a blanket over her
head and then some pot whatever water or
so in a bowl
underneath with her face on it but I
guess that's just when you have like a
stuffed nose or so then that helps but
it doesn't does that help for
a dry throat as well
I'm going now
[Music]
that's for your sinus sinuses
I need some life hacks
ginger lemon tea
I've been drinking a lot of like fruit
tea you know like actual like Pharmacy
stuff
and probably candy
and I mean I guess I also have some
some special candy from the throat
doctor that I don't like because weird
it makes everything so slimy but
maybe I'll try taking it before sleeping
tonight
it's so weird though I don't like it
makes everything so slimy
when I have a lot of them
from last time I went to the throat
doctor
[Music]
seasonal thing yeah you know I
understand that I have seasonal fruit
dryness that's when I had like a week
ago or so but then three or two days ago
suddenly this is so much worse this is
my next level [\h__\h]
and I don't know
what I'm doing wrong or is it me being
sick or I don't know
um
hopefully it will get better
soon because I can't live like this
especially not if my job is talking
yeah and I also have some recording
deadlines coming up
in the next
week
um
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
no no it's not that bad like I can talk
as you've noticed for a while this is
really painful at this point
as long as the streams don't go too long
I guess
um
[Music]
like
um swallowing my tea also hurts really
bad right now
uh
and I want to feel tired now so
have some super chats will not be red
streams I mean that's something future
kiwawa has to worry about anyway
hopefully future levels throat is doing
better
um
[Music]
I hope it goes away if it's a temporary
thing then okay I can take it
temporarily
I'll eventually finish the super chance
oh my God it's almost
tomorrow's the last day of November yeah
bye now bye
no boy oh God I have a million DMs
okay
what did I say last day of December no
it's the last day of November right yeah
yeah
[Music]
lay up salt oh I I had a lot of salt
today from the chips drink fluids
coconut water regular water restful
because maybe do some exercise to help
that just fill it some pure chimpurities
all
salt okay okay
yeah
but they're so good they're so good
[Music]
they're so good you guys don't
understand
[Applause]
uh thank you guys so sweet
I'll be around when the trailer drops uh
just on Twitter
when you watch it imagine you're
watching it with me okay because I will
be watching as well
help me let's see
[Music]
I am
I will
I know yeah
foreign
[Music]
for tomorrow
I guess
oh man it's in one hour and 15 minutes I
was so close yo
I was so close
oh
[Music]
the ouch
it is what it is it's only stupid three
minutes anyway
okay
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
hmm
dancing
[Music]
really mad Alex imagine playing a 7 to
12 year old video game
what this is new Oh you mean it's for
for 7 to 12 year old people what what's
your problem
why are you so mad
[Music]
okay plus you had your fun oh hey
you have an herbal remedy
what what is it
herbal remedy is it marshmallows because
I'm drinking marshmallowty oh
Chinese herbal remedy
[Music]
yeah to pick it up
maybe they have it here I guess I guess
maybe
[Music]
you're from Michigan I need the urban
mystica
yeah you have to collect five herbal
mystical to save me
words
is that like cough syrup
I wonder what that tastes like
[Music]
herbal stores here
yeah go go go go go catch some Titans
fight some Titans Titan attack
Attack on Titan
oh they actually
um I know of something in Japan that
singers use their
apparently
um also kind of very similar in shape
Japan or something like that too
and I actually I think I recommended it
to
Kelly or Iris
hmm
I think I did what did I
[Music]
feel like I recommended someone
right so free thank you okay
um thank you guys for watching today if
you want to see more Chihuahua play more
Pokemon tomorrow is the day tomorrow
more Pokemon
[Music]
um
port
I will shut up now
but in German we say Alfie does you
[Music]
um
thank you for being here
oh
thank you very much
foreign
DMS now
and then cook
some health
fresh stuff
yellow
bye bye or two I hope I have a simple
recipe
I hope past koala fought ahead and
thought Oh She surely wants at least one
simple recipe that she can whip up in a
minute
[Music]
um
bye-bye
also see you tomorrow I'll miss you
[Music]
um I might miss you
yes hopefully throw towards tomorrow
Braddock pickles well I made simple
pesto with pasta pasta yesterday and
some cherry tomatoes really fast some
Ram store-bought pesto so yummy though
no space um movie space yeah
[Music]
okay keep an eye out on Twitter
wait
when is it in one hour right one hour
ten minutes
[Music]
okay
hug your cats and your doggos and your
other pet does okay
mm-hmm
[Music]
foreign
laughs
[Music]
on my mind