[music]
[applause]
OG
[music]
DET
[applause]
[music]
DET
[music]  The
devil's
words, I showed you a
premonition that we were meeting at the door, and I opened the door, and I was so busy that I didn't have a fishing book.
What do you feel? Show me your cute, cute face.  The
classroom goes on forever, telling me it's time.The
secret of my smile that I can't show is the sweet, sweet treat.Is it the
devil's temptation?Even if I
ask about you, I'll go beyond the rhythm of my illness.I'll touch you, and I'll
be in the middle of the sinking moment.  Our eyes can't go back, and we
meet each other, and listen to the words of the eternal monster.I'll
wait for you.Even if I
close the door in this hostile time, I can't even get close to God.It
's how I don't know the truth of my feelings.  I can't do it anymore  I'll
show you what I want to see in Sipe.
Believe that the picture is right here. I can only show it to you.
Behind the sweet smile, the sweet
tingling and the devil's spider are always waiting here.
(Music)
Everyone, today.  Thank you for coming
[Music]
This time it's Black Christmas,
so let's enjoy both Halloween and Christmas
at the same time.The
hashtag is
here in kakana
and bra and chohiragana.
Pair it with chocolate and tweet a lot with Sharp Bra chocolate.
[Music]
Please, let's move on to the next song.
Well, it's Black Christmas, so I've
prepared a little present for everyone.
So,
here you
go.
Dodo. Now.  Now, I
wonder what's inside. Everyone's looking forward to it.
[Music]
Hey,
Bushidoru has clouds. I don't
eat glue, I don't open my shoes.
Nnnnnnn, that's right, the good girl, no, I left it to him. I'm
crazy about that girl who turned into a bad girl. Where are you
going?  Don't
let it
drown out the voices that don't
exist.It's still a little sleepy tonight.
[Music]
Hakusui.
Let's have fun, let's make a fuss,
where is the real thing? Where are we running away?
Dance
[Music]
This is where we are.
[Music] It's
okay from 2 o'clock yesterday until the time.
Hurry up and give up, Merry.
[Music]
Christmas.
That's what I'm saying.
Let's dance with our fingers. The
never-ending nightmare is a world where only Christmas scars hurt. The darkness is so
black that it drowns out the cries.  I'm
still riding on something,
and the love that's clinging to me is still swaying. It's a
happy
Christmas.
[Music]
Oh, it's getting dark. I wonder if it's okay if I come out.  I'm
going to eat from your enchanted sweets.I'm
sure the fog will get thicker, so I'm sure
everyone will gather around.Here's
my reward for putting up with the wait.  The
little monsters will forgive me today. Let's
go. Happy Halloween. They
'll play tricks here and there. They
won't give me any candy.
Happy Halloween. I'm tired.
Even Jack will dance. Happy Halloween. Halloween ghosts.
Let's
hang out today Happy Halloween Welcome
to the mysterious world Even tired Jack will sing
[Music] I
want more and more and I
won't be confused If that's the case then
Izunoe
[Music]  I don't
care about the house that doesn't turn around, I
roll the toilet paper around, I light a lantern tonight, and
if it comes out, it's sweet, but I don't have enough of it, because Happy Halloween is spinning
around,
and here and there and here and there, I'm eating pap ki pie, because it's
Happy Halloween, so I'm staying up late.
No, I'm tired and Jack won't sleep until morning 'Cause I'm
happy Halloween
Happy
Halloween Happy
Halloween Today is happy
[Music] I
don't want to roll Halloween red and go to sleep
[Music]
Ah
[Music] The
day when my tail came astray
[Music]
Panty
Nore
[Music] Narui's
Still Still
[Music] Let's
Monteru
Say There's No Good Morning
[Music]
Naishi [
Music]
Dance [
Konoteru  It doesn't matter to us.
Even God has forgiven us. We are free. We
are here. We are not there. Just run away. You
can't join us. We'll have
fun partying until morning comes.  It
's over
[Music]
No
Even the people who are going to sleep soon will turn their eyes and wait
until the night comes again Let's carve this day in our hearts
Happy Halloween will
be forgotten tomorrow I wonder if I'll buy a night before I sleep
[Music] That's
not enough Happy Halloween for us
Until the morning
[Music]
Dance
Ghosts are
coming in front of the house A hungry
girl smells sweet. That's
right. Please give me some sweets.  young lady
Even though it was chubby, I opened it in a package and passed it around for a long time.I
ate it all up.Halloween
night, the night of the party was dominated by ghosts.Give me sweets, or
attack me!Halloween night patty, the
carp comes dancing.It's my first time here with him.  So
Papa Papa
Jiran [Music] Our wounds still hurt We were always able to take in our lives with Papa.  The
laughing full moon is not too bright Halloween night
party In the evening, the ghosts are the main guests Sympathizer Lanban
Pampa Halloween night party In the evening we
dance Sosemato de la hote
again
[Music]
Jira
[Music] The
darkness pours out as the door opens.  It's
time to go back to the hallonite park.It's time to go back to the
blue lomini night party in this place.The night is dominated by ghosts.I
have to give you some sweets.
Let's go to the night party, now we're coming to dance. There's a chillum
outside the street.
[Music]
Is it because I'm buying it for Prey? Where should I
go? A song that made me cry happily.
Jack laughed.  Putting aside my feelings, I
cried for the real chocolate.It was
singing and shaking on the radio.My
fear was that of a pumpkin.I was
still
asleep.It
was boring.
[Music]  The
devil
and the witch who were raised by the devil seemed to want nothing,
but with their obscene feelings, Mandarake bloomed.
But
something
[music] was
holding their hands as they waited for the train, and they forgave them.  I'm
still playing music in the stupid village.
[Music]
Mr.
[ __ ]. I went to pick you up. That night, before I knew it, my
dreams were destroyed.
[Music]
I still want to dance here. Have you spit out the cherry blossoms like a dream?
Time is running
out.  Matayabuno
On the middle train
[Music]
Anki
Amis
Pumpkin Yes, so it's Yuzu's anniversary.
Thank you for the live performance.
Well, it's our 5th anniversary, so I called
two people over and got a reward.
So let's get some chocolate as a reward. Time please. Let's read it right away. Subaru Nata Wow,
congratulations, congratulations, congratulations. Nana, I
want a basket, right? Nana, nana, no, it's
our 5th anniversary. That's seriously auspicious.  I
don't know what you're talking about. Just tell me what you want. It's okay. I have a bad feeling about it.
Lately, I don't think the two of us have been good enough.  That's what I'm
saying, no, it's not enough.That
's right.No matter how you feel about it, you're still a boy.I'm indebted to Choco, so I guess I'll show you what's going on.Well, I'll stop, then.  Master Himo,
Luna-san, please take care of me.Yes
, then, let's start with number 1.What is
that?It's the first time I've heard about number 1.That's new.It's too
new.It's too new.It's the
one with the climax.
Eh, two people are going to chew it. If they do that, the color will be over. What's that?
Two people like that are going to chew it in front of the chocolate,
right? They're going to chew it right in front of the chocolate.  I
was so relieved. I was
so nervous, wondering what he had just said.
Well, now I'm going to congratulate Cho-sensei. I
see. I see, the two of you are
paying attention to Choco, I guess.
Well, just for today. Just for today.
Either way, I
can't help it. Excuse me for a moment, but I ca
n't help it. Why are you saying that you can't help it? No,
no, no, I'm sorry. I'll go.
Please. Yes, director. Please.  Well
then, Mr. Choco,
congratulations to the boy. It's so sad. Wow, sit down on the bench where the train is. There
was a monster there right now.
Even though I'm just a few, my cheeks
are growing. I
'm drooling. Maybe I've messed up, but drooling is a reward. So, just like a cat, I'm feeling
better. I'm so
happy that I'm feeling so much better.  I'll do my best this year too.Sorry,
that's
good.Well then, that's what's most important.So, let
's go with this excitement.
Let's see the red on my cheeks
[Music]
[Music] It's a
magical night, so it's a strange world
Even the world is playing pranks on the city and I'm so excited
[Music]
Sehun, I want to smile in my dreams
Let's dance together Yo
Papa
Halloween  Cute Oso Hello Halloween
Patty Pakin
Kukuku Patik
Patena Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan Pan
[Music]
Pan-Pan-Pan-Pan-Pan-Pan-Pan-Pan-Pan A
white child, let's
make the town colorful by putting it on the street.
Papa, it's like we've wandered into a
dream. Pan-Pan-Pan,
Pan-Pan-Pan Let's all dance together Yo Papa-
Papakishi Halloween cute cage
Hello Hello
Pazapa
[Music]
Kuku Kuku Pizza Pakidashi Halloween Kaioke
and Hello Halloween
Papak
Kupapatti
[Music]
No Pan La Pan Pan Pan Pan Pa Para
Pampanji no papaparapanpan
Panpanji no papaparapanpanpatty Panpapanpanpapaparapanpanpapanpanra Panpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpanpannnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn
Papa starts out with Halloween cute ghosts
Hello Halloween papa pizza papin Crazy
Crazy Crescissipakin Kuji
Party Napa  papa pizza pakinda sidashi
Halloween Cute Ghosts and Hello Halloween
Papapakuku Creshi Papikrepatina Patina Haro
[Music]
Halloween Crazy Patena Hallo Halloween
Crazy Patty No
[Music]
Ah,
when I open the door, the
timer is
rewound to the dream disco looking for you and
suspicious
Paddy
dances  It's too late to reveal the
virtual dance floor where Riderball spins,
I'm alone and give it to you.
What should I do to the rhythm of the song?
[Music]
Hello! Everyone's favorite pumpkin is
beckoning. We touch our hips, avoiding the stand. Let's all be fools tonight. There
's no Halloween. We
don't need words.
Forget about the unpleasant things that happen once a year.
Cannibal Ghosts who are free just for today
[Applause]
Hana
, Fuji, who can become whatever they want to be,
Harika, who is only a human, The
things that are important
are the things that were mine when I was a child, and I will be
reborn
[Music] It
's Halloween.
Before the song changes, I say the tape one more time.If you
want to meet me, stand out.It's Halloween.Get
out of the sledding waves of people who are crowded at night.I'm
going to fall in love with you in this corner of the world.Freddy, lady, happy,
happy, happy, Happy
Halloween.  It's
just the two of us, love is always a strong force HAL
LHLl
ohaLl
o It's not Halloween, I don't watch it, I don't blow it, the pumpkin
is inviting me, hit me now, my hips sway, there's no one tonight
Be an idiot, Halloween. I
don't need words. I hate it.
[Music]
Forget about the one-time
cannibal. The ghosts are free for today only.
[Music]
How did you all like the Halloween guest part?
Today is called Black Christmas.  So, I
would like to give you all a present from Hey Nechoco
[Music] Goods
commemorating the 5th anniversary of Masuyuzu Chico's activities First of all, click
here
Dodon Sato Pote-sensei Kakioroshi
Campus
Art Nantane This is Black Santa's
Chocolate was
a little late, and I thought it was private, so I turned
around and looked at everyone.It's
chocolate.I wish it were like this.It's a
wonderful piece of campus art that can be displayed in anyone's room without Choco Sensei Edges.  [
Music]
Masu and next,
this is the high glass that I signed a contract with Choco Sensei,
so I asked him to pour
some strawberry milk or something into this glass.
If you toast with chocolate, you're now my kin.Furthermore, the
new chocolate
necklace heart necklace that was announced the other day is now
available in the form of a sig.And
this time too, we have Yuzu chocolate.It's an
ASMR script, so it's a
separate voice.  There are two of them.The first one is
Chocolate Santa's Wish Examination ASMR.So
here I am, I
wonder if everyone has been a good boy this year.
So, Choco is a really nice girl.It's a
voice that makes me want to eat.If
you want to be attacked, please come by.The second one is Tsundere-san
Ta's reward SMR, so
listeners should listen to Tona.  I would be happy if you could listen to it while feeling like you're in the mood.And
here's the full set.There
are two types of purchase bonuses.The
first one is that I
'll write it properly this year as well.I'll write all the Yu chocolate myself.I'll sign it,
plus a foreshadowing message in white.  This
is a new post card written by Mr. Pote Sato.And then
[Music]
Sorry to keep you waiting, it's Deai Choco No Nurase.It's a
mean ASMR voice.This is
a bit of an SMR voice.For
those of you who haven't heard it before.  If you're a first-time viewer, please
listen to it and then sew it.
Everyone, please make sure to get your hands on a chocolate present.
[Music]
And after this, there's one more chocolate gift.  I
have a gift for you,
but before that,
[Music] Let's do the
usual thing, a scary red carpet. So, with the summons, here is the annual
red carpet.For those who are new to it, I would
like to explain
what this red carpet is.  If you
stroke the Super Chat, it
will open up to give you a present,
so we hope to see you again this year.Well
, this time's goods
were created with a lot of thought into the Bragg Christmas theme.  I
saw the live show with the black Christmas theme,
and the decorations
were cute. Ah,
thank you.
Yes, you made it cute this year too.
Thank you, everyone. Just a little more, a little
more, a
little more.  The
present is a new song, please
listen to it Barry
[Music]
Christmas is slowing down and we're rushing too fast,
and even the fangs are changing colors, colliding with the nightmare of the season
and getting caught up in the clouds of being late
[Music]  When
snow fishing
asks for a mountain of greedy wishes, I feel like being mean.
Beg for me. Bye
Christmas to the bad boy.
How about a reward for the devil?  The
coast key is already mine.
I do
n't want to worry about looking at this and that. I erased those things from my list of things I wanted. I
exposed my desires and became a
nobody.  I
put a box of garlic at Christmas, and the expression on my face is so bright.
[Music] It's
just a facial expression. You're
done, right? You
don't need a present. Just me, and you'll be satisfied. The
direction of your socks is sweet. Don't
give up, Christmas
Nova, Christmas Nova.  It
's so sweet to pretend that it's good to be in front of you and make it rain.I'm so happy that I'm happy to be with you now,
Chris.
[Music]
Nova
Christmas