[Music]
thank you
questions
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
moment
s
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
it's me it's a Wawa hello
uh
uh I'm drinking ice cold iced tea
unfortunately no one is your drink today
even though I feel like I would like one
because it's not like you know
I'm lacking sleep much
but
I know I just don't have energy man I
was I don't know it's like I
I went back to being a toddler where I
need a a nap every day but I'm not the
only one
you know I talked to
who was it
who is it
some Japanese member
and she was also like yeah
yeah I I also need Nap
like I also take a nap pretty much every
day
was it wait um
yeah I think it was a Japanese member
um
no it couldn't have been azuki I don't
think so no oh [\h__\h] it's hot today
I'm gonna turn on the the Dyson oh
no not chocolate I didn't talk to
Chocolate recently
[Music]
um
who was it
that's weird why do I not
remember
weird
um oh well hmm
ah the air what the air cleaners you
mean they don't make the air cold
they don't do [\h__\h] with the temperature
for sure
anyway
hi
I would have slept one more hour
if it wasn't for a [\h__\h] smoothie
I was like okay [\h__\h] I'm making your
food and I'm going back to bed but you
know then when you wake up and you walk
over and you give her the food you
already stood up and walked and then I I
went to the idol meeting and you know I
thought well I need idle meeting anyway
because my back hurts so much like I
wake up in the night because of back
pain and it feels like it gets better
when I got to idle meeting
and then yeah so then I thought okay
back to sleep but recently it just
doesn't work that way
it just doesn't work that way because at
that point I'm like so awake that I need
like an hour to sleep to fall asleep but
I only had one more hour to sleep
you know it sounds like it's enough and
one more hour of sleeping
but when you need an hour to fall asleep
then it's nothing
um
but oh well
it's okay spoofy I didn't feel that
tired it's okay spoofy
no it's not okay don't disturb me
anymore
the thing is guys I
stayed up
all night
talking to
people on the phone
um
I stayed up so long
I talked one hour on the phone with pomu
foreign
[Applause]
before that I talked one hour with
someone else
well over the phone yeah well using
Discord on my phone yeah
yeah
so I stayed up even longer than usual it
was so bright outside when I thought
okay I really need to sleep
I was tired but I wanted to talk to Puma
so yeah
but I'm okay
I'm okay I'm okay
it was very social yesterday yeah
and then
uh
for today
[Music]
since we played nine hours yesterday
and I ended up making a pizza
I really need to cook today and I really
need to like not stream for nine hours
because I also need to read super chats
and you know this and that this and that
so today let's aim for a maximum of six
hours gameplay okay
I will try my best to hold back
and then and then maybe like an hour of
super chats yeah
no tangents allowed during the Super
chats so that I can actually
do my schedule also after that because I
think you want to see the schedule
early this time
because I have two
collapse set up for tomorrow
[Music]
um
you might want to see at what time Etc
yeah
oh yes
two
so
um
why is it so stormy
I it just sounds because of the water
sounds so stormy uh
birthday gift oh
tomorrow no it's not promo tomorrow
what is so noise in here uh wait I hear
a sound of a shrine but didn't I already
does this the shrine sound still ping
when you already found it because I feel
like it does
I don't remember if I did find the
shrine here yesterday
no it doesn't but I heard it okay
uh
I didn't see that
[Applause]
why am I always so dramatic
why am I so dramatic ah
[Music]
well I saw that one coming
uh Mamma Mia I should just uh what are
we gonna do was I gonna like do anything
else in this cave
I think I'm done with the cave right I
found the treasure and I found the Frog
so whatever
um and like besides that currently
there's nothing really besides the
memory
there's nothing really that's keeping me
here
so last time yesterday in case you guys
missed it someone here we opened up the
map for this area
no we started out by going through the
cave again that I went for a loan once
but didn't go completely free with it
for the case that leads for the Hyrule
system
Hyrule Castle system
and after that we went to open this map
and we did the quest
that was uh
where I don't know the one is it this
one Aya here this quest with the dragon
statues and whatever that was fun we got
some lore
uh and some cool stuff from it good
knowledge and then
uh we most a lot of time we spent
yesterday going on the ground uncovering
some chasms and especially
down here we went to a Coliseum we did
three
free Colgate fights I think
free the second the third and the fourth
thus we were also LED over here which
was a pain in the ass to get inside
yeah uh yeah Friv
c-r-t-h-r
mm-hmm
and
uh oh yeah we got a treasure really cool
treasure down here
or so
this and that this and that this and
that so with colgar we did we repeated
one
uh one of the boss fights found out that
they do happen on the ground as well
we did a lot of shrines like eight or
seven or eight trines we did one memory
uh
uh we did this and that yeah and then
yeah right that's the important part I
forgot we did the
freemazes
that are here
in all three levels and got
uh also we got to fight with the hands
and what comes after the hands
and I succeeded in it wasn't so bad was
it mm-hmm
now
um
chihuahua has found out that I was
scammed by the Hyrule Castle
uh because now I don't remember the
exact place
but
turns out
the Hyrule Shield
was somewhere there too
what the [\h__\h]
you guys didn't tell me
it's like yeah kind of in the castle but
we were in the castle I have watched it
yesterday
and I already forgot
where where where where
Echo storm tender went there
ah
ah wait where
left right
someone pointed it out
it's not in the sky though
it's in a cave and ah yeah it was just
kind of weird like that it's oh placed
here okay in the place where there used
to be something else
uh in the docks the dogs
ducks
what no no f
uck or dogs isn't that where like ships
are
maybe if I go here
I Wanna Get The Shield
and I know it's very durable and all but
what happens if it does break
can you buy that one too like that other
cool sword that we got
or can you repair it and tear it down
that's also something I forgot to do
yesterday because there's just too much
to do
oh rebuy the shield for three pounds oh
that's good country burgers
I won't use it much so I probably will
never break
okay I want to get it okay so for today
first we got
this
um
wonderful Shield
there's somewhere here
first we got this wonderful Shield then
we try to quickly hopefully it's not so
difficult get to Tarrytown
and then we move on to do some main
story
that's the right direction okay see the
Gap at the northwest of the castle knee
honest everyone
here
we can make the boat
that we got to
learn I wonder if it can
if it's strong enough to work against
the current
but this is a bolt boat
I don't wanna I should have
kind of saved the boat the small boat
that we were using but this this one
called the hovercraft works too maybe
on the water
it should
I feel like it should
[Music]
foreign
could probably make a cheap version with
the with the wood but
okay it's kind of sinking right now
okay we are almost a submarine
well the current is strong
we are living in the turquoise submarine
turquoise submarine turquoise submarines
darker submarine turquoise submarine
I am really surprised that this is
working
foreign
what's that weird red winter it's
everywhere it's just uh you know what
what you get in Hira Castle ah
okay I'm kind of here
where should I get off ah maybe I should
get up here I haven't seen one of the
shield guys in a while
a little bit
keep going to the left
look for an opening okay okay but then I
will help him
why they're building the water I saw I
already forgot how it worked but I saw a
life hack for this
how was it again I know I
saw a technique that pretty much works
with every one of these
shields uh signs I mean
ah the hover pass yeah that could be it
yeah yeah
okay I mean in theory this one's kind of
but the water
maybe we gotta pull it back I don't know
this one's kind of
[Music]
um
do you have a hoverboard oh no let's see
if we can cheese it today oh yeah I do
okay
let's see wait I have to activate the
first ride
oh okay and then it uses up my battery
but that's okay and then I guess I would
put it here
try letting go
live back look look
oh my God
you're welcome for everybody who didn't
know you're welcome this is how you can
basically
this cheese every single one of these
pretty much
YouTube
that you don't know
yay
[Music]
dude
I knew it but I liked the challenge yeah
I wouldn't want to always waste the
parts either and I wouldn't want to
always do this like
I mean I've done so many without this is
the first time I'm using it you know
ah
oh sleepover tickets
two why are you giving me two
well yeah I I I don't know I feel like I
deserve doing it like this now because
I've done it so many times
normally
but yeah I don't know I I don't know do
this I don't have many capsules of this
so
I don't want to overuse it either uh
okay so
this opening I suppose
is probably it
oh
okay
come on
I messed it up I'm trying to fight
against the current
no
let's go
oh I see ducks
uh should I stop here or oh it's going
in though
oh
Circle
[Music]
okay that doesn't count [\h__\h]
um
I'm gonna drown
no wait um I am holding on
oh wait I can just there you go
how did you never get the shrine here I
don't know what why are you saying it as
if it's so
my
such a given
I I guess it's over there I am yeah
that's the Ducks
the Ducks not the Ducks
the dogs
not the decks not the Ducks not the D no
very important to pronounce everything
correct correct quotes correctly
trimming my ducks
correctly
what was that
what color
oh interesting damn this area
[Music]
give me some height at least come out
but they can they can easily go up there
I need a place where I would fight them
if I can at least
no you know what
okay that's kind of cool but no that's
gonna take ages
um
where can I find them where it's like
I can't reach
also I see a chest there
jump in the water yeah but I want to
fight them
oh they can't go over here
okay okay
really
I'm gonna [\h__\h] yell
interesting
no I was gonna fight you
no I'm not so scared anymore you know
anyway uh
there's an opening
oh well yeah
okay then
oh
wait a second is there even anything to
stand on
[Music]
how am I gonna
all right
there we go but like what where do I
bring in
oh maybe wait can I
maybe I can open it when it's falling
no
oh I can stand on it and still open it
no way
the platform of ice yeah okay I don't it
doesn't feel like I can stand on it
right now
okay
ice ice
yeah
okay
I've never used a choo choo jelly before
okay well I knew it wasn't the shield
anyway
but another hotel
uh
I do not exactly remember the location
but we will find it by exploring
no need to tell me yet I mean this is
really obvious that I have to go
upstairs
I'm just checking so that I don't miss
anything elsewhere
like smaller chests or so
I want to
I want to find a secret what if this is
a Kodak
oh wait
oh no this is the chest ah
okay
[Music]
somehow I think I saw this like
yesterday but I already forgot I swear I
swear I thought I had to blow some
Stones up to get to it
but yeah
[Music]
foreign
yeah I know I know I know it's crazy
it's crazy
[Music]
oh man
fabulous absolutely fabulous
where does it lead to here by the way
it doesn't break it does break but you
can get a new one for three thousand
rupees and until this breaks especially
with how little I use Shields
I think it will take a long time
oh
yeah okay
difficult I would say to find from
either path uh where is the shrine that
I keep on hearing it can't be inside
this is on top yeah nearly up above
okay and then I also honestly Wonder
why I didn't activate it
hmm
shrine dokodeskara
up oh they mean one that's flux and
somebody's like hey
what you haven't done the shrine yet if
it's on the floating Castle
then why why are you so surprised
you should go to the front and finish
that other class you have
what other quests
welcome
foreign
no wait what what
Oh you mean the main quest
uh okay I mean we were supposed to do
that today anyway
should I do this now
it feels like it's gonna like ah I know
I guess I mean we have to when I say I
will do the main quest
do the memory first okay I'm fine with
that too if that makes more sense in in
your guys's eyes then I would love to do
it like that
okay uh not kind of money
[Music]
there's one more memory
oh
I suppose maybe on the maybe in this
region
let's look at my screenshot
I got one ah and the game doesn't is
that the
game doesn't
um know that I didn't watch it yet
uh What uh here
this one
no wait no huh
which one did I get and I didn't watch
treachery this one we've seen
secret Stone he took from Sonia 13.
ah this is the one we watched yesterday
at the end of the stream what is this
why did I not see this one yet
I mean it's probably not a memory I know
that
um 11 doco
oh is that something I I shouldn't have
yet hmm
hmm
oh I want to see it first
but it's like like an important missing
puzzle piece that you're supposed to see
after all the other ones
or does it just so happen that I you
know I'm kind of late on that one
and we'll see okay so okay we can watch
this one and then pick up the last one
is
that okay so we shall watch it then
maybe it gets us in the mood ready
it's an item you read a hint about it
yeah but still what
laughs
preparing for
panel
Sonya
his hair is nice
ah Zelda
all right she died
foreign
[Music]
that's right here
and mine outside
so do it better
[Music]
oh
yeah
Sunday about it
that's ended
up
food is high
fun
is
deplete
foreign
[Music]
you would think so
Zelda
is
[Music]
quantum
you know what would be so funny if we
actually do end up with two Master suits
and then we dual wield them thus making
us indeed stronger and maybe finally
strong enough to kill Ganon because it
doesn't take just one master sword as
we've seen many times we've tried it he
always keeps on coming back maybe we
need double the amount of Master swords
customize the sword
oh yeah stick them together
no I think dual wielding is the key
yeah
it's just cooler
link becomes linkirito
ultimate master sword
master sword section do a wheelie is
always the key exactly
[Laughter]
um
that was um
a nice scene I can't imagine like
like purposefully watching these out of
order it's just not it's just so much
better watching them in order
let's be real
quick
um
[Music]
you supposed to no
it's coming to this no
dad
part of your system because it's stupid
what I'm doing is supposed to be the
system
oh yeah I wanted to check if there's
something in that cave but the hands
like were freaking me out last time
it's not really even a real cave is it
ah okay
what
is that not a Kodak
Hello nice to see you once again ah last
memory wait
why would you overlook it I I put so
much I felt so much importance
um to the order when we were shown it in
that Temple I feel like it's you guys
are saying
you're supposed to watch it in order but
then why does the game tell you the
order pretty early on I I I don't agree
I don't agree see they give you this and
they give you the locations
I mean it might be difficult for some of
them
some of the memories but I I to get them
in order but I didn't personally feel
that it was difficult oh wait is the
sword next
right
um wait no it's not wait yeah it is
but it looks different huh
from impa
because see the sword looks different on
the map then it looks like on
the image
because here it's just a sword
but you know here it's kind of like the
sword is in the middle of uh something
you never noticed that was the what put
one and one together
[Music]
oh you didn't find this how can you not
find this
before
I guess you just didn't do that like you
didn't talk to impa
um
that's the temperature and I want you
just watched
ah
oh okay okay then never mind I add now I
see it's at the bottom middle okay so we
know where the sword is
then let's go get it
um it was like
visible from
here yeah
if we go I am in the ah Maybe not maybe
we shouldn't have gone to the Skyview
town maybe to the shrine but it doesn't
matter
it doesn't matter it's in between
okay okay cool cool cool cool cool cool
cool cool
nah
I mean I understand that maybe you could
mix it up a little bit by going to the
easy ones the obvious ones first as
because thankfully
the ones that are really like spoilerish
this one
and this one and
this one that we just watched
our especially these two hard to reach
this one also isn't very desirable to
reach
so
as long as you don't do these too early
I think it's uh I guess acceptable
to mix them up yeah because I guess some
of them are like whatever
Village
dagger one
ah
lure demand Village
[Music]
that one that's what you guys meant
did the bottom part of that respawn
that flower Island
no way right no
would be really weird if that was the
case
never went back to Jack understandable
crabstone
cute
curious about this Forest too does the
main story ever lead me there because if
not I guess
I guess I'll go
on my own
no
hmm
[Music]
is the Sky music different from usual
um
ah it does
foreign
[Music]
and it's on the master sword oh that
will be interesting okay
[Music]
spoiler warning indeed
foreign
oh
what it happened and they're not showing
us
it's so messy steps
they're not showing us when it actually
happened
um
okay
pretty
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah she already has it though I'm so
confused
she getting double airpods not just a
single one
no it's a sage well
[Music]
yeah okay this is when we sent it over
via FedEx yeah
laughs
toffee come to see here
the biggest I'm living is this far
um
[Music]
don't treat it like a cat
Zelda to biscuit is
foreign
[Music]
ale
link
it defend me I
[Music]
uh impa okay okay
um
I will okay
ah
oh no [\h__\h] way
[Music]
ah
foreign
yourself into a dragon
um and she was like so happy about it
about the idea what the [\h__\h]
does that mean she thinks she knows
a way of going back
and she think she outsmarted the system
and don't don't answer my questions
they're all just me and you know
commenting on my thoughts
but
well
so I know that was the beginning for her
like her not quite it was
not the beginning after she traveled
through time right
but it's the her point of view of like
ages ago when we sent out the sword via
FedEx
and then the sword tells her like
reminds her of things that
she didn't really do yet or here yet
I guess but now I mean you know Paradox
time paradox
things that we saw kind of actually
later after
you know her FedEx
uh arrival
or or because maybe some of these scenes
um
are where she wasn't there
yeah
I don't know but
is the bulk gonna I guess not wait
um
oh what one did that happen
she was just remembering okay but this
kind of wasn't that I don't know did it
happen after she arrived and then you
know I don't know it's confusing it's
confusing to even talk about it I'm I'm
running in circles like this ball
and however I'm not finding the whole
while this one does
um yeah oh well
but it's okay I mean yeah she she
followed through and she's like well
well
how is that the end of the shrine
how
chest
am I missing something
is the chest on a wheel no
Nani
anyway
maybe there's a way of
using all the knowledge and the time
traveling to her Advantage so that she
can turn into a dragon but also go back
to non-dragon
right but um I mean otherwise that would
be insane why would she do that where's
his chest I mean maybe I don't care
about the chest content this is too easy
it's too easy
I don't think I really care about the
chest probably nothing special inside
just below the wheel
I hear something
like this
whatever I don't care
I don't care no
nothing says
probably just [\h__\h] in there I did not
care oh four let's go
it's just a topaz okay then I really
don't care not worth it unless you're
trying to get hundred percent and then
you also kind of question yourself
is it really worth it you glitched out
of the Strand ceiling what
okay
um
here's a question should I fly into this
I'm guessing no
we should go to info right I can
[Music]
like usually show it shows up in the
cities that I like fixed
after I fixed them
[Music]
or should I get the memory first yeah
right because
does that add on to the
last memory
okay
spider link has to go
and and maybe we can activate the tower
in this uh uh land of unknown
we don't know where it is maybe it's
there on the
on the little island looking thing
spy link spider link ah this place where
the gliac is
the Dragon
hi
where can I see the tower
from here
that's not it
[Music]
um
a bit hard in this weather yeah
stop
I mean
I'll just fly towards the memory for now
I see I see I spy I spy with my little
eye a village or something down there
interesting
and and whatever that is on top of like
a
Terror town this one or that one
we wanted to go to Tarrytown anyway
oh I see it oh
should I go here buff oh
want you there
oh they have a roller coaster
wait let's go to the Middle Island first
because that's kind of more difficult ah
snooze
too many options
Hudson construction site oh
this track is not really distracted I
needed the tower anyway
oh
foreign
stuff
I guess I'll climb the rest
what is it that protects this shrine
and
a tower
yo Jihan oh no
did I ever make something sticky
no because I'm always like I don't need
anything
for real for real
that's supposed to be sunny here
yeah uh-huh
that's what I thought
hi what's up
I see what's going on
don't worry I'll do what do you mean
stop
we met at another Skyview Tower didn't
we it asked people did you come to
subscribe your Tower I hate to say but
things are a bit of a mess right now
[Music]
the flying monster took the terminal
from the Skyview Tower
huh good grief that sticky claw Terror
has a habit of stealing bangs I'll never
fix the Skyview Tower at this rate don't
worry it's one hit wonder
did it go
[Music]
that's Zelda right
oh
[Applause]
uh I see the balloon
I haven't seen that one in a while
[Music]
stressful
uh uh no uh let's carry it over do we
have to attach it with our special glue
is he once again to fix it
I am the fixer
leave it to me
[Music]
oh oh okay I know you want to do it okay
that's fine
am I a glue is Maybe
shouldn't be used here maybe you better
do it thanks oh thank you
thank you
yay
wait wait wait wait wait
if I fly up I know I'm gonna like go
elsewhere first before going to him
so what do I do
I walked to the balloon dude and then I
go to the tower then I go to Terry town
then I go to the last memory
got it
[Music]
greetings and gun meetings
what a nice traveler from before you
gave me a bubble gum so kind funny
thanks you know it was a very special
moment for me yes very special
gems I must have more but I'm sorry I
wasn't answering Planet I've been
traveling from online
when will I become a Saturday what am I
to do I can't bring a coincidence for me
to get a traveler fate yes
wait brought us back together I'm sure
please if you get your fingers on any
more bubble gums would you give them to
me I promise I'll give you a suitable
Treasures in exchange for him for
example we'll come here
whoa that Misty clothing there is all
yours if you bring me lots and lots of
football gems
yes and yes if you get your fingers on
any bubble gems please bring them to me
I'll be traveling far and wide and
search all those gems myself so if you
spot the stall at night don't be shy to
come by
yes I forgot to mention something
important I wanted to come to Bubble
gems I believe gobbling down money at
once is the key to turn to Saturday
so in the future please bring me the
quantity I asked for all together the
reward I give you will be based on how
many gems you give me a good deal for us
both
I'll trade them for Treasure well I only
have 25
really
I feel like I have like 15.
what
hmm okay
gotta get more
gonna get get gotta get get gotta get
get get
[Music]
modeling mask okay I have to go by order
of what he gives me I suppose
I feel something bubbling up from deep
inside me
oh give me more I'm sorry now that I'm
myself once more please here is a
treasure I promised you
okay looking blended with the moblins
now let's move on in a little secret
ever since I ate the first bubble gem
I've been able to sense the presence of
bubble frogs no not all of them for you
I can put my bubble wrong feelings to
where I can see God's places they're
likely to be found of course if you
happen to have anyone no we don't need
that we already get if we ask sadly he
shows us the caves anyway
yeah well how how would you tell me
oh well let's see what you got next
the he knocks toenail what
there was gonna be like
more masks and other pieces you're gonna
give me a [\h__\h] toenail
or until I get the armor what it doesn't
sound fair at all
you little [\h__\h]
you what
what's next oh
oh something cool oh does it glow
looks kind of cool like uh the light
blue
pretty easy the Mystic rope what does it
do
of course let me tell you what about the
Mystic world the mistake headpiece rope
and trousers something really it's rare
Treasures indeed according to ancient
text Solera is protected from any in the
Holland
but it's also said these strange clothes
prevented whatever from becoming rich or
Turkish trade-off no I tried to win it
myself with the sizes doesn't seem to
fit what yeah
what how does what
how does that work
instead of taking my heart to text my
money why
pay to win armor I see if we're like in
a really really
it's like difficult situation we could
do it but um
I see
I mean at least it looks cool
rupee padding
yeah
I don't know
oh next we got some eyes I do like eyes
I do use them a lot so
that's fun
but then
the more armor wait is it just not as
effective now
and if I wear the full set I really
don't lose any hearts or how how is the
difference from wearing one piece to a
full set
oh it's another mask
the Liz Alpha's mask
cannot upgrade oh that's okay
three hearts herpes
[Music]
wait so if I get hit with something that
would take five hearts
it will only block free hearts
and take the money and then for the rest
it's still like
[Music]
makes me lose two hearts
ah [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
huh
I'll just use everything up that I have
for now
and then I guess if I ever happen to
randomly see him again I'll be back but
otherwise he's not a big urge to oops
[\h__\h]
do this to be honest
I just want the one set
I don't know if he has anything after
that but
he's already giving us the pants
Mystic trousers
aha
[Music]
why it made
Lionel white mate Lionel mace horn four
of them or what no just one
one okay okay okay I can put that on the
weapon that's pretty strong I think
it's
for your 40. oh
is this a Lionel mask no wait is it is
it a gun mask so Ganon doesn't recognize
me I don't know
well I surely don't have enough but
what is this
okay we're just missing the headpiece oh
it looks cool it has that big fluffy
hair and the subtly like thingies
eyebrows or whatever
but so far
it looks like this
okay the pattern is a little bit
Overkill maybe I like the pants though
like we could
oh there's no no it doesn't work
maybe this
oh
Oh I thought that matches somewhat
look at me with that fancy sword
sheesh dripping
I'm dripping money
puffy pants normally like IRL I don't
like them that much though
anyway
um okay
back to the tower almost forgot
yeah it's the last line of defense this
armor I agree normally I don't think
I'll wear it
but
no the more cloves in my closet the more
I feel like my heart my heart's
depression is being filled with fake
happiness and what
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is how women cope
this is why we have so many clothes and
shoes the more clothes and shoes the
woman has the more depressed she is just
kidding
well I mean I mean maybe in some cases I
mean maybe you know maybe you're a lady
likes to buy herself happiness with
material things
[Music]
[Laughter]
uh-huh
[Music]
[Laughter]
my closet
is filled to the brim with a ton of
clothes
[Music]
and I am a material girl oh don't worry
about me guys don't worry I'm okay I'm
okay
I don't want to talk about it no no
I I'm not having an existential crisis
I'm not I'm not suffering deeply in my
heart and I'm wounded by life and
scarred for life no no I'm okay I am I'm
100 okay I'm I'm
healthy I am happy
I am
good
yeah that am I am stable as a rock Crown
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
um
anyway we
color
no I'm I'm I am
I good I am really good yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
there's no tears in my eyes it's just
sweat
[Music]
oh
God I'm spiraling I don't know if I'm
lying to myself or if I'm just you know
oh let's buy them
anyway
t-o-t-k is currently
the priority
of my life this must be a level one
because there's no platforms
things
unless oh there's fans
[Music]
um
oh wait I have no
proper weapon wait a second
let me make although I don't have
the base act I can never use this I
guess
I can reuse it
because I don't want to attach donut
materials to
non-donite
basis you know what I mean because it's
like ineffective
so
that's okay I don't know what level that
dude is but
we'll see
I'll use this
hopefully that's enough
there's fans which is like okay a more
difficult way in my opinion to get up to
him but
like when but you know we'll see we'll
see
we'll see uh we'll see
oh
I see it
[Music]
smart I don't think he did that on
purpose that was by accident that just
so happened to be in the way
oh
okay
um
I see it but
[Music]
nice crab
wait
[Music]
no no time but thanks guys for helping
they got some hits okay uh ah wait
no wait no
[\h__\h] hell I can't see it
let's go go Lift Me Up
yeah
okay
does it get any stronger
alrighty
[Music]
hit him too late
okay we did good the good damage oh
[Music]
oh
and then
what
[Music]
it already turned its back on me but no
problem
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
thanks this is what this one drops yummy
steaks wait if I
um detach what's currently on it
and then attach this one to it does it
kind of like renew
the
like you know what I mean renew the
durability no
unfortunately
maybe on the desk Claymore away the
chests okay
please give me a base weapon I'm out of
weapons I used so many weapons yesterday
ah [\h__\h]
it really doesn't do much for pastry
okay
[Music]
oh wait the uh
oh Rock OCTA Rock specifically
I know aftermarks make weapons pretty I
didn't know they they fixed their
ability
oh yeah yeah I can
attach and then now that we're at
Tarrytown
well then I'll I'll just for now attach
it to the dusk clamor
I won't be using it though not really
planning on using it
okay welcome to the membership pool
um now
we go to Tarrytown like I promised you
but wait there's a
there's a flower Island below
is that below or above because
I don't see
one above
okay it was very very high above
Aldo maybe I want to try and get it
I don't want to try and get it wait
there's some tools over there
I had a plan we'll plan we'll plan
you can I didn't have a plan
what's that plan
plan
no such thing
I do not know oh this is perfect it's
already they even made
already how can I say no to this
uh
it's actually like it feels like it's
specifically made for the purpose that I
need it for
with that amount of fans
Ryan
is there another like interesting thing
up there possibly but
because uh
I'm coming for you I don't see it but
where is it
for now let's just rise
we kind of like added one more fan maybe
and then saved it in my
ah you'll be you'll be
now I can still eat some
batteries
well we can almost make it
[Music]
oh
maybe four is actually enough
surprisingly
almost not gonna risk it
um
not gonna risk it
yeah that's enough
I think
alrighty
maybe stay
it's why can you not turn the camera
wait
my father would fall down or am I gonna
fall down which one is it gonna be
please do not
thank you
okay I wanna like improve this if I add
some some of my own batteries
It's Gonna Save it too right
maybe two
like this
it would cost more that's okay
I want this to be a very efficient way
to reach height more than the hot air
balloon if I don't need so much height I
can just make the hot air balloon so
just saved it right now
I wish you could kind of name them too
that would be nice
[Music]
so we could jump over there
check out Elise
what that is
what would you name this
efficient
upheaval of Link Link evil efficient
link evil
yes I have the wingsuit of course I have
the wingsuit
they could just Glide right
we will we will
trust me oh wait fairy sounded I really
need fairies I really need fairies
I'm gonna get all four of them I think
it's usually always four
uh
why are you so high
oh it's descending for me
come on
Palmer I I was on the phone with you for
one hour yesterday why are you treating
me like [\h__\h] now um
do I really deserve that no so come on
be true to your feelings
or are you not really where I think you
are okay
wait
come on
I don't want to jump and mess it up
huh
ah why is it so high
ah
the next one
I see you
I know you don't even have to be this
careful
but I don't want to lose them so
wait is there only free
or is it so bright that I can't see the
fourth one
frog bird wouldn't play games are you
saying I should go for frog bird instead
where'd it go there
I thought it was always four
come on
where are you going
[Music]
oh
oh oh oh oh it's pretty low
but not low enough
what
I'm gonna jump
Maybe
maybe I'll give you one more chance come
on
bye
guys
a fairy bait would be nice yeah
jump down no
wait it's descending again
a little bit but not enough
what the [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
but
yuppie
oh it's pretty low
what
oh wait it's so confusing
please do not kill the fairy
thank you
I don't need to sneak with the stealth
armor really I don't know how careful I
actually need to be
I don't see the fairy I see it
I'm too stupid
for jumping off a wall
[Music]
how do I jump off
this way okay
descending onto Fairy Oh my stamina
a fairy [\h__\h] you
and [\h__\h] you [\h__\h] you till then because
kind of your fault too
because I pressed a but you know
I thought it was another fairy oh well
okay whatever I'm not gonna care okay is
there like uh
chest in here no
why
are these Platforms in there
kind of sauce
yeah the Sages
they they are the worst wingmen ever
we are going to the last memory
oh there's a Chasm here too
[Music]
what is that
I want the Tracer sauce
everything's so sauce
is that like a pirate boat no it's the
eyes enemy camp okay
probably gonna go to the very middle
right yep I see it I see it
[Music]
foreign
what on Earth
the dragon comes out of the
eh
[Music]
all of them do that
can I get a scale
[Music]
not again
um
okay eh
I want oh I want a scale
not that far am I
come on
yeah it flew over this time
[Music]
flew over again
what
the hell
was I really that far still
I want I want to get a piece of the
Dragon
oh
yo I want to go to the Maldives actually
the other day I was looking at
more hotels from the Maldives
and kind of I guess fantasizing
oh I could go to this one I could go to
this one but
I was even considering kind of going
alone
but apparently I checked again about the
monsoon season and apparently it's not
um gonna end until
like
November
it's so long
so I have to
I feel like it it did say that like May
and so on where we went before is the
most
like the worst the most rainy the most
stormy
there's like two months in the monsoon
season that are like the actual worst
and I feel like October so even though
it officially still is part of the
monsoon season
don't run
I feel like it it could be okay
but if I'm gonna wait that long that I
might as well
wait until
well November I guess
because I wanted to be perfect this time
I want to go to the Maldives again and I
want I want it to be perfect
I don't know with home though
I know I could go with Lena again but
maybe I should go someone else I don't
know just you know
more different kind of experience it's
not that Elena wasn't fun you know being
with her
[Music]
but in the end who will go with me but
Elena
oh gotta bring Subaru
if I tell her
this early
I feel like
even though you know she's also very
busy I feel like Japanese members are
just busy and always prioritize work
um don't think they don't even think
about vacations but I think
I think I think she could make it work
Martin
yeah one-on-one Maldives vacation where
I think she would love
the idea you know of going to the
Maldives
she's just usually like generally very
worried about traveling like she wants
to bring her manager
I'm like what's these you have me
but she's like worried about like the
flight really because that's the part
where she would be alone
it's not that difficult it's not that
bad you go into you know especially like
from Japan Japan to for example Austria
it's not so bad because in Japan they
still speak Japanese
and then you arrive in Austria and it's
really not a big deal here like uh but
she's so worried what is this anyway
huh
he's so worried man
I wish I could take that Warrior from
her
yeah I'll ask a couple of them because I
I really want to go again I think it
would be nice to also just share this
experience with someone else too because
I made very special memories with
um Dana but why not
like do it with like make memories of
others too
oh wait okay I get it
get Amy out of her comfort zone
I think Maldives is a little bit too
perfect for her I feel like she would
prefer more of a messy vacation I don't
know
not so perfect vacation you know you
know what I mean she's not like the type
who wants to go to the most perfect
picturesque
um
like honeymoon quality vacation you know
she wants to go either on like an
adventure type vacation
I would say
like you know Japan
or
I don't know
why is there flamethrowers
I don't understand this shrine
clapping oh yeah that would be oh that
would be cool but Ahmed would probably
prefer normal camping
because they're cool
strange just to burn me
well you throw them down
where did that go
ah
I literally thought I just died in real
life
whoa whoa what
yeah I was thinking of putting it like
here
oh wait oh chuck oh what
is
it hey why is there water now
wait
[Applause]
[Laughter]
huh
wait okay let's do like let's do this uh
this I mean no
um
I I don't even know what wait the middle
I don't even know what the end goal is
huh
[Laughter]
ah ah okay if if the water comes out
because if one candle or so
is lit
that's not enough it has to be all of
them lit at the same time otherwise it
will pour water over it and if all the
candles are on
then yeah
you know
but
how do I accomplish that if if it's not
if it's not what I thought it was
quick
it has to be something like and turn off
the fan first
okay okay
what won't it still lose its balance
maybe I have to get two
um
it goes pretty fast let's see
oh wait
oh
oh okay
apparently it does not lose its balance
if you have it on there from the start
oh chest
nah
and
maybe yeah okay
don't burn me don't don't don't don't
wait
it will not close the door again right
let's just make a normal wind so I think
that's plenty
three months up I'll hold my breath
until your official visit comes
huh
thanks for three months but do you mean
like when I would come back to Korea
yeah when I go to Korea this year too
but like really I'm just like when can I
visit all these places this year some
summer is like
hacked so far okay that was not worth it
um oh well
at least you know I've been kind of like
wondering oh who will go to a spa
vacation a short one uh two night
s get away with me right because
friend's too busy and friend no money
and I mean I I invited her to a spa get
away before that was quite luxurious
but I don't I don't think I want to do
it like all the time you know just for
the sake of not being alone
but I talked a little bit today with my
sister
because I have a sister
half sister
and she likes
Spa getaways very much too and wouldn't
mind going to them even monthly
and as long like she will pay her part
as long as it's not like too crazy
expensive she said so
so maybe you know maybe I'll go to
spaghettaway with my sister I haven't
done something like this like I I never
do one-on-one things with her
um so I think I might actually be really
nice you know bonding time and all that
um
she lives pretty
far from me
so we don't don't meet much either
and I missed the last opportunity
you know when my family was everybody
was getting together except for me
because I was sick and all and busy and
all that
um
right after America
so
yeah
yeah but I I'm excited so we're thinking
maybe in July because she's already
going on one this month
but she said she doesn't mind going to
one in July
yay
I'll treat myself to Something in July
excited here's the last last for real
for real memory anyway
no
idea
[Music]
foreign
I want to
Take It All In
properly
Bring It On
supposed to be some kind of Revelation
right
it has to be
good
didn't we hear that in English before
here
[Music]
mm-hmm
meaning
[Music]
cute
link
is
thank you
this is
[Music]
back
where I met some dragon is
[Music]
foreign
pill to swallow
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
[Applause]
don't forget the sword
[Music]
oh god
um
[Music]
wow
that's so lonely
we have to turn her back to normal
[Music]
foreign
Telco
tell them do you remember me
[Music]
so that's hard for me to get up that
high can you come down
ah complete
oh my God
she's literally a silent princess now
because she can't talk like you know
like you know her soul
her soul does she really have no soul
because if she didn't have a soul would
she really like we doing this as a
dragon you know oh man oh man
oh man Zelda off the stones are the
stones to reach her where's she going
where are you going
where does she go
after her but no I have to go to impa
mm-hmm
hey you little [\h__\h] I'm having an
emotional moment
man I quite a little bit
so after hair really
ah
I don't know this is kind of a guy thing
you know running after the lady sorry
I'm I'm I'm I'm not I'm not a pro at
this
all right all right where's this piece
but that's kind of like already far away
[Music]
foreign
to go after her now
[Music]
this is
do I just pick up the sword is that all
I'm doing
just take it out of her claws and I'm
like bye bye bye
bye bye bye bye
okay
is that Zelda
I guess it no that's sorry sorry Zelda
uh there it is
eldra sorry eldra maybe I'll say hi to
you too sometime
on Friday oh my dragon get on it
my pony my dragon
how's it go
instead of pony dragon
is it on your forehead by any chance
because I didn't see it
I didn't see it maybe it's
in her for I mean there's something
glowing there
but that's I think the tier
foreign
on her
Zelda hi
yeah okay
she's can I mine the gems on her back
was that maybe not like appropriate
chilling I can't
oh my God
what what is that anyway though
and also it's gonna fall down
eh oh
cool wait are they all used up now it
kind of looks like it deactivated them I
get just one
free shards on her back to pick up it's
kind of difficult to walk around here I
have I'm scared
[Music]
yeah
three shards oh I think I see something
oh
what
destructive when fused to a weapon but
only has 12 attack power
and also in views that weapon with
healing power
can I hit it again no okay
quite the hike
[Music]
yo
she's so gentle
if you fall off use the glider yeah I'll
be fine I'll be fine but I guess yeah
she's creating an upwind isn't she
I think that's plenty
one more
12 to pick up oh exactly 12.
maybe I got them all now
just Minecrafting my wife nothing to see
here
I can't believe she turned herself into
a [\h__\h] dragon
you scared me
he turned himself into a pickle
pickle Rick
unbelievable
okay I'm back
oh come on
thanks
[Laughter]
oh
there it is
hi hi Bella
good night can I head Pat you
you little snoot
it's really a nice ride man
selfie with wife
uh
I don't know how to take it but
it's a spoiler anyway so I can't even
upload it on Twitter I think shouldn't I
shouldn't do it
chill eh
wait one sword
[\h__\h] help
I thought like but smash myself
assistant smash smash but no it's like
holding it longer
also I need some stamina
let's see if I have enough
oh
[Music]
hold on
get back your sword
yeah come on
oh there's a lot of stamina
[Music]
think
I don't have much left please okay cool
oh
yeah you need quite quite a bit of
stamina which means for wait but I guess
you don't need to do you need a Master
Sword to finish the game
I wonder if like speedrunners need to do
this
no but it helps
um technically no okay
um
you gave up or what
or she just chilled out okay
wow
we're in heaven
holy light upon us
oh
wait a second I want to turn off mine
Dyson but it doesn't want to be turned
off
okay
oh no it's still on oh well
whoa
it's golden it's filled with light
oh
it peels off
[Music]
wow
wrong button
[Music]
link hmm
link
yeah
what are we gonna do about you
that's Master [\h__\h]
[Music]
in the morning
can it really though
[Music]
that is
better
[Music]
foreign
there's been thousands and thousands and
thousands of years
because she's been a dragon
foreign
[Music]
We Are Not Gonna Leave You like that I
promise I mean unless the game makes it
impossible impossible for me but I'm
gonna try my best
that would be such a lonely and sad
ending
um
swords
the legendary sword that seals the
darkness this time for real for real its
corruption was healed by its time of the
light dragon
what got the [\h__\h] monster sword wait
I just realized oh my God that means you
know we can use it
the blade gleams with a sacred luster
luster that can oppose the Demon King
oh my God
will it not break right maybe it needs
to charge or something like that
or not even that maybe
pretty we got the shield and the sauce
[Music]
it breaks every now and then
it can be fused
refuse it to a tree branch no
[Music]
oh
it charges up to 10 minutes okay okay
I thought you meant it breaks like
completely I have to go to Terry town to
repair it or something like that
okay we are back to this area
now I suppose it's time to talk to imba
um maybe look out Landing
oh she's in the temple
[Music]
what
oh
okay
I hear
what what's wrong or the temple with the
maps
there's like
are you one guy no there were two people
who said so I think there were two
people
[Music]
but
I did kind of wanna you know do this
like thing here too like I have not
dumb this thing with these things like I
don't I don't even
I guess it's not main quest but
I kind of want to do it
and now I'm here so
I guess I'll do it can't yet oh okay
what for real
mmm okay
everybody's moving around no idea where
she is at this point of the game
oh I will come back here okay
okay then
[Music]
let's go move again
force is also something we need to do
and also we still don't have the map of
this area I don't even know what there
is in that area
but anyway the ruins are here right
let's go
talk to impa
ah
quote of course is useless after getting
the muscle sword what mostly yeah we
have to go to territown
[Music]
what
I wanna do
yeah
I want to do co-work first too why is it
meaningless now
okay
I mean the weird thing is like the
memories that she was like seeing again
like I I feel like I saw all of them
except
for the part
where like there was a part where she
was talking to the tree was that from
breath of the wild or was it a memory
that I was like
supposed to see before going to her
okay breath of the wild then okay okay
I wonder I guess maybe the tree would
have
nudged me to
but I I guess I think I had all the
information I needed
oh the flowers
at her grave
um
okay there they are here yokata
foreign
defend them
[Music]
down
wow okay
it's so long
oh
ah link are you making progress in your
investigation of the Geo Clips wait what
what what do you mean you what do you
mean you finished them all and then
found another one that I didn't know
about another tier and and then jumped
on on on Zelda's back and pulled the
master sword wait wait wait why are you
not updating me more in between what the
hell yeah so the dragon's tears were
shed by Princess Zelda when she
transformed and the geoglyphs were drawn
by an ancient people who touched those
memories and saw a visions
other people also saw the Visions I
thought they lost my own private Visions
the [\h__\h]
perhaps in the past they were more
attuned to that sort of thing than the
people of today
um I understand now so that is the truth
of it all link is all of the memories
you saw are true then that means
since our Princess Zelda has become the
light dragon she can never again don't
say
don't return to her original form
it is painfully tragic our dear Princess
Zelda no
it cannot be I agree there must be a way
some efforts to restore princess Zella
to her former self
let me think chickens let's put our
heads together
let's put our heads together and think
think with me we have to do something
we use rewind on no way wait
we will rewind that far
[Music]
yeah the stone get the stone out of her
um link God will return to kakariko
Village and review the ancient
literature once more that is the most I
can do to help Princess Zelda
okay
that brings us
cool but before that
well I need to go to Tarrytown
because I forgot about it
you have to go
finally Terrytown are there lots of
beetles
beetle
whoa Terrytown
and aren't they gonna build houses on
all these like spots here or what
because the the building company is here
too right
[Music]
construction site
can I talk to someone
who is in charge of this here huh
yeah can I get my own house
because it would be nice if I could like
leave a weapon
like the dusk weapon or so
in a house but no way this is no this
there's a car
does that mean this is just like for
driving around
wait all right so and this isn't what we
agree to we left the desert and tracked
down the line here because you said when
to get to drive a vehicle like no one's
ever seen before and now that we're here
the only vehicle you've got is some
piece of junk that no one can control
okay
take us for
some lady
you've got it all wrong it's like I said
before I'm working without some
construction to make Vehicles out of the
solar devices another debris that fell
from the sky and yes that's true we
haven't figured out how to control these
vehicles but that's why we asked you
here we're hoping professional races
like the two of you can offer some
guidance so what's it what are you even
talking about we're a Racers not
Scholars okay don't try to confuse us
with your fancy words
um you found nothing among these tonight
devices capable of controlling your
vehicles
sadly no none of the devices we found
here in Terrytown work
hey I'm standing right here don't cut me
out of this old Chit Chat didn't you say
those Zoo finger mom blah blah before
from the age of Legends you're trying to
tell me that something that old and run
down is still useful please
we did come all the way here it couldn't
hurt to put our heads together
besides it's important for a racer to
know her right as well as she knows her
own hands wasn't it you who taught me
natural born
I'm fine if tally wants to help enough
is what we'll do
can I drive
so side quests I'll do it on my own
probably
we've got so much to do
um
what's going on here
oh well
I haven't been in a while in a long time
it's a fun side quest I'm join thank you
thank you
[Music]
um
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
what is the special thing about this
well because there's always something
special
about each well
is it also connected to a cave
actually I could have ascended here I
guess
oh well
it is a cave
construction site cave
oh
wheel wheel
rocket fan
steering stick and the small wheel
and a purple
wait how do I get to you
I did well I like the music here
and there's different different entrants
that will lead in there okay okay okay
huh
I shall wait them wait
it's funny how the main question is
called find solo but you actually find
her in the master Circle instead huh
I guess so yeah you didn't you kind of
don't accomplish it really
I like this this
normally I feel like it's used for like
tropical sounds but this place doesn't
really
like give me a tropical Vibe even when
hearing that
it's kind of different
you
good smile you want the kiwala figma
speaking of I saw
um apparently does this one actually
work I saw apparently the MMD was
already updated
I wasn't notified of it by Steph I need
to check with general like hello
it happened apparently
um
can I tell people now but I retweeted it
already
thinking
that was a good comparison
that picture I didn't even know
that my old model compared to my new
model that the new model has like uh
bigger shoes
they just look like more properly
modeled in the new model
I didn't even realize and then I was
like comparing the butt sizes because
this was such a good comparison actually
and I was I was thinking like hmm the
curve of the butt itself isn't like much
more compared to the old model and yet
it overall looks like a buffed right
especially from a different angle and
then what I realized is rather than
buffing the butt only the fights got
thicker
which
like balances out and makes it less
noticeable that the butt is bigger
you have to pay attention to how the
thighs are actually thicker
hmm
yeah but from behind it was way more
noticeable like there's an ass crack
like in the skirt you could see the line
the ass line
laughs
so it's like oh wait it looks like they
did stuff
I kind of just like pay attention to
where they did it
nicely sculpted
I don't know I don't know if I really
like the ass crack from the skirt but
you know at least overall the
so so so so
uh download
it's the new model like it updates on
its own
if you have already the old model
does it update on its own
or do you have to download it yourself
you have to re-download okay
see that's why I want to notify people
of the new model
um
okay there it is inside this thing
it's a catch a machine have you never
seen a castle machine before
I was wrangling to see that thing and
not be able to get stuff inside thanks
for figuring it out you could have just
broken the glass top
yes I actually think it might be
possible possibly it's really amazing
Discovery probably in Contraptions like
this one have shown up in places other
than just Terrytown yeah yeah
could it be that the type of tuna
devices inside each areas Contraption
yep
oh thank you thank you
oh thank you for telling me things I
already know
balloon whales
lots of Wheels here
is that all
yeah
Rockets Wheels everything
it's different things
and there's ducks
are they male or female hmm
hard to tell
Shabbat
ducks are terrible I've come to the
conclusion ducks are terrible
and
maybe I'm secretly grateful that Subaru
is not a real
what
it's better this way
I can't climb it's rainy
flower
okay we gotta go to Terry town
guess we're going with a cart
oh wait oh
honey I stand on the side can I go
they're actually using the donut devices
what
they're already
wow
making proper use of it damn they
figured it out
without my help
it's pretty impressive
ah
it's kind of a go wrong music but mixed
of Terror town
I hear it
some nuances in Korean music it's kind
of cute
ah Hudson construction yeah because
they're not using glue they're just
using chains to chain it together
but they tried
and what kind of works
weaponizing the local travel
oh wait there's a shrine Stone
well do I want to use I'm using it right
now you know
there's a fee for that you're free to
use it once you pay up
what tell me that before what wait so if
you go from the top to somewhere it will
cost
but if you go from the bottom to the top
it doesn't
what if I make my own rail car and just
use the track
that's so cute
[Music]
for real car repairs I'm coming around
but wait you have to film can I you're
probably not gonna give me the stone are
you
I thought it might be valuable when I
picked it up but this weird rock is
giving me the creeps I've gotta hurry
and find some sucker to um heading to
the construction Center there's a small
fee to use the rail car I'll collected
excuse me
no but I want ah [\h__\h] wait that was an
option
are you interested in this rock I found
it buried at the construction site it's
a rare Rock so I stole I mean I took it
as a Memento but if you're interested I
would consider selling it for you
hundred
nah
for once it actually
pays off to
get them so to Hackle a little bit
because like I saw him saying maybe
he'll buy this stupid Stone off of me
he's not sure like what the actual value
is
oh
now we got a quest
what are you doing
[Music]
are you trying to sell random junk for
an outrageous prices again look at that
thing it's basically just a really big
piece of flint
50 rupees is more than a fair price but
I already said in the absolutely fair
price and you might have okay no need
for the stern wife look
thank you lady what do you say 50 rupees
okay that's the lowest they go
I guess you could have bought it for 100
huh are you dead ah stupid chicken
[Music]
that's why you gotta watch my streams
okay Milestone now
thanks I'll take care of that later
look at him
nah
okay oh
just yesterday she was talking about it
happily perhaps you're overthinking it
though I do understand I know you're
worried about the about Madison moving
[Music]
oh I know he told me that America sooner
it's been acting cheerful lately I can't
help but wonder if she's you know just
putting on the bold face after all she's
going to be picked up soon
please if you keep acting like this it
will only make it more difficult for
Madison to leave this is a once in a
lifetime Journey for a Gerudo
is it their child
we should support her and give her a
grand sent off
you're right of course it's special
journey and we should do something big
for her oh my God
uh a customer
welcome to the Hudson construction let
me guess you're in the market for a
dream home yes
that's the surprise our unique modular
building salad to put rooms together to
create the perfect home but I'm so sorry
we're still not ready for opening our
business oh
look who it is it true has been a while
you know thanks to you Terry tale he's
doing real good
nowadays is to cut a village that World
Cups folks from all over to come live in
peace and we have a daughter who looks
just like her papa she's wonderful but
oh I hope she didn't like inherit the
huge ass head that you have
Egghead
my little medicine
Hudson you've got to get it together oh
is that her oh my God she did haha
I think she did sorry I've got to go
we're kind of busy right now I'm going
back to work now Ronson but don't worry
I'll try to think of something nice wait
wait
wait wait wait wait wait
hi you know what
it looks kind of cute on you
and you can still outgrow it when you
get bigger
I'm I I I I I pray for you
I pray for your Egghead
poor kid but girl it still looks
okay-ish
I think
um
but you know how
like so many Garuda or like all of them
have like almost all of them have like
these ponytails at the very like top of
their head I feel like this PO this kind
of style hairstyle would really not suit
you girl you have to
do something that's more like side side
volume
to even out you know because you have a
really long head I don't know if you're
aware girl but you're really long head I
got that too so you have to add volume
to the side of your head
um
yeah yeah
just letting you know for the future
right now I don't think anybody gives a
[\h__\h] about your head your head literally
looks like that Bell up there
okay I'll stop that I'll stop being mean
hey mister are you a friend of Papa's he
was gone for a long time but now he's
back home I'm gonna be moving soon so I
gotta make sure I'm playing with Papa
and every Sunday else
what everyone Ellen a whole bunch while
I still can't still can
they were added to my profile thingy
was that really necessary
[Music]
is this like a Minecraft thing where
everybody gathers if I hit the Bell
oh
well something happened
ah
oh and breath of the wild you get them
married I don't remember that oh
that's cute
oh what do we have here bombs
mmm Dazzle fruit
what's this
oh monster apparently it can be used to
make a number of monstrous meals
oh I see him
oh I don't know I think I'm good for now
thanks though
did you buy a house
hello again thanks for helping out with
those 100 oh it's you
I can't believe they misheard explore
all other paths as explore in underpants
yeah yeah yeah
I know that's not funny but it's really
funny anyway I'm just glad I don't have
to work in my Underpants and it's
because
where are you a guy
because you opened everyone's eyes to
the naked truth
enough
they have an in here
[Music]
um
cute house
inside it's kind of cute
outside it looks like this like playing
blocks that children use like Toddlers
and so on
oh nice nice Terrace as well quite
spacious
what's up with you
[Music]
I know it's just out there walking
awaiting my tour to chat with him but I
ended up falling asleep I came to help
clear out the donor devices
huh
[Music]
[\h__\h] I can't finish my yawns even though
it's so big yeah I was just acting it
out and that was the real one
laughs
[Music]
oh that was good ah
I got tears in my eyes from that that's
such an emotional yawn
okay
rude stuff fell all over the workshop
here I heard that you could use that but
I'm still really tired I think I'll go
sleep with the boys same same man I feel
you so much
so if I what what do I have to do for
you guys in order to get a house
[Music]
my husband I feel so unsure about things
I mentioned here earlier we have a
daughter named Madison she's wonderful
Madison as well she's going to leave I
moved to my wife's birthplace career to
town I'm going to have a lot of sets
they can't associate with men until they
come of age
I'm pretty sure she kind of did already
but okay
hmm
I should have raised her there already
Logan I mean it's fine while they are
very young oh okay but when they start
to become more aware of the world around
them someone comes from Garuda town to
pick them up that's crazy
that's like Social Services
picking up your child in Sims
ripping it away from you but here it's
normal I've been told that bogaruto
spending time in Guru town is an honor
and Madison does seem to be looking
forward to it anyway I want to give her
a big send of but I didn't realize this
would be so hard for me sorry I had to
listen
[Music]
how do I help you
you're so business you can't even take
work around my Muslims someone would
spend time with medicine so she wouldn't
be so lonely okay okay
oh
there he goes oh okay updated
where's she
go
[Music]
she was just running in circles here
is she inside
now
hi cute
well your room's kind of a mess though
oh she's like trying things wait what is
she drawing herself
and ah those uh manatees the sand and it
is oh oh and there's a picture that she
Drew off Garuda town as if she already
like knows what it looks like
good morning is
what's goodbye
unfriended me like that for a second I
thought you were here to take me away on
my big Journey
I'm doing all this studying because I'm
moving to Mama's Hometown soon where
she's from this is amazing language
called Cavuto
I want to teach every son
in the village to speak it to so I've
made in my mission
to memorize as many more days I can hey
would you like to learn some words too
mister ooh is there gonna be a test
I'm about to give a lesson to Granny
monadi you should come too after some
instructions from me you'll be speaking
Gerudo no time for this lesson I'm going
to be giving a Garuda Quest you should
try it oh I think I'll be fine
let's do it
let's do it let's do it
she has a
uh not only a rough
fate of
you know with her head to deal with
oh now she's going to sleep
God damn it
but also
the kuchigose the
um
her way of speaking Ariel what the [\h__\h]
it's also rough what the
[Music]
great idea
I'm bringing to you again
you met again with my younger brother
Colton didn't you Oh I thought you were
him
ah you see okay he's looking at him
here's a bit eccentric I know I know but
I hope you'll find it inside your heart
to try to move kindness
you probably Hilton at your service
response Upon a Time let me goes from
Monster Parks you're seeing travel about
some of them from my shop but once I
have saved up the title a little Nest
omelette I gave that salt to my young
little brother
I know just a lot of dirty land so that
I can at least make a real dream I've
dreamed since I was only killed sadly it
seemed so president of Hudson
construction is very busy
hmm
no true events and this is just between
you and me you and me well I have adored
monsters ever since I was a week Hilton
ah I want to create you know those cat
cafes in Japan I want to create a
monster Cafe isn't it genius you go
there to pet them with a slight chance
of dying when they attack you but it's
fun it's the excitement you know what I
mean
what Monster's disgusting that's what
they say well there you are so sensitive
to my sensitivities I know I know this
is a violent creatures and despise the
world oh because of it I'm not that I
cannot deny my theory also misunderstood
the way everyone hates them without even
trying to understand the pitiful traffic
and so I will educate the world about
monsters and once the world understands
monsters they will love monsters that is
my dream what's my plan to succeed I
require the system of the finest company
which one has never seen before
okay
[Music]
it's just like
the beginning of a house what it's kind
of weird
is this where his house will be
he got one of the special places because
I guess
are they gonna build more down here or
no maybe not but where does my house go
where does my house go
wait I want to wait at the fire
and maybe cook
um okay
um so we wanna make
something with stamina
let me cook we didn't think you wanted
the house but I do I do
heart resistance
oh wait
[Music]
let's make a few tiny ones for the cases
where
I just need a tiny bit more just to not
die
and then
one bigger one
and then just medicine type medicine
medicine medicine medicine
um
wait do I even have something for
medicine
yeah
uh
foreign
okay full wheel Plus
a full stamina and then this okay
it heals quite a lot of Hearts I don't
even want that so um
sure
ah
love the hint of dragon with Islands
theme
hmm
I just I generally love all the big GMS
it's so good
maybe one of these why not
sometimes I actually
could use it
man oh wait I can do this
character has a bit of all the town bgm
since it's a Melting Pot yeah yeah
that's what it felt like like it's
mixing them together
um
[Music]
foreign
they almost ran away
trade a little bit of World building
yeah full recovery plus 12.
oh [\h__\h] that's Overkill
but you know
if we're in a difficult situation
towards the end of the game I mean I
don't think we'll be in such a difficult
situation where I don't really need all
of this but
uh you know it'll make me feel safe
and cozy and confident
was this ah
defense
yeah I will eventually have to use it
um
[Music]
let's cook some more normal things
yeah I love cooking the simmered
Tomatoes it looks delicious
and
it kind of
uh is very useful
because I just often need something
that's not
filling up all of my hearts like too
many
oh
try cookies some of the truffles oh yeah
I know I know they're really really
special I know
but I want to cook something with a
proper recipe with them maybe
um
what can I do with a raw whole bird
I I wanna make something proper
maybe salt
Aya old jar
oh
where's the chicken
deep fried bird roast did you see that
look delicious
maybe this and then herbs yeah I never
use herbs
this can heal and
wait yeah speed up Hasty steamed meat
all right
[Music]
um
I'll be cooking all night by the time
I'm done the girl is probably awake
again
um what are these by the way
nothing they don't have a special effect
just herbs
[Music]
yeah we'll be cooking in real life later
how about
[Music]
this
okay
[Music]
how we looking
good I could make what three more dishes
um
[Music]
I need more ingredients
hmm
[Music]
I used to have so many
um
[Music]
I need to wait
um
what is this oh Fragrant Mushroom saute
it's new I made something new genius
oh this will be a mushroom onikini I
think
[Music]
yeah
okay I think one more thing I can make
[Music]
a truffle
with
oil
and salt probably just a mushroom Scala
oh hearty salt grilled mushrooms
hmm okay
mushroom when you get it doesn't sound
bad I really don't like mushrooms mmm
[Music]
yeah I got a lot of full heart items now
actually
[Music]
no reason to be sad all the mushrooms
can go to watoto instead
it's less than time
is there also what son
somewhere here for the lesson
[Music]
ah you're in a good mood today it's a
time for another lesson hey
and it's a special Car Zone too because
the new student is turning the class
okay now pay attention Granny monani
it's time for medicine going without the
quiz what is the good award for granny
um
maybe Baba because Baba
I think
yeah
that's my guess
yay I actually never heard it before in
the game I think
but I'm just connecting it to Baba
kibaba Japanese way of saying like kind
of a rude way of saying old lady
um Japanese coming in clutch exactly
good thinking
okay what's the next question Bring It
On
is there more
I feel better knowing Mama will be okay
but now I need to think of a way to help
Papa um I got it Papa's always so busy
so I'll just make it my mission to help
him with his work
okay I'm going to ride the rail car to
the job site where he does all his work
what I want more of the quiz
lame I wanted to prove my Gerudo skills
oh
Madison trees had to grow up too quickly
at her age you should be clinging to her
mama and Papa's legs not working up with
sweat to try to make sure they're happy
but then on the other hand they just
want her to be happy
oh it's kind of titty
I want to ride the rail car so I can get
to Papa's close Rock so I'm sorry I
didn't help him to get his work done but
I forgot that guy won't give me
permission to write unless I pay him
I go with you
I've never had to pay until he took over
that little bastard because I'm gonna go
have to hop aboard the rail car without
him noticing how am I gonna do that all
by myself what I need is for someone to
Maybe cover his eyes okay okay
um
uh-huh that's what I was looking for
that's it
now pay attention
uh there you go his eyes are covered
wait
what if I completely close it I guess
[Music]
yeah because I saw another one oh wait
oh
okay I can't use these
but that's actually already tall enough
and he's covering his eyes anyway
go now go now
you can go down yeah
I did that yeah easy easy but the real
car isn't where it should be I need to
get it you know
what is it at the bottom or the top
[Music]
oh
is that it down there
[Music]
yeah right here okay
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
pasta
go go go go go go go go
who knows how long he will be
covering his eyes like an idiot
maybe we can end him quickly
with our unable charge
that would surely help
he might never open his eyes ever again
come on come on
blocking my view thanks for telling me
I'm working on it
stop it
it breaks
oh
because of
that I thought you couldn't see
it didn't happen the first time I bunked
it
will he go back to me
ah
laughs
I messed it up
[Music]
okay
but why does it fall over this time
[Music]
huh
why does it bother him now that I'm
doing this
now he there's a pop shroom oh is that
also does that always work
my dad I'll I'll get it to work again
because I touched the battery
well maybe
[Music]
damn it
how did I perfectly balance it before it
actually is kind of a miracle
oh
whoa okay okay
I think we're ready to go
you can go now
everything's ready
let's hurry
no it wasn't glued last time ever
because like the only thing it offers
you to glue it to is the battery and I
didn't want that
it's kind of dangerous to go as a child
[Music]
I did it my mission was
okay bye
cannot not join
right this is also how I get to avoid
paying possibly avoid it goes down
so his construction site
is doco where's she here
[Music]
hey you didn't mention you were coming
here too mister it's strange Papa keeps
mumbling to himself
oh it's you so you know I've been doing
a lot of thinking trying to figure out
what I could possibly do for Madison and
where would I came up with is this
gorilla zone is pretty far from here
right there are plenty of monsters along
the way so for that make her your own
special air balloon but I want to make
it really special something just for her
I'm just not sure how to do that
it looks like the sun
your sun that's it let it let's color it
like the sun yellow
um Sun okay okay ten easy
I think I got 10.
probably
if you really truly collected 10 of them
which this you found them all for us
looks like a left no problem dying the
balloon the color of the sun
the sun almost sun sun sun sun so close
to sunness
there's no true medicine your papa is
about to try this ballooned into the sun
isn't she you know why don't you help me
with that
I will I will pop
up I'll help you make the Sun
cute
quick good quality blink and we're done
foreign
[Music]
they didn't paint the balloon they just
put a [\h__\h] tarp over it
but okay
that top looks really scuffed they're
just covering it
zatsu Young
lust it is done and morning is already
here
oh I've just had a pretty good to watch
my little one sleep a bit longer
Hudson
oh Ronson what's wrong no don't tell me
yeah her escort has arrived and is
waiting at the Village entrance I see
all right
let's go together in the balloon would
you join us as well four people in that
thing
and some of you guys are huge
oh kind of works out nice
wow
I feel like I've turned into a bird
oh Madison don't make such a Ruckus you
do not want to fall from this height
oh
hey everybody look at that and we're
good
um
sunset or Sunrise the sun is leaking
the blessing of the start of your
journey Madison whether you're in Garuda
town or Terry Town never forget that we
are all standing beneath the very same
Sun
the only distance that matters is the
distance between our hearts so you see
your mama will always be beside you
oh sheesh
we'll be touching down soon hold on to
it
[Music]
oh
why
[Music]
that was quite pretty though yeah
ha
but your present made me very happy
birthday so you know if you got lonely
you can come back any
um
sorry never mind papa needs to be strong
just like you my little medicine it's
time for you to go on your big adventure
oh wow even wearing a face mask
yes it's time
you can trust me I'll take care of your
Papa and Mama don't worry you can go go
become a wonderful wife and become and
come back with lots of stories to tell
can't wait to hear about your adventures
I'll come visit you in Garuda town
sometime when I do let's play again
oh I'm going to become a grapevine like
Mama and I'll meet a wonderful bow like
Papa
every song
cute
oh you're so emotionally invested
it is a cute heartwarming story yeah and
I guess you have to do this if you want
to get a house
Ronson did I manage to keep a smile on
my face yeah you did great she didn't
cry so it's good we didn't cry either
now this is the start of a new life for
us too let's make another baby come on
follow me
okay
I hope it's a sun this time
I hope my jeans are more powerful than
ever
sorry about that uh you know you really
were a big help to me honestly I can't
thank you enough
well it's a way of saying thank you
please take this
hmm
nice okay I was thinking it was kind of
low
um checking on Madison oh we should
eventually
oh I can go and I have special
permission you guys don't even know
now I've got to go back to work don't
you have a customer waiting for you dear
yes me
why why would I not move
oh
I don't have four do I
have one okay
oh hey hey my face only was moving for a
moment okay okay let's see how long this
can keep up before I start moving again
it's like in the mood again to
to make me mad
[Music]
come on come on come on
laughs
Ma
'am
commemorative gift
[Music]
a dream home please oh the discount okay
how much I feel like this is gonna be
very expensive
oh the land alone three thousand [\h__\h]
oh should give me a 50 discount I still
don't have enough and I stop moving
again
[Music]
it's like bugging around again
man why
oh
[Music]
yeah I can sell some gems through
tutorial
maybe I'll sell the diamonds or what's
going on here
but how many do I have maybe I can sell
okay I'm missing one Diamond to do like
a full so so I'll actually keep them
I can sell the other ones because I
think the lady always buys them in in
sets of 10 right
let's go do that really quickly
sorry main quest has to wait
[Music]
so if I buy the land how much more will
they ask of me afterwards
stop moving again
there's a problem with my app for a
couple days already
like the version updated on the like on
our PC but not on the phone
even though normally the phone always
updates uh automatically but like
recently it doesn't
for some reason
I know I know I'm a pro
at this language sapphires I think yeah
baby what's next please don't say
diamonds
yay
sapphires 10 more sapphires
ah damn it I don't have it
I would have 10 more topaz and rubies
why did she ask sapphires twice in a row
how much are these
300. I would need five that's pretty bad
no that's 50 1500. I don't know I don't
know
[\h__\h]
okay but we can afford
something now
wait I can't teleport to Terrytown
directly
oh God damn it
did I miss a shrine
[Music]
it's close
okay oh well I mean oh yeah well it's
the stone right that I have to
transport but even before I do that I
can already use it I know I know I
messed up over again every time I
refresh it just stops working for
it works for a few seconds and then it
stops again
well
and then there's times like until now
like three hours it was
it was like working rubbish stable
I'm messing around with me again
what do you
do you want to do while I was feeling
sick yeah
I could use our other app but that one I
cannot add accessories to myself
which I don't want
I don't like that either
I'll keep on refreshing a few times
eventually maybe eventually
maybe eventually it will just be stable
again nope there it goes
um
let me try
restarting
the desktop version
we have to wait anyway until we're back
up
there's a location for Talus that has a
high chance of giving a diamond really
[Music]
where are we okay and
let me try something
wait what multitasking
oh it's going back down it's okay
no I'm not actually sick
no need to worry oh what the [\h__\h]
come on come on
[Music]
oh the Hylian Shield
it's not so difficult
to get it at all
[Music]
you don't even have to face any enemies
foreign
[Music]
what
yeah put on the cloak of invisibility
pretty cool huh
[Music]
I'm here with Pata
okay one more try
[Music]
huh
why would you pretend it's bales's
stream are you not happy with me
streaming
do I not make you happy
[Music]
okay I'm switching the app no more
accessories then sorry
because it's just not working
[Music]
we were using it for three hours at
least
that's good
baby
okay
[Music]
um
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay
where am I
[Music]
yay
here is Wawa
[Music]
okay
wow
let's go
it's time to buy a house
and now pay it off
immediately
dream home please maybe the ground is
1500 and then the house is like the
first part is 1500 too
that would be nice
[Music]
uh southeast of here has an excellent
view
[Music]
um
okay let's just close to the shrine yeah
speak of him for more details okay can I
already buy like the the part where I
can live inside
no I have to meet him first okay
I need more money
oof
okay
I will do my best
you know I think the next tltk stream
will be
quite
um much later I um maybe I can squeeze
in one next week but I'm not sure if I
have so much time
ah but
um
damn it I want to do the shrine but
where does it go
talk to me stone you show me too right
yeah
[Music]
yeah and oh
how how
is it in a cave or just behind the
mountains
what's the matter
I need to make a bow this one sucks
I'll do it privately then
probably yeah
what were we doing we talked to impa and
then
[Music]
uh
um not a house no I'm doing that another
time now
I mean what were we actually doing we
saw the memory
so
really
oh you'll be
do we go through the cave again or
I kind of want to go to look at Landing
Watson pick up some weapons
how do we
how do we go up
oh I do have to jump from the tower
or have a bike
what's the like intended way of doing it
Castle has good weapons too that's true
I guess I can pick up a lot of weapons
there
um
[Music]
should I talk with someone here again
before I leave
there's no intended way
was this thing almost here
you
[Music]
know
okay I think she's still saying the same
thing as before
um okay she says think uh of something
yourself
how high
[Music]
do I need to go there's waterfalls
though can I not use the waterfalls with
the Zora armor
[Music]
yeah the Pom-Pom is killed
because I was going to Lost Woods too
yeah but today is main story time
gotta do some main story
I wish they would sell
it
Laura Lynn they have a quest for Laura
Lynn
worried about everybody in Ireland but
let's keep hoping they got away from the
Pirates
South East
results The Village leader so he'd be
the first to know how things took out
back home
okay
good that I got it before going there
oh okay okay
but possibly also
not gonna do this until
well
I have some time to play it properly
yeah I think until the next stream I'll
be having
a bit more time to play privately
so
next time we'll have a recap again
do I wanna
maybe use this one because I can gain a
lot of hype with that or just use the
the hoverbike hmm
you guys look a new hoverbike
I mean should I try to get closer though
um
[\h__\h]
no lizard for me
yeah
I know it I know I heard something
um
uh wait
okay okay
I'll try I'll I'll find him again okay
uh
oh
[\h__\h]
wait wait let me heal myself not that
I'm wasting a ferry again I don't want
that
is
no way did they just
but that was pretty fast
hey I thought they always spawned Ganon
what
no why do they always dip right in the
moment where I'm killing them
hey that's annoying but like previously
when I did it I also like had them in a
spot where they couldn't get to me for
like quite some time
um
I wasn't playing of course I was playing
Fair
um
man
okay
oh wow
how far should we go
maybe around here is okay
maybe on top of the bridge
what do you think
foreign
many ways possible
ah the sad music was so sad
I'm like it's so not not sad but it's
like concerning isn't it
I know I can open the gate so that I
wanted to gain some height
no I know
yep
found an entrance but there
remember your armor yeah
it's just like a am I going inside like
a dungeon now
should I upgrade my armor before going
or
because
I mean I guess I can activate something
again
that will let me go back anyway
not really more of a gauntlet
really
a dungeon okay
[Music]
okay I think
balloon here is
okay
this one's kind of expensive problem a
normal one maybe we'll do
[Music]
and then
we need some wood
push
we're finally
doing the very we're taking the very big
step or leap
like a historically very important
moment
of going up into the castle
you just flew in from the sky island
we are doing it in a cooler way we're
ascending
I think that's pretty cool
what I would have liked to turn around
my balloon before
I did this
bye bye I guess you're leaving me alone
after all I don't know what I got you
guys for if you're not joining me on
this journey right now
but okay
oh
this will be one
oh [\h__\h] oh there we go the proof that
it's a dungeon kind of oh
lots of corruption here
hmm
think
yeah I was just gonna Pour Some Water
yeah I'm on my way
is this Dragon Zelda or human Zelda
thank you
oh thanks
wait we're here what
um
yeah B1 I am kind of in B1 now
music terrifying
can't you sort of
maybe like up there
how big is B1
oh
so cool
go get them tiger
link
I'm home alone
should I should I jump off no
I think it's enough height or go here
that's that's probably not that's
probably one f
[Music]
um
maybe there's a quarter oh
oh it's breaking is there a Kodak maybe
on top of this no way right they
wouldn't they wouldn't
would they
I see one ah I see one over there though
oh in a chest wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait
[Music]
oh
do I have space
oh I do
very cool
Royal book damn music
stop guys tell me if it's too loud um I
want that can I do it from here
to an idol meeting oh [\h__\h] I use the
lion elbow
[Music]
worth checking
it's fine the music okay
actually I'm losing yeah hope but okay
um
my heart another chest in there
yes
it's probably the fake one
she's a [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] statue
sure
you [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
oh
she she moved it she's the fake one
or she or is she
[\h__\h] wait
foreign
[Music]
oh
damn
son the music I almost sticks on it
these sticks
God I feel this is so epic oh it's like
always storming here huh
okay nice
um we shall
make some weapons
um
drop that
I guess we can keep this one that one's
not too bad I think
so we have
one two three maybe four
weapons to put something on top
[Music]
um
one of these
[Music]
um
they're one of these
okay
for the broad
sword oh this is a modern one
would it fit better on this one actually
damn it whatever
okay
the king really wants him on the castle
speaker system what sauce do you get
when you order next always
um like in some countries they don't oh
really have this [\h__\h]
that one's really cool too almost looks
like my hylia shield but seriously sweet
and sour and it's not the same sweet and
sour that you get like at an Asian uh
restaurant I would say
low durability oh
it's kind of different
[Music]
um
do I want to bring it maybe instead of
the Zoro shoes I don't know
okay where to go next
uh
oh we're going down now
I want to turn off the lights
because it's distracting me
that's where the temple is at the tower
well this one that can turn off I think
a recipe like that that's awesome
going to sleep now good night thanks for
watching so far
after I put some Hydro building
oh they can do that
and how do I where do I go
if I climb out of the window
or I would go here
it's thundering but there's no rain
thank God
but such a combination
kind of weird
oh wait oh
yeah that's that thing again
um
maybe no need
heat lightning oh is that a thing very
interesting
oh
I wonder if the hands will say hello to
me here as well
okay
okay it's the same room yeah
best to leave it yeah but I think like
if you were to
like 100 then you have to take it at
least out of the
oh out of the chest for it to count
which is kind of weird I feel like it
should count just by once opening the
chest
all right let's let's start here shall
we
need
I know
oh a strength from Liz although like
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
I will bring that along
sounds really good
strong
Let's test it out with
oh it's just
oh it's the same actually
where is this Shrine I don't say it
[Music]
many many weapons hooray
there it is
um
there's enemies sleeping on there too I
don't know if the game will naturally
lead me there and it must right so let's
follow this path first I mean although
it's kind of hard to follow this one
maybe this is discouraging me from
taking that path
on purpose
you recommend heading to the shrine
first okay
I have to go lower anyway
true
and this is kind of closer to
our
actual destination
oh they woke up but they didn't notice
me
okay
[Music]
let's surprise them with uh no not with
that
with some fun classroom
um
let's see
I'll add another one
was that was that a sneak with a despair
is that how that looks
yeah oh
[Music]
look it didn't feel very sneaky
on
my way here it is there's also so much
Gloom
um oh my chest though nothing special
but wait oh wait I see there's a proper
chest as well
okay okay okay this is
just the appetizer
okay
I need to hit them from the backs
I need to try that more often yeah
maybe a bow in here then
this other one was oh no okay
uh no more melee weapons then
getting ready
[Music]
let's combine
let's always have my weapons ready so I
don't have to do it in the middle of a
fight
whip like quality whoa I was just
thinking like how does that work if I
put a tail on the weapon it turns into a
whip
Watch Me Whip
watch me Nae Nae Watch Me Whip watch
whip whip and watch me Nae Nae
didn't you see that coming when I
started
saying the word with
should have known
all righty
hmm
watch me watch me watch me watch me
I'm not Nana I wish I was she's so cute
huh
Hyrule Castle B1
oh
there's a path underneath too
okay but
in the middle of this exciting whatever
we have to do a shrine
I mean we don't have to we could just
activate it and then ignore it but we
might as well
I'm the cutest what do you mean what do
you mean stop
I love you
is it a blessing
no okay
the way up
up to the castle you mean haha you know
what you're doing there oh wait I know
what I'm doing too wait but not that
I saw it for one second and I know what
to do
no no
[\h__\h]
I just beat because I saw someone
saying I don't know about cutest
[Music]
okay one
steak
oh I guess I could make a bridge that
goes upwards
quite the simple Shrine huh this is for
like the assumption that some people are
gonna try to
skip a lot of content just to get up to
the castle as fast as possible so the
shrine that they put here is an easy one
[Music]
for chest yeah
oh
oh wait oh I mean I have an idea
it might not be
the intended way
can I ascend
while I'm recalling I think yes
super not intended but clever really
non-intendent
like at this point
[Music]
after
so so many shrines and so many
experiences
it's it's not that
unlikely that a player would go for that
yeah oh yeah I I yeah right I didn't
even need to ascend I could just stand
on it I know I know that is true
now how is this different from the very
first one
just the fact that I have to connect to
wait a second now we have to go even
higher
I mean probably
[Music]
oh
oh can't go that high
can I
um
hooks
yeah I'm picking up
putting some cheese on top again
[Music]
melting that cow with that cheese
doesn't when I'm up here
when I'm up here I can lift it higher so
okay then I think it's pretty intended
what I did before
[Music]
how else I would do it unless with
really annoying
um
strategies now
good I think that wasn't wild that was
really simple
meant the shrines in the end they're
always just there to
remind you to use your powers
hmm
you did it differently it was a bit
annoying then I think I did it the
easiest way
good out of the box think well thank you
guys what
wow it's just a normal easy small brain
solution
nothing special
nothing out of the ordinary oh
okay
oh okay
that's
a path
it just works
I thought should I check out something
here
oh there's some horror blends
a couple of them yeah
well I guess we'll go down
it always works
German brain always works
no more space for weapons I guess I'm
good for now
it's a library
oh
okay are you here Zelda hmm
is there any books that I can read
nothing really looks readable
oh
this is what you put down your book and
you read it
can you read of course come on
is my general image really like that of
look stupid cow
[Music]
ooh still band girl
I would hope not
I feel like
I mean you know sometimes I also like to
[Music]
it's not really act but like
enhance my dorkiness
sometimes
yeah I struggle with math okay
but that's just because my my brain is
just a bit more
you know trains
a lot of things
I have
strengthness and weaknesses you're
telling me this is not a call look
I guess inside
they don't place them inside
will they
like all the others are on it's just
that one that was not on
kind of kind of sauce
[Music]
so running after Zelda
it's kind of like activating
all the things in the dungeons but this
is kind of an easy version of that
I'm trying to find like stuff
it's not the first time this is not the
first time Chihuahua
[Music]
does that even bother him no
all right
oh he's got like a protection thing yeah
oh well good job oh we are right it's a
he knocks
look
Philly shook his eye again
I thought I could jump in the right
timing is that even possible you could
jump at the right time does it
like save you from the
kaboom
yeah
that's nice black units oh we never
thought of black Enochs before
um I want the Royal Claymore
ah damn it
so many tiny meals I think let's eat
this
um
yeah okay I guess I don't need it and
royal blue uh
[Music]
let's drop the lizzo ball I'm gonna take
this one too
we can get rid of this one Rusty
Claymore stick
or or this one actually the magic Rod
I'm
I was gonna force myself to use it but
nah
yeah yeah the rod why is the rod so
unpopular it's so sad it looks so fancy
but people just don't want to use it
that's so sad
uh
[\h__\h]
oh I survived it
is this another Royal claimer yeah
yeah I mean they definitely have the use
but
When comparing it to
all the other possible weapons
feels like
easier to let go of the rod
no other elemental weapons at the moment
I guess
make yourself a rod but oh yeah I guess
if you don't use the gems because I'm
gonna say the gems you should use for
money instead but I guess you can
um
put other Elemental items on there too
right
what's going on here excuse me should I
swim up
Sapphire and a shield
I missed something in the bookshelves
lore
I tried to see everything
I know is it just like a little I'll
watch it when domtendo finds it
because I have a speed boost up right
now
it is important
use ultra head
if he finds it he
usually tries to find everything really
[\h__\h] yell
okay
lower shelves maybe not the upper ones
ah hey yo okay there's surely a chest
there
ah okay it shows on the map too
oh
maybe this could be honestly this is so
special it could be an armor piece
no what the [\h__\h] what
why
oh this could be like
um like a bomb
when fused to a weapon very destructive
I don't know maybe not but
[Music]
um
oh is it more like a flame Hammer after
all okay well that's pretty cool
you missed it
but if that wait is that the dragon
that's also flying in the sky or is it a
dragon that's already like gone
because if it's flying then you can get
your own right if you just jump on him
wait there's more what
yeah
oh
maybe another Dragon thing always
what
I can't I'm already on the lowest level
what is that for
this one what does that mean a dud
trying to throw me off
[Music]
ah
foreign
study
oh
yo but I swear the top
you know how he's talking about the
armor last time
or saying the top is actually like you
can get it in the
in the broken off part of the
uh
uh a castle I'm pretty sure because Dom
tando got it too
um
I wanted I wanted
you
yeah and I think the other parts are
just up here
but the the main part the
the top
is in the broken up part that's down on
the ground
oh well
Grand Theft
ah
very cute okay I will try to go up the
water
I suppose
I hope it works
that was dangerous it wasn't as close as
I thought oh
this one too baby
okay
we are
where
uh-huh okay
now we're going the left side I think
last time we went to the right side
it's kind of like the the main entrance
I don't cheat what do you mean
close to sanctum on this part but she
the next one is here
what again
what haven't I found her there before
already
what
a side quest for the thing what thing
did I miss a important Quest
Champions tunic nearby
should I not go this way yet
what the [\h__\h] man should I go back to
her
but she's fake anyway
I left the library the long way
man I need to
wow
she'll probably show up here too no
that's what I'm thinking like I'll end
up here anyway probably but
[\h__\h] I really need to I can't
I gotta go
BRB
foreign
chonkers has been in the same spot for
like 10 hours
so cute she's like curled up like a
button
right at my pillow
oh
and she was there
when I woke up
I think she only made left a spot once
to get maybe some breakfast
and then went back to the same spot but
it looks like she never moved
so cute
she's so cute yeah she got the right
spot and she's like you curled up she
looks a good book
little button
um
[Music]
explore the inside of the cemetery I
feel like a
the game would bring me back there
anyway
so important you know
hmm
chunky wonky so cute
there's a cool thing at the throne okay
where
is the throne move to the side anyway
or is it missing like was it two frowns
next to each other
[Music]
let me cook
no
oh yeah Zelda is like totally
inside the castle Yeah we know it's the
fake one we just saw her as a dragon so
we have to know
wait
um
no
please tell me for once that my
instincts are correct
[Music]
oh yeah
I cooked
[Music]
what is it
the breath of the Wild
clothes oh
side quest complete so I guess I did
have that Quest that you guys like were
snickering about
I cooked
improved I want to upgrade it though I'm
gonna wear it now I need my upgraded
clothes anyway let's go back to Delta I
feel like I could even like teleport
shrine
not really I guess
don't feel like that might be the
fastest way but
[Music]
I can okay
it's Zelda playing games with me and I
am playing along
why do I do this to myself
[Music]
um
oh guys uh random topic
so you know how I showed you guys
the background of my aunt
[Music]
um
news show that I was planning
and I was like I'm working on it and
then like recently I was like okay like
for real I'll for real work on it now
and yeah
I'm a road to me the other day
you
and it's like oh I was told
who told you you you you're gonna do
like uh you were planning on doing a
show
um
you know
but well
you said I can still do mine sure I
could but
hold like the whole of Japan they have
like a few of these kind of shows
I think with whole life Japan it makes
sense because they have well like it
works it works just because
you think it will only last for two
episodes I don't know
maybe she'll do it longer this time she
seems pretty motivated
um what was I gonna say
um
uh yeah there they have way more members
so I feel like it's okay that they have
maybe more than one show
um like as a meal and Coyote's show and
so on
and
I feel like I'm not angry on anything I
feel like Ahmed would do a better job at
it anyway
um
yeah it's just so I'm like fine with her
doing it totally I just don't know
what do I do with the background now I
feel kind of bad because
I I Got It Made and now I feel bad if I
don't use it
I may had an idea that
I feel like it could at least at least
it makes it different from a normal new
show oh I did I did offer her to use my
background she said no
he said he'll just use what she had
already
no but
um she said I could do uh en news
and then translate them like Hollow talk
to Japanese so that Japanese viewers
know
what's up in the end I'm like yeah I
guess actually that's at least something
original and different from what you do
but I don't know if I if I really
like if I do that if there's even really
a like
if there's Japanese viewers who really
want to see that
if there's a need a demand for it
it's a good idea though like at least to
make use of the background
hmm
but but I kind of wanted to do you know
something that the en viewers could
enjoy I wasn't really planning on
doing it for the Japanese views but it
could be a way for me to also reconnect
back with my
Japanese viewers who kind of like um
are
kind of gone and get some new ones Maybe
I just I just wonder if there's a demand
for it really
I don't know we could test it out at
least
um
I could test it out
see how it goes
because I think at least you know I I
don't wanna
I don't want I'm just maybe
I just have this
I don't think we need two news programs
for Ian you know what I mean
which is 10 people
then we don't need to wait we're just
gonna be telling the same [\h__\h]
so then
I would even give up on the idea which
is fine too because I don't know how
motivated I really was anyway to begin
with
um
there were like times where I was
motivated about it and then I wasn't
motivated about it after all so I'm fine
with mama doing it but then I'm just
feeling bad about the background so at
least I could use it differently if I if
I did that and then we have two
different shows but they they do two
different things
foreign
nice [\h__\h]
guys
[Music]
you know
he can kick time
is
foreign
[Music]
okay I just
um asked like the few the very few
Japanese viewers in the chat they like
the idea but they're you know already
interested in the end that's why they're
here but
I'm asking if a Japanese Clipper because
there are some Japanese Clippers who
clip me even when this like
tangent in the middle of like a big
stream
but they find it anyway
just clip of things but yeah I'm asking
that a Clipper Clips it and then I can
read the opinions
of the
people
in the comment section as I always do
you know
so what he's just dangling up there
what
at least he's aiming for
my Sages
um wait oh wait how about I throw
it's moving so much yo I got him uh
maybe one more
okay nice
very good
foreign
[Music]
I think Japanese viewers also kind of
just want to understand not only what
we're doing but like
what
um what's just like
um
what the things mean that we we find
funny so I could like
explain it from a cultural side too
where am I going anyway where is she am
I going the right way
does this lead up again
ever
coming on to questions
I put untapped opportunity
yeah not really not really meme review
but like
you know explaining what's going on and
like maybe a cultural
side to it too
where the [\h__\h] do I go
oh
have I not even been here before
I don't know maybe I just teleport
Ascend up because it's kind of close
and I just need to go higher
see I do like the idea
and I appreciate actually I'm thinking
of it
I didn't think of that at all
I just don't know that there's a demand
so we'll see okay we'll test it out
we'll test out the market
I see you
and I I honestly I really think I prefer
am I doing the normal news
there's just something about amen
I don't know it's hard to explain
it's just just matches her
I think she would do well
huh she
I'm too high now
let's get lower again
it's kind of confusing
maybe here
ah
huh
I know eh I'm still on one f
what is that claimer
but here here here
I can go down
what is this
where did I go indecisive indecisive
[\h__\h]
did you see how it was running forward
backward forward ah
yeah
it's really bad to be indecisive
recall no well
I don't I can't think of such a thing in
such a stressful situation
it's Zelda study I was gonna say why is
there some princess oh
Royal Guards boom
cool cool
I chose neither exactly Royal
these weapons what if I just throw away
the monster shirt can I do that
um
time to
combine some things
maybe don't
[Music]
fitting
yeah I do like some of the designs of
like weapons that just seem like they're
meant to be others are like
they look really weird there's a room
below me
well
but I'm in here now
I'm going that's what I'm going for
though I think because yeah that was my
plan to go down here and say hi Zelda
hello
sheesh
give me your horns
ah oh well would you guys be okay with
me doing something that's focused on
Japanese views maybe not every week but
every second week
think would be okay
[Music]
yeah there's something in this room okay
okay
oh this thing
looks kind of random
I'll watch either way thank you thank
you
this is what you wanted me to find helps
us learning Japanese
in a corner
oh wait that do these also break really
easily or
so many good bows
yeah I want more uh Japanese Bros too
um
yo
very important isn't it
oh
awesome thanks
okay where is she now
is this gonna like end at some point
we have to go lower but we're kind of
close
um
I wonder if I could just jump out the
window
and then fly he says
[Music]
be free
maybe it's the last one because we she
wants to be free and we're setting her
free that's why the last one isn't be
free
[Music]
I don't want to fight there on the
tiniest platform
go
uh lower
can I go from here
yes
hi I'm back again kind of stalking you
at this point
were they
oh uh
didn't want them to freeze me
sheesh okay I'm happy with losing
weapons because we're getting so many
cool weapons I want to use them all
proof flurry rush I should use more
flurry Russian
how's it improve just more damage
silver marble horn let's go was there
more
um
I mean it wasn't a real Perry I can't
actually Perry
that is one thing I suck
and always forget at doing
[Music]
where's she now
we didn't set her free
well she's on the same
height
however it's not connected
oh never one of those bows
very overrated ah nice membership
gifting
my ring is hard
entrance to this one sucks
I'll figure it out
one way or another
this is fake
posture must pay
I guess it's here
um
probably have to go up and then jump
down again
that would be the easiest
I could fly around the side
[Music]
not 100 aware of where that is right now
though so I'll just walk
it's probably super close yeah right
here okay okay
there
oh we're going lower
okay
ah we enter from
here
we just have to do a trust fall kind of
belief in the process
oh that wasn't too bad
was I here before
I think so
yeah oh
is it blocking them anywhere nice
a nice shot
I was gonna shoot but
link was so slow to recover
from carrying his really heavy weapon
uh I guess we're not bringing us
it's okay it's okay we don't have to
feel bad about it
this one however attack was free
can replace with a normal wearable
oh
oh that was happening
did I do them all ah
that sounds
so
seductive I know it's fake
she doesn't talk like that
foreign
because
we just saw her as a dragon and she
cried you know cried for me
and I cried for her
because it's just such a
sad destiny that she has met
I will try
to fix her
she
oh she's in the middle now okay
yeah I knew to find the alley would be
there
[Music]
no I can fix her not you
she'll love me even more
let's go I wonder
who will we fight
you know what be cool like you know we
have Shadow Link what about Shadow Zelda
Zelda this would be the perfect moment
to make that a thing
I got two fairies
I think I'm strong enough
face whatever we're gonna face hopefully
hopefully hopefully jinx jinx
imposter
mm-hmm
that's how she seduced all the other
ones
oh dream world
you can't
be
it's pretty though
um
foreign
[Music]
yeah please don't rip it off
how do I fight a ghost
[Music]
wait is that the final fight right
you guys will tell me if I'm finishing
the game before doing so many other
things what the [\h__\h]
I'm scared okay it can't be so difficult
Cannon fights are always weak as [\h__\h]
it's okay it's okay it's okay
did you I need you
please do let's try this out
okay Ah that's it's good they're all
like taking care of someone else
nice oh I'm getting both
[Music]
to be like oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] he's hitting
me right in the face but no
oh well no it's easy it's easy though
well Demon King weapons cool is this the
same demon that you fight when you're oh
go on sword
wait I have the weapons can you fight
after the hands
okay
okay see I got some practice thankfully
got married please do not hurt him his
wife would be so sad
this is fun though
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I want to do it again
you're dropping so many weapons
oh the bow is like really really big
what if I use this Bloom sword on him oh
right wait it doesn't take my heart oh
[\h__\h] ew I don't want that ew drop that
oh
mom not as cool
what if I use my mouth
I keep on getting it though my sword
isn't even that special even though it's
glowing
it's not doing much more damage maybe I
should attach something
[Music]
oh well
I might have to fuse oh closer to my
sword
hi
more puppets
oh no no oh wait uh
did I do it what the [\h__\h] just happened
huh
[Music]
already what am I supposed to do I can't
clean it
I disappears after a while thank God
holy [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh that the Gloom sheds break
[Music]
damn
keep it
does that help should I kill him should
I try to kill him first
yeah
how dare you disrupt me
ah
oh what is that weapon give me give me
give me give me is it also something
gloomy
Gloom Club
uh well oh no
okay I should use it
I don't want to wear that no no no no no
no no no
[Music]
[\h__\h] hell
they don't do much damage though
thankfully okay
[Music]
what my master sword still has appears
oh no the Clone stick is fused oh
oh it's like a club with the hair
looks so unfamiliar
come spare but that's not feels
[Music]
the eyes
my muscles useless
sorry it's like lots of things going on
right now oh wait I wanna switch
wait
oh nothing oh sorry Rush
but with that
okay
oh yeah get him get him get him
[Music]
face free face free
Zer hours
you've been here since the beginning so
it's not a big surprise to me thanks
thanks guys
you're gonna Retreat now huh yeah
oh the real one all right
they're not the ghosts they came in
person
Chihuahua Fellowship
yay
first memory this is the first one
whoa what what what
let's go
is this the continuation from that one
memory
[Music]
or like his povs
yeah
sick
[Music]
again
that Cannon hits different
[Music]
let's [\h__\h] go
sh
development
cool
you guys arrived so [\h__\h] late
this is
[Music]
foreign
of course
of course oh this comes like as a
dungeon for real for real
[Music]
um
this
eh
it's not fused nothing on these ones
yeah but uh
Bloom spare on Aurora Claymore
um
Club
welcome to the Gloom Club emo kids only
what's this
column spare
is that
um
Gloom sword
I mean mad as well right should I
is this worth it
fusing all these things
take one of the balls
I think I have one of them from like
fighting
the
one previously this one no
do they always have the same strength
I already have one the bows look red
what
they get stronger with more Hearts
oh ah the balls don't Gloom
oh okay but I got so much stuff
maybe one more
okay
let's like explore a little bit inside
here did I miss something
we saw this
we got the treasure here the music is
completely dead now okay
oh we didn't go here I think
light the Torches I did I did
what do you mean even more torches
oh
nothing here
um
you
of course there's something there has to
be uh this is a royal broadsword oh I
could even take it
I've got some space Oh
another one
the thing I just got from
just
is that it
nice about vert up tracking yeah
I better be really nice because I have
no space for bows
oh my God no space
where where top
stop
um
there's so much
well if I need another one
I know where to get one not this one
um
little boy
you
where is top
is this the one that just opened
yes
you mean on top of all that Gloom [\h__\h]
I mean
I think I can survive it go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go
go go go go go
easy
mm-hmm
Kodak come on
you guys lied to me
wrong Tower
here
is this it
no
foreign
[Music]
so much loot here ah thank God it's
something I can just put in my pocket
and go
down
should I attach something to it oh
is this a riddle
all right
spare okay thank you I have never
bring it harder
[Music]
thank you I'm happy to see you
honestly I'm just happy I can free you
from this place
because it must have been really scary
for you
fear
oh
what's this
oh it's the equivalent of my pretty
swords
set up and used by a princess who fought
beasts of Twilight
forces forcefully fires long range
[Music]
and is there another Coral
okay
yeah okay
can I stand here
but here
and here we go
wow what a view
is this the highest point of Hyrule
no
I knew it couldn't be
I got you
no more playing games do little [\h__\h]
how I know
okay and we're now should we are we done
did I find everything really important
yeah she will be very interested in
hearing
from our
yeah Adventure
does it say Gloom tall
Ayah okay
bastard
just wanted to
kill him too because he doesn't seem to
realize that his owner has left the
building and
yeah instead of having him wait there
forever
for nothing
I feel like I don't know I'm helping him
did I say this before
yeah probably just left it in there
because I already have
[Music]
I didn't I did them a favor I would
agree with that
now
oh
I would have never seen this if not
for coming from up there eh what is this
a verb
hi babe
I feel so bad when killing birds
I really do
hi he's got berries
[Music]
on his sticks
okay look out Landing I'm coming for you
I know I could just teleport
it might just end up taking the same
amount of time
now what I really want to know though
is where is the top part of the
actually I really want to know
am I real good
I'm on a roll
[Music]
yeah the royal guard said
I know the top is somewhere in the
normal part of the
of the
Castle because
you know
let me first let me free
I want to go in there that's um I know
where that is
tops in the guards quarters
[Music]
I have the headpiece and the bottoms now
him
guards Court guards chamber
chamber
um
really
nah
that's just that I'd have to fly back up
now yeah am I coming back
Castle
I guess I could try to get it privately
um
I'll just get it sometime
another time
oh yeah I do have to shrine
do you have the shrine
I'll go on my own time don't want to
waste your guys's time too much and you
know we're at five hours now what did
Wawa say seven hours so
I have to be careful
but I feel like we did even in this
short time a good amount of story
actually
right
good good
no Kodak
what the [\h__\h]
yeah I said six
I think
it was a rock
huh
blind
and Blended in so nicely no I said 10 no
I said seven uh I said six I did I maybe
I did say seven
no no I added that
oh did I say seven
oh man okay we'll see we'll see
we'll see how accomplished I feel of
this Stone
how accomplished I feel after six hours
if I feel like I need more more
then
I will add another one yeah
no I said six oh
who is
what's the truth
and who is telling me what their wishful
thinking is
huh
yeah no but um I really shouldn't do too
much we did nine hours yesterday
so
chill
yeah
welcome back looks like it was pretty
tough so how did it go
let's see
[Music]
so to summarize there's no mistaking
that what you all saw at the castle was
the demon king from The Legend of the
imprisoning war yeah and the princess
you've been seeing was actually an
imposter the
and the reason she appeared at Tyra
Castle was so that the Demon King could
lure link into a trap
oh
sounds about right
[Music]
I know something seemed weird
I mean how about Princess Sarah not
doing anything to help with these
troubles everyone Hyrule but it's all
connected the upheaval the problems our
homelands have been facing the fake
princess it's all happening because the
Demon King came back
so then that means Princess Zelda isn't
actually here instead she's in the
distant past and not in the prison right
yes we should consider that to be the
case bizarre as it sounds it also seems
that Princess Zelda was trying to
somehow defeat the demon king in the
past
our ancestors made about Zelda they
swore that when the Demon King was
revived their descendants would awaken
as sages and fight alongside link
but with Princess Zelda in the past we
can't ask her what the plan is supposed
to be
and she can't be here to fight with us
either
we also don't know anything about the
demon king or the gender fact that his
bad news and super strong what do we do
based on what you each have told me it
appears that the princess was making
preparations and anticipation of the
Demon King's Revival in this area there
must be some hint we still haven't
figured out here in our time
right you are we cannot afford to stand
still at a time such as this it is
imperative that we Act
[Music]
but without any leads
oh wait
you said that six stages where I was the
king without it when he fought against
the demon king during the imprisoning
war right
wind
fire
water
lightning
and time
that was the princess
I see
what is it what do you see
that's it
there was one more stage back then
[Music]
lightning
time
and uh
was she
she wasn't Tam
exactly one more Sage that might be here
now
I'm sure this is the lead we were hoping
for it will be well worth a while to
search each of you awakened as sages at
ruins from the age of Legends right
maybe the remaining stages in a similar
location
that makes sense so we should search
major ruins from the age of Legends
there is good a places I need to start
if we just searched all of Hyrule
randomly would probably never find the
sage
all right we have a plan let's spread up
the work and get to it
you four go back to your homelands and
gather information about ruins that
might be related to the remaining stage
linky search around and see if you can
find any other undiscovered leads
everyone relying on you don't let us
down
um
maybe that's why I have to go to
kokoriko
you found the stage before doing this
they were surprised oh that's that's
interesting I would like to see how the
uh
uh how the whole conversation plays out
when you already have the saint you do
you do what the [\h__\h]
guys
[Music]
can you guys not hold yourself back
wards
mud follow the story is it so hard
everyone's playing the game wrong
um
[Music]
accident
hmm
well didn't happen to me
thank you
[Music]
a place that looks interesting
um
damn it
why do they make it possible to find
them so randomly accidentally
um
[Music]
you should investigate ruins from the
age of Legends which what
age of Legends isn't one of my uncle un
uncovered Maps
foreign
[Music]
ruins are
wait
[Music]
that makes sense because like the ruins
of the age of Legends so old ruins that
are obviously from
a long time ago and then kakolic was
like oh what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is
this stuff
um
but yeah you could do that stuff before
right
damn
why why why
your brain too small
yeah I'm not sure if I would have
immediately gotten it if you guys
wouldn't have told me like a hour ago
that I'll I'll have to do this later
and that I should do this later
name
Bob
um
I mean I came to kokorika before I just
thought this was some
um really nice side quest
so
I didn't touch it yet
it turns out it's more than that huh
[Music]
the ring ruins are the most intriguing
ruins I've researched special this one
the way part of it floats up there it
had the foresight to focus on all of
these special runes and invite the
server team to take a look right away
[Music]
I didn't know what that was I thought it
was a sign
[Music]
oh no I'm no Chief I just couldn't
refuse my predecessor when she decided
to pass the title to me rather suddenly
I'm really achieving name only since I
still have a great deal so oh
I said you must link
I'm so happy that I get to see you again
I'm Overjoyed that both you and Princess
Zelda are safe master link
hey
safe I mean hmm are we are we safe
huh
a Zelda who appeared after the upheaval
is an imposter
amokus
and the real Princess Zelda is still
missing
no no she's not really missing I know
where she is
I serious master link it's certainly
hard to believe yet I find it impossible
that you would make up such a thing
um come to think of it the Princess
Zelda who came to kariko Village
oh she came here too
she ordered us not to let anyone go near
that floating ring ruin no matter what
oh because that's where the stages and
they want to keep me away from them
up there no way
[Music]
she left as soon as she arrived I wasn't
able to ask her anything more about
those unusual instructions
we thought it was to protect the
villagers from harm this ruin does look
like it could crash down at any moment
that's what pie and I suspect at least
oh my apologies master link I was so
pleased to see you I completely forgot
to come on courtesy please allow me to
introduce Mr Tower an esteemed member of
the sonai server team I invited him here
to investigate the ringworms that fell
on our village he has incredibly deep
knowledge of the sunlight civilization
he's even familiar with the Zona script
he is truly an incredibly talented
individual oh
um
because wasn't Empire kind of into me
I feel like
she's a little bit into tolero now
Horn of shark
she got over me
[Music]
um
she still is well Truly Deeply in her
heart yeah but she's trying to get over
me with that guy which
I mean
look at us
compare us that little little small link
but it's it's not just about the body
shape you know
it's it's Link's heart but actually I
mean Tower seems like a really chill
dude too
he's not a bad guy
it's clear that the floating ring ruined
that we were a bit forbidden to explore
although he's a fuckboy maybe possibly
it's just a very smart one
to explore it's a unique and incredible
event what did you just say about me
anyway several more ring ruins was such
a shape have fallen down around the
village
most have broken apart in some way well
what's fascinating is that a stone slap
was with writing was found at each site
[Music]
I did read one of them
um
he's a good boy yeah good boy
decipher written the text show that each
slab contains rather interesting content
including mention of sages
there's still so much we don't
understand
I think that perhaps the Rune floating
in this in the air also has a slap that
makes mention of the sages until now
I've given up on investigating everyone
believing princess zella's orders were
for the best
but if that princess was an imposter
that changes everything
princess Zelda's imposter the Demon
King's underling forbade anyone from
investigating the floating ring ruin
that must mean that doing so would post
a threat to the Demon King
ah say all big hints it just makes sense
with what we've just talked about
if that is the case we must survey that
floating ring ruin as soon as possible
[Music]
right you are Mr Tara there's no longer
any reason to prohibit your research
let's open up the floating ring ruin at
once
knowledge is tugging on the line it's
time to relent some results
you're literal in phrasing is coming for
you Mr tower out you must really be
pleased oh it's just I don't know what
how to get up there
runes all out Sally there doesn't seem
to be an entrance
if the contents of the other ring ruins
are any indication there should be a
stone slab inside and grapefruit so I
scraped
[Music]
um
you hate this guy why
first we should look for a way to
confirm that there's a stone slap inside
however we also don't want to damage
these precious runes oh boy me as Wilson
thought I better hurry and tell
everybody okay
there is literally
a platform there
that is offering itself to me
oh
hello
[Music]
gross better
groose you say
[Music]
I will ignore that statement and act as
if it never
happened
I did not hear
this statement
oh there's a Chasm there
on that one
whoa
they captured
some of the gloom and it's
okay you can maybe tame the Gloom
because it's staying in the cage
same
here I'm searching the runes so is that
resistant Gloom expert I wanted to head
up this operation as well writing
oh
you guys need more uh more of the
sunflowers
I can help
I barely use them
but I think I just gave away 10 didn't I
oh
yo there's another storm slob
is the translation here
wind flame water lightning and time
light who holds the power
yeah but Zelda is time and light right
secret Stone and that person dwell
within power amplify great might display
the first of the message on this lab is
about something called secret Stones
they use the stones to attain great
might to accomplish their goals that's
what I'm guessing it would say if we
could read the whole thing
are you sure about that
should I take a picture of this
and it doesn't seem to be necessary
[Music]
I know I like went
in a different direction where I need to
go to but
curious
[Music]
to look at everything else first before
that stone slab tells me everything
what's there
everything that I didn't want to know
curious like a kitty cat
I'm a kitty cat and I'm meow meow meow
oh there's a lot of whoa
pretty flowers here whoa
was blue Nightshade the sneaky one and
where the hell do you want to go
um
I don't know
I never really have the patience for
these Crocs and I am honestly
Breezy
sorry
I'll help your other friends though but
you are probably even though I
I put you on my map you probably
destined to be here forever
the hoverbike does that have a bike
strong enough like
to carry him
then yeah I'll try it out but
I never did anymore
wait should I
maybe I should get that one first maybe
it will then ask me to go in here
[Music]
my jrpg brain is giving me hints
what
oh
is there a translation for this or do I
have to take a picture of this
[Music]
because I couldn't get in here
somebody bright go down that light
it's really bright and how do I get out
I guess I go to the top
[Music]
should I oh I'm already up so high I
want to check up the other side
you have to
I have to find out more
I'm hungry
for knowledge so once again
I really
enjoy the lore
of totk and Zelda games in general hmm
is there like something like in here
was I sad
no
sad from the last memory I don't know oh
no wait yeah I cried never mind I did I
was sad
[Music]
um
there's even the map about it here
oh do you need sundelions truffle
hearty truffle
he's sleeping on a [\h__\h]
stuff
push him off
13 discovered stone slabs the nature of
the Ring ruins they found this one in
the ruin above us oh so I don't have to
go up there to find it because it's down
here
Elena is able to read through my writing
okay okay
just who fought behind beside this rule
I left something behind in case the
Demon King returned or is me to know
this discovery talks about a Demon
King's return and here the people has
just happened if only we knew what those
sages did to prepare in case he came
back
[Music]
you can read the disciples Rising for
yourself it's all right next to the slap
oh okay
you already did decide for it
hmm The Demon King vast power no hope
Victory King's own life mainstream
prison him
in prison not indefinitely prepare
Daemon Revival researches must leave our
knowledge for future Generations
understandable I think right
talking in hashtags
so should I go on is there another one
I thought I had to give him travel to
like make him move but wasn't even
necessary
oh yeah that kind of sucks rain in your
eye
um
is it always raining here
I was on the road come on
the [\h__\h]
ah
I keep up although there's like almost
certainly
a clock there
and also
oh yeah I'm curious about these
waterfalls oh oh I'm gonna drown
drowning oh
what's wrong
oh
I got a second chance
and it's not raining
foreign
[Music]
recently
got so many batteries
but hmm
do I wanna do I want to try to go to the
top
seems like if I understand correctly the
slab that wasn't here was already
um
taken out right and translated or is
that a different one
I'll try to check it out anyway
[Music]
different one
and no rain again
okay I'm already at the top
oh
[Music]
into my pocket you go
yeah okay but
no more slab here
hmm
I think no more
open the chest
okay maybe I'll go down
what is that
okay
I know okay okay I'll go go go I'll go
give him the thing to translate
oh
what's this a graveyard
[\h__\h] why are you stones
um also that tree
is very Saucy I think I see
I think I see a stone come on come on oh
no okay
um
Instinct I think I've never seen uh or
found as many Crocs
I collected them
as today before
so who wants to talk to me about this
lab
what do you think
was this you could oh sheesh
pile of Caleb look at this
translated translated tell me
I need to know no could this be the
interior of the floating ring ruin whoa
sheesh that's so clear damn how much
pixels does you cam or megapixels does
your camera have
there appears to be so my inscriptions
in this one as well just like the other
ones
right let me see
um
promiscilla solemnly signed mineru Sage
of
hide the key
Southeast
and Trust future wish
defeat Demon King
that's all I can make out there's some
lettering I can't figure out but
Southeast I mean that mineru seems to be
someone's name
no
look at the context of look at the clock
I do believe that this is the first time
one of these slabs has put a name to
Sage oh that doesn't mean it mentioned
Zelda and the Demon King how fast
the scriptures are telling us all all
sorts of essential information
[Music]
what's the matter
nothing I just
um that part before the southeast
section
is it maybe not actually southeast of My
overall map but like Southeast
of something so if I go southeast of the
overall map I won't find it because it's
like actual somewhere else
Dragon Land what southeast of the Dragon
Land maybe huh
um
[Music]
player knows yourself this should be
read as Dragon Land South East
shouldn't it be southeast of Dragon Land
I don't know grammatically you know oh
my goodness I've proven useful
wait Dragon Land is maybe in the sky
hmm
it seems my continued sonai language
Studies have paid off
oh they were being upstaged
well where were we there's something
about a Dragon Land which selfish
how familiar are you with Southeast High
Roll there's a sight of Baron Baron
has long been known as Jonah ruins it
put it so the ruins falling from the sky
and is home to many ancient relics
hmm if memory serves they wear Dragon
there's orange on those runes
I don't want to read anymore
Fahrenheit
[Music]
clpr
oh
get deaf Dimensions
okay but how can you guys accidentally
know that
you must like purposefully do all this
and then go to Farren and you know what
you're getting yourself into
or did you do it without the quest
um
oh
what about this
and then what the sage is just chilling
there we'll see we'll see we'll see
[Music]
oh of course I'll help you
with that said let's be off to the Zone
like ruins and baron yeah
almost killed his pile
I mean yeah she's very cute I admit that
but you make me very sad
saying that huh
popular hotels are the Skyview Tower but
everyone's thank God I already uncovered
all that yeah yeah yeah
too far and we go
oh man
[Music]
there they go oh I'm sure they will be
fine
I must studying more about it so nice
civilization so I don't fall behind yet
it seems somewhat frivolous next to the
mystery of the real princess zella's
whereabouts I don't doubt that she is
safe in the well I must believe that as
chief of this Village I can't leave my
people so I must place a search in your
capable hands I pray that Princess Zelda
will return to us soon
oh
[Music]
um
what was I gonna say
the six hours are coming closer
um but oh
I wanna get this um Sage ring done
so I think at the very least
I'll be
doing that before
going anywhere so don't worry guys
let's make it seven Lucky Seven
well you know lucky numbers seem to
depend on the person
for me seven or honestly I don't even
know what my lucky number is
but not necessarily my lucky number
[Music]
I'm actually looking for wheat you guys
don't have wheat what the [\h__\h] but I'll
buy some butter
oh where can I get wheat
what would you sell if I did your quest
eggs
usually I like half ten or seven hand so
I can read some respect him
oh they want me too
bring all the chickens in one place
oh black moon coming
I'll do that for the chickens baby
some other time
exactly
okay then
uh let's see I think we can get
super close
oopsie oh
to where we need to go
um but there we go
now I can travel
um
thank you for gifting very nice
[Applause]
watch the first minute of this Blood
Moon's cutscene for a funnel Easter egg
does it change now
that would be
actually pretty cool
because
oh yeah situation has kind of changed
are you not worried about you know
what's going on here
oh
foreign
she's gone but it still happens
it's kind of sad about her it's so quiet
it's so much less threatening
yeah yeah
we've been thinking for a while Dad
that was the evil Zelda yeah I am
that was so big brain I remember the
moment where I was like
why would Zelda be announcing this so
happily
that's so weird
I should welcome you went to a humble
base of operations behold this is where
the real investigation starts it might
not seem like much next to the Skyview
Tower I'll concede oh yeah
going forward our research will proceed
from here tower has already gone off to
the sunlight ruins if memory serves he
spoke of starting his investigation
around draco's Lake
I don't know his exact word bounce but
if you go Southeast you should find the
donut ruins a volunteer to inspect
wait a second
is top don't answer me
but is Taurus say it's like a descendant
of
yeah okay never mind but oh my God
that's great
and he'll find the tear there and then
it's like whoa
what where are we going where there are
codes are like here oh
foreign
I'm on my way
Should I fly
up with the Skyview Tower
[Music]
or am I good without how far is it it's
pretty far and there's some there's some
mountains too
hmm
Shrine no
there's always a shrine nearby
[Music]
so I wonder if this
comes with a dungeon as well
we will see more news at 12 or something
like that
beetle is the sage that's why he's a
mortal and transcends timeless
Beetle after being so loyal to this
franchise really deserves some credit
been to this one before
probably
so he deserves to have a bigger role I
would say
oh should I get the shrine here first
yes I should
yeah
the more shrines the merrier I need more
what's this one
built for rails oh
kfp train system
oh okay
we're not really making a train
just using these cheap ass platforms
and let ourselves be careful I remember
there was like a similar Shrine that I
really struggled with
remember guys
I hope this one doesn't get that
complicated
this one
what
hmm
wait I'm not redoing a shrine right
I haven't done this one before
this one is famous oh really yeah
well the chat the chest seems fine
manageable
[Music]
I'll just put
some plates here and
um
okay
mind
wait
uh wait
pink
probably can't even take it with me
what's inside
sticky Elixir what okay
and I even went out of my way to make
something should I just
so there's no way there's no way
that this was eh
I'm scared
that's way too dangerous no no it's
gonna fall off
mm-hmm
[Applause]
I knew it
can just is that cheating
Shield surfiness
you could totally
turn it into a shape where it's like
closed off on the sides you know what I
mean
but
we can also
if I remember how
yeah
um
uh wait I forgot that's a shield stuff
wait wait wait wait you jump
what
ah is it because of my weapon
um
[Music]
I don't remember ah Shield jump a okay
thank you Shields jumping
wow
I mean
if you think of this instead of torching
your torturing yourself
to do it
was like attaching all these slabs to
one another then I must say
all the power to us however here it
might not work because like where would
I get the momentum from also there's two
rails
oh wait there are like broken
but again
the momentum should maybe help maybe
it actually works no okay okay okay okay
[Music]
I guess we have to
do it properly now
which sign
what is this
because you have to go once in the whole
Loop
okay it shouldn't be too difficult why
what too difficult why is this so
I just weren't so famous hmm
this part was the part you had to look
up
where are you
oh wait it doesn't fit to you
but
um
you think I'll get it on my own
Sam you have so much trust in me wait
this can't work either
can't really work
do I need more than one
probably
yeah yeah
more wind power please
and I'll take the third one too
I know I know that there is like a hole
but I'm thinking with all three of them
yeah babe that one's kind of tilted
of all three of them surely
won't have
that problem right
let's try
[Music]
okay
you think it's because of the lack of
balance really
who's the third
you need to eat I need all the parts
given
what
I know normally you don't necessarily
need all parts there's always a
different way of doing it
um
can I amend
the rails
oh
how about this
I mean
went wrong we're running away
let's see it
it's not gonna work probably
go in
no way
I can't even climb up
I'll start from the beginning
[Applause]
[Music]
but eh
uh
a very good place to start
you walked the rails
oh my God
this can't be any why this basically
switched out the middle of the short
middle blade
for
the long one
why would this work now maybe because I
can use both but then it's it stops
being too at some point
um I'm almost correct wait a second
I mean if I have to use all parts
there's only so many
logical eh logical options
right
so
I mean this
looks like incredibly stable but once it
loses One path
what's gonna happen
it fitsub do I need all of these
I wonder if I could just make also like
a
like a not a hovercraft but you know
like one of those
like a platform with all the fans facing
the ground and just get a lot of height
and then fly with my
just fly over with my
paraglider
also where do we want this do we want
these higher I would say yeah
that's what you did
where's case I'll do that with you but
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
please I mean even if it fails please
just don't fall down
oh wait it might
oh yeah yeah
how is this balance balancing
how's this one succeeding in my previous
invention which was basically the same
just
less lengthy
is failing
I had a
[Applause]
minute pretty cool
yay
that was pretty fun though once it
worked
statues oh
[Music]
I did it a lot faster on you
hey
you guys are so
nice to me it almost makes me feel like
I'm smart
huh
if it isn't new again
hmm
you know now that I've been to Tarrytown
I feel an even bigger wait a second
this one's actually easy I was about to
bring out another
of those uh floating stones
but
this one's pretty easy
yeah
you you dude you should do this always
it just makes so much sense
he's not falling sorry I moved it
just having a bottom platform
curing it with weight
you don't even need a stone that's this
big tiny one would do the trick I'm
pretty sure
um
thank you shock resistance
I don't need
a reminder
good
oh very tropical here
maybe there's some bananas
there's a fire Ah that's that must be a
tower
wait wait wait wait wait wait
yeah okay
oh can I oh
Fleet low too low two seats
what can I cook with that again
wait where is he
what
their calip the influence of the other
people has spreads to the Zone I ruins
did you see the pillar say ruined in
front of this tent there shouldn't be
artifacts of that kind around here an
anomaly
and there's more the Ravel at the base
of the pillar opened revealing a way
inside a new discovery naturally I'll be
going inside to investigate shortly join
me as soon as you can
what this thing you think that's so
weird
hmm
or does he mean something else
I want to check out this place this is
indeed special
look around before I go inside what is
this what is this what's this
watching a flavor I know now know how
much story I actually skip about
realizing it oh oh he's in here you see
I tried
um to get a good balance of
oh fishy
doing
story like as much story as possible
I don't want to skip it you know and I
want to do things
in the right order and all that
stuff like this for example
I guess you could find it alone but if
you find it with the quests together it
just makes so much more sense
and um
yeah the side stuff you know I think
the side stuff is all also very
interesting but
if you oh
if you want to see that I really
recommend playing the game on your own
Oh I thought it was a Kodak
taking the time to play the game on your
own because if I were to show all of
that on my stream
uh it would be a lot more parts
and a lot more
more like
calm play time where I'm just running
around exploring
not so exciting I mean for me when I
play it privately it's still fun and
exciting but as a streamer I just want
you guys to
get the best bites
when it comes to a game like this that
actually gives me the opportunity
to split it up like this
and motivates me to play it on my own
time
then you know
remember only I can't play this members
only no no no
but it's it's been nice to have a game
that I feel
happy about playing in my private time
too so yeah
anyway
the side stuff is good quality too
though so I do recommend
everybody
getting the game for themselves
and
you know playing it for the sake
of
getting as much out of this as possible
I could
I could speed run this game even more
and try to finish the story as well as
play through as fast as possible so that
we can move on to other things because I
mean I see
I see it's not like the best streaming
game as well
it's just typical of these kind of start
long story games
most people don't have the interest or
patience to watch it all through
so I could shorten it if I wanted to but
I
I feel like the game deserves more time
and deserves to be seen as much as
possible I feel like I'm surely also
missing out on certain
details and certain parts of the story
even
but I'm trying to
not miss out as much as I can yeah while
still
not wasting too much of everybody's time
you know what I mean
I want to find a good middle ground
um
yeah so let's see I'm really curious
so we're gonna revive someone to join us
are we gonna turn Taro into a sage he
does have the looks for it like he
doesn't look like just a random NPC
foreign
ruins but listen to this I've already
got a Whopper of a discovery on my hook
here
look at this
does this tell me something
does this mean something to me not
really it's a Zone it's an eye mural
complete with intact text the style is
unmistakable
it's nothing short of a rat of Miracles
that it's still here and basically
intact
Whopper did you guys see
Burger King Japan has a Diablo for
collab going on
but they're both double if not even
triple patties
they're both kind of spicy but one is
only one level spiciness
and I want to try it I guess but in
order to get like the
um
some kind of like special in-game item
or all of them you have to eat there
several times at different locations
that are participating
and I don't have that much time to and I
don't want to waste
my my short time in Japan that's
upcoming by eating Burger King every
[\h__\h] day maybe I'll get jenma to do
it
yeah no I think you have to eat once at
each participating Burger King and then
you get
uh like a full set of something
the Gemma love spicy things she would
probably love to eat that super spicy
Burger all the time
yeah I think she would actually like it
[Music]
um
and she can eat quite a lot too
so the triple Patty Burger wouldn't hurt
her a bit
I don't know if you know ever told you
but I know that like
one time
jenma went on a date with Vina
um to eat like the spiciest of the
spiciest food
when Ina was in Japan
they went together
doesn't even manage her
she's not even her manager but you know
everybody loves Grandma everybody loves
grandma
and you know I guess kind of one of the
like a dinner partner
for eating spicy food she talked about
it
but the thing is like I that was during
a time when Ina was in Japan and I
wanted to see her for the first time in
a long time
and there was like only this evening
basically and I missed out on her and
instead jenma gets to see her and I'm
like what
that fair
I want to go too but that was at the end
of a very long day for me
and I was already on my way home when
janma was kind of leaving
so yeah we kind of button touched and
then she went off to see you know
and I gave I gave Jenna some things to
give to Ina instead of me because I
wouldn't meet her for a while
yeah
anyway
which come to think of it might be a
scribble Scrabble to the donuts advanced
technology I've got a fair bit of
knowledge of the script so I just had to
try to suffering it thank God
some of it still eludes me
maybe it's a poem or some kind of a code
perhaps
here I'll read it out loud so we can
both get on the same page first part
says where the electric garb
hidden at the long-necked dragons
along the wide-mouthed forest serpent
I mean
I do have some
I do have some electric guard but this
is really necessary to have that
um
what do you make of for a serpent and
Dragons there to make calls to mind the
tall pillars found around these ruins
designed to look like dragons
for a serpent though I haven't seen any
designs like that what am I missing
wait maybe the fourth serpent is the the
river that flows through it on snaky
sneaky lines
genius
the first serpent bit does remind me of
a song that compared the dracos
I didn't even hear the song before
anyway there's more this code I'll keep
on reading offered Zona charge to the
altar at the tail oh okay
pretty sure it got that right but I have
no idea what it means what in the world
is it don't I charge and where is this
tale of an altar
hmm
if we could crack all the Riddles In
This code I'm sure that even greater
discoveries of waiters there's one other
thing I'm curious about
oh
the chest
yeah okay you can't open it leave it to
me
I was doing so much charge in case I
have none no way
[Music]
oh what
Oh I thought I was gonna wear
um
where is it
oh wait do I only have the pants
oh well okay
I am the sage
I mean
look at me
I just wanted to be the side character
who leads all to say yes
but okay
so
snake
that somehow opens its mouth I guess
yeah that's a mouth open mouth
[Music]
along the white mouth for a serpent of
its original tar at the tail the tail
not the mouth
the tail is like
what depends if it curls in then I just
can't see it
because of the trees
so we have to go to the back of it right
number one
but why
would these cloves in particular just so
that look but why are they like thunder
you know resistant
electricity
because that that element is already
Rangers element
I should give me something more special
no it's not that I'm sleepy it's just
like okay I don't know lack of uh oxygen
really
[Music]
bum
what do we have here
so night Warriors
but I can just sneak past them
[Music]
oh there's a wizard there too
I don't want him to see me
but the tail oh
at the end of the end of the Hill
let me really satisfyingly jumping into
it I wish I could jump into water like
that oh [\h__\h] that was wrong they don't
accept that anymore apparently
they need you to jump with style
but how
wait how do I how do I jump with Style
again
ah
do I flip
and wait what the [\h__\h]
ah place on there ah
hook up
[Music]
laughs
I don't know guys I don't know what I'm
doing don't even question it can I do it
from here
I forgot how to jump
oh there we go
[Music]
no no no no
don't don't think yesterday nine hours
today six hours
I will use this as my excuse
hmm I need more Splash fruits
that is totally the reason yeah yeah
whoa
that horn
did I miss no
what is that horn dude
oh it is
oh well
I'll get it back
we are
outside it's okay
[Music]
I thought if you attached it it doesn't
do that wow wow and silver one civil is
Alpha's one oh
[Music]
is it because the base was a glooms bear
but if it's on top okay I thought it was
on top but
I guess it wasn't whoa
wait where's this altar
this is where
this is where the the tail of the snake
is right
but
I don't see anything that
looks like an altar but
maybe maybe in here
[Music]
definitely worth checking out though
because it looks interesting oh wait it
might be just here
yeah that
is an altar
I shall offer
myself
in order to save my princess
even if it means
to give up my own soul
it is worth it and thus I shall do so
that's a little bit embarrassing
what
do I need a full set
I need a full set
[Laughter]
[Music]
but it's here
I offer it here
probably right
what the [\h__\h] do you want
hey I thought that that just felt top
was enough
okay that's why this place is so big
[Music]
where could the rest be I feel like I
have an idea
where one piece
possibly be I mean maybe they're all
alongside the river because I'm thinking
I saw something that I wanted to
investigate
that thing over there you
you push up
this thing oh
one piece I don't
I don't know [\h__\h] about one piece
they're obviously dressing me up for the
ceremony damn I know what you're doing
I know what you're doing
ah
foreign
[Music]
was there another one that I missed
oh
yeah yeah Zona I wore this once
or not not a donut like the the
this is what the uh all those people the
king and so on were like wait it's
another silver one
pleasure to fight you but I preferred on
land
[Music]
it's like a trampoline effect
I can equip armor
what's the plus well I mean that's not
really something that I have a feeling I
urgently need to do
[Music]
come here
what that's so annoying
[Music]
all right I have so many arrows I'm
finishing you off like this now
you're not a silver one
nice shot
oh
[Music]
why not
okay now we can go inside or focus on
going inside let's throw oh
and get the last piece of this special
ceremonial guards
[Music]
charged trousers wow looks cool
oh I'm pretty fine
[Music]
am I going the right way
what's going on oh wait
[Laughter]
a banger why who made the song
whoever made it must be a genius
ever made and sang it
they might be geniuses
we got them
butterfly
so guys tomorrow
s
and then
Tuesday
also
actually
yeah
to the two days uh
two days and three collapse
mm-hmm
and I'm currently very popular
everybody wants to collab with me no but
one of them is a Diablo collab
[Music]
it's gonna be morning time many this
time cronies going to suffer but next
time someone else will suffer
could be me it could be Cali I [\h__\h]
know what eh
oh there we go I was like nothing's
happening huh
again
sending signals to each other
I'm gonna be electrocuted I see it
it was a trap
[Music]
Mamma Mia
did I just open up a dungeon doesn't
really look like a dungeon
but I opened up something
cool cool guy um I was gonna say
ganondorf's trap Koga
Caleb did you see that lightning struck
that Dragon pillow too oh someone in
those ruins yummy
and I survived
and I'm coming out even stronger
oh I see you again
terrible lightning strong kids here but
I'm going to say you wouldn't hurt
I've never seen lightning strike like
that and even stranger the dragon
statues I seem to Glow just before it
link if you know anything about this
fill us in on what happened
unbelievable mechanism in Asian ruins
got rid of the thunder clouds and
revealed some new Sky Islands
great catch another amazing discovery on
the books in fact I'd say it's the whole
of the century
oh
significant Discovery to be sure I'm
going to investigate further but we have
no way of getting up there
oh you're right that doesn't make it any
less exciting though we need to report
just to Peoria right away
calip I'm going back to Coco Rico I want
to write out the recent events around
the floating Rune and the report for
Pura you should stick around here to
conduct a third row Pharaoh
investigation find out if there are any
more discoveries to be made
yeah even if we can't get up to the sky
there's so much discover on land
it's our duty to unrave a little of it
you can do this
no I think it's pretty clear
now that I am in fact
the sage
but
hmm
normally like all the other stages are
like related to
who they are getting their Sage power
from
I thought that was my role
well don't tell me anything maybe it
will still change maybe I'm just like
taunting the real Sage
and the real Sage was the
the sages we met along the way that we
didn't meet
the one stage that we didn't meet
do I hear horror plans
I mean I did not
get the fancy tier bracelet whatsoever
yet
it's not 100 set in stone but the fact
that I am wearing the clothes right now
really makes you think
but
I think I will leave it at this
is it monkeys or is it horror Blends who
knows
good people
ah
Wawa goes in circles
if you do more sorry next time you can
pretty much finish the game the next one
yeah
so maybe I'll do another hey
I'll do another side
stuff stream like yesterday Maybe
yeah it feels like I'm just so close
I don't like it
um
I mean what I still want to do is
explore a little bit more Underground
and
um
I think we need to still finish Koga
I think
and
side quests until the
Colosseum with the linels maybe if I
wanna torture myself extra hard
what
are you what
speaking of the yiga
oh this this place is famous for bananas
is the first banana I'm finding
nice oh
[Music]
[Applause]
I had two
enemies but
duplex bow yeah
does that mean doesn't mean that it
shoots two arrows because then I kind of
want it
you know duplex double sounds kind of a
lot yeah
okay
uh yeah yeah I got it
it was very Saucy that banana
don't ever trust
random bananas scattered on the ground
I I still have a
Lionel ball in case you didn't just see
it
three times shot is actually incredible
that I am keeping that uh bow live for
someone yeah yeah
money
Mr little [\h__\h] what
where is the cave
they always run towards the cave oh
hello Raiders
I always run so it's okay ah wait is
this oh
very misleading wait I want the fishies
okay but didn't I say I'm gonna end it
[Music]
Upstream excavation whoa
what is this place
am I supposed to open the
uh the door yeah but like where what
that is looking oh wait I see I see I
was like looking for
uh the electricity uh
connection but
it's up there
do the blocks
connected and does this also maybe
connected
wait I don't seem to fully understand
this
I thought these ones just you just have
to touch them and then they conduct the
uh the electricity
oh wait isn't that like
it was glowing yellow
foreign
[Music]
I don't know what I'm seeing either uh
because these these things what why are
these even here like they don't
team related
to the riddle
this movie has entered the room
um okay
okay
don't understand
you solved with only two cubes
how
to go up here
okay
oh
my God
oh no not the bottom one
oh but okay
[Music]
dropped it though
please at least show me that I'm not
done
wait
I have to finish this I am dedicated
whatever wow starts she finishes you
guys know that I start games I finish
games
this applies to everything
laughs
[Music]
hey I mean okay it makes sense
and there's more that's not the only
reward I guess the continuation of the
cave
is the reward or is it just heal
that's it
okay
um
[Music]
I don't mention all these like shameful
moments in my life
small see she's angry at you guys so
she's gonna hurt you
at night
it's gonna scratch up your face
completely
yeah thank you thank you for the mental
support and the physical support your
best thank you
okay guys it is
Super Chat reading time Hallelujah
you guys will get a little break from
tutk for a while probably then we'll
finish the game
although I could finish it next week
if I want I need you
[Laughter]
I was moving why
picked her up and her butt is kind of
wet
oh
[\h__\h]
she just came from the toilets you know
my eyes woman
okay I washed my hands and guess where
chunky wonky is
chunky monkey's still at the same spot
that's cute baby
same spot as like 20 hours ago like the
whole night she was already there
cute
it's okay don't expose movie
I mean she's gonna you know she just
came from the toilet the the fact that
she's a little bit wet there you know
she has a very fluffy butt
it's it's understandable
um she will clean herself up
eventually
um no judgment
sentimental no judgmento
okay
we go
over here to the girl's room
I started out this dream having no
breathing issues but I definitely have
them
oxygen door
oxygen door cool
um
hi Chad you are my oxygen
yes you are
um
[\h__\h]
I'm sorry guys
I'm sorry
me today
no oxygen cannot breathe
cannot function
oh God
no we are reading super chats
100 but we need some music
what
what is mean to small army
no
was she
you mean driver she wasn't driving in
her scene
what are you talking about oh but small
AMA was doing
so I opened YouTube and suddenly I see a
clip that says why is everybody being
mean to small London I can't let that
stand
be nice to small Mommy
[Music]
um
wait did you not hear eh you heard the
the clip right
that's the context here what you didn't
ah
it's just another Amy clip
coming up in my time it was surely soon
also come to your YouTube
recommendations
soon TM
oh this you can hear interesting it
should be the same routing
[Music]
what a surprise you guys always get the
things that I watch
[Music]
sit sit sit show up in yours now
Magic
[Music]
I am controlling your guys's YouTube
recommendations
I will use this to my advantage
okay guys
let me open whole liner
um because
I don't know how far we have to go back
not that far but
um
[Music]
damn
pekora's dream Kingdom Hearts today is
supposed to stream Final Fantasy today
oh man
Luna stream Final Fantasy today too
the games
that are unreachable
for us
hmm
it hurts
[Music]
oh yeah after seeing lots of blue
protocol too
well it's okay we will wait for
I wanted releases an En area
in 2024
you know
and did I ever read the Zelda
part six
[Music]
or wait that's part
yeah part six
maybe it looks familiar I think wait I
did I did
I did
Diablo's next I think
spot you've seen spawns and streams from
ff16 what from Whole level from other uh
people
[Music]
twitch yeah
IRL streamers
like Ira like flash tubers
yeah tons of twitch streamers getting
sponsored what
[Music]
yeah
good for them
meat cubers steak cubers
[Music]
Fletch flesh twitchers
V flasher
twitch pleasure beef cubes
it's not beef though because beef is
like a cow right
that sounds so funny
people
oh man it's easy to entertain me right
now
I think
[Music]
soon
okay
[Music]
thanks for helping with the installment
installation process of my Diablo game
um
[Music]
thank you
oh thank you thank you I agree it was
awesome need more
questions
we're born as a chicken Phoenix thank
you
huh
June 20 oh that's so soon
happy early birthday then in that case
it's very soon so I think I can say it
at this point
I think I'll be streaming on your
birthday too so
but no pressure you don't need to be
there if you want to be out and about
celebrating then I totally understand
whichever you choose it's fine for me I
just hope you have a wonderful day Brock
Sanders
you just came back from uh Europe
[Music]
oh you didn't go to Austria next time
then but sounds like you had fun anyway
nice thanks for coming to Europe
Skye thanks for the pinky graphic card
fun thank you
um
you know
during the the move day of my friend you
know I was disgusting with my friends I
brought up the topic of buying a uh I
wanted to ask if they could help me
create
you know not necessarily a whole new pc
but improve my setup
and then you know I mentioned not
getting the 40 90 and one of my friends
the pizza friend he was
like what no of course you have to get
the 49ing you have to go to 49 you don't
know 49ers
I already informed myself I read all
these comments and oh it doesn't seem
really like a good idea it's so
expensive it's not worth the money
um he said no it's the best value but
turns out he didn't really he didn't
really know what he's talking about he
just knew oh newest is best and he was
like oh there's all the people in your
comment section on your Tweet they don't
know
talking about then I'm like well I don't
know I don't know if you can necessarily
say that like
the you know arguments that they were
bringing up kind of
seemed like they made a lot of sense and
I also said you know it does use the
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h] ton of electricity and
all that but he was like no no you
should get the 40 90 level it can't be
so bad so he didn't listen yeah so yeah
then but I told him so so strongly like
I'm not getting the 49er that's [\h__\h]
like it's so big I have to get like a
whole case too that's annoying and it's
just not worth it and So eventually he
looks up the information
and then later on he admitted that 40 90
yeah it's not the best idea I should get
a 4080.
yeah he admitted it
[Music]
um
I don't know should I get the 4080 what
do you say what do I say about the 49 I
I value your opinion you know
they're like a little bit smaller
than the 49.
[Music]
I told him that I would go for 30 80 or
something like that because people
recommended me the 3080 instead 30.
but it was like then then you have to
upgrade again so soon
no not really not really
or the other one 7900 or whatever you
guys were
like you know offering as a an option
um
yeah I'm not sure but yeah pizza guy he
yeah I don't want to take his advice so
went to uh I I wrote to RBF who wasn't
there on that day
I wrote to RBF
he's up to helping me with my PC
gladly I think he knows a bit better
about stuff like that yeah
there's a reason pizza guy is not a
piece of guy exactly
it's not peace PC guy no no
he's really into pizza and into building
kitchens
yeah
he's really very very very very
into building kitchens very passionate
about it
like because like for his family
his parents house he like planned out
and I don't think he built it but he
planned out every detail of a full new
kitchen and they built it in and he's
like so proud of him and he always like
you know talks about it and then you
know our our friend moved right so he
very passionately uh told him about what
kind of kitchen to get and you have to
do this you have to get a kitchen
counter and you have to get
the the best thing would be to put the
the stove and the kitchen counter in the
middle because then you can look outside
while you're cooking and not against the
wall and you need you need even though
it's expensive you should get the
um the sliding thing is not the open the
door thingies in the in the you know
storage thingies
um
it was yeah very very serious business
to him
um tell me you'll take his advice 100 if
you ever build a new kitchen
yeah maybe I mean the things he says I
also don't necessarily agree about his
kitchen opinions either because he
really hates
L-shaped kitchens and I'm like it's not
so bad because he says you know you
can't use that part where the the two
sides meet in the middle and I'm like
that's not necessarily true like I mean
in the end I'm gonna put like stuff like
a toaster and so on down somewhere on
the counters so I might as well put it
there yeah I might not be able to like
work easily in that space But I mean I
could if I want to and in the end even
if I couldn't I could just put you know
stuff like the like a knife block and a
toaster and the rice cooker I can put
all of that there in the supposedly
unusable area of the kitchen counter
yeah anyway yeah yeah yeah they're so
sick to making pizzas
it's funny though like yeah
yeah it's funny
arguing about these things
um Pizza Frank getting roasted
foreign
is funny
[Music]
oh I'm running out of water hmm
yes movie did you clean your butt
huh
no
yes
when is it
no it's a little tangent because I
didn't I barely tangented it during the
gaming portion too
[Music]
okay let's go let's continue thank you
Skye anyway so don't worry I'm not going
to 40 90.
um
I'm so unsure there's like choices and
hmm I don't know I don't know
[Music]
oh but I'll I'll think it through with
RBF
maybe RBF
will actually give good advice
[Music]
I don't think I want two pieces
multiple right answers that's my problem
uh
[Music]
and like yeah I don't know if I get
something like does it work with what I
have do I need to replace other things
too Etc but I'll leave that up to RBF
no I don't think we really have
someone who's like
in charge of
who would who would have the position to
give us such advice or whatever in the
company no
no one in particular we don't have
a tech guy like Dad
who will
like a staff member okay can you guys
[Music]
I'm not gonna out of nowhere and like
hit her up about that because she's in
Japan she cannot even look at my PC like
in person she like I and she gives me
like you know like Amazon links to
Japanese items whatever I have no idea
if I can get the things here and like
what is the equivalent then you know
language is different and the stock and
price deserve is different stop stop
stop
I know you want you find it very nice if
I can
[Music]
use whole life members as my resources
but
no still I don't even understand what
she will say to me Japanese computer
terms I already don't understand English
or German computer terms if she'll throw
them at me in Japanese I don't know what
the [\h__\h] she's talking about
[Music]
snow
no I don't know just no no no no no no
no no no no
[Music]
no
no this man OMG not this woman OMG
this man OMG
[Music]
so I was like I scored an iceberg
how about no no
[Music]
no
ask Kelly if we like him
something Cali knows that you're
trolling right
oh
hmm
[Music]
watch Prepon thanks for the pinky
attention kill that one kfps we have a
clan in-game where you can socialize
trade and party up oh party party party
okay Pizza welcome to join until we
reach the member let me just press n and
look for kfp
what is it called only kfb cool
noise I want to join can I join
[Music]
my candy jelly
ah
[Music]
who the [\h__\h]
okay first of all that was a typo huh
you meant actually takanashikiana and
it's a AI cup AI cover
[Music]
do it now
anyway
oh even gave you yourself the title kfb
clan leader
well I hope you found some members have
fun together
it's been a while
[Music]
I can't look at the chat right now
uh really busy day in Georgia but I
watched all vods including the last tltk
stream and next day is my day off so I'm
playing Diablo and watching you playing
Diablo because timezone in Georgia have
similar as Austria by the way have fun
let me out
where's Georgia
[Music]
the country right do you mean the
country
[Music]
yo
Yoda so far you're in you're in Georgia
right now
my Korean bro
[Music]
do nailing in Korean
money
oh it's also I know it's also stayed in
the U.S so hmm
no but they say time zone in Georgia
similar as Austria
so they mean the country which is in
Europe
[Music]
no guys no no
no no no
[Music]
no
haven't I don't hear much from Georgia
from a day-to-day basis but I hope
you're having a good time there yeah
enjoy
[Music]
uh
salmon extensions
[Music]
what a name
this is a two-year Super Chat I became a
new orange and round thingy with two
Wings unfortunately I watched more of
your tangents than you gameplay last
year should I say that was unfortunate
still I love you blah blah and that's
certainly why I'm here
thank you so much yeah you are a little
bit of a lurker aren't you
see you around that much but I'm glad
that you've been here for two years
thank you so much for the long lasting
support
um
and I mean I see I know I know people
like my tangents that's why I always
bring them to my gaming streams my long
gaming streams
oh fortunately today I had basically
nothing but whoa the story is going
places in the game so
do we really need Chihuahua tangents
when the game is so interesting right
now
I say no
anyway thank you for the Super Chat the
recipe chat specifically
your name is difficult though very
difficult don't know how to say it ah
there you are
hey did you fall asleep good morning
it's not that late you're you're donated
in Europe so
you should be around my time zone
but don't worry I am going to end soon
and then you can go to bed
Unwritten Birds action thank you
it felt wrong to watch holotonin for
free like that if you were all at HUD
offense it would have been the talk of
the concert yeah
yeah that is true I mean I agree like I
I think I really
I was hoping for having four fast I also
made the suggestion I'm pretty sure
um
um but yeah they just had ideas for
other units I suppose I think it would
have been epic though but I think our
members also like were split
well I was on the same day as Will May
never
[Music]
was different day too right
um
remember
[Music]
Louis was day one we know day two just
her oh yeah right that's the only thing
that was separating us
[Music]
but they could have done like you know
how they brought suse
on both days as a surprise
they could have brought us
ah because all of hollow X was on one
day yeah I emcee
I did but yeah so what I'm saying is
they could have brought over
one small performance
oh well you know could have would have
should have but didn't
hmm
[Music]
it is worth it yeah so say it's cool and
all but
who just has worth it doing something
like that
um
they didn't see me cooking
[Music]
yeah yeah agree agree
thank you thank you
but I think
you know which was getting started now
that mumei and udenae have
officially used their 3D
there will be many many more
opportunities to show off
power of Horror Story
yeah it truly begins now
I think they know the worth
the Spain induction thank you Mr boy
thank you
[Music]
Cruz action
Jacob 47 thank you for the pinky plane
tickets
thank you also Lord so many flight
ticket funds thank you guys
yeah I don't know if I can like really
do all of these performances
it's not only like you know the fact
that I have to pay for the tickets but
it's also a Time issue like going
back and forth like twice for three
times a month
so stressful
and I also don't want to stay a whole
month because
[Music]
cats number one then second
um
it's just like
you know the whole I just prefer having
a comfy place where I can do my usual
routine
of how I stream
don't no need to worry about internet
connection
or being noisy Etc you know so I don't
want to be away for so long unless I've
really really
have something like I don't know if it's
for for a full myth
stream gathering in Japan I would do it
for that
but if it's for just like one random
appearance in somebody's anniversary or
birthday or whatever I don't know if I
can connect it with something else that
would be ideal oh yeah
yeah it's just
difficult
I wish
I wish Europe was a bit closer to Japan
if the if I lived in Indonesia then I
think going back and forth
so often is not such an issue anymore
yeah but for me it takes quite a while
to get to Japan
same for America
yeah
yeah I'm stuck in the middle
oh yeah true okay Indonesia to Japan
it's not as short as I thought it was
gonna be ever
it's real
yeah
for some reason I thought it would be
like a four hour flight
it really wasn't
[Music]
better than EU to Japan
yeah yeah that is true
oh and much cheaper yeah possibly
mm-hmm
no hemispheres yeah what the [\h__\h]
anyway
[Music]
um
Jacob thanks for the pinky no damage
and yes I need to get one of those fancy
credit cards God damn it
should
well
my upcoming flight is not coming out of
my pocket yeah
so
I cannot connect it to a credit card
anyway maybe next time
someone I'm flying out of my own pocket
[Music]
yay
I know right very nice very nice we're
nice indeed
Brandon Duncan Klondike Saloon
thank you
oh thank you that's our sweet
yeah see I could I could choose to just
not do all of that
because
[Music]
it's it's just eating up time and money
yeah
going to the US for recording motion
capture for a music video
I could just you know make a really
simple MB or no Envy at all
for the album stuff
[Music]
yeah
and then I wouldn't
have you know such a big
loss of time and money but it's for my
own satisfaction
and there are
the experience of having
some really Kick-Ass badass music videos
that I can be proud of
and I got to see him and that was a nice
bonus yeah
yeah I want to do it in this case
[Music]
it's just such a waste too to leave the
album like that with no music video
and
especially of certain songs that I have
in there they really deserve
proper Envy honestly I should have maybe
released them as singles I don't know
but I guess in the album they make very
very powerful
candidates you know form
people will probably re-listen to it a
lot
Michelle process was easier on you but
yeah yeah it's
rap and making me busy there's a lot of
things to organize that I'm kind of like
taking into my own hands
it's very different from like how Cali
does stuff I think because she's with a
label
I mean she writes her lyrics
so that's like an extra piece of work
that I don't have
but I think her label probably takes
care of a lot of the other things
mm-hmm
and I don't have that so it's taking
more time and it's taking more like
effort from my brain
but it will hopefully be worth it in the
end and I hope you guys will enjoy it
very much y'all
oh and I did have that meeting
I did have that meeting with my lyrics
on if I told you that I had it we talked
about stuff I just ah it was
embarrassing I I didn't in the end in
the end I didn't tell her like any
specific episodes of things
um but I just like pretty roughly
it's pretty roughly told her oh I want
these kind of topics touched on in the
lyrics
and yeah ah she's in there why are you
watching
makes me feel awkward what
[Music]
there she is money
and you know even though she's supposed
to be only writing the lyrics
I actually am asking her for help for
some Melody stuff as well
with some songs
she's so talented no she's cooking
because like I had some songs where I
felt like the melody
wasn't quite what I imagined
and and money she gets it she gets it
oh but I guess wait I didn't really
[Music]
tell you guys
that I'm working with her on the album
but she's the one who wrote the lyrics
for do you and also for Sparks I think
right right right right
[Music]
did she did she I think she did
my brain my brain
well I didn't
I didn't yeah
I did now well I mean
yeah well she's uh helping me definitely
with at least a part of the album um
but
as long as I'm not leaking melodies
be safe
[Music]
anything to leak to us
I cannot
but actually
[Music]
ah like two songs are like completely
finished and mixed everything is
finished and then the other songs
oh at least they're like
instrumentals are now fully finished so
I only have to wait for the lyrics and
then I'll record it
but I think like time line wise
we're we're good we're good with the
time
I think
uh it's working out pretty smoothly
right now
and I think the release date that I am
that I was Desiring that I want
to go with I mean there's no exact date
I was like I just had a release month in
my mind
but I think it's gonna work out without
any particular delay
um
weights faster me too
[Music]
yeah I didn't want it to overlap too
much with my birthday
also not with my anniversary
so
birthday is July anniversary is
September
[Music]
when could it be when could it be when
one could be
but let's not jinx it because I mean
there's still possible that
December no it's so possible that there
might be delays I don't know
[Music]
I wish I knew how to cook
knock on wood yeah yeah
yeah it must be November then December
November October
Halloween album
[Music]
but ideally what I wanted to do is like
if my birthday if I could do it for the
year birthday stream
I was gonna perform one song as like a
teaser
on
that occasion
but
I don't even know when the 3D birthday
is going to happen at this point
[Music]
so yeah in my my current strategy
strategy tragedy tragedy problem is
I don't know when it's happening so will
it be after the album or before way
after way before maybe around the
release time tragedy
[Music]
but honestly I guess like if it actually
happened on my actual birthday it would
have been possibly a little bit too
early to tease it anyway so a little bit
of a delay on teaser is fine anyway but
um
we'll see
[Music]
birthday delayed by a month or two like
akihad
yes or even more
[Music]
it could happen
so anytime I don't know hopefully
within this year
um
what the [\h__\h] no what a terrible advice
sometime after inas
didn't even have hers yet and she wants
to do it so hmm
I don't know
hello X got their lives on time yeah
I've noticed
but you know other Japanese members have
to wait to
um
[Music]
let's continue
where was I
here yeah
on kfp I just got home from work and I
solemnly declare that I will pre-order
your figure for my birthday if I don't I
shall live in the usual room forever
that said thank you I mean I don't even
know if uh if if a pre-order is that
necessary for these kind of things
but better safe than sorry right thank
you so much
thank you Louie I hope you will enjoy
the figure I wonder how long it will
take to arrive is it different from
like typical whole life merchandise
or does it also take like six months
oh they are also made to order oh what
can you not buy them
after the pre-order period
oh
[Music]
December October December
well time will pass very fast trust me
hmm
they can increase in price
[Music]
general sales is limited
so if you guys haven't ordered one yet
and you want a high quality Chihuahua
figurine and check out the
[Music]
good smile
figure from me
[Music]
please do
oh no problem thanks for coming anyway
[Music]
thank you guys for ordering it already
thank you you guys are the best
thank you soon
a papa parade
[Music]
oh yes
the connective World song Rather lady
yeah yeah she wants my figure
she she she's not she's not the okay of
peace
maybe she just likes everybody
it's just a coincidence
she probably just likes everybody
[Music]
good taste though yeah yeah
while I figma and Android and Android is
also still in the works I only saw
myself in Gray until now Pennsylvania
thank you so much for the support
blood donation
I do want to be ignored okay thank you
though
Jacksonville
diabolo
no more boodle you know the Japanese
members staying they like use the second
half of the word diablo and depending on
when they stream Diablo they they made
up these terms like as
[Music]
depending on when they're streaming
Diablo in the morning
and noon in the evening
cute you know how Japanese people
abbreviate and call tears of the Kingdom
[Music]
I just saw that yesterday
Tia King
tear from tear and kin from Kingdom
in Katakana they say tiakin
and like blue protocol is pretty simple
in this case they just use the first
couple letters of both words
sounds like chicken
yeah no I like Japanese abbreviations
yeah yeah but Tia King was a surprise to
me
um
but I guess it makes sense because
they're just skipping the two
unimportant words of that
yeah
but it would be weird if I called it Tia
King nobody in English calls it tyrkin
tierkin
I just say tutk
[Music]
Final Fantasy oh no they will just write
FF and just say
if if they want to say it shortly
yeah I'm pretty sure yeah I think I've
heard it like that
[Music]
you're right tltk rules of the tongue
nice I think so too you guys are welcome
to copy that from me when talking about
it oh yeah
meow because quests in Japanese you have
to say
[Music]
night blue
night
yeah it just doesn't work in English
[Music]
those are I mean those are like just
obvious I feel like it's just obvious in
a lot of cases no
foreign
[Music]
oh
what
wait what oh wait what I forgot you I
thought I thought you're talking about
the kiwawa figure like you're
you're getting a cute wow figure instead
of extended like Chronicles for you but
no you mean
what you're just not getting my figure
at all
you're getting my figure right
how do other people say yeah how do they
say it
you're abandoning the Xenoblade figure
well then get mine how about that
of course
yeah
hmm
you could have gotten both but instead
you get the Kiwa figure and a Super Taco
to me
thank you
what a deal
okay guys
Diablo is done
okay Minecraft is really
few
so
I'll Zoom for it uh the one Minecraft
stream that I like deleted afterwards uh
it was from Jacob 47 out he sent one
Super Chat thank you
and let me move on over to the actual
one
Kiara figure is cheap really
I sounded on some of like the figure
websites I was ranked pretty high
happy I'm happy that my finger is doing
well thank you guys so much I didn't
expect it to do so well
but
you guys waited for so long now it's
finally here
hmm
police
[Music]
hey you yes you I just wanted to say I
love you if you don't believe me that's
fine I love that side of you too that
sounds like song lyrics Kiss for the
homies boss
[Music]
why does that sound like song lyrics to
me
[Music]
what happened to your name
your your Sunshine right
I hear this movie dramatically crying
in another room I guess yeah it sounds
like I was thinking the same it sounds
like an Avril Lavigne song
like
a girlfriend girlfriend
no way no way
I think you need a new one
she wants to hurry up I want me to hurry
up too
I'm tired
I'm like a physically exhausted
iron ready
[Music]
foreign
on the subject of parking payment
a guy charged people free quit for
parking spaces at the Bristol Zoo in the
UK for 20 years through the point
everyone knew him as the parking
attendant he left a note saying he
retired
turns out it was a scam you mean that it
was always free
the parking was always free
[Music]
quit is that like three bucks three
dollars
[Music]
I guess at some point you know you fake
it till you make it that nobody doubts
you anymore
because you've been there already
forever
three pounds
[Music]
how many tips with the series oh my God
this is probably all in cash too
probably didn't even really give out uh
like receipts
so it's all like earned
in you know no tax
untraceable
sheesh I mean
have to command him for
doing it successfully never getting
caught
um
oh they only realized because suddenly
it became a mess when he was gone
[Music]
oh
no I never got caught and I guess you
never carried the consequences of it
because also in the end like who gives a
[\h__\h] right
I mean I don't know if it's like whoever
is in charge of going after or something
like that if they would really care
about some retired old guy who
pretty smartly
scammed a lot of people for parking
tickets like yeah
in total that's a lot of money for but
for each person that he scanned for them
I mean individually it wasn't much so
I don't think he really harmed people
but in the end I mean it was kind of a
job for him right so we because he would
be there right and do it personally or
did he put like a like a machine there
to do it for him
I would assume he was there in person so
in a way he worked for it right
he was earning money in his way he just
created a job for himself then
so
[Music]
it's kind of earned
yeah he looked after the parking lot
Captain secure he created himself a job
where there was none in
yay
that's just like a
a [\h__\h] hero
what the [\h__\h] what do you mean
what
this that is that is
impressive
oh come on guys okay whatever
Jeff this is what I was looking forward
to
Jeff the phoenixsonian Oh Holy One
You're faithfuls and I have just
returned from our holy pilgrimage but
the village seems emptier than usual
would you know what has happened to the
denizens of phoenixton I I don't I
cannot answer this question
I don't understand
what denizens means but don't worry Jeff
let's just sit down and have some tea
and and and yeah uh
so good like I think you're just
imagining the lack of people
[Music]
it's just because you got you you were
gone for a while right
um
[Music]
it's like when you
when you're gone for a while and come
back to the OG place and then
it just seems also different and fresh
and new
nothing changed yeah take this pill
swallow it
front of my eyes no I would never do
this to Jeff I would never manipulate
him like this
yeah but it's your imagination in the
end and and see it's just more organized
because maybe some people maybe maybe
maybe maybe
when people quit and left to go to a
different
Village possible that's very possible
I've heard such things
and maybe some were abducted by
rival villages
which you can't even call Villages
maybe we must save them Jeff
oh
but in any case
everything is okay everything's all
right I kept a good eye on the situation
[Music]
aliens could have been aliens yeah
I mean at night I was also sleeping so
maybe some aliens abducted aliens of
Minecraft when I mean because the
Enderman
it's like pretty close to an alien
but wouldn't it be funny
if they implemented aliens like for real
and UFOs at the sky
[Music]
wouldn't it be funny
no I will cook I will I will because
thank you
Richard
Richards
thank you
um I'll be honest with you I don't think
this will help
but
never give up
wrong pocket yeah
[Music]
it's okay like my hope is that I'm busy
with other games anyway
[Music]
um
and and so far it's not really much of a
cope I don't mind that much
I mean
foreign
just FF there are like other games I
want to play too
[Music]
since the beginning
before my debut
but yeah I just try to not think of it
[Music]
[Laughter]
was a typo I thought uh 14 Final Fantasy
I'm not good with like those old numbers
I thought it meant Final Fantasy 16.
I thought I could play Final Fantasy 16.
sorry
[Music]
nah I will not be forgiven
no no way never miss fish tank is
[Music]
oh yeah I heard what doesn't affect me
right
no thank you
Anthony Brown dancing thank you
[Music]
is exclusive to exclusively
to make the super jet reading go longer
I'm a very selfish selfish chicken
wanting more Wawa
okay it's
[Music]
okay so guys want more time with me I
want more time with you
um
[Music]
you're even being honest about it so I
respect that
[Music]
I'm just today I'm suffering
a little bit just a little bit you have
a problem nah it's not a problem no
only if you wanted to be
Bucks Head ad thank you soon iron
and Mr JC thank you
oh true
I am
classical
[Music]
what
it was false
thank you for the pinky
it was false we mean it was false my
last appetite was a lie I heard it and
saw a news article about it but it was
false I'm sorry here's a joke for
recompensation for the professional
comedian
how do you keep a phoenix and suspense
ha o
how
Phoenix and suspense
um
[Music]
how
ah wow okay
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
that was incredible
[Music]
I don't think I've ever been
so got them before
[Music]
and you guys all leave a knew the answer
what the [\h__\h] is a must be common
[Music]
just exchanged with different words for
Phoenix
I don't get it really
let it
be explained to you by kfp
[Music]
I'll remember this
black mango Indonesian and Jeff
stabbings
for Final Fantasy 16 programs or the
demo I finished a demo instant pre-order
this demo is the best introduction you
could have to any game really
if I play it it will not be now
maybe sometime
in the far future
maybe maybe in 50 years maybe in 100
years
maybe in a long time when all of you
will be dead
[Music]
yo I've been getting
mosquito bites
where are these [\h__\h]
where are they
[Music]
dude same yeah tis the season of
mosquito bites
they come to you and take your blood
it's the season
oh scratchiness
and you will never be left alone
this is the season of mosquito Nets and
mosquito sprays go get them all tis the
season
mosquito the socks we hate them so much
so much
part of my album foreign
[Music]
but if it's itchy then it's a mosquito
bite
you're welcome
uh-huh
tis the season of mosquito bites on your
legs and on your arms
arms test the season of mosquito bites
[Music]
maybe my cat's will
eat them up
[Music]
there's the season
of super chats I finished this so they
go
tis the season
of the end of the stream while we go
cooking and she go
[Music]
and in German we say outfit
I'll leave it there uh tomorrow
[Music]
wow wow wow wait
I probably
should send
a that's right okay never mind
thank you for watching today see eight
hours shorter than yesterday
[Music]
and the Super Chat reading wasn't even
that long will you make a schedule I'll
try I'll try I'll try I'll try I'll try
my best I'll try my best Adriana best
I'll try my best before going to sleep
I'll try otherwise otherwise you can
expect
uh streams around uh one at
1pm my time
and another one after that like
I think something like 4 P.M my time
maybe
one is not on my channel so you will
have to rely on my Twitter
so I will notify you guys okay
[Music]
oh my God what
okay bye -bye
I'm out of here
and Germany
another wink is over
test the season
of June
it's almost over then it's July tis the
season of my birthday it's less than a
month oh my God
what am I singing let's turn this off
bye bye are you
[Music]
Roar
hmm
[Music]
oh
uh-huh
okay belly rubs
oh he's moving
[Music]
okay
anything else to say um
no okay let's see
huh
cute