foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
in the middle of a battle welcome
uh I was like okay let's do at least one
or two side quests quickly off stream
um but I ran into this douche that
um it's level 43.
that uh I think is part of the side
quest
um
he he already hit me
in the face real good
um but I think I can do it anyway I'll
give it a try I wanted to flee but I
cannot flee
so I will give it a try and hopefully I
don't die yeah
foreign
this one's difficult
this one's easy
their moves that is limited you got this
people always uh have completely The
Duality The Duality of kfp this is what
it is all right then let's uh get right
into it
okay
[Music]
we have two Healers
oh my gosh there's so much going on guys
thank you
thank you uh we're enjoying your
membership no
okay
almost one fourth down
I will shook the first moment I went
into this battle he gave me uh
um
and he already brought me down to one HP
once but I I think
um oh my gosh
I don't think I can do it twice going
down to one HP since I have the the
skills uh flight oh my God
oh oh God can I do this
eat dirt I'm gonna die oh whatever I'm
just gonna do it coming through is this
the new one of the old one that looks
like
scarlet and first that was the old one
oh that's okay
let's go
60 percent
oh my God okay there goes my um Second
Chance of not dying oh yeah
okay okay we're doing good we're doing
good we're doing good
[Music]
then tonight's meal is
[Applause]
dirt
bikes
[Music]
[Applause]
I just realized it's probably the bgm is
probably too loud like the fighting sfx
is too loud
uh okay
I did that that adjustments in the wrong
moment it seems
what is you doing far enough
I am positive it's going to be today
I am positive very positive
oh [\h__\h]
guys
I like how I died by doing the Phoenix
move
it makes so much sense
[Music]
all right no problem
s
I'm scared I'm scared to get close
[Music]
okay I'm back I'm not scared I'm not
scared at all
this is nice warm up isn't it
dead and xiong almost dead oh [\h__\h] yeah
they're all coming after me oh baby I'm
so scared
you guys need to step up your healing
game
[Music]
did you have a nice day so far huh
my day only just started but I'm fine
um
yeah it's been okay cool cool
what do you mean what do you mean my my
problem I'm dodging fine okay I'm
dodging as much as I can when elephant's
movement is slow as slowpoke
[Music]
I wanted actually to do Revival never
mind
I'll just wait I'm not done yet okay how
do I fight again I forgot how to fight I
forgot how to fight
that again
uh
um
[Music]
okay I'm almost there yeah
who should be revived first maybe she on
a new lease online
rainbow LED I expected that I saw that
coming no problem let's switch out
[Music]
um
and yeah
I'll wait for a Revival I guess yeah
there we go
[Music]
and also revive very well because uh I
would feel sorry for her
I try to save one body and the other one
gets sacrificed it's the circle of life
it is the circle of life baby
[Music]
um I can't help you with that man I
cannot help you get out of here
you saw that that was rolling out of the
line oh
before
oh
no he's going on a rampage okay
I don't care about the bees the bees
must stay alive
that's okay that's okay
I saw that I saw that I just wanted to
you know bash out all those uh
wow
this is
warm up
um
I would like to be alive when this uh
monster goes down oh my God oh my God oh
my God
every time
calm down
um
let's restore those seats
anymore
[Music]
take this
okay do you want to be revived okay
I'll help you out oh do how I'm dead too
okay
ah
to be cutting
a revive yeah she is she is oh there she
goes um
please please help please help
see please help me
on the beat
okay just everyone
um come back to life please
okay okay
stay away from my friends
I can't I can't I can't lose now I can't
lose now oh
look at that almost party wipe no no
no no no
see I'm not gonna waste my elixirs and
[\h__\h]
yeah
I'm not gonna waste that
no
um
now I'm a bit scared that
the moment I want to use a gel he's
going to get hit and die whoever's left
on the field
uh read I'm not gonna read it what are
you talking about
they're there to videos Alexis are there
to be no no
that on the side quest
no way
oh my god um a free free life bottles oh
look we're almost done we're almost done
with him
no I'm not going to use it don't you
dare point a gun at me don't you dare
look at me
uh you weren't the same way when you
were playing there you go there you go
don't judge me
what should I do life bomb or I mean
they're just gonna
quickly die again
it's more important to have more people
a lot okay it was a lot to have more
people alive right now
um
ready to go okay okay okay okay okay
uh-huh
I'll do this this has got your name on
them
and then I'll do
oh my God
I'll do this I'll bring you back don't
you dare me again
okay chill focus focus focused
[Music]
come on
get out of here get out of here
no further
away
thank you
ah
Titans
oh we have zero see peace
yeah he is going all out just like he
wasn't this difficult for the first half
okay okay I finished him off finish him
off
pieces
[Music]
[Applause]
lightning
oh my God what a way to warm up
oh my God was that worth it
astral flowers to be stronger
I do I'm trying to level up here okay oh
man
time to suck up on items welcome so
welcome everyone welcome everyone to the
Stream
today is uh supposedly the last
um Tales of a rise stream
uh because not because I'm finishing the
game today but because we are going to
reach the
point of no return the cut off points
today I think I mean I've got able to
cook here your guys's uh opinions on it
and most of you say I'll I'll be able to
do it in uh if I don't do side quests in
two to three hours and if I do then
maybe in six hours very vague I think
like the highest estimate was six hours
honestly that's nothing to me and I am
that's what what I expected anyway
I expected something like I don't know
seven eight hours and the more the
merrier to be honest I'm I want to play
as much as I can so uh yes
um well we'll be fine we'll be fine we
can even raise livestock on the side my
super chair yeah well I'll read I'll
read them when there's time
um well I I want I want to read them
today when I'm done with the game so we
will see how how long it takes me
um
you will need it for the final boss if
final boss you mean I mean I'll I will I
will be fighting the final boss off
screen I suppose
or do you mean the final boss from like
today before the cutoff point you don't
mean that I think final boss will not be
something that I fight on stream which
means I can also kind of focus more
um to be honest that's probably better
for me
uh and I I'm I'm honestly not so mad
even about not being able to stream
until the end because
um as much as I enjoy streaming this
game uh I also want to have a little bit
alone one-on-one time with the game you
know
the idea of being able to just
Focus
and be like on instead of focusing on
entertaining but uh focusing on the game
so I am fine with that oh we have a a
new gel to buy
hmm and I got a stuck stuck up stuck
stuck up on live balls
let's buy 14 because we'll probably pick
up a live bottle somewhere and I don't
want to throw that away
and why did you say fine uh finally if
you're not finishing the game today I
already said why
it's even in the film neighborhood you
probably didn't see it in big huh it's
also in the Twitter uh post we're not
finishing the game today but we're
reaching we're finishing the playthrough
the series of me playing this game
because there is a cutoff point where
I'm not allowed to stream anymore
understand the
and
and now uh oh we need a lot of these as
well and now I'm out of money
oh
I got a truck before spending money just
imagine me with a stack of uh with a
stack of of dollars and then dollar
bills and then you know you know the the
movement of like
you know what I mean that's what you
must imagine
can I sell some armor that we're not
using anymore
this one
and oh this one's actually better than
what she's wearing now
let me
uh see there's some confusion apparently
about where the point of no return is
but I have once again checked
um to make sure to confirm 100
now the point of where I'm supposed to
cut off is where he says the way you get
the choice between that he says I have
to be ready to face anything whatever
happens
and then you get the choice between the
only ways forward or turn back for the
time being
and I've been sent a screenshot so that
it makes it a little bit uh easier to
recognize
uh he said something like soon we might
oh my God we might very well learn
something about xion and his own past
blah blah blah so that's it's very clear
now I think
so uh that is I think not the very very
end but I don't know is it the very no
don't tell me don't I don't know
whatever whatever
but at least we're sure now about where
where the point of uh cutting off is
um
foreign
for the accessories for the longest
amount of time we have in a kind of like
ignoring the accessories because you
guys said they only really have good
accessories in the late game but aren't
we in the late game now
uh kind of wanna you know we've got way
more animals I never imagined maybe you
get some good accessories now
would probably be a good idea
what happened to all our money what are
you yelling at me for
the term hangry she on
are you are you
she's mad at me you're my money
so I'm gonna actually go for an X exp
boost and no wait I have no boss fish
am I not the boss fish
wait what up l l is better anyway
I think so
um
I don't want it to be reduced by 20
percent
I'll just make it with someone else nice
and we talked to we can talk to anyone
talk to me can we talk a moment
do you mind if we chat a bit
now there's something I never thought
I'd hear you say
remember when we talked about what it
was like well
who do you think
as a child
my childhood maybe you missed the memo
that was going around but there was a
memo going around anything of my past
I know just whatever you can remember
man there's got to be something right
right
well have I ever told you you were the
boss baby back when I used to serve
under a den and master you have my hat
and you are a female yeah but that must
have been after you were already grown
up right
do you happen to remember anything from
back when you were younger
I remember I had a kid with me huh you
had a kid with him no of course not the
child's father was another Soldier
back in those days we risked our lives
for a master we'd never even seen we
just fought for them and didn't even
question it
when that kid's dad died and I saw them
sitting there crying
Felt This Bitter Indescribable feeling
it's like I was drinking something toxic
that I knew I shouldn't well but
couldn't stop
it was strange
I never understood why I reacted like
that
soldiers died every day it wasn't
anything new
what it tells me is that deep down you
were the same man then as you are now
you've never been able to accept
Injustice in the world really really
have grown to like
embarrassed me and elephants I wonder
whatever voice actors poor kid not that
there's anything worth knowing now
you know I just remembered that kid was
good at sewing dolls they gave me one
once I said good luck charm to protect
me dolls
Alvin has such a warm voice it's time we
go to sleep and she on just really fits
well she I feel like I'm she doesn't
have this like I don't know thankfully
she doesn't have this super classic
ready to head out uh anime like English
voice acting anime girl voice I don't
know if you know what I mean I don't
even know what I mean
but um yeah I don't know it's not such a
um typical
boring voice I would say
it's a little more unique yeah
um question so I was actually I didn't
want to actually kill the Google
I actually wanted to go to the priority
subquest taking root
but am I blind because I don't see
anything here going on
no wait maybe it's not even there
ah wait it's here
ah there it is oh I went to the wrong
map
okay I'm just gonna quickly
do the subquest it's it's I think a low
level subquest so
that was quite the little Adventure we
went
also yeah I'm still my singer who know
from somewhere and I don't know where oh
yeah
maybe we should gather the hoodle
also I have a lot of things to tell you
guys today I'm still not done telling my
story about wow about my vacation
whoop
potato
[Music]
that looks like the Google we were told
about which one which one which one
which one which one
which one
just courteous aren't you uh
easy
yeah this is uh I just went back to an
old area
um to look if we still have quests open
and I picked up these low-level
questions
so we won't be running out of work
anytime don't be surprised guys
okay
um well then we finished that question
we can go back what was that again
did I never open this up
or does it always come back do these map
actions always come back
strong
I'm just overpowered
uh
op yes I guess I'll give back my quest
Bandai Namco is here to support me
mentally when I have to end the stream
even though I don't wanna I don't wanna
you know some part of me doesn't even
want to read super chats today because I
kind of want to
um you know at the cutoff Point
immediately end the stream and just
continue playing territory probably
I see myself wanting to do that
but I I should read super chats
yeah no no I have to
damn it hey I'll leave that for another
day
continuing the uh play for alone gotcha
he wants to play gacha then I recommend
to you Tales of luminaria dude
tales of luminaria
um
Tales of God happy for someone who just
went on a wild goose chase
there's no need to sweat the small stuff
oh it's
doing a good job as the Ambassador you
know
what I will went well went well what are
you gonna give me for that huh uh
Freight right
huh yeah I'll let you go you're gonna be
sure I'll be telling you everyone just
how hero again I want more than that
not just words okay
that is less money than I spent on my
Revival portion potions are you aware of
that dude
I spent way more money on the items that
I had to buy
afterwards
but okay
okay
I think though I think Hmm or not
when oh wait maybe not I don't know I
don't know I think it is
there's also something here that bothers
me because it's in the first area
should we check it out I wonder how old
that Quest is
at that cutoff point I wonder if like
afterwards you can still do side quests
here in one piece if it's like a new
automata thing where you know you can't
do any side quests anymore after that
point
oh
not too often why is still bumming
around these parts oh I'm just checking
out side quests
you can you can uh-huh okay I know I
said you were welcome to come back here
when you need a rest but this is a bit
soon forward you wanna end don't you
think yes
now that you mentioned it it kind of
does look like I'm taking a little too
easy to be honest I'm feeling a little
lost with what to do right now all right
that's not true alphan we know what
we're gonna do today
well in that case why don't you help me
out a bit there's always so much to do
out here there's no time to worry about
things for instance I'm running low on
pepper you want pepper okay okay what
you need
take it oh recipe are we getting a new
recipe
how is this
give up thanks oh
hip-hop oh two live bottles thanks dude
can't be got you covered
thank you oh no I had to give one life
bottle back
quiet
still eating she's enjoying that K-pop
man
she loves that K-pop
you guys have ever have you guys ever
eaten a K-pop
you know
where am I going oh there's so many
quests here there's so many here
oh dear
a lot of it yes yes yes yes nope nope
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes most
people say yeah
[Music]
foreign
I'm going here
Mazda
foreign
[Music]
looking that way
confusing
oh it's such a nostalgic area
oh where am I going oh there's a quest
over there and know who it'll apparently
somebody's asking for help ah
why
um
you cannot get all the owls until after
the cutoff point oh okay
then is there a problem sir
um
shooting stuff
we mustn't ignore this dohalem dwelling
what's your camera cute cute
forget not we shall investigate we now
urge everyone to avoid the area until
we're certain this situation
thank you dohalem
this is difficult this Quest is for
later oh okay Spirit Temple
Temple
it'd be bad news if this had
something to do with that wedge business
why here
wait so oh my God there's so many quests
here too
[Music]
enemies on level 60
. wow yeah I'm not ready for that
I'm not ready for that I could possibly
be out here we'll find out for ourselves
whether it's coincidence or something
more Wayne's don't cry I think I feel
like somebody's watching
who who's watching us Hulu hmm
what's wrong
farming equipment is all ruined battles
he's got them circles every time yeah
leave it to me
is this also level 60 Quest
hope I hope not
look I heard it I heard chicken
s just go after anything that looks
remotely like farm equipment it's me
let's just focus on ensuring they don't
make you also have a quest by the way
hmm oh she had a Pikachu
hello
travels I'm not surprised right
you also have two big game hunter
okay
uh no we're gonna do the other one first
Okay so
girls
white and bright circles everywhere
don't go
and
wait
I am in the
huh I can't open the map wait
I'm in the area I think salmon
yeah oh my God that's a a big area
okay but maybe somewhere in the middle
of that area
[Music]
um
across the bridge yes yes one second I
cannot ignore items like that water is
not going to hurt it
I literally cannot ignore it also um I
want to change something here
he
wait no wait no no no no that's not what
I wanted to do oopsie
and
this is what I wanted to do oh God look
at my
[Music]
kid oh God
I don't know
Hawaii
cute oh cute butt
that she's so pretty yeah
no
are you the snuggles
don't don't the characters usually say
something when they meet the target from
the quest or do I need to fight all of
them here
we should be able to cook here I don't
want to cook here
what about you
they do right yeah gotta break through
anyway we're fighting this dude
weak point please
oh that was fast
so that was not it
clay fragment free more
la la
[Music]
oopsie
hmm
ah
that's the other Quest right yeah yeah
okay hmm well let's go there and then
maybe on the way up
oh what do I see over there is that the
Big Game Hunter Quest
he looks wrong thing right it's yourself
can I am I strong enough for this dude
foreign
[Music]
well then let's go
let's take care of him so that the
grandma grandma lady is happy again
oh
shape
yes go for the weak point indeed which
is here
as impressive as always uh seven if you
had like seventy thousand no and you're
even better than ever
calm down don't jump around so much it
will only make it hurt more actually
down
oh you missed you missed train well
[Music]
ready for the turducking collaboration
tomorrow
I wonder how that will go
[Music]
oh nice
finito
been looking forward to it all week
thank you
that was way stronger
to hear that you won't hear me
complaining
I wonder if we can use this of course we
can use it what do you mean it's money
there's the zugal we were asked to
handle ah these ones
these ones
okay that is very close very close to
the other Quest
s
okay
I think after this side quest we will go
back to the main quest
um because we gotta get somewhere today
right
we gotta get somewhere
uh uh wait is this it's too easy oh wait
the question is not done you can stand
against us there's more every battle
went so well what about these these ones
are okay
okay
uh what about these I ran past them
already like the zugal we were told
about ah
all of those in that shape okay
just the floating ones it seems
the
stuff
you and I both too easy
main quest yeah was that a new skill I
saw back I need to kill eight of them
on the side eight Generations there's
two more maybe you can just write all
this
I'll get level 19 dear God I feel like
I'm slaughtering them
I almost feel bad
I can see you so what a mistake in the
cold and release for the grenade and
just dump it right in front of yourself
yeah I can see that happening too
uh so these these two quests uh I am
done with
um
did you guys decide which warmth yeah
the one that's good
oopsie wmd where did I go where did I go
go back go back
really that worried about us winning oh
it's my farm
wow those horses look gorgeous
I mean they kind of look like cows but
wow oh they are ripped
oh my
okay sound fine
a little compassion oh my God the pigs
are so cute because we speak to them
what oh is there a problem sir
could you pick it's from the tailor ah
in town okay
oh we're not doing it are we doing it we
are doing it
and yes we're doing it
anything for you sir
all right
such good care look at those what
Casper clothes
talking about I want to help
out on a date okay
the kids
oh my God
wait there's another one here though oh
you better not come back got it oh he
ran right into the Trap oh no all the
cats are too focused on the other one oh
where oh oh wait can I actually take
care of the mouse problem by myself
because he's running out of my farm oh
there we go
oh
so if my pets are not doing a good job I
can do it myself
that's funny
so actually going to the farm is a
little bit better than remote control
huh oh no life bottles
give me a different reward please
I already have full inventory of Life
bottles yeah you did it yeah I did do it
getting rusty done oh well
oh well rats would run at you it really
rats would attack me I'm not so sure
about that
then if by that logic Casper was a
milestone because Casper didn't attack
me
he just
was there and was scaring me
rats are actually aggressive when hungry
that's a brave New York ratswood
really
we killed it we killed the thing 5700
that's not bad
oh
oh hello worth it doing those side
quests
regenerate
oh hello
not bad
reduce art casting time during combos
hell yeah
seven goal
what does this do Elemental defense
let's just do it I can fill it up
you're Healing Art yay
new Healing Art is always good what do
we have up here by the way increase down
damage
let's say Dad I'll take anything
two thousand points
[Music]
let's try to finish
um
the defense one
slack assault okay
um oops
this is useful for everyone okay
I didn't look at everyone but whatever
we are going to the main quest guys
wherever it is
here you
uh where are we going where is where is
the main quest
here
I don't know where are we going Suzuki
sakiara
you came running time yes you did uh the
wedge find the ship that's the main
quest why am I supposed to find a ship
where am I supposed to find a ship
they must be joking
ah here
okay
[Music]
well
always good to be back in familiar
territory I don't know about you guys
but I think I have a I have a feeling
that this is what's going on around here
yeah there might be someone who could
use our help you
do you want my help
[Music]
what do you want SpongeBob
all right you did it what is it
skybound swarm
okay not now though
um later main quest priority right now
unless I'm on the level then I might do
some if I notice that I'm on the level
then I might do some side quests
dude can you give me that ship
can I have please
ago
uh
please give me [\h__\h] the Blazing Sword
and his Merry Christmas
[Music]
of course I am if you land lovers can
make it out of that sinking ship alive
ain't no reason an old Sea Dog like me
wouldn't too oh nice sing you alive but
that wave hit hard
I'm glad to see you're okay
sorry we put you in so much danger back
there look at kisan looking so good on
that black armor oh my God you helped
make one of my life's dreams come true
the ship on the other hand she took a
bit of a beating though I'll admit
really what happened to it he looks fine
to me on the outside
she's fine now she was in rough shape
when I made it back here engine chamber
gave up the ghost without a lot of do we
need to repair the [\h__\h] to talk to the
head honcho what do you need things and
see if he could help us I have it all
and wouldn't you know it crazy fool sent
over running Engineers to help can you
believe it
renin
yep said they came from menacea they
were real professionals did what they
needed to and didn't give me Guff or
anything I was damn near floored
so they did the work themselves good on
them well they did a bang-up job because
she's better than ever now oh speaking
of which
can she go to space yes we need to get
out on the ocean and fast when can we
set sail
all right little lady I'm a man of the
sea I'll gladly help hop aboard folks
okay
[Music]
sorry I I looked up my memo for my
stories oh Idol motion
are you okay you ready to go
all aboard
foreign
[Music]
talking points memo
oh oh yeah
we have arrived already oh my God
oh wow let's see sparkly this thing
already looked plenty huge from afar
it's seeing it up close makes it really
hit home
I didn't expect the journey to go so
smoothly I figured the Runnings would
send something to sink us this will sink
us don't worry maybe they didn't think
we had the nerve to come
somehow I kind of doubt that
it's entirely possible they don't see us
as a threat
what do you mean
that they think they're beyond our reach
still this structure is quite the
unusual sight truth be told never seen
anything like it you're right
it doesn't look like the buildings on
lanigas at all or like any renin
structure for that matter no
it's weird it doesn't feel like the kind
of thing that has people inside either
yeah it's definitely something creepy
what the hell is it even made of
I don't know
it's not mechanical or biological but
it's definitely alive in some way
it looks like she on sports
are you okay run well
oh
is she on
I'm okay
it's nothing
um
well what do we do now we go in
we have to stop this thing
[Music]
that means finding the core and smashing
it to bits
okay but look at the size of it I don't
know if we'll find the core just
wandering around
good point can anyone get a read on the
astral energy around us any kind of a
sign
there's a rather enormous flow of energy
moving directly upwards oh if we wish to
follow it we'll have to do some climbing
what
renwell
renewal are you well are you over there
are you doing when well are you doing
well hey what's up with you
she hypnotized huh I
you okay what happened
written unwell I'm not sure
when I was reaching out to the astral
energy I thought I heard a voice
oh a voice
yeah
I couldn't make out any words but it
sounded like it wanted me to come to it
oh no don't follow it
it's a trap this seems like a trap right
it's not a trap it is a trap
listen I don't know why but when it
spoke to me I knew it wasn't hostile
they always act like that
and what do you think
it could well be a trap
it's also our only real option short of
wandering aimlessly about
you think renwell can run well
let's trust Rin well on this
are you sure
yeah you have a new favorite tails off
game oh
alternative I guess
that's good to know
what did I say sheesh it's like walking
on eggshells around here yo same at kfp
honestly means you have to choose your
words more carefully law you got to get
used to it huh oh right
attuned mage
okay no more Attack
One More normal okay
uh-huh
uh since we're back here let's get some
more points oh this one is almost
finished this gives me Elemental defense
plus 20. okay
and
what is this
uh-huh
resistance plus 20. why not let's get
this new scale oh
and I I read speed
spread okay beginner water art you come
at me with this now
spread is like cider skill
1800 left oh we could finish this what
is this the penetration
we could also finish this penetration
also increase Special ammo
increase the amount of damage dealt by
one of Shin's bombs when shot with the
last Patrol
I hope I hope the NPC Shield is smart
enough to make use of that
um
okay good skills Shion it's kind of
noises things should calm down a little
once we're through with this yeah
optimistic as always
it's so pretty
it really is pretty
cool
oh
my God
I wanna I wanna look around everything's
so pretty
wow
beautiful oh by the way can you like buy
items at the ship
is that a thing
or do you like have to go back to land
not as pretty as you
laughs
the eyes only problem is dodging obvious
AOE attacks oh
oh my
teleport as needed okay
wow
oh the wedge
oh looks very intricate looks like a
diamond that looks like to me it reminds
me of childhood movie uh the ant movie
was it dance I think it was ants
was it was it ants
I said ants
there were two of them bugs life yeah no
I mean Bug's Life I mean Bug's Life
[Laughter]
[Music]
if you know what I mean then you know
what I mean
I see that the interior of the wedge is
every bit as strange and unusual as the
exterior
intriguing if I didn't see it coming
golden magma I wouldn't believe it was
renin
what's with this place orange gel
yeah
whatever it's all for I'm stumped
what you what what were you stumped
stonked what did he say
stoked
oh way to go first so many choices oh
left and right
hello pretty
flies you stumped okay
let's fight
okay and I already will start telling
you about my location
because the first day doesn't really
count I guess oh no poison
um
so on that day we actually were planning
to do some hiking
but it was too cold
and it was raining pretty much the whole
day not not very strong rain but still
uh as I mentioned before I didn't really
who are you fighting with I didn't
really bring enough like proper
equipment for that
so we kind of have to cancel that
but I did have a massage at like uh 11
A.M so we had breakfast
and right after the breakfast I went to
get the uh went to get the massage but
by the way you know what was really cool
in this hotel
um every morning at the breakfast like
we would already have a reserved table I
have to do we would basically sit at the
same table
um each morning and each evening for
dinner and breakfast
and when you get to your table there was
always some kind of like paper like a
newspaper waiting for you
um I can get up there
oh
uh in which they wrote like the weather
and
um what's gonna be for dinner later
today
and
also
what activities you could do today
so not only like activities like outside
like uh go hiking go to this place go to
that place but also like activities from
the hotel
like a yoga lesson or I don't know any
kind of workout or whatever but talking
more doing and also activities for
children
so yeah they had a lot of programs
and it was really helpful for when you
go there and you you don't know what to
do
mine besides just chilling in the sauna
or chilling in the pool
that's not fun to do that the whole
freaking day right
I don't know it's kind of boring to just
be in the pool for the whole day like
what are you gonna do
besides swimming a couple of laughs
[Music]
I think yeah yeah that's it's over
I think on that day we didn't really
make use of any extra uh
activities
or did we I don't quite remember let me
see
chronological order
this ends now is there any sightseeing
spot around
um I I don't know I wouldn't say
sightseeing
like I don't know what I do with it the
Eiffel Tower for example no not really
um
but you can go skiing there it's a nice
skiing area just to my tastes personally
so anyway everyone okay
what is that thing
is that how I go outside
is this where I spawned what is that
well that's where I came from
um
maybe for later a portal anyway my
massage was uh the the second massage I
had on that trip I had three I think
three massages
okay it was the worst massage that I had
on that uh trip it wasn't like super bad
but it was just nothing
is too special and I just threw out the
whole massage I couldn't really you
don't miss calm down or relax that much
either
but did I already tell you this yeah
yeah the the one where they offer you
like different kinds of
um
smells from the forest
life burst sport radiant like three
different uh
yeah
I
it was all right
um
and then and then after that I just went
swimming and I met up with my BFF again
we went swimming and we went to Johnson
and again you know the fake Onsen
and then we ate some strudel again oh
Dana's astral energy
are you saying the renings are funneling
it through here to send to lennogus sure
looks like it we have to put a stop to
it wow
wow
ow can I go up here oh I can
uh yeah and on that day again they had a
different struggle they always had an
apple strudel but always an extra stool
as well
so yummy good lunch
hot pepper no hot pool water even worse
but it was it was so nice
I want some struggle me too
wait a second
oh yeah and then it was already time for
yoga oh my God we really filled up our
stomachs right before yoga
and
um yeah we quickly uh
walked over to the area where we would
have yoga
and we changed into our yoga clothes
yoga
this will be a delicious
I mean it wasn't a big issue because
this was just like a beginners
amateur class
so no problem here
um
uh I have to say
I don't know if it's
the same with every yoga instructor
slash yoga class
ES
maybe it's because I'm too serious or
too stressed out or so but I hope that
was impressed a big part of me better
than ever my fists are crushing it out
there couldn't really enjoy it that much
like it should be among creatures you'd
find in a forest cut it out I don't need
to hear that it's got to be man-made
right or it's so it would not be any
easier to predict remain vigilant
they talk so much oh my God and I
couldn't I couldn't enjoy that much
because
um I I was just
taking it too serious Maybe
and like the instructor was saying stuff
like you know and and now like we were
just sitting and he was like now you try
to feel the way your legs
are touching the ground
now try to feel the way your feet
okay it was not all the time that we did
some like like moves as well
but that's kind of talking
I don't think one's gone take it
seriously yeah
it just seems so it feels so stupid to
me I'm sorry but
[Music]
doesn't work for me either
um I don't blame you okay
I I wish I was one of those people who
can like connect with trees and with the
nature and be like be like I am a tree I
have grown out of the earth I am I am
Mother Nature's Child
but I am not I can't
I'm sorry I'm sorry fauna
so I just wonder if that's the same with
like every yoga or no choice if that's
just
isn't that kind of this the style of
yoga the meditation like you know you
feel this and that you feel your body
blah blah blah
[Music]
it's normal I feel like it's normal
yeah I would imagine it's mostly like
that I mean of course every instructor
has a little bit of a different style
but I I can see how this is just a
normal yoga thing
like
um
[Music]
I don't know maybe less talking and more
posing Natural Energy huh
a perfect combination the whole like
workout workout part if you can call it
workout was more of my liking you know
like doing those weird poses we did like
that morning reading
or the sun greeting I don't know what
it's called in English there's sun and
clues
um
it's fine and all is there yoga without
talking
is is there that type of yoga
is
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
you've been snaring to me
salutation a lot of people also do a
form of yoga dedicated to exercise
[Music]
um
okay that's a wasted Mystic art
I didn't see that there's a lot of
different types of Yoga and there's like
the ones that make you really work out a
lot
foreign
but that's also not really what I'm
looking for
me I think like what I'm what I was
hoping for was just a chance to chill
and
um at the same time stretch my body you
know get a little bit more
um
Mobility
I can feel my Precision improving but
that that talk of you feel this and that
it's just just it just died if only I
were a cat
it just doesn't come through to me
um maybe I need to do it a few more
times and then I'll be brainwashed or
something
I don't know
that's just physiotherapy yeah maybe
that's more my thing I don't know
Tanto yoga is just pretentious
stretching
hmm
gym workout
um
don't you want to be M tree no
I don't want to be the tree
there's a good app called headspace does
that kind of yoga I've heard about that
in in a YouTuber
um talking about their sponsors today's
stream is sponsored by headspace no it's
not though it's not though by the way
this stream is not sponsored by
headspace
don't quote me on that I was quoting
someone else that was a quote that was
literally a quote
[Laughter]
yeah but what was that again like do you
just like try to think what is headspace
what is that
this place definitely isn't easy enough
and I doubt this structure was conceived
with the ease of people's movement in
mind
you've been saying nothing but zugong
nests
it's almost as if we're inside guided
meditation vessel of some sort
spirit I just feel like meditation is
just not not my thing maybe
I I can give it one more try I I would I
would be okay with that
if that's the case and that would make
lennogus the Master Core that's
receiving all the astral energy okay
let's focus on the story hey Emma how
about that voice again
in her furthering we go
the stronger the voice gets never mind
we're going the right way I take it back
where's this voice
yeah don't move me I hear it inside me
but I feel like it's also coming from
every direction around us oh my God he's
so cute
surrounding huh
considering astral energy is involved
it's not that unusual
right but it's not scary or anything
what are you doing
if you think so just promise you'll say
something if the voice gets too clingy
are you jealous at the voice that she's
hearing
thank you for using your message
like that
anymore
I can carve through armor
um but anyway
um by the end of the yoga lesson feel
like at least
um it's good that I did it
was good that I tried it
and it was included in the whole package
so it was free so what the hell it
wasn't even a waste
it was an experience
that was okay
it was okay
hold up is valuable
check it out
baby baby baby
[Music]
foreign
that's Froggy by the way
what do we have here
stamina ring Arena may have the AG class
of an art when cast building especially
lucky casters unleash powerful Arts with
Reckless abandon
I found some equipment
should we give that to rain well
wait
equipment
what was the other thing that we found
before that
where is it here it is
I'm just gonna go with it
why not
how has your week been oh
oh how has my week been
um interesting normal as per usual
you have an armor for Donald thank you
sure
was it this no
are you sure
and I found an hour for someone else
no
the flare one was cute and that one was
wasn't even planned that was spontaneous
but it was so fun to talk to Freya
because like it felt like
like she was so excited
and you know she's just so it's just a
pleasant
um conversation to have when the other
party of the conversation
feels like or gets this feeling across
that she genuinely enjoys talking to you
so I was I don't know I felt really good
after that
spontaneous collaboration
like she'll she was always so
what I was showing her in Minecraft and
when she was so so sweet to me
she was so fun to talk to us
should have talked to her much much
earlier already marks ago
yeah no surprise me and polka do so much
together
is really really Pleasant to be around
so once again it has proved to me that
first gen is the strongest dreams
Do It win well everyone from the Virgin
is based as spoke
there's literally only base girls in the
future
foreign
[Music]
Studio
you don't mess around
for Gen best really excited for the
concert oh man
I have no idea
talk to her I mean I have talked kind of
with her before right like during that
for example during the the
um New Year's uh events that we have
like with takamori and foreign
we were at least like having a little
tiny
interaction there this one
this one nothing too big but still
um but besides that yeah and that was
way stronger than regular let's interact
more well you won't understand by two
hmm
what's inside
we're back we're babbling wait what does
it do
nothing
[Music]
a ring that may revive the wearer from a
KO there was once a whole Squad famous
for wearing these Rings known as the
undead Legion
etto
are all wearing that that ring because
they are married to Lucia and therefore
they at least don't die
is that is that what you're trying to
tell me
ah
the bandits and
[Music]
um
I'll never ring like that I don't need a
ring like that and besides that like for
real in the game I don't think we need
to use that one because
uh
every one of my party members has that
KO prevention
yes okay
let's fight this dude
thank you let's dispose of the trash
oh yeah
I wrote down some feelings that I had
about it it was a bit exhaust I I was
nervous first of all
I was very nervous but it was okay
stand back
whatever throw it at him I don't care
this thing is strong I was nervous but
it was okay and uh it was a bit
exhausting and I didn't know if I was
doing things correctly sometimes but I
feel more uh confident to go alone to
another yoga session in the future
but on hindsight I don't know
I I do feel like it's not really my
thing
but I wouldn't mind going again that was
my conclusion
[Music]
did I tell you about the slide I already
told you about the slide right yeah
that's that's uh
we did quickly use the oh
the 17 meter long slide which I was
really freaking on about the freaking
out about
one deal here's a Healing Art but it was
fun I felt like a child again
now I want to go to one of those
um
your Parks thingies where there's like
oh like a lot of
those kind of
slides
when I feel like a child again
[Music]
uh probably but I wouldn't be able to
chicken out for too long because if I
would go to an actual water park I'm
sure that there would be
children all around
and if I were to stand like right at the
um you know edge of the slide
and hesitate the children would look at
me and be like that adult Phoenix lady
is chickening out because of a
child slide oh my God how embarrassing
like in this case there was no such
pressure because me and my BFF were
basically the only ones using it at that
moment and I was always alone at the top
and had time to you know
get into my headspace haha
and think about what was going to happen
contemplate whether or not I want to
risk my life going down that 70 meters
line
uh
the screams yeah I'll have to hold back
my screams as well
if I'm gonna go to a water park a public
one
nah
no I do think they would think about it
because children are ruthless have you
forgotten how ruthless children are if
they see
like they ran up those slides they run
up those stairs and they're like go
again go again now I'm gonna go do a
trick and now I'm gonna lay on my
stomach and now I'm gonna do this and
that and this and that
and and if they see an adult being like
give me a moment I can't go yet
sorry sorry I need a moment I need a
moment
you honestly think that they wouldn't be
like
hair
chicken
come on think about it think about it
I think it's pretty obvious
they are evil
they are oh yeah
wait have I already been to Spyro one is
that the
ah okay okay I see that's the portal to
go back to the beginning
okay
an opponent like this should be easy
come and face
it's drunk in advance wait isn't it
usually
um isn't that usually not allowed
I feel like there might have been signs
that say don't don't use while being
drunk I mean what's gonna happen right
but still
isn't that like a general rule that
these water parks have
I don't know
usually right
also I don't drink alcohol
problems
we have a problem here
go prepare to crumble you'll drown oh
yeah maybe that maybe that does happen I
don't know I've never been drunk before
foreign
[Music]
guys make me laugh with that every time
man I think I'm getting stronger I'm
proud of that title oh money
a lot of money
yeah
okay so I think we go through here
moving on
always don't forget to hydrate
where are we
uh-huh
spy will uh what spiral free lower level
okay
they need to do something about their
plants here right here they're going
Rampage
rescued that one plant did I did I tell
you about my plants dying my pretty
plants did I tell you about that
rise in Phoenix
I'm ready
I did I did I think it's doing better
now
I gave it like my friends my BFF
recommended me to give it
um tea
yeah apparently that's the thing
I've tried to
um you know stop your life monitor is a
bit better
armor won't save you yeah teeth No I
gave it herbal tea
how much longer will our Healing Arts
last
um
Leafs
sure climbed up the wrong way haven't we
the plant is British no fencing in place
it would be quite hazardous to fall
ah we don't have fall damage in the game
have you not noticed so hollim do I need
to push you down so you notice
I can show you I mean I don't mind
no no no no no
so there you go
I told you I told you
that means
[Laughter]
okay what do we have here uh
looks like I can could go that way but I
can't
oh
can I what if I jump into that energy
will it warp me up I won't forgive you
Rising wipers
[Music]
thank you for reminding me I'm glad you
were thinking about the same thing you
don't mess around anyway off the side up
and slide it was already
um getting closer to the time of us
having to go to dinner
so right before the dinner we did
another quick dip into the sauna which
I'm personally
um surprised about myself
because if you remember on the day
before I was still kind of hesitant to
go
um and I'm just generally not the type
of person who you know likes going to
play places where people are naked
but the time when we went once again
right before dinner it was very very
empty so
oh
hi Uncle Joe it was very empty so
um I didn't feel that awkward anymore
yeah so it was it was uh relaxing a
little bit and hot very hot
no we didn't go to that view whirlpool
yeah I think we didn't we did not
we did not go to the whirlpool on that
day we only went on that day before I
think
oh my God
are you body conscious Kiara I don't
know how to answer that like I'm I I am
I'm sorry I don't necessarily think that
oh if we can't depend on one another
an unattractive body I think I probably
do have an attractive body wait I'm dead
[Music]
being around naked people
being naked myself because it's just
such a vulnerable state don't you think
let's talk anymore
showing yourself in your most vulnerable
poem
you missed and I need a hill but I don't
have CP
[Music]
m
subscribe
is the culture thing I don't think so
because like my mom was
someone who doesn't give a [\h__\h] at all
and she liked going to the sauna
everyone's still in one piece it's just
me
it's just me King leave us
oh there you go
anything else that's new that I missed
no
nice and tough
um
yeah okay but we went to the sauna again
and they had another like uh peeling
that was basically just salt
but I wrapped it over my arms and [\h__\h]
and my legs anyway and then I chilled in
the sauna the humid one first again and
then the other one that was
not as humid
very very
painful
but also kind of relaxing couldn't stand
too much time in there
but again once again it's one of those
experiences where I feel like well I'm
proud that I did it I'm proud that I got
over my you know
issues
and did something that I usually
wouldn't do
especially in a place where I paid for
all these things so might as well want
to make use of it
boom and proud
retreated
[Music]
foreign
come back it up
ER alert
foreign
[Music]
why is it so bloody whose blood is on
that coat
that is
you can't enter Finland of course
again
hey one of those saunas I went to no
wait actually no that was not the
finished sauna was the freaking hot one
right yeah uh I took one step into it
when no one was inside took a nice photo
not only of none of myself okay only of
the the whole sauna because it was so
big and it had a nice scenery
and then I and then I was like nope and
I left
[Music]
are you
yeah
I don't see anything
I'll burn it all
right
[Music]
gotta get used to it again
I wonder I I don't really have the the
time to look at how much damage
it's one of those Mystic art says but I
wonder which one is stronger probably
the new one
easily be fatal I'm gonna guess it's the
new one
just as well I'm here to stop it
won't save you they do have a lot of hpl
[Music]
no further
okay I'll give us some CP
a
oh man oh man
[Music]
prevent me behold the Earth whoa
tectonic fission wait is that a new one
there
okay
oh what the hell oh it's my turn
wait I'm not sure if I can do it this
time
turn it through
no
no that's the normal one okay
I didn't pay much attention this time
[Music]
oh my God
do you require
hey Pop blow them away will this help
yeah I don't use elephants loose attack
much I know it's because it scares me
you need to be careful
thrilling performance
I can carve through water
[Music]
because
of how it works
anyway
and another one okay we're using a lot
of money here
we are going that way
okay we're gonna open this up
these places also take up a lot of nice
CP but they give me good items how can I
say no
no it's itchy
what does it do restore CP each time to
wear it if he's an enemy Frontline
Fighters often wear it to supplement
other support that they receive
oh that's actually wait how much so how
much CP is that worth wearing
foreign
[Music]
one percent not worth it yeah one CP
U okay guys
yeah they are purifiers I don't know man
I mean there's only so much that an air
purifier can do you really think
you really think an air purifier is
gonna get rid of all the hairs in my
apartment
[Music]
um I always doubted that but I have all
three of them on I have one running in
my bedroom one huge one running in the
living room and one uh decent sized one
here in my office as well anyway let me
wash my nose
[Music]
foreign
okay
no
no no
[Music]
no
oh okay
[Music]
Papa
oh
oops I left the fridge open
up
come on
oh
[Music]
soft cat oh
quick bye bye
[Music]
I got you I got you you can't run away
hmm
oh baby
[Music]
[Laughter]
bye bye
I have cat hairs everywhere again
okay I'm good I'm good
I'm good
[Laughter]
she's so cute though
get in my weird sitting position because
today is a long stream and I don't give
a [\h__\h]
outside pineapple juice
I brought pineapple juice
according to Surah pineapple juice helps
with a fruit
[Music]
pineapple juice
how's the new chair I don't know
feels like a
like a chair
he's chair
I I do feel like I want to get that
um headrest though
you can buy that extra right I feel like
I want to get it
[Music]
you hunt I try not to hunch over too
much
I try I do try
um anyway I'm back
yeah I do want the headrest
um was I supposed to go in here
no I came from here okay
let's go
no no I'm not
oh you're just making a joke I was gonna
be like why would I donate the chair
that cost me so much money I'm not gonna
give it away but you're just saying
charity
oh my God
[Music]
dancing with the way
to me as impressive as always
[Applause]
nice
sick moves gross valuable as I think it
is
sick anyway back to my story
I'm so good at like making the story is
long as it can get
so we went to the sauna right and then
we quickly went back to a room and
quickly both took a shower and I think
we
uh with your stomach making all the
Ratchet
wait I ran out of the I want the EXP
buff again kind of
but if I go back here
uh
where can I
like there's there's this uh
uh
warp point right
where would that lead me
spiral free conduit
I hear
okay that's not that far away
maybe I should do that
I think I want to do that
yeah yeah cause I wanna I wanna go cook
again
wait I can go do it in the end as well
right
I'm nearing the top it's almost there
but I want the EXP
o yeah
let's do it okay so so so yeah yeah we
didn't have much time and we were really
kind of rushing the adventure we went on
uh
so uh
we were rushing
and I was asking if we could get like a
second
um
hair dryer because we only had one
and uh we both had red hair so in order
to save time wanted a second hair dryer
but the second hair dryer didn't come
until
uh we were already both done with using
the one hair dryer one after another
drying our hair so that was pretty
useless
made ourselves a little bit it pretty
and went to the to the dinner and once
again
the lady waitress oh my God such an
angel
I love her she was such a sweetheart
that was the last dinner by the way that
we had
so
um I was a bit sad that actually during
uh that uh dinner she wasn't serving us
that much it was like very mixed a lot
of different waiters and waitresses
we're serving us
simultaneously
[Music]
not only her so I felt a little bit
lonely I wanted her like every time she
was walking around but not coming to us
I was like trying to send her signals
like hey hey hey hey come over here come
come over to us I wanna I wanna chat
with you
she was busy
it was so busy
yeah
[Music]
at the end she did come though because
we were like the last ones uh left over
hmm we were the last ones in
uh for dinner because we were also the
last ones to come in the first place so
uh at the end like she was already
preparing for breakfast for the next day
like she was putting down the The
Cutlery
um
and then I was able to have a chit chat
with her
yeah and we talked we talked about a lot
of uh things like I I asked her like how
it is to like work those double shifts
you know and where she's from
and why she came to this place out of
all the places she could have gone to
um
no I did not try to get her number
no
why would I do that no no no no no no
it was nice having a nice conversation
you know
you could never be too
no wait I don't want to make accessories
after all do I I don't know do I want to
transfer skill
by sacrificing an accessory you can
track someone bonus skill to a different
accessory however this can only be done
if the accessory to be sacrificed has
reached its max level repeat this
process to forge the ultimate accessory
uh so this is when accessories get
useful
this is when they get useful wait how do
I how do I use it
I don't even use I don't know what to do
and I still don't know which one to make
Erica is a bunch of money okay
maybe maybe before the last boss
uh oh atonement Edge
yo that looks cool it's very slick and
slim
[Music]
let's make this one
nice upgrade
and oh
wow she has all those fancy guns
oh that one looks like a fish
oh that one looks that one fits her
current outfit
that one's the best one we can do
currently
let's do it
a craft in the clip
fish
oh we can make this one needs a
Nature's Beauty okay
that we came back we were able to do
some upgrades here
oh
oh thank you
okay have you guys checked your
equipment lately I did I did
I just literally just did
wouldn't you think I could sell some of
those
like the
I know the basic raffle probably don't
need that one anymore of a crafting
um
solid Edge look some of them are
probably not necessary anymore to keep
around
[Music]
this one maybe
and I want money I'm on the money guys
[Music]
sell the books probably
huh which ones
maybe the cheapest one
and maybe this one
yeah yeah yeah
oh and this on the sun probably too yeah
you're right you're right
oh
maybe this one wait what is it what is a
what does that mean when they have a
exclamation mark on the left side
I might regret this later you can fish
for money okay
but at least it would be on stream
they're new ah okay okay I will sell no
more Nigel will die trouble did I sleep
already no
[Music]
sleep and cook I will again make this
one
mmm good food is the best kind of magic
double
thank you
thank you for letting me sleep here it
was absolutely not comfortable
but that's all right let's go back
[Music]
are you cooking something next week
um
is next week the Halloween week I will
be cooking something
in the Halloween week which I think is
not next week
so the week after
holy wow her butt though oh my God she
she has quite the butt
the week after it okay well there you go
I was planning on doing like carving a
pumpkin
and also oh yeah I can't use it
did I not activate it is that the issue
[Music]
ah okay let's try to rush through
what was I just talking about
I wanted to carve a pumpkin and then
with the pumpkins I was thinking maybe
I'll make pumpkin soup
um
[Music]
yeah
certainly not
they have plans for the carbon
um I'm not 100 sure yet I was thinking
like I could try to make my own face or
I could try to um do like Kotori the
shape of Kotori
I'm not sure how many pumpkins I'm gonna
be buying and how many I'll be carving
um if it's more than one then I might do
you know Kotori and the other uh signs
from the myth members
you seem fairly simple
good I think hey move him away
yeah have you carved before no I haven't
but I asked my BFF about it because she
had experience with it I was like is it
difficult how do you do it
and uh supposedly it's not that
difficult
I hope so
yeah I need to do something simple
because this is my first time
[Music]
um
on your knees
commander of Heaven
absolutely divine
I'm excited for the pumpkin soup though
cause I love pumpkin soup with pumpkin
seed oil
um
that that oil that they put in Cube is
I think that's what they typically put
on top here in Australia
pumpkin seed oil take this
very expensive oil but I'm not gonna
make that oil myself
I'll be back in that separately
and
energy say no more
also guys I think I've mentioned this
before but I am putting out a song
I never missed
coming soon
consider yourself finished yay
[Music]
um currently still scratches in the
creation of the music video
and I also have not recorded the singing
yet
uh so
might still take a little bit but it
should be ready on time for Halloween
hey what do you say we fight that
no no no why would we fight that no no
no
I think we should though
shining enemy I guess what does those
shining ones what do they give me
against careless
special items
I'm totally fine
have you practiced
yes
all yours
[Music]
my mixer usually mixes my stuff in one
to two days
and the video is gonna be a simple one
the video creator
um only really needs two days as well
but we're giving her a bit more time
like a week
it's gonna be fine
recording studio might take time to book
it
I'm recording it at home
all all of my
um song covers are recorded at home
only even Sparks is recorded at home
only hinodorian heart challenge are
recorded were recorded in a studio
because I was in Japan at that time and
I was able to record it at the producers
Studio
but Sparks is recorded with this very
microphone in my home under my own
monitoring and control which I have to
say like I have a I have quite some
experience with uh you know recording in
studios and
um it just is very very different to
be in charge of like judging whether or
not this take is okay or you gotta
retake something or being controlled by
an actual producer
um who gives you really really clear and
really small
um detailed feedback
bro about
your uh
recordings
oh not again
should I fight him we get we're getting
exp at least no
I don't know I must sleep I don't want
to waste so many items again on him
thank you go man the spot of Beast
hunting anyone
yeah my CP and my items no thank you so
yeah
um like when I when I wake up a producer
he would give like very very very clear
instructions
there you go now the fast roll point is
that ah
like let's say
um
uh
goodbye singing let's say it as an
example although that one I recorded by
myself
uh or no let's let's go for let's go for
uh hinotori
um give me a line from hinatoli I can't
remember brain empty
uh
give me one line from hirotori come on
come on come on come on come on
uh uh
no further
[Music]
tell me I can hear it clearly tell me
happy birthday to you
okay so let's say I don't remember the
lyrics right now because brain empty no
further
where it goes like
[Music]
the producer look what I just found
would take that one line apart in like
five different parts
and be like
this part can you sing that a little bit
clearer or
[Music]
here there there he would be like yo can
you can you uh uh and I'll put more
aggressive feeling in there or whatever
so it's very very professional
and to be honest with spikes because I
had to record it at home
there were no such instructions
and I had to like judge it myself mostly
I offered to like re-record anything
obviously if necessary
but it's just such a different process
and
I would if I could choose I would always
choose to record it with the producer on
site
listening in a Flawless victory
um
they just have an ear for it and I mean
I have a need for it too I would say a
little bit but I'm judging my own voice
by myself
um it's just not always the smartest
thing to do
[Music]
if only every battle went so well I hear
it uh sound crackling sound one second
there we go
oh
okay
so where are we we're going to the upper
level right
foreign
that's a chest over that I already
opened right okay
this box is so good thank you
stream homemade spikes
yeah thank you thank you thank you
and also like not only the the producer
helping out with like
like telling you what line was good and
what line was bad but also just they
would use a different
um program to record and a different
microphone that's like suits your voice
producers usually have like several
microphones to use
more than just one
and a better surrounding for recording
like soundproof move that has uh that
acoustically is
um
wait what's the word this one's got
two ashes a merry distraction
what's the win uh I'm looking for
acoustically
um
no I don't mean I don't mean isolated
away the better you and I both
wait what was the word again say in
German I don't even know in German uh
uh I forgot
forgot
you don't get out of here not you two
again now can we talk
[Music]
and not looking they're not looking
okay
no no no no no no no wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait no no please
[Music]
stay away from them
looks like you came to my rescue again
demo
foreign
okay let's go spiral four level lower
level
wait did I just go no this is correct
okay okay we're back to where we left
off before
okay are we closer to the top I wonder
balance suited uh
optimize optimize that's what I meant
acoustically optimized
with what I sent him just fine
and in the future I think for future
covers and original songs I will have to
continue working like that
it's just I don't have a choice
yeah unfortunately
also in the future when like even even
if I could go to Japan if I choose to
work with producers who don't live in
Japan then I guess I'll still have to
um to have to
record it at home
howling
this could be useful
here's what it is at least it's comfy
and I don't have to go outside for it
and I can just record in my pajamas at
whatever time I wish to do so
um
foreign
getting a new microphone and found a
chance soundtensity I did get a sound
canceling padding when I moved in here
that was so shitty crappy material
then I will be giving all of it to my
mom she was like don't throw it away I'm
gonna use that for
um
uh
padding her floor
um it's warmer
isolation
welcome seems about right to me
yeah because we did um
like promised her a floor I don't know
if she already got to it to ordering it
um but
she wants to like underneath she wants
to use my soundproof pads to uh
well Pat it out
instead of me throwing it away which is
good so I don't have to waste it
and but yeah regarding upgrades like I I
was spanking for a while like right here
it goes I wouldn't mind looking into
upgrades
regarding a microphone
I do like my current microphone and it
was very expensive it is one of the
very good microphones that has a great
reputation and a lot of people use it
so I just
I wouldn't even know which other
microphone to try
I've never seen
um
commander of Heaven Phoenix Cyclone I
wouldn't know which one
but at some point I'll probably look
into it
stand back do not trip it up
not right now though I'm so very happy
with my microphone
this ends now consider yourself finished
yeah I love the podcast sound that it
has
[Music]
again it's very thank goodness we want
it feels very calming to me
[Music]
oh dear
foreign
they're protecting something
my nose is itchy again
thank you Mike sounds nice I'm no
experienced me neither but see I feel
like generally there's no issue with my
microphone I'm happy with it
I feel like no matter what
microphone I would get there's always
gonna be some how to call these people
odd audio files
foreign
would have no problem with any of it
because they don't hear the same issues
that you hear
yeah
I'll leave it to you and
um to be honest I trusted myself
in a bind
you're mine yes
the sm7
is pretty much three more standards not
only for streamers but also for like
professional radios
podcasts
I know that a lot of people use it for
radio programs
yeah however what I do see possible here
is using buying and using whoa
buying and using a different microphone
for you know singing for maybe padoka's
dreams
and for recording stuff that makes sense
to me
we work well together
song
he knows my voice and he knows a lot of
other microphones
you know the guy who made hinodorian
High Challenger and recorded it
maybe I'll ask him
he has a recommendation
[Music]
oh God
Michael
redwell's right
fall back to regroup and try again later
what the hell no I literally just fell
back and came back here no
no I refuse
um
wait no I could just
yeah
let's do that that's good
build your own home studio
oh wait we've already reached out why
did I just heal myself
but it gives me back CP right
hold on
ah
okay okay wait boss is coming boss of
this dungeon I think I need to go to an
idol meeting and wash my nose once more
uh
[Music]
um
I don't know
I don't mean
oh stretch
okay I'll be our Bean
oh my God I'm excited who is gonna
there's gonna be story and cutscenes I'm
excited I wonder who's gonna be awaiting
us
please stay here so we will find out
together yeah
[Music]
foreign
I ran by chonkers but this time I did
resist the fluffiness
okay that's illegal I know
arrest me officer good
okay
let's do this
uh wait
is this gonna be a difficult one
it's just gonna be a difficult one
raise his attack
I got so much attack like I should give
someone else the attack
um knock
Elemental defense
I don't know you
my throat already hurts I gotta tickle
oh thingy
a thingy
later on
does everyone have the best equipment
it seems so
foreign
[Music]
okay
what a waitress
behind this
door
slash Behind These Walls
we'll find out
now
a hoodle why there has been no hooli at
all which I guess makes sense because
why the frick would a hood will be here
in this new place
oh
it's alive
it looks like a face here
it's here
yes
all the energy flowing through the wedge
comes together and collects here
is that thing a zugal
holy crap it's huge a central core and a
guardian
once we beat that thing it'll stop the
wedge from taking in any more astral
energy right
it seems we're into a fight regardless
[Music]
oh no poison too stay sharp everyone is
that gonna be poisonous adventure oh no
is there well okay
tentacles tentacles tentacles tentacles
yeah
I don't know if that's a machine or what
but I do know it's pissing me off
pissing me off as well no knowing what
it is oh no that's poisonous
annihilation
[Music]
take this
oh yeah okay no take this
oh my God oh my God do they have shared
HP
now you see what I can do I don't know
what's going on
when it's like in the air because it
feels like I'm not hitting it but I
still apparently am hitting it but it
just feels like I'm not
no
more
hitting it though a lot of the times
oh my God I was almost hit by that
wait did we kill one because there's
only I think there's only three left
praise
yeah six
[Music]
HP Labs
what the hell man where are you
not fair
come down
can I even hit the kids yeah like yeah
feels like I miss a lot though
he's just fighting air or something
like a doll like what is he doing
now you see what I can do
oh my God
Crystal can't get out of this okay here
I go yeah we're fine how many
oh we killed another one okay okay okay
okay
I guess it'll be halfway through if we
kill all the tentacles and then it's
gonna regrow or something
go get it
you're wrong
[Music]
not the game today but the playthrough
because there's a kind of point where I
have to stop screaming which is very
much in the late game but not at the end
of the game
well that doesn't look good
[Music]
it looks like you came tomorrow
thank you
still looking very very good though
[Music]
okay okay okay cleaning up a little bit
why are you guys having so many
compensation
[Music]
[\h__\h] work
s
oh my God oh my God
oh my god oh wait I'm attacking the
middle right now thanks
oh I kind of want to attack the tentacle
dog oh no tentacles is dead no more
tentacles
okay
what's that
what is that okay I'm ready
that was not so difficult I suppose
there's a follow-up mom
um
was Daniel
over was this still because someone said
I had like
um
what two or three dungeons left
two short ones one long one was this the
long one well was this the short one
what's going on
this was a short this was the long one
oh okay then I have two shorts okay nice
easy
don't walk towards the light guys that's
all I can say
are you not listening to me
right well no
this is not a good idea right this is
not gonna go well
ah run well
written well
ring well
exactly is
she
but that little is fake
oh it rain well boy
did we jump into it as well
we did didn't we
oh no
[Music]
we died
Dan we're dying guys get your [\h__\h] back
together get yourself
such a fantastic and beautiful bgm but I
don't trust it
[Music]
even
are you okay
hey are you crying
I'm not the only one
what do you mean
whatever it was I heard it
everyone's crying
yes did I
I'm not sure I call it a voice but it
was there
why the world just happened oh no
that was Dana's astral energy we just
encountered
and I think what we heard
might have been its voice
you're saying astral energy has a mind
of its own
having the slightest idea
but do you remember what happened when
we fought balssef back in calaglia no
you mean when that fire monster came out
of the spirit vessel I don't remember
exactly there was such a huge overflow
of Astral energy it caused a monster to
spawn and take physical
thing happened here just with way more
astral energy and a bigger monster
does that mean if you gather enough
astral energy it can become sentient or
take a physical form
that's what I'm guessing but it's just
speculation Master cores are able to
hold a lot more energy than a spirit
vessel but we still haven't seen
anything like that happen in our
dealings with them
that being said there may be a mechanism
of sorts inside Master cores and spirit
vessels that prevent such reactions
fire monster
I remember how it only appeared after
balls have Spirit vessel broke
then the reason rinwell was able to
sense all that astral energy earlier
must have been because it was too much
for that zugal to contain by itself
so then where do you think the zoogle
went
all that energy and poof it's gone the
zoo go with it doesn't that sound weird
to anyone
indeed it does however in order for us
to move our hypothesis forward we will
need to gather more evidence first on
that note how are you holding up for him
well
I just can't work out why
why the voice reached out to me first
moving well
I can't help but wonder if it's because
of my Heritage that I was the one to
hear it
hmm sorry that's a strange thing to
think isn't it anyway we should get
going right we need to make sure the
energy flow has actually stopped
um
Invasion classes averted are we gonna
have to take this winding path all the
way back down yeah but if anything it
should be easier than the climate just
jump
really well then actually I've heard
it's easier to develop muscle aches when
going down seriously
have we snacking on something and it
came back to me trying to kill me and
take my life
but I didn't let it take my life I won't
let it take my life now
everything all right it kind of looked
like you wanted to get something off
your chest
uh-huh oh um
or not you know whatever
yeah
um you know
yeah sorry never mind just forget it
I want to try being a little less
cryptic maybe
all right all right geez sorry for
taking an interest
sorry I guess
put it into words
that's fine no rush it might help you to
talk about it though
I'll keep that in mind and thanks
now okay
okay
I'm okay
I think we have an emergency
[Applause]
wait can I just teleport out
can I change no
the batteries for the whole game I've
had an issue with you know no problem
with the game but it's just a streamer
problem
um
audio balancing I'm trying balance it so
many times now
Memphis
where are you going I cannot teleport
out okay that's fine
[Music]
thank you for pushing me to play this oh
you are more than welcome my friends
I am just here to give you guys
good games
no no that's the old one damn it
wrong
speakers yeah probably
I've been listening to it and with my
headphones from beginning to end so good
I don't know I guess a lot of you guys
are listening with speakers
which one is it headphones or speakers
using headphones so short order
headphones oh a lot of headphones
almost only headphones
no limits no this is your limit you're
like at 1hp
through
speakers headphones
foreign
[Music]
or if I play games anything besides
streaming I usually prefer to do it with
speakers
because
um like when you wear headphones I can
feel my Precision for like eight hours
or so per day you know streaming I just
don't like the weight on my head
constantly not saying that my headphones
feel that heavy
to me there they are really comfortable
weight but still like I prefer to be
freed from that
when I can be freed from it
should I fight you okay
yeah so whenever I don't stream on it I
don't want to wear my headphones if
possible
it feels better to me feel more free
noodle neck
this one's mine
[Applause]
in here that's why I have earphones see
that that I also don't like because
that's I just don't like the audio
quality too much and I don't have that I
don't like something sticking inside my
ears
that feels even worse to me
foreign
[Music]
tonight nine when I need to buy new
earphones because I lost the ones
that I used for like my my Nintendo
switch or my
um
PlayStation Vita I only have the ones
that work with my Android but you stick
it into the part where you also load the
phone
so those earphones only work with that
the cable
only sticks in there where did you know
what's good for you yeah
that generally is such a stupid idea in
my opinion but I guess
whoever created that phone model was
like yo people should start using
Bluetooth
earplugs but I don't like those
those I don't know look you little stuff
and Bluetooth sometimes I don't know
just work for me and you lose them and
you lose them
no I prefer the ones of cable
Australia
[Music]
I pity anyone who stands in our way
foreign
[Music]
that was a freaking Banger guys
presented to you by yours truly
takanasukiara
smile ages
um
[Applause]
air pressure
[Music]
oh good song
good song
oh man smilings just wait a good days
those were those good days I I remember
I remember I was at this um concert that
they had in Japan in like odaiba
um they had a concert and then a
handshake event outside it was the
outside venue not very big oh my God
[Music]
the second or third row or something I
was so far in the front not very center
I was a little bit off center but still
it was very close and I got a I got a
good look at my Oshi looks like you came
to my rescue again and I was looking I
was looking really ridiculous but I was
proud of it
because I had my my Oshi t-shirts and I
had a picture of my Oshie pinned onto my
chest
Scarlet Inferno I was [\h__\h] proud of
myself okay and I looked cute I looked
cute among all of those
um
you know honestly though that I feel so
so comfortable among my peers who no you
are all into the same group and all just
want to do
it's not in your dreams guess with a
safety pin yes forgive me that's exactly
how I pinned that picture onto my
t-shirt yes
[Laughter]
anyway so after that concert I lined up
for the handshake event I don't know if
I ever told the story but this is one of
my biggest accomplishments in life okay
it's too much
um
uh I went I think it was before I even
went like when I was just waiting in
line
um I was walking past the members they
had four members
she was my oti and Canyon is like my
second Ochi
is not active as an idol anymore Camion
is but in a different group
um so I walk past them I think I was
about to line up for the handshake again
see we're like oh yeah I can handle it
obviously they said piano yes yes this
was uh like
seven years ago or something like that
no further
[Applause]
this is really really [\h__\h] special
because you can't imagine how many
[\h__\h] fans they have
that's what real pain okay but it makes
sense because you know poor and foreign
girls for one young girl
um in the middle of a lot of oh I'm not
gonna get a Revival okay whatever
I'll put a fight waiting for me so no
more
um yeah and among all those Japanese
um
well look who's in a brush mostly male
and mostly middle age
support I'm not saying that that's a bad
thing or anything I'm just saying that I
stand out obviously and it's easier to
remember me are we going
down right
we're going down right are we going to
wait no we came from there no we're
going that way
wait does this indicate that I started
out here is that the gray Emerald never
noticed that before does that mean I
came from there are we going this way
then
yeah I I definitely stood out
[\h__\h] recognize me my [\h__\h] Oishi
number one and Aussie number two
recognized me
you have no idea that made my life and
my day and everything yo
honey
foreign
[Music]
right there
foreign
[Music]
I feel like I made it in life when I
when that happens
I've lived in Japan before I have met
Yago
yeah oh my God
hold nothing back oh nothing bad
I'm ready get
Steve bird strike
good morning from Hawaii oh good morning
thank you where am I going
wait now see now I don't see that
um
grayed out Arrow where did I come from
we're going that way
where did I come from where did I go
where did it come from Cotton Eye Joe
where am I I'm going to the this is
confusing
we're going this way right
my hotel
lower level really
descending yeah if only I were a cat you
know she really wants to be a cat just
like me shining foe over there
let's kill him
brace yourself this one's tough struck
ah look there together with Cali when we
met Yahoo to stop you dying
I remember together we went to the
office
I think before our debut yeah yeah yeah
yeah
I had a meeting
[Music]
video chat in the office and had their
talk that way
dude no no no no no she was pretty
freezing quiet and uh yeah shy a little
bit now I mean I was also I was very
nervous but I wanted to
Flex
my communication skills maybe so I tried
my best to
communicate properly where are we going
which way are we going where do they
come from
we're going that way
I'm from you okay okay we're going that
way
you know
oh no this dude again
let's kill him again
I'll give it to you this time
if you really want to be killed by me
I'll do you the favor
oh
[Music]
I don't I don't remember much what
happened but then what did we even talk
about I feel like it was just like uh
I'm Kiana this is Kelly nice to meet you
from now on we'll be in your company
explain to us what what color is and
how the company Works how the outline is
how it's built up you know oops I missed
my Mystic Arts
didn't even know I wasn't over limit
Ed connection they had a PowerPoint
presentation
[Music]
foreign
what I do remember though I don't know
if I ever told that story but
I remember like I wasn't on the same day
I think it was like I heard that
um soon after our meeting uh certain the
whole life members would come into the
studio and uh do some stuff there like a
stream and I was like
oh I wonder if I can stay and say hello
I didn't want to miss that opportunity
but that was before we were even
announced to the whole life Japan
members I'm pretty lucky
um so I I asked I asked if I could stay
and then say hello but
um basically the answer was no because
they didn't even know about their
existence which is understandable
it would have been a little bit
confusing maybe to introduce us like
that you know it makes sense it's fine
it's fine
you're right I think I think one of I
think it was um
I'm not sure
who was coming in but I think one of
them was my intent but I'm sure mommy
said they would have been happy about it
but yeah it was probably for the better
way to not have us meet in that
moments
but I was so excited
I was a bit sad to be turned down
doesn't know you exist
she doesn't know
teleported no I can't use it it said on
the map I can't use it
right
that finger
is out of order you used it anyway
dungeon teleporter
hey look at that is it usable wait wait
it's shining
it's not there right it's the other way
we seem to have come across something a
little unusual
none three of them now what I just
literally no no no no no oh
Gaga
I walked past no knock you again it
wasn't behind him
I think it was the hunting
sometimes
why did they make me walk all the way
back to this teleporter
oh
if I can use it why couldn't you just
like let me do a I don't know quick
u-turn
foreign
oh actually a lot of them
like in person I I only met
probably only a third of them
a fairly pole of Japan none none from
Whole Life uh Indonesia and
from Whole Life English only only Cali
um
foreign
probably maybe a fourth
um
oh
it looks like that beam of light has
stopped
then is it safe to say we've avoided
Oblivion for the time being
I can still sense a faint glimmer of
energy though
it hasn't completely dispersed
you can tell
renwell your senses seem a lot sharper
than before don't they
and you said you heard that voice right
I guess maybe I don't know interesting I
don't feel bad though
yeah I do want to meet the other girls
IRL
ASAP Trace Amounts however small do
remain then it leaves us no choice We
Must Destroy the entire structure okay
what do you suggest we bring it down
piece by piece
don't stop don't stop just go just go
here what do we do
burn it up we go to lennogus
even if we could destroy the whole wedge
like you suggested it would only buy us
time okay the fact they sent this thing
down tells me they're not giving up this
planet without a fight
foreign
how do we go up there
there's also the matter of the
Renaissance its circumstances still have
yet to be truly resolved
but how do we even get to learn again
good question next one please what if we
Hotwire one of their Starships there's
got to be one on the planet somewhere
right
starships are only seen on Dana at the
start and end of the crown contest
otherwise they remain on lenigus believe
it or not we renins down here aren't
quite as free to come and go as one
might think oh great well I'm out of
ideas then well when is this definitely
don't have a tech to build a Starship
and even if we found a renin who'd help
who knows how long that'd take yeah
waiting for a Starship to come down from
lenigus would probably be quicker than
that build one
[Music]
it had to have been in a Starship of
your own he is a Starship he's a
Transformer
you can't be serious that was 300 years
ago there's no way it's still gonna work
but alfin didn't wake up until a few
years ago that means it had to have
still been functioning that whole time
to keep his body preserved indeed you
wouldn't happen to remember where you
landed would you my memories around
where I parked are still a little hazy
took a car
so chances are it's still in the area
oh
that was a place to start whoa
luckily that realm is my old stomping
ground so I should be able to get us
well I wonder if the cutoff point is
gonna be when I reach land again
okay this is it yeah as long as lenigus
stands there there's no avoiding it so
what's this helping calaglia you're
planning to enlist
my buddy Nath
if anyone there knows something I figure
it's him but first I need to catch a
boat and get back to the mainland
this is not a boat this is a ship
how this respect respectful to mahavar
let's go
[Music]
excited
our first Port of Call isabeck ultimate
back where you first started out
yeah along with my dad
this ship gives me PTSD you don't look
so good
I think I'm just a little seasick that's
all
this place gives me PTSD liar
Hands On Fire
you heard me
you've never been good at hiding your
emotions Shion
excuse me just what do you
ah
no
you're right
I'm sorry
is it about Alvin
no not just him
something you can't talk about
when well I'm
I'm not like the rest of you of course
you are
[Music]
no I'm serious
back when we first met I think maybe
then I did think we were different
but now I know that isn't true
you and I are the same Shion
we're alike in more ways than you know
oh
[Music]
if any of us is different it's me
I'm a Danon who can use Magic
I may be the last to figure something
special living in hiding as long as I
can remember
everyone has their own pain that can be
hard for other people to understand
I saw the two of you talking and thought
you could use a third I mean she was
basically she was basically just
implying that she's more special than
xion I'm sure Ren will is special as
well but
they're about this if anything they're
about the same special and that are in
well being more special
she's literally saying that yeah okay
you got your problems but I actually
have so much more problems
yeah it's not a competition anyway but
she was she just made him do competition
very very uh gently
here I am sorry
if anyone's the odd one out here it's me
believe me you don't want to listen to
my channel
see everyone wants to be the one with
the most problems and the most special
she now she's now she on again
I have so many more problems you don't
don't even get me started
haha
you are all special okay all of you all
of you are very special
I didn't say that
I get that you must have a lot circling
around that head of yours
and that's okay
whatever's worrying you right now you're
allowed to worry about it and you don't
have to talk about it if you don't want
to
I know I'm not a renin like you or a
mage like renwell
I'm not a sovereign maiden or Lord I'm
just a Danon who used to be a Slave
but regardless of all that I'm here for
you xion look at that
for me too we all want to be there for
you me and hoodle and even the boys I
promise you're talking to a ghost renuel
I mean that is what friends are supposed
to do right
like today in a lot of these cutscenes
the only Hool that I see is a fake
hoodle on her head is uh is confusing me
I said this to alfin and now I'll say it
to you you're not alone in this
she lost Hulu probably doesn't want to
admit it but she lost it thank you
cool is one of the voices she uses
and right on cue I think I should make
my way back and lie down for a bit
my battle with this ship continues
yeah I better head back too we wouldn't
want the guys thinking they're in charge
can you imagine law at the helm who
knows a little trouble we get into who
runs the world girls girls who runs the
world girls schools
yes
if that's true
then it's all the more reason I have to
do this
oh my God yes bestie
yes
stop guys I didn't even I didn't even
start with that the whole chat suddenly
is like yes girl I think it's safe to
rest here now I didn't even say anything
silent treatment oh no what happened
all right something is definitely up
with xion
yeah something big by the looks of it
I've never seen her something big that
is up could it be the sky
you're so serious
so do you think we should say something
to alfin then
I was wondering the same thing myself
but then it occurred to me
hmm
whatever this thing on her mind is it's
probably the last thing in the world she
wants people to know about
if she's trying this hard to keep it
secret then it's not really our place to
go telling people before she's ready
yeah
I can't tell that
there's
there's just no way I could right
I
supposed to do she on
it's probably
probably nothing is it
you're gonna ask which pair of shoes you
should buy huh
buy both what the hell
yes damn oh can I go underneath no okay
I was hoping for another one of those
scenes if you know what I mean
ah
where am I going
if no go to Ultimate ah okay okay
I'm on my way
Naruto
Sasuke
the Crouch can yeah it feels like it's
been ages
hey chin up this this is your hometown
[Music]
everyone around here looks so much
happier than they used to
say
feels like an entirely different place
I suppose it's had time to adjust to its
Newfound freedom
sephir would have been so happy to see
this
yeah we really would have
especially if he knew Lawless
law
something bothering you law
nah I'll be fine it's just you know
it still weighs on you doesn't it
running away back then
when I finally come back it's been
liberated
what's important is that it's free I get
that I do I just hmm I should have been
here
hmm but we were somewhere else
liberating it so what can you do
all right it's been a while since I've
been in here
[Music]
oh just one thing after another and it
all falls on my head too
what do you mean Seth like a kitten hey
Nath
what can't you see I'm
Alvin Alvin
Alvin this looks like you have your
hands full
as much as ever as if I wasn't busy
enough and it's a running rule I'm up to
my ears and Dan in disputes
and then to top it all off that thing
had to come crashing down from out of
the sky pretty sure we've heard this
somewhere before all because I've lost
it what can I help you with
aha yeah we're looking for an old renin
Starship you wouldn't happen to know any
around these parts would you
a Starship what do you need one of those
for
to get to Lennox
lanigus are you out of your damn mind
believe it or not it wouldn't be the
craziest thing we've done recently
I believe it well Billy by the way I'm
afraid I haven't heard anything about a
Starship
maybe ask Nicki Minaj
sure we've got stacks of old sure she'll
help you mind if we take a look at them
[Music]
yeah okay
thanks Nathan every time they say
Starship I have to think of Nicki Minaj
I can't help I was I was holding it back
for so long this comment
I couldn't hold back anyone I read
through all of the records but I only
found a single line that might point to
what we're looking for it mentions a
rock that shot across the sky and landed
past the mountains the event was
recorded just before the first renin
Invasion oh you think that might be the
Starship I don't know there was nothing
else in the records that came even close
it looked like it was someplace called
Berg that's German for a mountain hint
that ring any bells for you it's the
mountain yeah that's one of the biggest
volcanoes in collab okay it's a volcano
whatever recently a volcano is a
mountain right meteor someone saw
another meteor is it is volcano a
mountain always
actually question
I am a spicy
but but
not always not a holder not a holder
okay then well the German word for
volcano is uh uh Vulcan so they
shouldn't have called it Burke just
kidding
kidding I'm not taking it that seriously
really
I wonder if it could have been one of
those lights out of the wedge all the
more reason to check it out
can you tell us how to get there
the Old Zion mine is up that way one of
the veins we abandon connects to the
volcano go ahead and use that
but you should be careful oh
I don't know if it has anything to do
with the meteor there's a giant zugal
running right
don't scare us no more do you know
if you head out that way
we'll go ain't gonna stop me
yes are you ready or what
oh I didn't notice you there Blazing
Sword I have a name for God's sake
this kid
damn when did you get so tall I can tell
you right now he did not change in size
can't believe a little peep pip squeak
like you is running around with the
Blazing Sword himself I'm sure your old
man would be proud is your old man bro
let's ask Sapphire kitten all right
go on ahead about me I'll catch up later
oh my God why are you laughing like that
I guess can't say I do even I've met the
guy before last time I would have seen
him would have been when I was really
little okay okay well then okay you can
make a comment about him changing in
size okay
okay
I'm the reason my dad's gone remember
you know how much they looked up to him
here oh sorry for getting a sidetracked
let's just head out okay
except for our kitten's death is still
Weighing on him pretty hard
RRP can't say I blame him even if it's
not his fault that's a big thing to have
to carry at his age
yeah but he's trying his best to come to
terms with it I Have Faith Hill Pool
fruits
good he's got an idiot support he's
still just a kid and set fire is only
one at that
I didn't like the sound of that monster
Nate was talking plummet what well we
have to press on we're going through
Zion mine to Berg volcano volcano
Mountain volcano okay okay
what's that
feathers ah most important skit
hold on everything okay with hoodle
renwell he seems kind of out of spirits
it must be the heat getting to him
we don't get these kind of temperatures
back in cislodia
galaglian's born and raised here
struggle with it too so it's no surprise
aha so that's why his plumage is so
white she was born in a winter
wonderland
actually Dan and owls absorb the astral
energy of whatever land they're raised
in where they're born doesn't affect
their appearance at all
but that's not why he's white the real
reason is that he's still just a baby
you mean their plumage changes color
depending on where they grow
and with all this
it wouldn't surprise me if his wings
ended up looking like a colorful
painting
I think he suits his snowy complexion
it'll feel strange to see him change how
awesome would it be
different colors and his stomach inside
I'm not okay for travels too cute
yeah so much for the heat making
only yourself to blame for that one
in his appearance you know
fascinating an appreciation of aesthetic
Beauty and an owlette so young
he's cultured
dohalim I think you've drawn his
attention oh he's so
like a marshmallow
mellow
cute where does the name for marshmallow
come from
mellow marching
how does that how did that become its
name
I don't get it makes no sense to me
good question right yeah
the Mellow plant what
[Music]
all right
oh we have nothing to sell
[Music]
now we don't really need to buy anything
another way
foreign
[Music]
that's all I can afford
night s
sell excess materials but the thing is I
don't know well what like what is X's
what do I need any what do I not need
anymore
anyway it's okay are we going that way
didn't he like show this in the cutscene
if it's over 30 you can probably sell it
you mean over 30 pieces
true
no wait
Hills isn't that the other way around
I
side quest or fish for gold yeah I'll do
it off screen
yeah
Olive chicken
hey where am I going
I'm here
oh shotokato oh I can't use it wait oh
well this is the closest I can get
okay
the stars are mine ah
we are close to the no return points
should I should I do side quests
if I would not do a side quest now how
long do you guys think I'm away from it
if I would not do any cyclists
a bit further a little bit away two to
three hours ah okay okay you made it
sound like I was so close
it's quite hot here
climate feels different from men and see
us it's gotten much cooler since leaving
town
eyes were burning holes in us what are
you trying to say
was that supposed to be a pun it sounds
sounds like oh my God
sounded like he wanted to make a pun out
of it
something feels odd be on your guard oh
God
so we're back in the Zion mine tunnels
who would have thought we'd be going and
I I have to tell you let's let me just
finish and also the first time we
touched as I recall cause every time we
touched I get this feeling and Every
Time We Touch there is for the sky can't
you feel my heart beat fast I want it to
last
[Music]
instance
look at this feeling
[Music]
I sang that wrong a little bit but yeah
uh I I wanted to finally finish my
freaking vacation story let me finish it
so last day morning I had breakfast
yummy breakfast and then we checked out
our our stuff
but I extended our state like you could
like extend to be able to use the
the um the spa
oh
and so we did that we left our stuff at
the reception
and they gave me potatoes I already told
you that they gave us potatoes
as a farewell gift
I was excited about that
you guys were confused but I was excited
to bird volcano We're not gonna see any
lava burst out in front of us
don't get so paranoid you let a rock
fall on your head law
organic potatoes I already used them up
by the way
um
[Music]
yeah yeah
I suspect the cutscene yeah
oh my God
the way that music just started
and they showed that lava it gave me a
lord of the ring vibes
Lord of the Rings
very volcano
okay
so hot yes yeah that's what I said when
I looked at Pizza
we need to find that Starship and fast
[Music]
okay
okay uh
oh
[Music]
there's no way we're climbing that oh
allow me to step in wait you're not
thinking of trying to Vault over with
your Rod are you
why I hadn't even thought of that in any
case stand back I'll handle this
Florence is he gonna make some plants
there so I can climb up construct
The Constructor
plants grow instantly
but if we use this for fruits and
vegetables smart I'd rather not be our
party's fertilizer thank you very much
come on don't take it like that you
don't want to be our parties fertilized
I mean why the hell knock
why not a little help
I help no problem
should have used it now now he's passing
something
okay so we had the breakfast we checked
out we gave our stuff to the reception
and then we made use of our extensions
[Music]
yeah relax and that then I had the best
massage out of all the massages again
I mean you're even better than ever and
this time we found a special special way
to eat the strudel normally they would
give you the strudel and then offer you
vanilla cereal sauce
hot vanilla sauce with it but what they
don't tell you is that there's actually
an option for vanilla ice cream as well
oh they didn't tell me but I heard
rumors I heard a roamer
that you can't ask for that
oh he just fell down cute
so I was like yo I heard you got ice
cream too
I got the Apple struggle with vanilla
sauce
vanilla ice cream
oh best domination I tell you
um
[Music]
ice cream
I'm glad you have your uses get toasty
burn strike
now
it sounds so good yeah yeah it was
really good I never missed really yummy
um struggle every day living that
strudel life
and oh yeah we had a second serving
again
like on all days we had two pieces
and
like on the day before I was looking at
the plan for the next day like what kind
of sessions they were offering
and as I told you they had this space is
starting to sting this mobility and
stretch my throat feels super part
profession that does advertised as being
easy drink too much and being for uh you
know people of all oh wait levels you're
hungry more than anything of difficulty
thank you like no matter how how shitty
you are when it comes to workout
you're fine
Mommy
and it just sounded like it would be
like a stretch session with a little bit
of movement you know
yeah that was what I was expecting
so we went there and it was so
exhausting oh my God
it was so exhausting uh am I gonna open
the shortcut here I think
oh
[Music]
it was way more exhausting than I
expected and my arms they died
I struggled so much but
I think it was good for
my body
and it was interesting
I was like it was I have to say that you
guys say noodle arms noodle arms blah
blah blah but I do have to like defend
myself
it was like
um
a real freaking exercise and very much
focused on working out the arms in the
beginning
20 40 minutes I had to keep on
continuously
um putting strength the pressure on my
arms me be my guest and well I don't
work out normally so that was freaking
exhausting
further away but I didn't force myself
like whenever I felt like this was
really too [\h__\h] much I couldn't keep
myself up anymore
oh my God
okay yeah
I stopped in the waited a moment to get
back into it
that at least for me made much more
sense
then the yoga I'm sorry but
there was no
weird talk I'm not judging people who
enjoy yoga and like
deal with it better than I do let's do
it but there was no blah blah like you
feel how your body touches the ground
and this piece of your body and this
piece of your body and how your neck
connects with your shoulders and your
shoulders with your arms and blah blah
blah
and now we thank our body and we thank
our life and blah blah I must keep
striving you can easily yeah the
spiritual part about it that's that's
what I mean yeah the design of this I
wish I could be spiritual like that I
wish I was like you know and it's really
interesting you might really like it
Alvin I feel it I feel the energy
flowing through my body also I missed
that whole part should I go back I
should go back
I will go through
I won't go back up and go to that side
because I don't know there might be a
chest over there that I missed
my yellow experience was less spiritual
but oh well really
tell me who is your yoga instructor let
me give me give me that number
it's just normal enemies there and some
some ore
Retreat if you know what's good for you
it's Raven ready and rare
[Applause]
still like can't get out of this house
this one's got your name on it a few
hours
there's still more to go
some instructors are not about that
stuff really
but it would be so difficult to find
yoga classes in my surroundings
yeah I shall ensure you survive I wanted
something close though something where I
can easily go spontaneously
and maybe don't have to take an Uber
each freaking time just something where
I can
reach by walking
[Music]
um well then I should probably think
about tonight's menu I don't know
I don't know I don't know that enemy
looks strong I bet it'll be worth our
while to fight it
[Music]
is
difficult to predict
Ed
and Robinson 80s was also spiritual what
do you mean
what are you trying to say
aerobics in the 80s looks fun
from what happened in those high-cuts
with the tights underneath
I'm ready
[Music]
oh my God I need I need healing hello
let's use this
game come to my rescue again
[Music]
did I do it
how many was it five flaming pillars and
just tried to push as many as possible
but was it five four or six
five where are you going right okay okay
okay
nice girl oh no more Miss nice girl
Hello I never called you that
time for the new membership a little
kindness huh oh she is strong
okay this one's got your name
I've been doing really great lately
there was a chest here
[Music]
Gothic dress
oh
did I miss something yes I did
okay might be some decent equipment
anything that makes battles easier is
okay by me
so anyway
after that session
um we were freaking exhausted
actually my BFF she quickly jumped into
the pool after that she wanted to
refresh herself which was honestly it
sounds great and all but I was so done
if only I were a cat meow
I I had I could barely move my body
after that workout session
so I just waited for her uh and then I
changed my clothes and uh yeah then we
started leaving
we took off
unfortunately yeah sad sad sad
I wish it was longer like I I did to
myself I thought when I booked this
vacation
first of all because it was a
spontaneous one I I couldn't really do
much longer because there's like always
so much to do
and second of all
I thought that three days of a Wellness
Spa would be enough
for me to recharge
but it was over an instance
you and I both
yeah
well then I should even we think about
it even if it was a whole week I feel
like I still would get out of there and
be like yo that was that felt like it
was over in an instant
or level 40 magma Lam okay hello
[Music]
can we smash your armor nine
okay okay okay we're destroying him
let's go
games
this one's got your name on it ashes to
ashes
they do talk a lot yes
is stronger than regular Firepower
don't hear me complaining on the way
back we had a long long long car ride
and uh then I had my stream and I tested
out my new chair and all that
oh the car ride was
was chill though most of the time we
were like driving through mountains and
stuff we didn't have a connection
um
to the radio so most of the time we were
just driving quietly listening quietly
to nothing I know sometimes
I'm glad that my BFF also
like kind of wanted that
sometimes you just don't want to listen
to anything right you just wanna
have everything be quiet it was like we
were driving through those mountains and
the sun has had already set but it was
not completely dark yet
it was kind of so Serene and calm
barely any cars until we reach the
highway which was which took quite some
time
yeah I know what he's like it is I know
a lot of people
the moment they get into the car they
turn on their music and blast it out
there so loud and anytime they listen to
some high energy super loud music no
matter what time of the day it is no
matter what day it is no mega who's with
them in the car
you know if if I'm in a good mood like
that then okay I don't mind that either
I don't mind jamming up to music super
loud either but sometimes
it's not the time for it right
yeah
I feel attacked oh no no no no hey you
do you you do yeah
you do you
actually when I was driving in the car
with my brother
recently with my brother and my sister
they were listening to podcasts instead
of music
it was interesting
I I've never met someone before but I
guess nowadays A lot of people do that
hmm
but that was
actually pretty chill
um
[Music]
foreign
I can actually get both of those I think
yeah
[Music]
you can get this
I don't know what to get next
I tried all new books for long tips hmm
yeah yeah no I like that idea podcasts
on your books stuff like that very
calming
and you actually I don't know maybe
depending on what you're listening to
you actually maybe even learning
something while you're driving so that's
cool
um
I don't know
I mean I don't really jump much but okay
just so we fill that up what does that
give us Elemental attack
uh 1600.
[Music]
oh wait we still have a lot here
jump Kings accident
I feel like I know what you're talking
about
hmm
hello
what are these effects
I don't know if they're good or bad
[Music]
I don't know
I wasn't listening that was my day off I
just wanted to be
doing something else
I didn't want to listen to any YouTuber
stuff as much as possible
um
ah
uh
on my day off
yesterday I got up so early I had like
five hours of sleep and I went to get my
x-ray
who wants to see the bones of an idol
let's go
who wants to see that the the things
that keep my body together let's go
I was legit thinking about showing you
my x-ray you can't even see that much
it's like a super close-up on my on my
spine they didn't even have my shoulders
on it which made me think a little bit
you know um what the [\h__\h] I feel like
the problem might not only be in my
spine it could also be in the shoulders
so maybe we should have the shoulders on
there as well but okay
yeah
anyways
imagine imagine
whole life YouTuber uploads their x-ray
of their spine on Twitter
and then and then there come all the
internet doctors who are like uh Kiana
so looking at your spine I'm not a
doctor but you know I I have uh read a
lot about these kind of things I would
say I have quite the knowledge about it
you know
I do know my stuff I may not be a doctor
but truly I am inside of my heart
[Music]
yeah that's that's where you're young
you're wrong and your body is so [\h__\h]
up here
diagnosing me on Twitter
spinal vaccine well at least I still
have a spine right
would be very very same if I lost my
[\h__\h] spine
at least I have one calcium
did I say that in English too like
someone who has I guess no Integrity
has no money for you all fine
see what I can do
in a bind
ERS
oh yeah so anyway that was super quick I
had an appointment
um so I didn't have to wait I just went
there it was super early I was super
tired I went there I went in five
minutes later I went down
and yeah they gave me my scans and then
later they sent me the before the best
materials in your garden whatever that
is in English that's quite the
Discerning Eye dohaline yeah they all
kind of look the same to me and now I
have uh both the befund of uh my x-ray
and my blood test
a diagnosis findings whatever
so I called my other doctor and I was
like I need an appointment please
and they gave me an appointment for next
week to talk about
everything that I have
campus yeah I
I don't think there's gonna come much
out of it nicer than you went on
although I was up I was able to I was
able to already look at my blood test
okay and you see I don't understand much
of it because I'm not a doctor
but you you can like already see
um
wait a second
you can already see
like it shows you this wait how do I get
back in here
this one
this is how we get back
blood says daddy issues
you guys want to talk about my blood
you can't understand
it
and so there is this there is this like
[Music]
they have all these things
and most of them are in the green okay
but then there's things that are in the
red and that's probably worrisome right
and I mean I guess there's a lot of
those things here in the red that don't
really matter that much and can be
easily fixed but I don't know which ones
they are
I don't know so apparently my my
cholesterol
uh
what Excel no I I don't know it's red my
cholesterine is too high what does that
mean I've heard about it so often that
that especially males have a high
cholesterol roll thingy
what what does that do
that eating habits that could very much
be because I also am very much
lacking vitamin B12 and vitamin D 25 oh
I'm giving you all the Deets here
I could even give you my my detailed uh
numbers
uh yeah I mean obviously D is meaning
that I don't go outside
there you have it are we surprised
uh
I have was also red is
I don't know what that is
there's a little bit of an explanation
but that's like in doctor language
um
oh and another one it worried me because
it's like at the very very maximum of
red
and now this one really worries me
that one really worries me
um it says something about borreliosis
or so that's I don't know isn't that
worrisome
but it says
it says I don't have burial borelliosis
[\h__\h] worst worrisome yo
you know the thing that you get when you
get bitten by a tick
I think
um yeah Lyme disease
I don't think I have Lyme disease do I
would I not have noticed already
if I had that yeah see I don't wanna I
don't wanna go too crazy about this yet
obviously but
oh
we'll see what the doctor says
yeah red is playing bad
but it's not that much not that much
red stuff
not that much most of it is green
um
I have enough calcium I have enough
blood sugar
goes for her blood test on stream
but the the coldest terrain man
oh
LDL cold estarin is an physical physical
factor of his heads Chrysler Cancun ah
oh [\h__\h] oh
that's what cholesterol was about like
if you have too high cholesterol is does
that mean you might have a heart attack
or something like that
is that done
LDL oh that's something else again oh
[\h__\h] I'm [\h__\h] yeah yeah so cholesterol
and LDL cholesterol is both in the red
for me
[Music]
heart attacking coming
up
[Music]
oh let's wait for my doctor
yeah but I don't think that any of this
is causing my my shoulder and neck pain
though that's that's another thing
don't hard challenge yourself
[Music]
we work well together cut back on the
fast I might be the owner of a fast food
restaurant but I don't eat fast food
Dutch
no like I mean
probably I probably eat less fast food
than you guys
help and yes they are also closed I made
Korea today
or Oreo shakes do it no yesterday I
watched yesterday I walked past the
Burger King and I did not purchase or
even think about purchasing anything
yeah pretty worn out yeah
no more lasagna Pizza
take lasagna away from me that's not
fast food
and even Pizza can be not fast food if
you get like a proper pizza and not the
not the frozen pizza okay you can get a
healthy Pizza Pizza is not necessarily
so unhealthy not unhealthy as like pasta
bone is whatever the [\h__\h]
did I already take that or not
um
I think I did
see there you go there you go here it is
here I have what what I what I should
have known I would be getting people
telling me to stop eating the land
people thinking they know how I
nurture myself every day and yes okay
you might have a rough and good idea of
it but it's gotten better okay
definitely improved
[Laughter]
um
all right
[Music]
yeah
very attention me too but I care less
about my blood than I care about my
shoulders and my neck I think if
anything were to uh kill me
it's gonna be my neck and my shoulders
say no more so please can we take care
of that please
ah come here reload
another height yeah high cholesterol
isn't that like a super common thing
anyway well look who's in a bright and
shiny mood
isn't that super common anyway
I'll be fine I'll be that job right
most definitely wait what was that oh I
won't make what was that
I mean honey
oh Mystic cloak
cloak
clock no
clock
there we go something new which one is
it
very common
dying is very common
yay
ah in America
um I can I can see that yes
your guys's servings are insane to begin
with like I can't I can't even eat a
fifth of the servings you guys have over
there
oh man
you guys you guys tell me to cut back on
my
fast food intake you tell me that it's
crazy to see rocks melt before our eyes
watch where you're going I often
often go like okay like the the frozen
pizzas that we have here are fairly
small I can finish
but when I order a pizza
Pizza
like delivery
I can never eat those fully never
usually I eat half
or
uh
a little bit less than half of that
pizza and then eat the rest of the next
day
so I really don't eat that much okay
exactly so don't but I do last one
um especially probably a lot of
nutrients like vitamins and no little
kid
go no furtherness
foreign
oh we need CP
we need CP thank you
thank you
Jenny horns
oh my God
that's a nice skills
help
how much sorry I'm late today no problem
welcome
it's last take sugar away from your
foods
no
I refuse
I will not
no no
no
you cannot make me no
I'm still
I will once again
stand strong and say my intake of shitty
food has become much much smaller
compared to one or five years ago
yes I used to eat so much more chocolate
speaking off I kind of want to eat some
chocolate right now
just don't die attention okay I will see
these guys I told you you guys still
think I'm a I'm a chicken or what
Eagle range
one's mine
that's gonna have many reasons
do it it's not fair
that's what built up over the past 10
years I swear I got better
oh man if you have high cholesterol you
should take it seriously
you need to be stronger
don't don't don't make me worry so much
I'll start googling high cholesterol
please stop you're gonna make me Google
that [\h__\h] and I shouldn't do that
because then I'll just diagnose myself
we don't want that we don't want that to
leave
Italian
[Music]
go this way
is this one of those small dungeons that
you guys mentioned by the way
I suppose yeah
we're getting closer ah this way ah
gonna use up all my freaking CP
better be worth it oh hell yeah I know
you had that sort of trick up your
sleeve do Helene I would have figured
rocks and plants would be too different
for you to handle both
absolute protection for actual Peace of
Mind luckily for me
sounds good
absolute vodka
this area is Rich not only in Fire and
dark chocolate can help lower
cholesterol oh interesting I actually
don't like dark chocolate I only like
milk chocolate and white chocolate and
any chocolate that's Yum Yum Yum
chocolate cookies covered in chocolate
chocolate cake chocolate brownies
chocolate ice cream
and like strawberries covered in
chocolate strawberry chocolate
uh chocolate with caramel
chocolate
um
with a cow pattern milk a chocolate
chocolate pudding is okay maybe not my
first choice but I like chocolate with
chocolate
and you know oh we're doing a boss
Babymetal has already said it before and
if Babymetal says that if Stan said give
me choco how dare you refuse anyone of
chocolate
you don't have that right to refuse
anyone of choco
give me choco
baby metal said it before I say it again
and this dude also says it chocolate
chocolate
give me chocolate
shot out of the wedge landed chocolate
by this location if if the purpose of
the wedge is to harvest Dana's astral
energy
chocolate though if that thing gets into
town
let's go
this one's tough let's see what are we
looking at let me know if you need
healing
here it comes focus on your toes
everything I can't choose an enemy I
thought there was like weak points that
I could choose from no who do I even
attack turning tail doesn't seem so
ridiculous why are you scared me I can't
find you even have to ask
Focus up before we become that things
like he's just talking wait questions
foreign
he's like showering us with fire
okay
[Music]
take this
oh hello
this one's mine oh my God
Stephen
[Music]
flashing
kiss
ES
how is something
boys
[Music]
no more
finally what now what now send us some
new people to fight
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no not on her [\h__\h] watch
[\h__\h]
I'm not scared I'm totally fine she's
fine she's fine look in the middle of
all that fire she says she's fine so we
trust her
we need to do that I I stopped him from
casting
see what I can do raging
say no more
no
take it
[Music]
back
I'm just trying to do the best oh I'm
done again
[Music]
take this
take what
oh oh
not a problem okay and do this
can't get out of this nice
who am I fighting I'm not kidding anyone
I feel
say no more
well done
oh yeah by the way my that tweet about
uh being bitten by a vampire was
obviously about
me getting a blood test the other day
and we have to do both things on one day
but I needed an appointment for uh the
x-rays apparently
coming through not for the blood test
though I just went there
the vampire who took my blood was really
really nice
but it did hurt a little bit
it was a little bit of an ouch
you fight better at a distance
and after that that was on the day
before the tales of luminaria Stream
So after taking my blood I went to oh my
God it was so annoying I went too
um I went to this like electronic
Supermarket because I wanted to buy
um an HDMI splitter in order to stream
the uh I'm gonna die
in order to stream the
um
the iPad Pro and I needed to buy the
iPad Pro as well
so I went there I bought an HDMI
splitter and I saw that they had this
apple Corner as well but for some reason
I felt like going directly to the Apple
Store
to buy it
it's about the strikes oh no oh no not
today
what
can I find it now no we won't surrender
no we're not all right uh is he gonna do
it again
Apple Store will sell it three times if
no way nah I don't believe that
why would they no I don't believe it I
don't believe it nope I think they have
a prac like the same price everywhere
official press
yeah what the hell
um should I heal us oh
I'm dead though she didn't understand
[Music]
he didn't bring us down to one HP SO
waiting for dance
one more
that's enough
[Music]
go back down oh
easy
relaxation down
not bad everyone okay
yeah I think so
that thing scared the pants off me it
felt like it had a different Aura than
others Eagles didn't it yeah it wasn't
like the one that Alma madria sicked on
us either it's Elemental astral energy
variants was out of world
guess it's safe to assume that if it
came out of the wedge it must have
played some part in helping Harvest
astral energy but what
perhaps a Living spirit vessel
plausible given the location
or it may be part of a new Force
dispatched to regain control of Dana
if we assume that monster was one of the
four beams of light
that prevented something from taking
place here
I'd like to think so knowing how much
grief it gave us
but at least with that out of the way we
can keep moving forward now
let's go
okay we destroyed it one more small
dungeon to go apparently
um
I feel sad
I don't wanna
secret key
I think I'm getting stronger
should I I don't know should I just stop
and do some side quests how long has it
been four and a half hours
[Music]
don't be crying all right
the cutscenes I I wonder if they're
gonna be long oh yeah I have to read
super chats too I know but I want to
play the game with you guys
I don't wanna not only if you guys but
just generally I'm sad about the Game
ending
no
it's so good I can't wait another five
years for a tails off game him sorry
crickets
hey is that it over there yeah
fashion
whoa judging by the stench I'd say the
animals at the ranch are all grown now
that's what you're thinking about now
that's what's priority right now
it
didn't they announce cilia remix excuse
me what the [\h__\h] what
excuse me when the [\h__\h] win
what the what what what what what
the hell are you saying
what
I have not heard of that and I don't
think I missed it
yeah I don't think so that would have
reached me I think
uh
[Music]
foreign
yet so I guess I'll just
play those
on which devices was Tales of Fantasia
again
because I don't even think I have the
right device for tells a fantasio
still eight hours left in the main story
all right I'll fill that up good with
some side quests and enjoy it privately
PS1 and GBA DS in advance as well
PS PlayStation Portable
ah I have one but I think that one
doesn't really work anymore I don't know
it had some issues I think no that was
my
that was my DS
I think no wait my PSP should work I
haven't touched it in a million years I
have a pink PlayStation Portable
PSP
that was Tales of fantasy on PSP really
yeah I know the original one was not on
the PSP but
uh
yes
hey a remake
not not just a
hmm
because I know that one is so good like
ah I honestly prefer the newer ones
because of the nice graphics and all
that but Tales of Fantasia or Tesla
rebirth and all those they're just such
Classics and I've only heard good things
about them so I know I should give it a
try
um
did you finish the Isle of Hearts not
yet so that's also something I could do
and and I guess in my free time I could
also eventually finish
um Tales of Hysteria
I mean I love Edna so
I I want to play Tesla cysteria I'm
hyped I wouldn't stream it I think but
yeah
um
[Music]
thanks for introducing Tales after me I
enjoyed my playthrough of the game
despite not playing many diabetes per
hour well trusty recommendations more
going forward
[Music]
I'm happy to hear that
thank you
Edna is
Netflix does have a limited amount of
shows yeah that's true you guys know
what I'm watching right now
I'm watching Seinfeld
so old
what you Seinfeld
Kusa
I'm liking it definitely more than that
other what was that show at the police
department that you guys told me to
watch I'm liking this one a million
times more
um still not as good as like the office
or
any of the other shows that I love yeah
Brooklyn 99 is obnoxious I absolutely
obnoxious
and but aside from
it and it has what nine Seasons so I'm
currently in season three already
it's nice to binge through I don't know
how up until now I missed uh this series
I don't know like suddenly Netflix
recommended it to me and I'm like where
have you been my whole life what the
[\h__\h]
hmm classic right yeah oh my God just
just yesterday I was watching this
episode and the dude not the Seinfeld
but his friends dude he said this he
said this line they were like in in this
restaurant waiting
um to get a seat and he was waiting to
get on the phone but there were other
people who keep on like occupying the
phone and then he said
we are living in a society and that's
what I was wondering is this where it
originally cut where that originally
came from
he was so angrily saying we're living in
a society and I was like
is this what a meme came from
[Laughter]
no
kind of that we have rules yeah
it's not coincidence
ah it comes from the Joker it really are
you sure maybe the Joker took it from
Seinfeld
it was it's always been there it's been
there since a long long time ago
or we can make the best one let's go
oh hell yeah baby oh oh wow big Shield
gotta hold up I guess we'll make this
one
there's a there's a mega evolution of
Our member in whole life English afauna
you see it's one of the ingredients on
the bottom left
megaphone
wow Mega Evolution
am I gonna fight someone I'm just gonna
save I assume no so if you just got out
of a boss fight but I'm Gonna Save
anyway
okay
can you believe that Starships
[Music]
open I'm about to fight did you remember
something
no he forgot I have seen that Starship
before Oh
this is it
this is the ship I traveled in when I
escaped from lennogus oh
oh
three centuries later and it's no worse
for wear I'll take a look at the
internals
damn I'm amazed it still works at all
after all this time
and then he flies off alone and he's
like bye-bye see you later suckers
bye to Holland
I really am from a different time and
play
yeah but you've got us now Alvin oh not
only that but you've helped out so many
people too
Law's right renwell too you're one of us
now no more carrying enough history on
your shoulders you're a part of this
world
right
thanks you guys he's ancient
he's a false file
oh oh he's back he changed his mind
it should fly all internal systems seem
to be operating hello considering how
long it's remained inactive but I
suspect it will take some time before
it's ready for takeoff
how much time are we talking here
Starship mechanics are not what I'd call
my forte so I'd rather not Hazard a
guess so we've just gotta sit around
here and wait
terrible at waiting that's because
you're a child oh you too though we use
this time to prepare and gather supplies
for the trip good idea who knows when
we'll be back from lenegas once we leave
we should prepare ours for every
possible scenario before we go
let's try not to stay away too long
I'd hate for anything to happen to the
place while we're gone either we race
ahead or we take due precaution to
ensure we have no regrets I shall leave
it up to you as to how we proceed wait
is this it
this is
no right isn't there one more short
dungeon
not here okay okay
I don't want it to end
oh
[Music]
it's funny isn't it
no not funny
all this
when we first started this thing did you
ever imagine we'd be going to lennogus
after all this is the sort of thing I
was rebelling against when I ran away
I hereby declare
I love the tales of Siri
foreign
I'm sure Zephyr would be proud if he
knew what his son was doing right now
and a little shocked too we're defying
the order of things that have persisted
for 300 years
deep down I knew our journey would lead
to confronting lenigus
yeah you may be but you're a renin the
rest of us can barely even picture what
it means to leave Dana
no offense to Shion and dohalim but it's
worth remembering we're heading into
enemy territory
no offense taken and this is no picnic
for me either
remember our aim is to ensure that both
lenigus and the renin Homeworld leave
Dana alone for good
I don't think we'll be able to avoid a
fight
is there no way we can talk them into
leaving us alone
the people of lenigus
sure I mean we found a way to make it
work with Xi'an and dohalim right
and it's not just us if places like
menencia can do it then why can't we
there are still many of my kind who
believe it was right and natural that
Rena Reigns over Dana
there are those on lenigus who have
never stepped foot on Dana I doubt
whether they'd even listen to dannon's
look none of us want to fight
but these are the same people who fired
that wedge down on Dana
what happens next is on them
right we're not going to sit back and
wait for them to oppress us again
right
don't forget there's also a good chance
the red woman is somewhere on lenigus
and wherever she is we should find the
Renaissance too
that's right
when he said the red woman because it's
kind of been a while for a moment the
only thing I could think of is Great
Game of Thrones oh my God okay I already
remembered that I remember I remember
that
if we can take it back then Xi'an can
finally get rid of her thorns
ah
Shion
what
huh uh yeah
hmm
where are you okay elephant
but he's like bugging out
my pirate is bad oh my God this game
over
where'd sheon go how could she just go
off on her own
she's not over there
let me go back to my friends Shiana
she on I see you look cute
that's a
yeah
it's like you know those people hiding
behind something thinking that they're
actually hidden but they're really not
[Laughter]
sneak
I know she's not hiding
she would still suck at it though sure
but why
okay
just now I looked like you used your
maiden powers to suppress your thorns
can really do that
hey
stay out of my way
huh
oil are you planning to go alone shut up
why would you do this I want you to shut
up
I won't let you
I mean it
I refuse to let you
I won't tell you again
move or I'll shoot
if that's the case
then go ahead and shoot me
drama baby
she'll calm down
laughs
we can talk about it
Beyond
I'll see you on
[Music]
I'm crying
talk to us
do you remember back when I was stabbed
by roll on
uh yeah yeah yeah I do I felt for sure
that he had killed you back there
that wasn't the first time
huh the first time
was when I was only a child
after that no matter how often
it just couldn't die
who couldn't die so you're Immortal
how's that even
I believe you Shion
tell me how how is something like that
possible
thorns
they're me but at the same time not
they're part of me
I have no idea why
but my Thorns will never let me die
at least not before I meant to
[Music]
be can't die before your death
when my Thorns free themselves
[Music]
it will be my death
I've seen it
a darkness that swallows up everything
until nothing remains
the vision of Oblivion I can't escape
sounds like Cali's rap lyrics I believe
it's all just a bad dream
but no matter what I tell myself
I
I know it's not
yeah but you
wait the whole reason you
you needed the Renaissance was to get
rid of your Thorns right
foreign
if I burn away what's inside
then what will happen to the rest of me
right
either way you look at it I'm going to
die
but if I am going to die
I figure I can at least take my Thorns
out with me
that's
what I've been after this whole time
hmm
that's why you turned your back on your
fellow reddits and chose to fight with
us isn't it
hmm
[Music]
and while we've all been fighting to
keep on living
you have been with us fighting
desperately to die
um
that was the plan
but then I met all of you
and I
[Music]
before I knew it I didn't want to die
anymore
[Music]
don't lose hope yet
find a way to save you there's still
time to
pointless why because the darkness won't
just consume me
truth is
of existence as well
this was only a suspicion at first
but
ever since the red woman triggered my
maiden powers
I've been more certain than ever before
[Music]
it was then
that I finally came to realize
my Powers were holding my Thorns and
checked the entire time
[Music]
but they don't anymore
not since line guess
when the wedge fell
every day
feel the Thorns power growing stronger
inside of me pretty soon
I won't be able to hold them back
anymore
and when that happens they will consume
all existence
[Music]
and that's why you wanted to leave by
yourself
you planned to find the Renaissance on
your own and sacrifice yourself to stop
the thorns
[Music]
too much it's way too much
when this all began
I didn't care what happened to me or
anyone else
then what happened to the renins or the
demons didn't matter to me at all
[Music]
I know I have to die
but I don't want to
now that I have this
[Music]
we had never met
she on it
I'll be living for the sake of dying
it's no better than being a Slave how
can you endure this elephant
I don't care what anybody says
I won't let it happen
[Music]
we can fight this
fight until the end together
[Music]
isn't that what you said to me before
even if it should mean
that it'll be the end of everything else
too
it's your decision ultimately
but if you decide not to fight fate I
will even if I have to do it alone
no you won't be alone
I'll fight as well
Count Me In as well
I want to be a force for good not hate
and me too
I meant it with all of my heart when I
told you before neither of you are alone
in this at all
and I for one don't believe this Venture
is without hope
Shion is the descendant of a maiden from
300 years ago given the circumstances it
seems very likely that those events have
some connection
imagine
sorry I have to mute this uh
sorry they're playing uh DM dmca song
the one of the opening songs
[Music]
mm-hmm
on to Lennox
oh that was good you guys should have
listened to it with the music
oh
[Music]
yeah it was a good good cutscene very
emotional
very very emotional
and we get more
the end of the world
that's hard to believe isn't it
I believe Shion is telling the truth
what about you
as a friend yes I want to believe her
everything that's happened seems to
point towards some sort of great danger
that's lurking ahead of us
still it's hard to Fathom something that
could Usher outright Doom to the world
that those really are the stakes we face
no I understand
even Shion doesn't seem to know exactly
what will happen to bring it all about
we have so many pieces of the puzzle in
our hands so many Clues
yet the complete picture eludes us it
definitely eludes me so where do her
Thorns fit in then
well I imagine they must sit at the very
center of it all
remember the voice we all heard while we
were inside the wedge don't you
yeah I remember
it was the will of Dana's astral energy
come to life
that's what we all thought
right
and from that we're able to hypothesize
how vast concentrations of Astral energy
can become sentient
let's return to when we found Xi'an and
uh I could honestly
um
um play the music as well but it would
mean that I couldn't monetize the stream
like I would my I might get a copyright
stricken and we want to avoid that it's
no problem though I am very very happy
and grateful to be able to stream this
game and also to be sponsored to promote
it in the beginning as well so I have no
complaints it's understandable have a
nice day Collegian when her Thorns went
wild they contained far more astral
energy than any mere renin would
normally have inside them
and honestly it's just been like the
only time where it was really bothersome
was now because it was while they were
having a conversation but at any other
times it was not really him
an issue that
um
caused a problem in the playthrough so
oh good so you think those Thorns might
be alive too that their will is what
keeps her from dying
but why would they want to destroy the
entire world
as for that
I really cannot say for certain
its goals still remain a mystery it may
be amazing
thus far
you know I've noticed since we've met
that you like figuring out riddles
can you blame me
when one realizes that the world they
once thought to be true is but a mere
facade they can't help but seek the
truth
especially when that deception has led
to others getting hurt
so halim
I imagine the remaining pieces of the
puzzle that we seek rest somewhere
Within lennogus
as for what the final picture will look
like who can say
I think it's best we not dwell on it too
much for the time being
right
oh man
he said for sad like how I say Passage
how are you holding up
homie
yes you
you took a hit from those Thorns again
didn't you
oh that that was nothing compared to
what xi'an's going through you mean
still
even if you yourself might be willing to
endure that kind of pain
that doesn't mean Xi'an wants to have to
see you get hurt by her Thorns you know
yeah I know I'll be careful
Shion doesn't know how lucky she is to
have you around you know dashing in to
save her at the last minute yeah yeah
very funny
I'm being serious you went up and held
her close like you still had that mask
on and you didn't even bat an eye
she really needed that
that's what I mean when I said you saved
her just like you did with the rest of
us
I just want for she on what we all have
the ability to touch someone without the
fear of killing them those Thorns have
robbed her of the kind of everyday
things we all take for granted
it's not right you can say that again it
may be normal for us but that doesn't
make it any less special or important
for her I hope she gets what she wants
um
I have my own dreams
fishing the biggest fish right guys so
we can all survive isn't a world I want
to live in
agreed it's like more and more keeps
getting taken from her and I'm done with
it
don't worry
I know where your priorities lay lie
we'll get those fish we'll catch them
all
trust me
can't sleep
after everything we just heard
how could I
fair enough
shions had to deal with so much on her
own
even when we were all laughing and
celebrating she just kept quiet and
didn't say anything
I thought she was keeping her distance
because of her thorns
that it was because she didn't want to
hurt anybody by getting too close
I just figured that that was the type of
person she was you know but it turned
out to be none of that
all this time she felt like she had to
die and sacrifice herself for the
greater good but even then
she didn't think she could say anything
to us about it
um
she was so alone this entire time
how could I call her a friend and yet be
so completely blind to everything come
on
I'm sure it made her happy knowing you
were there for her now you really think
so
yeah I do
she didn't think of us as friends I
don't think she could have ever opened
up to us like that
you were a good friend to her before and
you'll be an even better one now
yeah
I really hope so
I want to be the best I can for her
when you think about it we were all
alone in our own way
but over time we've all found ways to
let each other into our lives I hope
shion's able to do that one day too
no I mean I hope she's able to do that
more I know lots and lots more
I think it'd be really nice if we could
all just be there to support each other
when it really counts and forget about
our grudges and pain
yes preach
preach it girl
she gets it
do you know
you mean about xion
yeah I didn't have the slightest idea I
mean every once in a while I thought
something seemed a little off but I
never could have imagined
it's like a completely different world
with spinning around me and I couldn't
even see it
you and me both I mean I knew something
was bothering her but
I could never quite figure out what it
was
you but you're the one always looking
out for her but he's a dense protagonist
in reality I
I thought was helping and being there
for her it was actually just driving her
into it knows nothing at least you
figured it out in time though right
I don't think we're out of the woods yet
but yeah you're right
we brought her back from the edge and
we're going to stop those Thorns from
taking her no matter what
yeah with all of us together there's
nothing we can't handle she on the world
we can save everyone and I mean it when
I say we Alvin
I know thank you
hey welcome you're the expert on what my
dad would say
do you think he'd Pat me on the back or
tell me off
Zephyr I don't think that he'd have that
much to say to be honest you're your own
man now law and you've already made up
your own mind about what you want
I guess he couldn't say anything even if
he wanted to
sorry I guess those of us amongst the
living have enough problems to deal with
don't we I'm all good we'll need all our
strength to save xion
I'll probably end up wearing again at
some point but I guess I'll think it
over more then that okay I'm sorry yeah
I think it is
I'm sorry
I'm so sorry
last but not least
[Music]
hey you doing all right
I seemed to cause nothing but worry she
as much as I try to look like I have
things under control
everyone still worries about me
not the only one
hey
do you remember the first time you said
I was your friend
ah
no when was that
sorry I can't remember
that's okay it came so naturally to you
I'm not surprised you forgot
I was different back then the dannins
were not even people to me and I knew I
would always be alone
but in that room with dead I'm when you
called me your friend it just
shattered the wall that I built up
around me no
no because until that moment
I'd only seen you as a means to an end I
thought of you as a way to use the
Blazing Sword and to obtain the
Renaissance Alma
but after that day one time became two
and before I knew it you'd made a habit
of calling me and dohalem your friends
it didn't matter that we were runners
you cared about us as you would any
other people
[Music]
then everyone else started to call me
their friend too to think of me as their
friend before then I never even dreamed
I could have that
I didn't want to die and lose you all
but I also didn't want to live if it
meant you would all die in my place
um
that wouldn't be worth it but then I
realized
I'd only really been thinking of myself
that entire time
after saying how I felt
and hearing what you all had to say
finally understood that
don't worry it's okay
I'm not planning on dying anymore okay
so we're gonna destroy the world okay we
truly care about to give in now
[Music]
so I'll fight
for Dana and for myself
I'll fight against my fate to preserve
our future and I'll win come hell or
high water
I don't know how we're going to do it
but I won't let the world end because of
me okay
we'll try it's going to be
a large road ahead she on
how fight won't be over until everyone
both Dan and renins can finally live in
peace
I swear I'll be there with you until the
very end
thank you
remember what we learned back in
calaglia
there's no wall so high that we can't
break it down
I think you may be right about that I
like that
oh zoom out
oh
we're getting there guys
my party's back we're ready to rumble
thank you for the red super chat
you're not Frankie though
funny bird
oh man
everyone well rested yeah then let's go
we depart for lennogus board the stop is
what I read just now I don't know why
let me look at that scenery too also
also
I mean he sounds butt is beautiful and
all but I think we have to
go for our lady
wow
[Music]
foreign
I know that
oh well
tobymaca
all very emotional what do you say we
check back in on the rain okay
a buddy foreign
okay and wait anything else I should do
time right right right right can I
I wonder
uh I don't I don't have much money
[Music]
um
time to finish all the fishing Cycles
I'll be stuck on the [\h__\h] for a while
sell stuff sell mats if which ones the
the ones where I have too many
I mean I don't I don't need that much
money right now
uh so these ones huh
bright Stone like I could get rid of the
ones that have three here I suppose
maybe uh
like this one Manny honestly I think I
sell all of these
pretty hot oh there we go
sell all
uh oh wait I only have one Oh I thought
it was 30. uh ah
that was only one
wait
oh my God why are they listed like that
ah because they all got different
effects oh no you know what I'm gonna do
that off screen
yeah
yeah okay
let's go
[Music]
take off is now
wow
it's time well it's the moment of truth
can we fly lady hold together once we're
up in the air law don't say that you're
going to jinx us knock on wood speaking
of witch Elfin this bucket of bolts got
a name
a name hmm you know I'm not sure she
ever had one poodle number one I really
thought about it
well after all the trouble
we should give her one right fascinating
I was thinking something like
no it means owl in the ancient times oh
okay literally at the one drawn to this
is such a simp
such an owl Sim written well
I like it sounds perfect for our little
Escapade number one would have been
better though not sure I'm completely
convinced what the heck well it's as
good a name as anything from now on
she'll be known as the father how dare
you write that in my chat how dare you
okay people how dare you lead me to
Darkness first we need to get to
lennogus and make the renins finally
leave Dana alone
and then we need to figure out the truth
behind xi'an's thorns and find a way to
save her sound good sound good
all right and let's go
dramatic music
oh
wow it's all polished up
no oh
it's zooming
hiya
[Music]
speed
hi hi hi
[Music]
you know sorry to all Germans out there
I still hardly believe it
believe what
I mean just look at it the whole of
existence crammed inside a tiny frame
now you mention it I guess you're right
it does look more like a painting than a
living breathing world
from up here all the struggles we've
been through feel so insignificant
nothing like realizing how small you are
to put everything into perspective oh
true really makes the differences
between the renins and the dannins feel
pretty small too huh
yeah how much longer until we reach
lennogus oh my god there are better ways
to use your time than napping he's like
you should take a moment ourselves with
the facilities are we there now and what
about now I'm serving as our base of
operations once we're down there
think you'll be all right with the
controls
you mean the one set to automatic pilot
I dare say I'll manage I'm basically
just here to supervise
Pilots
so useful
automatician you seem a little different
different like in a bad way different no
not at all you see more driven lately
like you found a zest for life it suits
you
there's something wrong
no I was merely thinking how it had been
seven years that's all what what is this
these comments autopilot yep all the
piles sure other part nice
I was meaning
[Music]
what
huh
you mean since you became a Lord and
left lenigus I guess even someone like
you can get homesick huh
I am as prone to sentimentality as any
other
tell me though okay you too have a
history oh you're making fun whether or
not they would have autopilots yeah I
would probably mean facing up to some
difficult emotions
doesn't that frighten you
well
it is a place where I took the lives of
countless people
I'd be lying if I said I hadn't thought
about it very convenient forever
past is what it is there's no changing
that
but the future
[Music]
did you see that dakimakura
that hot as [\h__\h] ducky makura
see why why would I need to put out a
dakimakura officially when there's fan
artists out there who
draw a freaking damn high quality ducky
Makara
that's just as good as official quality
um
[Music]
we dress
come back and speak to me when you
finish looking around the ship
you want me to tap to everyone
get more talking
this is now a Saturday stream
what was life on Lennox homecoming queen
before you came to Dana
let's just say I don't have many happy
memories
I've had Thorns my whole life for as
long as I can remember it
you're just using me as a guinea pig for
their research
though you mean they experimented on you
just like pickled us and by experimented
on me
that's right all I was to them was a
riddle to solve they poked and prodded
me trying to figure out what triggered
my Thorns or changed the form they took
day in and day out every single day one
test after another
still surprised they didn't try to
dissect me
touch my skin
how could I forget it
reeling from the pain like I was a
monster or something
some existence huh a blight on any I
touched helplessly complicit in their
pain
ter defense mechanism it's gonna be very
useful visions of the coming apocalypse
[Music]
is it any wonder I lacked a cheery
disposition unable to so much as touch
another Soul so understandable
sure I survived but with the knowledge
that one day I'd be swallowed up by
Oblivion that's when it hit me
if I was going to die then it should
mean something
if I have to sacrifice myself to save
the world
so be it
I'm sorry I didn't mean to make you
relive that
no it's fine I'm in a much better place
now
You Say It's Your Destiny to die so that
others can live but why not the other
way around why shouldn't we be the ones
dying to save you
are you crazy why would you sacrifice
your life for that's exactly my point I
mean Alvin has been alive in your life
just because for a long time too I'm
sure that he's like all right I'm done
as well
he's ancient he's older
than xion he's been around for centuries
hundreds if not thousands of years
so
yeah
as you drew the Short Straw in the
destiny Stakes how is that even right
it's that logic that's used to justify
slavery
this struggle was never about saving
only ourselves
but that doesn't mean we have to give up
our own lives to save everyone else's
either that's that's why he has white
hair
if we're doing this to protect people
if we're doing this to save the world
from destruction
then that has to include saving each
other wait in the flashback that we saw
did he have white hair
oh he did
I should have given him dark hair back
then well
a world free of sacrifice
you've been fighting for all along
can you guys not
take me apart like that me and my logic
okay oh isn't it
not just me we're in this together
remember
fight is yours too Shion we're going to
win everyone has to win there can be no
room for losers in this fight
the nature of our struggle yeah the
champion Victory without losers
[Music]
you bet we can pull it off we have to
it's the only hope we have of things
ever changing
you're right no one's ever changed the
future without aiming for the Stars
we can do this together
[Music]
make our dreams come true
hey Alvin listen to this so law and I
were just talking and uh hey shut up and
what's got lost
[Music]
all that fussy made about naming the
ship too okay hey I never said I was
scared
I just think it's you know a little
unsettling how we're going to be
cruising through space in a glorified
Tin Can
glorifies to see you again dummy that's
what it's supposed to do it's freaking
old I don't think there's anything
strange about it well maybe you're the
one with the problem then it hasn't been
maintenance for 300 years I think we can
trust red and Technology
think got me to Dana in one piece
remember
oh that's a good point maybe it was a
throwaway style should be okay don't you
agree law
hard to argue with that seeing how you
hitched a ride in one of these things
before Alvin
it's just wrong okay
oh my God
[Music]
is chicken
no no hold on
I get it
one room just you and me I need
something to eat
okay excuse me
actually now that you mention it not at
all these starships are a remarkably
smooth ride all things considered
nothing like being at Sea thank goodness
glad to hear it
that device there Cuts your eye huh I
was just wondering what it is it looks
big enough to fit a person inside of it
it's a healing pot you wonder if it
could two people
people
it fixes injuries and illnesses
oh you don't say
that should definitely come in handy if
any of us get injured while we're down
there
alphan was it something I said
no I
was just thinking back to when I escaped
leningus sure that's what you were
thinking about the ceremony and losing
control sure that was a total mess
mayori laid me inside here
so you're saying you got in this thing
straight after escaping but that mean
you were inside for 300 years
Yes sounds crazy I know
but don't even ask me why I stayed
asleep all that time
that's definitely quite some lion all
right it was hibernating but still
or not speaking of bears
wait for it I sure am glad that it's
this Century that you finally woke up in
what do you mean with the amount of
fighting we've done we would have never
made it this far without you
and not only that but
minute
can you recall back to what it is that I
said to you back when we left menacea
about the dream of coexistence and
needing to learn what it entailed yeah
of course
that's why you came with us right to
learn what you couldn't at home
even in that time I was well aware that
what I was living was a lie but at the
same time I also felt really compelled
to fulfill my brother's wishes I'll
always remember him fondly
but the coexistence we're fighting for
isn't for him
it's for people now and those still to
come
the world's bigger than just menencia
my dream is for all dannins wherever
they might be to be free
if I've learned and the one I'm sorry oh
my God who brought me along was you
Elfin oh I'll forever be grateful to you
you see flirting with me well we're not
out of this Forest just yet you should
probably save your thanks at least until
we've dealt with the red woman
I know
but whatever we find when we get down
there I'm through looking the other way
she is
probably getting a little ahead of
myself huh let's take things one step at
a time
for president
that's what I say
that's what I say okay we gotta go back
to dohalem
um probably never cutscene so I'm not
gonna tell you the bear thing yet
it's just one fact anyway
foreign
before we do that just what exactly
should we expect when we get down there
good question get down
[Music]
thara has a point now that I think of it
I don't know the first thing about
Lennox
I'd like to hear more too
it's been Century since I was last there
and they didn't exactly give me The
Grand Tour
I'm stalling no I'm not stalling no
first and foremost Lennox is
was the base of operations in charge of
the crown contest on Dana of course it
also happens to be a city in its own
right complete with its own independent
Society no we're leaving this special
structure it's based on a strict
hierarchy
put simply the strength of an
individual's astral Arts carries great
weight
enough to determine someone's Social
rank you mean
but astral Arts are innate right so
people's positions are fixed at Birth
they can be honed with the right
training and there are admittedly other
factors at Play
but yes that's basically the gist
as a result family lines that churn out
Lords
[Laughter]
my mom
messaged me
wrote me a whole paragraph
say starting with
your blood results are horrible
[Music]
oh man
oh man oh
she said that the cholesterol is not bad
she has that too
uh uh uh
[Music]
um
what the [\h__\h]
oh
yeah
okay I read the message
so she's watching the Stream
hello Mama
oh it's okay that's just a
not so bad the test probably we gotta
wait for the doctor
contenders wield disproportionate
influence and those lineages are treated
as an ability
those capable of only weekends
denied the right to descend to Dana even
if they wanted to
okay
even the lowest wrong on the running
ladder is considered Superior to being a
Denon keep that in mind down there okay
how about we all just act as if we're
around dohole must have been pretty high
up in the pecking order right hectic
what about you Shion
come on you've seen her skill with Astro
Arts you really need to ask
Fair Point
on Arts alone you're right I'd have been
sitting pretty but you're forgetting my
Thorns they weren't exactly an
invitation to High Society oh
[Music]
but you would uh sorry
no it's fine it's amazing to be around
someone who says what they're thinking
life's less complicated that way
geez give backhanded compliments much
wait a second are you
he is lost blushing
I am not
of course separating people into casts
based on something arbitrary like Arts
his discrimination at its worst
as if such simplistic criteria could
ever be a measure of someone's worth
so this red woman are we expecting to
find her on lineages
I would wager so lenigus is too deeply
involved in all this to discard the
possibility
chances are she's also connected to the
rennis alma being stolen from us in
Collegian
thank you for renewing your membership
at all costs
that red woman's got a lot to answer for
just as well I've got a ton of questions
me too
The Descent could be a little bumpy so
brace yourselves
okay clues about your thorns
sit down
such a cute little butt down
my lasagna intake is not that high okay
chill
[Music]
oh you're coming out of the egg oh
welcome thank you for renewing your
membership
I don't want to wear my seatbelt I'm
going to put you into the usual room if
you don't wear it
it's on your own safety
oh
for chuckle
now
Mass Effect here you go guys for
everyone who wanted me to play a mass
effect and Bioshock and all that here
you go there you go um here's my present
to you
oh I wasn't expecting
infrastructure is largely automated
besides people won't be expecting
incoming traffic while the crown contest
is still underway that's a cool
spaceship
do you think anyone realizes that we're
here
[Music]
you may not have received a royal
welcome but I doubt our entrance went
unnoticed don't let your guard down
I really hope we don't have to fight
anybody while we're here
I doubt this is not gonna happen you've
come all this way on a hunch that this
red woman is here right
and if we're lucky the rennis alma too
any idea where we should start looking
nope
nope there is an area of the city that
is accessible only to the sovereign
that seems as good a place as any for us
to start
oh
from our ocean what are they hiding
I don't know hence my desire to find out
fortunately we just so happen to have a
sovereign in our midst
yes we do
in any case changing the shape of a huge
question would have required an immense
source
and you think that Source might have
been the renaissoma
precisely
Alvin said that he remembered the
Renaissance being used in the spirit
channeling ceremony three centuries ago
[Music]
whatever the ceremony's purpose if
preparations are underway for it to be
held once more
then the Renaissance Alma might be in
the same place as last time possibly
together with the red woman
hiding something of that worth in the
residential quarters would only Court
trouble
in which case
it stands to reasons somewhere normally
out of bed cool here is that it
the air is so clean
but it's been over 300 years since I was
made of sovereign
you can't seriously think I'll be able
to waltz right into the place after all
this time
[Music]
there's only one way to find out
if there's even a chance you can get us
in I say we give it a shot
right who knows we might even find a
clue to her Thorns while we're at it
all right
it's not like we're swimming in leads so
let's try to track down the forbidden
zone
coconut cookies
this is what I meant when talking about
on the other side cow tales off games
kind of at some point always like go
very very big like they they go into
like space and they go into different
dimensions and [\h__\h]
where you feel like you're not on this
world anymore
thinking about what could be lurking out
here is giving me the heebie-jeebies
that's a loudmouth you sure can be a
worry word my reward what's going on oh
I'm sorry how stupid
please would you two children stop
squabbling everyone to know we're here
what are these choices of words so how
many renins actually live in this place
I couldn't tell you exactly though not
as many as you might expect machines and
zugals take care of most of the city's
basic functions
there's zoogles out here too huh
sounds like we can't afford to let our
guard down after all
everywhere
oh it was that
just my way to go back okay
I can go back anytime that's so nice of
them of the Renaissance to let me go
whenever the hell I want oh can I really
though probably not
probably after I enter maybe then that's
because you guys said I'll be stuck for
a little while
hmm
as hello sorry fine Jordan it's me again
have you missed me
oh what the [\h__\h] oh they are very uh
preoccupied
it seems
what
[Music]
uh
the city is uh falling apart
the music is beautiful yeah do you hear
this should I make it louder
oh
[Music]
well thank you Linda I'm glad you
enjoyed it
it's being run in territory I was
prepared for a lot of things to look
different but this this is a bit more
than I anticipated the very foundations
of the city have shifted
what could have caused this yeah what
happened
when lennogus changed shape it must have
had an effect on the interior too Paul
maybe when they sent the wedge down to
Dana but they wouldn't move around the
places where people live
these are their homes right
I would think the citizens themselves
didn't have much say in the matter
either way locating the forbidden zone
just became that much trickier
is that you uh yeah
who is asking
um
I'm glad to see you're well uh he looks
so it is you but why are you here
shouldn't you be down on Dana
participating in the crown contest and
these people so you haven't heard what
happened on Dana then
her what they don't know
and they don't recognize us someone you
know
an old friend
hey dohalem don't tell me you've started
keeping company they're with me more
importantly what's happened here
uh I'm really not sure the city's
foundations began to shift without
warning and now everything looks like
this we're all waiting for the Sovereign
to tell us what's happening but so far
avakir listen to me we're looking for
the forbidden zone do you have any idea
where we might find it
is could you possibly have there trust
me you can't go there unless you know
the better
they're just the same as ever dummy
dummy I wish I could help but what with
the change topography I can barely
locate my own home
let alone the forbidden zone very well
it looks like we'll have to find the way
there ourselves it has an interesting
accent yeah I've noticed have you seen
fario yet
hi
no girlfriend
he's Crush
well nothing much has changed with her
if anything she's probably even more
I can well imagine oh
why did you come back Crazy
Ex-Girlfriend
you know
[Music]
you really are the same as ever
fine I understand just don't say I
didn't warn you
and take care of yourself okay though
foreign
I'm just gonna act as if I didn't read
that stuff
[Music]
stupid chat so who's foreign
they seem to be just as clueless about
what's going on up here in their own
world
despite the fact that it's actually here
that the wedge originally came from bunk
we need more information
see what we can find out while we're at
it we could ask them about the red woman
too and don't forget about finding the
way to the forbidden zone either
let's leave the talking to xion we can't
have a bunch of dannins poking their
noses around
good idea I think that's for the best
I shall assist
you sure
being a lord on lanigas has its
advantages
right can I leave it to YouTube
move movements among us should probably
keep our heads down what if people freak
out I shall explain it away by saying
I'm leading you what are we dogs
Atlantic is done for the residential
quarters falling apart
oh no
Oh no you're all gonna die you [\h__\h]
I think it could be so important
it's worth destroying people's
livelihoods and homes in the process
it's just
unbelievable uprooting an entire city as
if it were mere building blocks
someone's got an awful lot of questions
to answer
from how it looks they must be siphoning
off astral energy from Dana and then
sending it to Rena
but why do all this what for
surely they can't be using all that
energy for the crown contest
whatever their purpose disrupting their
siphoning process alone won't be
sufficient not while we still don't know
what their end game is
right we need to stop this from
happening ever again
this forbidden zone might be where we
find some answers right so what are we
waiting for what you're waiting what to
win
so anyway about the bear
and there's another skin
uh we have to talk to these NPCs huh
I can't talk about the bear yet but you
know what I can do
I'm gonna grab some chocolate
[Music]
you guys
I wasn't sure if I wanted to bring
chocolate or chunky so I brought both
hi okay bye-bye
junkies just woke up
issue
[Music]
what an unspeakable mess this has all
become just look at the state of our
city and even the zoo girls have stopped
heeding our commands
whatever did we do to deserve this you
really have no clue what might have
caused this
[Music]
what did I have at last there was no
warning no prior decree His Highness
must have deemed it unnecessary for us
to know he doesn't give a [\h__\h] about you
guys we have no choice but to grin and
inherit
thank you as well could I really be
his lordship no haleem of the house ill
courage indeed bow down to you Lord
the rise do not deceive you it is I one
in the same I have returned to fulfill a
special Duty the details of which I
cannot divulge
as your lordship wishes first lanigus
mutates beyond recognition now this
unexpected visit the sovereign's plans
are inscrutable indeed
house has produced a great many lords
over the centuries I shall be praying
for your victory in the latest Crown
Contest no thank you
your good wishes do me an honor I
[Music]
has that news not reached them
that only animals are dead and he's the
only one left alive
I guess they don't know
[Music]
so I've been wondering do you think
we're probably better that way it was
even made with people living here in
mind
what do you mean well none of this
happened by coincidence right they must
have designed it to transform like this
but then if they knew people were going
to live here you'd think they would have
taken that into consideration to avoid
all this chaos
ordinarily yes you'd think so trust me
as far as we were concerned lenigus was
our home nothing more no one knew about
all this
and makes you wonder whether the city
was just built on as an afterthought but
if so
to what exactly
sorry that probably sounded weird huh
the way who looks at her oh my God I
want someone to look at me the way who
looks at ring well I hope you notice
what you've been missing all along
this place is a mystery that's for sure
something tells me we'll find answers
where we're going though
yeah you're right xion I'm sure we will
can you guys look at me like that
in a way who looks at rinwell
it's so cute
oh I need to heal someone also
oh
I don't know man
is that gonna help my karma or something
because I mean
but it's an old lady but even all ladies
can be very very evil you know
um
should I leave her to die
I don't know
I don't wanna but
now you guys are looking at me like that
no and that one is a bit scary the one
with the two big eyes no no no no
sorry stop being heartless what
these people are heartless
oh my ears never have I seen such potent
cheering Arts thank you so much for
taking the time to help an old woman
like me no
okay
would be okay now
I know the basics of Healing Arts but my
skills pale in comparison yes I do yes
they do
sugar your lordship oh what a great
honor it is to finally meet you
I descended to Dana during the last
Crown contest also alas when the
contender I was backing failed to clinch
the title I returned
I witnessed the deaths of so many slaves
well indeed it doesn't feel too happy
about interrupt but we're looking for a
woman dressed all in red have you seen
anyone of that description
already no I can't say I remember anyone
like that I imagine she'd Stand Out
somewhat too they probably don't see her
yeah
what about down on Dana during the crown
contest you didn't see anyone like that
hanging around
what's with all these questions I've
never seen her okay not recently or
otherwise why do you want to find her
anyway
never mind forget I asked sorry to take
up your time
the way you guys look at me right now is
creepy stop it
[Music]
um
gonna take some pictures for Instagram
just one moment
yeah working great work it
yes girl
beautiful
[Music]
is everything okay you look a little
lost she has two points oh yes I can't
seem to find my way home is all I was
just about to make my umpteenth attempt
at a new route
I was hoping to head this way myself
situation is a real pain huh
suppose The Sovereign Knows Best
that sounds like
she owns voice actress trying to do a
different voice
no
like a cute voice hi Darren stay here
too long though a lower cath can only
linger around these parts for so long
before I outstay my welcome it totally
does I was hoping to avoid it but maybe
I'll have to go that way after all
you mean you know another way around
[Music]
but how last I heard you were in Dana
competing in the crown contest yes
strange isn't it if you know another
route we don't hear it you could tell us
hmm But but of course please forgive me
I know too much ahead of here oh it
looks to be an entrance in it I thought
maybe it was a passageway between the
different quarters but I have no way of
knowing for sure you could go for real
it's worth investigating at least
no way
you sure you have no way of knowing for
sure
do you have like wait you could go
through
I shall go and assess the situation in
the meantime wait for me here if it
looks safe I'll come and let you know
really do that for me
troubling himself
our lot in life is of little consequence
we are both renin first and foremost
no no no we are both human first and
foremost that's what you should say
what the hell
you've canvas the city for information
what do you think go through that big
hole just idea what's happened to the
city that's always the light they
haven't heard the news about the crown
contest either uh-huh you you'd think
that info would easily find its way up
here has it always been like that not to
this extent
which would indicate that something's
suppressing the truth that lennicus is
under some kind of control even
everything that's happened to their City
the people here seem weirdly okay with
it all yeah that one guy even said
zoogle had stopped listening to him if
that's true these people are in big
trouble
everything that happens here is
attributed to the sovereign's will
it's the way people have been
conditioned their belief runs deep
nothing happens devoid of a reason to
them it's all part of the sovereign's
grand plan The Sovereign
there is one thing I'm still not sure
about
just who is this person ruling over
lenigus
The Sovereign of course he rules from
Rena while presiding over both Rena and
lennogus
without the Lords or anyone in the
middle doing his dirty work isn't Rena
at least the same size as Danna
that's a pretty big Dominion for one
person to rule over I would have thought
ruling lenigus alone would be difficult
enough
points you make are valid though I
confess I'd never given it much thought
before here the sovereign's total
Authority is as natural as night turning
today
come to think of it I know nothing of
the nature of how Rena itself is
Shion have you ever been no forgive me
have you met or crossed paths with or
even heard of someone who's actually
made a visit to the Homeland
no I haven't who neither have I
in which case
I would imagine that but no surely not
can it really be that no citizen of
lanigas has ever been there
hold up what are you getting at dohalem
assuming what I believe to be correct
possible that no one on lanigas has ever
laid eyes on the actual renin Homeworld
itself
no one but the Sovereign that is well
but what about trade and communication
there's got to be a flow back and forth
surely
not if the Sovereign is imposing his
will on Lanigan single-handedly
could be a one-way Street
I thought you said that the sovereigns
all the way over on Rena
directly over lenigus from so so far
away
what if something were to happen to the
city like now
I'm beginning to wonder what the nature
of this Sovereign even is
alfin said he was forced into the role
right just before the ceremony
but Sovereign is also the title given to
the almighty renin ruler so which one is
it
whoever wins the crown contest inherits
the throne from his or her predecessor
before becoming ruler over all of Rena
and lennogus
thereafter that individual is known as
the sovereign though
it would appear that the current ruler
has gone silent yeah as for how volran
factors into all this
at this point I no longer know what to
believe
three centuries ago I became the
Sovereign here on lineages
just became I was forced to me a Dannon
300 years later we cross paths with
volran who also Bears the sovereign's
crest
that's not the only thing we have in
common
we both became Sovereign without winning
the crown contest
I think Vol Ron was made Sovereign for
the same reason
ceremony oh I can't say for sure
certainly sounds like it but that would
mean that two sovereigns would need to
exist at any one time
one whose job it is to rule and the
other for ceremonial purposes we never
did see Vol Ron's body back in Kenneth
Heros
is a new ceremony underway with Vol Ron
at its Center this time could that be
what's causing all this strange activity
here wait a second you don't think
volran and the red woman are working
together do you the ceremony can't go
forward without the Renaissance Alma the
same one that the red woman stole
or something else the ceremony needs a
maiden and unless there's another one
out there aside from me
questions questions and yet more
questions
ones that it seems will remain
unanswered
the sovereign's identity no no no if the
forbidden zone really is off limits to
everyone but the sovereign seems as good
a place as any to start for the sake of
liberating Dana too
that it's decided that's where we need
to go
one of the citizens mentioned the
passage that she thought might lead to
another section of the city it could
point us in the right direction
let's go find it
it's right there it's literally right
there
it's here
[Music]
if nobody left to run the show I wonder
what the people here are supposed to do
they're talking so much
I don't have a problem with it right now
but I do want to say the bear thing it's
so stupid when we were in the car
we were listening to the radio and then
there was a news reporting that that in
Canada
um a lady put out pumpkins you know
because Halloween and then you know
Bears apparently love pumpkin so putting
out uh pumpkins in Canada is a bad idea
so the bear
like when it was apparently captured and
unsecurity footage
security camera footage and the bear
came to her house and ate the pumpkins
and was apparently really cute but yeah
I heard that story I thought it was cute
I don't know I just wanted to share
I wanted to ask if it's true
if there's lots of bears roaming around
looking for pumpkins
cute good sorry right thank you it's not
even my story
well there was just snowmen there
pumpkin
it is kind of terrifying but it sounds
like a really peaceful encounter because
probably they haven't encountered it was
just the lady was inside I guess
Indian things I mean there's sovereigns
up on the run and Homeworld and all
their Lords were sent to Dana
but dohalem was a lord right only
current acting Lords have power
renin Society is quite strict about such
matters even if the other Lords were
around I doubt they'd be able to do much
about the situation I wonder what they
think if they were here to see lineages
now balsif cannabelt almadria and Vol
Ron now that I think of it aside from
dohalim we know next to nothing about
the other Lords well yeah why would we
to us we were just enemies we needed to
overthrow yeah nothing more yeah I know
seeing renins in their own City going
about their day-to-day lives
get you thinking it feels strange to
imagine the Lords living here too yeah a
little if you're that curious about them
why not try inquiring with some of the
locals every Lord in their household has
their share of supporters here on
lenigus and luckily for us the people
here are unaware of the events on Dana
which means they should be more inclined
to talk to us
oh is that a side quest
[Music]
oh I guess it is and where is it is it
how can people support the Lord okay
okay okay okay okay hello
[Music]
you want to know who who is
say till tell dilis
all right Lord bounce them oh we killed
him we killed him dude I'm sorry
um
but to improve the static of each and
every member of his house yes
okay you have bad taste
balseff headed in him to care about
someone other than himself
trust him a change in position can do
much to alter one's perspective
hey she on point 2.0
oh she probably likes to call him
[Music]
oh oh she's a simp for dual Helen
die ski
oh thank you may believe it's more than
snowmen and bears and Canada there's
also maple syrup and poutine birthplace
of Hawaiian what really you guys are
geniuses I love you Canadian bacon and
those damn Canadian geese
no I know that there's way more than
than you know bears and stuff there yeah
yeah I know I know and I really I'm
interested I'm intrigued I want to visit
Canada
you guys have a very good image in my
head especially because of handmaid's
Tale
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
I guess she intended to spread it
throughout all of Lent
good thing the lines were down so she
couldn't it almost sounded like is that
true though Hawaiian pizza maybe there
was more to the guy than at first glance
no way why did they call it Hawaiian
pizza
and mixed tail is not real Kiana not yet
what
um
[Music]
I do not care support people okay he was
invested in helping Rena succeed doesn't
that seem just a little inconsistent
because they are all perhaps biased in
this matter I admit however in my mind
while all Lords Vie to become the next
sovereign they're also meant to serve as
guardians of all of Rena
seems like Annabelle also had people he
cared about until the very end so why
couldn't he extend that to our standings
assistant I want to listen to this okay
I didn't realize red and suppressed
their own kind too
and yet weirdly none of them seem to
mind um the only one who finds that
strange
is the way things have always been so no
one thinks to question it you have
experience in that regard yourself
oh roasted questioning acceptance of
your own servitude
pineapple juice even so the quality of
life here seems much higher than any
Danon City we visited I used to think it
was impossible to build an ideal Society
without wealth
but I suppose having it doesn't always
mean people are treated fairly either
more to the point not a single citizen
seems to have even heard of the red
woman what if she's not here what if it
turns out we're looking in the room
still too early to say anything for sure
I say we hold off judgment until we've
exhausted every Avenue why I'm very much
okay thank you for asking the art of
conversation listen up everyone this is
it
[Music]
tell me dohalem has that skill of yours
got a name
and what skill would this be pray tell
oh my God
you know when you're talking to people
around town the way they suddenly become
putty in your hands
I'm afraid I don't quite follow
I do it's called friendly intimidation
look imposing and speak in a deep
booming dominance you'll have people
Wrapped Around Your Finger in no time oh
I would never stoop to such scandalous
tricks any feelings of intimidation are
solely in the eye of the beholder okay
so there is a knack to it
can anyone do it
now you've got me curious is there
special training to master
hmm let's see an obsession with being
elegant is a must oh and it helps to be
old-fashioned too bonus points if you
speak in a way no one can understand if
you have a bone to pick with me in
elegant German from now on they look up
to you that's all I'm just helping them
along
hey let's cut into Alvin and law all of
a sudden
I can barely understand a word they're
saying what's with the weird poses was
it something they ate
I hope you're willing to take the blame
for this one I wasn't expecting them to
take me so seriously I'll go and have a
word with them
interesting
[Music]
wait what about the side quests would
like uh would I give it back to
[Music]
it's not then
I guess maybe it continues on the other
side
bridle
hey let's walk through here see what we
got on that side
[Music]
oh it's Striker Pals
oh this area doesn't look as badly
damaged yeah I wanted to say that just
now indeed the effects of lenigus's
transformation appear to be less
pronounced here or viewed another way
this area was simply luckier wow
wow
looking good here
you want to tell me something
who's your favorite Lloyd pardon me
she's mad
huh
I must ask you to depart at once nah
hell no
madria
she did
she did though
no more house whatever I guess her
willingness to stoop to any love came
from a survival of the fittest worldview
and some people here not only shared her
belief but championed it as morally
right too
that doesn't make it true
too bad they couldn't see through her
yeah
okay a grandpa Grandpa
what you doing here
ridiculous
oh I was just reading about Bull Run can
I help you okay you a woman fan
I was always an artist supporter of Lord
Aura Gil hillarys myself worried not for
his sudden death down on the surface I
likely so would be in my eyes Lord
Oracle is the true water lord I don't
believe for a second that he perished in
some accident like they say oh okay as
for helpful and run scan of Harris don't
get me started I hear he enslaves not
only dannon's but even his fellow red
hints
we may live in a society
where to the Victor gold spoils when his
actions go against what we as people
stand for besides just what sort of
family line is just how sickness area of
is anyway
I never heard of it until he came along
which means they must be among the lower
Shreks of society
that's such an ignorable lineage could
suddenly produce an astral artist
capable of ascending to the lordship is
unheard of
foreign
either
Pharaoh's changed so abruptly
something suspicious
remember we renins are raised to accept
it thank you everyone
so adapted all of you say it in German
these days when you think about it the
families of running Lords must see them
differently than the rest of us yeah
despite the brutality they're known for
not because of the cat here people see
sometimes on their shoulders carrying
all the weight and responsibilities of
run in society renins live in a world
where strength and power determine their
position in the social hierarchy so they
tend to grow up fiercely competitive
but their loyalty to their people is
also strong
I think this is the longest in the whole
game that I've uh
went through without fighting
more than the Lords
that's what makes them the Guardians of
all of Rena so to speak
guess that makes you an even bigger
Oddball than we thought
so alfin have you gained anything from
all of this
yeah
I think it's made me realize that the
Lords were all people too
maybe that's because I skipped
everything they all had their own
circumstances they went through life
yeah but still just because they had
loved ones in their lives doesn't mean
I know what they did was horrible I'm
trying to dispute that
but at the same time they weren't
incomprehensible monsters either uh no
they are individuals
so I guess what I'm trying to say is
you're saying that they weren't bad
because they were renins or because they
were terrible monsters
but even if they did Terrible Things
they were still just people they were
terrible people though when well what
the [\h__\h] am I wrong
not at all being a denim doesn't make
you a good person and being a lemon
doesn't make you a bad one
I think that's something we've all seen
Shion and dohalem definitely make a good
case for it
to make sure I earn that trust as a
fellow human being Above All Else
how
[Music]
okay
okay maybe that wasn't me because I
skipped most of the text but still like
what no you can't just justify all of
that now
the service are caught up they have
nowhere to run now what
it's amazing to see how those of us with
only weak Arts can still do this when we
all come together what are you talking
about
oh yeah
keep it up team we'll have these pests
taking care of in no time
[Music]
never in all my years here on lineages
has anything like this ever happened not
even once there's always been a decree
before anything takes place Not only was
there not this time but the residential
quarter has seen damage and injuries
it's possible
[Music]
there's something I just don't get what
what is it Nani the crown contest itself
has always gone ahead as planned right
in which case the current Sovereign of
Rena should be whoever it was that won
the previous contest yeah
yeah that makes sense
so who was it then
freaked milgroth the former Lord of
cislodia if memory serves oh so then
this Han freaked whatchamacallum
the last I heard yes though admittedly I
haven't actually seen him since the end
of the previous contest
you're saying that ever since becoming
Sovereign he's never actually shown
himself on lennogus he's dead I guess
over holocaum maybe but not in the flesh
now that you mention it I don't recall
anyone ever visiting lennogus from the
motherland he became a YouTuber and that
never struck you as a little bit odd
when you live here it's as if you're
conditioned not to notice all these
strange quirks a lot of weird things
Yeah by whom and to what end
Alma is supposedly created to coincide
with every Crown contest meaning each
Victor is awarded their very own oh in
other words if that's true there should
be as many of the things out there as
there have been contests
true but going on what we witnessed in
Collegian it didn't look like the sort
of thing that could be made to order but
there is only one man is Alma because
all of those people who became
who won the crown contest before are now
dead so they don't need more than one
Reno's Elmo
and stand and stand just listen to me I
got it all figured out I got it all
right if even the Victor's speeches have
been part of some Grand deception then
where are they
quite frankly I'm not even sure what to
believe anymore
you and me both though we are running by
Blood neither of us even knew that such
a thing as a dark Master Core existed
remember
with any luck the forbidden zone might
give us some answers
no you standing around here chatting
about it then let's get a move on
uh wait where did I
left should I go left I'll go left
hidani
[Music]
um
this place has similar Vibes to previous
tales of places and I've seen
dough
dope dope Faria okay
isn't that the person that avakir guy
was
but why are you here wait okay don't
tell me you've given up on the crown
contest and come crawling back home from
Dana already shut up
it's over
nothing to say
even though you were willing to kill
tarnigan to secure your position as Lord
you still kill
I'm here to take care of something if
you wish to continue this conversation I
only ask that you wait until I'm
finished
oh of course
you always did prefer to take the
coward's way out
even after seven years and living on
that Dan and rock you haven't changed
one bit
but let me tell you I haven't changed
either not a day's gone by the past
seven years that I haven't hated you
[\h__\h] you
killing me will bring you peace and and
so be it dohalim what the hell are you
saying first I have business to take
care of if it's Vengeance you seek I
will grant you it
but you must wait
my sins are legion let me finish what I
came to do then you have my word I will
let you do whatever brings you peace
hmm
sure that's it run away like always you
don't even have the courage to die no
wonder you leave it to someone else
the hell is wrong
you're just a coward
uh
oh
hahaha
turn around turn around turn around
dolim
I apologize that you had to witness that
is it true
about you killing someone
each of us have our pasts I am no
exception
before back in meningca you mentioned
having taken a friend's life over the
throne
is that what she meant
the mistakes I made there were not my
first and may not be my last I will say
no more
did you mean what you said
about letting her take your life if she
wanted to
she has more right to my life than
anyone oh but you can't just how
whatever happens I have sworn to put an
end to the crown contest and to ensure
continued coexistence in menacea I have
no intention of expiring before I do so
there are far too many questions I still
seek answers to
besides you have just as much reason to
kill me as she does
forgive me
some things are best left unsaid
[Music]
that is true
I agree with that
um is that girl dead now
is she dead now
[Music]
so I liked the music that played when
suddenly she
was uh on camera I was like
oh
excuse me like a
water art
yeah
oh what's down here
oh
and Fire
ball oh
Google did not give a [\h__\h]
the fire had no effect on the Google
she's getting roasted and roasted
okay
toasty doggy
[Music]
you missed that detail there you go
that's what I'm here for
I skip a lot of the details but then
wait did I was right here before but
then I also show you a lot of the
details nope I was down here before
okay looks familiar
you guys will play or know the child
no why can I not help this one why can I
only help selected people
ah
I want to help the child
help has nothing to do with all this
[Music]
crazy how long is this going
I don't know normally we would have had
orders from the top breasts and forming
all the separate classes what they need
to do I doubt that's happening the whole
chain of command in this city seems like
it's broken down nobody knows what's
happening that doesn't mean someone
somewhere isn't watching our every move
oh believe me they are watching you
they are watching you red woman is
everywhere
[Music]
is that like the
castle here or something like that
oh
oh what's going on there
do you need help
oh I can't help you what are you doing
[Music]
oh
funny
they're trying to put out the fire
and wonder who started the fire today
couldn't have possibly been me right I
was somewhere else I have an alibi
maybe it was a chicken though
my chickens are partially arsonists I'm
sorry I couldn't stop them they're
Unstoppable they do what they want they
stream Sparks
because they wanna
[Music]
wow this place is beautiful yeah oh yeah
there must be some sort of rest and
Leisure area for the locals
you think man you know it reminds me a
little bit of that
um area from Texas cilia tool
where Jude what's his name Jude
studied I think or somewhere somewhere
there oh and these red and sure know how
to live
halim
Jude was it right I keep on forgetting
names but this one I didn't forget
we used to gather at this very spot and
play music together
um avakir Faria and tarnigan
that was a lifetime ago now
tarnigan
he was the one that Faria mentioned
right
he was once my dearest closest friend
as well as far as that's why she's so
mad
because he killed her this lower class
well she possesses a tremendous talent
for music
entranced by her playing
I helped her overcome her sense of
inferiority
and introduced her to tarnigan and
avakira
it was a time of great joy
four people bound only by their love of
music with no care for social standing
only the next song the next Melody
that was such a creepy cutscene back
then
a friendship based on mutual respect and
a society where everyone is a prisoner
to their social class
you really are different dolim
I suppose it's natural you would see it
as strange
I would have once
now
I think the idea of breaking away from
society's constraints and choosing your
friends based solely on affection is
something beautiful that's worth
cherishing
besides it was that way of looking at
the world that laid the foundations for
coexistence in menansia
praise doesn't mean too great in honor I
was merely following the wishes of my
own heart
and even then
it only lasted until the crown contest
began
after that
tarnigan and I became Fierce competitors
for the position of Lord
tarnigan had fallen for Faria by
becoming Lord he aimed to rest her from
her humble Origins and raised her to the
highest echelons of society nice but
fate was not so benevolent
what happened
tarnigan was no match for me in combat
on a Level Playing Field he wouldn't
have stood a chance
but he was desperate and low on options
and he couldn't stand the thought of
defeat
you mean he resorted to dirty tactics to
try to win right
but then why does Faria think
wait
don't tell me she doesn't know
who could I tell her combined with the
trauma of losing her beloved and by her
friend's hand no less
she would have been devastated
so instead you let her go on hating you
so she could use that hate as a crutch
for her grief
that's not the same as running away
though it is exactly the same unable to
face the loss of my friend and the
burden of my duty instead I decried my
fate and looked away from what I'd done
as for what happened after
that you already know
but if you hadn't become Lord menencia
wouldn't be what it is now
that dannon's there would still be
suffering under renin oppression like
before
she owns right
what other Lord would have treated me as
you did
anyone else and I would have been dead
long ago
you've saved so many people dohalem
you saved me it's thanks to you that I'm
here today I love you
so try not to blame yourself the burden
you've placed on your own shoulders is
too much for anyone to bear
Frank as always
I shall do my best to heed your advice
that goddamn Frank
he'll be all right stupid yeah I think
so he's got kisara
it's important to have someone like that
I didn't realize how difficult it is
just to be there for someone
sometimes just
someone's on your side can be enough and
he knows Shion
I promise he does hmm
I hope you're right
[Music]
her hands are pretty big
wait what are you looking at what are
you looking at you're stalking us
I never appreciated until recently just
how much you were always there to
support me
keep going
keep going oh there's an in here I still
wanted to say
thank you oh I see a medic and Supply
officer over there well it looks nice
[Music]
it look nice cute yeah
foreign
okay well do we need to sleep we have
full HP right
but not full CP
[Music]
m
I guess we can cook what should we cook
should we do another exp boost I'm I'm
guessing we're not going straight into
the boss fight so
might be might be good
that's the last small dungeon
accessory
yo guys if I end the stream today here
um
I'll probably be alone on making proper
accessories later on
I need your advice
on the ranch accessories
foreign
[Music]
you know you couldn't make a video like
like before you know what I got this
Mario Kart video telling me how to be a
proper driver
[Music]
um
oh
you got some nice armor there did you
get it upgraded soldiers we can avoid
biting them we don't need to it's on
them fight whatever happens be ready I
got an exp boost for a reason
it's been a while so much for them
I Am Lord dohalem of Elder menacea I
command you threat to the city must be
erased no
they've been brainwashed too brainwashed
or not if they wanna so we've
established uh we've established a
brainwashing as a fact now okay
wait I made the audio a little bit
quieter
in a bind
ER
oh wait there's four
no casting allowed here
[Music]
that's freaking rude
oh my God these are strong
this is how it's gonna be
strong
they're like I mean not strong but very
buff very defensive
ouch
thank you I was waiting for that
break it
[Music]
yes
oh wait I'm over limited I didn't
realize
make a preset while you play in the last
part oh that's a good idea
but like I don't I don't I don't know
like maybe I reserve the free day a day
off for that
I would think that would just
spontaneously decide when to play and
who knows if I have a pre-chat open at
that moment
[Music]
interesting girl good idea I can ask you
questions different from the citizens
we've come across so far and give you my
my feelings they weren't big talkers
that's for sure they just attacked
without warning
they weren't in the least bit faced by
dohalem's presence either
there will be no like later on streaming
of the ending no
um even if they were to one year later
be like yo now you can't stream the
ending
I feel like that would make no sense
like
our we're not our immersion is ruined at
that point it's gone
and I don't want to wait that long
either
to show that to you guys and it will
just be too much of a
Gap in between
I don't know it makes no sense and I'm
just gonna finish it on my own and enjoy
it while playing alone
yeah because that's um
at least
um gives me a different kind of
enjoyment being able to enjoy such a
beautiful beautiful gorgeous game
by myself
they seem to recognize us as enemies
nothing more
and yet
um yes I don't I like we have
permissions for a couple of other Tales
of games as far as I know and I haven't
heard yet of any limitations on those so
as far as I know I think we had
permission for uh castle sparia and
hysteria before and I could probably get
more permissions if I were where to ask
and I think this one just really has
that limitation because it's the newest
one out there and
um they put a lot of uh work into the
marketing and promotion of the game so
which obviously I am part of and uh
therefore one part of promoting and
marketing the game is not letting people
stream it until the end there's a reason
for that they'll obviously I guess they
wanna want you guys to buy it and play
the end on your own with funny thing is
that most of my chat has already done
that
the effect already worked earlier didn't
even need me to get to that point of uh
Cliffhanger most of most of the people
watching here got the game because of me
and enjoyed it and loved it and played
it until the end
yay thank you guys you are awesome
traditionally lennogus hasn't been high
on threats
a few friends it's fine to me though
honestly it's fine but not much else
um I don't mind it at all I mean okay
yeah I wouldn't have I wouldn't have
minded to have this this amazing moment
in the end where we were like oh my God
we finished this journey this was so
great yeah yeah I feel this and that and
this and that yeah what an ending oh my
God cry cry cry of course that would
have been great
but still uh we still had a nice Journey
up until now okay
and
it was not only the playthrough it was
also
four streams four separate promotional
streams leading up to all of this
so there has been a lot of tales of
arise content on my channel in the past
few months and past few months yeah so I
think it's it's good to cut it off uh
now soon today so that we can also move
on and do other things it's been a long
long trip
and for me personally like in my private
time I wouldn't mind playing Tesla games
every every freaking day
because I love them so much but it's
also good to as a streamer for my
YouTube channel to cut it off here and
then do other things for me I I see you
it's in a positive way
the ones in blind Devotion to vulron now
back to topic never seen anything like
that here on Lennox before
maybe someone doesn't want us here and
the soldiers are their way of letting us
know
starting to develop quite the growing
list of adversaries
at least we'll know to keep our wits
about us Kyle need to go to another Idol
meeting I wonder how short this place is
this dungeon but at the end we probably
have to fight something being great
um
oh my oh hello you got some cute Wings
flat flop
flap flap
cute
oh yeah yesterday I made I made Japanese
Curry for the first time in a million
years
I have like a lot of those uh Curry
cubes
that you get in Japan
yeah
Curry so Japanese Curry is so easy to
make with those cubes man
so easy
[Music]
foreign
I have a lot of them left over still
like from different brands and all that
like first of all when I left Japan
uh in what's February or so I brought a
lot of those
with me that I have yet to use
and they were they're not like
um
the expiration date they're not expired
yet so
edible and then while I was at docomo
jenma also brought me a bunch of
Curry cubes and other things
so I am stuck sucked up
Daddy's car is so easy guys you
basically you cut up and the meat you
cut up and by the way any meat is like
Japanese Curry works with any meat works
with chicken meat
with beef with pork anything really
maybe not fish though
so yeah you cut up the onions and the
meat and the carrots usually
and potatoes that's those are the basic
main ingredients
I think you could put some other things
in there too but that's just a classic
crafting material classic way you just
cut it up into bite-sized chunks
doesn't have to be anything fancy
no super easy gotta break through
and you can make it in pretty big where
are you going
um
did he ruin my combo no no
no he did I think he did or I ruined it
I don't know
damn it
That's the menu
[Music]
yeah yeah you can make pretty
and big servings
and they say that Japanese Curry
tastes better with each day that it
spins in your fridge
and even if you I think also well if you
warm it up several times it will also
taste better
haha so yeah I still have many leftovers
I made um
uh I used half of the package of the
cubes so that's like six six servings
supposedly
[Music]
oh my God
foreign
[Music]
why do I keep on hitting him with 69
damage
please heal me oh my god
oh again okay this time will I still
mess up we will see now oh oh my God he
ruined my combo I think
around my combo okay
[Music]
I never missed
I'm a piece
oh my God
he is going down
so yeah anyway remember to tell me if
you need healing I expect you'll be in
hiding I was telling you
I'll be eating Curry tonight and
probably tomorrow as well
I'm probably the day after as well if I
don't get already sick of it
I love Japanese Curry taste though like
I remember when when I first came to
Japan
I didn't like it
um I didn't like the taste because I was
used to the typical Thai curry taste my
mom used to make a lot of Thai curry but
she would usually make it not spicy
because I can't take the spiciness can
you take it
I was so used to that taste and Japanese
Curry just tastes so different
but after eating it all a few times I I
really started to like it
it gets even better with all those
toppings
although I'm usually fine with just a
normal Curry because as you know I don't
eat that much
all yours kisara
oh yeah besides those ingredients that I
mentioned I did put some honey into my
Curry because it was recommended on the
package
yeah coming through ah good idea
cut the cooking stream one oh I know how
to make it I mean it's basically a
schnitzel just with a different breading
and the meat is thicker
um
very thin
and I guess it's a different part of the
body that was one problem I had
yesterday
like I don't
cook that much with
or I don't ever cook with beef
um
what I do use a lot is is minced meat
but that's easy right you you don't
really have to think about what what
what mince meat beef well you have to
get
there's no body parts or anything there
but my problem yesterday was like I
didn't know
which part
of the cow body would be most suitable
for the beef in the Japanese Curry
but I wanted it to be beef not chicken
or pork I felt like eating the beef
my mom messaged me something again
so I ended up buying a goulash please
because I thought maybe that's kind of
similar it just said gosh people on the
on the labels I was like okay I know
I know who has beef is like
it's about
any of the other parts of the car like I
don't know how how the beef from the
shoulder really feels like
yeah so I chose Google and and I mean it
was okay but upon eating it in the curry
it did feel different
it's supposed to be way more softer the
goulash meat wasn't really that soft for
some reason
I would have imagined it would be soft I
can become even not gonna know
you know about you see that's good
I actually went on YouTube
beforehand coming through looking at you
know Japanese people cooking Curry like
tutorials
to see what needs to use but every
tutorial that I watched they use uh
either chicken or they use beef but
didn't mention what part of the beef
what part of the clown
s
[Music]
I don't know
don't worry I didn't use chicken I used
our s how are you our enemies
why would I choose chicken when I could
use cow
s
what is a spider I don't know what I'm
doing
no further you're finished
okay if he has a lot of ice enemies
destroy them
[Music]
my mom is trying to
um
uh get me to play Mass Effect but I
think we don't have permissions for Mass
Effect
or was that Bioshock I'm not sure
I'm not sure
if it's EA then it should be fine then
it would Bioshock I guess that we don't
have the permission for her
can't get out of this
how many times am I going to be over
limited oh my God
please try to imply you're gonna kill
yourself
no I haven't heard anything back Scarlet
Inferno unfortunately
I would think that they would be faster
but apparently not oh but there is a
good news like remember when like
Nintendo we had to like ask free
business days in advance for permissions
and that kind of messed up a lot of our
scheduling
that went on for a while
but recently it changed to one day in
advance
and that was already much more useful
but now it's like since yesterday it's
like yo
you don't have to ask in advance anymore
Nintendo likes us
we good now we're good we're good no
need for asking anymore so now we can
have spontaneous gorilla
button [\h__\h] again
yeah
Nintendo song
[Music]
foreign
but like one reason I don't do it was
kind of the whole Nintendo thing like
the games that I would want to do
Nintendo that I would want to do gorilla
would be like Mario Kart and so on
I don't know if I'll really do much more
gorilla from now on but it's at least
nice like for example if that's like if
there's a game that I want to play
that's not Nintendo and it turns out
like one day before Oh [\h__\h] or like half
an hour before oh [\h__\h] I can't play it
then now I could at least like quickly
change the plan to a Nintendo game my my
choices are bigger my Horizon has
widened
yeah that's good
that's pretty good it's like a backup
my backup has grown
yeah
to play Smash Bros sometimes
I have yet to buy and
play Smash Bros on this on the switch
I've only really played it on the
GameCube
gosh I'm gonna be such a noob such a
beginner you guys are going to be like
oh you're so bad Kiana it's gonna take
me a Millions dreams to get decent in it
just like with Maya Cart
you're gonna lose your freaking mind
with me
I owe you
did
is anyone gonna Heal Me anyone anyone no
no
[Music]
no no
no
okay I'll do it myself
oh I'm dead again almost
we have enough CP what's the problem
foreign
that's what I was waiting for not today
are you calling me I haven't show me my
skills here
but yeah I would be [\h__\h] at Super Smash
Brothers the one that I used to play
back then was a Chic Zelda
[Music]
yeah oh I can mine a lot here
oh
um
[Music]
Zelda main here oh teach me teach me
teach me your ways
I'm gonna go this way
hello Ian and ID Super Smash Brothers
I wouldn't mind organizing that
tournament
I honestly wouldn't mind but I've heard
that the penguin can affect stuff like
that pretty bad in the case of Super
Smash Brothers
when people live in different areas and
all that
this game in particular I heard it can
be very frustrating now I don't really
think
it's a [\h__\h] combo
whatever just do the normal one coming
through oh yeah I think all of the
participants wouldn't be that
competitive and therefore wouldn't care
that much
who knows I would have to test it out I
guess to see how bad it really is
carve through it would be sad though to
be like to start the tournament and then
had like I don't know how many
participants
when he participants and then turns out
like one or two
have huge issues keep getting kicked out
and all that that would be just really
really sad
unplayable if you are in different
regions really well then there you go
there you have it if you say it's
unplayable
yeah
pretty bad
well that's the problem because we are
literally all over the world there is a
whole lot of English members who live on
one side of the globe whole life member
who lives in in the middle of the club
and all that members living on the other
side of the globe
so that's problematic
and yes I am in the middle of your rep
is in the middle yes that's how it is
me as well I was shocked when I first
found out that uh
the continent that is in the middle of
the map varies by
where where you are at
I always spot zero everywhere it just
made sense to me
apparently it's not
but I mean if you think of it from a
time zone point of view Europe is in the
middle so
it does make a lot of sense to put
Europe in the middle
um
GMT zero
oh [\h__\h]
you're still think Haley was too late
you might yeah American Nest is
sometimes called Asian pop being
interrupted because there's no space
Europe is the center of the map here too
where are you
post check I'm I'm flattered that you
still think that
the host checks are gonna get me to
actually check and improve my poster if
only it were that easy I swear I would
be I would have the best poster
thank you for trying though thank you
for not giving up on me
huh wait the boosting thing
it's too late this one's mine well I do
drink a lot that's why I need to go to
two other meetings in one spring here
don't worry
too there you go
is
like you
did you see where he hid him
my exploit's a bit I'm also hurt oh
wow that's a lot of money that you guys
got lying around here thank you
um is there gonna be a healing Point
next
I wonder
are we already at the end of the dungeon
oh oh No Maybe not maybe just porting up
I'm Gonna Save anyway because I'm scared
Antonio has the same machine
let's go
yes I bought the chair to help me I
think honestly if it's like shortest
streams uh it will really help me but if
it's long streams like this I can't help
but get into comfy positions oh [\h__\h]
cutscene
but there was no healing point
you're kidding me eh
be it the entrance to the forbidden zone
but it's just a wall how do we get
bamboozle whoa we I thought this was
sovereign's only
Alvin
wait is this it
no
no this is not it this doesn't look like
the screenshot
wait no maybe it does no no it doesn't
ah
money oh
don't
don't end it ended here
yes it opened interesting if alfan's
presence still opens the way it would
seem The Sovereign of three centuries
ago and now are considered one in the
same
wait that what that does look that like
the screenshot that they sent
Jason
[Music]
this is our final boss yeah
often elephant
Shion
Dominos the spirit channeling ceremony
we'll finally play our parts as the
sovereign
this is the first time she speaks
how have you been feeling
what am I Sovereign enough
to lab always treated like an experiment
whenever they look at me all they see is
a Denon I don't even know what the
precious Ceremonies for
let alone what they're going to force me
to do is The Sovereign tell me we're
both in the same boat
why do you seem so calm right now
no choice
becoming the maiden's not something I
wanted for myself
but they they said Rena's Prosperity
depended on it
how could I say no after that
still as a renin at least you got to
decide
good for you
meanwhile I was taken from my homeland
you aren't the captive one here wouldn't
that mean that Shion had the option to
decide as well
to choose
to write what they did to you and I'm
sorry for what it's worth
when this is over I swear I'll help you
get home
I can't do this alone
one more day
how could I say no to that
it's not like I have any choice in the
matter anyway
so
what's your name it's naori nayori I'm
Maris
try to remember this time
you don't act like them
like the other remnants I mean
how come you treat me like a person
because you are
it's true we come from different worlds
but neither one of us asked to be here
right now in that sense you and I are
much the same she does sound like she's
like we couldn't do this peeking we
wouldn't be able to talk to each other
as people
if we didn't see the humanity in each
other
so I suppose the question you should be
asking is why wouldn't I treat you like
one
you're not like the others
maybe they're not like me
she's weird here's what we'll do
we give them their damn ceremony you get
me to Dana
that'll be the end of it
she looks so much like xion I'm trusting
you not them
why would they do that if she's not she
and she's cheating I still believe in
you can't bamboozle me eyes she's she's
still sheon
I am not going to be convinced of
anything else
oh the end is coming
what the hell just happened
that vision
did everyone else on the other side too
that person Alvin was speaking to
she looked exactly like she on
it was naori naori imaris isn't that
right
AKA that's right
she really does look like she on I'm
beginning to see why alfin was so
confused
so very well and fine but what did we
just witness exactly it was too real to
be a mere hallucination
it was a conversation we had 300 years
ago
before the ceremony you mean all of that
really happened
straight out of your past
but how is that even possible unless
could this be the red woman's handiwork
too I'll flick no I don't think so why
not
you guys didn't feel it the moment the
entrance opened it was like a stream of
Dan and astral energy rushing over us oh
I felt it too and not for the first time
either
he was the same sensation as back inside
the wedge
that would make sense after all vast
amounts of Dan as astral energy were
being siphoned and sent up here to
lenigus
for all we know perhaps we're close to
the spot where all that energy was
stored
so you think it might have been the
energy itself that was responsible for
that Vision we just saw but how and why
we have no way of knowing maybe it's not
even as deliberate as all that
Shion you okay
yeah it was all just a little sudden I
that's all
so that was my ancestor huh
I was like looking into a mirror Hmm
Yeah there certainly is a resemblance
what about you
how are you holding up
me
even putting aside the question of where
that Vision came from it's likely we'll
see more of those
reliving painful episodes from your past
do you think you can handle it
I can't just pretend like the past never
happened
besides if it helps us uncover the truth
of what that ceremony really was it
might also lead to answers about your
thorns
that's not all
this whole time we've been fighting to
free Dana from the renins but now that
we're here it seems those same renins
might have it just as bad
I'd like to liberate them too if I can
just another reason I can't afford to
Shield my eyes from the truth
either you're on Dana or somewhere else
you always stay the same
your indignation and righteous passion
your desire to free and protect they're
all hardwired into you
not that I'm complaining come on let's
bust this thing wide open
no let's not do it stay Sharp after that
last illusion there's no telling what
could happen in here
am I going to get to fight or
is the cutoff before the flight
oh there's my healing point
you're still quite a bit
[Music]
risk
oh this is it
no no no no no no
this looks like it's it though
because I got a screenshot of this
with elephants standing here at that
wall
no no no
[Music]
what
no
no prompt yet
vital
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] Faria how did you get it wait
something about her isn't right
what's wrong with her she doesn't even
seem to know where she is yeah you're
right
she looks just like the soldiers we
encountered outside
black hole
oh
hello friend
oh running
but that's preposterous she never had
that kind of power we can talk later
here it comes
Focus guys
I've never known Faria to control
zoodles like that before how about with
a stone
where did she get her hands on that
first wait I'm poisoned can I please get
oh [\h__\h]
uh wait oh two poison oh wait a second
do we even have
I have seven
healings
oh this is not starting well
how much hundreds 80k
men
where is it oh and I am motivated
[Music]
I will help I will help
as long as I can I will help tonight
wait I should probably try to hit the
weak point though Arts are being
interrupted it's nice standing behind
him feels a little bit safer but
[Music]
where's my support King
you guys need to hold the line
where are y'all
pretty much
[Music]
yes
this is my second time I've been going
down to one HP not very good oh get out
of there
good that I was Far Away hello
wait who are you resurrecting wait my my
leg hurts
okay are you Reviving someone else next
all right I'll leave it to me
burning hell
[Music]
I'm grateful
execution get out of here get out of
here get out of here
take this okay
almost half an addiction
for Gemini
one more Crescent Flash
[Music]
the game is not over yet
still it feels so sad
it's so incomplete no
[Music]
no
how about it now consider yourself
allow me to help you
hold it
together
I wonder if we gotta fight the girl as
well right afterwards
uh
[Music]
looks dangerous
fine but I will load up the CP
aper
oh okay
am I gonna die before I can activate it
I'm just gonna whatever I'm just gonna
go with the normal one I don't care
I'm under too much pressure got it
oh wait oh [\h__\h]
did I hit him I'm gonna die
too oh
yeah
are you healing him
he probably is right
I'm gonna kill myself
I thought you were resurrecting him
I can do I'll bring you back
[Music]
you're nothing I've seen way more
impressive boss monsters
in this game
I've seen too much already
don't even
show you my true family
won't Escape me
oh he's almost dead
the first time I died
in here
yeah I saw that coming
I'm gonna wait a moment
um
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
baby
yeah sexy
I'll help
basket
I couldn't make it in time
[Music]
pretty simple
Phoenix
Faria
can you hear me
you wanna fight too you're gonna be
preparing another
someone another help your health
disgusting is way too powerful to
control at this rate her body won't be
able to take much more make her explode
oh
[Music]
forgive me
oh oh wait a second when she destroyed
that just now
oh
man I thought we were goners
everything okay yes she's only
unconscious not her I meant you
Shion please can you treat her
I can try but I can't promise she'll be
back to her real self when she wakes up
all I can do is heal her physically
we're not even supposed to be in here
maybe it'd be better if we moved her to
somewhere a little safer don't you think
in that case I'll take her off your
hands
you oh over here
I was curious what you were up to so I
took the liberty of following you to
find out stop I overheard what you said
about carnigan about how he really died
oh I'm sorry I had no idea can you
believed me
what makes you so sure I wasn't lying I
like to think I know you a little better
than that dohalem
I'll take Faria leave her with me I know
better than to ask what you're up to but
whatever it is I hope it all works out
thank you I hope so too indeed
but no
escape the last sketch perhaps that
we'll enjoy together one to stand out
he was always hanging back worrying
about everyone else
as for Faria it's always the closest to
me who gets hurt you don't seriously
blame yourself for what happened to her
do you
somebody got to her strike back at me
someone who knew me well enough to know
that I'd hesitate to fight back
same goes for you as well neither you
nor far you would have lost loved ones
if it wasn't for me
you're wrong
was the one who killed my brother under
orders from almadria
as for tarnigan if it weren't for the
crown contest he'd still be alive that
and the whole damn hierarchy that makes
it possible
but that's why we're fighting to put an
end to this whole messed up system that
treats people as expendable
indeed
reading Society of this blight is really
the only way I know how to atone for my
sins
you can't atone dohalim
I know it hurts to hear
but those people are dead
no amount of soul-searching or trying to
make amends is going to change that
forgiveness acceptance those ships have
sailed
so I just forget the harm I caused no
the opposite in fact you remember you
never forget you keep it in your heart
always and then you go on living
not for those already passed but for
those still alive
for those still alive
kisora is right
so long as we've still got breath in our
bodies we can make a difference in the
lives of others
lives being the operative word
that's what living's all about being
able to still make a difference
punishing yourself for the past won't
make the pain of your conscience go away
fixing the problem and it's Stead
is that what you're saying
that's right
you have to live for tomorrow dohalim
not for yesterday
and not only that
need to live for yourself and for the
change that you still can be
she'll try
don't forget we still got
him solve
End Zone remember
she on
huh
thank you
you have my deepest gratitude for what
you did for Faria glad to be of service
I'm glad we could stop Barrio without
hurting her you all did much for her as
well
most grateful
sharks we're on the same team right
let's move on
I don't want to move
[Music]
one more skate one more skit one more
skin do you think I was really being
controlled by someone
certainly seen that way the question is
who the red woman yes the same person
who's behind all of this I'll bet
whoever that is
brainwashed or otherwise the feelings of
resentment she holds towards me are real
someone used her because they knew we'd
hold back
if that's not playing dirty I don't know
what is
it does tell us one thing at least
someone here in lenegas is watching us
someone who means us harm
there's no question
that attack was meant for us alone
we need to find whoever my guy Children
First
my
my bills
oh no
there it is there it is
what is it renwell do you hear something
again
yeah
Michael Gordo he's broker though
that's what that is it's that voice
the will of Dana's astral energy
an anime cutscene it is
oh
it's a ceremony
what
there's so much astral energy
but where's it all coming from it's
almost like it's alive
we've seen this before I've seen this
somewhere
oh my
God oh is that a horror movie
[Music]
oh
she died
no time stopped
what
uh
[Music]
what
did everyone see that one too
I think yes
that was the spirit channeling ceremony
just now
it was more than that she only scared
because she knows it's gonna happen to
her felt like everything was on the
brink of
like the whole world was seconds from
Oblivion
it's the same vision as the one my
Thorns show me a vision of impenetrable
darkness that swallows up us and
everything else
an empty void a nothing so complete and
dominating that there aren't even words
to describe it
the end of time
the visions of the Apocalypse you've
been seeing
if I'd known how bad they were I
so everything we just saw
those were nayori's memories right
that's right
if her innermost thoughts were speaking
directly to us
I know they weren't mine
that power flowing into her
it reminds me of shion's thorns
if they're what's responsible for all
these Vision she's been having then
maybe
my Thorns are made from that same astral
energy
if that is the case we just found the
missing link between your thorns and
what happened to your three centuries
ago
no more than a link
perhaps even the very heart of the
matter
I've never played industrial energy so
powerful what was that
it's the same energy your Thorns are
made of it must be dark astral energy
right and isn't that something only
renins have correct dark astral energy
is possessed by renins alone
and when enough astral energy gathers
together it develops its own form of
sentience
if so maybe that complete Oblivion is
exactly what the ren and astral Energy's
will is wishing for
but why
pretty vague thing to nail down
it's more of a Feeling
just like the will of Dana
but the will of Dana is made up of
Astral energy too right
and if that's what's been showing us
these Visions I don't know should we
really be getting so involved with this
thing I know that we would never want
Oblivion but you can't say that for sure
cut it out you two
squabbling over theories will get us
nowhere
let's keep moving
if it's danna's will showing us these
memories and I'm as clueless about its
motives as any one of us but if it could
lead us to the truth then I want to find
out more
[Music]
xi'an's right all we can do is keep
going
if these really are nailorist memories
we're watching there could be truths in
them I was never aware of
after the cutter I think they may be the
kinds of truths I need to confront if
we're going to keep fighting
sometimes it's better to not know the
truth I'm sorry about what I said
earlier come on let's go well at least
it seems better
finally we begin to understand what the
Thorns are yes
[Music]
no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
that's it nope nope well learned the
truth behind
[Music]
I'm going back though I want to hear the
cut the skin
turn back for the time I just need a
little time first we can we can we can
go do the side quests let's go to the
side quest could I leave if I wanted to
go back go back go back
that Vision we saw
it was as if it was meant specifically
for us
what do you make of it
do you still think the will of Dana
might be involved somehow
maybe it's trying to tell us something
but what well it could be Supernatural
you know like seeing dead people
messages from Beyond the Grave those
type stuff
that that's your grand theory that we're
being haunted come on law
wait
he might be closer to the mark than you
think what if a person's thoughts and
deeds were to somehow become indelibly
etched Into The Ether of a place what
and what if those with a connection
could then somehow pick up on them what
you think that's what it was a message
someone left here for us I am merely
entertaining the possibility
whether it was Dan as will or somehow
connected to the Sovereign and maiden's
Powers I do not know okay back up a sec
you're saying that if a place is full of
enough astral energy it can somehow show
us events that happened centuries ago
more to the point how does that much
astral energy Gather in one place anyway
seems unlikely it happened naturally
whatever it was
300 years
whoever left it for us the strength of
their intent is beyond
okay is there another skit that we can
watch to stall
oh
wait could I could I could go somewhere
would I like go here
I could I feel like I could
[Music]
yeah but
um
it's okay
I have many side quests but I'll just uh
I don't really have time to do that now
anyway so
it's uh
it hurts but it's probably a good time
to
end it and say goodbye
to this gorgeous game
this beautiful beautiful game
that also made a dream come true
to be involved with Tales of arise and
Bandai Namco
I might oh I might not be part of part
of the characters or whatever but
I was I was honored to promote and
support the game and after coming so far
or actually already in the first second
I knew that I'm proud and honored
to present this game as your official
ambassador to the English region
yes
Health authorized is a wonderful game
and for anyone who has been watching so
far and hasn't gotten the game yet
unfortunately
stop it read the air
she'll
unfortunately I cannot continue after
this part but you're welcome to get the
game by yourself and then see how it
continues after this
um I want to say big big big big big
thank you to everyone who watched so far
and everyone who supported the whole
journey from like the oldest streams
that built up and led up to this
where I promoted the game to you guys
that a lot of you haven't heard of
before and and the whole series that a
lot of you guys haven't heard of before
but you were open and
um decided to
you know watch it together with me and
see what unfolds
what the game brings
with its beauty
and and I'm just so happy that I could
get so many people to like this game
series that means so much to me and has
kind of shaped
my
my character myself
over the past many many years
yeah I know a lot of people
kind of don't have interest in jrpgs or
like not at least not that big
a lot of people when they think of jrpgs
they think maybe of other games
then the tails off series but I hope
that when you think of when you think of
uh jrpgs now
that the one that jumps up
on top of your head
at number one is the tails off series
I I like all though
um upgrades and changes that they made
in this one specifically as much as I
love the classic tales off game the way
that they have been until now as much as
I like it that way
I do think that all the changes have
been worth it and will lead to Tales of
getting the recognition that it deserves
yeah
but yeah are you just going to keep
standing
cookie oh Mayo
oh my god
um yeah I had a lot of fun I'm gonna
continue having fun playing this
privately because I'm not done yet I
don't know how much content I have left
but I'll definitely go and make I'll go
and do all the side quests
to get the most out of it and I'm gonna
collect all the hoodles because that's
the main quest of this game
and then I will save the world hopefully
and I'll get back to you guys with my
feedback
without
spoiling you hopefully
yeah
um
even though the cell
was uh you know a jrpg stream that
typically just doesn't get many many
viewers
um for me I'm just really glad I can
play games like this
um instead of forcing myself into a
into a
into a you know a draw a drawer a box
that doesn't feel comfortable for me
this is what feels comfortable for me
and everyone who supported me with that
I really really appreciate you thank you
thank you thank you
oh come on
[Music]
I know hi
atus
um
very very proud of
this playthrough I am yes yes I am very
very proud I feel like you know I mean
you could you could still stay if you
insist you can still say I was carried
by the DLC blah blah blah but
I I think you know compared to other
games in Tales of games I kind of know
what I'm doing
so I don't care I don't care what you
say about that
now the towns up games are
where where I I've grown up you know
um shut up
like I did fine yeah you guys told me oh
you'll be cared for a couple bosses but
then it will get difficult you kept on
saying that again and again yeah but
okay but the next bus is with the next
bus
what I what I am scared of though is the
last bus because last final Final Bosses
entails off games
uh are really really tough to be honest
yeah but up until now I mean if I recall
I had a lot of issues using uh Mystic
Arts
entails of games until now so maybe
that's one of the reasons why I had
issues
with with the with the final boss
maybe now that I know how to use Mystic
lights
maybe now I will not have so many
problems anymore
final boss isn't that bad it really is
okay
yeah
uh oh man
yeah yeah well we will read some super
chats now
um
and tomorrow is her duck and collab
through Duncan we're gonna play warrants
and regarding to what comes next on my
channel uh jrpgs I have not made made a
decision yet and
um I I will actually take a little break
for now
um the next one or two or maybe even
three weeks I will not start another
jrpg immediate immediately or any series
for that matter
I think we would like to see a little
bit of a break on our Channel have some
smaller games in there or just try some
games like whatever Mass Effect I guess
for one episode only uh I don't know but
we're not gonna pick up a whole series
immediately gonna take some time with
that and I might even do a poll on my
community board to see uh which one you
would like to see next yeah and it might
it might not even be a jrpg that's gonna
picked up next I have been wanting to
play for example Ori
for a long time so
that is a choice uh truly oh yeah that's
also something I wanted to plan that's a
short one anyway
um
we'll see we'll see we'll see him
uh oh man
I love tails off I love dance off I'm so
Ambassador I am the ambassador to the
English region English region English
region
I'm really really happy that that
happened
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
for you guys support and like positive
um reception I wouldn't have gotten you
know the tales of luminaria sponsorship
for example and who knows maybe maybe in
the future I'll have more opportunities
like this to support the tales of series
I would be very honored to even though
probably in the future it will mostly
only be like filler games because like
until the next big big Flagship game
comes out it will be years I suppose
um
and in between it's usually just like
you know filler stuff but still I would
still be very very happy to
um promote that that kind of content as
well because anything that's related to
tails off I'm honored to show around yes
us has been so so sweet and supportive
like sending me a PS5 which has up until
this point never arrived unfortunately
but that's not their fault
and also sponsoring the iPad Pro and all
that holy [\h__\h] they're so kind ah
I could have just started with an
Android or BlueStacks or whatever but
they they
um insisted on you know having an iPad
or something like that being used yeah
they didn't need to do that
so Bandai Namco yeah very based based
very very based
I don't know I don't think they're
listening anymore but
um maybe I don't know if they would
watch the archival or so I kind of doubt
it because it's a long freaking archive
but fun and Uncle once again thank you
so so much it was an honor to present
your game to my audience they enjoyed it
I loved it we all loved it we all had a
blast with this game
um
it was a little bit uh I might have some
I might have told the characters in the
game to shut up every now and then I'm
sorry that is not because I didn't want
to really hear them talking it's just
because I needed some space for my
tangents and I apologize for that I
didn't really mean for them to you know
I didn't want to be a rude okay I love
these characters and and I I love all
the dialogues and and and the skates
yeah I I I I I I I I admitted to
previously in other takes off games
having uh skipped a lot of skits uh I
have not really done this uh in this
playthrough at all so and that really
shows
to how immersive this game has been for
me
even though there's some parts that I'm
still very much confused about I hope I
am supposed to be confused about them
yeah
and thank you for creating the woman
that is called kisara because she is a
queen
Mega Millions
foreign
[Music]
but it's like almost midnight and I
really need to read like at least some
super chats so
thank you
um everyone for watching we'll read some
super chats now
um
ah goodbye
tell them arise
goodbye thank you for
a great time you've given me thank you
for being such a gorgeous game I still
remember when I first saw the trailer
when I still had nothing to do with
the whole life even I think yeah
yeah
and uh it was such a long time ago but
the moment that shield first walked down
those stairs and I heard those Click
Clacks from her shoes
I knew I knew this was gonna be a game
that's gonna blow us all away hmm
a legendary tales off game now I will
never forget
yeah thank you for loving in together
with me thank you guys for it
for giving it a chance
you did you did the right thing guys
foreign
I'm going to finish it off stream what
kind of question
as well
of course I will
oh yeah
I did offer did I say something like
that that I would I would pay I would I
would like pay to get permission did I
say really say something like that I
think it was more like
I would I would promote the game for
free or something like that I don't know
I said some weird [\h__\h] back in the day
but the
[Music]
things that was the chosen one I am the
maiden just like Shion
oh no oh no
[Music]
I am the chosen Maiden
no just kidding okay I need to shut up
now
and end it
I forgot how to play the game great how
will I ever play this game without you
guys
it's okay I don't need to it's not like
I need you I can have fun alone
I really can I'm I'm fine
[Music]
I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm coping
okay my coping mechanism
fine it's not like I had so much fun
with you guys anyway I didn't have fun
at all with you guys
you ruined the game for me guys you
ruined it
is
tweets on the game here I will
definitely tweet about it but I think
even in tweets I'm not really supposed
to spoil or anything at least as the
official Ambassador so I will I will be
very vague but if you played the game
then you will understand so what I
recommend is for you guys to play the
game
this little maybe or maybe not be the
last time that I'm chilling the game to
you
you will never be able to escape from me
Shilling tails off games to you
[Laughter]
[Music]
and with that
I will go to the
intermission and see you in a few
minutes in my office okay understand I
will see you
in my office in a few minutes
wait in front of it please thank you
oh my God it's been eight hours it felt
so short and I've been stalling so much
it's been eight hours seven hours 53
minutes and I'm still stalling anyway
no
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
ah
I think I have a lot of ollies in my
room
oh
oh no they're gone
oh how come they're gone
they should still be here like logically
and OBS I see them all there
like in in the in the folders in the
sources in the list of sources she's
literally there
but it doesn't show up here interesting
oh I think I know why
um
[Music]
oh wait
ing super chats was that only two was
that was that an only picture yeah I
think so
okay uh the chat chat
chat doko
where are you Jack
I've noticed uh you know
started using the same Halloween music
that I got from audio stock as me
probably because it was on page number
one so I'm gonna go look for a new one
right now
and
uh we are gonna go on a journey to look
for another
um Halloween music
great minds think alike that is exactly
what I was thinking also probably also
because uh click on the first thing and
you're like oh I'm sure no one else is
using this
hello
hello and um
[Music]
I think the last one I found for like
also looking for like Lo-Fi
what is that is that even a choice here
[Music]
um
I think not
at all fight
oh fine
well will they give me something if I
type that in no
no okay
[Music]
well let's just go on page
there's 46 pages when I look for
uh Halloween
let's go
on page
what's a Halloweenish number guys
what's a Halloween number
six six there's no 666 but we can do six
six no wait no we can't do that either
it's only 46. we can do Page Six
Friday the 13th okay let's do 13. let's
see what we find here uh
zombie dance
Electro
Stars
this is funny oh my God cat
star what did you do
was that the cat
oh someone's coming
oh
[Music]
this is kind of cool
uh
uh oh Halloween
Waltz
our Titanic no
[Music]
okay page 14 maybe doesn't bring me that
much luck Halloween metal hand Gothic
that's a lot of different things you put
together sir
but this one isn't even loopable I think
whoa
[Music]
this is nice only one minute long and
not really loopable though
ah this one eight bit
Dracula Loop
ah
[Music]
what about this
what
oh oh
yes
that's what I'm talking about
that sounds very loopable
this is the one I agree
[Music]
I look I like those
what are those what is that that that
click clock sound uh what was that
instrument again
oh it is dark not sure but this is cute
this is really cute let me get this one
now
yeah it sounds like cast Nets but it I'm
not sure if it's really casting it's
that's what what my first thought was
but maybe it's not
okie dokie put that into my VLC
yes is it a good balance for you guys
is this okay neck cracks is
sounds like it yeah
[Music]
a bit louder okay
so cute too I like this is really really
good for Super Chat reading I think for
Halloween
okay where have we left off last time
I'm not gonna read all of them obviously
because it's already past midnight I
played too much I stalled too much
um but it was worth it so maybe maybe
tomorrow
after turducken
maybe I can do a super chat reading
stream I don't know I'll see how I feel
afterwards
maybe I'll open an extra stream for
Super Chat reading I might do that yeah
um so
where have I left off
was it Tales of a rise
we haven't read the super chess from the
concert watch along we haven't read the
super chats from Minecraft I think
either
[Music]
have we read uh the ones from before
that
we were here together those ones I
quickly read I skipped them
those ones I just quickly zoomed through
so I do think it's Tales of arise the
previous one yeah
don't know
foreign
very fitting
this one
on the face
[Music]
there you go
to drink more water though I already
feel it crawling up my throats
trying to consume me
from inside
foreign
no oh no I didn't see the Minecraft
thingy yet no wait was that last like
the last 24 hours
someone linked something like that to me
on Twitter wait I want to watch
Minecraft
um news what do I look for in the
Minecraft The Wild update 48 minutes ago
it
no four hours ago is from wait which one
would I watch the Wild update oh my God
but when would that come to us
when would that come when is that being
released oh my God it's so cute
like I don't I don't know it says frogs
what the [\h__\h]
but I'll watch this is uh well this is
12 minutes let me watch the I guess
update highlights one minute and 37
seconds
[Music]
froggles let me know that
um
[Music]
one and a half minutes let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go
but this is 119 when what even gets
added in 118. I don't remember
you will get it later at least a month
after the ga date for the third party
service to have super uh-huh
and I haven't even released 118 when is
118 coming
okay
um in on zero
on zero
zero
is free two
one zero
coming later to see your caves and
cliffs part two yep okay oh mushrooms in
that place
Xbox game pass uh-huh
oh what what is this what not not for
Java right
dungeons I kind of wanna seasonal
Adventures wait when is that coming are
they having a Halloween event
now
that wouldn't that be good for uh
Halloween week the Wild update coming
2022 okay
Mangrove swamp oh new is that new by All
Me
don't oh my God oh my God I'm gonna make
I'm gonna make I'm gonna get so many
frogs oh my God
what's that what is that what is that
what's that house
deep dark oh new by Omi again oh where
is that that's is that in the never no
that's in the normal world right
new skulk blocks blocks what what
both with chest oh
that's it that's it that's it that's it
thank you
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
frog though frog froggle
um
the new biomis are hype did they show
too looks like they got two new biomies
coming
or did I miss something
that's really cool that there's still
new stuff coming
[Music]
thank you thank you I love it too
oh [\h__\h] you know what tomorrow is Sunday
and they still haven't
um gotten like I'm planning to do a
whole talk next week but I haven't
gotten like I haven't heard back from
the person I've tried to contact
um so since since there's still no reply
today at my last minutes try asking
someone else
yeah
uh sad
not gonna say who it is but I mean
eventually you'll kind of notice by who
has not come to hollow uh talk yet
you kind of figure it out eventually
[Music]
um
so I might ask someone else if I if I
don't get like an answer until I make my
schedule then there will be no Hall of
fault next week and also not in the
Halloween week though because Halloween
week is too busy
so I would like to do it next week
I would like to do it next week
but yeah
[Music]
Holo Yen collabs uh
um hmm
can you guys keep a secret
I know you can't
not all of you
I um
[Music]
there's some I mean I would I would
announce it on with my schedule tomorrow
anyway on on The Late Late tomorrow
let's just say
something big is happening next week
[Music]
which is not our new outfit
um that that's probably gonna happen
after October
yes hi
hi Jenny
hi she's ignoring me
[Music]
foreign
unfortunately
I got my hopes up I'm so sorry
come here come here come here this chair
is for you come here
come on
come come come come
okay yeah yeah
this is your chair
now where are you going where are you
going
dinner she will come here eventually
I'm not done it might sound as if I'm
done because I'm being more quiet but
I'm not okay let's read some super chats
eight hours today felt so easy it feels
like I played for four hours maybe
all right all right all right all right
all right all right Tales of horizon
checks
um
foreign
for eight hours they always just sleep
they really just sleep that's all they
do
um
oh I'm so scared Patrick
a ghostly complexion
honestly Patrick Chen
back in school
like
um the kids in school would make fun of
me because
um because of my lack of vitamin D and
being so freaking pale people were like
you're a zombie you're a ghost
laughs
yeah it was a little bit of a complex
back then but don't worry it's not
anymore because ever since I went to
Japan I got appreciated for exactly that
um so I don't really care so it's all
good I just wanted to mention it
children are [\h__\h] children are [\h__\h] no
[Music]
you know
foreign
yeah very nice Japan appreciating me for
things that I got made fun of in my own
country
yeah
and also like I'm hiding behind these
bangs maybe you can see it but Behind
These bangs I'm hiding quite the big
forehead
and that is something that I am still
very
um
something like very cautious about
and I got bullied a lot for that
for a big forehead
um
yeah and people the children called me
bald
so uh this is so awkward but I got
bullied so much and it was a huge
complex of mine that I would um come
back home crying every day that was like
in in junior high school and even before
that as well yeah actually more before
Junior High
that it was the worst before Junior High
and then in the first maybe first year
of Junior High I still felt very bad
about it and then I ended up cutting
myself some bangs even though my hair
doesn't naturally grow that way although
now now it's still perfect because I put
a lot of hairspray in it you might not
see it but they always stay in place
don't they yeah because I have a lot of
hairspray in there
so I cut myself uh bangs because I came
home crying every day and I was so sick
of it and I just wanted to hide my
forehead and ever since that day I made
sure that I would have perfectly styled
bangs every freaking day
I was so self-conscious about it
for so many years I still kind of am but
nowadays I give a little bit less [\h__\h]
about it than I used to I would even
style my Banks to go to the supermarket
um nowadays I don't really
I don't care that much anymore I'm just
like whatever
but I had that issue for many many years
um
they ask you how you are and you just
have to say you're fine when you're not
really fine but you just can't get into
it because they would never understand
foreign
[Music]
yeah I'm probably one of the biggest
consumers for Hairspray
yeah Ohio
continuing
hmm
think it's monkey thank you
is this working
is there a red Super Chat thing working
I feel like it's yeah it's broken it's
broken
I think I'm gonna use my I don't know
why it's broken but I think I'm gonna
use my Excel sheet
go and use my Excel sheets
[Music]
copy paste
where's my Excel sheet here
[Music]
okay
me
[Music]
a pound of soda and a pallet of
hairspray that's me
to see someone with a pound of soda and
a pound of hairspray in the cart that's
probably me shopping at that supermarket
yo why can I not pass it yup
got it
maybe this is the right one
this might be it
[Music]
Costco Costco I've been to Costco once
in my life
in Japan when I was living with a host
family
uh who had a membership with Costco
Costco is not so common in Japan
but they had that membership and I was
like yo I want to check it out too so I
went with them it was insane
it was insane they don't have Costco
here in my country
um
there yeah there are Costco's in Japan
yeah
oh
[Music]
I just don't think it's fair that you
don't get in there unless you have some
kind of membership what the hell
okay so now audit
this isn't working either
why is everything broken
my sheet isn't working Eva okay
[Music]
on there
on it
[Music]
and this one I can't even pass it what
happened
[Music]
save so much for what you get for this
membership
[Music]
there we go
let's see if this works this should work
[Music]
ah
oh
okay
why does it not
do the color anymore either never an
Excel sheet which is unrelated to the
other thing that I have recently the the
Chrome extension nor in the Chrome
extension in London
[Music]
wait a second I mean I've heard there
was an update for the extension but
isn't that like automatic
oh wait a second
uh how do I do that again
um
I don't want to miss any of these you
know oh
[Music]
there it is
it already there though I'll just delete
it and
reinstall maybe I should just restart
Chrome
okay I I reinstalled it
now is it I think I have to reopen
no I'm doing it now not all of them but
still
no this is not YouTube's fault this is I
don't know weird
uh history
recently closed today we go
okay
with the sheets be working now
no
oh my Crafter
I didn't know the the marking is still
not working why is everything broken
[Music]
okay I'll do my best to
um see it by myself I will ask you guys
for a confirmation
foreign
[Music]
why is it broken I don't get it but okay
I will I will read it normally
so what is a red Korean superchat
because this looks like a rainbow to me
uh what's AIM thank you I think this is
a rainbow I don't see any colors anymore
but I think that was a rainbow because
it's like
two point five thousand five point nine
four nine thousand twelve thousand
twenty thousand fifty thousand hundred
thousand fifty thousand twenty thousand
it goes down again
hundred thousand is a red okay
okay
[Music]
come down
I don't know what everyone thinks but I
wanted to say the specializes of kfp you
know Kiana has a warm heart and the kfp
employees are the same oh
I'm enjoying a fun kfp live these days I
tried to enjoy watching Kiana's
streaming one by one and understand
English sometimes I spend time talking
or singing with other kfp employees at
secret Carefree place what
oh
the Discord you talking about that
Discord
you talk and sing sing with other
caffeine please
[Music]
and you don't you don't invite me
you don't invite me
everyone that's in that Discord is now
going to the usual room
[Music]
I am alone on it are you sure about that
are you sure that I'm allowed there are
you sure I sure are you sure I'm gonna
take you by your word
[Music]
I feel some happiness now waiting stream
time and enjoy talk and other people
when I'm waiting it is a little thing to
another people but I think AFP is
another life oh it's super chat for all
kfb Why YouTube always called my Super
Chat
at them
thank you
thank you yeah you're you're a Super
Chat was apparently uh causing you
troubles
and you didn't even try to do a double
rainbow but apparently it happened thank
you
take this spy present
you're not doing a good job as a spy
when you are in that Discord and
basically feeding me information from
that Discord that's like the opposite of
a spine I mean I mean I guess no I guess
then you were my spy but at the same
time you're spying me for other people
as well so
just like at some point plus and plus
becomes minus you know
right I think I learned that before in
math class minus and minus becomes plus
and plus and plus becomes minus
I know math
[Laughter]
I do know math
[Music]
yes you don't know that but you guys are
stupid duh
yes no for real though that's actually
true you guys are stupid
it's not wrong
no
hey
you don't yeah two negatives made of
positive for example
shut up
Madison's plus but plus and plus is Plus
foreign okay maybe maybe that maybe it
was like that whatever shut up
my arm was closed though I was close I
was close to remembering it correctly
pretty [\h__\h] close okay shut up
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you what's AIM
foreign
please keep on enjoying my community and
my content
and support me thank you so much
[Music]
thank you for the pinky thank you can
you give us those edited images ah
I already answered this somehow they'd
make for some perfect reaction images I
bet you had a lot of fun making them
loving the game and streams by the way
wouldn't have tried it without you thank
you tell that to Banda and uncle
yeah yeah unfortunately I didn't save
them I'm sorry guys you can try to
recreate them
is that a pinky if 100 000 is a red one
would 50 000 be a pinky
in Korean one
[Music]
I think yeah
even intentional looking lovely and
yummy as always oh you wouldn't
you wouldn't be thinking about taking a
bite off of me right
I hope so
thank you though
thank you for the red super chat see
with pancake I don't even have to think
whether or not it's a red one because he
could cake only sends red super chat so
I don't even have to think about the
currency
thank you
[Music]
um
why does it feel like I've read these
before
it seem so familiar
[Music]
[Laughter]
I read it during the stream but wasn't
this still preach at territory
I don't know
weird
o
I did read it what
I'm a reacting to this already but
anyway let me see
uh I would maybe I was in The Brew chat
hmm
I'm always in the pre-chat hey
[Music]
it wasn't princess
huh anyway
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat I have
nothing special to say just wanted to
chew from Tanger that's all not like I
missed you anything I feel like I read
this one already as well
[Music]
are you here
have I read this one before delsa are
you here Delta doco don't start
yes I did
I don't want to waste my time reading
this double
I just I just reacted to okay I didn't
read it actively as a super chat reading
but I
I just read it when I saw it on the
screen
[Music]
is that what I did
I reacted
okay okay yeah another kiss for you
though thank you
hello
anything that I must do from a native
perspective in when visiting Australia
oh a native perspective
um
uh
I guess uh if you're here during winter
time try going to a Christmas Market
that's a big big big
um highlight for the winter time even
for you know normal people who are not
tourists
um and also go skiing I guess
and and if you're not here during the
winter time there's so many things to do
uh you could you could go even if you
don't usually like it that much just for
the experience you could go because
Australia it has a lot of history of
classic music maybe you could do
something in that regard
um
uh it really also depends on the area
that you're going to
because each area has something special
about it
um
foreign
can't wait for the German Christmas
Market we have here in the UK it's great
oh yeah they have like German style
Christmas markets all over the world in
Japan as well I think they had one
but I mean obviously the original is
not really ah readable
I'm excited to go to the Christmas
Market this year I think last year yeah
they were all they were all canceled but
it didn't affect me because I wasn't in
in Australia anyway I was in Japan last
year
because it didn't matter to me
but my friends were really sad
apparently
[Music]
Christmas is
the Blazing Sword oh my God I didn't put
it on today I forgot I should have worn
it today it was the last episode at
least I wore it last time
at least
[Music]
oh
no
okay okay okay let me Bonk you one
second difficulty
foreign
[Music]
thank you you guys are blessing me so
much
I have been blessed
bye bye chickens
[Music]
and it's time
xd0009 that is zero zero zero nine yeah
Mr can speak Spanish
I took two more of them yeah also uh
chunkers is taking apart the scratch
pool right now
she's trying to do a pole dance she's
aspires to be a pole dancer foreign
[Music]
because when I lived in Japan and
interacted a lot with Japanese people
whenever I was listening to
conversations I I or like when I was
having conversation with someone I
noticed that Japanese people in order to
let the other person know that they're
listening they would continuously
throughout the person talking for like
even in one sentence they would probably
do it
like two times at least
in one sentence
um like throughout the whole
conversation while in where I'm from
when people listen when people want to
show you that they're listening they're
just being quiet they don't say a thing
they don't make a noise at all
that was normal for me before
but
um
in Japan I really got used to it this
became a huge habit for me that I really
cannot turn off when I'm listening to
someone
I I usually uh do a lot of them
[Music]
yeah and nodding
like here maybe in order to show someone
you're listening you would at least not
but in Japan
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah that's something I will admit that
I picked up from gouda but like
everyone's been using it these days and
God is like I don't know
wait when did I now say girl if I said
it anytime now then that was just a
natural girl
I do say it on purpose sometimes to
impersonate Kelly
sometimes
but
uh God as well is also a word that Cali
didn't invent so most of the time I use
it to impersonate her but there are some
times where I probably just used it
naturally
yeah
uh but uh fuma Thurman is completely
just me being me yeah
so many people uh say that that's like I
don't know inasping but if you listen to
Japanese whole life members
especially when they're like collabing
with one another I think you can notice
it well
um
see how they fumofumu at each other
[Music]
it's like how Surah Senpai says that's
her kind of
foreign
I think I think a lot of people just
didn't really realize it because if you
listen to a Japanese conversation it
just feels so natural to you that you
don't even notice it
baby
yeah
yeah but the onion and that's a good I
think
so Joe Knight thank you for the rest of
what's that this red super has been a
long time coming but I wanted to say
that you have been amazing since debut
and have been shining brighter you're an
integral part of her life never forget
thank you
happy birthday to the canopy employees
that shared his birthday with me as well
carefully nikoi at it
it was your birthday sorry for the
delayed congratulations
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear Joel night happy
birthday
to you thank you for
spending your birthday with me and your
kind sweet words yeah thank you for your
support I hope you had a lovely oh there
you go I hope you had a lovely birthday
yeah
I hope getting older doesn't bother you
too much
it is what it is
at least uh at least at least you're not
um suffering like uh elephant or Shion
who try try to kind of die but they just
can't really or you're 300 years old or
something like that that would suck
wouldn't it kind of
imagine living for 300 years
imagine that having lived for the past
300 years and now is like the 300th year
imagine how much [\h__\h] you must have seen
how much you must be sick of this world
because you've seen so much [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
going on
oh my God
[Music]
and now imagine that's how I feel as a
phoenix
[Music]
so sick of it just kidding
oh
how must it feel
about business
and you need 13 e thank you for the
pinky Unit 14 e reporting was the wise
words from now is Lloyd oh if one
sword's attack power is hundreds two
must be 200.
oh no did he really say that
did Lord really say that you know I can
see that because Lord is a freaking
douche
no not a douche I guess that's the wrong
word he's an idiot he's a naive young
idiot
[Laughter]
oh my God he did when did he say that in
a skit
I mean is it's true but like it's so
obvious that it's like why would you say
that like what what what are you trying
to say
he was talking to Kratos oh you guys are
very informed wow
it's a door yeah that's that's probably
a good way to describe him
ah well thank you for that units virgin
e
spanking
congratulations Ambassador fun and
amazing gameplay we'll see how deep I
fall down this Rabbit Hole oh my have
you fallen can you hear me
hello hello
spankenheim spankenheim
can you hear me can you hear me can you
hear me
yeah I think he's pretty deep down there
well I'll throw you a ladder uh once
you're done with the game I'll throw you
a ladder to come back up all right good
I beg you Release Me From the usual room
I will never reference the trash bin
again I will Begin work towards
reinforcing all trash bins around kfp or
any other task
you would order me to do to serve you
better I beg you free me didn't I come
to the conclusion that um I wanna I'm
gonna short a new sentence to one month
anyway so that's where I still stand
I'm not gonna let you out that easily
nope no special
treatment no no no no no no no
have fun
have fun with the puzzles and the Legos
black friction thank you thank you soon
excuse me
are you kidding me black Christian
[Music]
are you already in the usual room or do
I need to bring you there
do I need to escort you
personally
huh
oh sending me hearts in the chat now I
see I say that's how it is
you think that will make everything as
if it never happened huh please princess
carry me there okay you know what I'm
I'm going to do exactly that
foreign
congratulations
my dear black friction you are blocked
for 300 seconds
while I am bringing you to the usual
room
[Music]
bye bye
one month for you too
sentences are getting longer no more one
day sentences
[Music]
are you calling me an idiot I know I'm
not I know not I know that's not what it
means but the way you make me pronounce
that word makes me feel like an idiot so
that that's not really cool you know
it's like you're calling me an idiot
even though you're not calling me an
idiot
I accept the accommodations of the usual
room but can I get a lavender pillow
why would I give you a lavender pillow
in the usual room what's the matter of
your chickens
where do you think you are
the audacity the other City
[Laughter]
oh my God
if anything I'm gonna wrap some spices
on you but not lavender or hell no
traffic and Captain thunderboltankish
and Mario H Danke Schoen Colin
kazadankishan Amelia's Ace Attorney
General language
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah
you are the savior of the GMT plus two
people sleep schedule thanks for your
streams I always enjoyed MPS Phoenix is
my favorite mythical creature thank you
mine too coincidence I think not you're
welcome though yeah
um I'm I'm glad to have a uh almost
uh Monopoly on this time zone
yeah
I mean sometimes like Cali also streams
around this time not this time but like
earlier when I start my stream sometimes
she streams around those times but yeah
I am biased why would I be biased
because I'm Phoenix
so are you
saying
that you agree with me being a phoenix
[Music]
clear that one up
nicer
everyone who calls me a chicken will
lose their freaking chicken heads
just keep that in mind
you feel a crucial needful content at a
good time knowing
I'm glad to hear that
[Music]
oh my God thank you for two
red super chats and one pinky thank you
small steps yeah small steps first the
harness training then leash walking oh
yeah right I remember this then kitties
got a YouTube Travel Channel profit oh
congress on the chair real talk after
you used it for a while don't be afraid
to replace it if it's not working out
even if it's expensive just think about
how cheap it is on the hours of
streaming per year basis and how
important your health is oh I mean
that's that's true yeah
um but like even if I were to replace it
I don't I don't know what else I would
get like what's what's something that's
better than the Herman Miller chair
[Music]
I kind of feel like there's not really
any better option just similar options
but nothing that's quite better
Two Urban villagers
you know what
you are right with that
sitting on an actual Cloud I'm not sure
about that
well if that will be that good for me
actually secret labs
[Music]
holy shy
I like the combination of that word I'm
almost at nine hours and I feel like I
have streamed for four hours oh my God
I could go for 12 hours easily
at this point I'm just chilling I'm just
vibing
foreign
no no no I don't wanna because I need to
prepare for tomorrow's stream I need to
make a thumbnail and [\h__\h] and get up
somewhere at a decent time tomorrow so
yeah
it ain't gonna happen
[Music]
and yes uh moderation streamlines this
is what you say in your pinky
um
that is today not the case unfortunately
or fortunately I don't know
but in general especially now that I'll
be taking a little break from these jrpg
streams I think we'll have a couple more
shorter streams
um so I guess that's good for a little
while to kind of detox on takanashi
Kiana
[Music]
thank you for the pinky oh that's the
last one actually my potential is doing
Dance Workout it's time for sad farewell
to the contactor of super trash bin the
garbage atom atomizer the dunk Ground
Pounder I've got the beautiful healthy
picture of my dreams but what cost
foreign
[Laughter]
unbelievable
I thought
you'll never forget
two years
every last time you're deserving
[Music]
little chicken so stupid
so so stupid
what can we do what can we do
what can we do about it
what can we do about this
dog
[Music]
stop that one day
foreign
[Music]
because you have angered me
no that's not actually their reason but
I will most likely do another stream
tomorrow after the turduck and maybe
move some hours in between like quite a
little bit later to do some uh Super
Chat reading and maybe have a little
announcement with the schedule
all right sounds good let's just take
some time for the Super Chat reading
just came back what happened I have been
challenged
I have been challenged and um
there have been some sacrifices made
[Music]
it's Kiana already
keep your secrets then yeah I'll keep
them for one more day
okay I'll go and download worms now and
then have a
make a thumbnail yes and make put up the
streaming reservation you guys have any
advice like for worms like I I offered a
sweater shampline to like play it with
me beforehand I'll be around like an
hour before if she wants to
any any anything any advice for tomorrow
remember how to jump
foreign
the UI
did I mean what they're doing
sheep pay attention to wind ah no I
don't mean like how to win the game I
mean like streaming wise I don't know
what she was doing
warm spit oh Grandma's coolest okay just
Gonna Get Wrecked maybe maybe I'm gonna
watch that stream to fall asleep
one of one of the many things I will be
watching
[Music]
um
okay okay okay thank you
camera in the game
I learned how to be a cameraman what do
you mean
[Music]
hide the friend called invite me said
the camera work could be better a hunk
a hunk
I will watch the stream so that I will
understand okay I
so then see you tomorrow for one
[Music]
on my channel and then later in the day
I'll probably do a super chat reading to
finally finish those that I have been
um
and not reading recently I'm sorry
I'm so sorry but it's already so lit and
I streamed for nine hours exactly now
now at this very moment it has
been nine hours
and I wanna eat my Curry now I think and
cuddle my cats my cats are impatient my
cats want want me to cuddle them
otherwise they're going to assassinate
me while I'm sleeping yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
kitties come first I'm glad you
understand typhen but you should be in
the usual room so
[Music]
have a good rest of the night rest well
thank you too first official turducking
collab yeah that's true
I hope to see lots of turd duck and Fan
Art after that because surprisingly I
don't recall any of us three together
I think
yeah try to actually sleep at a decent
time do you know who you're talking to
there's a shocking lack of it yeah
because we haven't really been
getting together as free at the same
time I guess
we will tomorrow so be there or be
square
yeah
I'm looking forward to it I hope you are
too and in German we say Alvin
[Music]
I totally forgot about Tales of her eyes
that this is the end too I was so
distracted
um goodbye
[Music]
what a great game it was I will let you
know once I finish it
pain makes me smoke
the pain makes me so small
[Music]
foreign
wait for me
[Music]
foreign