[Music]
[Applause]
D
[Music]
[Applause]
H
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause]
AK
[Music]
[  [Applause]
[Applause]
[Music]
T
[Applause]
DET A
[Music]
[Applause]
This program is brought to you by the sports you are watching
[Music]
Masu
All High
[Music]
Allwelcomethe
poipEP
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] Good
[Music]
kiMySoundboardbest
way
ever
are
[Music]
while everyone,
MISTLetme
EXPSHOWknow I'll give you a little explanation first.
Please listen.
isTalkWithThepurpOf
inter
andlyJapanesetalto
BRAS
is for English  This is an interview talk show,
and the goal is to let overseas people know more about mainly Japanese talents while providing live translation and interpretation.Today
is the 30th [Music] show, courtesy of the host, Takashi Chara.  Thank you
[Music] I'm
nervous,
but
beepAll please.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause] Please
say hello to everyone. Also,
please introduce yourself.
[Music]
Oh, wait, I'm sorry. Please
mute me.  Sorry, I
might have made a mistake after all. Wait a minute, I made a mistake.
Oh, I
fixed it. I'm sorry. It was a pompon. Yes, it's fixed. Sorry.
Let's start from the beginning again.
Okobadododo
[Music]
Generation Wrong
Wrong Wrong La JP Generation
Thank you very much, I
'm Fuji Uo. I'm a 4th generation student. I'm a 4th year student. I
heard that I'm not one of the members. It
was dangerous. I sometimes say things like, "Oh, it's dangerous."
Kiaro-senpai, please don't get me wrong, please don't misunderstand me,
happenstosay
that waynotlikethat
japanesat
so oh so cute, oh cute, close up, so
embarrassing.
Question: What kind of activities have you been doing lately?
Today, I
went to the Kakumaki Wataru HUB NICE DAY
. I went there today, so I got up early. That's
right. Oh, HAVE NICE DAY. Please
tell me.  You won't get it, what did you do? Yes,
today I
played a card game. Ah, I taught you a card game. It
's a secret only here. It
's today, but basically it's a little more rough.
Lately.  Recently, there have been
live concerts and music sounds have been activated.
Where have
we been?
Recently, I wonder if it's been recently. Second live in January. After all, it's still
recent, isn't it? It's not recent, it's not recent, it's okay. I'm
going to go with this.IaskedWhatbeenup
recentlyandoneofthe
ThingsShesaidisjust
todayShewokeupearly
becauseSherecorded
forHaveanicedayShe
WillIthinkexpltoUSa
LittleBitlaterina
differentquestion
butIwaslikeOhSurely notgnatelluswhatyou
didrightnotspoilIT butdidspoilwasdoing
someCardGAMEthis
timeinteresting
Maybe
need
MA
Littlehave
upMONandsaysJanuary
had
herercouldthink
that It's really
cool.Sheep are basically cool sheep.  Speaking
of cute but cool ships, the only one is Bame
Senpai.It seems
like it's a good program.I'm
curious about this.How did you first
find Hololive and what made you join again?
When I saw his 3D wide video, I thought, Wow, that's the first time I've ever
seen Hora Live content.I
think that other
vtuber doesn't know much about it.  But aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, yeah that
Kinaai-san, ah, I see, I
see, okalo might be the first Hololive, hmmm, that’s really helpful.Thankfully, that’s
how I discovered it, and that’s how I got into it.I
was doing a song at that time.  However, I wanted
more people to listen to my work as a hobby,
so I thought there was a
place where I could be heard, or rather, a place where I
could be active, and that's when I realized that
Hololive was the place for me.  I
see.
So that's why I sent it.
Was there an audition? Yes, there
was always an application form. I
see. I sent it three times. Three times, three times. I sent it
once a day or something.  Wait,
wait a minute, wait a minute, wait two weeks,
yeah, it's better to do it once, after all.I
thought I might have gotten the name wrong, so I tried again.Seriously, I
didn't get a reply in two weeks, so I'll try again.  I
sent it, no, it's good, after all, it was the first time, and it
seemed like nothing happened, so I sent it several times,
and thanks to you, I have a senior today, so
thanks to that, I'm here, okay, now,
do that WANTED more
people to have Access
Hersingingsowas
looking for a place
where
couldBL
ACatthetimeWas
Alwaysaud
constantly
HerWethere
Oh, there's such a good word in English. What,
what?
What's that? The
third time is the team. The third time is usually right.
Or something like that. The third time is honest.
Or that.  Well, that
's a good answer. I'm going to the next one. I haven't
been able to say it until now because of the language barrier,
but I'm going abroad.  Is there anything I wanted to say in my diary?
Yeah, it doesn't matter if it's
there or not. It's great that
there are so many people overseas, and they
do translations, but yeah, there are
n't many events like this overseas.  But
even in the midst of all that, they've been cheering me on, and I'm
more like that.The fact that my
seniors don't have many events overseas, that
's right, in Japan, it's quite a bit, like a
certain convenience store project or something like that.  I
don't have much, but I want to
do my best to do various things more globally,
so please support me.That's good too.
havesomuchtosayyou
guysbecausetoldfrom
youHeardfrom
guys
TheOf There's
something I noticed a little bit more
when I was collecting those questions.It's
like what Mr. Watamate from overseas said, but Ado-senpai
often adds subtitles to his content.  Is
n't that right? I hear they'll be doing it tomorrow.I feel like there are
n't many other members who put subtitles on their own content.That's why
Watari-senpai's feelings
may have already been widely felt overseas.I
think so.
Well, why do you
put so much effort into it with subtitles? Yeah, I've been watching
it quite a bit since a long time ago, and it's
true that more and more people from overseas are watching it.  My
senpai was just the same as my senior at school, so that's when I got a lot of
money, right? Yeah, that's right, I
felt really bad about that, so I
thought I should take good care of it, and she
said yes to me.
Okthatmakes, I
askedHerbecauseof
alllthinkthereany
otherJAPANMWhoput
muchefforthaving
oflandsubtitlesET
herentonYouTubeand
askedWhydoesandsaid
WhenJOINJOINsenpai andat
thattimeisWhenalot of
asviersstarted
watchingHerLIFEand
ShenoticedThatShe wasAwareofThatShe
tookNoteofitand
thoughtwellshewants
tomakethemfeel
includedandItwas
very importantforher
toyouknowprovide
them
translationsI guess that's the
type of broadcast that you like most
What about game chaos chat collaboration?  I
like all of them, but I still don't know how to sing.
Yeah, it seems like a lot of them fit together. I've
done it over 100 times already. I've done it over 100 times. It's
amazing. No, I've been doing it. I
haven't been able to do it lately,
but I used to do it every week.
There used to be WNS, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, so many comments.
Me-senpai doesn't just sing, he also
has a strong image of that Minecraft player, that's for sure.
That's why I want to listen to him. He's
been playing Minecraft for a long time, right? There are
n't many people who do it these days.
Yes, I'm doing it. I
'm sure you've built a lot of interesting buildings, but which one is your favorite?
I like them all, but it's definitely the square roll, the rock-paper-
scissors device, or the chomaki-cho maki-o. I
'll show you a little bit.
likes likes
.  Yeah, it's
rainbow-colored, super colorful,
RGB, and I
played with it a lot, so I
remember it, and I'm glad I did my best.
Everybodyalotof
peoplehavebeenusing
ITknowConnectwitha
lotofMemoriesInHer
MindandWhyitfeels
SuperSpecialtoher
andShefeelslike
WorthItShe
workedsoHardonitand
alsoIknowedWhenIwas
readingoutthe
questionThatssomuch
MinecraftACTIVEeven
Whenthere  Are you
sad that everyone isn't playing Minecraft?
Lonely, lonely
[Music]
Hey, can you please come back?
Everyone, Kira-chan, please come back. I have
n't used the Japanese server much in the first place, but it's
true that
everyone is using the server.  However, things have
become the same, or rather, when the Japanese server
became the main server, all the members of my family
moved there, which makes me sad. On
the other hand, I don't think so. It's just Ronri
Chiara.  So, I'm really feeling nostalgic about the time when
all the members of Minecraft's Hol Live were doing it. I
wish they would come back. I
want to do it with Nemi. I'm
building something, so I heard you saw a huge tree.
Look, look, look, it's huge.  Before I knew it, it
had gotten really big.And I do
n't think it's finished yet.Yeah, that
's right.Maybe it's not finished.It's not finished
yet.I wonder when it'll be finished.Wat-
senpai: There's something I'm working on right now.  What are
you making
NOW, senpai, how much Ram Vegas ah Ram
Vegas oh Rabe are you doing right now? What's about 10% now?
Eh, what 10% is it? But it might still be 340%. It
's not early, it's not late, it's not late. Yeah, it's early, it's not
late.  Hurry, Hurry, Wow, when
did you start making it? It's been a long time ago. It's
delicious, oh, then, it's late. When that thing was popular, oh, I want to go to Vegas. Come on, I'm making all kinds of things. Let's go and play slots and Minecraft.
Let's play sheep racing and now.  I'm making it,
reply. Hey, let's take a look at the
cutouts. Kaneo, let's take a look at the cutouts. Come and join us.
Chin, wait, I'm sorry, I made a mistake, so I'll start again.
From O 3 + 3, lower 3, [ __ ] has evolved.
3 + 3, lower 3, so this is 66318. No
, no, 12, wait, 3 + 3, right? 6,
right?  It's 3, right? Sub 6 Multiplication comes first 3
Multiply by 3 It's true that you forget 9+3. Does
Neme know this number
? 9-chan probably doesn't know the same thing. Even though she's
not good at numbers, it's 11.  I do
n't know at all, I don't know at
all, right? I
don't know what's special. I don't know
.  It's so cute,
cotton
isn't bad, right? Oh, you asked me how it all started.
Yeah, yeah,
wow.
Yeah, it's embarrassing for the first time. It's embarrassing for the
first time. It's okay for the first time. I played Yokai for about 8 hours.
But yeah, yeah, yeah, at that time I was 61.  It's
okay to watch a video that says, oh, the line isn't too bad.I shot this video saying, ``It's not bad when the line goes out.''It's a shitty fight against a shitty girl.''It's a good side of the line.''
Nekunkunkun, it's okay to be a pervert, it's okay.It's okay to
broadcast it on a pervert broadcast.It's okay to play it on a pervert broadcast.Important
perverts are saved.It's helpful.Repeat Acha.It's
helpful.Wakipaiwaki.''  Pai day waki
pie oh, waki pie, yes, my pako is my favorite trip.
The place is Kazuha.
Oh yeah, I know, but everyone,
waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaai  It
might not be okay, Minecraft,
this is it, Minecraft, this was so bad, oh, oh, it's
coming, everyone, the
incident, that incident, that incident, you're
still alive, please forgive me, I'm happy now, I'm
so
angry, this is not this, this is not this.  Oh, I do
n't know what it's like to wear no panties,
no pants, no
panties.
[Laughs] There are
so many English
versions.
Oh, it's so
hard. It's so hard. There
was an old video, but today's  I felt like I had become more mature when I was with my seniors. I've
definitely grown up, I've grown up
. Hey, after all, I've grown up. Hey,
after all, he's saying, "
Yes, I've grown up."  Why, why, why are you stuck? No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
tickets are growing up, but they're cute
. Even now, old Watari is still cute. Senpai has grown quite a bit. Now that I've
seen him, I wonder if he's worth it. Senpai's not that bad, isn't it
? It's amazing. He's definitely not that bad.  What's the meaning of that? I
wonder if it's Kaede. Let's
go back to Ogo.
[Music]
Thank you for watching.
Yeah, I get it, I think it's great, I think it's really good, it's really crazy, isn't it? The pie is the best,
from the side of the Beth to the pie. Yeah that
LINE. That line is
beautiful. That's right, it's art. Pihu, what
do you think? Abu, from the bottom of that poop,
for example.  It doesn't hide all of your boobs.
How about when you cut off your top, you can see your boobs from below? It's good, right? It's good, it's good, it's
good, it's good to have a bottom. Yes, it's good to have a bottom. Yes,
you can see it from the side, you can
see it from the bottom.  Which way do you look at it
? I know, I know, I understand. It's okay if I look at it from the side, or
from the side, or from the
side. Let's go to the next one. Let's go to the next one
. Let's
talk about the history of Bat-senpai's Night Fiba.
History.  I
don't know what's going on right now, but the
reason I started doing it was because I was
really nervous, and when I
sang it during my debut broadcast, my voice was trembling and shaking,
but I
understand, I want to overcome that and someday
live.  I wanted to do it, so I wanted to practice for Maso's live performance and also
get better at singing,
so I thought it would be a good idea to do it every week, so I
started One Night Fever Oe.I
started it right after my debut.  About a month later,
maybe a little later, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
after I did that fluffy song, I
was like, oh, yeah, that one night.  That's what I
wanted to hear
Sorry
I was trying to
gethertoEXPlikeHow
startedasamandthen
eventuallyafter
doingitlikeforalonglongtimeIT
becameyouknowan
actualConcertWhatI
wantedtohearwasHardtogetHertherebutShe
saidoriginallyShe
wasreallyreally
nervouslikeduring
HerdebSTREAMsheedto
singbutHerVOICEwas shakingre allyreally
badlyWhenand
herselfalsoto
performin
concertedtoget
betterforDADandShe
thoughtinorderto
improvedoitlike
everyweekandsolike
aboutmonthsorsointo
HerCareerLIFEShe
startedNightOfand thenafterdoingitfor
alongtimeITturned
intoRealLifeConcert
thatyoushouldknow
aboutthatwasATkyonaivenueieThat's
something I'm happy
about.It's like a dream that a project that I've been doing for a long time will
turn out like that.Yeah,
yeah, yeah, great host.  Yeah, that's great.
Oh, thank you, you're a great guest. You
watched the first live show at the same time. I was
so excited. Don't be shy.
Remember what I said? Remember what I said?  I
asked them to do the Hoover pose, but
everyone was very modest in raising their hands, so the
customers
were embarrassed and said, ``Oh, it's so special.''  That's right. What are you
so embarrassed about? You're
not shy. Then I
almost started speaking Japanese. You don't have to
be embarrassed. It's fine
. meWatcher
[Music]
[Laughter]
AARaboutIwaslikeWhy
yousoaraboutthisis
likeaSpecial
occasionbringUpYour
ArmsandBeexcited
takeapictureand
remembered that horribly
ago That's right.It
was nostalgic and happy.Wow, there's a history.That
's right, that's what you said.
Next E-uta-n live Un-singing slot
E-heck, when will it be? Is it in May
? I'm sorry, let's go, let's go, senpai.
There's a lot of interesting information, so next time is NEXT Hasinter
Things. Also the history of cotton, which is not bad at all.
Please tell me,
oh, it's not bad at all. It's not that
bad. Yeah, it's funny if you make it into an interesting video. That's
it.
It's like a hologram.
I think it's funny that they were able to make it look like that.  I
started, but please sing. I'm
singing now. Yeah, the
lines aren't bad at all.
[Music] Let's go!
Wow, did you
hear that? Everyone is so excited.
Chiara-chan also appeared, and I got a lot of gasps.
2  About 3 times, 2 times, yeah, yeah,
that's how I got them to come out,
and it's easy to work together with enem and everyone at ID.I was
really
happy.If you call me, you can call me again.It's
okay, anytime.  I want you to read it in a wide range of ways.I
want you to read it in a wide range of ways.
Yeah,
yeah, it's
not that bad, so
it's not bad at all, so it's not that bad
.
What kind of project is it, how
did it start, and how
do you want to proceed?The
risk is that I was
thinking of doing something that would be difficult to do live streaming, and it would be like a travel show.
Yeah, and card games
and things like that, when they're live streamed, they're pretty messy, but it's
definitely more interesting when you edit them.
Yeah, yeah, that's
right, analog games, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's
what I want to do.
But it all started, and I thought to myself, ``
Maybe this is the kind of thing I'm suited for,'' and then I thought, ``Maybe this is what I'm suited for,'' and then I started thinking, ``Oh,
that's a good mane.'' That's how it
started.  I wonder if I can give you a rough idea of
what I've done up until now. What
was the most fun
time I've ever had? It was the most fun meeting. All of them were fun. A
few. Yeah, it's
definitely a trip, right?
So I
went to Hokkaido with
Iris, and Button-chan and UiUi-uu-in went
to Kyushu.  I
play Beyblade a lot with my senpai, right? I played Beyblade too. I know Beyblade. That's Beyblade in Kyushu. Oh yeah, that's not it. So you don't have to go all the way to the vital parts. It's hard to carry it. It's so small. It's so big. It's
so big.  It's still huge.
It's huge. It's a big platform. It's a
rolling platform. The Beyblade rolling platform is
huge. It
doesn't matter where you go. It
doesn't matter where you go. You need a tool.  Oh,
what's the stage
like, how big is the stadium, how
big is the stadium?
forHaveanicedayYeah
andInTheBeginning
HerprevManagersaid
Do
[Music]
Andweknowturnedwell
Herprmanagerwell Talking
About
Likeenjoyedtrav
Episod
ofenJoyto
[Music] Y EnjoyedappaREPISOSODEWHEREI ASKEDIFTHEBLADES WEREBEINGSPUNAND THROWNINKBUTNOITWAS SPECIFICALLYTHERE WASASEPARATE BOUT
HOW
[Music]
A
Let
NEED
NEED I see, I really
want to go to Japan.
I've lived in Kansai and Kanto,
so I like Kansai and Kanto, but I've also been to Hokkaido. I
want to go to Okinawa with Nekari-chan. Let's
go snorkeling in Okinawa.  I want to
go. I've done souk ring. It
's really fun. I've
done it
in the Maldives. It's so cool. I've done it in the Maldives. It's so
cool, even if you're a bad swimmer.  It's
just floating, so I'm just floating and looking at the fish, and it's
really soothing. I want to
do it, and I'm
scared. How about this year?
No, seriously, I'll be in Japan quite a bit this summer.
That's a little bit 1.  Let's go for 200 nights. Let's
go. I want to go. I'll make a proposal. Oh,
if you want, I'll pay with that Jibara
. Hey,
that's okay. I want to go. Hey, it's
okay.
Hey, it's hot in the summer, but it's hot.  Yeah, it's probably hot, it's
really hot, it's probably September, August,
yeah, it's really hot there, it's
okay, I'm going to swim, so it's definitely water.  I do
n't have a reason to do
that.It seems like it's a good idea.I don't think it would be
easy to go alone.I can
go to places like Fukuoka by myself.I love traveling.I love
all kinds of things.  I like that image, but I think it's more
fun when you're not alone, right?
No, oh, oh,
I said that. I'm sorry
, I'm sorry. I apologized to my senior for saying that all of a sudden. It's okay, listeners.  No, no, no,
sorryIsaidsorry toherbecause suddenlybringupthis OFFtopicThingbutSo ExcitedifitWORKSOUT LetMOVENext, no, no, no, no, no, sorryIsaidsorry
toherbecause
suddenlybringupthis
OFFtopicThingbutSo
ExcitedifitWORKSOUT
LetMOVENext, it's wrong.And
how do we want to proceed?
When everyone came to Japan, I thought it would
be nice to play with them.I
think that's a good idea.
Well, Oewatari-senpai
is the person who created Holo Live Illustrated.
How did you come up with that plan?
And today, what do you think about Hololive Illustrated? I
wonder if Hololive Is there or not.  I wonder if I could say something like this. Don't you
know that there was music like that?
Oh, wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's that. I'm pretty sure that's the
inspiration. Ah, that's
Hololive, too. If that's the case, I'll call that new guy. I wonder if that's an
easy name to remember.  And that
's true.
[Music]
Yeah, I see. That's
how it all started. Hey, when did you make it? When did you first make it? At first, I
posted songs that were all sung by myself.  I
wonder if it's even me who participated in the 4th generation. I wonder what it was like at the ceremony after that.
Was it the first time that I participated in it? I see.  Yes, I
think there was one.I
remember there was someone there, but I
didn't know if it was the first one.Yes, the
lyrics definitely said something to Kari-chan.That's
right.
Yes, I remember being asked for it. I don't think I've been
invited anymore. I guess I'm graduating.
Times have changed, and now that I've graduated, I can't find out. It's just
normal. It's just Chiara. That's right. I
wonder what it is about us.  Well,
on the contrary, we became good friends, oh that's good,
that's good, I was so excited,
and now I'm feeling really horrified. I wonder if it's going
to be long, and it was performed at festivals, festivals,
or even expos.
How do you feel? No, I'm
happy, the number has increased.
Baba, now Sananka is
involved, Terue, I wonder if there's some kind of hoax. I'm lying. What are you
doing? I'm going to come up with a plan and
ask the management to do something about this Expo.  It's
not like Mr. Luck told me to do it, it's just that I had to do it myself.Oh yeah, I see.It's nothing to be afraid of.He
said, ``Ooh,'' and the management said, ``Well, I'll
do it in conjunction with that festival Expo.''  Kao
That's great that you said that
showyou
dolikethatandwould
beniceifwehadlike
thistowhereyoucould
alsoSingDanceAlong
you
knowandthebeginning
thefirstONEIasked
Whichonewasthefirst
onethefirstONEwas
actuallytheoneWhere Iwasalsoinwherethe
Japanesememberswere
uptoherGENERATION
andthenIguessthe
firstGENERATIONof wasthereandOnlythe firstGENERATIONofID
IthinkthesecondI
forLittleWEED
about me and the wayweyouknow dealwith EACHOTHER
nowsandIsaidjust likeactuallyif
anythingWeGotcloser
Shejustdoescallme
thatanymorebutYeah ShesaysthereSoMany
Now
andsomanyandIasked
Herifforthenewone
thenewestonethat
wasoEXPO
MayNoNoStill
actuallySheistheone
WhosaysIwanttodoa
newONELetdoitand
thenTheywerelikeLet
doitforEXPOthentime
ITfortheeventinthat
caseShenotbeingtoldtodonotbeingHatGun
goodI see,
that's great.I feel like I'm making a lot of plans.I'm
sure it's all the questions I've asked so far.  I know it's
not that good,
but I don't think so. No, my senior is an interesting person, isn't he
?
[Music]
English is okay,
English is okay, it's
okay
[Music] It's
hot and I have a cold throat. Hachi is cold and cold. It's cold.
Dogast or Saizeria,
I don't have
either of them. I don't have any other favorites. I like
family
restaurants, family restaurants, all of them, all of them.  I wonder if I'm
still
doing it or not.
Time, PC or game console? Yeah, I do
n't have either, but I like both of them equally.
Both are sem sem.Put pineapple on top of the pizza.Yes or
no.It's okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's
okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's okay.It's really spicy.Hold on.Which one is it?
Which one is it?Which one is it?
Spicy or sweet?  I like
Seungsoo tea or coffee
or teen teen Traveling on the peach of the sea
or traveling on the famous big year
Yeah yeah yeah the beach Eh
beach I'm the beach I'm not Paris I'm
different Paris I'm relaxing even if it's not Paris
Is that so? I
wonder if you can tell me what [Music] Titi Oh, when you go to sleep, you should be naked or cut your clothes off. It's a coo. Don't sleep. Events. Christmas chairs, evenings, etc..
Hmm, Halloween, Halloween, Okay, Halloween. Seven
, Family Mart, or Lawson. The one closest to me is
Semu.
Oh, I can't answer. Which do you
prefer? Text messages or
phone calls. I wonder if I should give you a phone gift or something.
[Music]  [
Music]
[Laughs]
I wonder what you're
thinking, seriously, there's nothing like that overseas, so I'm not sure if I'll walk the length of one station or
take the train.  Speaking of types, there aren't any people like that, so
oh no, it's
A. Is it A? Well, the color of the parts is,
oh please bay, check, check,
oh, black and pink.  It's a
bit
difficult to come up with a clear answer.There
were a few, but that's okay.Ah, you
're kind.Yes, you're kind.If you
ask people from overseas,
most of them probably think it's their own blood.
Well, I don't know, but there are a lot of people who don't know about it.I heard that
this was asked to me for the first time in Japan, so I
don't check it.I don't check it.Well,
when I donate that land,
I know it, but I'm so confused.  I do
n't think it's important
because we don't have that kind of personality connection,
so
people don't ask me.  It's so
cute
Pika Pika
Pika I'm embarrassed to be asked on the contrary I'm
embarrassed LetMakeAD Let's change the subject because I'm embarrassed
Why do you mean why? On the contrary I want to see how cute you are
and look at your cute side Unhame I'm
embarrassed by Senpai  Make me think,
What, it's
scary, it's scary, I might not be embarrassed,
but I'm sorry,
beandMay, oh,
wait a minute, that's probably the sound,
right?  Ah,
when I went in, I came in. Ah, I came
out. When I went in, I was behind you, so you too,
ah, before your heart pounded, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
came out.  Do it, oh
yes, I always had a smug face on my face, but when I'm
embarrassed and embarrassed, it's different from my pants.An
embarrassed and smug look is different.I'm going to
give you a smug, smug look.You're cute.Smile,
please.Get me out of here.I like
ONE.  I'll do anything,
so I just said I'll do anything.
Please don't make me angry, just do it, and I'll
do anything. All that's left to do is, oh, Mr. Kimi.  It
's true, it
's true, it's getting smaller, it's like this, it's
getting smaller, it's embarrassing.
Hey, look,
that volume Michael, Michael Jackson,
Sheep
Jackson,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I
said that with a big face. I
didn't say it, I didn't say it.
FACE, oh, Angry FACE, do
your best. There's more to speaking English.
At the time of Angry Face Light Fever, Nathuba actually
looks great with all the accessory options.It suits me,
so I didn't want it to end so suddenly.For some reason, it always ends suddenly.It looks like
this is a cutout.It's a hot
cut.Sorry, sorry, it ends suddenly.It's okay.Madison  The
sheep are so good so so so so so so so
embarrassing.
Next time Michael Jackson dance. It
stinks. It's hard. Just J. Yeah, I'm kidding. Don't do that. Let's
go back to the noral.
Let
are OK.
Maybe There will
be a bit of a deep feeling.  I thought I'd ask you a question.Jin, I
was curious about this.I heard that
before joining Hololive, you were
making Kao for Aa-senpai.What
does that mean?
Hey, even before joining Hololive, you didn't sing.  I was at a loss.
Yeah, I didn't show it publicly, but
sometimes I'm asked to do a temporary song due to music connections,
and it's either a
song I wrote or a different temporary song.
Yes, that's right, I was asked for a temporary song, but
that song
is Aqua Eropare, right? Yes, it's
Bevery Surprise.  I
wonder if it was after seeing the 3D debut. I don't remember, but it must have been some time ago. If that's the case, then I guess that's how I
found out about Holu's live performance. Yes, it
must have been before.
That's right, Aqua-senpai was also
surprised when he joined Hololive. I think he
must have known the voice, so I
think he was surprised. We've
talked about it together before. It's not coming back. On
New Year
's Day, he spoke with the convex part of his mouth.  It was the
first time I talked about it the other day.Yes, that
's right, I may have said that right away, but that's a lie.I'd
like to hear that story.Let's
look at it later.My mom told me about it.  Oh, I
see, all those viewers,
that's where they first learned about the story.
Yeah, I didn't mean to say it, so I
kept quiet about it
because it was my song.
ThisisinterIwasso
shocked becausethis
cameUpandoneofthe
questionsthatyou
guys suggestedThank
youWaTyouknow
EverythingsaidShe
waslikedoingMusic
stuffbetweenrightBut
itwasReallyLikea
publicThingsolike
sometimesShewould
Getaskedtosingthe
DEMOlikeShewould
makethesongShewould just
likebeasked
becauseShecansing
andIknowmaybeShe
aquWasthattheoc
Maybe thatmust knowthenIaskedHer ever talkedmustalso surprisedWhenjoin theandrecognizesThe VoicelikethisVOICEI heardinmy DEMOwassurprised aboutbutturns OUTTheyfirstbrought thisupveryrecently actually That's that.
That's that.  Yeah, I'm kinda shy, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, but I wonder if it's because of this demo song
that we've
become closer and become friends more easily.
Well,
ink, ink, it's difficult, right? I wonder if you
can open up. You haven't
really talked about this much, after all. I
think you talked about it on a live broadcast the other day,
but before that, you
talked about it in private.  Well,
when I first came in, I didn't say anything, but
when I said hello, I actually heard a song with a red palette,
and I was like, oh, what kind of reaction did you get
?
Let's move on to something interesting. You have held two solo concerts in Japan
and one solo concert in Singapore.
How do you prepare for a solo concert? Also, please
tell us about your feelings and memories of solo concerts.
Preparation
is very difficult, but it
's fun. Yes, I'm a little nervous,
but when I try it on the day, I realize that the
period of practice I had was due to this. Yes, I see. It's
quite an
opportunity to do a solo live.  I don't have any. It
's special. It looks like it's going to be hard. I see. Is
there more? I
want more. I want more. I want more. After all,
lessons are hard, right? Dance
lessons, etc. Yeah, when it's the first time,
yeah, as that Hololive.  Yeah, I
don't have a lot of experience doing solo live shows,
so I feel like everyone's just trying to figure out what to do.Wait a minute, I
didn't get to listen to Holo Liveba-senpai, but I think it was Holo
Live's first solo live
performance, and I don't think it was their first time.
Probably Fu-chan and Atan. I don't know if I've
done it before, but it
was back when there weren't that
many. I guess there weren't that many live shows in the area,
but now it's
like the second time or something.  I feel like I'm getting used to it. It's amazing. I'm getting used to it. It's amazing. I'm getting used to it. It's
great.
herfirstshehave
youknowany
experiencewithityet
soDANCElessonsand
AllThatreallyrough
forherandalsogener
Itwas
Ithasbeendonelives
atthispointinWHOLE
LIFEbutkindoffresh
andforherShewasjust
likeShesaidlikejust
fumblingeverything
andhavingAHardTime
butnowIaskedHer
sinceShealreadyhad
Oneandthendid
anotheroneifitFELT
justlikeeasierfor
herbutShesayswellIT
becamemoredifficult because also
Everythingwas
likeJAimprovingand
moreAdvancedandyou
knowmoreHighlevelof
technicalevolutions
ETCsoalotofNew
Thingswe reabletobe
doneintheConcertso
MaybeEASknowYeah, I
see, andofimprove
Yourselffrom
Improvementand
EvolutionFromThe
SecondLife
Yeah,
well, that's the feeling of a solo concert.What are you
trying to say?  Speaking of that,
how does it feel to do a solo concert as opposed to a live show? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, it's nice that everyone comes to see us, everyone is
on our side.  When it comes to live shows, everyone is on my side,
but I think it's
pretty good because there are a lot of people who are really deep fans who are watching.No matter
what I do, they accept it.I'm sure they
enjoy it, even if I do something weird.  Yeah,
yeah, that's great.Even if I fail, I can say things like, ``Yeah, yeah,'' and the
second time, I'm like, ``Yes, yeah, I'll try my best.''The first time, I
didn't say anything, ``Yeah, that's right.'' That's right.That's right.Ah,
but still.  You can feel the support from the hand-holding and things like that, and it's
amazing when you do that, don't worry.So,
do you have any special memories from the live shows you've done so far?I'm sure
there are, but I can think of them.
There are a lot of things, but I was finally
able to sing out loud for the second live,
so I got the impression that everyone was telling me to do my best when the show started, and I heard things
like Ambiguous Chocolate in a really loud voice.  It's
nice to hear your voice, sing it firstThat
Shedidwasduring
CORONAtimesIfor
tocould
thatforthe
secondthelikeshe
likeheardShewaslike
backstageandheard
thefirstCheersand
screamswerereally
reallyoverwhelming
andSpecialtoherand
alsonotjustinthe
beginningbutalso
duringSONGSWhere there
specificCHthat
EverybodyDohearing
loudly
LThat contrast is really
big, isn't that Corona live and the
non-Corona live? Yeah, well, good, good, good, good, good,
good, good, good.
Hey, let's move on to the next one.  Yes,
NextOneis, I
have performed a lot with my senior, Hakari-chan, but are there
any interesting episodes from the time we spent together?
Well, I'll talk about that later.Okay, let
's go first.  It's true that I'm always busy,
but I feel like I'm tired.
But when rehearsals or songs start, I get
really excited and start moving around a lot. I do
n't know where they get that energy from.  When it
happened, it
felt like Ripa, but all of a sudden, the more I felt, the more
Ekari-chan was there. I wonder where that poop is. It's
amazing. In my image, it's probably the festival from that summer.
But I feel like there's going to be meetings between
Wa-senpai and others at festival festivals,
and I feel like ``I'm so excited'' is
pushing it too.  I'm
including Baby,
right? Yes, that's what the management has
decided.
But somehow,
even without that, we're still doing things together. If you
put that together, we'll always be together.  I
thought it was strange that we had such a strong relationship.
Is there anyone else in my house who would like to make music together? It doesn't have to be me,
though.  It's not like that. You do
n't have to say it.
Then we'll both
say it. It's Kia. Yeah, I feel like I'm making you say that.
No, I don't think so. But that's different. I want to
do dance music. Oh
yeah, that's fine. I'm going in that direction.  Yeah, I'm going there,
so yeah, the dancing is really cool, and the singing is really good too.
Thank you. Also, the second person is
Ina-chan, Ina-chan, and so on. When I
put it together, it's kind of fluffy and fluffy. It's a
beautiful sound.  Singing,
Soina-chan is usually kind of slow.
Singing the song is soothing, so it's soothing for Wataru-senpai too.
So I think it's perfect when we put it together. Oh, yeah, let's
play takoyaki with a proper bounce width. Oh
yeah, and we'll do something together.
There are
some things I've said I want to do, but when did I do them? Last year, maybe last year. It's almost
time to move on, but it's true that things like this take time. There are so many things to
do, so I don't know when to be
specific.
saidknowimpristhat
alwaysseembusyandEX
themomententers
roomupic
really
MINGandIupthatjust
happen
toonly
their
totheman
themandalsosumerfal
recentlywas
ManagementchoiceSoI
waswondering
likeIwonderwhyIget
thisimpressionthat
Theysosopushed
Togetherbutlike
Mysterious
Managementmustlike this
combinationand
thenSECONDPartofthe
questionwasifthere
someoneELsewantto
makeMusicandyouhavetome I
knowkindofpushing
for
sauseDANCEMusic
STYLEMusicwith
meuseIdoandalsosays
IHaveA
goodingwellthat
makesmehappyButThe
personPER
[music]
he
[music  ] I
hope someday there will be a collaboration between Neina-chan and Wata-senpai. I'm looking forward to it. I
want to do it together with Kira, but I feel like it does
n't have to be Watari.
I'm fine with Japanese members or someone.  That's right
enid I'm on
GB station I'd like to try it together
Hmm, honestly it doesn't matter who
I am, but I'm happy just to do it
with anyone I'm honored to be with anyone But yeah, if you
say no, I'd like to do it with you,
Senpai.
I
guess I have no choice but to do it, I have no choice but to
do it. [Music] I don't know if it's Danmi or anything else, but it's difficult.
Kiara basically makes some kind of K-pop type of music, so yeah,
yeah, yeah,
that's the direction.  There are people I think I'm going to meet,
like Laplace-chan. Yeah, Laplace-chan came up. Lapu-
chan really
likes our music, so maybe Lapu-chan wants to do it, too.
Muna-chan, I'm
sure.  I want to do it with Moona-chan,
Moona-chan, Moona-chan. Ano-Muna-chan
also likes KPOP and
has a few songs like that too, so that's true for Mona-chan. And Muna-
chan has an image of having something to do with her,
so Kia is not the mayor,
but I don't know.  It is said that the image of the sun is the
sun, so if you put two people together, it's an
eclipse.How do you say it in Japanese?
The moon and the sunThe moon comes in front of the sun.Even if the
moon is the sun 2  Two colors, two colors, yeah, yeah, yeah,
the moon eats the sun, yeah, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
so Muna-chan and Kia eat two meals,
right, so we have to do it together.
No, I'm really strong, and I
want to do it anytime, anytime. I want to do it, so let's do it with three people. It
doesn't matter, but it's better to have two people. Yeah, I cried. Good, no, just the
two of us, Mu-senpai.  Looks like it's just the two of us
. I
want to say goodbye and sit on the ground for a while. Having
All then, let's
go to the next question. Oh, I'm going to drink some water, so please
make that cute face.
Thank you, mytalk. By the way, that
hot talk is already here.  It's the 4th anniversary this year,
but it
's a long-running show, so on the 2nd anniversary, they
released some merchandise. I
posted a photo on Twitter today,
but it was released about a year and a half ago.  It
arrived at my house
about 2 months ago, so it seems like it's been a while since I
last saw it. Today, there's a log of Holotoku drinking water from the cup for the first time today. It's
really special.
anniversthough
annivOh yeah,
there's a shirt too.It's a senpai, and on the back it
has all the names of the hottoku guests that have appeared so far written on it.Next
time, if it's still possible, please write the senpai's name
as well.Yeah,
yeah, I'll be waiting.Yeah, MaybeOne
DayDoAnotherTand
havenameonmaybe
maybe Ajaa Next Let's Go NEXT I
think one of Haibame-senpai's goals is to perform at Budokan, but for overseas audiences, why
is performing at Budokan so special and why is that a goal?
Please explain to
me. Budokan is a
place where Japanese musicians aspire to be. It's a place where
everyone aspires to a high level of formality.
Yeah, just like me, it's not easy to get into. It's a strange
place, but that girl
sings like that.  When I was doing a video called ``Unmaki'', people were
watching it at the same time while playing rock, paper, scissors.
[Music]
Tewame Budokan,
let's go to Budokan.
That was the trigger for me to become conscious of the sense of martial arts, and I wondered if it was a good idea to aim for something like cotton.No, it's okay, isn't it?Having a place to aim for gives me the strength to work hard, so that's the place I aim for.  I've been receiving this, so I
've been saying that as a goal for a long time,
and now I'm not just dreaming about being with my mate,
but I'm
also dreaming of being
together, so I think I can say that I want to stand up.  I
really liked the idols from Hello Project, an idol agency, and their
graduation concerts were usually held at Budokan or something like that, so it's
not like that, but the special concerts are
no, no, I don't mean that, special
concerts have a bro feel.
That's right, I have that image in my mind. Yes, yes, yes, no,
no, no, no, no, that's
not what I mean.
May
know Tokyo, is
n't it?
ofShewasdoingA
STREAMWhereIthink
shewaslike watching MUSICVIDEO
orsomethinglikethat
and
thenbasicallysaid
Youshouldgoto
and
reallyformetotryto
AIMfor
[Music]
somadeHerandmany
times
inamandherDreamwith
theandHOPESthatOne
Daycanmakeit
come on
theageher
[Music]
So
yeah, this year?  I wonder if it's my age.
Well, someday I'll have to try harder.
Will
happenI think
has the next question is long. I'm sorry, but
it's fine.
This isn't your question,
it's my opinion, but when I was preparing this interview,
that summary-senpai  I understand how much
influence you have had on Hololive.Yes, I
think you have given a lot to the community and the company.How do you feel about your
own position and your constitutional contribution to Hololive?  He
gives me a lot of praise, even though
it's the truth,
but he's just doing what he wants to do.Oh, I guess it's
not that much of a thing, like
carrying Hololive on his back.I
don't think it feels like he's doing it for Hololive.Yeah, I like it.
What I'm doing with Hololive and what's more,
Hololith is also
good for everyone.I'm happy to
do what I feel like doing because
it feels natural.It
's natural.  It
's probably best to just do it on your own. I don't think so. If it becomes an obligation, it's
tiring.
I'm Kim
. I'm Kim. I'm happy. Oh, I'm Kim. I'm Kim. I'm happy. Oh,
hey, I'm going to catch him.  Yeah ref
basicallyShe
reallyhappytobe
praisedsomuchByMe
butShejustdoeswhat
shewantsbasically
likenotThatShedoes
itforlikeforWHOLE
LIFESAKElikelikeforthe
Managementor
somethingorlike
tryingtodosomething forthemjustifShe
doingitfortohave
somethingforthe
vierstoenjoyforthem
tojustbenefitfrom
[Music]
Isaidprobablythe
bestifjustlikeyou
knowifthatwhatit
feelsIspeakEnglish
anymorejustgo
Personally and
as a colleague of mine, I can
say yes to this live performance.  I haven't been involved with Kana or Kama Hibanai yet,
but I'm
very grateful to Watari-senpai for creating fun places where I can participate in projects like
that.  It's the same with holotalk,
right? Well, that's what I'm
trying to say. I'll call you everyone. Thank you for translating it, Sayana.
Actually, there are a lot of people. That's it,
Nakanaba-senpai is among these
viewers.  I think everyone knows this, but I
feel like it would be nice to know more about it for those who can't speak Japanese, but I
also feel sorry for it because I'm not very good at it,
but I guess that's just how it is.
Planning: Yeah, I'm doing my best, too, but it's amazing how many seniors are
doing it.I
can't do it at all, so I always have to rely on it.There
are subtitles.
toShecreates
projectsandfunIdeas
whereWecanbePartof
ittooandIThinklike
reallyrespectable
andhonorableandI
lovethataboutherand
reallythankful
[Music]
Thank you so much
for all the comments.
Did you ever have any difficulties while being in Hololive? And
is there a reason why you were able to continue your activities
? I mean, I had a lot of trouble right after my debut. I guess I'm
done with the crappy, crappy, crappy network.
Yeah, it's been a crappy line for about two and a half months, so
wait, it's
a bit long, but it's so quick
that I'm trying to do my best, and that's
it, so I'm pretty disappointed. Oh, and I
can't even collaborate or call people on the line.  Well, I've
never done anything like talking while playing a game, so
it's difficult at first, but I can't seem to do anything interesting
while talking while playing a game.However, I've
gotten better at it.  Well, I guess I did it right away.I
think I
did it because I'm good at speaking, so I
think my seniors will be happy.That's why I was able to keep going.The
truth is that everyone
supported me, and the Kurama members were the same, too.  To all of
you who have commented like this, I hope that
someday this crappy network will become a funny story.I
hope you're encouraging me, and it's completely
funny.I mean, it makes sense because there are people like that in the
first place.  For many months, my
computer was weak, and
for the first month, I didn't have any money, so I
lived in a one-room apartment in Japan, and
even when I spoke in a voice like this...  The person next door was buzzing right away,
so I
couldn't stream it right away, so even when I
moved, I didn't have an internet connection.First
of all, I lived in my manager's house for a month.
But the manager's
computer was so messed up that I
couldn't even play Minecraft, and it really
felt like a bit of deja vu.You
know, it's frustrating when you have a hard time at first,
because the first time is important, you know,
debut.  But it's
still a time when I want everyone to know about it.Even now, I
wish things had gone better at that time.I wish I had done better,
and now I'm saying things like
sayingforaboutwas.
famousOhGodInhad
famous
shidthatwaslikefor
twoandHalfmonths
whereShewastrying
HerbesttoamHERHER
InternetCUTout
[Music]
disenbythatand
crushedandWhenwas
sayingthatIBIG
momentandShesaid
alsocouldcollab
eitherwithpeople
becauseofthatinthe
beginningandANOTHER
THINGWasthatshehave
streamingexperience LIKETALKINGwhile
gaminglike
multitaskingSothat
wasreallydifficult forhertooShefelt likeMaybeShewas
really entertaining
becausewhilegaming
Shejustwas ableto
talkaboutanythingwhatshe
FELTbutsureshelike
improvedinthatIknow
ifitreallywasan
issuebutsureShe
improvedinanycase
andthenShesaid
becauseofeveryone
supportshelikeShe
wasabletogoThrough
thatfaceandShe
reallythankfulthat
Everybodywasthere
forhereeveninterestingWhen
EverythingwasGoing
reallybadlyAndnow
justtoaboutthoseand
[Music  ]
In Word, there are so many famous words like "Matawa-senpai isn't that bad"
or "Shut up miscellaneous answers". It's so popular that I used it
too. I used it unconsciously recently. It's not
that bad. It's not that bad. I use it too.  The
small fry line is also used. The
Shisshit small fry line is probably the chairman. Is that what you
were saying about Aba-senpai's line?
Yeah, that's the shitty small fish light. Yeah, no, that's right,
from It's
nostalgic, it's nostalgic.  Hey, the line is fast now, it's
fast, it's
speedy, it's strong, it's nice, it's
nice, I recently moved, and the
internet was really dead,
but whatever happened, it's finally resolved.
spetoGOODGOOD I'm serious about this,
so I'm at work, so it's a problem if the internet connection is slow,
right?
Need
JO
Watari: Yes, my next question will be my last.
Well, if I
don't finish it soon, there will be Watari-senpai's stream after this,
so that's right.There will be simultaneous viewing, so
was
Lady
M will be streamed at a really late time, senpai.I
thought it would be a good idea to include this as a question.  I didn't need it, but
is there a reason why you stream it so late?
Is it because it's the time when you're most energetic? Yeah, maybe the
viewers aren't like that, but I'm
sure there's a
good chance you'll be bored.
But recently, the number of people who do it late at night has decreased, so on
the other hand, if
there is no one else who can do it, I
hope everyone will come to see me.  You
said it would save you time to stream it overseas. On the contrary, it's
easier to watch overseas.
SoManyotherpeople
WhoSTREAMinthenight
likeherbutIgoodyou
canhave
andYeahgetallthe
viersAtNightandalso
saidyouguyssaidthe
vierssaid
Overfor
Watch
EU
think I
can't sleep I can't sleep I can't sleep at night I really feel
groggy in the morning What time do I go to bed in the morning and in the morning it's
usually 6
o'clock 6 o'clock Well it
depends on you but it
doesn't get dark.  You
can't sleep in your room You can't sleep because it gets bright You can't sleep if you
don't have curtains Curtains, strong and thick If you don't have curtains, yeah,
strong and thick If you don't have curtains, you can't
sleep.
It's a place where dreams come true,
oh [Music] Wow, the PlaceDreams
come No, it's not emotional.
Should I have said something more beautiful? No, no, it's good
enough, it's very good, thank you very much. Dreams won't come
true. Dreams have come true, but there's
still a long way to go.  That's right. I'm sure it'll
come true. Then, then,
World, I
want to do a world tour. I
want to do a live on the moon. Live on the moon, live on the moon, live on the moon, live on the moon, live on the moon,
live on the moon, ah, it's a different moon,
ah, on the moon.  Oh
no, it was so impossible that I couldn't understand what he was saying. Then, at that time, yeah,
who's going to watch the concert? It's an alien. It's going to
be an alien. It's
difficult. It'll take a while for everyone to go. Yes, I'll
check the schedule.
[Music]
Hey, ok, Senpai, it's been a while since we last talked so much today, so
I'm happy. I
'll contact you again when I go to Japan. Or rather, I'll contact you first. Let's
play rope in Okinawa.  If it's
that difficult, you don't have to worry about it at all.Yo,
no, let's go someday.But I want to go to Snow
Clinging.
Thank you very much for inviting me today.
[Music]
Let's do our best, let's
do our best, let's do our best. There's always that one greeting at the end of a senior's broadcast,
but I wonder if I've told you this before.
I'll tell you one more time.  Well, what are all those lines?
But I want you to come in at Aphra's part. It
's German,
but it's avidin, avidin, avidin, avidin, yes.
Goodbye Mame-senpai's final greeting
: Thank you. I love you
[Music]
Cute
DETDET
[Music]
Ah