[Music]
[Applause]
n e
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
K
gety don't look at me
why are you embarrassed you not like
when somebody watches your stream no
let's watch this more you just got done
judging your
stream damn girl you stream like
this you stream kind of the same way it
was it was kind of like this just a
different
laptop
Ki
hello I
are we
[Music]
all M hello
hello it is a shitty setup I know it's
not it just works sound okay oh a bit
louder okay
wait but that Peaks you know you know
we're working with shitty microphones or
like one shitty
microphone
[Music]
uh just Frozen don't don't froze don't
freeze in
time it's the Revival of the rare
Pokemon n my inan who we all haven't
seen in a long time I mean besides that
g stream today but you've been on
vacation yes how's it how's it been
[Music]
going do you feel vacation do you feel
um like you're doing good great have you
kep caught up and sleep
yes I think yeah yeah I think you need
to talk a little bit louder cuz you guys
are like surrounding yeah yeah like that
I think closer then if I'm closer I'm
wait wait let me change let me change
this out after we'll change it to this
circle one after all cuz that's like
surrounding cuz you guys are more
like sorry guys that must have been
loud okay testing you guys talk hi much
better that is much better let's
go yummy now we're about the same all
volume I think all right and on my right
side we have the birthday
child
go okay sorry if that's loud I'm sorry
you guys you have to deal with ITA how
you feeling now one year
older I don't want to talk about it good
it's good woo
you feeling good yeah yeah feeling the
birday blues you know I want to eat this
freaking
poptart oh no wait first before we do
that well let me first of all say yes
this is an of
Colo see I'm touching she's touching me
so s really yeah I took a shower like
yesterday it's it's um it's really
awkward um cuz they're both looking at
hey
[Music]
K look at me it's making me feel awkward
but um I must say I'm an uh a looking
offender as well can I say yeah yeah um
did you guys see of course you saw you
must have seen the birthday concert
thingy life thingy on G's channel so
actually I was sitting next to her the
whole time like like literally how many
how many centimeters is that but I
wasn't looking at her face I was looking
at the screen and then trying to hold
back my
laugh try not to cough
try I was sitting on my feet the whole
time and I realized at some point that I
was about to get a a cramp so I just
tried to like slowly move without making
any sounds of the chair and all that I'm
surprised then just burst out loud I sh
I I had to hold my mouth yeah at some
moments could have said some stuff that
I don't know what what did you say what
made me laugh so much everything you
know but I think good have felt also
very nervous because I was right there
you said normally you don't you're not
being being watched when you no we all s
in our little Gremlin
cave and then we have somebody watching
it's like oh God we actually have lots
of people watching but they don't
actually look at us yeah no I I only
looked at like the screen no I didn't I
was just watching you know judging
judging her performance no but it all
went quite
oh Ena you focus on on not being Frozen
please
[Music]
oh so I think I think people want to
know um I know this about popt but we
got to get some some things uh straight
here first first of all uh am I left her
in the car um unfortunately when we went
to the Walmart I went to Walmart it was
so cool but also intimidating and um
crazy um but see we originally went to
Walmart for different reason right uh I
wanted travel
adapters but uh couldn't find travel
adapters but what did I find poptarts
and the moment I saw them I was like oh
this could be a stream let me could let
me buy as many poptarts as possible so I
put them I was carrying as much as
possible and now my arms really hurt do
you want a basket no fine I didn't think
I would buy so much but the moment I
seconds after you're like do we need a
basket no one thing and then yeah but
why do they only sell them in such big
packages what the hell cuz you eat them
all at once and you just want more you
eat them all at
once the that's not very healthy it's
how they do it here you know go big
go go big go home wait I will introduce
him in a moment but uh what else do I
want to say uh oh yeah um I guess we can
m talk about how we felt about finally
seeing one another while we're eating
Pop-Tarts so let me int introduce the
contestants because we have um five
different sorts of Pop tarties um by the
way not sponsored number one contestant
is oh okay these are
bites uh bites why didn't we get the
bites because because I thought they
look smaller I mean they are smaller but
the package is even bigger than the
other
package those are yeah those are the
blueberry ones blueberry bites put in
the microwave yeah oh you can microwave
I want to set this place in no don't do
it in the FL no no no no and then number
two contestant wait is there no applause
for the bites
place oh Blueberry Blueberry peeking
Applause let's go okay so number two
contestant we have
the
chocolate frosted frosted chocolate
F this one is my favorite it is the best
piece of cardboard you
eat I mean it looks like cardboard it
tastes like it too oh it's so bad it's
good appeti you know if if it's if it's
very chocolatey I think I can get over
the shittiness of the product
itself I'm very honest honest can I be
honest yes be honest hoft Tarts all
taste the
same okay I need to give some background
story um I sometimes do these snackbox
reviews right and the first one I did
was a trial that I did members only it
was an international snackbox and it had
uh blueberry poptarts in them and it was
the first time I ever tried and the only
time so far I ever tried poptarts and I
got to say I tried it uh raw and then I
think I tried it toasted or microwave
but I did not like it at all did not
like it at all and then people tried to
defend it by saying uh oh but there's
better ones this is not the good one
there are so many better ones so now I
would like it to be proven to me that
there are indeed better ones
I think the uh there's a spectrum of
tastes the range the Pop-Tarts fill are
very
narrow so we'll see we'll see maybe
maybe it will be different it's been a
while since I had poptarts wait what are
your personal favorite Pop-Tarts not not
out of these ones out of like General
cookies and cream and' and cream and
s'mores pink lemonade pink lemonade
oh those sound fancy Unfortunately they
didn't have s'mores or pink lemonade
they're popular so they're all gone you
know
oh so this was a chocolate FL where we
have we have no no it was on OBS my side
my side [\h__\h] I need to where is this
okay I am back it might just be the
internet dying for a sight
second the
room me what green block good red block
bad
I always ignore that oops one second uh
let me one second guys here we just need
to um do you see it cuz it's I can I can
enter
again
[Music]
wait yeah yeah we want to those pop
doarts we're back sorry guys we setting
it up again we have all
disappeared uh we'll be back in a
[Music]
second guys see
it no
no I'm holding on keep holding on these
look like did you see it
cheesee e no no no no no
no I mean it's
EG I don't see it what oh don't let
[Music]
me elma's giving us TCH support oh there
it is okay oh you're also inello okay
just have to uh okay make yourself maybe
bigger good thank you B yeah
yeah yeah oh yeah yeah the there is good
D is good okay stay like
that okay we're coming back
um there's it's a nice song isn't it
okay we're back okay okay we were
talking about pop dots yes so next next
Contender is
sorry no problem sorry sorry
sry frosted brown sugar
cinnamon y yay it's pretty standard like
is it it sounds good to me cinnamon like
when it comes to when it comes to
desserts you know it's usually like
sugar
cinnamon it's a very looks
like kind of remind you have those
things where they're like they just put
like it's like a really really Cassy
restaurant except like on the plates
it's just like
cardboard just put like a little bit of
cinnamon I got
to the image on the packaging looks
promising and good and the ingredients
look promising so it's
BL okay it's very don't spoiler me the
taste it looks BL all right next
contendant we
have the classic ah the classic frozen
strawberry onion
[Applause]
amazing like the go-to poptart this is a
poster child yes i' I I feel like I
understand why just a classic yes yes
and last but not least our fifth content
is EO I'm actually looking forward to
towards this one cuz it's new as it says
on the bot it's new I love
ego cheese it's frozen maple flavor
cheese no no cheese no no but it's from
a collaboration with cs I guess yeah
what so EO what is EO EO is frozen
waffles we don't have that we have
kellogs in Austria but we don't have
this Lego legoo oh I need to try those
okay so
bad kfp do you not approve of these pop
flavers they don't like this is what I
got this is what I got we got to deal
with it and if this doesn't if there's
nothing good here that pleases my taste
and I must forever give up on poptarts I
guess so I would like to have the first
poptart um maybe um uh Toasted please ah
these ones I guess you can toast which
one shall we you try these while I warm
just like okay okay we'll try these raw
we'll try the Pop-Tarts bite uh
blueberry umber raw because we can't
throw them into the toaster yeah and
it's raw GAA is going to toast which one
I'm the toaster man what do you want M
EO maybe not what you think would be the
winner because we need to keep it for
the end you know hype hype build up the
H what did she take she take chocolate
but you don't didn't you like this one
very much I don't think you're going to
like it okay but I love
chocolate this is not the chocolate okay
we have GAA on the toaster meanwhile Ena
tell me tell me about the hugs that you
have received from kiaba and GAA yeah so
I promis like death hugs to both of them
except I realized my arms are just
noodles and I can't hug that time same
same yeah and but my hug was strong no I
I think I was had hard hugs I think like
literally back breaking they were
actually trying to crack my back
but but but your H this very warm m yeah
uh um just for side info I ran towards
Ena from the back while I was screaming
trying to surprise her but I was just
like running and
yelling were you surprised no cuz I
spoiled it cuz I was trying to be sneaky
and I saw like I saw a shadow just like
Zoom by I was like I Lally just like
stood in front of the window just like
just like the what the the the Michael
moose
and I just I just I just stood in front
of the window and just stared inside
until G came up and
show and then I heard like a Lou like a
distant like yelling from the
back I'm coming for you and then I
immediately um threw myself at her yes I
give
her give her another one oh I'm getting
head pets I mean I don't normally like
them but thank you so I will now
distribute the the popart bites the
blueberry ones sniff first that's why
I'm CU I have a
very actually oh the the smell is really
good different from your first BL wow
yeah I think the when if I remember
correctly I did not really like the
smell from the first um I got I got to
ask just check the expired date on the
first
M that actually was indeed a concern
back then I think but I don't think it
was past the expiration was it does
someone remember from kfp like I I
remember we were looking at a few things
from the snackbook and some of them were
like kind
of iy mu iffy pop dos don't expire they
say yeah aren't they like it's just like
it's like when there's apocalypse you
just stock up on poptart is
mhm no the poptart must have been fine
whatever anyway eat this take take one
take a bite you take a bite wait let's
compare it to the diagram at the front
look at this it looks coverage on the
icing I mean I think that's okay there's
at least there's a lot of sprinkles as
this like this is like why is it hard
like a 30% decrease in the icing
Department yeah but at there's more
sprinkles in on image it looks like
those Panda cookies you
know it it looks and uh the texture
looks a little bit like the fortune
cookies to me like the it's supposed to
be soft yeah this is weird are we biting
it at the same time okay three two
[Music]
one what is that
be what is that this is exactly as I
feared what is that be s in the middle
it's uh very lacking you know
massage it's like it's like H it's like
gura without the goo it's just
raw cuz it's raw sorry
yeah
I I think I actually like it more than
the poptart I've eaten back then does it
does does to you guys does it taste
different than the blueberry poptart not
the bite the popart it's dry dry dry
it's drier cuz like the taste is the
same The Taste is the same but it's
drier because they need
to wrap like the little little bit of
jam thing in there and they just wrap it
in the
mhm thing no people don't know what
we're eating oh we're eating this one
right now
mhm it's okay I mean I wouldn't eat a
second one which is a problem cuz we
have a whole bunx
but it's actually I'm not throwing up
yet it's fine it's actually fine the
fact that it it smells very artificial
when you open the bag you
know water sorry was it open no okay
reaching it's artificial it's
surprisingly not as bad as I thought it
would be oh no is it good
though it's not bad scale of 10 what do
you where do you put oh yeah right
because I want to raage these well H I'm
not going to like compare to act we can
use this as like a base for everything
El be like better than the blueberry or
worse than the blueberry okay but I'm
going to rate it as a poptart not as
compared to really really delicious
stuff like Kinder chocolate that is like
out of the window okay cuz that would be
unfair so I'm going to say these
blueberry pop
up
bites put me heart as a
poptart seven out of 10 as a poptart
shocking GAA looks at me with a shocking
face shocked face sh I mean I would five
like like gyy five well I'm if I would
write it as a food in general I would
give it a two out of
10 even the popar scale there are so
many flavors like like for example like
the strawberry blueberry strawberry
blueberries are flavors you find in like
everything you know so they're kind of
like a
baseline put them a five well maybe my
writing will still will have to
forcefully be changed afterwards when do
you say gooda what's your writing two
two the ratios are all
the texture is not like the real deal
that's true actually yeah that's true if
I would to have original bber poppers
five but this is definitely worse than
that it's too much cookie why are these
do more critical than I am right now
I we eat we don't we consume H TI
actually W I guess
so I guess I just went in with the worst
um worst worst assumptions ever yeah and
that made it better than I thought it
would be how's the how's the toasting
going I didn't toast it because I wanted
you to smell this one before okay okay
okay okay so we are dealing with
chocolate fudge Fe okay okay then uh
back with this and now we're looking at
this I
guess what do you think smell smelled
the part smells like a
brownie I thought it smell bad really
really bad so bad cboard doesn't even
smell so strong ites smell like cboard
it do it cardboard it smells like
cardboard that had
chocolate chocolate
cardboard it's like it's like if you
took like like a um what's what's
chocolate
Bo it's
it's I get the cardboard if I think
about it I think I can smell it let's
say you know one of those like chocolate
bar you're only putting in one yeah okay
we can share that one sorry too much all
right let's let me also try like
chocolate bars like chocolate bars that
are covered in like the uh the cardboard
thing and you just open it up and you
like SN all the chocolate pie it smells
like if you sniff the box
outside I
see speaking of I see the icing I'm
telling you the pictures are lives the
image I'm I'm looking at the popt in
front of me and it like CH you know how
there's like the the Pooky Pooky holes
like you see the holes in the poptart I
feel like that's just done wrong and we
see a lot of them right now I thought
that like belongs to it but honestly the
problem with this one is that
everything's Brown like just one color
looks like de on the side yeah it looks
like it looks like gingerbread but you
know there's no color variation like
with the other poptarts I feel like like
yeah I mean there there's only so much
you can do with like a fudge chocolate
fudge it doesn't look very appetizing
but you know a brownie is also just one
color and it's delicious so I am
[Music]
excited what a what a fire ex just in
case just in case use the Pepsi that's
next to the
toaster as a fire extinguisher ah
it will work I mean it's electric fire
it depends if it's electric
fire oil
right yeah I think so I never had that
happen about the electric good I don't
think you need to worry so much about
the fire from a toaster you always you
never know K you never know oh oh it's
toasted you need a
fork she she continues to toast it where
that that not enough no appar not the
professional samier of poptarts has deed
it not enough mm
oh be on the
left what I'm going for like a p a knife
ah Tong Tong Tong I can't find Tong it's
use two
forks there it came out again she going
in with take hands hands will she make
it she made it she maybe a a fork though
yeah separate it it's not just cot
now is that I don't know what's normal
like is that what should look like when
else toasted I like it brown it's
already Brown it didn't get much Browner
done now it's worm like a gooey
brownie it it smells worse now no it
doesn't it
does e it smells like some is thrown up
now it
smell oh no smells more like brownie now
oh okay she likes it more now I like it
less now like I think it smells around
what about the fork Mrs
assistant it's going taste like pizza
that's Pizza Pizza Fork Pizza Fork
speaking of forks have you guys tried to
buy a goodness merchandise yet cuz she
has a trident Fork thank you trient
it's amazing it's
genius you're welcome look oh nice oh
yeah here fork for you too it's out of
stock wait really okay to make a fair I
need to eat this this cor
yeah wa you eating a corner or do you
the best corner should go to me
I imagine eating a poptart thinking the
corners are the best part the absolute
Center hello oh true cuz that there's
more like jam in there right
[\h__\h] well you can have it
after
you underestimated my plan
girl the corner there go we have switch
Corners
again I got busted sorry what are you
doing what is that oh you because you
know you won't like it you she took like
a like a tiny tiny 1 mm size take that
corner now will young lady you take that
or take something else that's bigger
it's wob and
fall when I bit into the the blueberry
one it reminded me of taste I did it
reminded you of what
taste and after I've been into the this
one it also reminded me of another taste
you don't know what it is thank you I'll
take another bite after you oh you're
you're taking another bite so you
actually it's because it remind me of
something that like gave me through very
very harsh days you know oh wow that's
so beautiful yeah I know something
called calorie me oh my god oh
calorie this tastes like the the the
tastes like the chocolate flavor
coloring me isn't that that like Solid V
it yeah it's literally just like a
driest biscuit ever with just the bare
nutrients SP food all right guys dig in
all right
I mean it's exactly like how I imagined
Itor I
remember you know when
[Music]
you when I put it when I put it like
when I B bit into it and breathed in I
feel or like when I inhaled the Pop-Tart
m in my
mouth it it was kind of like throwing up
but then when I bit into it and tasted
it it was okay it's a very it's actually
AR what I'm liking this waterart and I
thought I would chocolate
flavor with a bit of calorie made you
know and L to sug I'm glad I didn't take
the corner yeah the chocolate is
actually the the the filling is decent
sauce right we had a whole discussion
about sauce and and spones and all
cookies and yeah Ena was like Ena
honestly was like what's the difference
between cookie and SC aren't they the
same well I said the exact words at what
point does a cookie become a scone and a
scone become a cookie and then I looked
it up and read out a lot of professional
answers why a cooking in a scone are
different things you know what at the
same thing at the same time this is
pretty good I must say okay I ran out of
thingies oh that's why you have to use
hyper chat guys
um yeah hyper chap first you what you
say it was like I said sauce for the jam
inside the poptart oh now you call it
Jam though like I said the first time
and then gur said saying sauce is weird
I was like it's basically sauce Jam is a
sauce not a PO I was and then I was like
and then girl was like then it's like
saying like pizza sauce and I was like
pizza sauce is tomato
jam no
no no no no no no no that's not how it
works you put the sauce in the P you put
the sauce on the pizza anyway I will
give my rating now so I will bring down
the blueberry from 7 to 10
[Music]
to 5 out of 10 okay partially because I
already forgot the taste and that must
mean it wasn't so
good and then uh the chocolate fudge
will
three a glorious 6 out of 10 for me oh
six I thought we were going to put it at
like seven or eight I might but I'm I'm
anticipating even better Pop-Tarts
because GAA really um likes or or you
both anticipate the EG so I need to
leave some space you know what did you
guys think about this
one
three it's a three I like that you're so
critical I'm my taste bu today not have
okay so if the bites were a two then
probably a three yeah not hold on okay
okay okay very critical U please next uh
maybe the maybe the brown sugar cinnamon
ones you can't even like order it so
it's like in the order we that we ateed
them ated ated them let's do this for
Speed we didn't eat those yet I'll take
one and you can like sniff okay yeah cuz
nice opening skills each things
I opened um some other packaging for her
already
today to I loosened
it I struggled so you what is it I I I
walked what I don't know what it was but
then she made fun of me when I was like
after carrying all the poptarts when I
said that holy [\h__\h] I can't feel my arms
anymore they like jelly and then was
like looking at me with those eyes
of disappointment and because I was the
one that asked you as soon as we stepped
in I was like do you want to get a
basket no cuz I didn't think I would and
then when you had those can I carry
those for you no can I get a basket for
you now well GA we also both forgot
about many other things that we wanted
to buy okay what is this cinnamon
nothing it looks like it's half I smell
a cinnamon it's like smelling a cinnamon
stick just a little bit weaker okay
blushy
color very look the icing is lighter
than I remember so we're now dealing
with this one everybody the brown sugar
cinnamon is being toasted as we speak
what will it taste like
like this is our diner night by the way
yummy there have pizza we had
pizza we had a American Pizza and I got
to say it's not bad that's spsh I I
liked
it that's not an American acent I know I
just want to speak like this cuz I'm
impressed you
know oh you guys you know when I when I
got out of the
plane why are you laughing at me I'm
sorry you're entertaining okay when I
got out of the
plane I heard so many people talk in
this cool American English and it
fascinated me everybody you know I've
heard American English before but then I
was surrounded by it like surround
system do be
digital and it was amazing was cool but
also
intimidating very cool English does
American English sound scarier than
like no it
sounded like to me the people from from
the
television how people from TV or from TV
shows sound like like Scrubs or whatever
yeah it's cool s to you sound like
actors to me I guess or like you sound
like TV characters wow although I must
say British English British English is
quite something
though I love me British
English Ina give me your best British
English a bot of water it's toy in it a
bot of water
more oh it has been toasted are you
toasting it twice again yes she is
supped you okay I've perfected my
water water that's you could
say more she's thinking she's
staring it's too late my brain is St
it never works but still that's real
good a
CH okay the smell is um a little bit
worse this looks
um poop
Dart poop
Dart
not oh hi Bales ba Bales actually um
sent me look forward to this guys uh
Australian snack box uh now however it
arrived exactly when I the cont Tim I'm
excited yeah I don't know what she put
in there five different flavors of tim
tams I they're probably going to be 10
times in there and I'm excited for thing
Vite did she send Vite I told I think I
told her to not send it because if I
wanted it I could get it in Austria
anyway all right so get your fork girls
um we are also uh maybe um GA can you
separate that so professionally again as
you did before please give me a good
piece please a good quality
piece so uh in the future uh once I am
back home smaller pieces
please find smaller can we get a knife
is it gross my pork no I'm just saying
because of my pork I shouldn't go for
your pieces
do you mind
I cuz I was not feeling so good recently
but now I'm fine it's already too late
cuz I just like bug into chocolate I did
too and I probably eight pieces that you
had is that
good you can split into I'll I'll make
it smaller yeah so which one you
want take a good one yes this is the
Moment of Truth you've not you both both
haven't eaten this flavor before Oh no
I've had this one oh so you know what's
coming
I have actually I have confession to
make I've never toasted my pop carts
wait oh well how do you eat them M just
eat them raw m i see that's the piece
you go for by the way which one that one
that one okay I'll take
that also if we like best piece the
middle piece when you're when when I
usually eat pop or used to eat popcorn
it's like on the go you know oh like I
need some sugar for the brain like like
those anime girls running with the piece
of toast in the mouth you just R the
PO that's cute okay are we ready three
two
[Music]
one very dry that's drier than the
others and I have a lot of jam in
mine wait if we shared Forks is that an
end kiss we can have a direct kiss if
you
want suddenly she looks away and can't
look in my eyes anymore I thought it
would be funny I didn't expect you to
I'm
sorry you were supposed to go girl shut
up didn't expect that one huh I didn't
turn tables you know from from the
wrestling one that I can hit pretty
hard I saw like me whirling on the
ground I was like that's that's so true
yes just you you know when I was setting
up the stream GA GAA and Ena were like
sitting on the floor like cross from me
um but Ena was not just sitting she was
L the moment she came in here first
thing she does basically and the F first
5 minutes she laid down on the floor I
have to judge the floor you know is this
a good floor like can I defend my life
on this floor is it how is it it's
decent is it a 10 out of 10 floor not a
10 out of 10 but floor speaking out of
10 speaking of 10 out of 10 whatever we
rate this pop chart it's trying to choke
me
do I think I like it better than the
chocolate one cuz the chocolate one is
like so obviously processed artificial
flavor but at least the cinnamon saves
this one I honestly already forgot what
the previous two is keep on foring
Cinnamon is there it could be more
cinnamon it was too dry did didn't you
think the same how how do you Rite this
one is a free
four I I was going to give it like a
four four oh wow it gets higher and
higher it more cinnamon it just all Tes
to Sugar Sugar a little more cinnamon
with little more okay you can like if
you have cinnamon at home you can just
sprinkle some more talk I think that's
why I like the pink lemonade cuz it
actually like a flavor it was like sour
sweet and M all
right I will give give this one uh 6 out
of 10 which I think is the same as I G
gave this one I think five out of 10 6
out of 10 6 out of 10 or did no 6 out of
10 I don't remember well you guys got to
keep counting you're ready forgetting I
say no I
say the dry is kind of ruined it for me
and I had the middle piece y' will not
dry it fell where draw to me I say five
sorry I'm going down 5.5 out of 10 sorry
sorry I'm very sorry cinnamon I love
cinnamon what are we going for next are
we going for strawberry strawberry
Strawberry the classic classic um I
think um the classic I I expect this to
taste very
artificial it's probably around the same
level as blueberries
artificial okay then let's get but you
know there there must be a reason it's
like the poster child the pop carts
maybe you'll find something in it what
you like about it I know banana flavor
banana flavor like like banana cream pie
flavor there could be is there is there
banana pie what was it called banana Fe
pie banana Fe you know what that is
banana Fe is amazing I want that it's a
poptart I'm
opening the poptart oh pretty it's cute
artificial pastry it's artificial yeah
there is okay cream po smell the smell
is look at it not even close to
Strawberry it doesn't even smell like
strawberry actually it's probably cuz
the strawberry part is covered up so
well but once once you actually like
taste it you'll taste the all right then
please get to work young lady it's your
birthday but I'm making you work but but
G was really excited about the thought
of tasting Pop-Tarts when I brought it
up she was very supportive I'm happy
about that it's good I mean it's good
small amounts it's just when you eat
like the whole pocket you just feel like
a sugar wash so much sugar if you guys
wonder why Ena just sounds so distant is
because she just laid
down your tumy please she's sideways
she's
horizontal how could you
tell she's back she's back I'm back all
right well it's go that me and um we
forgot to like you know get something
for breakfast but it seems like we have
more than enough for breakfast tomorrow
oh no but if we if we if we eat this for
breakfast we won't last very
long very lovely for the very first like
30 minutes and then we're just de
yeah the
for's
vegetables I forgot the word for
breakfast vegetables what breakfast
and a salad we still have leftover
pizza let's pick off all the Green flers
from that it's good cuz a girl doesn't
like green pumpkin you don't like
mushrooms I like them yeah I took off
the mushrooms I mushrooms thank you
thank you very much you didn't have to I
like actually my family we fly over
those mushrooms like you know those TOS
that like fall off when you like take
the P out of just like fight for it with
our for like I would fight for it if it
was corn corn M corn or pizza pizza why
are these people so shocked I've never
seen cor wow
uncultured you see this is the cultural
shock the culture exchange
that just like ah not Mar no pizza no no
it's I I talk to Italian people corn is
okay tuna is okay
[Music]
too that's what it is you little
she stiny oh you already done that was
fast oh is it's leaking it's liing it's
juicing you can you please cut
even
cutting okay Ena is the cutting Master
now please cut poptart PL small part
please small what's leaking the poptart
it's leaking juice guys so this one I
like the the visuals isn't this what
theang cat cat looks
[Music]
like wow you're doing such a good job
thank you you cutting enough pieces for
a whole party you guys want to come byy
eat our uh remaining poptarts we have so
many I'll this is what poptart you guys
I'll take this one be responsible don't
poptart popart respons popart don't pop
the
Tarts yeah don't pop the Tarts like you
pop the
pimples I I could never resist all right
I will say I have popped my pimple
yes have you popped your Tarts I have
never popped my
Tarts whatever popping the Tarts means
all right okay 3 two one
[Music]
go e why is it
sour
sour I don't like it why is it sour I
don't like it it's
sour the S part you you two have eaten
it before I haven't it's been a while
though and as a strawberry coniss short
that is an atrocity that is offensive
there are sour strawberry strawberries
out there like I mean normal
strawberries as a
fruit people eat this
Frozen yeah maybe this one is better
Frozen what you is better not
toasted the not toasted flavor of the
strawberry one
it hot strawberry I don't know about
that it's notp it's like making
strawberry jab except instead of like
letting it
just just dig in while
it's it's better not
eat wow roasted you roasted the poptart
I didn't know that was also a way of
eating it roasted not toasted no but um
I will I will give this I
oh so it's even hard to give it a one um
really this one is really really like
bad for me I I mean I'm not fing up so I
guess I'll give you a one is it worse
than the the blueberry one you have
before memory I can't even remember the
flavor of the one I ate 5 minutes ago I
cannot remember the
last yeah I'll give this a one out of 10
because at least I by the end you're
just going to be like they all taste the
same yeah cuz all that's left over is
that sugary flavor in your mouth M but
we have one last one EG go EO yes okay
this one is a pretty not the one that
you guys see on screen we actually have
a a value pack in front of us we're
getting
this sorry that's loud I know guys
sorry go away go away I can feel the
sugar M sorry sorry loud sorry sorry
apparently this is an ASMR
microphone wow very yellow ew looks like
cheeseless
cheeseless Okay Okay the reason I just
um looked so disgusted is the first
smell that you get wait I shouldn't say
this cuz it sounds bad the first smell
that you get is a really strong Maple
Sy um I mean no problem with maple syrup
but it's just not what you expected I
yeah did you expect the smell cheese I
guess yeah when I looked at it I
probably expected egg
yolk oh yeah it's definitely syrup yeah
very strong maple syrup
uh which
does have some potential because it
smells so legit like zero okay are we
toasting this one or we just going to
try it I guess we're toasting it
let's toast it we do have to defrost the
Legos
egos my OS yeah well you know I think my
viewers know that when I eat um waffles
and pancakes that I do not put maple
syrup on them I'm sorry
Ina why are you sorry I put Nutella on
it that's good yeah she gives me a
Nutella and if possible if I have
anything there put also blueberry fresh
blueberries or fresh strawberries or
raspberries with the Nutella and and
then one more yeah whipped cream or ice
cream as a chopping vanilla ice cream
makes it even better the girls are green
to me m yeah great well we
disagree I mean I found a weird when
there was when I found like waffles and
fried chicken worthy I was like I ate
that before I ate that in Japan
um chicken waffles it's called chicken
waffles yeah yeah I ate that cuz there
was like a restaurant who was doing wait
where are chicken waffles from again in
America there's one place that
specializes in chicken waffles one area
something sou yeah something sou like
yeah
Texas Missouri New York City South South
no no I don't mean the restaurant I mean
the area yeah Florida okay whatever it
was just a restaurant in in Tokyo that
specialized is on Dad Cuisine so I tried
it but it was just wrong my w does have
to be
sweet I can't have you know I love
chicken I love waffles but I can't have
chicken on waffles I tried it though it
was I mean it's decent cuz they're
they're balancing the salty with the
sweet but it's just there's better
things that you can do that with instead
of chicken exactly I would I would take
order the chicken waffle and then put it
both in separate plates and then eat it
separately yeah the waffle is the
dessert waffle yeah waffle dessert it's
just not the same time what about wow
eggs do like a sweet egg
on cuz I put sugar you can put sugar
wait what you just said I have to expose
jenma right now oh no JMA spare her no
you know jenma is as real yeah yeah yeah
no she knows I'm exposing her at some
point because I wrote I wrote this down
in front of her recently was a guest at
dami and jenma came to support me there
as my manager and um so we had breakfast
together and jenma is very busy so she
likes to be efficient so she um took a
bowl oh no and she put everything in
there scrambled eggs I don't know what
what all the things she put in there but
one of it was scrambled eggs and then
probably I don't know some pan yeah
pancakes small pancakes
and Nutella and fruit or something I
don't know she mixed everything in a
bowl and it looked like a mess like you
know like those Pok
Balls yeah and then I was looking at her
judging judgingly looking at her when
she took a scoop and in the scoop was
scrambled eggs pancakes and
Nutella e she has and I thought okay
that was probably just a mistake she got
the Nutella on The Scrambled EGS by
mistake but no the second scoop once
again she combined scrambled eggs with
Nutella and I'm like she's JMA yeah are
you okay you know I'm going to expose
you yeah and she said um it's just
efficient yeah I have to talk to girl in
a few hours so I'm
going no she said that and she's right
that in the end it all just comes
together in the stomach anyway that's
why I excuse sometimes but just not
I'll
try I mean I mean it is true like salt
brings out the sweetness and things and
maybe the egg adds you know creamier
texture to the food as you chew it I'm
trying to defend Jemma
here we don't need to defend Jemma we
all love Jemma here yeah just roasting
her a little bit all right we need to
here she's going to wake up in cold so
she like what's happening somebody
talking about me our new separation
Master uh Ina will separate the the last
this really looks like mustard I
I it's like Pac-Man it looks weird yes
tast like Pac-Man but you guys looked
forward to this I hope you guys like it
I feel like this is going to be like the
sweetest out of all of them I just have
a
feeling it's like everything is sweet
already but this is just oh I just want
to uh also one more time say I have no
problem with maple syrup itself but like
if I have a pancake with maple syrup I
would like to add more things like fruit
but maple syrup in theory is okay just
not oh she took she took a good piece
I'll take this
is this middle middle piece Namy numy oh
dear okay the last one three two one
[Music]
H
sad what
happened what
happened well it's I I can tell you it
tastes like maple syrup I guess I guess
tastes like sugar no do it just tastes
like maple syrup right yeah there is
definitely a maple syrup taste but
barely it's it's very overpowering over
any other flavor no I me I would have
been more impressed if it tasted like
cheese H is there any like like Savory
poptarts like turkey dinner yeah maybe
there's a I haven't seen one I haven't
seen one okay I mean it's not bad I'm
surprised like half a water balll every
every Bight get that out of my mouth we
going to have the cold s
going to dream about bu being buried in
pops
no um I
mean oh G continues to eat it wow that
is a bold Choice it there's like it
tastes like it the aftertaste
like wasn't even that
bad oh was it a uh it wasn't so bad or
uh it was bad bad oh I don't like ITA
doesn't like it what's the
rating two wow I would actually put
these higher now that I've had the rest
this one gets lifted blueberry gets
lifted the bites the bites flavor the
texture I will bypass the texture and
maybe you just forgotten take one
more she's doing it and you will
remember that it was lacking some
moisture oh she's biting
in she remembers St your looks a little
better than the ones we have oh the
ratio of well maybe yeah it's
inconsistent it's hard to get if it's
like yeah okay uh so as is the rating
going down
againat okay well I will write this as
a personal just personal it wasn't
bad like cuz it tasted like maple syrup
so if you like maple syrup you will like
it I'm not a big fan generally but it's
not too bad that I
say I will thr up so I'll give it a 4.5
out of 10 what about youa I'll prob the
same as the cinnamon on these on cuz at
least the the flavoring is not like
fully artificial like the other
ones okay actually tastes like water
advertises yeah yeah yeah yeah I point
for that but pop Parts in general are
just wait I don't remember which one
Chad do you remember which one I rated
the highest cuz that will be the winner
chocolate is it no what what no this one
I don't even have this in such a good
memory are you sure you said was nice I
thought you going to hate that one I'm
so s well I like chocolate a lot you
know
really that it seems like I red this one
yeah I think this one was like
seven or six ah choco was six oh six wa
what's your personal winner
everybody oh dear I'll take this home
I'll take this home
then will I will I tell I think yeah
only the cinnamon for me okay this one
go to E was too too sweet wow what about
you did you want to same good up I hope
not if I had to can C paste another V
yeah if I had to pick one out of the
remainings I would pick the strawberry
oh classic classic an appreciator of the
classics we were so excited about the
Egle and now so one of the few ones left
out maybe it's because we had such high
expectations that we're let down
more let's give it to the chat here
some you guys are of
eggs you can have these ones to the
bites are good to share yeah take them
to school if you go to
school all right and with that we
already are over an hour you know I'm
sorry guys but we got to keep it uh
short but look forward to more of
collabs what more more
different combinations of people perhaps
in the coming days
yes very exciting yeah more more but
wait there's more yeah there will be
more but there was more yeah wait
there's more yeah there will be more H
but also uh yeah sorry that this was at
a late time for a lot of you guys but uh
you know we have stuff to do okay busy
busy yeah busy um but we'll we'll we'll
get to you guys we of course want to
share these memories of us hanging out
together and the poptart testing was
really a spontaneous decision but it was
fun so I hope you guys enjoyed that now
poptart sponsor us soon please thank you
we are very nice to your products I
think giving you good
ratings K we love you Kell's Kell's very
good I mean I would do I I would be
happy to review their cereals yeah I'll
just leave
it Kell how about a collaboration with
kfp Kell fried cereals kogs is a staple
on the American breakfast
[Music]
table yeah Mom and I like K too actually
like they're like Health they they're
healthier brand actually probably see
probably should
yeah
oh they they have a healthy
my
lips okay okay they I think they do but
we probably shouldn't be talking about
specific brand specific this specific
brand oh come on yeah this specific
brand we have we have to stay real girl
stay real let's just say that sometimes
cereal is good to make those like yogurt
parfit if that's what I to say yeah yeah
I you know I I like corn flakes in
general but um I noticed uh we don't
really have this in Austria but in Japan
I ate a lot of pafet and they ow stuff
like 50% corn flakes in there and I'm
like I don't want you stupid cornflakes
give me more of the ice and the cookie
and everything else you're going to put
in there but the cornflakes necessary
yeah they're just trying to fill it up
to make it look bigger and nicer hello
where am I oh oh I sorry
uh I have disappeared
o the berries yeah oh well um so if that
is coming back then that would be nice
but maybe it won't happen so I want to
say goodbye anyway um kiaa power down
yeah power down dead I'm so dead what
happened I don't know man I'm
just overwhelmed by the feelings of the
sugar very nervous I was so nervous
about meeting you
two I'm I don't it's
okay and were you two not nervous about
meeting like us one
another
no no no
no okay I I don't think I'm coming back
today
um but I was nervous me in cuz like in
the end it's like you guys are you guys
it's not like another person
right I was just
nervous
[Music]
things stupid [\h__\h] phone go away okay
think it's time to leave you won't get
my face moving anymore tonight uh GAA
and Ena please um share your sentiments
for
[Music]
today hurts Ina goes first so GAA can
have us the birthday child the last word
yes you know what your
sentiment had a lot of fun haven't had
poptarts in like couple of years at
least um and I'm finally happy to see
you both in the
flesh and give you guys big hugs and
hats you guys have to see my lazy self
on the
floor but it's perfect I was just like I
was saying like oh Ena you're so
incourage
character it's just me real the stories
that you told me about lying on the
floor in your room just randomly falling
asleep on the floor seem to be
real beautiful beautiful but yeah let's
have a lot of fun together yeah yes yes
very memorable let's make nice memories
yeah thanks for the Memories even though
they were really great in the back oh my
God she's alive a you brought me back I
look very concerned nand your back looks
broken I think you guys are going to see
some stuff that doesn't work by the way
it doesn't work it's okay okay yes then
birthday child good hi last
words I know I'm excited this is nice as
is fun yeah I'm excited to did you have
a nice birthday I did I was really
stressed out but it's okay cuz U
everything worked out fine
you've accomplished accomplished you've
been you got through you got through the
most stressful face maybe yes yes but
I'm excited to hang out with you guys
now yay and now we're excited to fall
asleep so everybody thanks for watching
good night and in German we
say keep an eye out for more collabs
that um you know today was on my channel
so the next days it probably won't be on
my channel so keep an eye out all right
byebye thank
you both well amazing sh oh there it is
wait
[Music]
you know can we go tomorrow tomorrow
tomorrow that wasn't even the real voice
C
tomorrow can we get it tomorrow tomorrow
oh nice
[Music]