[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
happy birthday to
me
[Music]
happy birthday
to
me
happy birthday
dear
me
happy birthday
to
me
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
there's so many people where these
people come from
what oh thank you so much thank you so
much everyone
thank you so much for coming to
celebrate my birthday with me okay stop
looping
[Music]
okay
nothing nothing this is nothing to see
here nothing to see here okay
excuse me
you saw nothing
hi guys
hi
it's iris
[Music]
wow
can you guys hear the can you guys hear
the ambience in the back there's so many
people at my party today
i'm so happy i'm so happy there's so
many people at my party today yay
ah
thank you so much for coming to
celebrate i'm so nervous
i'm so nervous guys
anyways
is it bgm a little loud can't wait
i can lower that a bit
alrighty
ah
oh
i can't believe it's already it's
already my birthday
time flies i thought when i debuted i
was like oh it's i don't i don't have to
worry about celebrating my birthday
until until
after after the half year mark i'm
totally fine it's what i thought and
here i am already
uh okay
man
this is a huge cake though
this is a huge cake i wonder if i can
eat it all
specifically prepared for me
yes
crony flies i know right thank you thank
you so much guys
uh there's so many of you see i see i
see
uh three of you sorry there's actually
one more view in this
image but i can't
i can't fit you all
i can't fit you all but you also notice
that there's you know some some some
partying going around in the back you
know people drinking and stuff i'm not
taking a sip of alcohol today though
just fyi
all right
anyways today
um
i think i mentioned before i do have um
some
some stuff already including you know
yeah yeah that
that mistake just now but um
[Music]
i
surprisingly
surprisingly or you know
to be honest i'm very happy that um
i will have be having some people call
in for tatsu's today or um collins
birthday collins i'm really nervous but
i'm also really excited to talk to
everyone yay
um
let me just i've never done this before
so i'm gonna do my best to make sure
that like you know i'm
everything works out
everything works out hopefully but um
yeah let's just pray for the best
all righty yeah
let's pray for the best
huh
anyways how did you guys like my cover i
uploaded a cover today like an hour ago
if you haven't checked it out please do
check it i think i have it in my
description as well identity i wanted to
get something out for my birthday yes so
that's why i planned this cover like um
about a month ago
yeah
some people are like oh she's singing
identity by herself it's not necessarily
ha it doesn't have to be like a full-on
duet song and i thought it'd be a good
song to like show you know both the the
angel said and the demon side my
identity is sort of you know vibe i
thought it was perfect
and i really like the song it's a great
song
please do check it out if you haven't
yet yeah
it's like my first uh
non whole live song cover
so exciting
i do want to get more covers like that
out in the future as well so
hopefully
hopefully everything hopefully i can get
more stuff out yeah
man can you guys hear the ambience or
maybe not oh wait maybe accidentally
maybe it just turned quietly oh it's
okay i don't i don't have to necessarily
loop it i'll say it might be loud
when people actually start calling
[Music]
thank you
thank you ina and thank you guys thank
you everyone you know a lot of people
helped
helped a lot with this
i'm just i'm i was really nervous
sending out invitations too being like
oh my god is it okay for me to even like
send these like is it okay like i i
don't deserve this but
but i went and did it because you know
yeah
i needed to
muster up that courage mustered up that
courage
people say that right
anyways today yeah um
i think after after toasters i do want
to do like a mini like maybe do some
some some karaoke like you know sing
some songs of it maybe not a lot not
like a whole like singing stream no no
no no but like
maybe a couple
two to three songs maybe yeah
at the end so stay tuned like after
after all the collins yes
and of course there's gonna be
announcements it was not exciting
oh god i need to drink some more water
ah
and yes thank you so much for all the
the presents or like all the art i
received ever since ever since it turned
like um
12 12 am jst like when it turned the
seventh over here i noticed some people
like you know uploaded stuff like right
off the bat and i'm just like i was like
i was busy procrastinating getting ready
because i'd be procrastinated like that
um i was
panic readying everything
so i still haven't been able to really
look at things and i kind of slipped
really late yeah um
but i will definitely oh definitely look
at everything
look at each and every one of it
of what you guys made for me or all the
messages and whatnot um after the stream
yes
man
so like i do have two bottles of soda
with me i didn't
i didn't like actually i'm not gonna i'm
not gonna be drinking this right off the
bat yet yeah maybe maybe when i feel
like i need it
let me just put these on the table
oh and for some reason why is that gone
wait
i don't i didn't mean for that to
disappear
hey there you go
confidence juice yes exactly i need my
confidence juice guys
two bottles i don't know if i'm gonna
drink it all though sometimes when i get
really hyper i just forget to drink
forget to hydrate
yep
oh you know like oh yeah i also received
like a huge present from bay right
and uh you know what maybe i'll talk
about this like later when i'm talking
to dave
[Music]
so yeah i'm really happy
to see like a lot of a lot of people
answered my answered my invitation to
my social anxiety
is that the right word to express this
video
i
what sort of video what are you guys
talking about
[Music]
there couldn't be a video letter for me
what are you talking about
whatever and whoever could it be from oh
anyways uh
yeah to like set up all the calls and
whatnot i really really really do
appreciate manager son thank you so much
manager time for you know helping me
organize this organizing and everything
was kind of last minute
i was like i kind of want to do totsu
but i'm scared i'm scared but i want to
do it i'm scared like i was i was
basically juggling those feelings for a
long time
when i was thinking about doing birthday
stream
and then i decided like maybe like what
a week or six days before i'd be like
you know what i want to do
and
i'm yeah i'm going to muster my courage
into tatsu
and i was kind of worried that maybe it
was kind of last minute
my manager sounds like yeah yeah no
we'll make it happen let's do it so yeah
thank you manage your son so much
and sorry for the last minute
kind of last minute notice on that yeah
um
but yeah ah
there's so much there's so much there's
so much to think about so much to like
it's this is not like a regular like oh
i'm i'm gaming
oh this bus is so hard to speak
it's nothing like that so
i'm just kind of nervous
oh man it just sounds like last minute
is our middle name
[Laughter]
last minute is our middle name yes
it do be like that
do me like that mm-hmm
well what
what a chat
but yeah i i don't know something about
something about last minute adrenaline
that's how i always procrastinate my
stuff i just depend at all on a
last-minute adrenaline
and that's part of the reason why i
pawned so much
part of the reason why i met i
i pulled so much
because it's all last minute
preparations i'm sorry
but you know but i'm surprised that you
up until now
most of everything went according to
plan
so like
i do feel like even then i am still
leveling up or how do i say this
like
improving myself as a person as time
comes goes by i was worse when i was a
kid
as as i'm as i'm you know growing up and
passing by these birthdays
i'm i feel like you know everything is
becoming more smoother i'm
i'm learning
and
becoming a better person yeah
yeah that that's that's the thing that's
the word yeah
and what level has iris gotten to over 9
over 9 000 is the word
yep i'm evolving i'm evolving do you
like my hat by the way
do you like my hat yeah this whole this
whole birthday set came from
i bought it
i bought it from um
booth be like oh i like this
i think it's cute
don't don't don't mind about the angle
when i turn my head instead i like it
and yeah and all of you guys did you
guys notice that you know i was
wondering if i should make you guys all
wear like a hat but i'm like you know
what why not why not i'm worse at
drawing hair so
just put a cap on you guys
just put a cap on you guys i'll make you
guys i'll make you guys move away though
when when people call because you know
you guys yeah we don't we don't want you
guys to you know block our lovely guests
views yeah
who knows says bolt no no no no you just
guys are just wearing a hat
and there's nothing wrong there's
nothing wrong with that now there's all
sorts of hairstyles i love all
hairstyles
and hell hey hey if you if your hair is
shorter it just means that
you don't have to worry about
like you know taking forever to wash
your hair
whenever i cut my hair shorter i notice
how much easier it is to wash my hair
why wearing caps indoors because it's
cool
because it's cool
and sure this room might look tiny but
look at all these people in the back
it's a whole it's a whole house party
it's a house party i've never been to a
house party before
i heard those can be wow
but no worries
we are going to party well here too yeah
looks like an office party to me what
no
no not an office party
this is a me
birthday party
and i i don't honestly don't know how
office parties goes except i watched
like a few episodes of the office yeah
and those look yeah i i still remember
that birthday party
seeing that really scuffed birthday
party episode yeah
at the
office birthday party where like i think
her present was like oh you get a nap or
something
that was kind of memorable yeah that's
my image of office parties now
obviously i feel like that's totally not
how office parties are actually actually
are but
you know
everyone likes the office i love the
office
and obviously you know a nap is great i
i will take a nap after
this after this i will take a nap but
nap is the birth best best birthday
present ever
it's pretty accurate yep
i wonder if they actually do that like
you know if it's your birthday at work
you get to kind of slack off for the day
or something
take more naps yeah
but even then i still got like what five
hours of sleep so we're good very good
we're good
oh thank you so much for those who are
joining membership welcome to the family
and thank you so much for all the
support and all the super chats and
everything and just for coming too thank
you so much
you know i'm probably gonna be saying
thank you like at least 100 times today
so be prepared
man but
i really hope you guys enjoyed the
identity cover
yeah like
i
i worked really hard on it i worked
really hard on recording it why not i
recorded it like during my my what
my
break
last like on january yeah
like late january more like early
february i recorded it
being like yes i'm gonna make this by my
birthday there's a deadline
there's a deadline gotta release
something from a birthday
so yeah please do stream identity and
also don't forget to stream uh see the
world though as well yeah
original songs too
because i'm the singer
yeah sometimes even i tend to forget
i'm facing
so i gotta sing sing for me yeah
ah oh my god
i'm getting more nervous
i'm getting more and more nervous
okay it's okay we good we good we good
here
maybe i should start already start
opening my my hype soda bottles
actually i think maybe one of these
actually might not be soda what is this
blood orange cider
bloody
iris is recent what what
ichi on it
yeah
yeah v v tuber slash v singer yeah
blood orange is great
you wonder why it's called blood orange
until you see the color of it be like
yeah that's very
it's it's so different from a regular
orange
but you know that opening for today's
stream it was basically um
an image of how my birthdays usually
would be before before all the cheering
and whatnot
before
before this year that's how i celebrated
most of my birthdays in the darkness
and just singing happy birthday to
myself with a humongous cake
in front of my face
where i won't be able to eat all of it
so
some of the leftovers which is kind of
rot and i would it'd be a waste yeah
so sad but not this year
no
not this year
that won't happen this year
i have you guys
see you guys
step step step
of you guys and i have everyone i have
all the people joining joining the titan
and all my all my friends in home alive
even those who couldn't make it and what
not
there's like
it's just everyone's just so supportive
in this community and this
this group
i really i'm really really glad i'm
really really glad to be here and i'm
really really glad that
everyone is so nice
um i really hope everything goes
smoothly
i don't wanna i don't wanna screw things
up
and i do have some questions
to ask people
too as well
and
i'm gonna try my best to not hold too
much of it too much of an awkward oh
how's the weather sort of conversation
sort of conversation
you know what that's gonna be my trump
card how's the weather how's the weather
that will be my secret weapon
oh wait
uh oh there we go
how's the weather have you been out have
you touched grass yeah
[Music]
that always works yep
it's like um it's like the magic word
right
it's like the magic word to start an
exciting conversation
exactly
[Music]
ah
yeah not touch grace touch grass
touching grass is a good start it is i
wonder if i'll touch grass today
to be honest i don't know if i'm going
to touch grass today i might just i
might just not touch grass today i
should touch grass it's my birthday i
should but
i might not
i might just feel like eh i can touch
grass tomorrow
dress is overrated yeah the grass is
overrated let's go
when you're when it's your birthday you
can just do whatever you want
and for me that's
stand indoors
staying in the comfort of my own home
with everyone and having a house party
and just
having a blast
just got it oh
yes just got it yeah just get a potted
flat exactly oh my god that is genius
yeah just get a potted plant
just get up just get a piece of fauna
inside the inside the house and you can
touch grass in the house as well yeah
exactly
you know what i'm going to tell font i'm
going to tell fonda that
i'm going to tell fan of that being like
hey finally did you touch grass today
oh yeah
oh no phone
[Laughter]
um you can you can ignore what i just
said oh no
i think it's almost time for colin so
you guys should you guys should get you
guys should move away you guys should
move away boom
you guys should move away let me get
this
over here okay
[Music]
yeah if you want to touch grass just
touch vada just pat pawn on the head and
it's all good or get a potted plant
okay
um
i wonder
if
it's already
yeah okay okay
totals are gonna start very very soon if
not probably anytime anytime
and i'm oh wait am i supposed to do that
okay wait i know what to do
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
for the next five minutes
all right so all right
hello hi how are you doing hi hi thank
you so much
yeah don't you dare ask me how the
weather is
how's the weather bay no
no
said pirates no
anyway
thank you babe
uh
can i talk about that gift you got me
i got i got like a huge box from a
special rat
yeah yesterday
and it was like oh call me
while you open him like okay okay wait
and it was like a huge box yep oh my god
totally unnecessary and absolutely
unnecessarily huge yeah
unnecessarily huge but like it was like
it was really cute it was like preserved
flower flower um
ornaments with like like a cute glass
slipper i felt like cinderella opening
that and there was yeah there was there
was two there was two guys
there was two flowers isn't it so girly
don't you guys think we're so girly
she gave me flowers
i know because i remember um this was
like ages ago remember you talking about
how like it kind of sucks how flat
flowers die so quickly ah yeah yeah well
you know preserve flowers they say they
lost like one to three years so
it's it's more you know i'm going to
force them to force them to last forever
i'm going to force them to last forever
what do you mean one to three years no
apparently if it's enclosed it lasts
longer oh really
i'm gonna have to get myself a glass
case then
uh
yeah how are you feeling i'm nervous
help me you'll be fine
you'll be fine
actually we were talking last night and
uh iris was procrastinating on setting
up
yeah
yeah i was just like
yo don't you need a setup i'm like yeah
yeah but i'd rather talk to you babe aka
a game parenthesis i'm procrastinating
for the virus oh no how long did it take
you this morning oh no no no it didn't
take me like necessarily too long it's
just like a lot of stuff was like oh
maybe i'll do this maybe maybe i'll put
this up oh balloons and that just kind
of
oh my god i'm a big fan of the apples at
the beginning man
thank you thank you yeah i love stuff
yeah
yes
don't worry just just just everybody
wants to talk to you you'll be fine
great thank you
thank you
i know yeah you you've experienced it
already just last week right
yeah that sense you're a senpai at totsu
babe
oh my god
oh my god is pirates yeah oh it wouldn't
be the first time you called me senpai i
really have ever called you somebody
before yes you have yes you have oh my
god seriously i don't remember this yep
i would never leave my memory what um
can you refresh my memory
um i feel like you called me senpai in
minecraft
oh like in the beginning
yeah yeah yeah oh
yeah
the mistake i make in the beginning yeah
ah yeah
yeah
i didn't know how to do anything i
remember those days yeah yeah when i was
a freshman
you're melon genius in minecraft oh i
still look at guides while i'm doing
that
i don't remember how to do it anymore
but yeah ah thank you so much for coming
bae
of course
of course happy birthday enjoy your
birthday don't be too stressed you'll be
fine thank you i'm gonna enjoy your
flowers too i'm gonna stare at the
flowers and relieve relief all the
nervousness after this yeah okay just
there like yeah just you literally just
stare yeah just stare
anyway i'll say thanks for having
man ex-wife or i don't know maybe she's
not ex-waifu not so sure i wonder how
studio mart works if this is fine
alrighty
next up
i think someone else i think next up
ah
let's see
let's see wait
who's this
who could this be
to you all
thank you all
happy birthday
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man
you sound nervous i'm very nervous i'm
very nervous and things are things are
kind of acting up on my stream right now
okay
yeah i'm touching bodies between bay and
fauna
i mean you can also ask me how the
weather is oh yes
how's the weather how's the window
oh the weather it's uh it's hot because
you're here
oh oh no
are you guys jealous are you guys
jealous
i just got hit on i just got hit on guys
she flirted with me
[Music]
my stomach okay
um they helped me
come up with that one because
we were we were waiting for you to pull
us in and she was like you better not
ask me how the weather is i was like you
can just stay like oh it's it's uh it's
sunny because you're here
[Laughter]
she didn't want to i'm assuming right
she didn't want to i was like well guess
i'm using that
yeah i did see you guys you guys
chilling over there i was like i wonder
where you guys are talking about
we're talking about the weather of
course
yeah this is perfect conversation
starter
um
but i do have a real question for you
though oh yes yes hi what's your first
impression of me oh yes the basics
oh the basics the first impressions well
i thought
you were
like the seizures creature on this
planet
when i first met you
also
so say so
but you know what we say about first
impressions often times they do change
and uh
i'll leave it at that
you leave it at that i wonder what she
is well you became even more say so than
stay swiss or see something
you'll leave that to everyone's
imaginations ah i know exactly what you
mean i know exactly what you mean first
exactly i would say so but even right
now oh my god the safest has just
leveled up yeah i know i know
i'm helping a lot with the say soonest i
know you're welcome you're welcome thank
you thank you that is the best
compliment ever
yes i
um
yeah yeah they say first impressions
never lie
anyways um
i just wanna wish you a happy happy
birthday thank you we want to also
congratulate you on your cover as well
he was listening to it just now thank
you so good thank you
i mean i love i love your voice and all
your songs and i am looking forward to
hearing more in the future yeah i love
your singing i love your cover i love
your covers
i listened to her every once in a while
to get some
soothing i want to sing
i want to sing something with you
yeah let's do
it yeah
i know the perfect song for it
okay okay thank you so much
yeah thank you happy birthday
[Music]
ah
i gotta worry i gotta be careful about
remember switching bodies
remember switching bodies and that was
inaudible well
that beginning part really surprised me
everyone just abusing their going so far
all righty and next up
we're gonna keep moving moving moving um
oops
i think you guys probably know who's
next
oh wait why is it not working
oh
there you go
hello
who is this lovely
voice huh
yes
happy birthday thank you
thanks for having me no thank you so
much for coming although i heard that
you wanted to put me into a pot oh
touch my head
yeah i saw i saw the potted fauna art on
twitter once it was adorable
and they're like yes i will keep you i
will keep you in my house inside a tiny
little pot yeah
uh usually i'm the one who locks people
up in my house so it's kind of a
reversal of fortune i'm not used to
being on the receiving end please don't
turn me into a tree
please it's not like i'm the one getting
turned into a tree this time yeah it's
my birthday i get to turn yeah i mean
you're already you're you're nature
yes but i'm not a train it's very
important
don't let anyone convince me otherwise
i'm not a tree okay yes no no you you
you are not a tree you are a lovely
a lovely
forest of trees yeah you're not just a
single tree
it might be your birthday but i can't
let you get away with that
i do have i have a little something for
you
this is your birthday what
can we just spend it other nature oh
it's so cute wait wait wait wait i
wasn't ready for this wasn't ready for
this thank you so much wait i'm going to
share this oh oh my god i wish i could
draw like this
whenever
you
you can
if i practice yeah
very simple if i practice
let me put this up here
oh it's so cute thank you so much big
sorry i forgot to scale it there's no
worries no worries no i'll just do it
this is i always do that too
let me put this
this is gonna be this is going to be my
new
my my new discord icon oh
i just wanted to draw a cute iris happy
birthday it's adorable yeah i i love
your art you're so cute i still remember
when i like when i saw like your your
debut and like your your first loading
screen it's like oh my gosh you can draw
your dad's so cute oh my goodness
i also remember when i heard your your
debut practice and i thought oh my god
she can sing
thank you yeah i remember the davie
practice yeah i was scuffed it was so
scuffed
man you are you were in big big senpai
back then how about now
of course you may send pirates but back
then
you were the first senpai we got to meet
so it felt like i mean you
only had a few months ahead of us but it
felt like you knew everything
you were
yeah not even a few months your stuff
together no no i did it i was surprised
how much you guys had your stuff
together i was i only dated like what a
little over a month before you guys so
felt like i needed to say 75 like ah i'm
your senpai
yeah meet your first senpai i'm like oh
oh hi
you did a good job convincing us
of of your senpai nature thank you thank
you i'm glad that i convinced you i'm
still convincing you even now right
oh yes yes senpai
i love that word
man
uh what a cute koha i'm i'm i'm so glad
to have someone cute like it was a cool
hat and i can can i patch on your head
on your head so that i can touch grass
yes you may you may as long as you don't
uh turn me into a tree all righty i
don't wonder what these twigs are i i
wonder what they're horns they're
curious it's like yours
we're the horn gang
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah oh my god that's that's so close to
sounding like something else
but we wouldn't know about that because
we say so yeah of course of course
obviously
ah thank you so much for coming father
yeah thank you happy birthday thank you
bye
bye bye
thank you
all righty
mother nature
so cute she's so cute
alrighty
man i'm so not used to this oh
oh
i wonder
all right iris
thank you so much for coming on me
yes a genius detective i'm a buffson
wait let me switch this okay
am i am i have i arrived yes you have
arrived you have right oh bubba's here
too yeah
i love bubbles so cute there we go
ah thank you so much for coming away
yeah uh i know i know you also have a
stream later on if you do this so
good luck with that
oh thank you yeah i listened to your
cover it was so good thank you
i really well i don't know it confused
me a little bit because i guess i never
thought about the word identity but if
you say it like identity it sounds like
when you were recording was that going
through your head
kinda
i mean yeah i i was really debating how
to pronounce that but you know i'm just
like yeah you know why not why not why
not just pronounce it like that mm-hmm
it's really catchy though thank you you
know i feel like if i if i try to sound
as cool as possible saying it you know
i'd be able to pull it off
wow you sounded really cool saying it
i did see some comments
what
oh it's so cute
yeah a bunch of soda cans and they're
like a council colored oh my god that is
adorable oh wait wait wait
let me save this
oh
thank you i made it to you from wearing
the hat
oh
it's so similar
it's so silly
yeah it's the same one wait
i'm just surprised oh wait you pulled
things off so quickly wait there you go
oh it's so cute thank you mommy
i love it i love it
it's so much better than my stick people
like three irises on the screen
[Music]
thank you omi i have a question for you
too if you don't mind
if i
if i was a fruit what fruit would i be
oh
i want to say dragon fruit because like
the spikes kind of remind me of like the
horns that you have ah
i think i do get that i do get that
comparison
i want to say passion fruit boy actually
i don't know yeah
it's like your color like
it actually it kind of looks like a
pomegranate or like an apple
it didn't look like how i thought it'd
look now that i'm looking at it yeah i'm
looking at the dragon oh yes dragon
fruit i i get the similarity i've never
actually had dragon fruit before though
it's good well the yellow ones are
better than the red ones there's yellow
ones
yeah
but the inside it's like your design
because the inside has like it's like
white meat with like the little black
dots and it reminds me of like the
floaty thingies above your head ah
oh it does yeah i get it i do see the
comparison
man i should try this one day eat the
fruits that almost said i am yeah
it's good
thank you so much
i want to say i'm really glad that
you're with us and i was surprised i was
surprised because you're the v singer
but you're you're so entertaining to
watch every time i tune into your
streams i'm just like listening and i
can't stop listening oh really oh my god
i i i'm so honored to hear that from
from the creative available
okay buff sun is genius i was watching
your um your your cookies yesterday
rolling on the floor
thank you i'd love to see buff iris too
come to life like ally drew you that'd
beat me yeah one day i wonder i can't
wait to be able to do that one day yes
hope to ready let's go
hello
thank you so much for coming on me
of course good luck on the rest of your
stream happy birthday thank you
bye
bye bye
ah
and that was i mean i keep i keep i i
keep wanting to just call her amelia
buffson alrighty
is someone here already
hey
oh who is this who is his beautiful
voice
oh you know who it is happy birthday
oh thank you courtney hi crow hey
i listened to your song it's so good
thank you
yeah it looks like you're wearing a
tomato foot in the reverse meet-up it is
it is pretty much a made outfit that's
what i asked for i think the original
also was wearing a made out fit so
yeah
oh it looks good man
they never heard this song was so good
oh you should totally listen to their
journal so it's great look like stuff
man but yeah if we think about me so i
think about you
oh
oh t oh stop it but you look pretty good
in the maid outfit too so you know i
can't wait to
see a full-on
maid made a roni made a roni outfit one
day
iris so made
it's made for you it's made for me oh my
god
the naming sense
we're so good with naming i know right
it's perfect
it's perfect how do you how do you feel
you know all this time as a v singer um
i feel like i've
kind of
kind of derailed off of what i was
originally thinking in the beginning
yeah
how about you
what do you know
me about you um well you see
i thought there was gonna be
a balance between the angel and
uh like angel and the
like the dark side but i feel like
you're leaning more towards the dark
side where's your angel side your
angelic side huh i have no idea what
you're talking about what what
what
my doctor
my angel
your
angelic side where right where is it
it's right here cronie
you're looking at it right now
oh
i
oh oh
i see
oh my god i'm just i've just been so
tired i think i've been uh yeah you
should get more sleep cronie you're just
tired i know
i know maybe but you know i just had to
be here because i want to wish you the
happiest birthday and also
you know
we got it we gotta finish
our way out yeah
yeah yeah oh my god just happened that
like every time like when i when i catch
when i just suddenly break my throat and
go on break it's like oh sorry i had to
cancel and then your pc breaks when i
come back
it's like hey i'm ready and it's like oh
it's like oh my my throat
oh yeah and then hey my pc bro
something keeps breaking it's screen
yeah no like it will happen it will
happen soon though it will happen soon
yeah light finds a way out
to break things i guess i know
man how destiny how cruel destiny can be
or fate
as you call it wait yes yes
oh it's just a throwback
sort of sorta
but yeah like oh my god yeah i can't
wait to play the rest of the way out
it's gonna be great it's gonna be great
i can just tell it's gonna be great and
i'm probably going to carry like per
usual what
is that such a thing isn't that good
i have to be the better
better teammate i guess better team
player but you know i'm the senpai here
so i'll you can i can carry all the
weight crony no worries iris senpai yes
virus
[Laughter]
yes so senpai right this is just for
today just for today just just um put up
with that for today
okay
oh you know
have a great one yes thank you know
enjoy enjoy the day to your fullest and
what else
what else what else
uh
high risk it's virus
virus
why
why saying hi and bye at the same time
why why crony why
what a way to end it off oh my god
alrighty
oh
next person already here
[Music]
my pleasure
i just watched your cover oh my goodness
the crispy piano is so good yeah i love
the piano and canary songs yeah
so good so good i know i know
thank you so much for the speaker ah of
course of course of course man
ah your voice is so cute listening to it
like this like it's so close to my ear
i'm just dying
[Music]
what am i getting am i getting some
personal asmr
sweet nothing's to me
sweet sweet i wish happy birthday
your birthday stream is so cute too i'm
seeing the confetti and the balloons
everywhere are you in an office though
who are these people in the background
uh no they're they're just guests
they're they're guests that are of
course are not as important as you guys
they're just
the mobs yes the mobs
i have the power to call in mobs yeah
mom
wait like mom's like you have to defeat
them in the end oh um yeah yeah the
goodie bag to the ira's birthday parties
yes yes it's
not necessarily death no no you know
it's not a permanent death you know just
after the party i'd be like okay
now die and
and everything is over yeah i hope you
enjoyed egg now it's time for you to
perish
exactly
but no worries you know i won't i won't
lay a finger on you and everyone else in
in holla no worries no girl you can try
though
it's all right i'm sure you're you're
you're you're easy it's fine easy take
down huh
can you fight on land though
[Laughter]
oh no
she knows my weakness
yeah yeah and i don't i don't go in
water because i can't swim so if you
want to fight me outside
me neither oh maybe it'd be fair if
[Laughter]
like that that minecraft that minecraft
moment
oh my god that was so much fun though in
the boat there came up behind you i
literally that was a huge jump scare one
of the biggest jumpscares i've ever
experienced in my life like i did not
expect you to be in that pool
jumpscare minecraft accomplished
[Laughter]
that was like one of the best moments
i've ever had in minecraft uh i was
flying
[Music]
yeah will remember this i can't i can't
wait to you know play play stuff with
you too in the near future maybe
maybe yes yeah oh my goodness yes maybe
maybe ellen ring you can carry me yeah
cause i
i
i've seen you play ellen rangel okay
okay
no i've never played those games before
no that was my first souls game but no
no no no no
[Music]
it's just practice it's just practice
yeah in practice makes perfect yeah but
oh my god i do want to play elden ring
like you play on pc right
yeah yeah
let's girl let's go let's beat some
monsters and bosses
i'll stand behind you and i'll cheer you
on with you as you bob and weave but um
let's do it let's do it yeah
yeah yeah no no no worries about the i'm
pretty sure souls games or elder ring
also is just one of those games where
you just kind of have fun struggling
right
yes yes deep breath one boss at a time
over and over again over and over yeah
you can never have enough lives in that
game
true flask
[Music]
of course happy birthday good luck with
the rest of the stream thank you girl
yo happy birthday bye
[Music]
me be very nervous oh
alrighty
um
mad
so cute i can't wait to play i can't
wait to actually do co-op in in elden
ring though oh my god it's like it's
like my favorite game at the moment it's
just so fun
and i feel so honored being being told
that i'm i'm good at that game i don't
think i'm necessarily good but i think
i'm getting used to dodging though um
alrighty
i wonder who's next i wonder who who
could it be i'm i i'm not so sure that
because i'm
oh are you okay
hello
do you hear me wait i don't hear you
wait wait what will you hear me oh i
hear you i hear you hello hello
hello
hi i'm this happy birthday
thank you
thank you mommy
i was kind of worried for a second
because
you told me how like your internet was
like
yeah you so i have i have none yeah oh
my god looking at that i need to make up
a proper gift for you but i have i do it
on something really fast do you want it
i of course i want to give it to me
god i did it really really i want to
make you ambi something more problem no
no no no even just a doodle from from
you oh wait i said the wrong thing
is
what is this
is that is that you with a hat
oh it's so cute thank you wait let me
sit down now i look when i'm driving oh
driver i can't i can't imagine you're
behind the wheel
in the car
the car is what it's what i want to be i
want i want to be
i want to be that person do you do you
understand
oh that person in the car
really
would you like to be that person in the
car
yeah
[Music]
oh yeah next time next time you can join
me
you can join me in a beautiful car ride
oh my god we should totally do that
actually i'd love to please i want i
want you please yeah oh my god that that
chocolate i didn't even think about that
until now oh my god that is genius yeah
chocolate yeah you won't you won't
reject my milk chocolate would you
um
no i'll take it i'll take it
oh oh are you are you a dark chocolate
then
or is it just yeah i do i actually i
like all chocolate i just wish i could
say now you just wish you could say now
yeah oh does she forget does she forget
that
she's an underling basically because
she's cool hi just for today oh sorry
i'm so forgetful i'm so sorry oh yeah
she just for gore
oh oh golly oh golly
i also heard your color and i really
like it sorry i wanted to see that real
quick
thank you
no no your your singing is amazing i
love i love your singing and like
country songs too and whatnot oh your
unarchived karaokes are like the best
[Music]
thank you i love your care your last
like all of your singing is good but
your last card here that was just so
good
it was
it was beyond the singing too
yeah oh my god yeah we should you know i
really i really wish we could just do
like on offline like online singing
collabs too like
that'd be so cool i feel like it's
possible i don't know
why aren't there stuff that helps like
i'm not so sure
looking into it and doing research oh
would you like because like
bands had to practice for a few years
online uh-huh how'd they do it so i'm
trying to figure i'm sure yeah i'll let
you know yeah
yeah show me that civilization and
technology mom i share oh yeah yeah yeah
clutch here
thank you so much for coming with me
despite the dead internet
i'm so glad it works i was panicking i i
i i can see i can hear it's beautiful
yeah no it's it's you you sound perfect
you sound great
also
happy happy birthday i hope your stream
has been going good yeah
i hope i can watch the rest of it thank
you
thank you so much
bye-bye
man all these presents i wasn't
expecting it so i'm just like putting
pulling these up out of nowhere
ah
and
all righty oh
oh
oh that keeps
suddenly sorry
it's very are you outside
no once again i'm in a taxi just like i
was
oh taxi i remember you did that you did
that for me
i sure did
i'm really bad at scheduling
a lot but oh my god i can't wait to see
the fruits of those rick that of all
that recording man
you know i know what you went through
now i'm understanding you're recording
your busy recording schedule man
oh that means that music we must be
prepared for a bunch of bangers yeah
yeah
i hope so i'll do my best but speaking
of bangers recover it's not ugly yet is
it isn't it coming out after this it
just it just came out it just came out
like uh like an hour ago yeah god i'm
gonna go listen to it yeah
listen to it on your free time and just
having uh kelly and listen to it is it
isn't more than an honor yeah oh our
list happy birthday thank you kelly
[Music]
you deserve you deserve so much good
stuff happening for you and you deserve
the best
and i can't wait to see the rest of the
stuff that you do um
throughout your time here and i'm just
really proud of you and i think you're
great and uh when are we going to collab
is the question maybe you want to get
more time
to do it
oh yeah club i can't believe now that i
think about it yeah like i feel like
we've been collabing quite often maybe
because of all those totes like not
toasters but you know those those
jumping gorilla call-ins
yeah and chad cast and what not but yeah
now that i think about it
yeah outside yeah
yeah i love those t-sessions they're
always so much fun we always have too
much to talk about
yeah definitely i always feel
bad leaving because i always have
something to do afterwards but like
but i could like continue talking to you
for like the entire day
me too me too you know you're just
you're just you're just so you're just
such a heart workaholic
i need to fix it to be honest it's not
the best thing that's bad but i really
really do like
it's it's really inspiring how hard hard
working you are seriously man
but you too i want to work hard i want
to work hard and um i want you to work
hard too yes i mean honestly at your own
pace
please
you know don't forget to have fun every
once in a while and like you know
because you love it that's what's most
important i guess yep yeah preach it yes
but um
for your birthday um i i did not get to
write you a wrap but i'm i'm thinking up
one right now i'm gonna post it on
twitter i hope it's not too cringy oh my
god i
i will love it i don't even have to
listen to it and i know i will love it i
can't wait to hear it is it where are
you gonna are you gonna post it later on
yeah i'll post it later alrighty just
all of the things that i can rhyme with
iris i already know it's going to be
like a no-brainer
yeah
yeah all the words that rhyme with iris
like oh i risk my wrist
there's cyrus many words that rhyme with
it mm-hmm get ready it's gonna be wild
oh my god i i'm my heart my heart is
ready i
i hope i hope i can share with everyone
too when that happens oh sure
as long as it turns out your viewer is
too bad but you know what everybody
should get a cringe wrap for their
birthday i still need to make it up to
base somehow
i'll get it to everyone as many people
as possible the best present ever a
cringe wrap yeah it couldn't drop from
me
he doesn't know what's happening
for everyone yeah yeah from the rap gods
guys you guys are jealous right you have
to be special to get to get a wrap
[Applause]
i can't wait to get all your birthday
merch by the way whenever i see it oh
thank you i'm excited to announce them
too
yeah i'm looking forward to it you have
a great birthday you too and and have a
safe drive or uh you know uh get get to
that studio or wherever you're recording
safely
yeah i will i will thank you so
much bye good luck goodbye
thank you
oh she called from the taxi mad mad
she's so busy
cali be so busy i can't wait for that
cringe wrap
you too
you too yeah
man this is fun this is fun
just like
scrolling through it's i feel i feel i
feel like uh
how do you say this in english like an a
dia jew or like uh
i feel kind of like a nor is it is that
the word normie
like all these friends all these friends
man
alrighty
i wonder
if
next
day
[Music]
were you singing are you singing did
you want you
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you oh my god my favorite nephilim
my do you need to flip my nerve
thank you
but have you noticed how your hair is
the same shape as the table
huh it looks like i don't know like it's
like see see the corner see the corner
oh feel me oh like the the edges of my
hair like the yeah
i just i just keep looking at that and i
was like
confusing me like table is moving mm-hmm
oh no no it's my it's my hair
oh you've are you talking about the the
edges of my hair the ones that's
sticking out right now like it goes like
this
i think i get it
the color too no i can't unsee it that's
all i've been saying
oh yes the table's rumbling it's the
rumbling
but you're balancing like the cake and
um the mug and everything on your hair
yeah well yeah my hair that is one of my
one of my tricks as a nephilim yes the
lore
my hair moves and can carry a whole ton
yeah
i don't know i think my
my body is missing oh yeah yeah yeah
sorry oh
there we go there we go
excuse me excuse me mademoiselle
oh hello oh so cute oh so cute
yeah you dressed up for the occasion
you you blend in well you don't have to
you don't have to wear suit like those
people in the back
accompany you
yeah
yeah just as long as you you hold some
sort of sort of drink you just can't see
it you're holding a drink but you just
can't see it
yeah so you you fit him perfectly blend
in
oh no no actually don't you don't blend
yeah you stand out you stand out from
the crowd
yeah i'm pretty pretty big
but you're bigger than me today ah yes
because oh birthday girl
i oh
reminds me yeah
remember when you were big senpai wait
fourth i said this before
um you're a big senpai to the council
members all five of us mm-hmm
remember like when you went back
that we talked to for a while so you had
all of us alter yourself
yeah
i remember that lucky lucky me
yes do you remember that audrey um yeah
i remember yes
yes yes the horns were big i can hold
all of us yeah i remember that i
remember having that as my discord um
what'd you call it the banner for like
the longest time
it's actually still there it's still
there yeah yeah
it's like you know it fits perfectly
with my current discord icon because
like you know it's you know the the
buffers from cali
was destiny it's destiny it's like
double buff oh my god i want to share
that but like wait i i have to dig it up
from it's it's in a different folder man
ah
that was so long ago but i know like
longer
it doesn't i still remember watching
like anime and stuff with you guys
before your debut
oh yes yes
movies as well
yeah yeah the ghibli movies i remember
that time time is up but i still want to
talk to you about
go ahead go ahead go ahead it's
no worries i i really wanted to talk i
really wanted you to cover that song
actually when it first came out i
thought this is really iris but but
there was just a passing sword i never
thought that you would actually
um
yeah yeah i'd like i i i when i first
heard that song i was like
yeah and then like yeah it's not like
this is really iris
um
yeah i'm glad that i'm glad that some
people thought that because i also
thought the same thing too and i'm just
like yeah i should tag this some people
think it's like a duet song but i'm
saying
i'm gonna i'm gonna sing this
and do it with me
sort of survive
ah thank you sana yeah like no worries
about the time though to be honest no
nothing you don't have to worry but
man
yeah that song it's like
having like the two sides and like how
the original it's also like kind of
looks like you know the black and the
white
yes yes yeah
just like oh my god i could totally
imagine this if just just get put that
as an iris and it works it works like
wonders
ah man i can't i can't wait to hear hear
more sana soon maybe
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
take care though
take care with whatever you're doing
though right now
yeah
oh my god ah thank you so much for
coming sana even though i know you're
really really really really really
really busy right now
like let's play let's play together
again like i don't know the time let's
play it well this is far this far off
but let's play splatoon 3 together oh
yes it's not too far off
i don't think it's gonna be that far
right like it's gonna be summer maybe
they said i think they said summer they
said summer so we can expect something
definitely by like august maybe
i can't wait splatoon gang let's rise
man yeah oh my god yes let's play
splatoon yes yes
even before splatoon i feel like there's
also a lot of stuff we could do yeah
just just please please anytime when
you're trying to hit me up yeah
definitely all righty thank you so much
for coming okay bye bye
[Music]
bye miss yeah pirates
oh yeah
oh my god
all the adrenaline this is this is a
huge adrenaline rush guys
this is a huge adrenaline rush ah
man
and then
so yeah the reason why i told her didn't
have to worry too much about time is
because
we have this in line afterwards
wait wait i gotta i gotta be careful i
don't screw up which is the month in
here let me just um mute my bgm real
quick
you guys not hear my bjm right now
you guys should not be able to hear my
bjn but let me just double check
right okay
all righty alrighty okay okay
next up
[Music]
happy birthday iris
hello this is
[Music]
sorry i can't be there alive
i am currently hibernating
yeah it's your first birthday since
joining a live isn't it exciting i
remember the first time was really
exciting i think i was really nervous
during the stream so i hope you're not
nervous don't be nervous i'm really
nervous right now i always feel lots of
happiness health
and success in the coming year
and maybe right now you have a cake in
front of you just like i have right now
yeah it's for you
it's for you but just
for the internet it's hard to give it to
you
get yourself a big dress cake okay
yeah um you should stay the way you are
you're doing great i think
i hope all your dreams come true oh you
goals
sorry that was my cat
yeah and if you ever need something
don't forget you can always rely on your
senpais
yeah myth is always happy to help you if
you need our help
and in germany
[Music]
now let yourself be celebrated i wish
you all the best
bye bye
[Music]
thank you so much
just fyi though um here we go let's get
the bgm back
just fyi
i
did not
i did not watch any of these beforehand
i set them up yeah i know i know kiara's
time zone is just like it's like
horrible this is like a horrible time
for time zones i always i always feel
bad
it felt so bad but she made me a video
instead thank you so much kiara
oh yeah
no no seriously i didn't watch any of
them like maybe okay maybe i
accidentally watched like a couple
seconds of it when i was setting up but
i didn't watch any of them so this is
all this is all a surprise like i know
that the videos are there i know that
the videos are there it's just that i
haven't actually you know
watched them
yeah you've re it's like 5 am yeah of
course of course you can't she's in
hibernation and i love her i love her
new outfit i guess maybe not be like
might not be super new at this moment
but i love that mask and everything it's
just so elegant
and everyone's just so supportive
everyone in ian i'm just so happy i'm
just so happy to be here i'm so happy to
be an ian it's just it's such a warm
community
everyone's great everyone's wonderful i
can't ask for any better like better
group like better friends better group
mates better
a better
better group yeah in general
alrighty okay
i could take a slight breather with um
collins for now we still have we still
have round two we still have round two
round two collins which is going to be
even more nerf wrap
it's gonna be even more nerve-wracking
guys i'm just my hands are sweaty
but you know we we have we have this the
short respite respite mm-hmm
i really hope round two works out well
i hope i didn't screw up with anything
man
mom spaghetti yeah mom's why do people
say mom spaghetti with that i wonder who
i wonder who
but yeah oh my god i'm so glad
everything is going pretty smoothly so
far
and oh my god oh my god
i oh my god i'm totally gonna watch this
later on i'm totally gonna watch this
later on but
yeah so many
so many presents from everyone like
i love everyone like oh my god the art
is so cute and i i i love how like
mommy's
doodle is like on a piece of paper like
i haven't seen that sort of this sort of
piece of paper in a while like the ones
with the lines on the side what do you
what do you call this folder paper you
have folder paper you wonder why it's
called folder paper it's because you
stuff them in folders anyways
i think it's time for an announcement
loose leaf paper i've never said leaf
paper before i would always call it
folder paper
notebook paper really
notebook paper i don't really say i
always said folder paper
but yes are you ready for
some announcements i think you guys
probably already have a an idea of what
that said announcement would be
but let's do this um
wait where is it where is it
so many my obs is just like there's a
lot of stuff going on
already
[Music]
birthday celebration merch
i'm so not used to um
the
obvious
image sliding
it just kind of automatically does it to
me uh are you guys ready are you guys
ready for merch that's going to be on
sale march 27 today um not it hasn't
started yet but first let me introduce
you what what i have in store for you
guys
yeah oh my god it's this is so cute
right this is so cute i love this
birthday merch all right oh my god i
love it to death all righty
hey birthday celebration 2012
iriz oh my god this is like this is like
one of the best parts of a birthday is
like
getting to have merch wait wait why is
why does it move like that why does it
move like that when i try to make it
bigger oh there we go there you go maybe
i'm supposed to move it like this okay
um can you guys see can you guys see you
guys can see right
so
we have a lot we have a lot in store we
have
one birthday voice yeah yeah yeah yeah
and
merge items what what could this be
i cannot tell what what these things
could be just by the name the dusk match
wrist the mugrus the doll wrist what
could these be
what sort of what sort of goods could
these be have no idea what they could be
no no idea at all
no idea whatsoever
but yeah oh my god and yes let's let's
introduce them one by one
oh wait maybe this is not one by one
okay
the desk mattress
the desk mattress oh wait let me sorry
let me just move this this to the side
over here yeah
used to this side over here alrighty
artist by curtis
so cute
and you know i've
ever since even before the whole
keyboard
phenomenon that's been happening to me
i've been like i want desk matte i want
desk man look at how cute it is and all
the detail
me and my nice cute fluffy worm room
wear
with a whole live
holiday english tank top all right stop
moving
it's so cute i love it
and i think you guys will like it too
the desk mat make sure to put your your
fancy used keyboard on like right on top
of it
fanciest keyboard only the fanciest
keyboards are left to
be on top of this desk mat
it's a desk mattress yeah did you guys
notice yeah
there's a there's a bay figure there's a
bee figure in there too there's a big
figure in the bag it's it's cute so i
love the bay figure the details are
amazing
this is like
me
right after stream yeah just grab that
mug chug chug down some some juice or
water or tea or or soda you know there
might be soda in there there's nothing
wrong with soda and mugs
sorry let me just i accidentally opened
like accidentally
cracked up a pocky open
like i didn't actually really mean to
open it just my my hands
they just
started opening things
accidentally no seriously it was just it
was unconscious reflex
it's so cute right
and i think this will fit my desk too
this will fit perfectly on my desk but
first off i i'm i can't wait to get
bay's base despite too ah but yes
i love i love the art i hope you guys
really like the art as well the postcard
is also going to be on this all right
the postcard is going to be a special
you know um postcard for people who buy
the whole set
so if you want you can buy the whole set
and get a special postcard with this
beautiful art on it and my sign and i'll
tell the details later but anyways
and
then we have
the dolores
the dollar so remember do you guys
remember
me asking in a poll
a long time ago
i mean do you guys want a doll
obviously that that was not raising that
wasn't very very um discreet discreet
way of asking you guys and you guys
would
have no idea i was going to release a
doll
for my birthday right you had no idea
whatsoever
and i remember asking like oh
what sort of doll you guys want
and you guys gave me your answer and it
came into this cute little form
oh my god this is going to be so cute
design is by some uncle i still remember
seeing like something uncle sans like
it's like she she drew like a doll iris
art like pretty close to when i when i
first debuted it was so adorable i'm
like oh my god i love this
if i were to have a doll this would be
great this would be great as well
man it's so cute yeah i can't i can't
wait to see how it's going to be like
pretty decently big like not too big
not too big you know 300 300 millimeters
up that's like 30 30 centimeters right
wait wait
am i
it's 10 10 10 millimeters in a
centimeter right
it's a decent size
it's very detailed very detailed i love
the gray gradients and the hair
that's how conversion works math uh-huh
it's it's gonna be made out of polyester
you guys can have an iris in your room
and you can hug it
you can hug it when you're lovely be
like i need hope in my life and you just
get it just hug it
and your day will be that much better
then
i'm i'm i can't wait to hug myself
i can't wait to hug chibi me
but yeah the design is still under
development so
but the technical design will be will be
as shown here basically yes
can't wait i can't wait to get samples
you know i'm i'm already prepared to buy
my own goods
buy a few copies of my own goods so i
can
i can smother myself in in
in iris land iris land make make my
roman iris land room
yeah i'm trying to i'm trying to imagine
how big 300 millimeters is
it's kind of big isn't it
it's kind of big
it's not going to be like
yes
about three soda cans yeah that's cut
that's a decent size
it's huggable definitely a huggable size
the size of a ruler about the size of a
ruler yeah
don't drink no no no no this is this is
polyester don't drink polyester
yes the backside and everything and the
hair i think
everything is just gonna look great i
love it i love the design as well
ah and that's the dolores which is of
course it's a plushie of course
self-explanatory i love my naming sense
don't you
love it
wait can i can i take a sip of soda i'm
gonna i'm gonna i need to take a sip of
soda right now
oh it's it's in the mug it's in the mug
uh-huh
speaking
of mug though
what
what what could this be
what could this mug be
could it perhaps be
a certain mug that you guys perhaps
are familiar with
like this one
the mug is real guys
you believe the mug is real
the mug is real
when i thought birthday goods the first
thing that came up was just like i want
i want this mug to be real
the mug from my desk yeah i want this
mug to be real and i bet everyone would
love to have this mug to be real
i still remember this is like yeah one
of the first mugs that that james 2
chew
presented me or gave me
i really appreciate it it's so cute like
all almost basically everything on my
desk usually and maybe not the cake this
time but every everything on my desk in
usual streams is
mostly it's pretty much everything james
chew
man he makes really good stuff makes
really good stuff so i i asked as staff
being like i want to make this mug i
want to make this mug can we can we can
ask james too if we can make this a
reality and thankfully thankfully
thankfully he said yes
yeah
this is so cute and you know i saw like
um
i saw pictures of samples uh it's still
like uh
how do you say this um
not demo not demo you don't say demo for
items but like a demo sample sort of
thing
for this and it's turning out great it's
even gonna have the horns
it's even gonna have the horns guys the
horns are gonna be so in the way when
you try to drink it prototype yeah the
prototype
polka it's not gonna be super like sharp
enough to actually poke you on the eye
when you drink it
and to be honest if you don't want to
poke your eye just drink from the other
side the other side does not have horns
so
as you can see in the side view and
whatnot
but yes
the design is basically
it really really
it really really is um
befitting of the original design like
tried to replicate pretty much the same
mug
so you guys won't see a difference and
whenever in future streams whenever you
see me stream you can also have the same
monk on your table while watching it
we can be matching
we can be matching i can't wait to buy
like at least three of these
we can be matching
and yeah and what's cute though is that
if you don't wanna you know if you don't
wanna technically poke your eyes
um and you drink from the other side
you'll have the the the cute the iris
iris face
on the front side when you drink it so
if you're ever drinking something like
drinking tea with your friends
they're gonna see that cute side with
the
horns and the face on whenever you take
a sip of it
see it's perfect right
it's gonna be like a perfect image just
like that um that image uh the desk
mattress the dust mattress is holding if
you guys noticed that she's holding the
the the mug
she's holding the mug
it's gonna look like that basically
very cute very cute
and yes
i love how in the description it says
size approximately 96 out of 196 by 100
in parentheses including the horn yes
including the horn that's the height so
we'll assume that the if you don't
include the horn stuff the height is
slightly shorter
including the horn yeah
it's so cute
but we can all have matching mugs this
is this is like oh my god when i thought
about goods i was like definitely
definitely make this we have to make
this a reality
we have to
so i'm so glad we were able to do it
it's gonna be made out of porcelain i
think manga size wise it's to be pretty
um
standard
standard size
because you guys always tell me
don't drink too much soda
guys always tell me
control the amount of soda you drink so
it's not going to be like a one liter
mug or anything now
it's not gonna be a one liter mug so
yeah
maybe one cup of a soda this size a day
should should be no harm right
no harm right
but yes thank you so much james i also
really like how it says iris on the side
like you know under the hair it's just
iris on it like it can't be any more
self-explanatory just
shove the fact that it's iris in your
face because i love it i love it
it's the cutest thing ever and the horns
i swear i saw pictures of the real thing
the horns the horns are it's it's
actually there i really i was wondering
if they could actually make the horns
part of reality and just like
oh yes we can they just go oh yes we can
i'm like what
this is like this is like the mug where
i'm just like i'm so
i'm so glad i have horns
this is the moment i'm so glad i have
horns
and yes it has eyes no worries
um the back side and the back side i
love how it's so detailed it's it's
printed on both sides and it's not like
it's not like the same image on both
sides right
on the on the other side is the hair
it's my wavy hair
it's my wavy hair now the spoon is not
included no no no no the spoon the spoon
is different no
the spoon in the at least in the in here
right i know there's a spoon no no
they're just fyi no spoon included
no spoon included
spoon next year i wonder
i wonder
but
for the lemon part you can just kinda or
i think this is an orange i don't know
is this a lemon i'm
not so sure but you can just kind of
stab your own uh slice of fruit to make
it look exactly like this
it does not include the lemon either
that's the mug it's like the most
important part obviously
the strip on the side are you talking
about um if you're talking about the
strip
on the side view
that here wait let me try to zoom in
to this
if you're if you're talking about um the
thing in the middle over here the
the stars this is the um
the handle the handle
so there's gonna be my halo stars my
halo stars on the handle it's very
detailed that's cute and the underside
of the handle if you notice is also um
has that magenta color the same same
color you see in the
in the image
on my desk as well on my the mug on my
desk as well
so it's really really
it's surprising how how identical it is
to the mug in um on my table and how the
insides is also
it's also
gonna have that color
in it as well the magenta
yes so it's gonna look exactly like it
it won't poke my eyes just drink it from
the right side
wait wait wait wait where'd it go no oh
shoot why does it keep doing that to me
okay okay
it keeps eating off the screen why does
zobius do that to me
don't be nervous um do i still sound
nervous maybe maybe
ah
don't eat the mug i'll try not to but
yes
man i love everything everything about
my good set i love it i love it
hey so yes this is the complete set
it's gonna be the desk mat
mug and the dolores and also yes
individual voice sales there will be a
situation voice chilling after a stream
where you know
after i finish like a singing stream
perhaps maybe i don't know
we chill
you chill
voice pack yeah
not a voice pack it's a voice individual
voice it's also gonna be salty you guys
can you know hang with me after stream
as well yeah
yeah
and you can basically picture this
picture the same picture that you see on
the screen right now
so if you get the whole set if you get
the whole set including all like the mug
the desk um
the
the mug the desk and oh my god i forgot
already
and the blushy
and the plushy the doll and
the
the voice if you get everything you also
get a bonus
postcard
that beautiful drawing
i'll have my signature
and yes this is my official signature if
you haven't seen it
if you haven't seen it is my official
signature
it took a lot of creativity on my side
to think of this
yes
a lot of creativity i'm not really good
at thinking of signatures
but i think it turned out it turned out
pretty cool
it's fancy yeah
if you notice that yeah the eye i think
some of you guys might have noticed the
signature also on my coupon that i got
during her stream um but i forgot to put
the dots next to the eye yeah because
i'm i forgot like that yeah
it's fancy
and you will also also have a special
message from me that you can be excited
for when you actually get it yes
so yes and
me to get a postcard as well
i will maybe also explain this in the
japanese as well and let's go through
the slides in japanese really quickly as
well
where'd it go
oh oh there it is
why did why did decide to go there i
have no idea but
it's okay
huh
oh oh oh okay sure sure let's let's move
it like this
[Music]
uh sales work are gonna start like um by
the way at 3 p.m jst which is like an
hour and 20
six minutes from now
by the way
i might still be streaming by then so
i'll remind you guys i'll remind you
guys
or is it one oh sorry one one hour and
16 minutes excuse me my math
so yeah get it before it's too late when
it starts alrighty this is the japanese
version
let me just uh switch over here
to
a
this is the um the image that i
accidentally just went whoo skipped in
the english version so let's go through
this again um
first off there's the desk mat yes the
desk mat
it's by the way rubber
one hour and 16 minutes why do you guys
have to bring it up like that it's no
longer that it's now one hour and
[Music]
i'm so glad that this this will fit my
desk otherwise i'm really gonna have to
force myself to get up to
be at a place that can fit a bigger desk
it's so cute
fluffy room where
the fluffy room wear that's usually
usually invisible on my stream
but if you look at it from this point of
view you can actually see it
so cute i love it
i love pajamas like these they're so
girly but they're also so fluffy and
comfortable and warm
so pick a point in it that's gonna
rinse a coin there
if you guys notice that it's a ponytail
ponytail ponytail ponytail
yeah
all that ring fit
oh that's
all that sweat from all that ring fit
leads to beautiful
beautiful belly button tum tum yeah
be
ah
it's adorable
i do hope that i do hope that we can
we can get like maybe a
uh
a model to to model and hold this one
day a special model maybe one day
i do hope
alrighty
i think we are
yes oh oh oops oops
i think i kept some people waiting
oopsies
alrighty
we are going to be going back to totsu's
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
and that was
soda senpai
that's so cute she's so cute
sometimes i sometimes i'm like maybe i
should
i should be
more how do i say this
up
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah
um
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
in fact you should teach me english
you're elite english
yeah
english
[Laughter]
english teacher
yeah
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
sorry i think the order went a little
bit off we're good we're good let's
they sound similar
if it's bazooka then it's kaboom
i thought those were called bazookas for
some reason i don't know why
it's all right bazooka is also an
instrument isn't it oh yeah yeah it is
an intro an instrument of destruction
yes
[Laughter]
thank you so much for your birthday
thank you
i was waiting like oh iris is going to
have a birthday and i was invited like
oh i'm so happy of course i'm like the
cutest nissan empire oh my god
you're kind of an inspiration to me with
your your no not november no you're no
non-stop not november
it's okay probably this year i might uh
i might invite some guests who knows
oh my god i'd love to be a part of that
i'd love to be a part of that
that was like it's like the best thing
ever it's like the best month of the
year thanks to you
nice
looking forward for this year as well
yeah i'm excited already
also
i'm sorry i don't really uh have any
gifts
here in indonesia uh we sing a little
bit uh we have a
slightly different happy birthday song
so
i think i'll sing it with with bazooka
go right ahead
all right okay hey here we go
oh no no the discord the discord is
cutting her out oh no
um
i think
[Music]
yeah it sounds like that
i love the bazooka oh my god
there we go
[Music]
a
oh my god that bazooka i didn't know you
could change a pitch like that or the
the kazoo because well it's it's it's
it's mouthplay
this is too powerful
she's
ah
that was beautiful that was that was
beautiful
thank you
yeah welcome thank you so much for that
that that play that was beautiful yes
once again happy birthday though
thank you
thank you so much i can't wait to get
myself my own irish plushies
[Music]
i can't wait to hug your tail one day
your fluffy tail
all right
thank you so much
yeah yeah okay thank you for inviting me
no thank you so much for coming let's
collab for some time
let's go
thank you so much for coming bye soon
bye bye
i loved your kazoo
loved her kazoo
for some reason i really thought it was
called a bazooka i don't know why
no idea why but i thought it was a
bazooka
alrighty wait
let me just
oh
i wonder who could be next
hello
oh
anya
[Music]
it's the birthday girl hello
happy birthday
oh thank you so much
let me let me get an anya up let me get
another one hello okay you're an
invisible anya right now um
[Laughter]
can you try it you you gotta try it
on
[Music]
uh
i got you right here i got you right
here yeah that's my other identity i
don't like it
like your cover identity oh speaking of
covers i love your maximizer
i just i just checked it out like i
don't know like three four days ago i'm
just like oh my god this is great
oh thank you
thank you i loved your identity thank
you you shall definitely do more song
covers thank you i love your song covers
it's just they're great and the amount
of harmonies and whatnot
thank you
i love it i want to hear more of yours
thank you thank you happy birthday our
birthday is so close to each other i
know your birthday is yeah it's like not
even a week away right it's like yeah
not even a week it's like five days away
five days yeah yeah yeah it's high
pipeline
can't wait to see what you have in store
thank you so much for coming anya i have
a quick question for you
what is your first impression of me and
has it changed
my first impression of you yeah my first
impression of you um your japanese is
really good um
that hasn't changed ah
thank you no your your japanese is off
the charts is off the charts
yeah you remember the first time we
talked to each other though yeah i
remember i remember the total
and then and then you know a lot of jp
clippers were clipping our conversation
i remember
like a bunch of people talking about
that yeah basically how like we're not
we're not in the jp brunch we're id and
ian we're just talking jeff
yeah like sometimes i go search my name
in jp on like twitter you know and
sometimes my name will get mentioned
alongside of yours and the one thing
that people always mention is that one
jp conversation we had
yeah yeah
yeah that conversation was legit i
remember how you were like you're like i
i was apparently pretty like um
scary
yeah because you wouldn't stop talking
about craziness yeah raisins yeah i was
like i was like why won't she do this to
me
yeah i gotta feed you those raisins i
love that i love that idea though like
yeah
forcing you to eat raisins if you what
was it like if you answer a question if
you don't we can't answer oh um
um if i if i use the topic from oh yeah
the topic
yeah i love that idea
how many reasons did you end up eating
um
i i don't exactly remember maybe like
two or three oh
no
or not i'm not sure oh well you're
you're you're here today which means you
survived it
yeah
i'm alive yeah
i'm alive i live
you've lived through the raisins i'm
proud of you yeah
thank you thank you
happy birthday thank you thank you so
much for coming anya thank you for
having me i'm really happy we should
definitely play something yeah it's
definitely i had fun playing
the hide and shriek where you don't get
scared at all yeah
and also payday will also have that
collab yeah that was great yeah yeah i
can't wait to
you you're you are fearless senpai
you're fearless yeah
thank you so much for coming i thank you
thank you so much for inviting me to
have a good day thank you can't wait for
your birthday as well
[Music]
thank you bye bye bye
ah
alrighty
i wonder what where where where did
nanya's on your speaking tree go
i'm worried that maybe everything isn't
not in order anymore it's okay it's okay
we got we got this we got this we got
this i have another way to do things
um
ah oh my god my my throat
it's too much laughing no scuff no scuff
whatsoever no scope whatsoever nope nope
we're good we good
alrighty
i wonder who who could be next
i wonder
before that
i still i still can't get my my head
around how much anya can speak japanese
how much you can speak japanese
um
i wonder
i wonder well
totally no she's next level i know i
know it's like it's different like i
still don't get how sugar space so
whichever it
still can't get it it's just
it's just it's just mind-boggling
i can't wait to do more stuff with it
though she's very cute
i really like her new outfit like every
time i see it on my screen i think i've
seen it a few times because
what you can call it um
the
the sports festivals
because of the sports festival and all
the past collabs
oh can you guys hear the hammering no
don't worry about the hammering here let
me let me just uh raise my gate volume
so that
it won't bother you guys it's just it's
just some construction
no worries whatsoever
oh yeah it might be bethlehem it might
be a buff on the ground pounding
go go red sea i i still i still love
those memories i can't wait for a sports
festival the sports festival this year
like this upcoming sports festival which
will come i don't know not anytime soon
of course but you never know time flies
when you think about how last sports
festival was like what
was it october
it was
october when you think about that it's
like it's already been like what five
months since then it's almost half a
year
it's almost half a year
so if you think about you just have a
half a year more maybe
maybe i do it imagine how how much
trouble it is to actually get all that
down though
all the preparation
in general like mikko senpai and like
how um
also that what do you call it the
the me coronet the me coronet uh
new year's new year stream as well
time really flies i know i know
i mean cronie is technically she does
have something on her head that could
possibly make her fly i'm never gonna
say that she's a helicopter but
she does fly
are you having fun at the sports
festival i can't you know i can't wait
for that again
it might be with new people i don't know
but
we'll have a lot of fun definitely
can i eat the rest of this pokey
it's actually melon pocky
it's delicious delicious stuff oh
oh
i think someone
dang it yeah
discord discord just kind of
this could just kind of
couldn't handle your energy what
i was saying oh somebody needs to i
wanted to do like an impression like i
needed
oh my god i want to hear your impression
though you want to try to get here i'll
i'll i'll erase it for remembering my
memories for now you wanna try oh okay
[Music]
wow that was a really good impression
and that sounded almost just exactly
like her
thank you you know it's funny how how
you were you were looking for anya's pnd
but when it comes to me you're like bam
i don't even get a chance to talk i'm
ready
yeah you were prepared for me to fumble
huh no no no no no no
not today not today no not today not
today honey
anyways happy birthday
thank you
thank you so much for coming
oh so so does this mean you're getting
older or are you like any other member
who doesn't age
oh um my age is basically however long
hope has been in your heart technically
so
this birthday is kind of just like the
day i first uh descended to this world
the first time i guess
i i guess my memory is kind of distant
because it was a long time ago but i
made it this day yeah
because
yeah that's the date
then wait oh wait then if
you know there's a lot of holes here
this
is so if you just descended today then
that means um a few years no not a few
years back then centuries ago if hope
wasn't wait how do you know that both
the hope is born to wait what
the way i'm bored it's it's a
it is a company secret it is a company
secret of how i was born
she's laughing too much discord
let's not worry too much about the
details mm-hmm
okay yeah yeah
i i i got you a present
oh what could it be what could it be
that i sent it to your dms
oh yes of course of course of course
it's gonna be
wait wait let me let me let me get this
up
hey
that's the perfect ticket it affects
playdate oh my god it's still it's still
i keep saying oh my god let's play apex
and it's just
timing is so hard
yeah it is it's funny because because
we're always like okay ask me any time
but then but then we we just never get
the timing right yeah but but now you
have this ticket so literally anytime at
all need to call me and i will come
you will you will come rushing no matter
no matter the
no matter the circumstances
no matter their circumstances it's a
demo baby it's demo baby it's them a
baby
okay i will i will ask you to play apex
with me at the most inconvenient time
no just kidding of course
uh
it's a big time you know that meme where
uh there's like this girl and then
there's this like guy with a worn out
face like oh yeah
it's epic simon i'd be that guy being
like yes yes ma'am
exactly yeah you are you are the apex
the apex predator in whole life aren't
you
technically in a lot of different ways
you're the apex predator
in different ways
wait
so not not in a little sense but like in
different ways
yeah yeah you're the apex holo apex
predator right
do you do you have any objections to
that nickname that i just
no no no objections at all so does that
mean um
where did i keep my ring will you marry
me iris oh it's that um
i'm i'm i wait isn't bae your daughter
oh no oh no
oh no
oh no this is
what what could this mean wait
bay's mom just
just proposed to me
well i'm just forced to what
explain yourself
explain yourself daughters
explain yourself ollie
i'm sorry
it takes predator am i right the carbine
and then charge rifles yeah
i still remember watching that clip of
your charge rifling yeah
[Laughter]
okay uh change of topic
i'm wishing you the best of health i
hope that you thrive more
i heard the identity cover it was a dope
thank you so much ollie who was it yeah
i'm happy to hear that happy to hear
that
i'm really looking forward to more stuff
from the irish i'll do my best i'll do
my best thank you you too ollie can't
wait to hear more i loved your your kudo
to hey kids it's like perfect song for
you it's a perfect song
no stop stop it we're supposed to talk
about you it's your birthday
[Laughter]
alrighty thank you so much for coming
ali
yeah happy birthday once more thank you
thank you
bye
ah
and
fx play date yes of course it's a of
course it's an apex play
i love i love that chibi ollie on the
side that's so cute
the the dongle i just love how she has
those huge dongles on her head like on
the sides of her head
so cute
and back when she was olivia oh my god
sometimes whenever you still whenever i
see olivia i just i just
i just freak out my heart freaks out of
how how how elegant she can be
hmm
alrighty oh
hi
hi rhys
happy birthday hi ryan is ironic to say
hi with
hi
yeah
yeah yeah it might be kind of a little
bit hard to pronounce
[Laughter]
girls
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's fine yeah today is fine
yes i guess you understand where the
weather is yes i i maybe actually
haven't gone outside yet today so okay
okay let's go
thank you for um asking best question
yes you're welcome i know that's the
best conversation yeah
[Laughter]
fantastic skilled talented voice thank
you
i love your personality so you're really
fantastic singer so i love i love it
thank you so much i i love everything
about you as well you're such a hard
worker and you support everyone from
like for the back and like it's just
your existence is like crucial yes
is it your favorite food
pasta
english and sing things yeah no your
english is amazing you're improving by
the day
yeah happy birthday yeah yeah thank you
so much rachel
bye
ah
that was funny especially since i know
that she's out she's probably out right
now
already
i wonder who's wonder who's next
to revive my memory oh my god
it's okay you you your memory back right
you do you know who you are now
yeah i i think how vid health is yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
i was meant to give you something but it
didn't make it i can't make it on top no
worries he just you being here is the
best present no worries
thank you
thank you so much for coming you'll be
ah
what do you think i think you and like i
think i think apex
like
even even though ali as well i'm just
like oh yeah
yeah
oh yeah
and yeah you already gave me speaking of
the gifts though you already gave me
like the best you really gave me the
really beautiful beautiful irish drawing
when i deviated i remember that i
remember watching
you again i'm just going to give you
again to see here oh my god really
really yeah
and your request though any requests um
in that case i want i want an iris in a
in a maid outfit
oh
man
i'm on
it really is
yep yep the artist the artist oh
yeah it is
oh my god oh my god oh my god there's a
lot of idea coming right now oh i wonder
what sort of ideas what's your creative
juices are flowing in your brain
yeah yeah i mean the uh the mid outfit
is it was it to be a little long for a
shoe that was kind of like a little bit
short though
it could be whichever whichever you
think if you want to go the sa-so route
we could make it long or if you want to
say yeah this is the long the
traditional made outfit or if you want
to go a little you know a little on the
bad side or the devil's side you can
make it shorter
sure
so there's the sweet and spicy rude
the spicy root it's a like do you like
spicy foods
yeah i like spicy food
yes i i don't i can't handle like too
much spice but like
yeah
good yes i like sweet and spicy also put
together too just like me
oh yes for the spicy iris oh my gosh
it's been a while since last stop i saw
it
what am i talking about say anyway happy
birthday really we're looking forward to
play with you again yes definitely let's
play something we have something right
we have something i plan to do yeah we
do we do we do yeah yeah
exciting
you can't see my wing
yeah you're already waiting
you're already
spicy sweet and spicy mid outfit
yes
very very looking very much looking
forward to it thank you so much
you're welcome
my channel yeah you look so beautiful
today thank you oh
that's all i wanted to say
i think you look you look beautiful too
and that i love that outfit like the
sort of military-ish sort of outfits
cute
it's gorgeous thank you
i'm waiting for your new outfit wink
wink oh
yeah yeah yeah
[Laughter]
yeah you can't you can't you cannot
handle some to this much winking right
yep yeah right right yeah
are winking so much here yeah one coin
yeah you better give in
great i'm winking 24 7 here and i
thought yep you have you caught you
you're too strong you're too strong for
you
oh my god all righty thank you so much
for coming here thank you
we're gonna come thank you soon thank
you thank you so much i can't wait for
that i can't wait to play with you soon
wink wink
thank you happy birthday again thank you
ah
man i can't believe i already i already
got
basically settled in stone uh
made iris from eofy you can't believe it
i can't
i just caught so cute yeah i just
noticed that yeah she was winking the
whole time
let me just take a sip of seven up
ah perfect this is a slight breather
oh more soda
it's not that bad okay
i've only taken like what four or five
sips of soda so far it's not that bad
i can't yeah no horax
i'm sorry like i'm sorry if i'm
butchering that
that accent every once in a while oh
oh
hello
how could this be what's your goddess
could this be
[Music]
thank you for inviting me
no thank you so much for coming moon
awesome bye
man
i'm so nervous i'm so nervous i feel
like this is
not the first time we're talking though
because like i mean
sports festival
yeah this is this is our first time
talking like one-on-one yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
and that sports festival really brought
back a lot of memories
go go red sea
we should do it again yeah i really i
kind of hope that we can like have like
the same team
next year too it was just so much fun
with everyone that gang
anyway um i have a present for you what
what what what
so no
lately i love making a cake so
oh my god i love it oh my god oh wait i
can't wait to put some wait let me let
me put this on wait
it it's on the i get to be a cake what
are you sure
oh a meal cake
oh my god what's what flavor is this
wait oh wait why does it know
just like in your picture actually
yeah
really yeah really just like my picture
yeah i just like uh since we we barely
talked to each other and i don't know
what uh
what kind of cake that you like so i
just like oh
oh there there is a cake in ice i'm
gonna make the version of the moss kick
no this is perfect this is perfect oh my
god
i love it you know this just reminds me
of all those you know um at carnivals
and stuff like that they would have
those those things that you can like
stick your face in
yeah yeah it's basically that i haven't
i haven't experienced anything like that
in a while so this is fun oh my god
a little bit bigger yeah i feel like a
really special birthday girl all of a
sudden
thank you so much
strawberry let's go
anyway
yes matching with babe perfect perfect
i have a question for you moona
what is it
what is my first impression
you
have a really wonderful voice
oh my god being told that by you by you
is
really really it really really comes to
me in a special way what
what
welcome i mean you are the one who is a
like yeah that original song you
uploaded
yeah oh my god that was like the pv the
vocals the song everything was just like
holy moly
this girl this girl's
the power the power of the moon
like you're even stronger than the moon
to be honest even though your moon
you're like the sun at this point that
you're the power in your voice
thank you hi todd
i love it
i love it thank you so much moona i'm
really happy to hear that yes
yes i love your yuri music video too oh
thank you so much
oh my god i love that one
a couple of times i think i think i saw
i saw a clip i saw a clip of that i'm
just like oh my gosh she's singing it
she's seeing it that song is really hard
too it's a really hard song so that's it
for the timing it's hard it is it is
just there's no there's no vocal breaks
after like the first chorus it's just
like oh let's go to the second verse i'm
like oh my god but yeah no you nailed it
you nailed it it was amazing
thank you so much for watching people
mirrors you too you nailed it as well oh
thank you so much
thank you i can't wait to
i i want to sing high tide too when i
can
anyway since since it's your birthday um
other than this uh cake
mosque um i will give you a free
collaboration
game or music
just hit me anytime oh thank you so much
yes it definitely hit you up oh my god
let's yeah let's definitely do something
together yeah
thank you so much for coming luna
bye
not that one
all righty
that was munna
her presence
presence is just so
it's so
celestial so let's stick slastic
heavenly
is
[Music]
m
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
um
i'm dead
okay
oh
foreign
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
and when i first heard tmt
i thought it was like i thought people
were just misspelling tnt
tnt which is like you know t tnt um
dynamite dynamite you're like wonder
what wonder what what's with what's
what's empire and dynamite and then i
learned it was really tmt
yeah just add another
just now there's another stick to that
end it becomes tmt
i'm tmt i'm dynamite
yes
ah man
i can't wait to play more stuff with her
and yeah
i do tend to like watch a lot of her
apex
and be like oh my god she's she's too
strong she's too strong
oh
hey
oh my god you actually you actually said
that again
so iris how's the weather
oh no oh no oh no she she did the
reverse the reverse uno reverse card on
me now
how's the weather i haven't gone out so
i don't know
oh okay yes i'm i haven't touched grass
today right now oh okay you should you
should do that sometime have you touched
yourself today
no no it's not been a while maybe it's
been like what maybe three or four days
but it's not a while yeah three or four
days that could be worse that's fine you
know by the way i have a present for you
what what
yes i do have a present for you um
let me see here we go
i think it's this one
naming my file slot billy but
oh my god
[Laughter]
do you like it i like it i love it oh my
god of course i would love it oh my god
what this is like the best the best wait
this is the best way
i mean and i love that the name of the
file is just i wish
i wish
i went in full count yeah oh my god the
map
post
[Laughter]
it's hard to draw the keys individually
yes of course of course of course
kind of like how i draw teeth whenever i
draw teeth i just draw like that
yeah
yeah actually what if you know what if
you like keyboard so much you modify
your teeth to look like keyboards
like keycaps
i got my teeth and new teeth implanted
keycaps
gmk let's go
it's our ortholinear teeth
oh my god linear linear how many grams
of actuation points of actuation force
can chomp down meat in like five seconds
oh my god
i don't know why we're having
conversation about teething on your
birthday but you know i was like what
should i talk about here you know
everybody's being so wholesome and i'm
like
what should i talk about
the pressure i know the pressure is on
and stuff like that yeah like give me a
question give me a question so i can be
like you know facebook everybody else
like iris i think you know all right
yeah
uh say so question right oh yes of
course
okay let's face the question
yes
okay
what do you think i'm thinking right now
um you're thinking that omg rainey is so
awesome she's um she's going all the way
to my birthday giving me this present oh
i love raining so much thank you so much
for raining someone is that what you're
thinking
[Music]
it's a little a little off i would say
something a little just a little bit
[Music]
but it's okay it's okay it's all right
it's all right yes
yes anyways nice nice cake head thank
you thank you this is from luna
for the birthday girl very very very
nice
you know one thing i just noticed though
i love how this this president gave me
it just says happy birth on it
yes
yes it just says happy birthday yeah
i had like a prototype wait did i save
it i forgot i drew it on
microsoft
paint
everyone's favorite well so actually i
have two gifts for you but then i was
like wait i'm gonna make a better one
you know
maybe it's this one it's dumb
yeah it's double oh my god yeah i hand
delivered it but like the upgraded one
has me with the truck so you know it's
like an upgrade oh my god wait let me
let me get this one up too
oh even this one still says happy birth
on it
oh but it has more keyboards though
oh my god wow such a generous soul
so so generous right so generous these
keyboards are these keyboards that
really do cost a leg
exactly exactly it costs all your
clothing you have to sell all your
clothes to buy these keyboards so you're
not wearing anything
yesterday
i just noticed i was naked yes you're
naked you sold all your clothes for the
keyboard for the hog oh my oh my god
very very virus as they would say yes
very very vibrant
no no no i'm not your virus what it's
just your imagination i guess the me the
me and your imagination is is not
wearing any clothes on what
what
what because i'm i'm never i'm not i'm
never thinking art imitates life or
something or is that not applicable in
this case
what what i i have no idea what you're
talking about huh
yes same i don't know you know what i'm
gonna go to bed all right and go to
sleep yes to go to sleep before
everything turns it turns by
[Music]
oh let me let me put and make these tiny
gotta love reina
i love reina and how she basically
dragged me down this keyboard rabbit
hole
it's all her fault
if every guys are like oh iris talks too
much she she likes to keyboards too much
i'm jealous playing right now blame
right now
um
what
happened
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
so
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
yeah we have something we have something
that we want to do it was a secret but
we have something just i'm just going to
put that out yeah
she could she could yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
alrighty
we have been blessed yes we have been
blessed i have been blessed as well that
the missing pie is just
top full full-on fluffy full-on like she
just makes my heart fluffy
oh yes merch merch is now live let's
let's talk about that let's talk about
that real quick i do have some you know
some stuff that for example something
that just happened to you know uh play
when i started the stream but first
let's let's talk about the merch a
little bit um
i can talk about it more right after
that as well but here wait let me just
get that up real quick
birthday merch is now live oh wait why
is it not showing up did it did it did
it disappear again
no nothing
ah there we go
ah there we go it went it went over here
okay yeah
merch so
it's gonna be great it's gonna be great
i'm also when i finish the stream i'm
just gonna buy
get my credit card out
and buy everything
buy everything
and maybe not my my voice though
maybe not my voice but besides the voice
i'm gonna buy everything
my voice is already stuck on my body i
don't
i could just i could just say it to
myself
boys
how long
are the sales gonna be continuing i'm
not a hundred percent sure
but
yes
merch
is now live
if anyone can let me know when when does
that start until until april 11th thank
you thank you april 11. nice so you guys
have a little over a month a little over
a month
but
it's always it's always better early
than late or better not late than never
but just don't don't forget to buy it
like i know some people are like oh my
god i forgot like for the half year
march some people are like oh no oh no
is it over already i forgot like you
know
that's in order to avoid that's best to
best to get it out it's an asap asap
if i can get
let me try to see if i can find a link
of it
yeah let me let me find the link
yes
link these up
what if i can post more than one link in
a comment
we can try let me just get this
global
here we go
yes
merch now alive
get it now
does this look okay
nice
rip my wife
don't abuse your dude
but you know there is a limited time for
this so if you if you want it get it
while you can yay
because yeah you'll you'll never be able
to get it once
probably you won't be able to get it
once
sales are over so
i can't wait to bust out my wallet too
while they couldn't die boom
man i feel i feel so i'm so happy i feel
so happy guys i can't i just can't
i can't
everyone's just so
supportive oh manager song gave me a
better link i'm gonna i'm gonna link
this one instead
i'm gonna link this one instead i think
this is probably a better link
let me just make it so it's a little bit
easier to see
oops
oh is it too long maybe it's too long
it might be too long it's also in my
stream description nice
thank you manu jason thank you manager
if you go to the official online shop
right the link that i just posted
that will work too
that will work as well
for zero form not found does it not work
oops okay
no worries no worries let me just fix
that real quick
it's also in the description so
first comes first you can just uh
get the link that i just posted um i can
just get that link again here wait
excuse the scuff
but i'm surprised everything went
surprisingly smoothly also thanks to
oops
thanks to my manager son
i kinda i kind of did
oh my god why do i keep doing that okay
there we go
no it's just a identity iris it's the
other iris that was an identity yep
e
let me do this
hold on
but thankfully everything pretty much
went smoothly now we can kind of chill
and watch and watch the special stuff
that was in the beginning of the stream
yeah
yeah i'll get back to the merchant in a
bit but
maybe some presents i can find online
first off
oh wait maybe i should mute my bgm real
quick
alrighty
it's muted you guys can't hear anything
right
you guys can't hear anything right
doesn't it alrighty
thank you
happy
birthday ideas
thank you for inviting me to your fuzzy
party today i'm so happy
i'm sorry i couldn't tell you by
my message in person today
but
i'm sure
we will have lots to talk about the
impasse on next time yeah i hope to get
to know ando
be friends with the ideas a lot more
ando
don't tell anyone
i
really really likes irish sweet and
beautiful singing advice
singing voices
it's amazing it's great thinking might
not be no singing
perfect
she told everybody
singing
no
thinking
[Laughter]
hope your special day is filled
with
happiness
[Music]
is
bye
yeah
yeah like her english was perfect
i like how she was thinking just asking
her herself
singing
yes i
i can tell why she's so she's so well
loved and love her love her so much
they're all so cute
man sinking
singing the grammar the grammar was
great it was perfect perfect that she
after she corrected herself exactly
are you thinking now i'm not sinking
i haven't sung yet either i'm not
sinking or anything no
thank you so much
even though she's so busy you know and
and i think she right now she's
currently taking a break
she's taking a break and even then she
still sent me this video i'm just like
um thank you so much
thank you so much and i hope she you
know her her throat and everything gets
better soon yeah
streaming and doing all this stuff can
really can really take a toll on your
threat so
hope is sinking i'm not sinking
i'm not sinking shut up
i'm just it's my birthday of course i
won't be sinking vsyncre
v synchro shut up shut up i'm not
sinking no
ah but you know we do have we do have
one more we do have one more video we do
have one more video
we do have one more special message i
wonder who it could be from
i wonder who could be from
let me let me meet my agent again
[Music]
my name is
nice to meet you and nice to meet you
too
foreign
[Music]
and iris uh coney and iris are best
friend okay
best friend okay
i love you okay
okay okay
add yes
the pressure is on
this red okay
it's so cute and scary it's like it's
this this embodies everything that's
great about corona senpai everything
amazing about coordination is all
embodied in this one minute in this
video in this video i'm done i'm dead
thank you forever i still i love all her
like her reactions to stuff they're
always so clippable
always so clippable like how she's like
how sh
sometimes she
a lot of people i see a lot of people
using her her reactions in clips
thank you forever is also one
and also it just reminds me of that game
you know that um that coordinate game
like a game
what the [\h__\h]
it's so cute
psycho
[Music]
man she's so cute i'm just so funny
and that head that birthday that huge
birthday it's so big man
you think i like the cake on my head is
big no no no no it doesn't even compare
to how big the cake is on her head
didn't she like she also has like a tree
on her head too once in a while right
didn't she do that like yesterday or the
day before she had like a huge tree on
her head
the tree quoted it and the face is
different too oh my god
it
um conan senpai's like room review where
she was like reviewing like every like
her listeners room with like the the
what you call it
looking for coronet and sometimes some
people some people would send her like
room pictures without with
where she can't find her at all and she
just kind of freaks
yeah professional comedian i know
the magnifying glass i love it so i
don't know how to view
was her room review was hilarious it was
it was so good
the magnifying glass like where am i if
i'm not there you know what the
consequences
is the bgm gone oops
sorry i forgot to turn it back on
this
yeah that was fun
why are you guys talking about my
attention all of a sudden
yeah they're different konaneski are i
just don't know they're on a different
level right if you watch if you played
that game also
ah
man
you
beat i feel so blessed to have everyone
around so this is really fun this was
really fun
i'm glad pretty much everything went
pretty smoothly
pretty smoothly a couple a couple
mistakes on my side i'm sorry i'm sorry
let me just say sorry right here but
in in general everything went pretty
smoothly thankfully
so what happens now oh
you guys like going out here i want to
check out some presents i got from you
guys as well
but before that you always want to do
you guys want to maybe uh
do some singing
you guys want to do some singing
sinking no we're not i'm not gonna sink
i'm gonna
sing
singing
let me just double check that
okay we gotta be good
let's sink
oh no
legendary video
all righty let's move to the sinking
room then i
i do have one song i'm just like yes i
will definitely sing this one but
so much
good
you guys got some of it just from that
what
it's okay
appreciation
here is a love song to you guys
[Music]
is
my
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
is
my
[Music]
is
thank you so much
[Applause]
or i guess
sure
thank you
that was not on purpose
thank you that was definitely not on
purpose let me just say that
i want to sing love songs to you guys
i have another love song i have in mind
just now
another love song that i have in mind
that
pretty sure wait wait let me find the
correct karaoke
i'm pretty sure that's true
feels like our birthday instead what you
talking about
yeah let's sing this song this one song
that
this truly is truly a song that i think
is perfect to sing
for a birthday
maybe an original song
what
an original song
yes
papa
despair
has descended and you are not alone
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
darkness
m
[Music]
so
[Applause]
is
[Music]
again
nothing
[Music]
foreign
fade
[Music]
our journey has only just
and no no there's no secret ending yet
there's no secret ending yet
i know you guys
probably were like all secret hunting
but no no no not yet at least
[Music]
yeah
this song is tiring let me just say that
[Music]
let me just say that that song
it's a great song it's so tiring hold it
now
a very tiring song
especially how like after the first
chorus it just automatically just jumps
into the second with almost no
no breath no breath point
thank you so much guys i'm so glad i
descended to this world i'm so glad i
was born today i'm really really happy
i'm really happy
trying to figure out if it's wait wait
i need to double check if this was
oh no no
[Music]
tough song and it's great yeah
it is a tough song
alrighty okay
do you guys have any requests
i could maybe answer one request one
request that that
like i might not be able to answer
everything but maybe something that's
like
that is okay
[Music]
hmm
i'm seeing a lot of one last kiss again
one last kiss
[Music]
god i would totally sing something from
a whole lot from from one of the other
members but
i can't i can't i don't think i have
i don't have the karaoke at the moment
so
yeah i don't think i have the carrot
keys for those
[Music]
righty
oh this is a classic at this point but
i do love the song
see the world actually don't have a
karaoke for that yet
i actually don't have the karaoke for
that yet
that didn't cross my mind yeah it didn't
cross my mind
look if i asked for it okay i can i can
get a bit i don't have it with me right
now
i actually don't have it with me right
now it's too new it's too recent
i'll get i'll get that i'll get ls for
that soon i'll throw that soon
i'll ask for that soon i don't have
spotify at least not right now
alrighty
oh this is all this song is always a lot
it's a love song to everything right
it's a love song to everything
[Music]
let me think about the order for this
mythical
alrighty
[Music]
[Applause]
i don't have the karaoke the world yet
can i restart that
it bothers me how i i started too early
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you so much for celebrating my
birthday guys
thank you
[Music]
oh
can you give me
[Music]
you'll ever know
oh can you give me one last kiss
[Music]
oh
i love you more than you'll ever know
[Music]
oh
i love you more than you'll ever
[Music]
i love you more than you'll ever know
more than you'll ever know
[Music]
go
and that was
one last kiss
thank you thank you thank you so much
it's really it's overwhelming how much
support i received
throughout there ever since i deviated
and even even today especially today
from everyone in whole life and everyone
over here right now right here
[Music]
you know what
kind of up for one more song though but
wait
i'm just trying to think i was really
really only planning on singing
i was really only planning on singing my
tv song to be honest
but you know what
this is my birthday today's my birthday
ian core what
foreign
yes
really do i have to
do i have
i to
to
[Music]
you know i actually have this one song
that
oh wait
i've never used this
um karaoke before but
actually i don't think i've ever sung
this before
i don't think i've ever sung this before
but it's it is a good
it is a good song it's a love song it's
another love song it's a good song to i
think
and this uh maybe on this i don't know
the good love song to
say that you know love
is always
it comes around goes around it comes
around in a full circle
like a circulation
did you get that
[Music]
foreign
this feels really birthday
[Music]
[Applause]
is
yes
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
my
so
[Music]
foreign um
my
[Music]
hey
thank you very much
thank you
to another year of committed content i
mean it's not really an
anniversary but it's my birthday so yeah
until next birthday
ah
wait a sec all righty
thank you so much i'm really really
happy to be here yes
yeah maybe maybe hopefully maybe
hopefully maybe i don't know
we can celebrate
my next year's birthday in this in a
different way too the spirit was this
this year's birthday has also been
amazing but
to many more to many more to many more
[Music]
i do want to you know go through like
gifts from
from all the aristocrats as well i think
i might do that during like a um super
chat reading
in the near future
but yeah it's
i let me just
i'll do that i'll do that very soon i'll
do that
very soon
but
maybe i shouldn't keep everyone to here
too long but let me just
put in a quick reminder
a quick reminder about um
what do you call it
my goods my merch
wait
where is it
i have it somewhere wait
i have it somewhere here
how is it going to show up over here
it's probably going to be really big
or something
[Music]
my birthday merch
don't forget to get yours now don't
forget yours to get yours today
it's already started the seals have
already started
um
wait a sec
let me just do something real quick
you might hear double iris for a second
you might hear double there we go that
the sea i told you there was a double
iris here wait
yes
merch link is in the description
it was more like triple iris no worries
and
let me just go through a quick one run
through it one more time
it'll help it will include the dust
mattress yes
the dolores and the margaret's just
getting the whole wrist set
you should get the whole wrist set yeah
and the birthday of
the the reason why i haven't really been
talking too much about the birthday was
because i'm just embarrassed
i'm just embarrassed you guys you guys
know how i'm really shy about stuff like
this
and if you buy at all you get the
postcard
yeah
i think the voice you can already listen
to it i think you can already buy the
voice
like i know um goods uh shipping and
whatnot is gonna be like a few months
away but the the voice you can kind of
already listen to it i think
so yeah i hope you guys enjoyed that yep
you're very obvious am i
i tried my best i tried my best i tried
my best
so yeah
please do go to go check out at least
the birthday voices already available so
good to check that out and yes the whole
merch set don't forget
oh of course you know
bring up a reminder of that every so
often also i did release the cover i did
release the cover for for today since
today's my birthday i thought it'd be a
good occasion to you know get something
out
uh i sang canadians identity i then did
it i can play it in the back for a bit
um
so if you haven't checked that out yet
please do check that out that's also in
the description
yep
i personally really really like how this
turned out
i'm very very very satisfied with how it
turned out it's it's like i can't really
ask for more
i love it
and yeah it's supposed to reflect my
identity my identity of
yeah i thought it was people's
perfect song for to sing
it's also good to self reflect on your
birthday right yep
but yes please do go check it out thank
you so much for coming once again
and uh thank you so much
thank you so
so so so
so much
for everything
i really really do appreciate
everyone here today and i really really
do appreciate
like even at just everything
not just everything
yeah
let me wait wait
i hope i was i was really nervous how
this was going to turn out
i was really nervous
this might be kind of like relief relief
relief tears as well but
like
yeah i really appreciate everything
thank you so much everyone yeah
and
i
i will do my best to you know
continue continue
uh
my activities
as
a proud member and whole life yes
and i might take a couple day break i
don't know
i'll let you guys know more in the
details i do have a doctor's appointment
on the 9th so i'm probably gonna take a
couple days off for that
and mainly just so that because the
doctor is probably going to check my
throat again and i wanna maybe take a
day a vocal break before that yeah
yeah thank you so much for coming in
thank you so much thank you so much for
all the super chat
thank you
uh
see you guys again very um
i won't take it take too long see you
guys very soon and
let's be excited for all the all the
good things to come yeah all the good
things to come
i did i did kind of mess up a bit
over here and there today but
all's good all good all's good today
i'm so glad i'm so happy so so so happy
i am the happiest person in the world
today
thank you very much see you guys again
very soon yeah
alrighty
virus
the
five minutes
is
oh wait wait where was it again um
darkness will fade away
light will die your way
hope has descended and you are not
alone
[Music]
do
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
darkness for you
[Music]
excuse the construction sound but
thank you so much for coming guys
happy birthday
to me
to
me
happy birthday
near
me iris
happy birthday
to
me
let's get that out
thank you
thank you very much
see you guys again very soon and do
check out that merch and that cover
stream identity stream see the world
stream everything
and here's to many more great times
we'll definitely
go through everyone's gifts and whatnot
and during
uh your my super chat reading stream
thank you so much paris pa paris
this place shoot everything since my
birthday please