[Music]
so
hello
[Music]
hello hello i've been okay i sound tired
but i've been awake for a few hours okay
don't worry don't worry
i've been awake
hello everybody
hello
looking fancy oh thank you i haven't had
uh i haven't worn my kimono
like this in a while so i figured
let's do it let's do it last episode
of pokemon today
um
it's
i'm not planning anymore on getting
archaeos today
um
[Music]
or within a stream at all which is a bit
as a streamer a bit sad because the
title it's in the title
the name is in the title how can i not
get him in the stream but it apparently
takes so much work and it's kind of
considered the third end like there's
three endings
and we got the first ending last time
but now there's still so much to do
until the second ending and the third
ending
and i kind of by them by the hints that
you guys gave me i judged it to be too
much work
to
um rush it on stream at least for today
and i think i'll just to keep um
this game as a play in my free time game
until i find arceus myself after today's
ending so i already have been spoiler
dude
see that's not good guys that's
i i like getting those hints you know
but
now i know who will be fighting at the
very end
uh so
even if you just write one letter
the starting letter of that person's
name
it's a pretty
obvious answer to me who we're gonna be
fighting
um
so that's that
oh that's such a premiere okay uh yeah
anyway so i know who will be fighting i
will be muting this out now it's
starting um
so we'll do that and i suppose that will
be the ending uh for us
but i think until then it will already
be a lot of
uh work today anyway well we'll see i
honestly don't really know how much
uh how long we're going to stream today
but yeah let's see
am i the only one reacting to this in
her life right now
i know that a lot of the japanese girls
like to do reacts
uh to nintendo and pokemon directs
but today it seems like i'm the only one
nadia hodo well i wonder what it will be
um
so i it will either be about our i'm
thinking maybe an arceus dlc but maybe
it's too early for that
or some people apparently think this
could be gen 9
yo i talk like a pokemon nerdy let's go
i don't really know [\h__\h] about pokemon
well link is in the pinned comment
[Music]
uh
please open the link
now
it's it's 11
four
three
two
one let's go
[Music]
is that real on the background
oh
oh really i didn't realize
26 years
that's so old isn't it
man
26 years ago huh
yes i will how long is this
wow
are you so handsome
wait is his is that his natural hair
like his skin is glowing but his hair is
like you know gray
wow
anyway
it has nothing to do with this
what is this
pokemon go
cool
not gonna play it anymore but cool
[Music]
oh my god it's an invasion
hmm
what is it with his skin and versus his
hair damn
although some people i know i have a
i have a friend who
has like uh
he uh like the like a
hair thing where the hair is gray but
they're still very young it's like a
it's a thing
for some people like a
jean thing
jeans
sorry it's so unrelated
what is this
what what game is this
phone pokemon
oh is this gotcha pokemon gotcha
oh cute
man latias
what is it
pokemon
i don't know anything about that game
it looks
looks good how does this game work
do you do normal pokemon battles
is there a story
whoa
well one lady got a huge hat there where
is she from the huge hat lady in the
middle
gata
there's a bit of story oh
katelyn gen four
she's cute
i want a huge hat like that
pokemon cafe
cute
wait a second isn't he from animal crus
i know that's a proper pokemon for a
moment i was like is this like a like a
collab of animal crust
oh it's a cute game
it's a cute game
oh cute
well pikachu looks kind of
why
is pikachu's head so cute
oh my god it looks so wrong
oh cute bumper thor
bulbasaur looks fine pikachu looks kind
of
messed up
something's wrong there the proportions
are so off
shiny people
cute
cute cute cute
pikachu though
looks like a fake
imposter that must be an imposter right
that pikachu
anton wow the art the artist is really
cute
besides pikachu
why out of all pokemon why pikachu oh
pokemon unite
that was that that had one like league
of legends style game right
um
did you guys play that or did you
i don't like phone games sorry
generally i like to stay away from phone
games i want to play on a console or on
a pc not a phone
except for what the [\h__\h] is that
is that new never seen that before
except for tower defense games this is
what i was gonna say
this is on switch but the controls on
the screen looked like uh phone phone
controls the little touch
touchy buttons
is it both
hoopa
wait is this pokemon new like for real
above
koopa is broken
sun and moon i played sun moon i never
saw hoopa
yeah a post game oh that's why i don't
know about it
yes
what's about shining pearl
something interesting dlc for that one
instead
ah the music brings back memories of our
gameplay
oh is this is is uh this pokemon uh
coming to the game new
member
oh
that's it okay
shaymin
i actually oh i'll tell you about this
later [\h__\h] shaming man
[\h__\h] shaymin
hey
it's time for me
hi
hello uh
next up what next up what they said what
it stopped for me
yo yo yo yo yo
yo
what yo wait yo
yo what's that what
[\h__\h] youtube
[\h__\h] youtube i kiss wait wait
what the [\h__\h]
am i
my youtube is just dead
paige unresponsive go [\h__\h] yourself
nothing works
my hyper chat doesn't work either
oh [\h__\h] sake
pretend that youtube dad i can't no this
is absolutely dead what's happening guys
tell me use your phone my phone my phone
my phone but then i'll have to mute my
microphone
oh my god
free update i'm looking at my phone
what just like a little quest or
something
this is so stupid
balls
my youtube is so bad
i can't even close the brow okay no now
i couldn't close the browser but i can't
refresh
anime they're making an anime okay
what shiny alphas what was the thing
that i missed
well let me get an anime about any
anything aren't they so
wait that's it
i'm watching a japanese program now by
the way this is the first one i got
suggested
what's that
security guy walking for a building
he's gonna find a pokemon
oh
are you guys watching getting the same
thing i'm moving
or game freak
honey
what's behind the door
uh
old stuff
coffee
oh
well everything's going crazy now
detective pikachu too i like that movie
i think i watched it
i think i enjoyed it
wait that's
looks like sword and shield
was our case
new world wait what
hmm
is that
new game
but that pokemon
i mostly see old pokemon i guess that's
on purpose they wouldn't want to spoil
our new pokemon that much in this
trailer
wait it looks big that it looks big
oh cute house
wait isn't this so early like we just
released two games
it is gen 9.
it looks like
what
yeah maybe in december they like to
release games uh for christmas i think
oh
you start
that cat is cute the green can the greek
title is cute the the dinosaur and the
duck where they're all [\h__\h] gonna
have to get all of them pokemon pokemon
sub scarlet and violets guys and violet
scarlet and violet
scotland and violin yoho they look so
cute i want all of them
wait i like all of them
either the cat or the duck wait the cup
the duck looks so normal though like
what type is that i guess water
oh my god oh my god
cool
so that's gen 9
right
wait was there a date but i think 2022
i'm surprised that they announced this
like so early
in the year
because like oh my god it already looked
like there was a lot of it already like
done
holy [\h__\h] late 20
wow
cool cool cool wait
i'm hyped with you guys i feel so hyped
hi pipe hi pipe
thanks youtube for breaking and falling
apart by the way
when i needed you the most
i saw it on my phone well that's
exciting that's exciting yeah then the
dinosaur looks so derpy so cute
oh my god
omg wait a second oh i need my chat
hyper chat come back to me i don't know
what happened there
i don't know what happened
wait a second let me i want to read the
chat give me a moment
chill everybody chill chill chill okay
my new song scarlett
green cat looks like chiara's cat
cute right what the [\h__\h] a green cat uh
a plant cat ah that's so weird like they
already did like fire cat
but plants cat is so weird
[Laughter]
starter yeah what the [\h__\h] but don't i
already have what's that duck pokemon
again with the
with the
with the that's holding the
though
bleach
leak leak
not psyduck not psylocke i mean uh
i guess i mean ducklit
farfetch'd farfetch'd yeah
firefight
wait i want to look at the what the [\h__\h]
i need to look at that again
wait give me let me let me look again uh
let me look
i'm opening the archive i want to watch
the trailer getting better quality so
give me give me a moment
i wanna i watched it in such a tiny
resolution
give me one sec
he's opening the door
there's a room with lots of old stuff in
there
how does this
like make any sense like
like what's the why
why does he find the new game
in the coffee
[Laughter]
what what i don't understand
this makes no sense
they connected all the regions
that's what you think
okay now he's like
in the pokemon world i suppose
maybe there's a coffee pokemon
okay okay okay
well i think
if it's this early they're probably
still gonna work a bit on the graphics
no
holy [\h__\h]
fps in the background
yeah they gotta work on some things but
that that was that pokemon in the in the
desert neil i've never seen that one
before
this
oh
no
that huge tower building looks nice and
oh my god well a lot of the buildings
look nice
oh that house on the beach looks so nice
wait is that
is that the alola
huh
italy generation oh
oh they never did italy before did they
now that you say it
it looks maybe a little bit like ah the
stardust looks so cute
wait there's an apple but then we
already have like an apple dragon
pokemon in sword and shield
but this one looks different looks more
like a not dragon but dinosaur i guess
apple dinosaur but are they repeating
their own ideas
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah i guess the one before was an apple
dragon and this one is an apple
dinosaur
it's so cute
the duck is adorable too but looks like
this like the
the simplest out of these ones and the
cat is just oh
my god
so adorable
i want to see the i want to see what
they look like linda i want to pet the
grass cat you ain't so cute they look so
happy they all look happy except the
duck the duck looks
not impressed is that is that hair or a
hat i guess both at the same time
on top of the duck's head
looks like a
oh
[Music]
no they're cute they're all cute the
the apple
dinosaur
looks to me like it would be in some
other game i don't know what i'm
thinking of
as the police said also
oh my god
you're choosing a duck calling it
of course you are going to call it that
oh cute
wait that's so hype
that's so hype let me let me go through
the
hotel does that look like italy
i don't know not really
i don't know what i think about
what the
what the humans look like
it doesn't look very pokemonish to me
if you know what i mean i'm looking at a
still at a still shot of the
what looks like the protagonist boy
it looks like i don't know
a different kind of game
it looks like they tried to make them
look more realistic than before
it looks
different yeah
they don't look like pokemon
protagonists
also like when i saw some humans walking
in the background
but i wonder if you can like swim again
because there was like a huge water area
so i suppose that we're gonna be able to
swim again
maybe even fly again to maybe they're
gonna take a lot from arceus actually
that would be really cool
yeah the humans look
they look like
i don't know they look weird
i'm watching it again
[Laughter]
sword and shield had a road on bike
wait oh yeah was that was that bike able
to swim on the on the water i guess it
was
was it floating on the water i don't
remember anymore
[Music]
yeah
i guess archaea's was a testing ground
yeah but i mean they must have worked on
this
way before
because
yeah they were working on this timeline
simultaneously to arceus
damn which means they were working on
three games at once although
shining
pearl brilliant diamond was was not by a
game freak right
as far as i know
eh there's a pokemon meme with me what
do you mean
the player characters never swam on
their own before true
it seems like humans can't swim in the
pokemon world they always gotta use
pokemons for that
they're just oh no wait trainers
trainers were able to swim so i guess
okay
it's just it's just a protagonist who's
unable to learn how to swim
maybe they're scared of water
yeah there's swimmer trainers with the
best
music ever
[Laughter]
the new region is based on spain where
did they say that that's
spain it look it does let indeed look
more like spain than italy because when
i look at the that little house with the
palm trees and all that i don't see that
in italy italy is beautiful but it looks
kind of different i've been to both
countries
yeah spain
spain looks
more like that i think yeah
yeah
nice
there's a map on the wall that looks
like spain oh
oh people are already becoming
detectives and investigating
[Music]
but what spain
has no desert like that does it
i don't think spain has a desert like
that
but i guess that's just in order to add
some kind of biomes
to yeah so to have a variety of biomes i
guess
spain is a desert it does it doesn't
have a desert like that
a crazy desert like that
i know spain is pretty dry i've seen
like
not very lush places but a desert a
full-on desert
spain has the only desert in the
european way in a second
spain desert
oh tabana
yeah okay something like that
uh but that still has like a lot of you
know bushes and stuff
i mean like
the what we saw in the trailer had like
no bush bushes it was like 100
sand and i was like that's
that doesn't look like spain
um
not quite
now although there are some photos of
that desert that have no pushes
hey i didn't know
uh cool cool cool
looks pretty cool tabernace desert
europe's only dessert is hidden in the
corner of spain
damn i didn't know we have something
like this
[Laughter]
well then it makes sense no
there are good images on a japanese
pokemon website oh pokemon
um
japan
[Music]
oh wait
scarlet
violet
scarlet violet
scarlet violet remember the name guys
uh
wait
i can't even find the pokemon website
is it pokemon.japan
nope
there is no pokemon dot japan what a
waste what a waste of uh
of a website name
uh
whatever i saw i saw what i needed to
see
beautiful
exciting i mean beautiful
it has a
a potential potential to be beautiful
[Laughter]
uh
um
i wonder what my uh what my nintendo
youtuber
uh says about that looking forward to
watching his reaction to this
i've seen enough i'm satisfied yeah i'm
um um wow which person are you which
version are you getting oh i don't know
i never really
uh carry that much
but i went for shield
i always go for the on pop wait i really
always go for the unpopular choice i
went for um sun in sun and moon while
most other people went for moon
at least in my friend circle moon seemed
more popular
i went for shield for sword and shield i
went for
a pearl
shining shining pearl when most people
went for a brilliant diamond
yeah i'm the underdog
i'm not doing it on purpose i'm a
contrarian maybe i am pokemon hipster
maybe i am so what
no but why did i make those choices for
some i just felt like
um i like things to be sunny and bright
i don't even care about the legendaries
i think yeah my fault behind choosing
sun
was because i liked the i like the
sunniness of of the idea of it being
sunny
uh
yeah
i go for warm colors
it's true
oh no no sword and shield shield was
blue no
wasn't shield blue
i'm a phoenix yeah
[Laughter]
uh
i'm pink moon because i like nighttime
wow
[\h__\h] was red oh wait
[Laughter]
oh
what does that cell
was that cell
or maybe i am
subconsciously always going for wrong
colors
[Laughter]
and then in this case
i guess i would go for scarlet i also
like the name scarlet and then the the
color scarlet i like the color scarlet
is sexy
really like scarlet i like violet too
those are both nice colors ah
i like them both but i like
if i had to choose i think i would
choose scarlet scarlet is hot
it's a sexy color
scarlet red
[Music]
but ina ina will go for violet i'm
already excited
she literally has to go for violet
all right
[Music]
damn damn pokemon fans must be so happy
to hear about the new gen now
damn
how is the pokemon community doing are
they happy are they mad
i wonder
how's it going on let's look on twitter
how's twitter going
babies yes dakuma
polika says
new game isn't it too fast eh whatever
somebody says
oh wow pokemon new game i'm excited
fubuki says
uh the title
screen already is yabi uh-huh
an artist that follows says
uh the duck makes me think of superhero
senpai
and the name wait there's a name to it
already the name apparently also is like
subaru what where are the names what are
their names what are their names
what are the japanese names i guess
pokemon
where were the names i didn't see any
names suka
do you say starter in
in japanese too wait um
where are the names what are the names
where the names pokemon
scarlet
the artwork's released
oh i'm on the website now oh
okay the cat is in japanese
[Music]
obviously a cat sound the
uh
it's it's not a dinosaur it's a
crocodile
it's an apple crocodile crocodile apple
it's called colgate
and the
way the color looks so different ah now
it makes sense the color looks so
different for the duck pokemon
in the actual artwork uh it's called
kuwasu class
which i think is like
i think it's imitating the sound that
the duck makes like
oh i didn't even get that fire gator oh
maybe yeah
plus
oh
kogamo pokemon
baby duck pokemon oh my god
[Music]
the time for the cat says kusa neko
pokemon i don't even need to translate
that for you guys right
and she says grass cat croissant eagle
it's so simple i like it
oh
uh here are the
the artwork for the
characters looks fine but in game i
don't like what they look like in game
i don't like it
i like the artwork not the in-game look
where is this at i'm looking at the
pokemon.co.japan website now
yeah they look like i don't know
something like a game a a game for girls
a cheap game for girls where you raise a
horse
do you get what i'm saying
[Laughter]
it's very specific but but that's where
i can see those models at yeah maybe
like a barbie game
not exact no barbie the barbies would
look a bit
different style wise
oh well we'll get used to it
[Music]
they have like a
school uniform shirt but with like
something that looks like bathing shorts
like as if they're ready to go
jump into the ocean anytime that's cute
that's cute
[Music]
looking at the scenery screenshots
the house is so cute i want to live in
that house
i want to live there holy [\h__\h] they also
have like a lot of gardening
patches my mom would be so happy there
hey
okay okay enough of that enough for that
enough for that enough of that uh no
more no more
we need to play pokemon
that's so cool that's so cool oh my god
oh my god the crocodile is so cute
[\h__\h]
but
i have to i have to go for i think i'm
gonna go for the cat
uh
system update oh yeah what did i add
some extra quest or something all right
let me um
turn on my switch one second
okay
yeah man the starters all look good
though that's like usually there's
always like one started not not always
but often there's like one starter
that's like
[Music]
but here in this case whoo
ikea's adventure okay okay okay okay
for free pokeballs okay okay
um yo they're so cute yo yo yo yo
gaming time i played a lot yesterday
um
trying to get the the wisps
most of my time was wasted on the wisps
uh tried to catch some pokemon too
um but
oops oh my god okay wait
i have to turn it on again i hate that
ah i have to get up again
almost slipped
i always have to work around a walk
around the table that i brought in for
that one stream now it's huge man
but now i have like a second
table we could do some more stuff
uh
okay let's
oh i have that thing again where
my [\h__\h] hell now my elgato is
wait wait wait okay now it's is it
moving no it's not it's not moving
[\h__\h]
give me a [\h__\h] break
game capture
absolutely broken
game capture why you do this to me
it moves on obs but it didn't move uh on
my screen
how about now
there we are okay
[Applause]
so
today
uh the plan is
to
uh
oops
to
yeah
get to that second ending which
apparently
um
is
about
fighting a specific character
i want to sit on that bench
uh did you not prepare of course i
prepared what do you mean shut up
of course i prefer to prepare to watch
the the
direct with you guys
yeah no sounds oh yeah
there you go
[Music]
oh i guess no i didn't download the
update oh
now i spoiled you yes i have a target
kiss now
i i caught the one that was flying
around and i was like hmm according to
sana target kiss is very strong
maybe i should get it and i leveled it
uh as much as i could it's still uh
lagging behind a little bit
um
compared to the others i also put solar
arc in my team because you guys said
they're up very strong could be helpful
but i don't know about this team
i think we got a lot covered
we have water stone
psychic fire ghost electro
plant uh
what else
dark
uh
yeah we got a lot covered dragon
dragon
what the target kids have again
oh yeah fairy
fairy flying normal
as which is suggested ground type well
but we have ground attacks at least i
don't know if i can cover a ground type
i know dragon is weak to dragon i know i
know
so anyway yeah we sparks are staying
forever
i love my obese sparks
my fat sparks
okay what was i gonna do change hyper
beam i added hyper beam because i was
like i don't know what else to add
they had some lame attacks so
uh oh yeah i need to
uh i need to
oops what am i doing
uh
how to play on the switch again there we
go
oh would you look at
i
um
don't ask
uh
i think i got them because they were on
sale while i was buying some other games
and i was like maybe i think i'll play
it at one point
[Laughter]
did it did it update anything
plus button
okay
oh oh it's not out yet ah okay okay
okay no problem mario rabbids is that a
cool album uh i think i think you can
actually i don't know i only saw
gameplay of it solo and it looked like
fun i like rabbits
so yeah i thought maybe for like a short
stream at some point
could be fun maybe maybe
maybe
i don't even know if i have permission
to play it but i just thought it was
really cheap and i was like ah yeah
whatever let's do it
let's buy it let's download it and
ninokuni the thing about ninokuni is i
feel like i played it
before
like years ago
but that's so long ago
that i barely remember but i think i did
but is this this is the first
ninokuni right
not the second one right
i'm pretty sure i played it
yeah i think so
eldon ring
i'm still thinking about it i think
maybe
one more
stream to judge
but yeah it's probably not gonna become
a serious because i feel like
it's a great game and i want to maybe
like play it eventually
without the pressure of pressure of
streaming
um
i don't think
someone like me could
do it justice
playing it as a series
a regular weekly series on my stream
anyway uh where the [\h__\h] is the main
quest right now
meet volo at the heights camp in
obsidian field lens
that
that's
we're not
that that's not it right we're still
gonna do a lot of stuff in between right
that's not it right
oh
last outbreak from miss drivers
cool
i've got ways to okay okay
miss drevis
[Music]
miss drivers
ms dre this is cool what does a shiny
mystery this look like
i wanna look
but wait so how do you do it again you
save before you go to the outbreak right
i heard some people do it differently
though
uh
oops what am i doing i can't i don't
know how to play this game anymore i
played on on on handheld yesterday
oh
god
save
save at the cam save in the camp
okay
saving the camp
okay go
let's take a look
it's the same buttons yeah but they're
like kind of in a different place
uh
safe
right and is autosave off
wait
what settings
uh
i'll just save why does it always enable
itself
save and exit
there we go
okay where is it go go
i haven't been here in like a long time
man
there's still so many pokemon here i
think that i didn't catch yet
summit camp
now save the game again
oh
okay
save again
okay okay yeah yeah yeah yeah cause it
went back to where the game was still on
autosave
uh
no
oh there they are
shiny
no shiny
they're pretty dope hello
okay
and then and then i just restart
but wait wasn't that the wrong eh but i
saved there
are you sure
[Music]
go back to the town now
without saving catch catch them
captain mantilla goes away
i guess that's another way to do it
i don't have that many balls though
[Music]
they do be looking at me oh
oh
damn it
that went above its head
no no don't fight me
i'm not here i'm not here
wait the sound is so quiet i hear
nothing
if i don't hear anything that means you
guys don't hear anything either
a baba
okay now we got some sound going a
little bit tiny bit
got one
what
[Music]
and
if i
if i [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
if i clear everything and still don't
uh
see a shiny that's when i
reload the save file
that [\h__\h] tree hitbox yeah
they notice me but they don't attack me
that's interesting
they're so easy to catch what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
guys if i only do that one ending
how long do you think that will take me
like i need to
know
how long i'll be streaming today roughly
reset go back to town come back if the
outbreak is still available
out of a dog
[Music]
a few hours
that's not that much so we can waste
some time doing shiny stuff right
i still haven't found a single shiny
i don't know why
i wanted to shiny too okay that's it oh
no there's so are they still respawning
[Music]
i'm out of wing balls
i'm on the wing balls
uh i'll just reset them
46 hours yeah if i do some stuff in
between i guess so
okay close the game
but
but now i go back in but i i saved after
i was already at the camp
so
at that point aren't the isn't it
already loaded in
did i do it wrong again enter again but
then go back to town
and
then there's still
the outbreak is not going to go away
okay
oh sure
let's put on a little bg unless that
might take a while
dad no the code is apparently not active
yet we tried updating the game but there
is no update at the moment
oh wait i can unpin the comment
um
i sure okay now go back to town if
outbreaks go away reset eh
checking now makes no sense right
save at camp encounter outbreak close
game go back to town if no outbreak and
close game and retry
return to village
only have one to two minutes for the
outbreak yeah
now i'm going back to town and now i'm
going back here and there's an outbreak
so all good uh which one's in summit
camp
we're shiny hunting let's just just a
little bit just a little bit i'll
probably give up early enough
shiny doko
it looks ugly though
it looks like it's covered in poop
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's covered in poop
yay
[Music]
my dear my beloved my beloved
my beloved shiny
my first shiny
now we gotta put it in the team now
are you
really shiny the non-chinese look better
than you do though man
those non-chinese look better than you
do
[Laughter]
yay
i did save
there we go
[Music]
we got it look at it oh my god it's
shiny my first chinese
and i like the pokemon itself like it
looks cute what is it what what's the
what's the
same again
what's the what's that what's that
evolution again what's it called
wait isn't it like a super
ugly evolution
miss
miss maggie is miss manches
oh no that looks cool too
and then shiny
ew that's so ugly
the color
[Music]
[Laughter]
sparkle oh
man
i don't know well yeah if it's only
ghost i guess we're not putting it in
the team because we have like
zero zero arc
being ghost normal
um okay i'm happy i got my first shiny
[Laughter]
doesn't look horrible
it looks like
it looks like it got it got bullied by
the other miss drivers
and was pushed into a puddle of uh mud
yeah
that's what it looks like let me do that
side quest where the thing rolls down
there i want to save it how do you do i
just run down there
my darlings feel went rolling down the
hill please you've got to save it okay
oh
i didn't catch that one before today
oh man oh wow this uh
this area
interesting how wow do i need to catch
it something's attacking me i think
this feel
so cute
so round
sweet
no don't continue rolling where are you
going
they keep on rolling rolling and rolling
and rolling and rolling right
like uh kelly said
rolling and rolling and rolling and
rolling and rolling and rolling
i keep rolling rolling rolling rolling
rolling
see
it's like this is like me in alvin ring
[Laughter]
on this field oh it wants to like roll
around with the
with the geo
rock thingies do you do do rock whatever
oh my god oh my oh my god
it wants to be like them
wants to fit in it thinks it's one of
them probably but this would be a great
ski slope
dude
would actually be a great ski slope
probably uh
probably red or black though
ah probably red
speaking in skiing language
well that's that's the bottom so i can't
roll much further oh you wanted to go to
the water
because it was too cold up there maybe
i've barely explored this area
where are you going now
out to you boy
alphys feels hilariously
large your escorts feel all this way
right thank you so much you're welcome
it's cute
meet me back at the summit camp eh
why won't you thank me here
is me
you're cute
cute nenetie
there's a bag
i don't want to fight you
but i could i could catch some pokemon
here
[Music]
you know what i'll walk
a good night
all right we'll see if i'll still be
streaming when you
[Music]
come back
sometimes i do okay
oh isn't this where we came from
what is it a dead end
oh wait did we come from the left here
sorry
wrong
half
crunchy salt hmm
did this boy whoops this boy this boy
can we catch him what do you think
that's
oops
uh
should we give him a berry
it's not the berry that improves oh god
he doesn't even like it he probably
likes salt
yo there's some salt for ya
please don't look at me though while you
eat it
terrifying terrifying
go eat the salt yeah yeah yeah roto it's
a sock oh it's gone
[Music]
you're too slow it's not my fault
this is level
you saw me
uh 60. okay that's manageable
a space-time distortion seems to be
forming guys i never did a space-time
distortion in in this
in this area
plant was strong against rock right
doing all the work for me
wow that's a lot of recoil
i don't even have to attack anymore
[Music]
don't kill me don't kill me little [\h__\h]
all right good
i think i can turn off my btm now
oh [\h__\h] sake
no no no no no no i don't need you bye
bye
golem yeah that was that oh oh that was
one of the pokemon i was um missing for
my pokedex so that's
beautiful
don't mind me just getting this wisp
here and i'm gonna mark it on the map
and then i got the wisp
i didn't get to do any wisps on this map
yet um
but i'll do that in my private time
this is my sign for wisps
volume used to be really difficult you
could only get it for trading with other
players oh
really
this was a great path to take why
why are you saying that because i got
the alpha
[Music]
oh yeah hell to the air
hell to the air
ah i know right i wanted to go to the
yes space distortion
let me go
although it's not ready yet you always
have to wait until
uh
the other thing happens
thank you
i found one
i found one this is not our mission
today don't worry guys i won't be boring
you
guys
hello with
with wisps today don't don't worry
marking
and fly
oh
interesting always i'll watch out what's
flying in the air because sometimes
there's
pokemon flying around
all right let's see
i'll just hang out here wait until
something interesting pops up i guess
but let's save
stiff safe
it's really steep here it's gonna be
annoying to run around oh did i catch
that oh oh there's an alpha thingy there
[\h__\h]
ah that one is really strong too but we
already got that one right because we
caught it uh with the main quest
i'll be back when
the second part
of the distortion starts
saving does nothing no i just want to
save in case i die
[Music]
just for that
so that i won't
fall too far behind especially because
now i don't have all the safe on
maybe i should put autosafe on again
gotta
um what are some other things i did
off-screen i just did some side quests
did some leveling did some catching
did some wisps
uh
what's up
but i realized while i was doing that
yesterday that it was taking so much
time
that i cannot possibly
uh
do it all until today
the normal pokeballs even still work
well
let's see
it's so cute it looks like looks like
one of those swimming hoops
damn it
you want to find
no
what is that uh water uh
yo wait
let me find you it's so cute
and that really hurts
yeah good as floaties like a oh okay
you're not water
good to know
but i'll i'll guess i'll give you a fun
away
a dragon only dragon
maybe i should just poke it with a pen
or with a scissor and then it should
explode
so dragon in that case got it
oh wait wasn't dragon is it only
effective
dragon steel oh okay well then i
actually
fighting is effective oh
nice
let me drink some smoothie i have this
movie with me it's uh
it's with apple
vice
what's vice in english
and banana banana and uh
[Music]
and i forgot the word for that too
grape yeah and vice versa what was what
was riso
like suffice
you don't even know what that is in
german it might be like um
uh oh
or austrian
uh
an austrian
[Music]
[\h__\h]
word for cherry maybe i don't know
oh
you're a little cutie patootie
but i already have you on research level
10. i don't know why i'm catching you
oh hello
[Music]
we can't catch you okay that makes a lot
of sense
let's find um what's effective i don't
know
that's cops
that was a rowlet a cute
did i ever catch a dust club before
ah
when in doubt i just always go for obese
sparks for some reason
i did put quest oh okay
[Music]
okay
then i can just kill it
[Music]
wait
wait i wanna i wanna give me a second i
wanna look at
i'm obtained unobtained i'm okay
oh my god
don't want to kill it
you think i'll kill it
[Music]
don't kill it
okay good that's good
no
uh parallel parallelization
that's sad
oh
oh man they're ganging up on my fatty
pikachu
[Music]
rock my japanese name is boober
because it has boobs on its uh
i wonder
[Music]
i'll go with palkia
i'll kill the other one and i'll catch
uh
i'll give you a great ball artillery
take this
oh
[Music]
oh wow everything's effective
i'll go with aqua tail
bubba
abuba
[Music]
okay
um i need
i need healing
i wish i could use heal items on myself
ob sparks need ceiling too
and i need to make some space in my
inventory
i mean i should have used fine remedy on
you
um
what can i make
nice
this
and this
and
[Music]
and a smoke bomb do you have space again
yes
good
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
give me those items
who the [\h__\h] is gonna wait can i also
pick that up i never died before in this
game
does someone else have to pick this up
with me for me or can i pick this up
myself
my full revives man my max revives
uh
someone else
it's gonna be some unreliable [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
if you're online someone else will get
them and even even not online just no
one
gets it
is that thing still happening
no
wait but if i just no [\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h]
i saved before catching the rowlet
oh oh no wait it saves after
i catch something even if i have auto
save off
someone
game is
crashed oh
today just everything goes wrong yeah
youtube crashes game crashes
it just can't be helped guys
so how's it going
oh okay so it's gone
but it's before
before i
die oh hi
is this before yeah this is before i
died right
okay
[Music]
i look at my inventory
um i don't know how many i had before
but that seems about right wait mummy
fainted at what point
what point was this
hmm
check your pouch menu ah
i can see that here right you're lost
okay there are no lost satchels
nice
oh nice okay then i'll just continue
with the main quest i guess
yeah
let's go
i caught two pokemon which ones
oh my shiny
no rowlett but that's okay
or it doesn't count uh it doesn't
mention that i uh caught a
shiny not a hotel
could give me a reward for that too
auto save back on
i guess so you got a shiny yeah not long
ago it took me two tries
like one one reload
yeah oh yeah i got a new rank off screen
i'm one rank higher now
return to the village
[Music]
wow
got it shiny
looking ravishing oh thank you
you too
and
i will turn autosave back on
yes
and then i guess i need to save again
yes pokemon gen9 we reacted to it
together
in 20 end of 20 wait did it actually say
did they say end of 2022 or are you guys
just guessing that oh
cute
happy knee shiny
i want to check it out
check it out
i want to check that out too
damn it they said it oh okay
okay
no no we must we must i'll collect
chinese when i'm
playing a game privately
uh we will go to the heights camp
late 2022.
oh that's exciting
i mean it was kind of expected because
they bring out
a new game every year
but i guess
yeah
voldo
i came for you
oh that thing
i've seen it in other places though that
that sign
kiara there you are
have a look here if you will a good long
close look please
see these patterns modeled after pokemon
i've come to think that they might be
letters rather like hieroglyphs if you
will
i've inspected runes across the region
and have concluded that they all seem to
tell the same tale
the tale of a brave soul who together
with the pokemon at his side went on a
journey to search for the fragments of
an all-incoming encompassing deity
uh i didn't understand
both words can i ask about both of them
dude
all
encompassing i think deity is something
like a god but all encompassing i don't
know
yes an all-encompassing deity a creator
of this very universe he didn't explain
the word to me
arceus
okay
perhaps you've already heard his name
yeah it's in the game title
of course what else could i have
expected from the hero who saved the
history region but now let us discuss
the fragments they must surely be the
plates yes the very plates you collected
as you went about quelling all the
frenzied nobles haven't you noticed that
they all have words carved on your backs
go on give them a read
i read the text engraved on the back of
the first plate i don't play i could
i've got
the original one braved alone before the
universe came
this original one is none other than the
pokemon known as arcus
so what you say kiawah i think we should
try to gather all the plates how many am
i missing
and i've got just the idea and where to
start our search join me in the heart of
the grueling grove
yeah
where was that again
yeah i saw his foot glitching out too
is that a whole live stream just kidding
sorry i had to roast uh
her 3d streams
anyway
[Music]
18 plates representing 18 times oh
how many do i have i already have a
bunch
[Music]
[Applause]
second ending today
we're gonna get it no matter what
supposedly i have all the wisps in
[Music]
the swamp area
by the way
uh i don't know did i do it i'm in this
area too
ah the swamp area and the beach area i'm
not sure if i checked all of them here
yet
but one question guys
um
when i was doing the ones in the
i think in the swamp area
um i was kind of like i think i was
watching tv on the side and um i think
i think i got them all but i missed the
last message that would have said
probably
there are no more wisps in this area so
now i don't know
since i missed that message i think i i
think the last one i got was the last
one
but is there any way to check
uh
or do i have to collect all of them in
all areas and then they'll tell me i got
them all
because now i'm unsure
ah the little girl will tell me how much
i have left in each area
or
okay
okay that's good okay okay because i'm
like unsure but i don't want to go
looking endlessly for one mysterious
wisp if i already got all of them
i get rewards from it like in between
two not only at the end
okay okay okay now kiawah according to
my own investigations
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
my stomach hurts
i can't
[Laughter]
i have a laughing fit i'm sorry
it reminds me of that one movie that we
watched where i had a laughing fit that
was crazy too
and members only no man
no man
that was shocking
oh my god
my princess brad yeah i have tears in my
eyes
nami nagani
[Music]
my eyes
oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh god
i
i was so shocked that i i don't know if
you saw it in in the if if my camera
thinks oh
if my camera picked it up but i uh i was
so shocked and like
moved away with my head like look look
to the right side quickly because i was
so shocked
oh my god
i'm so sorry you gotta die at times like
these
so sorry
[Music]
i got a dodge
oh i almost rolled away like an elven
ring
i almost did a roll
well thankfully my my chair
catched me
caught me
and kept me safe
[Music]
sponsored by chair
i got the stone plate oh what that was
easy what the [\h__\h]
really am i really allowed to get it
that easily
why didn't that alpha pokemon have the
plate we were looking for maybe we just
happened to find the plate lying around
[Music]
not sure about that in any case that's
the only other plate that i had any
information about so that's that
useless
and yet nothing seems to be happening
which makes me suspect there must still
be more plates left out there for us to
find oh one more thing i want to do
today is get mana fee because i know how
i know how to and i've had the quest
lying around for ages we're gonna get
manafee
wait is it is it even called manafee in
english too
yeah
i kind of looked up how to get it
yeah i need like uh like certain pokemon
in my team i think one was the
uh i don't know what its name was
uh yeah manafee and fiona we can get
those quickly fairly quickly i should
have the pokemon for it
not to worry though i know the perfect
person to ask she's bound to know all
about the plates mistress cogita
sheep
i would probably not know who he talks
about yeah boyzell man tyke i have those
and overkill i forgot what that looks
like forgot what that was but i probably
have it
the one and only mistress kogita you
haven't had a chance to properly thank
her for helping obtaining the red chain
am i right only more reason to pay her a
visit onward to the ancient retreat i
would not mind hearing
more from that lady
i like her
[Music]
i hear an alpha
i do hear an alpha
ah i caught the alpha one for the mini
quest oh over quick ah the spiky puffer
fish aha
okay okay okay that's the one
[Music]
oh dear this one i caught uh yesterday
off screen this alpha this specific very
specific alpha
where was that
[Music]
yeah i have to get out of here
should we be so nice to pick up some
satchels really quickly let's do it
we have time today since we're not doing
archeas today
i'm gonna do that in my own time
because i i want something to play
sometimes
um
[Music]
in my alone time
and this is one of the few games that i
feel motivated to play alone
i'll just do it whenever i feel like it
because you got the um you know that i
think i did that was like the only
unknown that i got yesterday i'm think
i'll eventually just look at a list and
try to find them
through the list
on set eb
i'll just do it that way
i hate sneezer
i hate the mount i don't know it's kind
of
annoying to use somehow
i don't know it doesn't deserve that
much hate but
i'm not so happy with it
it's the best game to enjoy on the bed
and chill yeah yeah yeah
i was playing it in bed all day
yesterday i literally didn't leave bed
at all yesterday
like not a single time
which ended up in me having a little bit
of back pain but oh oh yesterday i
finally
had the chance to get uh have the the
the rng give me uh a wobbling tree on
this island so i finally cleared that
[\h__\h] combi quest
coconut
[Music]
it only took me a million times
yeah
but is there something there
oh
i never find anything with this boy
old verse 17.
part of a series of old poems that have
been unearthed around the history region
judging from the handwriting it appears
they were all written by the same person
it's like a probably is that a side
quest thing
those are surely very hard to find huh
would you like to read it now sure
once there was a god of field and once
there was a god of spring
open history's winds it wield brought
life to every growing thing
where go you when you are not here
asked i one day the god of spring
no answer would it give me clear but
still did i have an inkling splatoon
there is no great dark truth untold it
simply does not like the cold
i understood nothing
nah no hold on
[Music]
reference that's the only thing i got
from that
okay we gave back three or three things
uh whatever i'll do this one too
i'll do this one too cause i'm so nice
we don't want all these noobs to be
sad about not getting back there
yeah
they're little
purses
where is it there
i'm so nice
that's the one thing i was i was
thinking yesterday like
once this game gets like
less hyped like when when less people
play it actively
what
happens with all the statues like i
don't think there will be enough people
to collect them
what about five years later
what about eight years later
where am i going
will there be anyone to collect the
satchels
those are npc stats just not players
that just sincerely
i've been collecting
npc satchels all this [\h__\h] time
that's why the names are all like
the same
and weird
what
so that oh so that people who don't play
online also still get a chance for those
points i guess
i thought i was being nice to people
foreign
what so it's also like
automatically generated these random
places
what
yeah they keep on repeating the names i
was like yo this ava
always dies what's your problem
what a noob i was like they're such
noobs i need to help them they die so
often
[Music]
i didn't realize that
the [\h__\h] i thought those were real
people but i just thought it was kind of
weird that they had these names
yeah it's bec for getting some marriage
ones i guess
that's kind of embarrassing now
return to village
uh we're gonna go to lady kogita
yes we watched the trailer for pokemon
scarlet violet together at the beginning
of the stream we did
really exciting news
um
this place
yeah
i like the name too
scarlett is such a nice name
scarlett johansson
grass cat grass cat the start is also
great but i think
since i'm so torn between them
i might just decide uh judging by their
evolutions because those are not public
yet right
those will be revealed at a later date i
suppose
so i'll maybe judge my dad although i'm
really leaning towards the cat
but that would be me doing another grass
type starter hmm oh well it's one year
later so what the hell
let's go
ah last one
it's miraculous what you've done it
seems the red chain served its purpose
well
and you carried out your duty
as you were bid
but what brings you here
have you yet what brings you here have
you yet need of me
shabbat the plights
ah yes
a tale whose origins lie a millennium or
two ago
those were the days of the ancient
sinnoh people from whom i and descended
across many
generations
these
four
bears
of mine worshipped arceus as the pokemon
that created the history region and i
have heard of certain fragments plates
as they are called
that were given to the ancestors of
pokemon such as cleaver and word ear
is owl i thought that's true you could
tell us more about arcade center plates
four bears what
i'm afraid i have nothing new to tell
you
why the diamond and pearl clans would
never have confused the alga and palkia
with the creator arceus had anything
concrete been passed down
if only we had more to go on the answers
to these mysteries may even shed light
on waikiawa here fell from the sky
ah
i see what you intend
very well
i'll help as best as i can
there are still other tremendous pokemon
in history other mysteries to be solved
whether they are connected to arcas i
cannot say for certain but in searching
them in searching them out wait it's too
quiet
uh perhaps you'll stumble upon the path
you seek
let me think
there are the pokemon of the lakes of
course and the temple giant i got those
right
[Music]
the crescent moon the volcano and
perhaps where did i get those
perhaps you might even return to the
very beginning
now then what would you hear of
okay i guess i don't have them i thought
i already had them i imagined that i
guess
okay
if we like pokemon elizabeth's first i
know who those are
i know them
uh yes then you already know oh i don't
know yes i do know i i guess i don't
know
go give them your thanks for the right
yes that's why i thought i already have
them because i already met them okay so
now i have to catch them
[Music]
and show them how strong you've become
the plight of the lakes
now then what would you hear of oh i
guess
i guess all of them now okay
well where could that be but fire spit
island
i know where that cave is i've seen it
and the crescent moon
you must go where you may meet the
moon's gaze and obstruct it does that
clue illuminate your path no
well make for the court on the highlands
for now
[Music]
um okay
and temple giant
the secret that lurks in snow porn
temple to find it you must open the door
that is sealed
uh-huh
okay you guys can help me with that
and the beginning
indeed a beginning for you certainly
where was it you first fell to earth
here
okay well that's easy
was there
there was no no cave there though
i think i got them all now
very well last one
the rest depends on you and your efforts
it appears that the opening of the
space-time rift-compelled pokemon that
might otherwise have stayed hidden to
come out and see what has befallen the
world i hope you succeed for your own
sake and for that of the pokedex you
labor on
anu we could rely on you mistress kogita
that's more than enough information to
work with now let's find those plates
let's go
they're all pretty easy to catch when
your level is high enough eh
did the temple one last okay
okay
the crescent moon first the pokemon is
op
but that sounds like it would be
difficult to fight as well
crescent moon first okay
it's just as i had suspected pokemon are
the key to our search kiawah
if we can gather all the plates from
them and decipher the messages on the
backs of the plates at last perhaps we
can meet our kids itself
first need to get that pokedex we're not
doing that today dude it's not our goal
you should go search for the pokemon
that kogi dimension kiawah i have my own
avenues of research that i'd like to
pursue
argus creator of all history
it's true i truly can't wait to see what
kind of pokemon it might be
yeah
okay yeah
then
where where is the corner of the
highlands the moon cosa
thank you for renewing your membership
[Music]
oh dude
i've had a message from mistress coita
i'm told you're collecting plates of
some sort with the merchant volume
yes
then we must go to prelude beach meet me
there oh is that uh you're gonna
force me to get the first one now the
prelude one
i guess i'll go with hill
why is this different
was that always there
it's stone
baby
is he gonna fight me
standing on the dock without his kimono
he's in his night armor
or is he leaving maybe he's like uh i've
done so many mistakes
i don't
think
i deserve the honor of being
the boss here anymore i need to
find myself a new path
and find new lands
or battle
prelude beach indeed a place of
beginning
now is not the time for words
face me in battle okay
okay
challenge me to battle let's go
was that good that i started off with so
much
more on that later
or now
[Music]
[Applause]
let's see if it's enough
strong style
we played
yes of course it is oh
critical yeah
[Music]
damn damn damn cool attack oh he killed
me okay
not bad
guess maybe that was their special
attack
swap two or base box
[Music]
kick
i will never never get that name snorlax
into my brain i'm relaxo is so
so
um
burnt into my brain that i i can't think
of anything else
okay i will stay
this will be a tough one i relaxo is
already so defensive and i have like
nothing strong against it that's that's
tough but
we'll do our best
oh i mean that's pretty
stronger than i thought it would be and
we got him paralyzed oh
the chunk out chunked my chunk
[Music]
we can only fight with another junk then
let's see
out chunked me
oh maybe i should try hyper beam
because it's got 120 power
maybe that's the the best attack i got
in this move set against relaxo
what do you think
i'll do it
[Music]
only she's still paralyzed oh nice i get
another turn
[Music]
show me what you get i didn't give you
the name yet by the way
okay we're getting there
no
[Music]
it paralyzes
now what did the most damage does that
do decent damage but [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
oh that will be a tough nut to crack oh
giga impact will it kill
me alive
i'm alive
with this one i get to go twice
i'll try
revise moment should i use my second
turn to revise moments
[Music]
is
showing me how strong it is
maybe i'll name it sana
because all i can think of is sana when
i think of togekiss
[Laughter]
okay we do have fighting
of course
foreign
i can go twice
[Music]
oh good damage very good damage yo
hallelujah
easy
what's next
[Music]
clapable cliff fable i don't know how to
say it
raising your stats
from the get-go
psychic that hurts again mummy that is
the second time you're going down this
battle i'm so sorry for
keeping on bringing you out okay it
would be nice to have the steel move
down
[\h__\h]
um
[Music]
let's see
okay
how do i fight back with shadow ball oh
i can attack twice
that's pretty good
wow it's so big it's over arc
look at you
wow
wow freaking
kind of escalated with that evolution
[Music]
ah should i do snarl to low in the tank
hmm
also very defensive man he got really
beefy pokemon
but okay he's also six levels above me
please don't clear my team please
wait i can attack three times
sorry
should i heal first
cause he got one more pokemon i don't
know what he has
i can attack three times oh if i use
extra sensory two times if i go for one
of those
use nasty plot first
okay
[Music]
and then
oh nice
wait do i still get a turn
for reviving if i need it let's see what
he oh
wait am i fine i think i'm fine
i can find i can just burn that
[\h__\h] down
nice
we were lucky with that last pokemon
yokatta
battle decided
um
even frightful creatures like pokemon
can become powerful allies
damn i needed
xp [\h__\h]
should have revived at least one more
pokemon
you've grown even stronger since we
faced one another on mount corona
it's clear you do not view pokemon as
dangerous enemies but rather as
trustworthy allies
enemies but
allies with home you can reach great
heights
perhaps you're a divine you are divine
but yes i am
sent to bring escaped from above
here you should have this you have a
plate
wait so is that
the
the plate that i was supposed to get
here or is there another one
huh
okay
nicer
on the very first of our galaxy
expedition team myself benny and the
others set foot on pre-loaded beach i
found that plate
clearly held some kind of power so i've
kept it safe
i find it fitting that it should now end
up with you who likewise arrived here on
this same beach
[Music]
perhaps something is guiding us
indeed it must be so you and i and your
chat filled with backseaters but that's
okay you don't mind do you no i don't
it'll appear we're all being guided by
the one same backseating chat
[Music]
it might be more appropriate to call
this region this inner region
i know i have no right to say this but
we are truly fortunate to have been able
to count you among the survey corps
ranks
if you had not joined us we would have
fallen on mount coroner we would have
lost our home
we would have lost our future
oh
it's okay
i did it happily
now then carry on with your survey work
the knowledge that you collect about the
wild pokemon of this region will serve
to illuminate our path forward as we
walk into the future
i'll do my best
it's been my pleasure
[Music]
it seems there might be four more places
left what'd you find
okay
[Music]
so that one's down now we go to uh wait
am i did i get healed
uh
yes i did okay
good
um
i guess i'll save
four more that really isn't much
i hope we can get some levels though um
quote on the highlands
so they hinted that there is a specific
point where you can see
uh
it summit camp
is that so
maybe where we fought the
uh
the lord
maybe
i don't know
wait what what was the description
i feel gore
moonview arena
one seems to be
that's it i need to here again
what
here where i felt electrons so it is
here okay i don't suppose a god like you
would even know but i guess it behooves
me to ask do you know the pokemon called
priscilla
uh i i think
i do
well i figured you know i would i
wouldn't expect any less from someone
who managed to defeat me even if it was
just a fluke
chris elliot is said to be the very
embodiment of the crescent moon
her feathers are called luna feathers
and legend says that if you hold one as
you fall asleep you'll be visited with
wondrous dreams
well i call her a nightmare that pesky
crystalia ew she descended upon moonview
arena and caused my lord to hide itself
away
i'm so worried about electro that i
can't even sleep never mind dream
i think you might be able to catch
cresselia and perhaps even claim one of
those luna feathers
oh do catch that pesky flying croissant
do it for my poor electrode
though i suppose crystalia can't be all
bad if she at least recognizes
the perfection of the arena looked after
with loving care by the great mellie
okay her face
all right
oh there it already is
uh
what's what's what is the element of you
psychic or or something like that
oh dear oh my god
pure psychic
what
i'm confused
what the [\h__\h]
what
is this like a invisible um wall that
gives me confusion i have to find the
right path to get to her what
i flips my controls oh no
psychic what do i use
what's strong against psyche
can i just catch you normally i'd have
to fight you
bug or dark okay
yeah okay
ah well i've reached you
oh wait i only have nasty blood
uh dark or a bug
well something some dark attack on zoro
ock
wait i don't i don't know
dark ghost ah okay
what
there we go there we go
we're in about level 7 day
okay but it is effective um
[Music]
we should do shadow ball and then bit of
malice
although it might kill me before i can
attack a second time
agile style
does that hurt it does
oh no we're going down
okay
remember to catch it oh
um
do you think
i'll kill it with a hex maybe i should
attack with fire instead
i can attack twice so i can throw this
at him and then throw uh
don't kill it don't kill it don't kill
it okay okay and throw a pokeball
let's see
it's an ultra ball good enough for you
say yes
say yes say yes
[Music]
cycle cut
okay
[Music]
we can survive that uh
another agile flame thriller
and then we're gonna try to hit a uh to
not red yet okay
but it was burnt oh that's actually
maybe bad because
it might die on its own
we'll see
but it now has a status effect so that
gives us higher chance to catch it too
[Music]
you guys said this was so strong did you
say that because you want me to uh use
it in my team but only psychic move
type i don't know
is that really worth it
i think we got psychic covered no need
for that i think dread plate
and his fairy tales moves too yeah but i
have toggle keys together kids can do
psychic and fairy as well and this is
defensive
oh but it is level 70 yeah
ah
because i might be under leveled
true
maybe we'll use it
ah
just for the sake of having a higher
level
yeah
well well this is unexpected instead of
a lunar feather you got some kind of
plate that i do feel power emanating
from it though in any case if cresselia
did not gift us with any of her feathers
then i suppose she thought we had no
need for them
i suppose so
not bad at all grunt though i suppose
anyone with enough luck to the
enough luck to best
the great melody you should be able to
handle at least that much thinking about
it uh halfway competent person like you
might actually make a decent sparring
partner to help my lord and i grow
stronger still
i will go back to the settlement and
tell the others about the feathers that
we didn't get
we got something better guys don't worry
so is that him saying i can battle him
now
if i want to
maybe another time is there an incognito
somewhere here i feel like i'm sure
there is
just don't know where or did i already
get it
when i was last here
including
oh sorry they're called you known
i call them incognito because that's
what they are called in german sorry
i mean unknowns
maybe i've got it already where where
was it supposed to be at
on the tree or on the pillar
i don't see one now
that's what you meant to be wait did i
did
did i write incognito in my tweets
oh no
wait let me see
oh my god i did
pogba babes is the incognito and the
whis request necessary for finishing the
game
why no one told me on twitter
no one said anything
[Music]
know what i meant yeah because i called
it that before
but
some twitter people might may have been
confused
do we want to fight you
just to know to you know practice a
little bit but i might want to rest for
a moment
yeah some of you guys seem to prefer
that name
i guess it's a fine name
i make mistakes too yeah
okay so can we fight him
yep
electrode
what are you here to do have a rematch i
guess wait only against what who who am
i fighting
electrode only
oh
on the way embryo oh
oh wait sorry that
can i cancel cancel cancel
oh no but this one was still fairly easy
i think no no
an hour and now we're doing it i guess
[\h__\h] what's what's strong against
electro again oh god oh god oh god
oh my god i forgot oh my god oh my god
oh there's a timer now
see we're in the elgin ring now
fire ground okay
thank you
oh he's so mad he's shaking with anger
same tbh
so bad
someone
[Music]
throw bombs at yellow again
oh no
yes
[Music]
no sense why is he frenzied again
story-wise doesn't that make absolutely
no sense
why is he friends date again
wait i should have done normal probably
is he stronger now because level 70 i
don't think he was originally level 17.
for funsies
don't question it
okay
now
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
can i just run away i don't want to
fight you
is that about
oh wait that's what happened
when i thought i could cancel the battle
now
oh
[Music]
nine nine nine
let myself go down i would um probably
be able to escape the battle but
nah
that's too easy
oh [\h__\h]
pokemon album ring practice
[Applause]
okay i'm back
i'm a true gamer i don't just run away
[Music]
what the
[\h__\h] paralyzed
[Music]
halfway down don't kill me no okay okay
but he gets a second attack i think
oh no
[\h__\h]
yo
he don't
i don't know i don't know
i don't know what's what's uh
what can i do
[Music]
okay
hello
let's give you a try
[Music]
it does the trick
it down the trick
[Music]
go go go go spam those
he kills myself because i can't one hit
him
here we go again halfway down
hamburger
okay don't get hit anymore chihuahua
better be
careful down
that was mean placement there
that was not nice of you
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
yeah
people said it's easier if you just do
this
maybe
maybe i've heard so some people say that
instead of fighting instead of going
into battle
somehow it's supposedly easier
you can just
continue throwing bombs although i'm
kind of [\h__\h] now
okay i'm going
to be more careful now
[Music]
whatever
shut up
shut up just shut up shut up shut up
just shut up shut up shut up just shut
up shut up
oh no no no room
oh
look at that pretty moon baby
going back into the town
and
gonna go get the first plate
crystalline
that's isn't that a legendary
is it a legendary
people say putting legendaries in your
team is kind of lame but i feel like
honestly they don't even do much
more damage than other pokemon once they
are in a disadvantage with your type
you're [\h__\h] anyway
it doesn't really change much
but if i
are you telling me
i should put it in my team but like who
am i kicking out then talk a kiss
i just worked so hard to raise target
kiss off screen
don't tell me i need to replace it
[Music]
don't say it to me just uh just general
luna blessing op
um
replace the right you nah
i have gujarat too yeah i think so i
have her too
is cute yeah
um
good tank yeah
girl plays palkia but palkia actually
has so many useful moves right now
covers um oopsie okay
covers ground rock and water and dragon
for me all moves that i would otherwise
not have
so i'm keeping polka
psychic flying fairy
oh
wait can
cresselia whatever her name is learn the
fairy move
fairy flying
remove sparks
yes yes
it's also the level though because it's
12 levels higher than my target keys
oh man so by the way i got two target
ticks off screen and i got the leaf and
off screen
and another flare on
i kicked out my kusuogaki
i got some new fish off screen
yeah
okay so you
i guess wait what are your moves right
now psychic fairy uh it already has moon
or moon blast and apparently lunar
blessing is strong
should we change anything
i'm sorry doggie kiss i'll get you back
maybe after that last fight i'll get rid
of cresselia and i'll bring you back
thank you lady
[Music]
700 800. oh but also um oh wait i don't
have any
i used up like almost all of my
grits
grit tests
ah
oh when it's already raised a lot
on its own
what
it just came like that to me
nice
your voice tickles my eardrums oh thank
you is that good
thank you
i still have a few exp thingies why is
that here
[Music]
okay
next up where do we go next up
[Music]
you guys said uh temple last
shall we go to fire spit island let's do
that one
because i know where we have to go for
let's go
did you take a look at your shiny i saw
it before i caught it and i was already
disappointed so
no need oh yeah
that festival attended by everyone in
the clans and galaxy team alike oh it
was wonderful
being able to spend time with eason in
front of everyone was like a dream come
true
i'm sorry paulina here has something she
wants to discuss with you
that's right you should also hear this
irida it seems something is once again
very much a miss on fire spirit island
oh fire spirit island
oh dear you seem reluctant to get
involved
it's just
very hot there
my you're speaking such a disparaging
terms of the seat that my lord archanine
calls home and to think you call
yourself leader you're the hey okay
don't feel you're you're exaggerating
she just doesn't like the heart okay
no no lena i didn't
stop with that silly old nickname in
front of others won't you yo yo yo yo yo
chill
chill for a moment be nice to her she
didn't do anything
why is she so aggressive
oof man
i'm sorry i didn't mean anything by it
it's just an old
habit well anyway you heard her oh no ah
well anyway you heard her please get to
five spit island so we can resolve this
truly please hurry i might melt out here
okay thank you for welcoming me back
here
yeah always nice to be
in this area look at me
look at my map i worked so hard to get
those wisps yesterday it took me an
eternity
okay actually this one was still fairly
easy the the swamps were tough
the swamps were tough man
i korean gaming um
hard to keep track of what you have and
what you don't have yet
sometimes
uh
yo
you again hello girl thank you for
coming so far out of your way
ah martin isn't wasn't lina joining us
oh yeah about that uh
it seems she ordered some time with her
lord so she asked us to check the lava
gym sanction without her
what the nerve of she knows i can't
stand sweltering places like this
well i'm sure she might know it will
the water of the lord of the islands is
such a kind gentle soul
er anyway
shall we go might as well get this over
with her
he has that he has that oval mouth have
you guys noticed
what do we have here
wow wow what is the light here man
[Music]
i already was in here ow before but
there was no pokemon so i was like oh
this must be for later
oh god oh god i'm scared
okay what are we doing uh
i think
we're gonna use those balls of mud
otherwise they wouldn't be here
it's gonna kill me
oh there we go there we go uh wait what
what do i use uh [\h__\h] i don't know
i don't know i don't know what you're a
fire steal or something like that
oh my god okay chill chill now
uh [\h__\h] wrong pokemon
[Applause]
wrong pokemon uh fighting
fighting and ground and water okay
palkia would have been
[\h__\h] yeah better have been better
sorry dude
why is he turning his back on me
we don't want to kill him right we want
to
wait is this like one of those lords
fights where i have to kill him several
times or is this only one fight
it would leave okay then let's uh
i don't know how much damage that will
do
i want to do
some damage
he knows i have a ground move
earth power is four times okay now we're
not using earth power
aqua tail shouldn't kill
yeah let's go safe let's go say it
okay
a normal one might have been fine too
but okay we can't too much more besides
maybe a
special rend
or a power gem
to get him ah but no critical no no no
to get him to
catch now you think sounds i feel like
you might
need a bit more damage but okay
hope soon sorry
let's try an ultra ball
come here
he looks so cute funny design his his
feetsies are cute
looks a little bit like a spider with
those pizzies
like a bug
cute
sorry i generally most pokemon if they
look
uh
if they look feminine i call them she no
matter what they're
oh god
gender is and if they look
more masculine i call them he
uh
well well then we'll go to moomae
spiders are cute you heard it here
i mean i still wouldn't be that happy
about having one hand with me in the
room
to be honest
i'll just try again
but some spiders like small spiders are
cute when i see them on a video or in a
photo
yeah
or like spiders that are
from like a movie an animated movie
those little usually look cute
i did it i got the iron plug
it's pretty going pretty fast you
oh at least the heat slide up a bit holy
[\h__\h] her face
damn was your face like that the last
time she was uh doing that pose i feel
like it got worse
we're both cooking underneath red spoon
flames about on a volcanic island it
certainly does get a bit toasty
i have to ask do you think there was any
need at all for me to be here
nah probably not
after all you were the leader of the
proclaimer this trouble cropped up right
around the scene of one of your clients
noble so uh yeah we're surely the best
for you to come to see it
admirable of you to look after you close
your face
do you really think so i was wondering
if it might not be revengeful all the
times i pushed lena to train her girl is
harder
that's really not the case
even if warden panita may have mentioned
something about the need for a tough
love
i thought so to think she was so patient
and kind with live but when it comes to
me
oh man they have a complicated
relationship
hmm
well killer you did great well i'll just
head back ahead of you dude
i sound like the hippo from a grad
school oh i've never seen that
two more plates
easy
i guess i'll get some more balls of muds
while i'm here and i never use them but
why not i guess
[Music]
okay well if we really have issues with
the last battle then i could uh get rid
of so fetch and replace with
heat friends maybe
maybe but we'll see we'll see
maybe
maybe the game wants us to use all these
pokemon because they're all strong
they'll have different types and
maybe they all cover something that is
necessary
for
um
the battle that is upon us
maybe
play some old legendaries yeah we'll see
i don't want to do all legendary steam
but if we have a lot of problems
um then we might
if we go game over we might try it what
do you want by the way
okay
all right
leaving i'm leaving
[Music]
heatran
level 70.
not bad
[Music]
make sure you use great items you've
collected from catching stuff along the
way that'll help you i used them all up
on the team that i had before switching
out
uh took a kiss
i was like yo i gotta get these this
team strong so i used
millions of grits
for
my team
now i switched out tongue kiss
but that moon pokemon it came already
with some
uh
upgrades i guess
releasing releasing pokemon gets me that
too
what oh i didn't know that
[Music]
oh
um
all right next up
uh
the plate of the lakes
i like verity like failure oh they're
still there
the same places where they were before
okay
okey-dokey
one reason to encourage you to catch
[\h__\h] but be careful since you need one
of everything to advance their text
entries
even if i caught them once if i kick
them out of my
wrench
then
it will be as if i don't
like never had it anymore
yeah we saw the pokemon scarlet violet
announcement together
welcome good morning
you missed out on some
thank you molty
one more month let's go
you're so close
are you excited you don't look very
excited
it's at least this pokemon looks pretty
i don't dislike the design
[Music]
good morning no problem
i won't lose their research okay
if you need to use them for advanced
resources you need to help them
advance research levels
i don't know what to fight them with
but well we're just gonna
go in
and see what happens
are you gonna let me try to catch you
this time
oh oh how are we gonna do this
the easy
wine the easy way really
really
wow
getting wrecked again
uh okay
ghost
yes
safe oh i didn't save
[\h__\h] but all the safe is on again so
i think
it should be fine if we
reset oh [\h__\h] i don't want to kill it
yeah yeah how
how much damage would that do
um
[Music]
how many times is dark effective and how
many times is cost effective because it
always only says super effective max but
there's something that's like super
super effective right
above two times okay
i'm gonna i'm gonna try
normal no agile come on come on
yeah easy easy easy the next time we can
do agile though
okay okay okay
ow you little [\h__\h]
stop it
oh twice yes
[Music]
offensive stats lowered twice and now
we're going in
with the ultra ball
come on be a good boy
oh girl
please
yes
thank you
this time no deaths in my team for once
two more like pokemon
two more
yes yes yes
otto
yeah speaking of gamers
i i did um
i was aware of
the girls meeting up the
n.a girls i guess
um
and where is it where are the others
again
i'll talk about it just tell me where i
need to go i forgot i forgot where were
the other places grilling grove is maybe
one of them
wait were they in other maps
they weren't on the maps right okay
okay okay
um
actually i i kind of found out by
coincidence when i was talking to mumei
about the holotorii collab
uh
and and i was talking to ahmed at the
same time a day
and then ahmed
i don't know it kind of came up randomly
otherwise i wouldn't even have known
about it probably until last minute
uh but i knew about it since maybe
a few days ago
a few days a few days before it happened
like really recently i found out
on the evening before the holotorii
collapse they kind of like organized it
behind the scenes like i didn't know
anything about it
until i just kind of it came up when i
was talking to ahmed and and mummy and
it just kind of came up because it had
to i don't know what we were talking
about but yeah
um
and i was like
it's so cool it was so like mummy
actually
beforehand when we were planning the
holotoy thing
um
she was like ah i'm probably gonna be
with some friends
uh but i it's okay i can still
be there
and i was like oh okay
i guess her friends don't mind if she
streams in the middle of the nights last
morning
and then later
i realized oh
you were talking about other hollow live
english members gosh mumma you could
have told me she was so
so vague about it that i
didn't understand
i don't know why she just didn't say it
clearly to me
why was there a need to keep it a secret
from me
uh anyway
so
uh
yeah yeah i
i knew about it but kind of late if i
knew about it earlier like much earlier
to be honest i feel like
i might have tried to join too
it would have been a bit difficult you
know but i think it wouldn't have been
impossible
i would have maybe given it a try if i
knew
early enough to travel there because
like
huh
[Music]
i want to meet those girls too
like
i hate it when i'm being left out of
this kind of things
i mean it's
they probably thought that
because i'm in europe i wouldn't
be able to go i wouldn't want to
go well i wan i wanna go too
is this the same psychic time
yo wait can you wait what the [\h__\h]
ami said that she will
um come over to me to help me with some
stuff and to meet me but that's still
like a while to go
so
like actually like
a long a long time to go
but i'll i'll still be alone here for
i feel like that might kill it by
accident
but if normal did this much damage
[Music]
i'm scared i'll do extra sensory
okay
yeah missing out
it doesn't feel so nice i
i was so excited for them doing the
karaoke i was planning on watching it
but then when it happened and i saw them
all together
i i quickly closed the stream because i
was like oh
it's good for them that i'm so happy
that they met and they did some fun
things and
got to know each other i asked inna
we had a recording
uh
like shortly before they all met i think
um
and i asked her like was it awkward to
like
meet
them like how was it how was the
atmosphere she was like oh no not at all
so apparently they clicked immediately
and that's nice
that's nice
[Music]
don't kill it good good good good good
that's good
yeah i wanna
i wanna be there too and sing together
with them
man
must be nice
they're coming oh i don't think they're
all coming to me at the moment
[Applause]
from what i know
like amma is pretty
and then maybe one more member that's
like
or so sure about
uh joining the trip to me
yeah
so i
i don't know
it's not like suddenly all of all of uh
n a will come to see me
that's not gonna happen
although i would recommend them to see
europe europe is nice
we could go so many places we don't have
to go to austria we can go to other
countries yo
spain france italy
sweden
germany
so many cool places yo
europe is cool yo
yeah
yeah yeah yeah but that happened uh
seemed like they had a lot of fun
oh man
why
oh
see like whole life indonesia and whole
live japan
they all
are like in the same country
so if they wanted to meet up they can
meet up
so easily so quickly
but we are like all over the globe
scattered
in like austria australia
n a
japan
it's like everywhere
the day when we will all be together
will be a miracle did you just say alola
did you just say alola to me
ah just the person i've been waiting for
my killcam wandered off to go play but
they haven't come back yet do you think
you can help me find them
that's the snow vulpix uh
quest i'm sorry back home and alola
vulpix were called kale killer oh really
what's their name kale kim i don't
remember their name being koko it was
vulpix anyway i know
ken can
uh
oh did you not go to play with the wrist
are you so cute
you just went in alone and vulpix looks
like i know i played the game
they blend right into the snow with
their white fur so trying to find them
all just by myself would take ages and
i'm still missing five of them oh
cutie pie
sure um maybe not now
but
there we go we need to go there
all right
and then i saw so much fan art of the
girls
it hit me right in the coconut there was
this one fan art of
um
ama and ina hugging
so happily with a big smile a big laugh
they look so happy
and i had to imagine that moment in real
life when i saw that fan art
oh
i don't know it's a complicated feeling
i want to be there too
and also it must be so titty
oh hello alpha chimecho
oops
yeah good for them
wasn't it kind of sense that all of them
were like
taking a break guys
did you guys not realize what was going
on wasn't it such that they all didn't
put out a schedule
some of them were saying oh we're
traveling
like it was pretty obvious
but you were like oh no way it can't be
it can't be
it can't possibly be i was super
suspicious
some people were guessing it
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
it all worked out perfectly
how well you're the last one i need to
get
i didn't even know they are on the break
uh you are hashtag hashtag i see i see
[Music]
i only follow you off you often so i
hadn't noticed thank you oh there's a
bunch of bunch of hashtags of yolk here
duncan
[Music]
i'll go with normal attack
oh that's
interesting how
this one seems the most defensive i
don't know
maybe that's just me wake up
is there a chance that it will attack
anyway or is it sleeping for real now
is there a chance
it'll attack
anyway
i'll try
too drowsy okay
can you combine them all and do a cut
dice
damn that hypnosis
sleep isn't
in this game
oh okay i guess it's just drowsy
[Music]
no you can't future pokemon maybe
i'll try this
let's see how much this one does
go girl
oh but so many people
eh
wait i forgot what was i gonna say
literally the moment i started talking i
forgot what i was gonna say
restart restart reset my brain
uh
i i tweeted out uh
some emojis
that was
about the about
kisuna i
graduation
graduation okay it's not the graduation
it's a break thingy and and um
the karaoke as well it was like both i
was feeling so
piano my feeling can only be described
in pn no words just pn
okay don't kill it
yeah officially it's not supposed to be
a grad graduation
officially
i watched i watched some of the concert
of kizunai
i love you guys are up to date but
kizuna i had her final concert
uh
yesterday the day before yesterday
the day before yesterday
the day before yesterday i think
um
yeah it was great
it was great it was really really
inspiring and emotional
it gave me shivers and and goosebumps
yeah it was beautiful she went to sleep
yes
[Music]
the first meetup i watched i think for
most people she's the first first
vichuba
they have encountered even if they are
not fully aware of it
because they didn't know the term
youtuber at the time maybe
do i get the plate now there it is the
draco plate oh
for dragon types
yeah for me too i think
i remember watching her in the early
days when she first like started booming
but but
i also think i was not quite aware
of the whole youtuber thing like not
actively
okay last one is in the temple
last but not least
youtube and yes so i have a lot of
respect for her
a lot of respect
and i wish her all the best
in the future isn't the temple here
here is this where i need to go the snow
point temple for the last one
let me see yeah there's no point temple
okay it's close by perfect
um
yeah wish her all the best i hope she
can
um find something
like a job or whatever
or just enjoy life
do anything she likes to do
enjoy life to the fullest enjoy having
not to work maybe for a while
having some free time
um
hello
i guess i'll just walk in
yeah
cause she was like
i'm sure she was like working daily
very very busy
life
and but what's cool is that she was kind
of like
they made something like a vocaloid out
of her not exactly a vocaloid
but something similar to it so this way
her voice
will be
accessible
and you can like make things with her
voice for the end of time isn't that
beautiful
it's
i read where the dif i read about what
the difference is between um
a normal vocaloid and what she uh
god it's like uh
something like a
intelligent thingy that learns the voice
by
i don't know
and i can't explain it [\h__\h] i need to
kind of damn
you know what i'll actually go to
can i hear myself in the pearl
settlement
machine learning is something like that
because the vocaloid is apparently a
little bit different than that
um
something like
yeah i guess it's something like that
like a deep fake but for the voice yeah
yeah yeah that's maybe a good comparison
the one that that the the thing that
they made out of her voice is that and
the vocaloid is i guess just a computer
generated voice or something like that
um
yeah
i think that gets the closest wait so
wait there was no healing here [\h__\h]
i guess it's only the ones with the
camps i have just now realized that
the icons are different
uh morning
yeah synthesizer
so i don't know if you guys saw the
concert but like she performed with that
vocaloid which is not really a vocaloid
they called her kizuna so she has the
same name and they perform together
uh
in the concert they perform the song
together and she sounds so natural
exactly like kizuna especially when she
sings when she talks
it's maybe more noticeable
um
but yeah when she sings
it's like 100 kids in the eye it sounds
amazing
uh
really really cool it's like a voice
changer no no no no it's like a vocal
light you make you can like let that
robot
make things you want her
to say
makes
sense you can make her say things you
want her to say or make her sing things
you want her to sing
yeah
yes that's it savio i c-a-v-i-o-a-i
that's
what she is
he's not i robot
should have bought some balls too
there we go
i go this way
wasn't there like a really scary alpha
somewhere here
oh
oh yeah oh yeah
a door
they said something about the door
yeah but i think that's beautiful
because like one thing that i think is
really scary when you're like
a celebrity or like an internet
um
thing
influencer or i don't know something
like that
a streamer or whatever
like
people know you
while you're active but once you're gone
people so quickly forget about what you
did who you were and all that and move
on with their lives
and so it can happen so quickly that
you're not part of someone's life
anymore
or something is not part of your life
when it always used to be and seemed so
important to you
while it was a part of your life
but especially especially with kids and
i
like all things must come to an end but
it would be so sad that something
someone so important with so much
influence who created a history and a
whole genre the whole world
would so quickly so easily
disappear from everybody's minds
and be forgotten you wouldn't want that
to happen right that would that would be
so ridiculous how can it be so easy
to just fade away and be forgotten but
thanks to
making that voice into something like a
vocaloid i think that's really really
smart because that way her voice can be
um heard
any time you can always make her
continue to sing if you feel like as a
kiss on an iphone if you feel like oh i
miss her singing you just can
listen to that vocaloid thingy sing
something
and you feel like she's still there and
that way
something
something will be left behind you know
that's something
that
i hope that
i can do too but it's just really hard
like to leave something behind in order
to leave something behind for ages that
people will remember
you really gotta do something
unforgettable something huge something
that makes a difference
and i mean that's objective like
you but some of you maybe will say oh
you already did that i will never forget
sure you say that but
it
it's not the same
it's not the same as what kiss and i did
and it's not the same as i don't know
someone like michael jackson or elvis
presley or madonna or so did
those people will never be forgotten
because they made a name for themselves
and
yeah
[Music]
um yeah yeah
i wonder if like in 20 years
there will be people who
like watch old whole live streamers who
don't exist anymore and they're like
so that's how it was back then huh
too bad she's not around anymore
become a legend
yeah
would be nice to become a legend
but that's not something anyone can do
that easily
no matter how hard you work
no matter how many things you accomplish
and achieve
it's just that kind of
that kind of
honor
is just not something you can
get that easily it's reserved for
special people i would say
um
[Music]
anyway that was my two cents
on the kizuna eye
thing
[Laughter]
it's a really really beautiful way of
leaving something behind so i thought
that was really cool yeah
yeah yeah and i i really hope that
she'll
have a beautiful
beautiful life
and is able to
move forward
in her own way
yeah
yeah why is it bumming you out it's a
positive thing
don't always be so negative some of you
guys are so negative always
like unbelievable i'm i'm already a
super negative type of person but some
of you guys are just like wanna see
everything so dark cheer up cheer up
for real
negative nancy's ah exactly
exactly
oh we're talking about some beautiful
things someone someone who worked so
hard for so many years who created all
of this i wouldn't be here without her
probably
left the stage and i want to honor that
by saying thank you and i want to say
how how beautiful and genius it is
for her voice to be left behind in a you
know in a capsule like that in a time
capsule
that's amazing
genius anyway moving on
oh i wouldn't have expected to run into
you up here curable what are you up to
it's not even anything sad no
i feel like she deserves a break and she
deserves to move on like
yeah like if
certain certain kind of
graduations and and and ways of ending
activities are definitely sad and
regrettable um
but i feel like for kissing i
i'm i'm not even like i don't know
i mean it would be cool if she was still
if she would continue
of course but i feel like i'm not even
particularly sad because she deserves it
i think she did what's what
what she could do and what she uh
um
i don't know she did so much and
everyone deserves a freaking break
yeah she left on a high note too
agreed agreed
yeah
beautiful graduation concert although i
shouldn't call her graduation but like
it just felt like a graduation concert
an insane graduation concert that was
amazing if you guys missed it it's on
youtube you can watch it for free so do
it
a pioneer yeah inspiring
you're here to try and find the secrets
lurking in the snowpoint temple aren't
you that's what my clairvoyance told me
i'm sappy my baby
it'll tend to get mixed up in all kinds
of strange goings-on kiawah
this door here well they say behind the
sleeps of pokemon so great it could toe
around the entirety of the continents
that lie to the south
no matter what we do this door just
won't seem to open
get caught
when you say that because she's green
but
don't you but when you say gekko i think
of a gecko
um
at least in german it's called gekko
and that is also green and it just fits
really well
it's like a lizard what do you guys call
it gekko too
investigate see i'll i'll open it with
my fingertips now
oh over the plates
oh okay okay
[\h__\h] i didn't save again
are we good still
wow
and so i had to come here last anyway
expecting something like a like reggie
steel type of pokemon i don't know
something weird like that
it's not you
it's not you either
what are you guys doing here
and you guys
no i'm not interested
sorry i'm not interested
i'm not interested oh here we are oh
wait isn't that register
a ranking
[\h__\h] i didn't save no i did save i
didn't say it before i went downhill
okay
what in time is that thing it's colossal
yeah
i'm sure i'm it sure seems to be a
pokemon but let's see what my
clairvoyance has to say
okay
she says gekko
imagine gecko
definitely a pokemon gekko
my grandparents taught me a vision of it
in motion
um
what type is that
steel well it also has plants around it
i feel like with cell fats with fire
we could do pretty well that's what it
looks like to me
a normal
do i have to fight it
hello
i did save
can i push those buttons on your chest
no i want to play with those buttons oh
they're shiny
since
[Music]
i was so wrong
what are you what time for you
[Music]
okay it's fine
i can attack twice
whoa easy yo and bird nice so fetch i'll
switch now
fighting is once again effective
good for me
oh
okay okay okay
that was super effective
it barely did anything wait i'm supposed
to catch it right not kill it oh whoa
whoa whoa whoa i was about to kill it
and i'm always in the killing mindset
what's wrong with me
eh what do you mean slow start
yes
[Music]
for once there are no deaths in my team
beautiful
the blank plate blank
nine are the normal type makes sense
no that was one solid pokemon like a
giant born of the very earth
i guess this is just part of your job of
the server corpse huh
what kind of pokemon is that one you
just called gekko i can't wait to see it
in the pokedex when it's done
yeah i'm pretty curious to read
everything mr professor writes up too
this is how it feels to be in love right
you give you guys a monster after five
turns
ah
that's what you mean with slow start
beloved
i should head back to kogita's retreat
alrighty
[Music]
easy
but wait
i'll catch that one
can i get it from here now if you move
away like that
i'm not sure if i've ever caught that
pokemon
so just in case
while we're here
oh
what he's gone
the [\h__\h]
oh the hitbox is gonna be a pain in the
ass here i think
there we go
not like i don't already have these
pokemon
this one i feel like actually didn't get
the small one before
stop
i'm gonna get you the little one
i won't let me have i
see unobtained damn it
okay okay okay okay
wait i can't move right now because i'm
being attacked
i am gekko
i'm getting cool
uh
[Music]
while we're talking about uh kissing the
eye i guess that makes sense to segue
into another topic but
um
the day
where
everything
fell apart
uh
it was not a good day
let me tell you
how my day went
on that day
i
didn't get much sleep first of all
because i had to go to physical therapy
pretty early
um
so
i um
like
i woke up
after barely getting some sleep
it was the last day of my physical
therapy the last day
and i woke up like um
as skinny guinea last minute as possible
to get to my therapy because i just
wanted to get as much sleep as possible
and
i
[Music]
every time i wake up i just take a quick
look at my a quick glance at my phone
but i wouldn't have had much time
because i needed to go get an uber as
quickly as possible to get to my therapy
but i wake up like really really sleepy
really
feeling already not so good i look at my
phone and i see
these
hints that something happened
and i'm like what
and i go on twitter and i'm like what
what what what the [\h__\h] what what
i was like
i literally just woke up and i was like
so confused and i was like what the [\h__\h]
is happening what no
what [\h__\h] what what
i was starting to
panic i i didn't i didn't know i was
like
i was like [\h__\h] i need to go to physical
therapy what the [\h__\h] what what what
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] like
literally i i couldn't i couldn't
comprehend it i couldn't process it i
had no time to process it but i was like
i was i was really trying to like
i was like what what what
like really holy [\h__\h] but then i had to
i had to quickly go to therapy so i
grabbed my stuff and i i jumped into an
uber and then i arrived at the at the
therapy building and and i'm like still
the whole time the uber drive i'm like
always just like what the [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] like i couldn't realize
what's going on
and then i
[Music]
i went in and this lady at the reception
she tells me oh the
today's your last day but the usual
therapist that you had
it's not here today so you're going to a
different lady and i was like oh okay
but with this lady that i had all this
time i already kind of like built some
trust you know
um
because yeah we were like
getting along well and then she was nice
and all that and especially on that day
i was like so stressed out in that
moment and and confused and and low-key
like about to have a panic attack and
and i just i think i needed someone
familiar but then i go to this new lady
and she was like that kind of
lady that kind of like a mom-type lady
um
talks in a little bit of an aggressive
way but nicely you know what i mean
um
very very direct and like
let's do this type of person and i walk
in and i'm trying to
um
you know not she doesn't know me i don't
want to like tell her what is going on
at all i just want to get this [\h__\h]
physical therapy behind me because it
would just be um
uh what 30 minutes anyway i was like i'm
just gonna get this [\h__\h] over with and
then go back home and then try to
process the situation
um and and i i go in and she's like yeah
yeah you are this person right i'm like
yep um today is my last day and she
asked me what i've been doing with the
other lady until now
and i tell him we've been doing these
exercises but the last few times she's
just been kind of massaging some some
points on my neck and my
shoulders um
so that's what we've been doing and then
she starts
then it starts this is where it falls
apart
oh she
she walks up to me like she's super nice
and all but the in this moment it was
really really critical she walks up to
me and she says
darling you're standing completely wrong
to begin with your poster is horrible
you need to like and she starts touching
my my my body like trying to fix my
the way i'm standing and she's like you
need to do this and you need to do that
now you can't be like that and that's
when i start crying
that's when i
absolutely lose it
and i'm like i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry i can't just really really
[\h__\h] stress i'm so sorry
[Laughter]
i [\h__\h] lost it i just i i broke out
in tears and then she suddenly she
suddenly saw that she's like oh oh dear
oh dear what's wrong oh oh it's okay
it's okay it's okay it's your last time
right let's let's just just lay down
here just lay down on the massage table
it's all good we're not going to do any
exercises okay okay thank you like she
also asked me like what's going on when
i was like i can't really say it's
something at work
i'm just i just didn't have time to
process it yes it's like hap it happened
like less than an hour ago and
i was like okay okay calm down calm down
just calm down lay down there
and then she gave me 30 minutes full
like not a physical therapy massage but
like a legit relaxing massage um i think
she just really wanted me to
just i'm so glad she understood instead
of like forcing this on me she just
realized that this i really need
to chill right now
so she gave me a really nice massage and
i calmed down while i was
sniffing on the massage table and at the
end she also put like some
cooling crazy cooling cream on my on my
body that felt like really really chill
that was supposed to help
um
the pain i guess but yeah she gave me a
proper nice massage and that was
that was the
my last physical therapy session i could
not say goodbye to the lady that i had
until then
but it really helped i really needed
that
um
like
i mean it would have been even better if
i could have just stayed at home
and just process it
at home but this was the best way to
process it
um
in the in the situation i was yeah she
was so understanding like i don't even i
don't even blame her she was just the
kind of person who
um
it's like um like she has this mom aura
about her but like in a in a more like
demanding way
the moment she came up to me and and was
like kind of criticizing the way i was
standing
i just couldn't handle it in that moment
so then i went home and um
i i
i was
trying to
um
find someone to talk to but only genma
was around so i talked a bit with genma
to process it and then
and then i just because i had a real
huge lack of sleep i i took a long nap
after that
and then i woke up and it literally felt
like it was all a dream
i thought
it was it didn't happen it nothing
nothing that happened on that day
happened
nothing but no it did
it did though but yeah so that was that
was that day
i just had a
really really terrible
um stride of the day
um but i i am okay now i processed it
and i mean it's still a very sad thing
that um
[Music]
uh lucia
uh
no she has contract has been terminated
um
it's
yeah
uh
the the name is not ng you can talk
about it but yeah there's not much i can
say um
the
the way it was announced is the way it
is
and i didn't talk about it in
the eldering stream because i thought it
was not fitting
and i didn't really
say much on twitter even i just said i
love the third gen because i do love the
third gen and um
um
you guys maybe know that i always was
not only a fan of piccolo i was a fan of
the virgin
um
like as a whole
and
i i understand
the decision and i respect it
but as a fan of course it hurts so i i
get you guys
but i have been able to process it and
yeah
let's
wish her the best
and
do our best to move on
hmm
yeah
yeah i only had a collab with her once
but you know i wanted to do holo talk
with her eventually soon because i just
started with the virgin
that's uh that's that
um
even though i only really had one proper
collab with her i
i mean i watched her streams every now
and then and
it's a
it was a bad day a really bad day
[Music]
but yeah um
that's all really i can say
i wish her all the best i hope that she
finds
her path
a new path
damn
yeah
[Music]
oh
i'm sorry golden
yeah sorry i'm not i it's it's tough for
me to say something about this topic
because
it's uh i can't i it's difficult you
know um
please understand
moving on moving on
here you are again
have you collected all the plates
of course kiawah is a famed member of
the cervicorps after all
thanks guys thank you
so what more can you tell us we're so
close now you must now more
you must know more about the plates
if there is yet more you want to know
kindly bring me wood
free logs will do
what
she wants to make a fire and burn some
marshmallows
saying wood is somehow tied to the
plates no she probably just wants to
make food but you see bottom right
bottom right girl you got some wood
right there it's even chopped up and all
that
yeah she probably just wants to cook
something
well it shames me to admit as merchant
that i am i'm quite out of wood of
course you are of course you are out of
wood
do i have any wood i mean can i pick
this up and give it to you directly this
is ridiculous she has wood here
sending me on the ghost chest do i have
what
i've i've also barely collected wood
because it's just for those stupid dolls
and
yeah
they don't even sell for much
of course i have no wood
[Music]
can you buy it uh in some shop
oh anonymous thank you
love love love thank you for the red
super chat
yeah yeah i say yes mommy okay yes mommy
um
yeah what is annoying to get i don't
know does one of these people sell it
maybe no
no
the only probably the only item that's
not being sold
ah otherwise you're right they're
calling it a trail
by the way recipes
[Music]
um
pancakes on pink
wenger jackson
your birthday on the 25th
the 25th when was that ah when i played
ellen ring happy birthday be later but
still
congratulations i'll sing you a happy
birthday in the super chat reading
[Music]
congratulations
happy birthday oh i can't hold back i'm
singing happy birthday to you happy
birthday happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday oh look at her
dancing
[Music]
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday happy birthday
it's my little dance for you
oh where am i a [\h__\h] wood man where
which map has the most wood
oh man
magical
[\h__\h]
kinda look at every tree here
very closely
there's a lot of trees here
oh man
really
[\h__\h] wood
she said free
thank you for the pinky tanaka
oh thank you
thank you
yeah i've heard that there are
um
like i i kind of went too quickly to
directly to the boss apparently i don't
know that felt like a logical path for
me to take at the moment but
apparently there are some like more
beginner friendly areas
that i should have
visited first but
for me it seemed like i needed to go
there and i was expected to i don't know
somehow be strong enough for that mob
there
apparently not so that makes me feel
better
that makes me feel a bit better i can't
speak english what
one more one more one more
yeah so the problem with open world i
guess that's like how some people
in breath of the wild just go directly
to um
the castle
although even i wouldn't do that that
seems ridiculous
who
who does that by accident i don't think
anyone would do that by accident i think
i guess actually breath of the wild
there's a better way of telling you
to maybe not go there immediately
only if you're like you know doing a
challenge or so um but you i don't think
you would unintentionally do that right
in breath of the wild
uh you would have to be kind of drunk or
whatever
yeah
around level 24
oh and you probably also have some
experience with the game i suppose of
souls games
guys it's okay i i was hi monkey
let me see 10 okay i was feeling
like i
just was really bad at the game which i
am too
um but i guess it's not only that
so
hallelujah
was not not only me being bad at the
game
the last piece of wood doko
doko
higa hoshi
maybe there
is a cliff
it is well for a first time souls player
thank you
i rewatched a little bit of my gameplay
and i have to say
yeah
pretty bad although it did get a little
bit better there were some good moments
but it looks it looks easier than it is
like for real
it's not as easy as it looks
yeah
i will defend myself
for that
ah there's no wood here do these trees
in general produce no wood i wonder
now this horrible weather
great
maybe
if i go that way
it's not
[Music]
i realized japanese people call these
games not souls games but from games
interesting huh
i was saying souls games in japanese as
well but people refer to them as
from games
confusing [\h__\h]
yeah
random little info
uh
the [\h__\h] there are no trees and where
there are trees but there are no wood
trees are these all made out of plastic
or what
huh
oh man
[Music]
so the plan is for me
um i kind of have to plan it very far
ahead if i want to play elden ring
so i'm thinking maybe
for next sunday
maybe we also have whole talk
next saturday
uh
which i will announce in my schedule
who it will be
um
[Music]
yes yes
oh but yeah so i'm thinking maybe give
alden ring another turn on sunday
just because
why the hell not
and then after that it might not happen
much more often what the [\h__\h] why is
there no wood
maybe over there
yeah but i'm thankful that i can play it
at all to begin with it's okay got to
plan ahead
we have to plan ahead with a lot of
things so i'm used to it it's okay
i'm actually
surprised i ended up being the only one
in hollow life
besides no i didn't
but definitely the only one in whole
life english who ended up playing eldon
ring on release day huh
hey
i didn't think it would be me i fought
everyone to jump on it
like everyone was so hyped for it yo
it is surprising yeah
i'm going to go inside let's check here
there's a lot of uh
honey here too i think
i don't want the honey i want the
wood
hallelujah
yeah kelly wants to play elder ring too
i think but she started on her own i
think
and uh
she said she's gonna play bloodborne
right
she said so didn't she
yeah
i'm so happy she can play games now that
she always wanted to play
like since the beginning
um
[Music]
oh cat hairs
oh
[Music]
um there was like a bunch of cat hairs
on the lid of the bottle that i just
sipped from
and part of it entered my mouth we could
do we could but that's oh god
you gross they say you guys are not cat
owners are you
oh dear
it's not that bad
calm down
[Music]
yeah i was saying
really happy for her to be able to play
those games that she always wanted and
and i wrote to her yo
thanks for helping
she was trying
so hard to help giving advice and so on
but she's gonna look so cool probably
playing those games
i'm excited to see her play
because she's probably gonna do
a million times better of a job than i
did
[Music]
supportive
yeah i appreciate it
you could play co-op oh ah
i think she is plotting that with
someone else
that's okay it's not my kind of game
i don't want to i would just drag her
um
uh
behind
drag
i would just be uh
a drag
if there's yet more you want to know
kindly bring me wood
there you go
[Music]
drag her down burden her yeah
oh
yes this certainly ought to do
now the moment comes in last the big
reveal and this is so stupid she's
making food secret your expectations
need tempering i fear this wood is
merely for fashioning myself new cutting
boards
really he's not even cooking with it
i thought you needed to make a fire out
of it
the place where after our dinner place
so this is hard
oh stupid pun
[Music]
how you complain for one shirking his
own work this very moment what
what does this sentence mean poor guinta
of the ginkgo guild must have his hands
full with you
but honest work earns honest pay here
you are kiawah a reward for the wood
you've brought me i'm getting something
for that
a pixie oh a fairy play we haven't had
that one yet
damn he's shook i'll play the hero beat
wait a second
[Music]
i'm dizzy
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm [\h__\h] dizzy
no get that you're a beat out of your
head that's right
apologies
that's indeed one of the plates that
we've been searching for
what do you mean a plate let me see that
again
oh
this does rather look like one of the
plates you've been tracking down
while the engravings upon it made it
less than accommodating as a cutting
board she was using it as a cutting
board
whatever ingredients crossed it
certainly gained a more pleasant flavor
perhaps that was the board's power the
plate's power rather
well no more and he's saying what do you
two intend to do now
i fell in the cliff and died oh my that
was calculated all according to kaikaku
well we've managed to collect quite a
lot of plates by now but i still don't
know what where to do with them exactly
it's just a hunch but perhaps we should
have a look around celestica ruins
seems like he knows something i'm gonna
start snacking now
i have chosen the salty snack not the
sweet snack today
but also need to drink more water
the salty snack aka
pom-pom
yes my beloved
um
i didn't eat the burnt kiyosa
i ended up making frozen pizza
i see a fine pretext to continue
shirking your mercentile duties to crawl
about in old ruins as you so enjoy on
with you then
i don't need you telling me i'm going
to the celestica ruins kiawah i'll see
you there
yeah
man those skills i miss them too
go on now to the celestica ruins i'm
curious myself what you will find there
what can we who live now learn from the
remains of our ancient myths and legends
holo english legends coming soon
to your tvs
hell yeah
i ate those foods
how did you end up burning what happened
to have them get burned um
do i have to explain
a simple
chemical reaction to you or physical
reaction
when you put something
on a hot plate
and you turn it up
and then you wait a little bit too long
if
if you're stupid it you might end up
burning it
if things to get if things get too hot
then sometimes the food becomes black i
know it's crazy
[Laughter]
i know it's mind-blowing
it's science
stupid questions deserve stupid answers
is what uh the grown-ups used to tell me
yeah i had to
uh had to the heat up too high and i was
i was preoccupied with something i think
but it happens also fast it all happened
so fast man
all right wait is this the battle
already guys
just tell me that or is there still
something happening before that
soon
all my tangents today we would have
already been there ages ago
[Music]
okay
okay so should i change anything else in
my team
[Music]
i can still give them some levels
um
how does this one attack what do we want
to improve
change cycle cut
[Music]
my whole team has to be 70 plus
to start the battle or just because of
safety
[Music]
you beat it at this level okay
well leveling might be kind of tough
um
good night i had some yeah only a few
exp candies
maybe i can buy some
i mean what else am i gonna use that
money for
that those those points
just do this dude
wait is it with money or what some
points with money okay
i'll buy some
yeah that's expensive oh [\h__\h]
wait doesn't she also sell some dough
[Music]
no not trading
uh
yeah she does
one thousand
i you know it's 42.
is there anything i didn't report yet
no
okay
so two of those make some stars i
alright okay
you'll have some stuff for them i
already created a lot
and sold them yo those are really good
like hot sandwiches
those sell so nicely
wait not worth too late
too late now
ah this one i can sell
i can huh wait i can barely make
anything i think
let me see
uh this one i can sell to [\h__\h]
[Music]
i have to have blue plates
am i blind
[Music]
all right i don't even have any blue
blades
i think
i can't make
those things right now
a couple of years of summer granski now
i'm gonna say you did very great for
someone you do soldiers thank you you're
too nice
you are too nice
yeah
oh
oh the store is really looking very uh
upgraded now
they didn't always have so much stuff
out here in the front today
that looks nice
okay i'll be selling these
this
and
thank you
and then
we will
be use this on mostly levels zero arc
there we go there's only one level
one and a half
get this one too that's nothing
f what is the best way to grind in this
game what do you say
we can do a few levels we have time i'm
still very much energetic it's only been
four hours let's make it eight hours
guys are the training grounds good for
grinding
the dojo here
i'm trainers in the dojo okay
let's do that then
uh
oh i guess not here are you the one i
need to ask
oh
who are those people
i'll make it 10 yeah who should i fight
well kamado was pretty tough does he
come with the same pokemon i wonder
let's do it
we got him once we'll do it again but
this time we'll keep more pokemon alive
ain't holding nothing back sure
do i hit your twelve do i hear twelve
make it twelve
although i would like to have some time
at the end to uh
have some dinner before midnight
preferably
we can also read super chat so that's
that uh well we're starting out
wrong again
i feel like last time you also sent out
that pokemon first i should have known
i should have known
[Music]
next week um
might look
a little bit scarce
uh in terms of the amount of strings
maybe
and like maybe more shorter streams
because i have to prepare whole talk but
i also have to use
probably a lot of monday to prepare
um the omo cat thing
um
so
yeah
because i'm i'm the one choosing like
going through all the submissions and
there are hundreds of submissions and i
want to be fair and go for all of them
obviously
um
yeah
i will take a while so
on monday on monday there's also
something else happening aka i'm getting
my kitchen
so monday actually yeah i think i
tomorrow i won't be streaming i think
i'm very busy tomorrow and then on
tuesday very early in the morning for me
[\h__\h]
hey
um
very early in the morning
[Music]
uh i'll be having the omo cat stream is
i think it's 8 a.m for me but i gotta be
awake a little bit earlier obviously
um
doesn't matter
i'm getting a whole kitchen no i'm just
getting a addition to my kitchen that
i've ordered like ages ago but it takes
a long time to actually
make it happen oh you again oh my gosh
still one hits me probably
wait
how's it looking
i want to
[Music]
if i switch to muma she'll just get one
hit or two i want the i will never want
to be alive to get the um experience
points but
let's see if i can
revive a heel boom right now switch to
moment but then zoroark is probably
going to go down
let's see
[Music]
i'm still alive
okay
mama's
yeah i guess i could do that too
let's see how far we get how much how
much exp we get from this
i guess killing alphas might be a bit
faster
getting a pizza oven oh no
i was thinking about that um
because of uh
because of a friend of mine who has a
pizza oven
and yo it just tasted so good that pizza
out of there and it was done so quickly
but you gotta get like a lot of fresh
ingredients all the time and so on and i
don't really
i don't really
want to be that committed so i might
just
no
[Music]
continue eating my frozen pizza
oh my magical magic
so mad oh [\h__\h] i just saw cresselia has
over 300 hp yo
okay i get to do two turns so
oh man
thank you my membership welcome
can i just
no i'll do one more
hopefully i don't need to use
obese
sparks anymore okay we're still alive
that's cool that's all i wanted just to
stay alive
and now
wait i can attack twice okay
i will
what's the most effective here that i
have
[Music]
doesn't illustrious orb make pocky
stronger probably
special rend
aqua tail stab
huh
okay
oh
i'm not welcome here
mummy don't die again please please
please please please
please
please don't die again please don't tell
me
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
i did get the thing from
um
adamant
i i fought him yesterday off off screen
off stream off-screen
uh-oh
oh my god
i want to revive everyone before
um
before the end of the battle
[Music]
oh you [\h__\h]
is it gonna one hit me
does this [\h__\h] have anything super
strong against me that can one hit my
pikachu my raichu
with considering i only have 103 hp left
use crystalia to revive okay i will do
that maybe
maybe yes moon blast oh no
[Music]
i wanna
not die i wanna try that for once
okay okay that would have killed me but
we're still standing
um
go for it
i didn't
do damage to me too no it doesn't right
iron tail wasn't
[Music]
fighting alphas will probably been
easier
does it make sense to revive them now
should i wait for the last pokemon
recycle and ferry is actually not going
to help us at all here but
[Music]
the first page is a lot easier to farm
recovered from elm ring yeah i'm good
i'm all good
[Music]
fight fight fight fight fight fight
fight fight fight fight
yeah
do i have something
[Music]
strong
super effective [\h__\h] even cresselia has
troubles here
okay we have something effective just
want to stay in the battle while
reviving everyone
can we stay alive for a while
please
[Music]
sword stance okay okay okay
um
this is so stupid this is so stupid i
don't want to wonder if it kills me next
it's one of the revival bee sparks
question it was what the question is
what's it gonna do next
you know maybe i hear myself first
so stupid this is so unnecessary
just because i want
those exp
[Music]
okay
[\h__\h] it okay to be sparks you're not
getting the
you're not getting the exp
i'm sorry
lunar blessings
[Music]
foreign
she can't kill me
you can't kill me
[Music]
you're gonna kill yourself before you
kill me
well we have time
so wasting but these normal revives are
okay to waste i would say
okay there we go
i'm getting my exp whether you want it
or not
the trolling they're [\h__\h] trolling me
[Music]
that little [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h]
yeah i'm gonna end it
although i have two turns yo i have two
turns i have two turns
until then
i will risk it there we go
that exp better be worth it
oh no
okay
everyone got one level up
so what is faster everyone getting one
level um versus and fighting alpha
pokemon where
they don't even drop the full one level
candy but
um
maybe this is faster
maybe go with someone who's a little bit
easier than him
alpha blizzy
[Music]
really
okay where was that for [\h__\h]
in the first area right
field lens
but we have to keep on enter re-entering
the map right in order to make it reload
re-reset
um
around the waterfalls yeah i think i
know where i
caught it before
uh
here
i think somewhere here
uh
what's what's the her weakness
what's alpha blissey weakness
over the tunnel
fighting okay
[Music]
[Applause]
hi guys
big snake flying snake
i was so excited when i first found that
gyarados flying around there and i tried
so hard to catch it
and then i did it and i posted it on
twitter and everyone was like okay what
was it no
that's so cool
i felt so cool
isn't that
turn here
oh there it is
let's catch it unaware
boom
[Music]
yeah
your eyes are kind of scary but
everything else around you is really
cute so i'm kind of
confused damn you strong too oh but it
damages you as well
[Music]
let's see how much damage it does
oh good we can
we can kind of one hit them
[Music]
hallelujah
no dying burps this time
mummy stays alive
ah beautiful
i'm afraid of blue beans
whoa
that's a lot of exp
i think
yahoo
ah what
what
that is much faster
but i have to leave the area right
stop it
it's already fart
i'm so far away no way it's still
chasing me
but the i think it goes away so slowly
hello
let me leave please
a rest of the camera ah does that work
too
okay
and we can go to this one
uh oh it goes away quickly when you fly
another hotel so if i rest here i don't
have to leave the map
blizzy
it's a new day
it's a new chance
to be killed by me
isn't it an honor
i should feel so honored
[Applause]
don't forget to save oh
oh yeah yeah
yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
right three times two different times of
the day
i'm telling you it won't be bad
we're supposed to be here rest three
times
one time is not enough
yes
i was thinking about feeling good too
it's a new day
it's a new life
for me
and i'm feeling good
checking again
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
until nine in the morning okay there's a
kind of weird order but maybe it worked
anyway
please please please please please
please please please please please oh it
looks bad
[\h__\h]
damn it
oh god i sleep until morning again
one more time
[Music]
go back to town
we'll try this we'll try this and we'll
see
if this doesn't work then
maybe we'll
[Applause]
maybe then we will
uh go back to town
can you play final fantasy 7 remake i
want to
but no i cannot
maybe one day
it's also something
i've been
hoping for
one day it's not here
don't play the remy play the original i
want to play the remake
[Music]
we're going back to the village also
takes time
loading screen
oh i mean i can play it but i can't
stream it
at the moment oh
that pokemon that evolves into something
that will always kick my butt
could be as shiny there
but
i don't really care about it
gimbal yeah it's kind of cute
i'll try getting it
[Music]
guard jump yeah yeah
wait what am i doing
is it easier to go there from here
um
[Music]
[Applause]
um
not planned on stream today we're doing
this
basically the second ending
i guess
yeah this this path is a pain in the ass
[Applause]
and
there it is
hello
hell now
sorry i'm bothering you but i need you
to give me some levels please
you big chunky egg monster
[Music]
oh that did less damage than last time
inc
okay we're fine we're fine we're fine
we're fine
seed of mastery and grid test
alrighty
and
going back another time
wait how many level ups did we get i
didn't look
[Music]
[Laughter]
i want to go back i want to go back
try to get an infernape at reminisce
island that monster can one hit both oh
i got one
uh before
really can it one hit
really
but then that one gets the exp no no no
no i'm doing this with this team
i'm doing it with this team
um
one and some exp on the right oh
okay
but this one this one will give us
some more level ups again
next month can come quick enough
[Music]
thank you guys for being in the
membership
as always
thank you
last membership stream we wrote a song
tt aren't we camping writing songs
together beautiful
[Music]
[Applause]
did you finish that no i didn't have any
time yo
i'm extremely busy and occupied and so
much [\h__\h] is going on
[Music]
you never knew about the flying gyarados
over there
you can catch it very early if you
if you try your best live your aim
[Music]
it takes a
few tries because it is pretty far away
[Music]
let's take a look
okay
they are um
getting closer and closer
thoughts on sapphire and violet well if
you would have been in the stream
since the beginning
then you would know my thoughts already
but i will once again repeat myself for
the
fifth time today
it's okay people come in later times
it's okay it's understandable
i'm excited
i was surprised
oh
it looks okay so far
um
the starters look amazing
but the character the
character
the style
the art style of the character is throw
me off
of the humans
they don't look like pokemon characters
like this looks fine to me these people
they look like pokemon um designs to me
the art style looks like pokemon art
style
but the humans in and then this one and
then scarlet violet they don't look like
pokemon humans to me
yeah so that's kind of weird
but
i doubt that they will change that um
but maybe maybe we'll get at least
maybe in the one year that they have
about a year maybe they'll improve the
graphics but
but i doubt that they'll change the
design of the human soon
that is most likely not happening
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] out
good job
oh it's um
cloudy huh
oh
there go your knees
this one
[Music]
does not miss
but also doesn't do much damage
oh
[Music]
maybe this one
there we go
[Music]
three level ups
and speak candy
very good
hold up there's a new gen after a moment
i was like yeah
where whole life
oh you mean
you mean pokemon yes
[Music]
yeah we're farming exp right now maybe
um
maybe five more times or so
they said my pokemon should be level 70.
i do have a few candies though
[Music]
oh you need it desperately
okay so uh so fetch and uh
sophist and palkia are very close
mummy is getting there kristelia is
already 71.
zoroark needs to catch up
[Music]
i was saying 75 no nobody ain't nobody
got time for that
ain't nobody you're dead for that worst
case we're just gonna do our uh max
revive strategy
revive until
the pp runs out for the opponent pokemon
best strategy there is
yeah i'm gonna buy more max revives uh
maybe up to i don't know 20
or 30 i don't know
how many did you guys
use
or buy before going into that fight
50.
last time
i think we bought a little bit too much
but better to be safe than sorry i don't
wanna know
look it's uh
cloudy again
but we caught it unaware okay no
no
i guess not
wow
nice
don't kill me what's up boyle oh that's
such a cute attack but
really unnecessary now
why
you do this to me
yokoso
[Music]
um
that was nice
there's an outbreak there but not really
one i care about
unless no
mermaid too powerful sometimes yeah
does a good job sometimes
it's coming along
and another one
wow so many outbreaks yo that one is
interesting hmm
oops wrong camp sorry
was there anything else i wanted to talk
about
oh
apparently
it has been oopsies
oh [\h__\h]
apparently it has been approximately
uh one year
since i
um
left japan
and
came back to austria
did you guys realize that
[Applause]
makes me miss japan a little bit
but i had a one year visa and
extending it was not really an option
for several reasons first of all
my cats and second of all
i couldn't have gotten
[Music]
i would have needed a sponsor and yeah
like a company
company sponsored
visa and it didn't really seem like a
possibility at the time at least not a
long-term one i feel like maybe like a
short-term
yes but long-term visa yeah
and to be honest i was thinking about it
back then to
extend it maybe for like
um
maybe for a month or two or so
[Music]
um
for certain reasons but
more and more after time passed it
looked like
it would make no sense
um to drag it out anymore and i i think
like i barely remember how i felt back
then but i didn't i didn't feel very
good did i i think you guys remember
my
mental state
was
not the best maybe you can get one now
um
now is a little bit difficult if it
weren't for
the c thing perhaps
yeah that's
what hopefully would happen
getting a
business visa or something whenever cool
the saving is gone
yeah cat fair a bit
yeah the thing is just that like i was
extra
lonely because i felt
surprisingly
um
homesick because of my cats like
originally when i was in japan for that
one year
i i was planning on
visiting them
oh
hey
i was planning on visiting them
uh like four times in one year that was
my plan
but i i arrived in japan
at a moment where
the sea thing was already known but in
japan
no one cared yet
oops
so
like there in japan when i arrived they
were already like kind of talking of
actually no barely talking about it
they were
not really thinking
that it would come to japan at that
point
yeah
it was before they closed the border
yeah really really kitty kitty i was
actually quite lucky i guess
if i would have gone like one month
later i wouldn't have been able to enter
probably one month i'm not sure when
exactly they closed the borders but
yeah
oh yeah
yeah i think every every country was
like oh it won't come over here and
we'll be fine and then
bamboozle surprise
knock knock it's the sea thing
we would like to [\h__\h] up your life for
the next two three years
you must
[Music]
yeah
so in some way i had good timing when
someone had bad timing
i came right before the border would
close but by me being there right when
it closed i had like nothing to do
and i also couldn't go back because i
could not put my visa on hold
my type of visa
was like a working holiday visa for one
year and you those are
once-in-a-lifetime visas
uh with a special application process
and once you start it it runs out if you
leave like you can leave for a month but
that will not give you an extra month in
japan
yeah
so
um and and if i would have left to see
my cats i would have
had a high chance of not being able to
get back in actually not a high transit
100 chance
because even depending on the on the
time i guess but even people with like a
um
more proper reason than i had like
foreigners but with uh with japanese uh
um
aju uh
what's it called again the the
uh
where
when you have a long term no long term
but what's it called again age you aid
you
in english
yeah permanent residency i guess
even those i think had troubles getting
back into japan
for a certain amount of time
did you not like it in japan
that is not the point i've been to japan
many many a million times
i've lived in japan besides that one
year before as well
way before
when i was much younger
i lived in japan for two years and then
until one year ago i lived in japan
again for one year
so that's like a total
land please
a total of
three years approximately
what what
and
after living there for a while i
i wouldn't mind going there again
uh if it was like super easy to bring
your cats to another country without
them being in pain or whatever you know
what i would probably wouldn't mind
moving there again for a year or
whatever
um
but i don't want my cats to be um
in pain i don't want to risk anything
and i don't want to leave them alone
here again
um but i'm i'm happy
in austria
and
well i think i'll be fine just visiting
japan for the next
couple of years
when i have the opportunity
i'm just gonna visit
like i don't know maybe a month at a
time or three weeks or two weeks or
something like that depending on what
there is to do
yeah i still like japan and i miss i
miss it too
i miss it too there are so many fun
things to do there
and so many fun people to meet
yeah but at the moment it's not only
because of my cats i have my friends
here in austria
and i have my family here and just other
things are much easier like
it's it's difficult to find
an
apartment in japan um
for several reasons
um
yeah
and even if you find one and it's
probably super tiny and has really thin
walls it's not meant to be a
room where you stream in
so you gotta get one of those soundproof
ones but those are really really rare
and really expensive and a lot of them
don't even let foreigners live there so
it's like really tough there's like so
many um
hurdles that you have to overcome
i
uh the last place that i lived in i kind
of got through
some
contacts
so i was lucky with that
living in that one house that was slowly
falling apart
and infested with
mice or rats we will never know
oh
yeah thankfully you had my own place but
before that when i when i started out
with hello live
i was still living in like a really
cheap
um apartment
[Music]
and that was really small i liked it
because it was cozy
um
but
i could hear everything like even
footsteps and
yeah anything even whispers from next
doors
and they could definitely hear me so
starting out streaming while living
there
was tough i don't even know how i did it
man i
i tried to stream during the day i think
in the very beginning so that i wouldn't
bother anyone
night time streaming definitely not
possible shiny italy
that is actually something we should get
sheesh
um am i already too late if i save now
i'm not too late right
because you're safe once you get there
you just have to save now right and turn
off autosave
oh my god
don't fast travel
oh oh don't fast travel
don't fast travel not even to a
different camp
okay
turn off
oops turn off other autosave
[Music]
and
save we're gonna get that
shiny evoly and then we're gonna turn it
into some kind of shiny evolution
eeveelution is there a chance that you
can get two chinese
i guess there is a slight a tiny tiny
chance that there could be two shinies
in one thingy fast travel is okay
okay
but you scare me now
i saved right i saved right
good okay we need to go here
i'll fly because i'm scared
i'm gonna take a good look at all the
evolution shiny versions
and decide which one is the prettiest
and that was that's the one i'm gonna
get
[Applause]
shiny i'm coming
i'm not gonna
have this chance this opportunity taken
away from me
let's see
okay
uh
i guess let's catch him
maybe shy
[Music]
here we
go hello
they're so cute and so fluffy
where are my shinies huh
oh he's so cute stop running
hello
[Applause]
[Music]
remember when i was like looking for one
so desperately i came back
so often
i think this one won't have a shining
this run
what do they look like anyway this shiny
eevees i know it will make like a
sparkle
so i can see it by that i guess
they're white oh
wow like
a alola
vulpix
as if it's like a snow version
of itself
okay i think nothing does it no more
respawning not one respond over there
oh and another one there okay i'm
running out of balls
but we're
okay
we are
resetting anyway
and now i think now we're done uh
close and go back
right
uh close and then go back to the village
and then come back here
if i remember correctly oh no my game
crashed
oopsie doopsie
oh the update is available
but i'm scared that that will mess with
my thing right now
so no thank you
not now
oops oops crash y'all me
oh man this game is so unstable
[Music]
anyway back to the topic by the way i
guess
i'm happy that
um
i'm happy with how things are right now
mostly and uh
yeah i'm happy with my apartment happy
living here so
it downloaded update data anyway [\h__\h]
and yeah i'm um i'm i'm satisfied
should i go back to the village even
though
they're here
yeah i'm supposed to go back right
yeah
okay
what would you need to be happier
uh
no see thing
and be able to travel to japan
immediately
that would make me happier
and a pool a pool would be nice and the
beach would be nice
don't leave the area what
we did like this before
uh
an oreo shake
yeah oreo shake always helps
[Music]
yeah but all those things are kind of
difficult to especially accept the oreo
shake
so
yeah it's okay
i'm
happy with how things are
so good
and um
i think
it really helped me to come
to austria
yeah
it's just when you're in your own
country
things just feel so much more familiar
and that makes you feel more safe and
secure am i going the right way
oh no i'm not
yeah
just have an environment uh that you
feel familiar with and also like
the laws and [\h__\h] i don't know
and anything really anything that has to
do with living
somewhere
why would i save before
there's no
shiny
why do i save
why would i stay here
we already saved before
anyway let's get that shiny
whoa
give me that shiny evie why do you
refuse to be mine
[\h__\h] that is so
heavy
oh wrong ball not a holder
yo
why did that just bonk off your head why
also
stubborn
nah
i don't want any of those
oh no one's sleeping that one's cute the
sleeping one is good and stop sleeping
so now it's not cute anymore
they think they can
act up like this
and we'll forgive them just because
they're cute
we'll look at their eyes and we'll be
like i forgive anything
nobody is staying in my balls
stop running around in those shits
stop it at once
did i just hear shiny no that wasn't my
imagination right
that was just my imagination
oh yeah we're sleeping
aren't you sleeping baby i don't have
any good balls
[Music]
you guys are so far away
is that it no more spawn
okay
i think no more no more spawn oops
[Music]
i don't know how to i don't know how to
use a switch anymore
oh no my game crashed again
oh
so unfortunate
oh no
oh i need to i don't know buy a new
switch or something
that's their way of making me buy a new
switch i'm telling ya
you're just trying to make money off of
me
i don't know how it keeps on happening
maybe maybe someone hacked into my
switch
maybe i have a virus or something can
you have a virus on a switch
i wonder
[Music]
ah now i have to go back
i have to go back
i caught that
[Music]
technically possible in practice no
we'd have to homebrew now hold on
but when there's nothing you close the
game again right
and then you open it again
why is it why is it that sometimes it's
gone and sometimes it stays
hmm
oh
[Music]
turkey time
return to a village
guess what kiara what
what
i want to eat chocolate now
please is it over is my chance gone my
chance is gone
it feels like they're not coming back
anymore
the [\h__\h] update what the update that
literally just came
but when i came back once and the
outbreak was still there
but then yeah that was it updated while
the i first came back into the game
right
oh come on
so
what else can i do
[Music]
just re reload like this does this
change anything even though i'm already
in the field here
does
[Music]
foreign
they were watching my stream and they
were like no kiwa you already got one
shiny today
we don't allow you to get any more
they were like sitting in the game freak
offices and they were like
this chick
we can't have her too many
let her have too many shinies
it's not fair
she doesn't deserve it
but don't i have a chance if if i like
catch them now and they respond
like after catching one by one oh is
that already calculated i wonder
is the respawn already calculated at
this point
look look what a good baby sits there
is me when i look at my cats oh you're
saying you're so cute while you're
sitting
oh you have higher chances though for
shiny if you have level 10
um
a pokedex entry by the way which i do so
i have higher chances for this one
it's already calculated
shiny evie would have been so cool i
should have disconnected my internet on
the switch before i did that man i
should have disconnected completely
[Music]
[Applause]
i want the shiny last me let me have a
miracle come on
a
miracle maybe i need a miracle
that stop running my little [\h__\h]
they're looking at me they want to be
shiny but they just are not shiny you're
not good enough you're not good enough
you're not good enough you're not good
enough y'all are not good enough
[Music]
this one is just completely like
bye-bye i'm out of here
i don't belong to the outbreak i'm
cooler than that
stop it
that's it
that's it guys
[Music]
yeah that came out of nowhere
you sound like my mom maybe because
i am your mom
ever thought about that
did you ever think about that
huh
it's okay i'm just restarting because i
want my balls back because if there's no
shot in here then i at least want to
have my balls back
we're gonna
level a little bit more
akira okay
he said
xbox
chihuahua we don't even have an xbox we
can't
afford a [\h__\h] xbox kiwa
give up already
you noticed me don't tell the other one
i don't know if i ever caught one before
nice roll
ah really okay
already had one
well well well
sorry guys you will have to bear with me
a little
little
longer
i'm not crying no crying
you are crying the sky is crying
[Music]
i got two shiny ears go back to town
but no it doesn't work anymore
it doesn't work anymore
stop trying to get my hopes up
i'll
i think there are other ways to do it
too
um yeah i'll just find another outbreak
off stream and i'll get my shinies
no matter what it takes
wrong camp damn it
can you can i give you a free shiny no
it's okay it's okay
i'm not that um
crazy about it anyway it's okay
oh my god frank
oh you're going here eh what is she
doing here
what is she doing here
her name was mai i think
yeah i mean bear with me as in bear
bear with my uh
level grinding [\h__\h] for a little while
longer please
new update oh that's from the new update
i'll keep that in mind
oops here i stand with my ninja clan
danger clan
here i stand
yeah
bubble bubble the bum
believe it
[Music]
trying to
get me again
run away run
[Music]
baby
oh
[Music]
no i have not done the final boss yet
we're getting there
what does that mean does it have any
meaning in any other language
before i start making fun of it
i better ask
[Music]
it's made up okay
it sounds
get me some of those max revives by the
way wow that's so expensive
yo
very much expensive a few wait which one
was it max potion can be used to
completely restore the max hp of a
single pokemon can be used to fully
restore the max speed of the center and
cure any status conditions natural hotel
and the full heal
does not
heal
the hp right that's what i got wrong
before
otherwise it wouldn't be that cheap that
makes sense
but why is it called full heal
that is so
misleading is so misleading
unbelievable
mommy goes bye bye
yeah
that looks like a salad like a cabbage
to me
anyway
anything that we could sell no
full heal yeah for the foods like me who
think that that heals me fully but it
doesn't
more like speed candies yeah i have a
few ones maybe we should use them
we are at oh wait moments level 71. wait
everyone accept ob sparks and zoroark is
uh over 70. okay we just need a little
bit
um
take those okay okay okay okay we can
also use those
grit dust chrysalia oops
you get this one
and this one
another speed
and that's it for you anyway
grit pebble
for so fetch
wow special attack so high i hope she's
actually a special attacker because
otherwise that was uh
meaningless that i got it so high
oh it's over
how is this one attack
what do we need for zero arc
yeah one more blizzard maybe one or two
she is okay what about this one
this one also special
okay
maybe maybe some hp too
trust me you'll need it
[Music]
crystalia also special attack
oh yeah
yeah
okay
all right what was that again
ah
no no no
okay
we are
becoming very very strong but i feel
like we're still gonna have problems i
i know that the battle is gonna be
really tough and apparently even tougher
than what was her name again
she didn't impress me at all that's why
i already forgot her name
cynthia apparently even stronger than
cynthia
but sophia left absolutely no impression
with me
that's why i forgot the name she was so
weak
i don't even i don't even know what
color
her hair was i recall
yes
no
who is she
who
excuse me sinful
sinful
never heard about a person like that no
no no no no
least memorable pers memorable person
i've ever seen
in my life
take that cynthia
take that
can you stop always recording my
findings
what
it was so traumatic that i wiped her
from my mouth no no no no no no that's
not it don't try to
don't try to
make her sound
make her
make her look like she was memorable on
my stream no no no no we don't want to
make her
feel
too cocky you know she got stuck up
she'll be like ah
i ruined that kid's life
i am something
to remember
no no no no she'll continue ruining
children's lives out there
giving them a hard time
beautiful you a little big
egg
lady
let's go
let's fight again
one last time
i need to be
the one who takes you
on last time i promise after that i'll
let you go
hey i don't care if you hurt
going
down and the winner is mummy
[Music]
and i want a chance of meeting luma in
real life
i want to see if she's also so crazy in
i want to see
all right are they level uh
level 70 no
ah
one more maybe one more one more one
more 69 both of them
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on come on come on
one day i'll get the chance here
i believe you just gotta believe in it
and then surely it will happen
i mean i don't i don't mind traveling
i actually looked up like
if it is even possible to travel to
america or wherever right now
looks fine it's just like kind of
confusing because like there is this
website that says like almost about
every country also about austria
that it's uh too dangerous to to
ravel that was like two weeks ago
too dangerous because of corona but
the sea thing but it's uh
i feel like that's
even if it says that it's
still totally
easy to travel there
i no i didn't say that i was talking
about coronet senpais
[Music]
senpai
youtube
please believe me
believe me
oh yeah there's a there's a alcoholic
drink as well right that has that name
and i wonder if that's like selling
worse or better now
because of the whole situation
is it a beer
ah
yo am i getting the levels i want
no but i got one
candy
yeah but i think we got a
it's overall arc just you just need one
level maybe we can go to another
another uh
i know which one
i'm gonna go to
the monkey
we're gonna go to the monkey
[Applause]
did you take a hit first um
yeah i think i heard about that but by
now
who the hell case
monkey monkey
monkey
i'm coming for you
man flying is so nice you guys have no
idea
you guys use planes and [\h__\h]
i don't use a plane
i become boob
and i i spread my wings and i just
swoosh
it's a lot of fun you know
a lot of fun
but only cool people like me can do it
sorry about that
i'm not trying to discriminate you guys
it's just the way it is
reject plane become good
um
gosh you're so
such a freak
funky is freak
okay
you're
[Music]
i will destroy you
that's not fair
ayo
yo
how the [\h__\h] did you one hit my pal
it's a [\h__\h] legendary and you're like
six levels underneath it it makes no
sense
max no sense well okay uw
you were a little [\h__\h] and now pocky i
didn't even get those exp so you know
what you get a candy you got a candy in
exchange
didn't even need to revive you because
we're going back anyway but
you know
oh no not the accident what's your
problem with my accent what's your
problem with my accent huh
i see what we're gonna do
or
have i been doing this wrong all along
what what should i give to this boy
uh
what's more important
you want right
you got a license
i don't need a license i am the license
special attack for this one too really
spade
spade and special attack all right
yeah
thank you
thanks mate
so kind
lovely
can't use any of these should i just
sell them yeah
okay
i go
to
kill
um our enemy that we don't even know is
an enemy yet
but i somehow know because i have been
spoilered
no i know nothing i know nothing
wait
uh
what did you guys say was the item that
makes palkia stronger do i have it
i should give it
to the pakia before i'll go
enemy
let's choose orb
uh
do we not have that
dr erida
in the snow place
is that a whole like quest or so or do
we get it like immediately
[Music]
i have to fight her okay
okay
let's go
she's weak as hell unless she's secretly
trained
behind the scenes
was this a snow place
no this was the snow place
all right
she can't she can't be stronger than
ottoman
adamant had three evolutions
this will be
a piece of cake
this one
the pearls settlement
um
[Music]
oh wait am i blind
yeah pearl salmon
[Music]
a girl
oh there she is
girl
i can't believe that you're feeling too
hot at the volcano area
but wearing these clothes you feel just
fine here i don't get you girls you
girls are so weird hello
i was just about to go find you and tell
you about these super amazing skin color
tights i am wearing yeah you were just
talking about aquarius not feeling cold
here but you know actually these are
really thick and there's like a like
kind of like a um a fluffy fabric on the
inside that you just don't see you think
i'm i'm barefoot actually i'm not no no
no no i'm wearing some really thick
tights yeah it's genius i'll tell you
where i got them maybe maybe you'll want
to make use of them too
okay i'm curious about those tights
as you should be yeah it's uh you know a
necessary item for girls like us
it's freezing out there and we gotta
adjust to the temperatures but still
look cute right
understandable have a nice day
all right then um
i'll give you a taste of it um you want
to try on the tights that i i'm wearing
maybe
and maybe let's just see if the size
fits
okay
good idea
[Music]
oh beautiful hey
my partners and i are going to get
strong and travel across this wide world
[Music]
let's fight
wow
once again huh no foreign
[Music]
oh my god that hurts
free little cats are ganging up on me it
feels good because they have fluffy and
i wanna fluff them i wanna touch them
and give them treats you know me mew mew
mew me meow meow meow meow meow
they are cute
with their goggly eyes
they smash me in my head with their
fluffy beans pimpy beans i don't care
i enjoy it
it's not my guy
i'm myself
i just love cats
i just love kids
i don't understand anyone who hates cats
you ain't stupid you don't get in
[Music]
wow other things are not cats are the
only thing i want
sorry
i want nakia
are you insane it kind of scare me
loving cats so much kind of creepy you
should maybe i don't know open the cat
cafe or something
and then leave us all alone with your
crazy fronts
but yeah um anyway here's the treasure i
promised you
the lustrous globe
is that a cat toy is round looks bouncy
i think my cats want to play with that
that's why i got it in the first place
right that's what what was what the
purpose was right
[Laughter]
thank you
thanks my cats will appreciate it very
much
it's also it wasn't on purpose that i
had palkia out but i guess it makes
sense because we were fighting for an
item for palkia
and now you get to use it
oh wait doesn't that um change it to its
like other form
oh but does it actually make it stronger
does that make it stronger too
and have we even seen this before
wait why is it confused
why is it confused
damn it looks like a horse
wait i don't know
we've seen the alga
but not pogba
low hp oh that's why oh man
oh okay
well now that we also did that we're
even stronger i think hopefully
foreign
you'll find that party if you join
ottomans
[Music]
yeah okay
well
then it is time i hope our team is ready
for what's to come let's see
although i'm not sure if it comes
immediately but okay we have i think
enough healing items we have a lot of
max revives
um we have a few full restores
you guys say that's not enough probably
is it
i think it's enough
we'll see
we'll see i'll try to buy a few more
hello
worst case we're gonna cheese it
oh wait i'm in the wrong store
never mind sorry sir for disturbing you
wasting your time
and this this place really changed
what should i buy more off
[Music]
a little bit of everything
you do be expensive though
[Music]
okay
no more no more this has to be good
enough
[Laughter]
you guys are once again underestimating
me
and my powers
[Music]
scatter bangs i mean i've used them like
once or twice for like the tasks in the
pokedex but besides that
uh sacred plaza where is that the
closest to
just gonna go to the mountain camp now
i think you'll be fine really did you
did you play until this point
join the other circle yes okay
we can do that
oopsie
thank you for believing in me
i'm gonna show you my cool side now i
may not have been able to show you that
in elden ring
but now
it's a different story
this is my territory i mean i'm still
still uh i still don't know all the
elementary
effects and [\h__\h]
but i'm better at this game than i am at
eldon ring so
so
i have high hopes
let's go
this is why i got my shiny oh what the
[\h__\h] is that
what are you doing here
i need to catch you
terrifying
frodom
why is it rhodomia
it doesn't
okay whatever i'll get you someday
hello
have a look at this kirawa
what is it
it never broke its statue oh but that
looks like four feet no six feet
this statue has been kept here far from
the statues of the alga and palkia
broken and shattered and yet it remains
do you know what it is
i think so
of course you would you're the greatest
wielder of pokemon this land news the
one who could bring low even tiago and
park here
is hmm
this crumbling statue once was the
figure of a pokemon one that was equal
to both yaga and palkia yet banished
from our world the great pokemon
geratina or gerartina
it was banished for its violence left to
dwell in a world on the reverse side of
our own it is a being that has lane and
weight for the chance to bear its fangs
and defiance and tear down our chaos
itself
now tell me if this geratina desires
more than anything else to challenge
almighty archaea's where do you think it
might appear
a temple
exactly where one is closer to the
heavens than any other place in history
and where that space timer first opened
[Music]
oh okay
i can feel it we're getting closer to
the uncovering the secrets of this world
i dare say the excitement is loosening
my lips more than it should but
you've seen ever since i was young
whenever i met with something painful or
heartbreaking
i couldn't help but wonder why life was
so unfair why i was cursed to live for
such things
of course i imagine we all go through
something like that
eventually i choose to direct my all my
energy into my own natural curiosity and
ambition
and what tickled my curiosity more
strongly than anything were the
mysteries to be found in
legends in history in ruins
you see i fancy that by unraveling these
mysteries i could find out how the world
itself came to be and with that
knowledge maybe even forge a new better
world
now if we can find a realm that exists
on the reverse side of our world and
meet the creators unwanted child
banished therein
perhaps then we'll be able to understand
the nature of almighty sinnoh itself
don't you want to save of your own eyes
we must make for the temple of sinnoh at
mount coronet's peak
diagon palkia both appeared from within
the rift that once escaped open there
didn't they
these plates can call anything at all
it seems likely that is where it would
appear
i thought it was going crazy there
uh but apparently not
[Music]
but he was getting close
goddammit
up there
[Music]
that's
what it looked like totally
ah
fly
that is up so high
i can't go from here
it's just the right way to go
can i go here
yeah no not really
damn it
wait i feel like i went
the complete wrong way
what
oh wait are you supposed to go for the
tunnel
ah suppose so all right this one here
okay okay
that's fine then
yo
enter
no more exploit excuse me
i'm not exploiting anything
the music has always been like this here
it's really nice
oh you guys hear that
i think it's a bit quiet but
i don't remember it being like this here
you recommend saving now nadia
the time has come
i see i see i need to um
take an idle meeting really quickly
brb
we should
[Music]
kia i used
can i use hydro pump excuse me
who says
who says there's any liquid anywhere i
wasn't the model meeting
important business with juggle
you know because jago is an idol himself
yeah
hey
okay let me take a fruit candy because
yeah
volo voicing volo hurts a bit
when y'all calls you gotta answer he's
like nature in that sense
volo
[Music]
isn't this
nice he called me up here because he
wants to have some one-on-one time with
me he's in love with me oh man
so cute ah it's a nice date spot we
could have a picnic up here it's the
highest spot in all of cinnal
i get you i get you this romantic it's
romantic volo very romantic
you have a good sense for that
romance
the temple lies in ruins now columns
cracked and broken like pillars now
turned into spears stabbing into heavens
well
i detect a distinct lack of geratina
hmm
something bothering you you're shiny
you're very shiny
i do beg your pardon uh i put a lot of
highlighter on my face today
i suppose i must seem to be behaving
strangely
i dare say you deserve to do what i'm
really after by now
plot twist
ever since i became convinced that
arceus really does exist there has been
one question that consumed my thoughts
how can i meet such a being myself
it wasn't an attempt to answer this
question that i originally sought out
giratina and had to tear open
that rift in space and time it was him
oh
after all geratina wished to stand
against our kids but that didn't do the
trick
so then i asked you gather the fragments
of the all-encompassing deity just as
the murals of the ruins directed
eighteen blades said to be the fragments
of the all-income encompassing deity
you're holding around 17 of them so you
must be wondering where is the last one
are you have it of course
why it's right here
oh you're a victor did you hear me down
again
[Music]
roll down the windows
and here we go
i'm moving so fast the camera can't even
catch my movements
[Music]
wow
[Laughter]
what a plot twist oh my god oh
hey
he's like from dragon ball
now hand over you'll repeat
don't hang over the plants you got it i
will be the one to bring them all
together
well first of all he looks so weird now
that smile is freaking me out
second of all
man you're such a nice character
why'd you have to ruin that
though
my desire to meet argus cannot be
contained any longer
oh
he's so excited i need to know what it
is he wants to get his autograph from
his idol
i must know what it is
if i can read our case myself then i may
also be able to subjugate its power and
using that i will attempt to create a
new battle
really did we have to go
that path
was there not any other motivation you
could have had
no
it was having to create a new better
world
that is so cliche
ah
that is so
cliche of course if i create a brand new
world then this history region that we
currently exist in will be undone and
returned to nothing
can't you there's so much space in the
space
that's why it's called space
because there's so much space
why does this one have to go can you
just make your stupid extra new world
somewhere in the space that's up there
in the space
huh
sana is being
damn
you everyone you know and all the
pokemon living here will vanish in an
instant as if you'd ever never been
so stupid
if you want to keep this world from
disappearing then face me in battle
okay
[\h__\h] i'm probably starting with the
wrong pokemon i should have asked you
guys what he starts off with
um
that's really bad
now that if you have a choice even if
you don't wish to battle me i'm not
above using force to take those plates
from you
that's all
i don't think he uses big doof
i like his new design
ah
except for his hair so
i like the outfit i'm starting off with
palkia okay
um kind of big
do we have anything good no
[Music]
fairy
switch to cresselia or do we want to
wait
um
only way to
right we're gonna
we gotta go
gotta go brb
start it off with the oh i get to attack
anyone okay starting off with the wrong
foot
um
um yeah i think we can afford i don't
know how strong spiritual is like how
how defensive how much hp
doesn't show us here does it
it doesn't
um
[Music]
i wonder if it's necessary to go strong
he will probably one shot me back
well then we gotta go all in you guys
said fairies is only
weakness we gotta go in
go go
yeah no one shouting me when i one shot
you first
drive one shotting me from grave [\h__\h]
oh fluffy boy
okay okay super effective i'm out of
here
i think
yeah i'm out of here
so we have fighting
and
groundwater rock
should i throw falcons
yeah
pocket has everything holy [\h__\h]
every answer to arcanine i has
so far very good
[Music]
i wanna one hit you
i shall do that
four times a week then probably even a
normal although arcanine is very strong
should i go strong
[Music]
let's do it
go kill him
kill him
yeah yeah yeah okay so far so good so
far so good okay okay okay okay okay
we've we've come to this part with
mostly no damage and no deaths okay
target kiss tugger kiss
pogo keys
strong style
moon blast uh how does that feel
it does not feel good
ah
okay it seems like obese spikes is the
way to go here
holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h] right
uh
uh is iron tail stronger body champ is
it like four times and the other ones
are two times or should i just go from
the bolt
[Music]
it's buffed yeah
i hope i can take it down but
let you know what never mind sorry sorry
i still saw that i just saw that i'll go
first like this and then strong because
that way i can do two moves i didn't see
it right away
okay say it stay safe
[Music]
okay
normal would have probably been enough
to yeah oh
doesn't cynthia have the one too isn't
that one that terrorized me though
now this is where we're gonna get in
trouble
oh cresselia
okay
this is where we get in trouble this is
where we're [\h__\h]
uh i have two times to attack okay
would crystalia
survive an attack
because i might need to revive
[Music]
let's see maybe we can even kill him one
hit i doubt it but
okay
should i kill or should i revive
[Music]
probably better to kill as quickly as
possible
right
[Music]
okay
this monster is gone this one cost me a
lot of revives in
shining pearl lucario
okay oh it barely does any damage
i'm still alive okay that's good that's
good that's good that's good do i have
something effective no okay then i'm out
of here i think
[Music]
so fetch super effective fire
easy
we're not blessing agile
okay good
[Music]
how much does that feel oh
i became obscured but when i switch
myself out i
that goes away right that will be reset
i think
should i do it again should i stay in
i will lose it
okay you want me to try for as long as
possible with cresselia
[Music]
ah he buffs himself too
now we're about dead
oh okay
[Music]
what's it gonna be
i might not
shouldn't he obscure missing
shouldn't he be missing at least once
okay so fetch let's go
[Music]
at least we got palkia back
we yeah the obscuring that gives you
like
makes the other one less accurate right
anyway
we have two attacks
okay
[Music]
of course he does they all do they all
cheat
what's your last pokemon buddy
oh perfect perfect
i can just burn it down you don't have
any effective do you anything
good okay you do apparently but it
doesn't hurt much
poison
but you plant right yes yes
[Music]
um
and i guess i can go twice
i'm wondering if i should do that
i'll go twice
[Music]
the thing is i know this is not the end
of it
i know i know guys
um
[Music]
and i need my pokemon after this
but okay i wish i could
heal a bit more before we go into next
stage okay okay we still have a lot of
alive pokemon so i guess we can totally
stall
it should be fine
or you should be fine
okay okay
[Music]
why why
why do you have the blessing of our kiss
[Music]
why how
i've devoted myself to arceus beyond any
other i worshipped it as the creator of
our entire world
i bent all of my passion and interest to
its study
all the time i've spent pouring over its
legends everything that i've done
you outsider it's almost as if you were
sped out of space timer just to get in
my way
no
this isn't finished yet
can you feel it the chill creeping for
your veins the eldritch presence icing
your heart
mhm
he's becoming a pokemon
cool the cutscenes are pretty nice in
this game
nice
screenshots
striker down
[Music]
um
oh big boy versus big boy is that good
it's pocky i'm good again seratino
do we can no i wanna attack fish
you better give it all you got you
better give it all you got
no
it's not [\h__\h] fair
oh yeah cause it is obscured but what
about my obscured cresselia
i'll get one hit it though
he'll one hit me but let's see
dark or ghost
we're in trouble yeah
oh it's jumping
goes
stop oh yeah okay
oh my god
i don't want to die here it's gonna kill
me after this i better do as much damage
as i can in that one turn don't you
think
maybe try and get two turns to survive
to revive someone
but i
it
the agile doesn't help me now
except if i do extra sensory
hmm
extra sensory would make me fast enough
to at least
do damage and revive
otherwise i'll do that
okay
[Music]
oh
and now attack or revive
[Music]
i still have
two other pokemon alive
what a [\h__\h] chunk man
i feel like i want to
use this opportunity to do some damage
i want to lower the defensive stats too
i'm i'm just gonna do it guys i'm sorry
yes yes yes
[Music]
right choice
and i'm still standing oh never mind
good job silver x
again
now
uh
so fat is pretty much dead anyway i
wonder if mumei would
uh survive one hit probably not
probably not
so let's it's better to send in someone
who's dead anyway
i think or hex with hex
we could take him maybe even down but
can i do
agile
but is there a chance that agile will
kill him
do we even want that
now it's better to revive after that
let's see how much damage does the agile
hex
a lot a lot a lot
although he has also never used a heal
item yet right will he do that
will he be such a pain in the ass
who do we revive
first palkia or cresselia
he won't kill geratina
go for the kill
let's kill
[Music]
really
stop playing with your food
if i like when he okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
it became a baby worm
reject feet
return to
warm shade
see this is i don't know man
i don't know man
this is the problem
wait before i revive can i do anything
to get two turns no okay probably not um
now it's kind of bad cause we don't have
anything to fall back into
okay
maybe i'll
survive one hit for some reason
for whatever reasons
[Music]
you making me so proud
so proud
[Music]
i'm so proud
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
mommy
you are
the best
you are the best
mommy
you just changed everything
uh okay
who do we want them for when you guys
probably gonna take cresselia
um
you guys want to say cresselia aren't
you
but but
yes
okay
[Music]
i could do it twice
i can do it twice
okay
salute to women yeah everyone salutes to
the verb
wait already down to ford oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i think i don't want to go strong
because
i don't want to give it a chance to
attack twice
i think that's too dangerous
if it attacks twice i feel like it could
take me down
[Music]
whatever it will do we will see we'll be
fine
this way is safer a little bit safer i
think
dragon spirit does more okay and it's no
longer obscured okay
now
i only have three pp left man
only three pp left
go should i go strong could that kill it
could that kill it
that was easier than cynthia somehow
was i just better prepared wow
wow
that was a good fight first try
insane i mean it seems like we didn't
even need all those revives because
christelia was just standing strong
but still that was epic finally getting
some rng here
i wasn't on the level for this one i
guess i was on the level for cynthia a
little bit yeah
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
turning tail and running from this puny
human
pathetic
i would still want to feed you the power
you needed so that you could take
anarchy as yeah so did he just uh take
the plates
did your retina take the plates now are
the plates gone or it would happen
no i still have the plates right
i was the one who gave you the chance to
claw open that space timer of driving
the deity of space and deity of time mad
so that you could drag the creator out
from hiding
yeah so proud of mummy
i still have them but i need his plate
too right
how how could this happen
almighty argus if you have any heart
within you then tell me
the blood of the ancient sinnoh people
flows in my veins does it not
what is it then that you find so lacking
in me
do you mean to tell me that this world
doesn't need to be remade
that's pretty fine
i can't wait for such questions
and what what's your problem with this
world it's like pretty fine
i can't bear without stop satisfying
this egg to know
answer me dan kiawa do you have some
dream that propels you as i've heard
uh going back home
so you do
that doubtless that dream of yours would
never leave room for the dreams of one
like me
ew there's nothing to do with it dude
i'm the great wielder of pokemon and you
you battle alongside your pokemon in the
end i was alone but not you you will
fight together with your pokemon to
seize whatever dreams you have
here take it your eyes still kind of
scare me can you like turn that off
please
you you act kind of nice now but i can't
trust you as long as your eyes are as
small as that
take the plate that started me on this
path
the plate i once received from geratina
my journey is over my story ended when i
lost to you
wow we broke him we shattered him his
heart is in pieces a spooky plate
seeking the remaining plates completo
i suppose now you've gathered all of the
plates said to exist in this land of
history
[Music]
what the hell is that
it's now a multitasking flute
also known as the doodle suck
so that's that's it there's your flute
huh
it comes to you
so our case wishes to meet you
wishes to meet you of all people you had
to be the one
thank you
is that why you were brought to this
world
thank you chad thank you
i have no desire to watch from the
sidelands as arcus comes to you and
absolutely cannot accept the world in
which you would ever manage to defeat
argus
someday
i'll solve every riddle in the legends
of history's pokemon and on that day
i'll stand before rockers at last no
i will conquer it
no matter how many years how many
decades
how many centuries it takes me
thank you
okay
bye
that was
it left some things to be desired let's
say like that i felt his reason
was cliche
it was
i mean i understand plot twists but that
was just out of nowhere
is that is that uh
it for today stick out all the pokemon
there are to meet them play your flute
upon the dice and okay yeah i understand
so
yeah this is it
right because like
would you like to play the yeah but it
won't do anything right
[Music]
oh still makes the same sound
why did we upgrade it makes it seem oh
now it's changed
[Music]
music makes the world go around
oh nothing
[Laughter]
oh no
i've yet to see all the pokemon
seek out all pokemon have i not been
clear enough already oh my god you're so
stupid
[Music]
okay
oh my god do i really have to
uh
god texting me
and he's like doing your [\h__\h] job man
i told you how many times i have to tell
you
eh so yeah really i don't know i don't
want to end it yeah can we get manafi
can we get mana fee
let's go get monafi
it's not the end yet
we're not ending it yet uh
oops
i look at my nappy do i have that what
what was the third pokemon i don't know
if i have it oh you guys did say i have
it okay
that's uh one of the ones that we caught
from the quest i think
[Music]
yeah
i wanna return
over
that's right
yeah yeah yeah
oh shaming yeah i wanted to tell you
guys yesterday i did the shaming quest
and i tr i swear
i
reset 10 times
every time that stupid shaymin runs away
in battle
every time
and i tried catching it without a battle
too
but it won't let me i'm just unable to
get that stupid shame in
that [\h__\h] shaymin
i saw someone else got it on second try
so i'm like yo rng doco
did you try feeding yes i also tried
that but i didn't have raspberries with
me so i went out looking for raspberries
but i couldn't find any
but i guess i'll buy some here and
try it again
yeah
why is it such a pain in the ass you got
it first try
i tried so much
sticky globe
held it with mud i didn't try mud no
i tried smoke bombs yeah
i was using ultra balls yeah
it just didn't work it makes no sense
chime in oh
wait who's talking
oh you the left guy huge shadow appeared
in the club of coastlines and then just
vanished without a trace
you are where my good you must tell me
you went to the temple officer with rolo
correct what happened
oh [\h__\h] that protagonist doesn't talk i
forgot
i say
in that case the shadow in the cobalt
coastlines may be none other than
jarrett tayna a pokemon said to have
once been banished to a reverse side of
our world ye
i do believe this calls for a survey
[Music]
uh i guess it gives me a chance to catch
it
but i wanna do the other one first so we
need
this pokemon in the team
and we need uh
this this one
quill fish
was it the
uh evolution
evolution folk
don't i have that too
am i blind
i also need
this one
wait
overcool is the evolution
[Music]
uh
i killed all the quill that was perhaps
an overkill
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
can i uh
where where is is there like an alpha
that everyone knows about that i can
quickly catch
grind evolution
it's not in the wild
yeah
link called please
can i have your
q over quill and maybe your credit card
number to go with it please
please
i need the the three number code too
now i suppose it's an eight number code
perfect just like a credit card
oh really
no that's [\h__\h] gabrielle don't [\h__\h]
around with me
no maybe that's also [\h__\h] no those
are all [\h__\h] who'd i trust
who can i trust
you can't say no that's the thing
please
please which one is a real number
a humble move is that really it
i trust you
i will trust you
but no taxi back seats
because that's that's not it that's too
short
nobody thought that was real
no
so yeah
we're so young
no
it's not even a number saying that's
really
is that just a random number
i will hate you if this is a random
number
[Music]
this is your real number
did you troll me
you troll me you're not allowed to troll
your attention you go to the usual room
seems fake
this seems fake to me
one sec buzz be there real quick you're
lying to me you're gonna go buy milk
i'll never come back oh
phoenix
your name is phoenix
do i have to give you something too
look at this
one here
oh wait no
you didn't put anything in there yet huh
how's this wig
huh
i have to give something in return okay
i think this is very uh
uh fair
oh he's looking there it is there it is
[Music]
cook
we're going to space
[Music]
sure you don't need it anymore
you sure
oh spikey
it's like a cactus
thank you
thank you duncan
that was an amazing animation
where are you
i just want your confirmation that you
don't need it anymore
it was
a anything else i need everything but
i'll try to get them on my own ah it's
not me you get stuck
who is phoenix
but didn't you write that code to me
or did someone else enter uh
confused who was it then who who is this
phoenix that i don't know of
eh i i did what did you do
who is
mystery chad
me
really i don't believe you
okay
thank you
anthony
[Music]
well whoever i was yeah you're welcome
to tell me on twitter with a screenshot
it was our kiss
wait i didn't put it in my team did i
ha
he got zulu
this is
this is titty
uh
manafee
i hope we're fine with this pokemon
let's go get my number because i don't
want to leave you guys yet
shiny garden
thank you guys for your offers but
i think only shine is of
my pokemon that i'm actually using would
make sense for me
um
because otherwise it's just like what do
i do with it
what do i just do with it
didn't even get it myself can't even be
proud of it
yeah
anyway do me if i understand correctly i
just need to have these three pokemon
with me and then uh
zoom through those two thingies over
there
with my fish
that's i looked it up actually i looked
it up guys
yeah yeah yeah i did my homework
ah at sunset oh it looks like sun is
going
up
you're right there was something at the
time
sun rising right now
sun looks like it's rising
even in town okay well there's a camp
here
right
there i have to voice out with me too
don't worry about it
hello
let me get into the cozy tent
um
cozy i want to go uh camping
haven't done that in such a long time
million years
i was i was i was so small
when i last went camping
tent chalk
that's what i will call my tent if i
ever get one
of my own
i heard you cry
now we gotta go to
uh
i think that cave
i think
if i'm
not not wrong
bring smoke bombs and silence please
spray silence break
i have
i have some some smoke bombs
every year camping nice
you saw a bear nearby what
what
did you give it a hug a nice comfy huge
oh my god tomorrow's monday right oh my
god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my
god oh my god i'm just excited for my
kitchen oh my god oh my god and i don't
even have to lift a finger isn't that
exciting
ah
i'm so excited i don't know why but i'm
just so excited because i've been
waiting so long this whole time i had no
uh
i had no proper
um
dinner table or anything and i still
won't have a dinner table after this but
i kind of decided that since i never
really have guests anyway
and
um
i myself
usually i know some of you will be
shocked but i oopsie [\h__\h]
i usually eat
if it's something i can eat on my bed
then i
usually eat it on my bed where the [\h__\h]
am i land
and
don't judge me
gasp
cancel me
yeah it's just so comfy because i can
watch netflix there that's why actually
why i do it yeah
and uh
before i had a tv in my bedroom i um
like when i lived with r t
i
my bedroom
just had my pc so i would eat in front
of my pc
yeah
now i eat on my bed mostly so so what
i'm doing is i'm getting like a kitchen
counter like an eye island we call it
island
that style of kitchen counter
do i have to find them
wait
they immediately notice me can they
unnotice me when i'm here
oh god
just find me
they fought me but no that's not how
they were supposed to fight me
legendaries need to be stunned first
oh
what is that so i didn't realize that
huh
where are we
only faster if we go here first
do i have
anything to stun and live stun done with
no not really
yeah no i don't have anything
perfect there's the the mud thingies
right here
i just remembered perfect that i uh
came over here
doing that
[Music]
ganging up on a human i thought manifest
were like nice pokemon
i thought they were nice
but they're just
outright evil
just need to start stand one to start
about oh okay
all righty where are we going oh
that way but i think i can't
i can't fly there it's so stupid because
i think it is because if you fly over
the lava basically in theory you can
accidentally or purposefully
drop yourself and fall into the lava and
the game didn't really want to
they probably didn't really want to
you know make it a thing that you could
die in lava
that would have been apparently
too complicated they could have just
used the same animation as when you
drown in water though
but i guess it's a bit too brutal
i get that okay i get it
it's maybe a bit too brutal
[Applause]
yeah whatever
[Music]
yeah so i think that's why they decided
to not make it possible to go there
[Applause]
okay never try
uh i'll actually save in front of the
cave because i'm going to get here
and
um
now be a good baby
i'll be nice to you if you're nice to me
otherwise once i caught you i rip out
those
weird stringy things that you have on
your head do you want that
no you don't want that trust me
where's the stupid mud bow there it is
great start
oh
well wonderful that was too easy
okay
fiona nice to meet you
did i already try catching it
yeah
wait level 50.
uh
let's go with that this one first
ultra ball
[Music]
reshuffled iphone oh
it took me a moment to understand what
you're talking about
iphone
be on it
[Music]
don't say it to the pokemon directly i
think
it will be a bit sad
if you call it iphone
glitch what glitch i didn't see a glitch
i want to catch without fighting yeah i
feel like i'll kill it by accident
uh
[Music]
maybe he'll
let's see if it kills
we have free tries for the fiona's
oh okay
halfway
and they look like they will fall apart
the moment i touched them
you're an ultra ball now what do you say
now change your mind because you saw how
much damage i do
that is
a respectable choice but okay you're
against it still what is the matter with
you
woman is no longer pumped up yeah we're
all disappointed here
come on get a move on so you don't waste
our time anymore these people want to
hear their names being read with the
dankest and afterwards they want to hear
the super jet reading okay
don't make it so difficult
chop chop
oh no
oh no the manatee is getting aggressive
ah
if your defensive stats are raised then
i wanna try
one more and get you into the red area
nice beautiful
if you want to stay in the pokeball now
i'm gonna be mad
i like how they always wait
look around
when will manafee attack me yeah
it's okay
nice strat thank you
i mean i just i just what
i just finished the game
by killing
bonus spirit
so i think i
i should be respected as a pokemon
trainer might have been just looking
around okay everyone's just looking
around
how why why did i do that i don't
understand like they get a turn but they
choose to just ignore it why is it just
the rng being nice to me
because it's too many enemies
in the battle
they're looking at their eyes
there we go finally so we can kill the
others and we can catch manathy
okay okay okay chill chill chill chill
sorry guys am i making you dizzy
when i run around like that
i can't stop myself from running around
[Music]
you good okay
see i have this legendary you could be
one of us
join us
join the revolution
okay i didn't need to make that strong
probably
way
one of us one of us
one of us
they have really nice cute clothes
though i like the
the curls
and fiona
one more
and then manafi oh
so strong
move was necessary to kill it
they are a bit annoying yeah a little
bit
[Music]
okay
here we go magnafine you and me
um
you easily survived
you would survive that one show
no maybe not maybe normal is better
i'm scared
okay another agile one maybe
there's a catch what i caught a feeling
but the metaphase i have yet to catch
we're good though don't worry about it
unfortunately it's not in the red area
but what can we do
we have to catch it now
[Applause]
[Music]
i got the map
all is good report back to professor
lavinton
okay
hey thank you chad thank you we did it
and thank you to the person who gave me
that pokemon that i needed the over
quill i will always remember that now
because of the overkill joke
see i thought you caught a mysterious
swimmer so it was my feet all along a
sims manifest here is a migratory
pokemon drifting to and fro
fro across the state since long ago at
least that's what it says in the city's
legend i had a jolly hard time getting
hold of this tomb but it seems it was
more from the end
yeah
okay
maybe
one more thing we could do is get
geratina
i guess
is that difficult
to get
uh
where were we supposed to go for germany
not
i'll switch out my team again
i will go get it's on the same map oh
then i guess we can stay here
don't leave
let's switch out team
uh i wanna see my pokemon
uh
move
let me get you in here again
[Music]
so hard to see what i'm looking for
ah
hey
what am i looking for
i could put in turkey kids back again
so that nah
because then i have to get rid of this
although maybe it's better
it's it's just too
no
too powerful we don't want too much
power it will eat us up and then we'll
become evil
and uh
who did i switch out for boyselle
fetch
solve it oh yeah
[Music]
did i miss it
uh
i think i did i might be blind
nine tails
search
it was on the last page
okay
and what was another one
oopsie
yeah
it's a bit difficult to find everything
here
right oh
did you guys see where that one is our
chunky boy
can't go without our eye too
nacho has been with us for so long oh
you're close
but you're an imposter
you too
huh
search
ah there it is i was right next to it
okay
[Music]
now
uh
time to save again
our last quest today
is
getting
geritina
which is a side quest um
there it is
find out the truth behind a huge shadow
in the cobalt coastlands
there's no
guidy thingy maybe here
because there was nothing to do in this
area yet
cave top left oh okay
yep just as i thought
just how i thought it would be
[Music]
makes sense i i found that place when i
was looking for wisps and i was like hmm
sus
this place will sooner later
be used for some kind of legendary
charlie
yeah
yeah what's right with that here
oh man
damn it
uh
moment here this is for you thank you
for getting bullied by those stupid
manatees
you didn't deserve that kind of
treatment no no no you were so helpful
in that battle against
volo
so proud of you
i'm so proud of you whoopsie
where is uh the cape entrance
is it at the top
no
no no i think it's at the top
down
[Music]
[Laughter]
we'll just be right there
scared i'm scared
zaratina giratina
giroudtina
we meet again
oh oh it's in this form
i saved before coming here don't worry
are you
you want to talk what
warm form
it's it's it doesn't even look more
intimidating in this form
because now it's really just so warm
or do you guys think this is more
intimidating
[Music]
so last time our special rent missed and
it was still unfair but we got revenge
later on
let's see if it misses again
wait i want to catch it though right
okay okay
i think i need to oh i want to catch it
okay i guess i'll try already
oh nice thank you for killing me you
bastard
spooky noodle yeah
pocket kiss help us out here
i'll try
i'm trying maybe we're lucky sometimes
sometimes
it works
[Music]
easy peasy lemon squeezy
so easy
found something shiny where giratina was
that probably makes it so that it looks
like the
the noodle
shape
why was i so scared
there was nothing to be scared of
what what lesson do we take from this
home
don't be scared
it's too easy
man
i missed an unknown oh don't worry i'll
do it on my own time
i'll go violence
volume eventually returned and told me
more about what happened at the temple
of sinnoh
wait rolo return and talk to you do you
know that he absolutely went that [\h__\h]
crazy
you said geratina that it chose to
protect land of history after
discovering it was no match for you he
said that we should study it and add it
to the pokedex it wandered off after
that saying this was probably the last
time we would meet but i can't help but
feel he's far more invested in our
completion of the pokedex and he would
have us know
ah
oh volo
you're really [\h__\h] up we could have
been bffs forever why did you have to do
it this way
such a such a sussy buckle
i think that's the best way to describe
him
[Music]
a sassy little buckah
but with that said
it's kind of anti-climactic
but we
have i consider this finished now i
consider the
um series as finished now and
because we did we saw the credits we
destroyed volo all this left to do for
me is finish all the tedious
grinding and requests the quests and the
wisps and the unknowns unknowns and uh
seeing all the pokemon and all of that
takes ages and
i don't want there to be too much time
between this episode and the next one
but i also don't want to cheat and get
everything from you guys and and i also
don't want to rush myself too much to
get everything immediately so i decide
that this is the last part
and uh yeah um
thank you everybody for following
pokemon legends arceus with me from
beginning to end
oh
[Music]
thank you very much oh
i really really like the game
definitely my favorite pokemon game
um it's very different from the others
but it offers so much new stuff so much
more exciting stuff a big change from
the old pokemon games
um
i totally get if you prefer the older
ones just because that's the typical
pokemon style but i really really liked
um what this game had to offer obviously
there's still things that
could be improved obviously
i don't think i even have to mention
that but i like to appreciate the good
things about it and
i really had a great time playing this
game
yeah of course i saw i saw it gotta go
watch the gen 9 reveal we watched it at
the beginning of the stream together
if you follow me on twitter you would
know hey
oh so reason to follow me on twitter
yeah no
anyway yeah um
it seems like they will continue to
be inspired by
how archaeas turned out and maybe use
some
of
the
of the functionalities and whatever
traits for future pokemon games i would
personally really really really like it
um
yeah
so it was fun it was really fun and
and i oh the thing is i can't really
i was just talking about how it would
take me too much time to continue but i
just realized again i forgot but i
realized again i can't play any longer
anyway
i can't play this game any longer anyway
and
yeah after the end of the month
is
no more so it's good that we ended it
today
um
yeah february is ending
um screenshots when you finish yeah i
will let you guys know but for me this
is gonna be a game that i play maybe
when i travel when i'm in a in a train
or in an airplane um so i'll take my
time with it
whenever i feel like
yeah netflix is not doing it for me
today i'll play uh pokemon
i want to actually
keep it for as long as possible
i i want to drag it out for as long as
possible i don't want to rush it at all
i'll take my time with it maybe i'll
i'll instead of just seeing all the
pokemon i'll probably try to get old
pokemon on pokedex level 10 even
yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
and then i'll flex to you guys
[Music]
i talked about triangle strategy before
i i don't think no i don't think so nope
maybe in my private time one day but not
on stream
not planning on it
thank you guys yeah
uh yakuza yakuza i think will be our
next series i'm
not sure if we'll start uh right away
next week because
next week feels like kind of stressful
to me
i have some things to do next week
but at the latest the week after
uh i forgot which one we're playing i
had one in mind
i forgot which one
i think of the one before the latest one
i think
[Music]
yeah i think we wanted to do zero
so
oh yeah actually good idea i'm ending
this with all 195 scene 146 caught
and
seven star member i think we've got
pretty damn far i think out of whole
life english
i got the furthest
yeah i like to i like to finish the
games i start you know
so i mean it might not be
one million percent finished but it is
pretty close to that
to what i would consider it being
finished
yeah
yeah i think i'm the only one that kind
of finished even even the first ending
i don't think anyone else got it well
well girls you
one
uh
keep up
girls who have english girls you gotta
keep up with me
they can't keep up with me you know why
you know why because i'm the jail pinchy
master if this is not a jpg you know
what i mean you know what i mean
[Music]
challenge issues yeah
yeah
it is a jerry okay
yeah okay well then we
will uh
take a short break and then i'll read
super chat so if you want to hang out a
little bit longer you're welcome to do
so
yeah
i'll read super chats now but i'll go in
the
intermission for a moment
maybe three minutes four minutes
all right see you
in a little bit in my office
[Music]
thank you pokemon art kids for a great
time i had a lot of fun playing this
this month
really enjoyed it
beautiful
fun exciting very different from usual
pokemon game
thank you pokemon ikeas and one day one
day i'll meet you rks
i'm not done with you i'll find you i'll
find where you're staying at which hotel
you're staying at
feel free to stick around i'll see you
in a few minutes
for watching
[Music]
max take him down take him down
he caught me a chicken
[Music]
yeah i know that's a joke
and we'll have to take him down himself
actually kind of corrupted
kf politics
he did it
he didn't
[Music]
how do i know i'm eating i'm muted
do
[Music]
hey
alright baby i have to wash my hands
[Music]
okay
gosh i really need to clean my kitchen
before these people come over
uh
nope
here
welcome back welcome back and bang oh my
god is the end of the week this week
felt
kinda long
[Laughter]
actually i'm sorry i
um
i sneeze more dramatically when i'm with
you guys because i i i'm so happy you
guys enjoy my sneezes um i i i like go
all out when i sneeze
i was gonna say i'm um
i kind of took uh
yesterday off and kind of also first day
so
i'm sorry for oh you know actually this
week was supposed to be more fun and
more filled
and packed but
things happen
but we got ellen ring so i think that
makes up for minecraft
um
yeah
uh
let's see how many super chats we have
to read
uh
also it seems like i may not have so
many troubles
with scheduling
elden ring as i thought i would have
so
it doesn't even have to be sunday
i'll try to figure out how my schedule
looks like next week but i want to
probably do it uh on sunday anyway
because i usually like to take a day off
uh before whole talk to work on whole
talk
and
we will see
really yeah
it seems
actually
to be looking pretty good
[Music]
i
have to close the game i keep on hearing
um pokemon sounds in the background
oh sure let's listen to some bgm
what do we want
um
[Music]
do you guys want something more and
something more energetic or something
really calm
hmm
elevator music again elevator music
really works well doesn't it
sparks
no not sparks
something chills let me call okay but
you guys are gonna fall asleep
i dare you
i dare you to fall asleep
okay i have i have the following ones
calm i go to
it's too calm i think
ah was that the other one i used for
the kimono reveal
this is almost too cold
to come back as long as
this i like this one
i like this one this reminds me of zelda
i think
[Music]
i love that instrument
that goes like
this
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah i get that a little bit it reminds
me of zelda tracks
um
[Music]
it sounds like something that would be
playing uh during
during a dialogue
[Music]
okay so
i think the last few streams have been
super stretched off and horitory got
cancelled but there were i think some
some super chats in both of those
streams oh and karaoke super chats right
uh
the
okay so i think the one from crafting i
did read i think
did i
no did i not did i read the ones from
the crafting stream
i did okay then i will start at the ones
of the guarded phone collab that didn't
happen because there were some there yo
oh did you like my
look at my thumbnails
look at those thumbnails
i i i
before
before the
collab day
i worked hard to make this
[Music]
now i have to make one more because
probably if we reschedule mummy might
actually be able to join
thank god i saved the ps the psd file
otherwise i would have to remake
everything
oh
look at those they look so matching and
nice don't they a detailed detail for
the japanese members i wrote the pov in
japanese and for the english-speaking
members i wrote them in english yeah
yeah
uh-huh
how considerate i i am
yeah
my lip neck shut up my neck looks fine
no it has the same length as everyone
else if you actually if you compare it i
think
odaina's look pretty long too because
hers is so thin
we all have long necks
now that you say mummys looks really
long to me too
yeah anyway i like these thumbnails
and i've rushed the
i rushed to the the order of the
logo because
yeah i thought it was gonna happen so
it's unfortunate but hopefully after
somebody said boys break because she's
going on a break for two weeks
i hope we're gonna do it asap
um
[Music]
i feel like it was only a matter of time
for her to get her throat [\h__\h] up
uh surprise surprise it took so much
time
all right then
now that you looked at my beautiful
thumbnails that i'm so proud of
because they look so nice
now we will read the super chats from oh
from exactly that sorry i could have
kept it on the screen now
all righty
we'll just put it on here
and
reading super chats
there we go
[Music]
not the best reason but at least she's
taking a break yeah yeah i i think i
mean
taking a break like that
she'll she'll have some time to relax
and chill too i think
maybe she'll go to an onsen i should
tell her to go to an auntie somebody
said bye go to onsen do a swim
do a swim
i i guess it's more to prevent that's
good too better to prevent
she said she's visiting her grandparents
oh
that's nice i think i heard that
[Music]
thank you guys for the few super jets
and now we have the unarchived karaoke
again i love that art it was so perfect
the moment i saw it i was like i have to
use this
as a karaoke from nail
so gorgeous i i had them i think i
already told you but i had them sent me
the big version of it
because the resolution on on twitter was
so so tiny
it's wallpaper material yeah
i i don't know it feels like there's
like emotion in this image
i'm okay i'm okay i i have uh
i felt a little bad for
some days but now i'm fine
i mean
as fine as one can be
in
the current times
my throat
my throat is i mean after a long stream
like that
uh
it's a bit
meh but i'm okay
[Music]
for the rest of the chat splurging for
the box seats this time
i might as well sign the chimken
attendance sheet as long as i'm here
also congrats uh to chimpkin john weber
i'm passing a tough exam and tk has one
coming up how do you know all these
things
could i pass my red super chat kiss to
tk for luck tangiel oh
of course oh you're so considerate have
you played the game cookie yummy before
doug joseph
if you were to play it i'm sure you
would get a high score
we told him oh
ah
so sweet all right tk i don't know if
you're here right now but here's the
case for you
[Music]
good luck
good luck for a big big exam i'm glad i
don't have to do
any exams anymore oh man i hated the
time in school where i had to
do exams
it was terrifying so glad i don't have
to do that anymore um i don't re uh i
don't envy you guys
oh by the way you want to know what i
was just eating
in that short time
i ate a graphene
in german they call it a berliner but in
austria we call it a
coffin
it's a
a puffy
um
bread
thingy
fluffy puffy bread thingy like a donut
yeah donut with no hole
and um inside is jam usually it's
apricot jam
at least in austria usually it's apricot
jam and we like to um we like to produce
about a million a day
in our country
uh
around the time of uh
fashion which is like carnival
um
but there's some versions with not with
apricot jam but like for example vanilla
um cream or chocolate cream or
strawberry jam there's so many but the
classic one is apricot jam here and i
remember like in school
in school when fashion
carnival was around i was always so
excited because they would give out
coffin in the whole school like more
than you could eat it was exciting
coughing
all you can eat clapton in school
yeah
yum yum yum for um
for someone who really likes to eat
sweet things that was heaven
yeah
they're really yummy but i always have a
problem eating them because the first of
all the jam spills everywhere like once
you bite inside
it like
spills out there's so much jam
everywhere
and the other thing is there's like a
powdered sugar on top of it
and sometimes there's so much and like
my whole face would be covered
in powdered sugar when i bite into it
are they glazed or top no not not glazed
but they have powdered sugar on top
usually
super chat
[Music]
i enjoy listening to sparks about 200 cc
speed drifting in my car no
it sounds like fun
secondhand diabetes
yeah powdered sugar is always a great
way to make a big mess sometimes i don't
think it was with these this specific
food but sometimes when there's like a
lot of powdered sugar on the food and i
like
breathe in while i bite into something
do you guys ever do that
and then you're like
[\h__\h]
shouldn't have breathed in while biting
into this
damn
it happens it happens and then big
regret
[Music]
inhaling this should not yeah
i guess i did that
a few times too often
[Music]
churros oh i rarely have chores i want
to eat churros
i had it like two or three times in my
whole life churros
okay anyway dr thank you thank you for
the support thank you so much
[Music]
love you forever ever
thank you
i'm also happy to be here thank you
for i appreciate the support
blue dunk
deja vu yes tai chi thank you for the
rest of the chat
i don't blame you guys if you uh ask me
to change the song at some point it's
very repetitive
[Music]
who joined kfb this month i would like
to dedicate uh
i don't trust you
an acrostic poem with your name in
korean for you
that already doesn't even look like a
poem it looks like a dialogue and i know
you're messing with me
[Music]
ramen i don't know who's asking me
but yes i would love to have some ramen
but i know you're just [\h__\h] with me
that's not a poem
next time you better write me a proper
poem okay
i have expectations
that you have to meet
always bullying me these korean
korean employees they come here and they
think they can just bully me like that
make fun of me
[Music]
mmm
says
[Music]
thank you it says i'm a god if this is
translated correctly it says i am a god
[Music]
very nice of you
i am i i guess i am
yes because there's so many people
always here praying
at my stream
i wouldn't be surprised if some of you
guys have some kind of like shrine
dedicated to me
thank you soon
[Music]
i couldn't watch the live stream because
of work the next day thank you attention
thank you no problem
yeah a lot of people
suffered by watching the first one even
though i told you guys there will be
another one
but thank you for watching it and i'm
glad you were able to catch it and
i hope you enjoyed it i want to do a
k-pop only karaoke at one point for my
korean fans and non-korean fans as well
because who doesn't love k-pop
um but i have to get my hands on those
sweet sweet instrumentals
like i need like a written
uh permission and i like i got like i i
contacted some channels who have a lot
of
uh
a lot of instrumentals
and they even say like feel free to use
it whatever like on their description
but that doesn't count but they don't
reply so
[Music]
it's suffering
suffering
one day
i'll find
some channel who creates uh kpop
instrumentals then and then they let me
use it hopefully
um
[Music]
i know
getting ghosted now
now well i have to find some more
channels and take the time to
uh
reach out to them yeah thank you
derek
joseph
uh here's a
one from today that's just mixed in
optimus prime dan kashun elsie lapin dan
kishan
[Music]
who knows k-pop better than me is a real
korean
it's just because i sang some korean
songs now come on i mean the nobody from
wonder girls was a little bit old but
i'm sure you've heard of it before too
come on
come on that's famous famous song
don't doubt your korean-ness
i just i just have a really superficial
knowledge anyway i only know the popular
groups anyway
[Music]
thanks kenneth for saying this this was
the song that made me fall in love with
youtubers via a certain clock
which one
now that you have done it too
it just makes me glad that i have found
youtubers
i wonder which song you mean
yeah cronies song that cronie also sang
maybe
maybe the chandelier did crony ever sing
chandelier
we know one clock
yeah rooney
i wonder what song it was
uh mk bf 1907
sundance
i love that song
somewhere only we know that song and
favorite things also
so many good songs
ah young and beautiful kroy sang that oh
i wonder if she sang it because she
likes the song and the artist or because
she likes the movie
because i got to know it for the movie
for once
usually it's always the other way around
for me
not to
[Music]
can you please sing a song with german
ah
generally
yeah
i don't really know many
german songs
that i like and are good
[Music]
a few songs there was there was a group
that i really liked that i can recommend
to you
that maybe one day i'll sing in karaoke
uh it's called via saint hilton
via send helden
[Music]
we are heroes is the translation i did
like them that was one of the very very
very very few and limited
uh german groups and music artists that
i was listening to
isn't hidden
[Music]
honestly they are so
so pushing
uh on us to go to webcams minuschat.com
maybe we should do them the favor and go
there
just kidding don't go there
but if there's hot girls and boys video
chatting there
i feel like we belong there we're also
hot girls and boys
we should give in i mean maybe it's
meant to be maybe it's destiny
i feel like we're pretty hot
i feel like we belong there
they just tried to make true what is
meant to happen
i still pinned the message oh no
hot wings in your area
had wings in your area
[Music]
hey gate
you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
right now but only a few because i had
to close them before the stream started
[Music]
yo
i feel like my outfit was really fitting
to the game now
at least better than my other outfits
with the golden elements i feel like i
looked pretty cool
immersed
thank you thank you guys
don't question it it's just how it is
some some people some companies are good
with it some are not
that's just how it is gotta be thankful
for being able to play their games
they are doing us a favor
jacob 47 outback
patrick
thank you for always doing that so
properly now i never have to be worried
about you again
i never played a souls game even
attention but i hear they are tough not
tougher than tantra though good luck i'm
sorry to disappoint you even though you
believed in me it was tougher than me
uh
but it's just a matter of practice
and training and playing the game every
day for one hour
or five hours if it must be for someone
like me
yeah it's it's okay though it's okay i
didn't expect it to be like super easy
you guys warned me so much about it i
didn't expect it to be suddenly
my new talent
[Music]
it wasn't really about being stubborn i
just really thought that this is where i
was supposed to be
yeah as i said today i didn't realize
there was like a kind of like a
beginner's area somewhere close by
[Music]
um i did level up a little bit later on
and then i went back to the bus just
because i after challenging him so many
times i didn't wanna
didn't want to just give up there
but it's okay if i play it again i'll go
level in that other area
and then hopefully by the end of the
next stream we'll be able to kill
that bastard
[Music]
62 times
it's a magical number
[Music]
i'm glad to see that hallway i'm
starting to play souls like games and
i'm interested to see how a newcomer
like you can handle er
i don't doubt your skills you've already
proven yourself as a pro gamer
yeah right
it's such a game it's just such games
can be infuriating be patient kiara i
was pretty patient i would say hmm
i definitely was very patient
i even stopped like
uh raging after a few deaths because i
realized oh this is just how it's gonna
be huh
also i'm in trouble i don't want to miss
your stream and i don't want to be
spoiled by it i only have a small window
to play er myself oh oh don't worry i
didn't get really far i'm curious to see
which one of us will make more progress
today oh well and now you have a lot of
time to catch up anyway because my next
stream will probably just be on sunday
i think i'll do one more stream give it
another chance and then
yeah because i'm really torn right now i
i like the game
but it's like really difficult for me
i don't want to just give you give it up
because it's so difficult but then again
i might just be suffering all the time
but if we kind of play it kind of
casually
um
at least one more time with like a
casual feeling
not the pressure of wanting to make it
into a series but just like a kind of
like a one-time thing once every once in
a while
[Music]
and i just kind of also needed to get
used to it i guess now now i kind of
understand what
elden ring like how it works how the
game
uh how the game is like roughly
[Music]
no but oh you said you said i didn't
play bad i just entered dead too early
but then i saw yesterday or today
morning
i saw this video on my timeline
someone retweeted it uh oh
baby you guys saw it they got a lot of
likes and retweets someone doing the
same boss walking in their shirtless but
still looking stronger than me
and just absolutely obliterating zero
damage zero damage run
and like it was always just him walking
so slowly menacingly did you see it
he like didn't even try to run he was
always just like walking menacingly he
had this menacing aura around him
yeah but obviously yeah that person is a
pro that person has a lot of experience
with these games but watching that i was
like oh you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah
man he just had it down
he just knew exactly what he was doing
the secret is going in shirtless clearly
oh i just have to take my shirt off next
time
[Music]
it was it kind of uh i felt i felt like
here
like that video was was like
hard to say mocking me i felt mocked
it's mocking everyone who's suffering
with valden ring
thank you anton m for the rainbow i'm
i'm i'll give it another try especially
also for people like you who really
enjoy these kind of games and i do try
recently to give you guys like a little
bit of a
of a variety on my channel
if you have noticed i played fps games
and i played horror games i mean i mean
whole life ever is not really that scary
but
for horror games
[Music]
that is the least likely for me to go
really like into it
that no no
but yeah i'll i'll try to play some
games that you like but honestly
elephant ring
in theory isn't really out of my comfort
zone i like games in that style
played it like when i was younger too
like um
uh gothic
reminds me of
i didn't ring or the other way around
and uh
similarly games that i forgot the names
of but yeah
i didn't only play
anime rpgs no
[Music]
of course it's easier but like the style
reminds me of it like a classic fantasy
rpg
not anime style
hmm
[Music]
well i was so young back then but
um i definitely preferred that kind of
game over like i don't know for example
futuristic shooter games or something
like that
a witcher playthrough
i know we don't have permissions for
that do we
probably not i don't know i don't know
i don't know i don't really know much
about witcher i just know it's a very
hyped game
and show on netflix or so
i've seen a lot of uh
what's it called again gender bending
cosplays of that main character are
really hot
[Laughter]
a lot of a lot of sexy
cosplayers doing that main character but
in the female version
geralt yeah
i'm sure you guys have seen those too
[Music]
a siri no yes that was siri
yeah i remember it was
they wrote siri cosplay
wait is that
well a different person
i thought it was a gender bend of the
main character
geralt oh
is that so
hi siri
it's an independent it's his daughter
well that makes sense why they look
similar
[Music]
she's all mine
i don't know if i want her yet
[Music]
and now we have today's pokemon super
chats
[Music]
i was honestly when i was lacking like a
show to watch the other day i was very
close to watching
witcher
i was so close to starting
to play it on my tv so close
and then i was like no i want to watch
something funny today
maybe next time
[Music]
i have a time
this is my calm rpg everyday music
[Music]
hot girls and boys video chat
he's literally isn't that describing our
stream right now
[Music]
oh
i'm pretty i'm chatting with you guys
[Music]
wow that was a big one
not catfishing well i like cats
[Music]
i want to fish my cats
with fishes
[Music]
oh she's doing the same like she's
around the same
part of england what does she do
[Music]
no wait that's rcs i just oh
she's fighting rcs right now yo
[Music]
what am is fighting rcs she's been
playing for seven hours
damn how did she
she's level she's around level 70 how
did she even
get to rcs but it's still like on the
same around the same level as me
don't know if she also traded a lot of
pokemon
[Music]
he could
wow fancy attacks that pokemon has
damn fancy
she's so focused she doesn't notice me
that's okay
nice
she's so calm calm sheep
are there two three
they're using uh that naruto attack
she's so cute
[Music]
she has the fire starter
sample
i respect the sheep for getting that far
she's so cute how's she so cute
oh she's so cute thank you how's she so
cute
oh she's so cute hold up food strong
excuse me don't give us that group name
please
i didn't ask for a group name like that
[Music]
she's so cute oh i need
i actually didn't want to check out the
streamer i was going to go to youtube
studio
okay okay i'm sorry sorry sorry sir i
got distracted but she's so cute how can
i not be just distracted you hold the
food kind of catchy stop it
stop no
yeah she had the hat i should have used
the hats like that too
i wanted one too
okay hold up pray
stop
no hold up pray no no no hold up cute if
anything hold up cute
oh you're soft or you're fluffy
or your hug
[Music]
oh the kid would have 50 members
so what
it's just all of our life so what
then anyone can be in a unit apparently
uh torah senpai and canada senpai are
like
having an official group like supported
by
cover slash whole life like
they are looking for a name right now
but they made a post that they have a
they're they're creating a official unit
but i guess not only like umi c but like
more
more than that i think let me see
wasn't it wasn't that kind of like a
like a one-time thing
yeah i think that was supposed to be a
one-time thing and then
uh yeah
but kind of
are they going to be like a long term
thing i think so
i suppose so
um
so
i said thank you to you on the stream or
there too what was that about
i don't know
what did i do
[Music]
is there a clip of that
i didn't do anything
a long time ago
oh you don't mean it's recent it's very
long ago oh
that was something
unimportant
not interesting i think
i think it was just because uh
i may have
modded her chat and she saw it
it was a couple days ago are you sure
[Music]
super said thanks recently to me
i mean someone who's saying thank you
makes a bit more sense
could be anything with somebody saying
but
hmm
interesting anyway um i'll eldering that
one boss is the type you don't find in a
normal souls game until halfway through
really not as a beginner to get him to
near death in your circumstances is
something to be proud of
thank you also preemptive congrats on
the finishing arcus thank you
i guess now if you say it like that i
guess
maybe i am a little bit proud of myself
as a absolute 100 beginner
and noob and on the level
i forced him
pretty far
what i may want nice i don't want to
look though because it will spoil me the
ending you guys shouldn't look either
if you didn't know the ending yet
play it yourself
slayer
[Music]
do you super chat to iris with that name
dangerous game you're playing
it says iris's boot brace our big wrist
something like that
doctor thank you for the rainbow
wow rainbow look look guys look in the
sky i always i know it's dark
in my office and snowing but there's a
rainbow i see it
i registered myself in your chimpkin
attendance pokedex also thanks for all
the fun streams this week even with the
jammed glue gun
and having to reschedule the whole
attorney collab our phoenix still rose
up to deliver amazing content thank you
thanks for your hard work boss thank you
oh i i do my best i do my best yo
i try to
deliver
as much as i can to you guys even if
sometimes
i am busy or tough uh not feeling bad or
not i can't speak anymore not feeling
good
but feeling bad
and uh
yeah
but but i don't know this coming week
might be a little bit of a lighter week
yeah
[Music]
yeah thank you guys for waiting for me
and for always supporting me
whatever i do thank you
thank you doctor
this one's for you this time you didn't
ask for it to be given to anyone else so
it's yours take it
wow
charity thank you for two pinkies that
make one red in line of recent events
and you've probably forgotten i've
decided to bestow upon myself a new job
that perfectly suits perfectly suits my
skills
client owl
sadly i can't ask a kia crazy attention
to assign me a role since the poor gal
is delusional
are you calling me delusional
but kind of speaking in third person as
if i'm not the one reading this hello
you're addressing me trevor
are you aware of that
saying i'm a bucket oh and then calling
me a snack
like who'd eat owl
what an infested [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] he's on
fire
any cool i'll perform my job to the best
of my ability here on
so i'm no burden
by testing out the options
that how all the options that kf has to
offer ps gesundheit for the sneeze and
elton ring thank you
are you good
you're so on fire that i feel like you
just roasted yourself into some nice
roasted owl
damn
he's on fire
that was a
combo
[Music]
delusional owl delusional delusional
well you're welcome uh i guess thank you
uh for your support i hope you have fun
with your new job
but but but but but you need to respect
your potential
no crazy no no no if you're looking for
kudaisy that is kudaiji only in whole
live indonesia okay
you're wrong here
thank you
and hey hey hey hey hey hey you're
you're a family member mummy
she really rocked
uh the last fight today
[Music]
i like you owls i like you
it's so much fun watching your aussie
grill to see you go from zero to hero is
so satisfying
there's this song
there's this emo emo song
um
[Music]
zero
hero
da da da da da
[Music]
again
was it even that
that melody was a different song from
them
[Music]
i'm not talking about hercules no
actually not
have you guys never heard the song
before
that's heroine ah that's that one [\h__\h]
but didn't they hear a heroine
yeah boys like girls didn't they have
like a yeah maybe i'm just mixing it up
because the title is similar boys like
girls
or or they must have had the words zero
to hero in their lyrics or so
i think so
that was that was something that emo
kiwawa
was listening to boys like girls
but mostly only that one song
i like the hercules version by that wait
hercules
do i know that one
let me listen let me listen
zero to hero
a damn one
yes
um
but i know this one in german
let me listen in german
insecut
oh yeah
here's a link
oh
um that's so nostalgic
i missed this this was such a good movie
i love this
yeah when i was i wouldn't watch things
in german anymore these days i would
watch them in the original but back then
i was younger so disney movies i always
watched in german
that
they had banger voices
a watchalong
the irony is i can't sing disney songs
but we can still watch disney movies
and then silently sing along
oh
i barely remember this song i just
remembered the visuals of it
[Music]
amazing okay
okay anyway
[Music]
anyway
the lion king
why not why not
uh you made so much promise in er maybe
not story-wise but skill-wise you became
so much better just in a couple hours
those games are all about that
thank you
yeah and there was some improvement
visible thank you for noticing
[Music]
71 times
71 push-ups
yo
doc joseph daniel with a pinky also
talking about the same thing shout out
to patrick chan who did 71 push-ups in
your honor intentional chimpkins made up
have to do one push-up potential er
death
i'll do mine and sets throughout the day
for the empress
that is often quite a lot
uh but i guess not not a big deal for
someone who
uh
always works out my hyper chat kind of
stopped moving wait a second
wait a second
what did i say about no your senpai also
didn't manage to kill margin market
did she also immediately go to the bus
like me wait my chat is dead hyper chad
i believed in you but you know what i'm
not even gonna blame that on hyper chat
i'm sure happy chat is great
this is chrome's fault
this this is all on chrome
wait
wait a moment please stop commenting
what she did another boss
i promise
what i'm curious
oh [\h__\h] sake youtube
why are you so painful
[Music]
uh
ever since like
when did that start i didn't always have
problems with the chat okay i reloaded
it i had to completely
open a new youtube window and then get
it from there
[Music]
didn't always used to be like that
youtube
no it was before the fancy outfit
even
anyway it's back
uh
yeah we'll have fun with the push-ups
i'm not gonna join in though i did i did
other hard work
like fighting that boss
tiny dad
patrick
[Music]
to translate once again
thank you thank you
you guys
you need to add
english reading to your names please
please
[Music]
come sign it up for the pinkies
thank you for watching i guess you're
probably asleep by now valden is here
molly is here yo
hello uh
[Music]
and now you're probably sleeping so this
is a good night
sleep well dream of me you
know and
i want to let you know that no one else
didn't beat margaret in her stream and
fail she's playing against him but i
think she shows that even the night
hands are stranded like you well i'm a
part-time warrior though
[Music]
i'm a part-time warrior she's a knight i
feel like i'm pretty much on like the
same level when it comes to that
i used to be a full-time warrior so
moondog
uh albino
[Music]
come here
come close up
[Music]
close that
close up
[Music]
you say baka
will you shut up
[Music]
you little [\h__\h]
you stupid
[Music]
wonderful
enough said
he wrote
an evil message
elsie lavendancy
[Music]
thank you very much
i appreciate it very generous of you
darkeshan
hope you enjoyed today's stream tai chi
maybe
michael fang danger squid kayode
thank you i don't know if you'll be able
to see the ending today but
congratulations in advance i have to
wake up early in the morning so i'm
going to leave early without permission
hey
but at least you were here thank you
if the room of truth really exists i'll
be there when i wake up right
no it's okay you have to go to work it's
okay
[Music]
i totally understand but i'm happy you
were here
thank you very much
hope you had fun watching the stream
and please please be healthy get a lot
of sleep before work okay
don't always push yourself
room of truth
dingo ringo jungkish in random channel
thank you
what really
[Music]
is
that is
i mean on this the reasoning is
understandable
[Music]
i don't know
remember the fandoms i was in as a child
and kfb is no different hope it lasts as
long as possible but i'll never forget
being here
[Music]
well the people that you supported i'm
sure they're happy
if they knew that
hopefully
it will be the same for me
looking for the top down question
anonymous 247 and thank you for the rest
of the chat and a heart back to you
thank you very much
[Music]
i hope you had a great day today
thank you so much
enjoy the rest of your weekend will ya
jackson fb thank you for writing the
chat as well hi kid i wanted to send
this on the 25th but superchats were
closed i just wanted to thank you and
the chickens for spending birthday with
me this past year has been made so much
better because of you so thank you well
i already sang you happy birthday so i'm
gonna leave it at that but once again
happy birthday and thank you for your
support i'm always happy to have you
here let's make the best out of this
coming here shall we
[Music]
during elven ring evil but i wanted to
say it was a great stream and don't
worry about margin i'm a huge fan of the
dark souls series and that boss was
filtering me too oh please don't put
your foolish ambitions tourists
i say that is like some kind of meme
yeah because they say that in the game
you the best thank you
[Music]
yeah
i i don't know i was kind of led there
by i don't know i feel like the game was
leading me there so
i don't know why but
[Music]
he seems um to me he says very often to
me
one of the few memes that i understand
now
thank you tanaka i'll give it another
try at one point brandon wood thank you
for the pinky my head cut on for a
breath of the wild is the speedrunner
who wakes up in the tank
runs straight to ganon and kills him and
links underwear
yeah i'm sure there's more than one
people one person who tried that before
right
oh
good night
oh good night
it is late
[Music]
um
defend yourself from who your gameplay
was better than many expected suffering
is part of the first soul game you play
so if you have some fun with it i bet
many will enjoy watching you play it
seeing how you tackle the challenge is
why i am here
[Music]
i'm i'm glad you guys enjoyed watching
me suffer
seeing how seeing how you tackle the
challenges why i'm here is another word
for seeing how you suffer through a game
is why i'm here isn't it isn't it
[Music]
well as long as you had fun
thank you for your support miss vistage
in the game mccree thank you steven
breakdown
kitchen for the pinky
finally caught up with the er stream
today and i must say you did very great
for someone new to the soul series you
guys are too nice
looking forward to more er thanks for
sharing your stories with us and thanks
for another roller coaster of emotions
love you buzz thank you
you guys are too nice man too nice way
too nice
yeah my chickens
they know that if they're not kind to me
they will be stuck in the usual room for
forever
[Music]
are you guys
stop
stop i'm gonna blush
lexington the lion dance and put your
legs down danielson fire home with an
oh by chance i had my first double tree
cookie this week it was a tasty cookie
why is it dot dot dot before that i
didn't know that i was booking a double
tree when i made the booking oh wait why
is it just a dot a tasty cookie were you
disappointed
pirate homina where are you explain
yourself
it sounds like you were disappointed
[Music]
did you not like it which which one was
it maybe that hotel [\h__\h] them up maybe
you have to complain to them for [\h__\h]
up the double tree cookie
the emoji is missing no i see the cookie
emoji but then it's like this week it
was dot dot dot tasty cookie
it was fine that's not good enough
that's not good enough do i have to
write a strongly worded letter to that
doubletree hotel that you stayed at
fine it's not enough tata you just use
it a lot yeah
don't seem impressed
i i was really excited to share this
cookie recipe with you guys and then you
go and eat the original and you don't
even like it that much
i'm i'm sad
i'm sad i'm devastated
[Music]
it shouldn't be just passable
it should be amazing
you should say it was life-changing
but my mission to you guys is if you
ever look for a hotel somewhere look if
there's a double tree available and then
stay there and then eat the cookie and
tell me how it was because it's life
changing
they're actually so good right
right you get me
if it was made by my hands it would
taste a lot better but it also would
have cat hairs in there so that's that
[Music]
yeah i saw that there they wrote like oh
that's already pla plan the next one
let's do it but i think they want to
play on the next one probably and in an
n a again or well if they tell me early
enough i
i want to try going there too
jim tracy tank joseph thank you
but i already have like a lot of plans
of going to places
in the next couple months so that's that
taipei and dan kashun how confident am i
in you well i'm sending this pinky now
because i know you're about to show your
full power and i may be too blown away
to send it later
as always this has been a great trip
with our powerful and stunningly
beautiful fan show
you guys are just so charming thank you
typhon
thank you thank you very sweet thank you
for the pinky pinky
sorry i couldn't uh take up on your
offer in the end i i decided i'll get
all the pokemon by myself now
[Music]
but
if i ever if i ever struggle too much
with one then i'll hit you up you you
and the other kf people
yeah casanovas assembly of casanovas
that's what kfp is
um black friction duncan
thank you
i'm gonna
skip the flush chats
right ghana thank you for the pinky
though
congress and finish pl8
[Music]
i think he's more than like older than
just being your uncle
he's awful cynthia says volo is awful
he's kind of weird yeah
maybe he's lonely maybe
you know he doesn't seem to have family
around him
oh that's probably what messed him up
having no no parents and [\h__\h] um
can't blame him
the game accretes down cushion daisy
thank you my pinky can you beat pokemon
satan let's go let's go
thank you
who do you mean with pokemon satan volo
or his pokemon
thought about your dinner yet i actually
um have a sandwich
that i bought for a snack in between so
i'm just gonna eat that
yeah
giratina oh that's supposed to be satan
is that like the description of the
pokemon
or you're just deciding that yourself oh
because arceus is god jeretina is satan
he's basically saving the pokemon lord
what
that's interesting
yeah
yeah wow
that's pretty dark
it was banished by our kid yeah yeah he
did that he did do that it rebelled i
guess so
that doesn't necessarily just say that
he's satan but
maybe there's more to that
struck him down and banished him like in
the bible
is that a satanist thing to do
okay so
huh
evil evil evil
[Music]
so what makes what does that make me god
too
am i god now also because i i also
banished a satan into a poke ball he's
in my pokeball now
i control him or do i become satan
because i control satan
somehow that must make me satan
[Music]
dragon's fire thank you for the pinkie
let's go pokemon
thank you for your support as always
thank you i cleared another poker game
[Music]
a second one on this channel
the next one will be end of 2022 i
suppose
[Music]
although i do wonder
oh
[Music]
publisher
nintendo
[Music]
uh
ah
not that one
[Music]
publisher
the pokemon company
pokemon called sam
is one of my favorite pokemon games
i was just wondering who publishes that
hmm
the gym is peaceful it's nice right it's
nice the one on gamecube
yeah
so nostalgic i mean it's actually really
difficult
[Music]
called in a sick day to watch the post
stream oh you didn't have to do that
thank you doll oh my god but it's
already ending
i love that game yeah
i played it with my brother back in the
day oh great cool this best
[Music]
love me gamecube
cynthia and doug joseph
[Music]
and skydiving
thank you
you guys have such good matters
uh
eden excel
do you think i don't recognize your
profile picture
you've made a big mistake
you've made a
big
mistake
[Music]
and i see what you did there
i see what you did
[Music]
he was trying to make me say one of
those
i am a muhammad
[Music]
it's another one that i haven't seen
before
i think
the way of riding it
[Music]
feeling a bit emotional happy you'll
know why so i just want to say kiwa are
you in your streams make me so happy
thanks for being a part of whole life
stick around for as long as possible
maybe it's the long hair so cute
i mean my hair is making you feel
emotional
oh i must use it more often then thank
you
don't worry i'll be
around for as long as i can so i hope
you'll do the same thank you viral
magic thank you for section high health
[Music]
thank you no wait this one i already
read now it's up here
this one too i think have the most prime
done
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
um
[Music]
[Applause]
have you guys seen it
uh
eitan introduced our song like journey
like a thousand years there and said it
was our first
original song and then this person was
kind of confused about it so they they
wanted to
know why myth for treat is not
considered our first song but i feel
like even john just kind of forgot about
it
or or they might consider it like a
myth or treat was like uh
i i compare i compared it to how there's
like indies songs and then there's major
songs from a major level label you know
and i mean cuz like they've been
released in a different way
yeah maybe
or honestly i feel like they maybe just
forgot
yeah it was like a mini meme thing as
well kind of i would say it's unofficial
but
also it was insanely hyped so i don't
know how you could forget about it but i
think she probably just forgot
yeah it can happen
it can happen
[Music]
yeah did you also do the 71 push-ups
i'll be doing 72 as i like even numbers
[Music]
hitting with the ocd thanks for the
great elden ring stream and being you
eres
[Music]
gracias
i think that's saying that i am very
pretty
i think
but that one that one single push-up
will surely
make you buffer than everyone else
audi vertida is funny ah
i see
i'm funny and beautiful well tell me
something new
tell me something new gosh oh my boring
i'm getting bored in here
it's always the same thing just kidding
thank you so classical fighter let me
know when you're done with those
push-ups and i hope you don't end up in
the hospital
i want to see if you're able to do them
martial
[Music]
hey boss it's been a long while there is
some cool magical weapons and elder ring
you may like give you an edge and have
more fun
i mean
just different weapons or even like are
you telling me to do a different class
maybe
i'm glad to see you gave a try and i
hope to see more streams of it hope
you've been well i'll be back soon
what do you mean if i'll be back soon
where are you going
worrying uh mom kiwawa strikes again
where are you going where are you going
going to get milk oh my god come back
come back
different weapons there's blood weapon
and does some good crates and blood
explosion
now answer my other questions
[Music]
don't think he didn't come back you're
still here
you've been promoted at both of your
jobs wow
oh
well i see you on tuesday
or monday not sure i'll see you there
hey promise
[Music]
looking forward to thinking your thing
fried screwdrivers for the pinky hi
danger about er let's say that you were
trolled by the depths you went into that
area really under leveled
yeah blame the diffs
do it
there is actually a beginner's zone
south from where you start just look for
a jumping platform to another island
with your host horse goat thingy a
jumping platform to another island
how
how why would i assume that i would need
to go to another island
who would think of that
[Music]
that that's like
it sounds like so hidden
[Music]
yeah open world game sure but like
if if if someone like me naturally walks
that path
that i did
[Music]
then something's wrong there
they could have like given you a hint or
something that there's like an easy area
somewhere i don't know if maybe like uh
maybe the quest could lead you there
first rather than to them boss
i don't know oh well okay
oh sample duncan
[Music]
we can do but i think she's just gonna
play bloodborne for now
oh but maybe
i don't know it's not co-op and elden
ring as as far as i understand only for
the boss fights
or can you run around together
at all times
[Music]
basically everywhere
outside the boss place
both
oh okay
okay but for that i don't know uh i'll
need extra permission for that
uh make well thank you for the rest of
the chat hold up
last time i sent you a super chat i was
promoted on my work oh so far so good as
i said i'm working and enjoying your
streams also i'm finally a big chicken
in six months so can i ask for a proper
position at the kfp headquarters much
love from your espanol speaking fans
thank you
coin polisher
[Music]
please uh
do your job well work hard
congrats on six months and looking
forward to having you around for much
much much much longer your school
[Music]
yes dream job
sure
and that will make your name really long
i guess you you could you could totally
get rid of the the family in your name
because corn polisher will otherwise
probably be too long
so
[Music]
all according to k-cock
your coin polisher you can be a corn
polisher too
hi
i missed you so much
i missed you so much smoothie
thank you for the red super chat miguel
duncan
wish you good luck slowpoke dance and
welcome back home please be aware of the
big spiders baby one and two purrs are
so adorable
[Music]
cause in the beginning they were called
baby but what about spiders i had
spiders in my room
sorry for being late i had a hard time
finding the stream
oh because that was shadowburn
is that a hint at that
means the end oh
[Music]
really
the ant slowpoke wouldn't make a mistake
like that slowpoke knows what they're
talking about
[Music]
oh big spiders
just saying that because i was saying
i'm going to australia
oh such a big brain
such a big brain
such a big brain man
nice
baby one and baby too
[Music]
advert the dude foundation thank you
thank you
like freaking donation for the pinky
being connected online has led to nobody
invading me in over 18 hours aside from
npc invasions
that's so lonely should i invade you
maybe you could set something up but
wait invasions isn't that like is that
what they call co-op because that sounds
more like somebody's going to come over
and try to kill you
like in death loop
is that a good thing
[Music]
it's the opposite it's that invasion is
pvp
oh wow you really you're really asking
for it aren't you black christian
you want someone to kill you
[Music]
maybe they are there they just didn't
find you
maybe they're lurking
[Music]
well maybe let's set up something up
running through it together as a collab
could be enjoyable
i think kelly said she wanted to call up
well well well
the thing is like i don't know how
regularly i'll play it and i don't know
how regularly cali is playing it
do you not kind of need to be like
at least roughly around the same level
and stuff
[Music]
um
wow
[Music]
i will see
same platform oh no no she's playing on
ps5 she's i know i know she's playing on
ps5
[Music]
create a new character
maybe well well well let's first play
another time on sunday and see how it
goes
how i feel
[Music]
no i don't mean if the game even makes
it possible i mean more like
like generally
if she's like much higher level than me
like
that's
it doesn't sound very balanced but
it would help me a lot i guess
[Music]
you say she'll probably be much better
than isis but who knows she's very busy
working so
she might not have as much time as she
wants
hi smoothie
i'm dance movie i'm pretty much done
[Music]
that's not halloween i don't know what
you mean
and doug joseph danishan
thank you thank you fluffy pillows i'm
looking forward to that
i want to jump into my bed immediately
so hey ask everybody for watching [\h__\h] i
can't jump into bed i need to make my
schedule but if i don't stream tomorrow
then then i can maybe i can have more
time
if i don't stream tomorrow then i can
just put out my schedule tomorrow
she's impeccable timing i know
it's crazy
smart maybe i'll do it tomorrow
because yeah don't think
oh but but but chat do you want to do
something
i can't call in for bail's uh birthday
stream but i told her i'm gonna make a
video
uh wanna record together
you can you can wish for her a happy
birthday here
on in the chat
thank you dylan thank you happy birthday
you're 16 now oh
were you even allowed on youtube before
that hey
[Music]
bingo ringo thank you
wait
what
did i miss some super chats matching
eight i don't recall reading that did
that just come in now
one second i'll check in a moment again
okay
ah
hi
spoofy
one second maybe
meow
there's a melody on
meow audio stock did you hear that
goldie's dog
odie stock
why does it start there
oh this dog
is
[Music]
i feel challenged to write a song
is
[Music]
for this part
for this part i'm gonna write something
you're cute
i won't eat you
please come to my kitchen again
how long is this what the [\h__\h]
one minute 40.
oh my god one second
uh
okay we'll write the song quickly
[Music]
fingers
okay
[Music]
um
when i first
met you
[Music]
i really liked your voice
and your spirit
[Music]
is really
dope okay
[Music]
when i first met you
i really like your voice
and your spirit
is really
dope
yeah
and
happy
birthday to you
now i'll sing it in english the first
time i sing it in no the first time i
sing it in english
second time i sing it in german
[Music]
you're
what do we say what are we saying the
second verse
today is your day
wait
[Music]
hope it goes your way i i'll make it a
bit shorter
i hope it goes your way
[Music]
today is your day
i hope it goes your way
uh
wait what what
eat some good cake
and
share
it
[Music]
and let me sing it in uh
japanese
wait
that's just english though then okay
let's do korean
thank you
okay one more verse
[Music]
one more verse what do we do what do you
do
it's always the same melody
the last one i think
[Music]
listen
take care of your body
you work too hard
sometimes
okay yes
oh that's the end oh we can't end it at
that
we can't end it at that
that end so abruptly
or maybe maybe we'll end it like that
okay maybe we will end it like that
let's test it
[Music]
bye
stay
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear bails happy birthday
to you hey hey
when i first met you
i really like your voice
and your spirit
is
[Music]
today is your day
i hope it goes your way
eat some good cake and share it with
senpai please
[Music]
take care of your body
you've worked too hard
sometimes okay yes
no that's a stupid end
you work too hard um
um
hit me up
when you need me
oh my dad
[Music]
listen before you go
take care of your body
you work too hard sometimes
hit me up when you need me yay okay i
like that one
oh yeah we're recording now we're
recording now we're ready guys
uh wait uh
happy birth
birthday
damn
yes
okay are you ready
it goes up
you gotta spam happy birthday in the
chat
hom bunny goes up
stop
three
two
one
happy birthday
bails
i will
sing
for you now
[Music]
i should have been a bit louder stop
just continue continue chat continue i
already do a bit louder
happy birthday
there are bails
i will sing for you now
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday
[Music]
[Applause]
i really liked your voice
and your spirit
is
[Music]
today is your day
i hope it goes your way
[Music]
thank you
take care of your body okay
you work too hard so hit me up when you
need me
happy birthday bills
shall we look at it
okay i'm shaking i'm like shaking i
don't know why i'm shaking
[Music]
you hear that was my teeth that was my
teeth
that's me happy birthday
they're back
okay here we
[Music]
go now
[Applause]
[Music]
happy birthday to you yes
[Applause]
[Music]
is
it's gonna be like how many
verses are there
[Music]
thank you
you work too hard so hit me up when you
need me
happy birthday
[Music]
i'm shaking
this is good though it's cute
i'll send her that i'll tell her to
watch it on on her stream for the first
time don't watch it before that
i'm shaking i'm shaking
i think i need a break but
i think a few more super chats came in
let me quickly quickly go through them
quickly
just quickly no center you're reacting
to it
no no no no um
ah there we go okay uh option eight
dungeon high tension for elementary
might want to explore a bit more and
maybe
i didn't read that one let me out that
wasn't mapped to eight for the pinky
good luck thank you i'll do my best
thank you thank you i'm not giving up
yet don't worry about it unknown thank
you conduction dylan duncan mrs sanchez
and cherry 3757
hello good morning annyeong good morning
thank you for today's streaming i woke
up just now because i wasn't feeling
well oh
always take care of your health you too
sorry i'm ending the stream right now we
just we just were about to end it just
made a quick song
on the girl thank you though good
morning feel free to watch my archive
okay
miniature picture
thank you for the uh pinky as well
tomorrow is the last day of february a
lot has happened this month hmm i hope
everyone always stays healthy and happy
next month but you know what
you know what oh my god aren't you guys
like realizing what happens
next month
is
is the concert
and the first time you're gonna see us
in in 3d
holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h] it's next month
and next month is like in two days oh my
god oh my god holy face
and i get to
oh my god that's so exciting 20 days oh
my god only [\h__\h] 20 days
it's not even at the end of the month
it's like somewhere in the middle slash
end
yup spanking and thank you for the rest
of the chat i wasn't working all that so
i have no idea what's going on right now
and i think that's the next major hit
single from takanashikiya that's right
that's right
yeah that must have been confusing to
come into
bamboozle good morning or so
have fun at work
thank you black friday
you guys didn't have to send super chats
for that but did you make it in did you
make it into the video i wonder
did it work out for you
uh okay and skye duncan okay and
speaking of dancing now i'm gonna go now
i'm gonna thank you everybody
i'll see you on tuesday i'll put out a
schedule on monday i think tuesday will
be a really early stream so in ferry for
n a it will be a monday evening late
evening stream actually
um
as you've seen maybe um
yeah
for n a i'll see you monday evening
i'll work hard to
make the selections for the omo cat
collabing i'll work on that probably
for the whole day tomorrow besides doing
the kitchen thing
i still have to clean the kitchen now
[\h__\h]
and then i also put up the whole talk uh
question thing
[Music]
thank you take care of yourself thank
you
thank you thank you you too that's your
heart working
yeah i just i just do i just do what
needs to be done
thank you
take care have a good rest thank you
you couldn't
thank you enjoy your cat cuddling and
restaurant you too
take one skeleton to thank you you too
take care please
thanks for your hard work today thank
you for watching
hope your kitchen goes well
i'm excited i'm excited i asked them to
add like a like a like a electricity
slot thingy on top of the counter so
i thought that would be helpful for
streaming and for cooking
it costs extra but big brain big brain
sometimes calls extra
can i go numbers yes you get an outlet
yeah yeah
okay
okay there i go pokemon sayonara it was
fun
uh playing this game
uh i hope i i'll be able to play the the
gen 9 game
uh scarlett i'll go for skelet
yeah let's hope that the time until then
passes by
um
quickly for the sake of playing another
pokemon game but slowly for the sake of
making the best out of this year yeah
i'm stuck
i'm torn oh well
let's enjoy every day as if it was our
last one okay
thank you guys for watching and in
germany we say i'll be done bye
cupcake
[Music]
do
you