[Music]
so
do
[Music]
i'm
already in the game i thought we wanted
to show like the characters off and uh
yeah no no no okay oh
you're out of the game yeah like just in
the in the loading
just like the character select yeah
well okay okay all right i'm gonna show
you guys the characters
we played this game before a while ago
but back then we played it with
normal characters however one of the kfp
members called zero duke shout out to
zero duke
has made mods for all of us
as you can see we're using them um each
of our characters are now modded into
the game
and each character has like not only
these these cute outfits
but also like special like skills
and and and i don't know funny um
interactions yeah powers yeah i mean
guna doesn't have much power
apparently yeah
stream guys
and i think every character also has a
little variation for example here i can
take off my hats and then says i agree
but i also don't understand a famous
quote by takana shikiyada
i'm not sure if the taking off the hats
or whatever uh
changes their skills well anyway i'm
gonna go with the regular clothes out of
your way
are we ready to jump in everyone i'm
classmates
a halo or no halo kit yeah and
are no tentacles or tentacles always
there if you need no
that's not just my onion ring
deep-fried halo here we go
[Music]
this is how we're gonna do things this
is really cute too
like yeah why why is it when i take your
hat off all it says is onion
but what does that mean because we have
noticed that when i take off my hats
um i look like an orange onion you know
that is true i can see that
well well we're ready to join and play a
little bit oh by the way
the announcements will be um at the end
of the stream but we won't play for too
long so don't worry guys
just play around with the characters
yeah yeah okay
let's test them out yeah okay okay okay
oh
then she loses sanity when i'm too close
to her body
oh no it's what we do
is
much better okay
[Music]
you guys want to dance with me yes how
do you do if you press
why
oh
[Music]
okay
juice you gotta pick up flowers and
that'll help your brain juice get bigger
okay brain juice uh eat nice adorable
you can eat seeds and berries but
if you build a crock pot it's like
better because you're making full meals
oh
i can go into water but i get weaker or
something wait how did you go into the
water
they're aquatic wait what i can't go
there even though i should be supposed
to i don't know
hide your dynamic i can see my god
i'm open but i've gotta be more to do
that okay
okay
there's
turkey legs
thank you
okay i died
[Music]
is
i didn't do anything i just died and
revived myself no it's because of you
it's because of your i
am frog that's why all these frogs are
here i swear it's written into the
coating
and frog yeah exactly it's all yours
chicken leg with the frogs they're easy
to kill
if you make a rabbit trap but i think we
might need to make some pineapples i
love the rabbit truck
uh i can haunt things
another tree
let's haunt the girls here i am here let
me look at you oh that's so cute
everyone has their own like individual
little picture
girl's got a floaty too that's so cute
what about me what do i have
where are you girls i want to show you
my ghost form
where are you
yeah i can use soul strike i need to
read more to do that
i don't know how to use my ground pound
oh i see something see the watson ground
pounds
[Music]
is
but it doesn't really do anything
however i'm waiting for my cooldown down
to revive again
so then everything around me will burn
wow that's cool it's getting a little
bit late so i'm gonna head back
here oh does anybody have wood that's
okay i can make a small i have
more chocolate yes that's not healthy
[Laughter]
i have some carrots we made a really
awesome pot
before i'm kind of thinking about it
again it was a crocodile
yeah yeah yeah we have to burn um trees
we have to burn stuff
yeah what does it do is that a tree
normally oh i guess i can do that
i'm killed how do i get political spots
what
why is it i have the most health out of
everybody so
with great power comes great
responsibility how do i revive
normal um
you could try on the gate maybe
some more no stop there's some oh i
found a mole
i can't actually hit this with my scythe
that's unfortunate it's very accurate
you can't just have trades with the site
how do i gain health back uh i have
a an injection i can give you if you
would like some help
i have 20 health oh it's countless okay
okay
all right
oh it's giving me a toilet
no eat this carrot
oh my okay
what is that where are you off oh
oh you're puffed easy whoa look at that
go
yes here you go ina drop wait hold on
drop
it you're welcome
[Music]
wait was that supposed to hear me oh
yeah uh the watch compaction i think so
did it not work i just sent me on a
really cool
[Music]
oh
my future
all right so let me see i can probably
look at it you can make that
make a rabbit trap and you can lead the
frog into the rabbit trap and it'll die
nice idea uh i want to make rabbit traps
because
i was getting pretty good at that before
actually let's see oh yeah you're just
fishing around
twix what aggressive rod you need um
you need spider web spider webs i was
thinking good i would be
good with that oh i'm fishing a
minecraft
are
we need to find gold so if anybody has
gold i'll
find the gold mine twigs
[Music]
hunting is my specialty wait you can't
come back alive
i i did it i came back to live once but
now i die i
died again and now i have a super long
cooldown so i'm just waiting for the
cooldown
but then everyone has to come to lunch
so you see how i revive you have to see
it
yeah okay it's me tell me what hang on
maybe 60 seconds left
i'm coming over i'm on my way i went
just see christopher revive
yeah i would like to also see but you
have to have the same distance like
social distance
because everything around me will burn
can we get balloon
got it just like that one time in mind
i'm gonna die for this
[Music]
oh
i'm sorry i'm sorry my dog your
assistant's watching i can send you to
another place
are you dead forever
you guys will have i have to guide you
okay you have to find a touchstone
so you have to explore or you'll have to
build a resurrection heart
wouldn't you need another sport in the
swamp habitat
are there monsters in the water uh it
depends
in some areas there's the ocean i think
there's monsters in the ocean but not in
the rivers
i want to get rid of my sword but i'll
probably die
okay i'll i don't think so can i
hurt them something when you don't know
oh no is it my big flowers i'm getting
stupider
i want my sword back i'm in let's go huh
crystal funny water is here good night
[Music]
oh there's a drumstick yeah that's from
cali she killed the turkey
can i not eat right now yeah i'm i'm
hungry i was really proud of that
you know that i'm really proud of that
killing that turkey
there's a lot of spiders over here and a
gold if you guys want to come over here
oh there's a watermelon
yeah yeah oh my god
everything i'm gonna go lazy mushroom
okay
i'm to the west from the west
[Applause]
is
but we need some stone i dropped like
six stone i think but with six more
stone we can make
pretty quickly oh my god i'm just gonna
eat them
oh i dropped some food if you guys need
to eat it i dropped carrots and
berries yes thanks because i'm really
not feeling great okay
where is where are you going make a
campfire okay
follow me oh it's going to be late too
yeah i don't have enough stone
or wood i don't know some rocks
here contemporary fire oh how many guys
wait can i make a campfire do you see
that yeah you can make it
i think you need flint and logs
oh never mind i didn't need to do that
my body
oh can i eat my skeletons
[Music]
although you can see me right i can see
you
i cook
but i got some food for you look at me
i'm gonna stay away from the house
because uh food yes
you guys stay over there now kelly stay
over there i don't want to lower your
sanity because if there's a ghost nearby
it'll like lower your cindy i'll just go
wait really
the texts are so cute though the things
that they say
so adorable okay okay
[Music]
how did you think i died what do you
mean but i told you to go farewell away
oh nice nice thank you oh my goodness
this is something
you
all right
gold here so yeah you get that and then
okay you can set up rabbit traps for the
spiders and then
yeah i'm really not doing anything for
them
[Music]
oh
i killed it
you can make health sounds if you burn
like small stuff and make ash and you
can mix it with the spider glands to
make like a booster shot
the ultimate guys
there's so much good [\h__\h] here oh my god
[Music]
i'm a little closer
oh wait can i not actually die you're
immortal yeah
you're just sleeping like you like you i
want to attack you all the time
you guys are ghosts too no
i'm gonna go okay okay
cool you guys are now
eating monkeys
[Music]
we won't get any of the spider web from
it
i i
i need to wake up and eat first it needs
to be the first thing i do
already kelly kelly are you okay kelly
oh no there's more i'm not going to test
me
to be honest no okay pick up the stuff
that i left please scoot out or someone
uh it's gonna be dark soon so if you
guys have some um
to go back to go pick up the glasses
for now this big of the spider webs if
you see any those are useful
yeah i got a lot of those bad buddies
make a fire
yeah i think you need 12 stone to make a
permanent fire
oh okay
i'm moving it for you
wait you being near me is lowering my
sanity
[Music]
i hate the monster me
oh wow there's a really big oh my gosh
attack the crawling horde
and i hit it with my soul scythe
[Applause]
[Music]
thank
so many creepy
i think we're all gonna die probably
it's okay
i don't think we're actually trying to
accomplish much today we're just trying
to showcase these
and then have some announcements so it's
okay if we don't accomplish too much
it's the torches
[Music]
i mean i'm still here but that's because
i have to be i can revive
in like five minutes
just give me five minutes i'll save all
of you dad
no don't maybe we should go to another
timeline yeah
[Music]
okay
i want to go hunting should i come to
you to help you
i'm gonna make the crock pot uh
i don't think i can be saved anymore
i'm a little uh dead why can't i
what it's dark here we want to do this
thing now
well it makes sense maybe we should have
like a
like a ghost meeting um what do you call
it like talk really far
[Music]
alone in this universe because i can't
die why is kelly still
sleeping
[Music]
just wait for me okay i'll wait for you
please
please tell me they can't flip you see
they can't
[Music]
i mean haunted yeah this one's really
cute is the game
it knows how to mine please no
i want to live oh my god you just got
this shark cat on top of you that's so
funny
that one's fast hello yeah
split me in a swim it can slim
here girls try to when
[Music]
the only way we can respond is if we
find a thing in the map called a
touchstone
or we have to make um these revive
potions thingies but it's yeah it's
gonna be hard with me because i can send
you to kind of go to sleep over and over
again which is
which is actually kind of worse than not
being able to die
so look how the frog is right next to
you it's like that's me
oh yeah and you're also right next to me
away with you
still alive i'm having a really bad time
for enos
anything though yes i am dead
we're all dead give me the seeds i'm
just trying i'm just living off of seeds
to be honest at this point
oh my god please
oh my gosh
[Music]
you okay you okay you okay sorry
you're okay
running like not a problem in the world
i am invincible oh that's so cool your
book
your book
where's my side where am i you get to
keep picking up flowers
i lost my sense of direction where's my
goal where's my sword
right has anyone seen this ancient ones
you killed them
[Music]
wait what happens when i lose myself
uh you start going crazy and start
seeing monsters and they start attacking
you and then you die
okay cool okay she's like a manga
i'm going to lure a spider here what how
is this like among us is
[Music]
[Applause]
left okay anyone bottom oh yeah it
doesn't look like
their head okay hey there's a lot of
flowers over here but there's a lot of
also deadly bees if anyone wants sanity
i'm probably fine go bottom
[Music]
are there like caves and stuff in this
game um
i think there are caves in single player
but because of the way caves work
it's not easy to do with multiplayer so
there's
i picked up the trident oh well it's not
gonna revive anymore anyway yeah i'm
just gonna use it
maybe we can find a touchstone we should
do that try to look for a touchstone it
looks like a coffin
uh surrounded by a sticks with pig heads
on it
must be somewhere don't find one those
are my seats
are they nearby or typically
it's like random you got it you found it
that's all right wait don't don't use it
all up though i can't find it
at all don't worry i'm just keeping it
safe because yeah you are ghost
how do you need to be charged i'm gonna
recharge it
oh my god i think you can recharge it
but i think you need like some electric
new dad or something
oh i found this area this is good for
something oh
okay oh i can make this awesome actually
yeah
yeah is that what we need at the bottom
of the top
where the [\h__\h] um
yeah i've lost my [\h__\h] way the way
you're going in if you keep going
straight past that water and you keep
going
you'll see it's this one there okay i'm
gonna google it
the heck is
how about we all just die hmm
how's
okay okay it's really easy all right
callie
all right callie
what should i do tell me what i must do
what we need is um
spider glands do you have any of those
yeah i killed a bunch of [\h__\h] spiders
okay um okay
okay if you have spider glands we need
three grass
and if you go into like the tabs on the
left side you should see a heart
and you might it's called a telltale
heart and you should be able to make one
it's gonna take some hp and you'll die
but then you can resurrect one of us
with the heart oh yeah sure thing
i got your bag demon show yourself
you're basically the reason i died
but is this what's his payback is that
why you followed me the whole time
i'm too hungry no no no
where's the goddamn fence all right i'm
gonna sleep again i'll i'll do it it's
just
i can't find my way back so that's okay
oh it was right there oh yeah just just
haunt me for a while
he goes down when seeing ghosts
considering who i am but
oh yeah it's just a little overspray
just a little oversight
yeah i love that the book talks i love
it souls should uh
those should boost your sanity instead
yeah they give me like
like souls yeah exactly i love seeing
this taking away sanity from other
people
oh yeah wait no
did you get standing after me
[Laughter]
really quick if i cook the meat then
it'll be fine
i can definitely make those things
though two ghosts walk into a bi
what do what do they do
let's grasp without the cheese
oh my god oh my god oh my god
i'm so funny i'm such a
i have no grass that's the problem you
know it's really hard to think of jokes
like that in english because it's not my
main language no
not my mother tongue so i would like to
praise myself
i'm proud of you i'm so proud
i left some uh one spider gland close to
the
gate really close to the gate because i
died there and i dropped it so there's a
there's a spider gland there
okay guys i have a little problem so i
want to help you
but when i open the tab i don't see any
heart or anything like that
uh it should be under survival the news
oh it's under survival okay got it
oh yeah
okay this is like the survival knot i
don't know
the survival because survival survival
isn't
good news i need ashes
and that's the problem is that i need
ashes and actually i need
ashes
i will revive you guys leave it to me
just i need to make sure you're right
now
why is it not kelly you need a spider
gland and three and
a half all right wait we're not gonna
turn in the grass
some of us should have a ton of grass
because i picked up a bunch so there
should be some here by the heat
yeah okay i got three grams of whole
bunch here yeah
yeah there's grass right here hang on
there's a turkey there's a turkey i'm
going to kill it really quick
how do i open the 16 grass right here
16 grass i can
i know right i got one spider gland
what am i here
uh we need one spider glam per person so
there's another spider glenn by the
spiders too
and so i'm gonna go beat up some spiders
then but i need to get back to the gate
first
wait is
uh yes i do but it's not marked on there
oh wait i can see where everyone is
though yeah
okay
so how do i make one potion is it in
survival
yeah it's in survival it's called
telltale heart and it's gonna take 40 hp
so it's probably gonna kill you
oh cool oh my god oh okay now one of us
can
can rest you can raise one of us if you
use it on us you know you want to go
first wait look
you can go first you're more
knowledgeable okay come here i'll revive
you because i'm in phoenix this is this
is very fitting yeah
you killed me and you should make it i
don't know what to do
uh
okay that's okay because we have
spiderweb and twigs
now oh i think someone's gonna tell you
you can make it
here you make it there you go
so you want okay i guess
who wants to come back
can we get everyone back to live before
uh in seven minutes because
uh that would be a nice day yeah
that was everyone being revived oh thank
you
[Music]
oh i bought it
it's going to be dark soon though so oh
yeah
does anybody have two stones i have four
rocks i don't know if that's that cause
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oysha
thank you
have that one and then just vibing
okay fine i'll go pick up all done
can we do a group picture once kuda is
back alive i want to do a group picture
with everyone
your in-game watching screen
there's no chicken too close there's no
such thing as being too close
this is luffy get away oh we also i'm
not supposing
oh no wait no it's going up wait it's
going up
oh it's going up actually uh-huh yeah
cause we're by the fire
oh okay huh oh yeah right okay
guys wow
barbara give us a sign
barbara give us a sign mary davis
hello how old are you mother efforting
mary davis
[Music]
okay okay we can go
oh there's a ground here yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Applause]
i can't pick it up because i keep going
sleeping
you still have that problem
there's another gland there kiara if you
want to get that one
how you doing oh this one i'm just gonna
oh over there i see it
oh god come here i'm here
[Music]
okay god damn it
i'm running does anybody have over 40 hp
i do oh okay if we have two glands then
we can rest chiara with the heart
oh i cannot be alive before we do
announcements
nice oh my goodness can we do it in four
minutes
yeah yeah we can pick up that other
spider gland in the nest
everybody gets that one that was there
nice
i got one okay oh okay nice okay we have
two okay yeah and then i have enough
grass
yeah yeah this should work and i have i
have ashes as well don't do any dashes
uh well if we were to keep playing we
would need them because then we could
use it to heal to make like heal stuff
oh i see oh that's right yeah the
healing one okay
never mind then all right i'm gonna drop
my [\h__\h] here okay
okay let's see here's the gland all
right sure
oh
[Music]
stupid frogs okay
i'll drop it on the ground for you so
here you go all right yeah
do you have grass for it um
i think nope okay don't do it over here
go somewhere else
okay so you know let's get it and then
good evil rings me
three two one
it won't chase you that far so just go
oh there it is
okay it's fine yeah it takes hp now
red is good enough i need to heal i'm at
4-hp now
that's fine nothing's going to attack
you
i'll i'll kill the [\h__\h] you can't build
the heart
how do i use it you just click on it and
give it to good uh
if you can catch me oh
not that yeah okay
again so oh kill it i'm back in hp
almost oh my god oh my god
um we can do well let me build a fire
here too
okay everybody press y and then when in
the typing box you can type forward
slash
dance and we can all line up and we can
all dance at the same time
forward slash dance bar
ready for now for the photo ah
yes i'm gonna get a little bit covered
up for my size
am i flossing i'm sorry
just get in the line right here okay
next stop
all right next to me
i'll go on this side the same way i'm
facing hope
i'm going to the right like this yeah
you might have to rotate your
perspective if
oh like you know oh we can't yeah
wait is this okay
at least in my description so if you
want to use the mods and they're in the
description
shout out to them one more time thank
you for making the mods now it's okay
thank you
announcement thank you thank you and
that's the time
[Applause]
okay
whole live english myth half year
anniversary unbelievable but it's been
six months can you believe it guys oh my
god
yay exciting so of course we prepared
uh some things for you many things
actually and we hope you will like it
yeah and we will start off
with uh the second slide everyone move
on to the second side
as you can see we got a whole live
english myth acrylic stands
merchandise
english myth mascot penta keychain
[Music]
acrylic stand yay
absolute standing standing perfect okay
so with these stamps
um you can buy them separately or you
can buy them together i say buy them
together so that way we can all be
together and we won't get lonely and we
won't miss one another
you can put these on your table you can
put this on your desk above your bed
you can get creative and then send us i
guess send those pictures about how you
plan on displaying them that would be
really fun
[Applause]
yeah i don't know how big they are but
yeah hopefully you think they'll be life
size
no unless you are
10 centimeters big
maybe for girl well well
uh next slide everyone
and uh it's being introduced by ina
this is our second merch it's gonna be
our mascot
the five in one key chain you get all
five of those charms at once yeah
it's gonna be um put on a leather strap
i think and it's gonna
the leather strap is gonna have the
hollow life english logo
and yes very cute five in one what a
deal
adorable yeah
the key chains it's possible that we
won't have like a second
um like a second wave of orders so
only one wave of orders okay get a
[\h__\h]
yes yeah better get them the first time
yeah
i mean it's not it's not completely
impossible but
prob probably no second yeah unlikely
yeah
yeah so the page to buy these will show
up at
booth at uh 5 p.m pst
which is 8 30 pm
in 30 minutes from now on yeah yes yes
yes it will be on geek
and on booth both and just follow check
the official twitter for the links and
uh the announcements that's alright
you would think
however kelly oh wait
oh it's my turn okay well i guess
um um it's it's i'm supposed to
introduce this one but we uh have a
little
it's actually more of um sorry big
stretch
it's actually uh we're gonna let it do
uh the talking itself and then talk
about it afterwards yeah
indeed um so anyway i guess we'll go
ahead and kind of count it down
but uh you guys um you guys will all get
to
see in real time with us is something
real special
something real special coming extra soon
okay
so everyone shut up i'm gonna meet you
guys really quick yeah
and then click on go okay it's very
important okay
okay okay so ready okay four
three
[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
yes indeed let's go let's move right
along to the next one
so this is
an image soundtrack for a whole live
english myth
[Applause]
very special our own very special uh i
guess
image bgm made for us it's instrumental
um i think we'll actually probably be
using them in streams i know i will at
least
because bgm that was kind of the
intention but you guys can also
get it for yourselves as well releasing
everywhere march 14th
local time for you wherever you are 2021
so uh get it or be be square yeah
a lot of people ask but yeah there's no
vocals there's a bgm
cali rapping oh yeah
oh man am i going to rap to this like oh
okay it's bgm but still hey
um and all tricks are made by uh
camellia
hmm
uh suits each person so i think we maybe
want to get a little give a little
comment what do you think about your
song callie
freaking dope when i heard it for the
first time i was like wow this is like a
combination of um everything that i
think makes up me it's got
like this kind of regal and like um
almost like a
gothic tone to it i guess dark
it's also [\h__\h] dope i don't know yeah
it's gangster there's a little bit of
hip-hop in there yeah
i like i can bob my head to it which is
like the title is really good
um
it's perfect for me what about you guys
and my second channel is mine yeah
it's i love how the title actually
um is like for it stands for kfp it's
kiara fry fry
party i think
[Music]
you can also say like at a party you can
be like oh
i get all the other popular kids and the
clubs are like
yeah raised raised raise the volume
raise the roof
yeah and uh my song is
my song is pretty energetic pretty happy
pretty
kawaii cute bobby poppy puppy style
so i'm really excited to um have that
being played in the kfp
stores all over the world worldwide
franchise obviously so it's going to be
played in every store
for until we all die yes
the first tracking track
yes uh i really like mine because it has
like kind of like the oriental feel
field
it's like really chill and i can listen
to it like forever on loop
i probably will i really really really
like it
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you i was
bopping to it while i was playing while
i was playing i was like
still good yeah yeah and fourth track is
i think good ass track right target
adventure with the delicious absolutely
delicious finger looking good baseline i
get the i get the spank face every time
i hear it
the first time i heard that i was
the rhythm gamer census
you gotta play it very loud get that
bass line to full potential it's like
super funky
your song it got dad
and it's got the i think it's the
shamasan maybe also it's got
my favorite instrument and the bassline
and i melt when i hear it and then i i
dance to the beat i'm just i'm in love
with it i'm over the heels
yeah the last one is mine and it sounds
like a pop
yeah it sounds i don't know it kind of
sounds like a nostalgic like it almost
sounds like a song from like an older
game
this is really nice and it's called miss
t
this like mysteries yeah i thought it
was a typo and i
[Laughter]
yeah i love all the drugs like i'm gonna
be having it on loop
for like five yeah all of them in my
playlist immediately
i think this is slam dunk i think it's
the first time that
like some like whole life members like
release
like just like background ost like kind
of music just a soundtrack
normally everyone releases songs with
their singing in it but we
we're going to do things a little bit
different right i mean would be cool if
one day we also have songs together
where we actually singing
yeah but for now take this team
[Music]
hey is that what every soundtrack means
like image soundtrack just means like
yeah it's like yeah like like uh
yeah it's like concept art but like yeah
but like music concept songs
your life's if you if your life had a
bgm it's it's fun
one of my goals was actually to make bgm
for all of you guys but it looks like
a punch that's not like the album cover
i'm just looking at it now it's like a
shield and then it has
the size and like the tentacles and the
cards really cool yeah
magnifying glass the middle is
my shield is like in the middle
protecting all of you from danger
yeah yeah yeah like another portal
oh yeah
[Laughter]
that leads you into the darkness the
rabbit hole of her life
with that being said i know we're all uh
very excited but there is
actually one more thing
yet okay after my drum roll then you
guys can show okay okay
okay drum roll please
[Music]
mascot plushies
recently actually the reason why i asked
my viewers like
two weeks ago or three weeks ago for a
name is for this
and we named it
actually it's actually a really smart
place on my name
because takanashi my last name normally
is read as koto di
so it has two ways to read it so
actually
we write it differently for this one but
actually my takanashi can be right it's
cool totally too
funny funny thing oh it's cute
yeah and it loves a little feather at
the top too it's got a hat with you
and then we have bubba
it's like an anime scene like a battle
scene it's like
he chose his eyes
and then we have a academy's death
sensei
destiny and then we have guinness bloop
they're all so cute it looks like he's
about to commit very very very very
illegal crime
as the document comes blue nothing's
happened
[Laughter]
i'm so excited please coming soon
i'm gonna be hugging them all night
once i get them i'll try to stack them
up yeah i wonder if they can stand on
top of each other
i wanna buy multiple let's do a
balancing contest
you can balance them on top of each
other
yeah yeah no cheating no cheating you
have to there can't be any support
around them
you just need to be on top of each other
winner gets
i don't know my endless love and
affection maybe if i feel like
oh that's
did we say that did we mention that
these are designed by inna
oh yeah luna designed these yeah
designed all of
i'm looking forward to my thick fat ass
burp i'm
i'm excited to grill it
you know i think if you burn it i don't
think it'll come back
yeah probably not maybe don't do that
i want all of them i'm gonna put all of
them on my bed
well yeah so that is uh key chains that
then the
acrylic stands and then the album and uh
the plushies yeah lots of stuff welcome
to
lots of just to look forward to again
details will be posted
on twitter and i think uh if you're not
on twitter then maybe we'll do community
posts or i don't know probably also
gonna be on the under hole
um maybe i don't know um but if you if
you're not on twitter i'll probably
put a link in my description in the
future streams maybe the other girls
will do that too
yeah yes exciting
i had so much fun drawing them also
please look forward to it
okay thank you very nice
well then that was pretty much it thank
you everyone
for joining in on the streams today for
celebrating together with us
does anyone here have some individual
announcements that have nothing to do
with the merchandise then do it now
yeah okay so basically
first i just want to say to everyone uh
thanks so much
for your support in the chat super chats
will be read next time
next time okay so look forward to that
uh at the in the just chatting and also
um my my new ep is coming out
very soon yeah um yeah birthday secret
my birthday yes that's right it's coming
out on my birthday uh so please
anticipate it
um i'm working really hard on it and you
can actually pre-order it
um as well uh you can check my twitter
for the link i'm gonna go ahead and
retweet it again after this
you can pre-order a physical copy get
special stickers
it does ship overseas um
and uh yeah if you don't want to get a
physical copy because
overseas shipping is uh kind of scary i
understand that
um you can just go ahead and stream it
as well
it'll be coming to all streaming
platforms um on the same day
yeah exactly so so you guys can check it
out there
um please check it it would really it
would really make uh my day and make my
birthday really happy if you could at
least
give it a shot give it a little listen
just a little listen you know
whatever yes so yeah look forward to it
that's the only announcement that i
guess besides announcements everyone can
also just say a nice message
so i move on with ammo
yeah uh yeah i wanted to like talk a
little bit like about how six months
have been for us and stuff like that
uh for me i don't know how life has been
like kind of life-changing
i know a lot of you guys too it's like
so much work
and i don't know i'm really grateful to
be with you guys too because i think
everybody like we just contribute so
much to
the group in general and
everybody also who worked on hololive
like behind the scenes and stuff
all this stuff too everybody puts in so
much work
so i want to thank you guys for six
months and more months to come
and we'll do it again on the one year
anniversary yeah we'll have more stuff
but yeah thank you guys so much for the
past six months i really appreciate it i
don't have any announcements other than
that okay
i would like to announce i love you all
i could
ask
[Laughter]
thank you let's do our best from now on
too
yes love you all
thank you for everyone's hard work
okay yeah that's it
okay
um um i i also i guess would like to say
the same
uh-oh okay uh i would also like
i'm emotional that's all i would like to
say
oh my god
say thank you to this absolutely
incredible
team of the most lovely people my gen
mates that have changed my life for the
better
i'm really lucky to be surrounded by
such really great people did you write
something did you write a letter
no actually
to you guys each one of you you've been
so incredible
and i want to say thank you to all of
you that are watching no matter where
you come from oh
[Laughter]
think that's okay
well uh from my side um i'm
celebrating the half year anniversary in
a
few hours when i don't know 15 10 10 i
don't know how many hours
uh with a whole life original songs only
karaoke i've been learning a lot of
songs
from our senpais to show them to you
guys tomorrow
today oh i heard a kitty cat is that oh
that's my cat oh
that's my cat yeah and um i also
just uh i'll probably get more into deep
detail about how i feel
about uh this half year uh in that
stream but generally i just want to say
i hope that uh when when we do our one
year anniversary
that we can all be together in one room
and just hug each other
and yeah you know that would be really
nice because now i hear gouda
cry now makes me sad i want to hug her i
wish i could hug her
let's work towards that making that a
reality making for dear reality making
new outfits our reality and making a
long long
uh future together with us and with some
co-highs as well
and a reality and making whole live
english even bigger than it already is
yeah yeah let's do it i love you thank
you
[Music]
wait a minute i want to give a sappy
message too
um actually i'm really bad at the sappy
stuff but i just want to say
i just want to say i really wanted to do
creative stuff full-time when i was just
a reaper
and because of everyone's really kind
support i was able to get
the chance to do that uh but i wouldn't
have been able to continue on
uh like this if it weren't for you guys
i definitely couldn't have done it alone
so
thank you guys for having my back
for being great gem mates i don't i
think that um
i mean i can't even imagine a world
where anyone else
um where anyone is not here or
different or anything like that yeah um
i don't want to
uh because everything just kind of fell
into place exactly
i feel like how it how it should have
been um
and i'm just really grateful thank you
so much i'm glad that it's us fun
i'm so glad to have the exactly these
members hey
yeah i'm gonna give you a hug so badly
here
let's do it someday it's a promise okay
let's do it yes
no running please do it yes
i promise i do want to give one last
thanks to to the viewers yeah like good
my goodness
and it's really yeah the support you
guys all show all of us
is crazy so many people from all around
the world to me that's like the most
mind-boggling thing that's just from
everywhere people are watching and uh i
really appreciate it i know everybody
else does too
so thank you guys for your support we
wouldn't be here without you guys
thank you wouldn't be able to do this at
all actually yeah
thank you yeah and then it's teammates
taco
buddies and kfb
many many fun memories from now on as
well together
yes yes let's do it
all right then i think okay that's it
yeah yeah we're gonna have an
after party privately right on discord
yeah
so thank you everyone for watching thank
you
thank you thank you thank you so much on
the flip side
and in germany
[Music]
okay oh my god i made an uh
you