[Music]
May in the
morning
[Applause]
[Music]
could find me in
the your
[Music]
fore
Wonderland
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
[Applause]
speee
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
wonder
I'm name
[Music]
fore
me in your
[Music]
[Applause]
Wonderland
[Music]
[Applause]
I
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
foree for
take
[Music]
speee
[Applause]
fore
L God
[Music]
forgive I
the
[Applause]
[Music]
CU
[Applause]
fore
[Music]
foree
[Applause]
he
[Music]
took
so
[Music]
he
[Applause]
[Music]
foree
me
[Music]
[Applause]
all
good morning afternoon
evening welcome to my birthday live yay
it's finally
happening thank you guys for being so
patient I know this was originally
planned for around May around my
birthday but it's finally happened
happening in
December thank you so much everyone for
being patient and supporting me so this
could happen thank you so so much staff
son for all your hard
work I'm so happy and I'm so nervous can
you
[Laughter]
tell so did you guys enjoy the first two
songs uh Wonderland and the Wonderland
is uh Ms songs it's not ena's live
without an MS song
I don't think it's as well known but
it's definitely one of my favorite songs
by her so I wanted to perform it for you
guys someday and delete It's actually an
insert song in The Sword Art online
movie um ordinal scale and I really like
the song in the movie and I you know I
wanted to perform it for you guys
coincidentally too they're both composed
by Yuki kajur asan which I'm a really
big fan of cuz she has a magical scent
for creating these these mysterious yet
mythical mythical
songs yeah and as you can see we're kind
of in a monochrome world you be like hey
did did they forget to add in the colors
to this this place like what's happening
but you know I it's intended I always
said before that before I joined Hall
live and all the world kind of looked
Bland and monochrome But as time went on
here I met all wonderful F members
wonderful staff and became a lot more
colorful so I wanted to kind of add that
into the special life my first birthday
live so yeah maybe you know if we go
down this live we'll find some color
again and of course I got to mention the
title of the live Neverland Paradox it
sounds very difficult but if you break
it down Neverland it's kind of this IM
imaginary Ideal World that's not
supposed to exist but if it doesn't
exist why do we know about it why how
it's a paradox so you know kind of like
that let's pretend that this world here
right here is Neverland and we'll uh go
down this journey together yeah
together anyways if you want to talk
about this live somewhere let me see the
comments later too #a Ena never land #a
Neverland is it here is it here is it
here
somewhere so tweet about it tell your
friends it's happening Ina's first
birthday life
yay
anyways anyways I hope you'll have a lot
of fun during the live let's enjoy our
trip through Neverland together never
everland never ever Neverland never ever
never ever ever Neverland
yeah let's
[Music]
go
fore
[Music]
spee
speee
[Music]
fore
foree
[Music]
fore took
secet
[Music]
fore
could
[Music]
hallelu
[Applause]
[Music]
a
don't she
[Applause]
[Music]
hi hi
[Applause]
[Music]
for
[Applause]
[Music]
speee
for
hi
fore
[Music]
ohon
hi hi fore
spe
fore
[Music]
foree
fore
fore for Fore
spe
[Music]
fore
very
[Music]
for up
there
[Music]
for
[Applause]
foree
[Music]
for
your
[Music]
for I
know
[Music]
fore
come me
walk
[Music]
to see know
good like the
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
spee
[Applause]
[Music]
for
Kash
[Applause]
[Music]
kiss shall we
dance
my this is
[Music]
the
n
[Music]
n la
la
[Music]
yes shall we dream
you this is the
sh
dance this is the light
[Music]
sh
la
[Applause]
[Music]
shall we
smile this is the light Shadow light
[Music]
[Applause]
la la la la la
[Music]
la la la la la la
la la la la la la la la
[Music]
la
I'm look God that
[Music]
fore
youe
[Music]
speee
foree
[Applause]
[Music]
fore that of your
heart
[Music]
[Applause]
Mee
for
[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
foree so you
could
oh hi welcome
back that was do quite a lot of songs
and look we got some color back what
color is this uh
Violet well I hope you guys enjoyed the
songs we sang a couple of songs of first
one being uh dummy dummy
byan um it's a song I've Been fond of
for quite a long time actually it's uh I
I think it's lesser known than some of
his uh really you know famous songs but
it's it has a special place in my heart
so I really wanted to sing it for you
guys and I hope you guys enjoyed it uh
the song I sang after that is
called I think it's a really fun song
that's perfect for a cult although I
wouldn't know anything about being a
cult definitely not a cult by the
way yeah and uh the song after that
was um if you guys know I really love
eist and one of my favorite songs by
them is actually this song uh and I've
sang it I think once or twice wife in
karaoke before but I really wanted to
sing it in a live as well so I hope you
guys enjoyed
it the song after that was called Shall
We Dance by Leona uh it's a song that
you guys actually lot of you asked me to
sing it after n n because it's also from
the uh same series anime series Shadow
house but um since you know the title
itself is shall we dance and it's a very
dancable song I thought I might as well
save it for the live which I I hope you
guys
enjoyed um I think the Cory was a little
difficult for me to learn but I I think
I pulled it off did I did I do
okay yes and the song after that is
violent my first original song it's very
nostalgic to me um every time I listen
to it and I guess it's been quite a
while since I first released it um as it
was my first original song I I learned a
lot from it and so it it's really
special to me but as I've said before um
it's been a while since the first
original so maybe it's time for a second
one sometime soon soon
soon but anyways thank you everyone for
always uh supporting me thanks everyone
who helped in making this life happened
without you guys um sta s Everyone this
wouldn't have happened so thank you very
very much uh yeah I guess we'll move on
to the next song uh I hope you'll enjoy
it
[Music]
s our Patt fall through inin BL
SE Misty was first that call drowning
endless
dreams is my sanity clinging for my
memory
this
Humanity forgotten
[Music]
friend
in no I
keeping without love is not the world
that I want to see if such
I tell me how you I
recile in
[Music]
my I know TI death may love is
now for
[Applause]
forever
[Music]
time Al The
[Applause]
[Music]
Eternity
in I will keep playing at the of world
when I love is not the world that I want
to see
if I
always tell me how do I recile the in
[Music]
[Applause]
my
[Music]
dream
for
beond
love
enough
enough I will keep
playing a world where the love is not
the world that I want to see if
s are oh can't see tell me how do I
reconcile the in my
[Music]
[Applause]
memory I know take death may die love is
now and for
[Applause]
forever
[Music]
spee
foree
fore
[Music]
for
foree
all
[Music]
foree
[Applause]
[Music]
for
fore
[Music]
I
[Applause]
[Music]
foree
fore
[Music]
foree
tle come here sit
sit how's the live did you enjoy it how
was it
fun I'm glad I'm glad thanks always for
your
for without you this wouldn't have
happened well it's been a long 3 years
huh well let's continue to have more fun
from now on too okay yeah forever ever
ever ever
ever
[Music]
[Applause]