hello kfb
welcome to
the cheer guide for heart challenger
for this you will need
one or two or no light stick doesn't
really matter
or even better
now i don't have a towel but this maybe
looks like a towel supposedly and what i
want you to use the best choice is a
lengthy relatively small
towel not a huge ass bath towel okay
just a relatively small towel that you
can swing like this yeah yeah you know
what i mean all right we'll be swinging
it like this during the chorus so get
ready for that besides that we're mostly
just vibing so let's get started i'll be
using the towel for this okay
if you don't have a towel you can also
just wave your hands or the light sticks
whatever you have
ooh
let's go
[Music]
oh
yay
[Music]
hi
let's go
[Music]
please
okay
[Music]
yay
let's go
[Music]
please
oh
but you know what i mean clap
yes
[Music]
okay
please
[Music]
daisy
hey
[Music]
okay
yo there are some parts that
i added that you don't really need to do
but for example the parts like chocolate
and so on where i really screamed i want
you guys to also scream that at me okay
also make me made of me for example all
right
looking forward to hearing you guys and
seeing you guys cheer don't forget your
towel let's go