[Music]
This
program is
brought to you by the sponsors you see.
[Music]
[Applause]
Iknowbabyfo is heading to the new studio. It's been
a while since I last saw it, and it probably isn't that different from the previous studio.  It
may not look like it is, but it's
definitely different, but I wanted them to create the same atmosphere.
[Music]
Senpai
Before I call Hanena.
Well, I'd like you to take a look at this new studio,
so I'll have you take a look at it first,
so my
seniors are taking a little break and
taking a quiet break here and there.Okay,
then, and un, yes, isBend
saveman. It's
been 7 months.
[Music]  ]
Well, I
went to America and got sick or something,
so I did
n't just purposely take a seven-month break, but I didn't
do it because things weren't going well for a while.  It's
been quite a while, so I decided it was time to
go back with something new,
so I
decided to take a break, but
yeah, I'm going to
look it up
and the news study
I think you're going
Friend and VRX
Beautiful bottle I'm
actually in this studio.
There's a certain really amazing feature that I
'd like to show you again next time, but
when I was looking at a cutout with a guest a long time ago, there
wasn't anything special in the room.  The
room is now ready.
[Music] The
pattern on the wall in the back is interesting, isn't it?
It's cool. [Laughs] Yeah, this is new.
For example, when someone enters, it looks like this and there's a
music video behind it.
Music.
Another one.  What do you want to show me?
Jean
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I'm
sure Ayame-senpai
is there somewhere too.
There's that stage on the right. That light.
Stage 3
[Music]
There's a chicken with a camera.
Now onto the action.
Hey
[Music] It's been
5 days.
Since I'm doing it completely in 3D, I asked Ane-chan to
make it in 3D so that everything is connected.
Yay
Thankyoufunkingmy
NEWS
This talk
is a special prize for the interview of the English-speaking model.The purpose is to use
herbal medicine while
also painting mainly Japanese celebrities.  My
goal is for people to know more about it.I'm
sending this to you through the broadcaster Takanashi's compensation.Okay,
okay.
WalkerMygusmys Please,
Yami-senpai
[Music]
Everyone is like this,
yay, yay,
this is a giraffe, and hey, Ayame-senpai Welcome, hello, hello, hello
[Music]
Keyto, such a collection of keys, when you
put them together, it becomes exciting
[laughter]
Please, please, this is a
really
special episode
Thank you very much for inviting me to this new stage.
[Music]
[Music]  I wonder if
this one is a bit too loud. How about I
raise my voice a little and lower my voice?
OK,
yes.
Where is my [Music]?
Okay, let's get into the questions now.
[Music]
Let's do our best, let's
do our best, let's try our best.  Yes, Ayame-
senpai, what kind of activities have you been doing lately? Please
tell me. Lately, have you
been streaming games? What kind of
games are you
playing?  I've
always wanted to play horoki, but seriously, I've never done it before. It's a
game I'm addicted to, and I really
want to play it.
Now, just
lie a little faster, please, please, please
do it.  I think everyone would be happy if I did that.
[Music]
So, just to give you a little bit of
information,
my daughter Kobo-chan's Hololive ID, Kobu-
chan,
really loves it.  I'm
really into it so much that I think it would be a good idea to do a collaboration.I
would love to do a collaboration with Kou-chan someday.When Kou-
chan and two other people
were collaborating with Bararan, I got so
excited that I decided to do
that collaboration without permission.  I also
joined Discord without permission and
participated. That's what I like about it, right
? That's right. That's my
favorite question. Ah,
right now, that seems like it might be my favorite. I see.
Okay, okay, that's
perfect. Let's
move on to the next question. Yes, I'd like to try it.
Kobo-chan and Ii-koo-chan are
really
cute, so it's true. They're really cute, and their songs are delicious. OkOk. As
for the next question, I
haven't been able to say it until now because of the language barrier, but it's from
overseas.  Is there anything you wanted to tell me?
Well, I'm
not very good at English to begin with, but I
wanted to understand what everyone was saying, so I've been studying a little bit lately.  I
want to tell you that I'm
studying. In what form do you study
? Do you have a teacher?
Yes, I buy books on my own,
and I study and memorize a few words.
Really,
for example, what movie did you memorize earlier? What do you
remember recently?  It's difficult when words are said to me quickly. You
have to try hard, right?
Yeah,
wait a minute. I
'll translate it for you. It's supposed to
be fresh, so I choose Wings. Did you
find it?  I
found it.
What I learned recently
is Increase this. It's the word yasu, why,
why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why, why. Emo, which may come up quite a bit in a vocabulary book. It's a
Japanese term for maintenance.
[Music]
Eh, OK. Well, it's quite a difficult word.  I think
this also
comes up a little in listening and other
things.Ah, ok, then I'll
teach you some English sentences from the teacher Takanashi.Oh, please teach
me.That's what everyone was saying earlier.
Points in Christmas, I
understand
, please turn up the volume, Ayame-senpai.
''
[Music] I
can even use it in such situations. It
was just the right word. Now that's what I'm talking about.
Okay, genius camp. Ok, then,
umm, how about
studying English?  Hey, no matter how
hard you try, you're still
struggling to learn English.Speaker:
I'm a
member of the family,
and it seems like it's my first collaboration partner.That's
right.  I
'd like to know if there are any other members of my family that I'd like to collaborate with. I'd love to talk to everyone,
but I'd
especially like to talk to Ina-chan.
Everyone, Ina-chan, Japan.  It's
easy to talk to her because she can speak Japanese, Ina-chan, and she's good at Japanese.That's why I
felt relieved.You
know, she's good at Japanese.It's a
bit like a Mim from overseas,
hmm, that Japanese person.
For example, when I met a foreigner and
said "Hello," the foreigner told me that Japanese people
were good at Japanese, so
even my enemy on stage thought it was true, so
thank you for speaking to me today.
[Laughs]
No, that's not it,
OkOk
Google
Overline in Japanese
[Music]
There's something about it that seems like it would go really well.What's going on?
Actually, Ina-chan loves puns just as much as Ayame-senpai.That's right.It's been
used by both men and women for a long time.Oh yeah, that's right.
After all, there are puns in English, too. There are quite
a few.
Okay, okay.
From now on, I'd like to use Tiara as a project,
use it as an opportunity,
and collaborate with the members of my family. I really want to talk to everyone about it.
Please,
please, please come anytime. It might
be a Japanese employee.
Gaze
[Music]
Okay, let's move on to the next question.
Okay, I may have wavered a bit at first,
but it's a little subtle.
Well, what kind of streaming do you like most, Senpai
? For example, games, karaoke,
chatting, collaborating, etc.
[Music]
I like all of them, but
[Music] I
might like chatting. I might
even like talking to everyone.
Even later.  I have the impression that I'm doing a lot of collaborations with my seniors. It's a
big collaboration.
[Music]
Yeah, that's great. I get invited all the time. I'm
very thankful that I get invited,
but I
'm really shy.
There are times when I can't talk when there's a lot of people, but I
like talking.I see, this program is
perfect.Yes, that
's right, but I'm a little nervous.It's
okay, don't be nervous.I still
have a lot of questions, so
I'll do my best slowly.
Do your best.
Eh, then
turn around.
[Music] There
's no need to be nervous. I'm
sure everyone in the chat will say the same thing.
Have confidence in your seniors.
I'll do my best.Okay,
now on to the next part.Now
for the new questions, I'd like you to explain the basics
for those who are seeing it for the first time.First of all, I see.So I
'm being called in?Finally,
this is it.I
don't remember reading it, but I
noticed it.  Everyone called me Tara Ojo.
No, I didn't do anything, but for some
reason people started calling me Ojo. I
wonder if it's been that way ever since the beginning.
Or maybe it's been a while since I started.  I
think it was after a while that
everyone called me Ayame-chan at first.
Everyone in the chat, I
think there are fans of Ai's senpai, but I wonder if she's
a boy or something.
She has a ladylike vibe. Oh, let's have some tea.  It's because of the atmosphere and the fact that her
fan name is "
Nakigumi"
that's why there are so many older ladies who call her Ojou.  That
woman at the top inside is called a young lady. I
guess that's what she
looks like.
[Laughs] To
put it simply, that's what it feels like.
OK, that's easy to explain.
[Laughs] I
didn't think of Gummy as a yakuza.  But
I guess that's what it's like. It's
like a group. Let's
get the failed members.
[Music]
Yakuza-buying
[laughter]
[Music]
OkOk
Next.  What do you
mean by your condition
? And you call yourself "Yo."
What does that mean?
Um, Japan.
Should I say "Um?" in the past,
but now, I
don't think there are many people who call me "Iro."
Nowadays, we
don't say "noisy" or "boku" in Japanese, but it's like an old version of that. That
's what I used in my old videos. People from that era. Ah.
And for example, I
think there was a way to say it that was especially used by samurai, but
the bottom line is that it was used by a certain type of person.It's kind of
like the old days, I
think there are a lot of great people, so that
's the image.  Oh, OK, I see. It
feels like it's in the first person now. I see.
And one more
thing. Which song is that?
I know which one.
That's right, I don't know.For everyone, that
was a Minecraft broadcast, and
when I was going to my destination, I didn't know which way to go, so I lost track of it, so I
improvised and said, ``Which direction? Which direction?''
Some of the fans made up a song for me.Why?  I
think there was a time when it was really popular around
me. Have you
heard that song yourself a few times
?
If I asked you, could you sing it? I might not be able to sing the full song,
but I can sing it just a little bit, just a little bit.  It's probably the
members around me, the Japanese members,
who are singing it.
Everyone around me remembers it.
[Music] I
'd like them to sing a little bit.
So which one?
Which one?
Wait, I'll play that, then I'll play around a little more.  Do
you want to move to the stage? There
's no sound source. It's okay, a cappella. Let's
move.
Please show me your whole body. Okay. Ah, I'll pay
you.
Okay.
Well, behind the microphone.
Yes.  It's so
nice of you to use it.I'm embarrassed, but I wonder
if you remember the lyrics.I
wonder if it'll come out, which one.I'll come out, which one?
Yes, it's a bit
strange, but
I sent it to you. Ah, it's
true. It
was, it was, it was.
Yay,
OkOk
[Music]
Eh, for the chorus, I think I'll sing just the chorus. I'll
keep it quiet. Let's
go.
Eh, wait, wait a minute, remember the notes. You
can do it while listening. Ah, which
chorus is cold?
Wait a minute, there's no sound source for this.  There seems to be a karaoke version of this too.
There's karaoke. I'm
looking for Jan, and here's something. I
won't sing.
[Music] Yes, there's
walking karaoke.  It
probably won't flow, but here it is.
Yeah, it's okay. I'll go. OK, mute. Shusteidin. Ahaha, wait a minute, wait a minute, get nervous. It's okay, it's okay. It's just which one, which one.
Ah, I
'll say
which one, which one, which one, which one, which one.
Reverse animal.  Either way, which way, which way, the other way
around. [Laughs] The fire is almost ok now.
[Music] I
'll be back.
[Music] I'll
make it louder, whichever, whichever,
whichever, whichever I
remember
Well, you know, I've been researching it for a long time, and it's
just come to my mind lately. Thank
you.
Thank you for singing. Thank you.
Hey,
now that I know more about it.  Now
I want to see Ayame-senpai's cute paulownia tree.
Wow, that's
embarrassing. Oh,
this place is already here. I
wonder what I can do with it.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Senior
gathering
[Music]
What are you saying?
It just sounded like a cat's meow.
[Laughs] Pretty
Cure.
Crying, crying lady.
[Laughs] That's
all.
[Music]
[Applause]
Actually, that's the Mist Tree.
Well, a
certain staff member,
um,
Ayabe-senpai,
I always say when I ask for a cutout like this,
but this time, a certain staff member made it for me.
He selfishly asked me if I
could make a collection of cute sounds.What
happened?Oh
yeah, that's right, this is a masterpiece.It seems like he really
wanted to make it.Thank you
very much.
[Music]
Great, great job.  Thank you. It's
embarrassing.
Well, well, well, well, well, this seems to be Ayame-senpai's
charm point. Ah-
chan's laughter is Chan-chan's point, and
cute sounds are Chan-chan's point.
So, the
next question is
Ayame-senpai's.  The
meme "sodium", which is about unique laughter and happy energy,
is popular among people overseas, but I'd like to
know if there's a similar meme among Japanese people who have heard of it.
Well, I've heard of it before, so I wonder if they're
using a fan brother in Japan, because I'm
making it, and I'm using the
same thing. Sei-
sensei, I
wonder if this was first thought up by people overseas. Well, I guess that's right, but first...
Is it from people in Japan that I heard?
[Music]
National The cryium that is understood all over the world. The
world's
common language, Kirium. Maybe that's the case.
Moreover, I wonder if today's All Talk is also charged with crying.
[Music]
[Laughs]
Oh, that was really good.
[Laughs] The
clippings from before now are more
fully charged than just this clipping. It was
written in English. It's
easy. It's easy, isn't it?  That
was an easy answer, so let's move on to the next one.Well, I
heard that Iam-senpai loves making puns, but do you
have a favorite pun?And if you
have any good puns, please let me know.Well,
what did you say earlier?  Didn't you say, "I like streaming?"
During a game,
when you lose, you make excuses, right? Yoga: You make
excuses, like it's because of the current situation.
[Music]
When I'm making an excuse,
everyone says, ``
Okay, now it's okay for me to make an excuse myself,''
which is why I quite like it.I
understand this, but it's a bit more
English.I'll
give it a try.Yeah,
that's it.
[Music]
Make excuses, make excuses.
[Music] I
think I was able to explain it. It's
easy to understand. There were some puns as well. I wonder if it's
a little bit. A long time ago,
when I streamed Animal Forest, I streamed something like that.  There
was an Easter event going on, so I
collected a lot of eggs, and
when I opened the item run, I
said, ``This is the amount of eggs.''
If that was the case, I think it would be a little
easier to use
Japanese.
[Music]
Atsumori
[Applause]
[Music] You do
n't say that, I'm just a simple family mart shopper. It
's normal for it to become uninteresting if I explain it
. Well then, it's a
joke. I'll tell you something. Well, this
is also a pun about eggs.
Eggs, there's
only one word, that
perfect value,
or the word wonderful.
In English, it's
exce.
Soften it and
put the egg in.
For example,
in the morning, if you
fry an egg and you
get a nice, nice picture, that's it.  Ha, you
can just call me Eki-chan. Ah, I
see. It doesn't
mean "excellent." Yes,
I'm
not as good at making puns as Ayumi-senpai, but
no, no, no, I
'll try it from now on.
[Music]
What kind of changes have you seen in your broadcast content and personality since you debuted? I
wonder if there have been any changes like that. In the past, you
may have been a little calmer and quieter.
Maybe it was a little darker.
[Music]
Even though it was dark, it's like being in middle school.
Car: I
won't say it before, but it's not as crazy as it is now.
[Laughs]
okokokiUSBMycomeand
&
dogs
[Music]
Is there anything else?
Well, I don't know what else to
say.
Maybe he didn't make a pun. Either way. I see. He might have been
wearing a cat mask. Now that he's wearing a cat mask, I don't know if he's
wearing a cat mask or has an accident. Where is the cat
?
[Laughs]  We
were really talking about cats.
[Laughs]
Cat wearing a
spiked aspanion is a
proverb. It may not be a pun, but cats...
As soon as I said where, it became a pun.
[Laughs]
No, this isn't a pun.
[Music]
Oh, that's amazing.
But it's amazing. It's called an idiom, but I know what it means.  The
phrase "cat mask, imitate, hide here" is
something you hear quite a lot in everyday Japanese. It's
amazing, it's great, it's
Japanese. I
want you to see it. It's
amazing. I found this right away.  I
thought it was interesting,
so I had it made for me.
It's my birthday, so it's
not my birthday. I was sent a saran lamp as a present, and the
saran
wrap was so strong that I didn't have to buy it for the rest of my life.  What's more, Barry and I were so rich, and we
ended up with about 10 of them in various sizes.
Oh, yeah, that's
right, the culprit is
throwing matches. I'm
going to carry it out. I'm going to buy a lot of Saran Wrap with this
[Music] I've
been getting yelled at. Even with this, I
came here to try to get you to buy Saran Wrap again, but
thank you.
The other day I used up only one long one, so I
got a new one, but
seriously, I'm laughing. I still have it
left. I seriously got it, so I
guess I only have about 4 left.  Is
n't it already
yen?
900m is strong.
[Music] There's no
saran wrap. Wash the dishes.
I don't have any of them either. How much is that?
Of course, the one who wants it
is the souvenir. What will this senior be like?
[Music]
What do
you think? I'm the Saran Wrap senior.
[Music]
[Laughs] I
have a question about this. That's wrong. Oh,
what's the order
?
[Music]  It
seems like that, but I'd like to hear more about it.How
much of that 900 meter Saran Wrap have you
used up so far?And
this is the strangest gift you've received in the four years since you joined Hol Live.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Well, what about Saran Wrap? There
are several sizes of Saran Wrap in Japan,
but they're kind of large.
I've used up all of them, and I
still have about 45 of the short, medium, and small ones
left.But I've
used quite a bit, probably
half 50%,
half a little, half a little
60%,
about 65, 65,
etc.  I wonder
when this happened, maybe 2 years ago. I've
used 60% of it in 2 years, so I'm already using it quite a bit.
I wonder if I'm using it at all. I can't wait to use it.
That's why I'm afraid I'll come again.
Even if
it's bad, I probably won't give you a present. It's good, it's good, it's good. It's
okay to increase again. It's okay to increase again.
[Music] That
's not it. It's
not safe because they won't send you a present.  I
might even tear off all the Saran wrap and put it in a letter. I do
n't like it.
Saran wrap letters are coming.
[Music] It's
like a love letter.
This is the weirdest thing I've seen in the four years since I joined Hololive.
That was the strangest gift.It might have
been something like that.I wonder
what it is.It's the
thing that babies put in their mouths.It's ice cream bread.Bubba
's
[laughing]I do
n't know why.It's like
talking and talking.  Hey, they
sent me a grip strength measuring device.
[Music]
Wait, I saw a cutout of it. I
wonder what they'd call it.
[Music]
What do you want me to say about grip strength?  I
wonder if Kanata-chan, that Japanese member, had a grip strength of 50 kg, so I thought maybe Ayame-chan sent it to me because she wanted me to measure it too. Oh, grip
strength. Yeah, grip
strength.  I think I was about 25
Rice field nyan
Babu Babu
Maybe if I did that too I
wouldn't have any problems at all My arms are so weak that
people say my arms are nude
[Music]
No, but I
can't get enough grip strength because I'm 50kg,
so it's amazing from the stars
[Music]
[Music] It
seems that people on the amazing chat are saying 60.
Eh, 6056 Akana Senpai is 56  Oh,
it's about 5 o'clock and I'm 56 right now. I
wonder if he's been working out. Wow, I really want to know.
Next time I see Kanata-senpai, I'll
ask him to give me that lift.
Well then, I'm
senpai.  My
hands are only here to measure my grip strength.
[Music]
Ok, okay, I hope that strange gift
never
comes. Let's
move on to the next question.
[Music]
[Music] My
senpai.
It's a demon,
but what does it
do that is typical of a demon? Well, it's not like it does anything typical of a demon,
but
yeah, in Japan,
demons don't like
beans.
Kira Aso, that something, that something
demon I want the demon to disappear There
's probably going to be a fire, so you're going to throw beans Ayame-
senpai: That day's going to be tough, isn't it?The person being thrown is the one
[Music]
But read it carefully.I hate beans.  Yo,
really, oh, I
can't eat it in any way, I don't like it anymore, it
's perfect, Sichuan,
demons, Japanese
[laughter] I
see, there are other
things that demons do, it's normal for demons.  It's
kind of scary, isn't it? He's not scary at all,
huh? He might be really scary if he gets angry. I've
never seen him get
angry.
[Music] It's
not currently being streamed, but Ayame-senpai is 2  He
got so angry that he punched a hole in the wall.
[Music]
[Applause]
That happened to me, too. I
thought I'd cut this out a little bit.
You know that,
right?
[Music]
When was that? How long ago was that?
Well, that was,
but it was already
78 years ago. Wow. I'm
not scared of Ayame-senpai after all.
Ah, but she
might be kinder now.
Well, that kind of demon.  I'm sure there are some, but kappa
and others are also called demons, right?
Leaves, leaves, kappa, kappa, kappa,
etc. Kappas are different, but they're not demons, so I
understand. I wonder
what it is.
It's a monster, but
[Music]
Leave it alone
Next time I
looked at OkOk, it's already been an hour, and I
asked a question, but what is
Mim, the island incarnation? Could you please
explain? Oh, that's it, that's probably
Minecraft, but I'm going to hunt for treasure.  I was
looking for something in Minecraft.
On the map, it said there was a treasure on a small island,
but
while I was looking for it, I was digging and the entire island disappeared.  It
looks like most of it was erased, so I used it
in a drawer for a while in the sorting room.They said they were going to
destroy it and sort it out.I wonder what
happened to that turtle?It's so
nostalgic.That was right after I made my
debut.  I think it was,
but then I realized how Mako's
island was erased in the first place, but
since then, I've said the word "sort it out" several times.  I
think it's gone, but when and how do you
use it?
If you get angry, your island will be erased. You do
n't have time, right? What do you erase
?
Oh, but I see. There are ways to use it like that. It's
interesting, it's
scary.  Well, that's fine. I
just said it, but I didn't say it right now.
I see. It's a
bit kamekamekamekame
[Music]
English ah
What is it? Turtle
Turtle.
Turtle Turtle right now.
Dougs and
Originals
And
then, I
hope I explained it well.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
[Laughter]
OK, one more thing.
Mim, I'm
glad you understand.
Next, let's talk about Ayame-senpai's cute hobbies.
Senpai:
Shrine  I
heard that you have a hobby of collecting goshuin stamps when you visit the shrine.I would
like to know what kind of hobby you have and how much you collect.Thank you for
researching this.  I'm
embarrassed to say
this, but in Japan,
what do we do at shrines? To put it simply, it's like a
stamp rally where you
get stamps that sound like stamps. I really enjoy collecting stamps that are
unique to that shrine, and I've
collected about 15 stamps so far.  I've been collecting these things by visiting various shrines that don't have a lot of power.
[Music]
Senpai: I
want to give you some knowledge about that point that doesn't matter, but
actually, when I lived in Japan, I learned about it.  I used to work as a shrine maiden
at a shrine.
That's right. I
wanted to see it. I
worked at a really big shrine, and there were
quite a few
tourists and Japanese people there. I
wanted a goshuin stamp, so I
asked Chiara for it.  So, I
didn't play the character, so I'm going to hand it over
to that person this time and
ask for 5 wins.'' That's
right, that's right, I put it back again and did that.
[Laughs]  It's
okay to imagine things like that.I saw a tiara in a place that sold fortunes
and charms.Eh, I
wanted to go buy some, but it turned out to
be Tenmangu Shrine somewhere over there.Eh, the
top is a little big.  It's a big place. It was
really fun and I learned a lot.
So I was kind of happy that I had a hobby of making goshuin stamps.
Well, when I heard that, I felt a bit of a familiarity with it.
[Music] I
always used to talk about that book about goshuin stamps,
but I've never received a goshuin stamp myself, so
someday I'll think of Ayame-senpai or something like that.  I
want to know how to
do it.I
want to go with you.
By the way, Chara, I'm going to Japan in December, so please say hello
. I really want to go.
[Music]
I did it.
Thank you very much. [
Music]
I
did it. [Music] - I got really excited.
[Music] -
What... [Music]  [
Music]
Yay,
if you can,
please answer in English. OK,
do your best. That
's it.
Next time, that's it. Which is better? It's cold.
Food is the main thing. Last
or rare?
Gusto.
Same.
Twitter feeling Instagram or
Twitter
Apple or
orange
juice Is it better to climb a mountain or run a marathon?
[Music]
Marathon is OK. I can't
put pineapple on pizza.
[Applause]
[Music] I'm
going to cry.
Something spicy or sweet.  Which do you prefer,
tea or coffee?
Traveling by the beach or studying abroad in a dreamy big city?
Hmm,
beach by the sea Do you
sleep
naked or clothed?  I'm
getting dressed.
[Laughs] My
favorite event is Halloween, Christmas,
Issa, etc., Tanabata,
Setsubun, ah
, I wonder if Setsubun will be wrapped in beans. Christmas, Seven or Family Mart,
whichever is better. Seven, okay, I prefer Amoshi Moshi Seven. Which would be better, a text message or a phone call?
Eh,
phone call. I'll
give you a present.
[Music] I don't need that
gentle Saran rap from the Hammer book that I'll give you
[laughter] I'll
walk the distance of one station or I'll take the train or I'll take the car.
[Music]
OK, what's your blood type
? I've
never done it before, right? I've
never done it
before. I know [Music] So, what color are your panties? [Laughs] [Music] Well, actually, Ayame, my senpai.  I
asked him about his blood type.I
knew that I had never told him.The
staff member who made the iron cutout said to
him, ``I knew a lot about Ayame-senpai.''  If you have
any
questions, please let me know.'' I said, ``If you have any questions, please let me know.'' But it
wasn't there, but since I've
never told you my blood type, I wanted to know.
Unfortunately, it was a secret.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music] I'll secretly
check it later with Chara-chan and
let you know. Thank
you. You know, actually overseas, I used to be
like that, and I'm like that even now, but it's like not many
people know my blood type.
oh yeah
Not really, you.No
one asks what happened to your blood.No one
at all.Japanese people are like that.It seems like it has
something to do with personality.No
one thinks about the stairs, so
no one knows their blood type.
[Music]
Why are you telling me the color of the parts
?
[Music]
There's a saying in English that says, "A woman is no good without a secret.
This is a
secret that will last forever
.
[Music]"  I've
never said this before, but I just don't think I've ever had a reason to mention it.
OK OK [Music] I want you to watch it calmly. Please
[Music] They
're all young ladies, but among them are
imposter commoners.
Even in a situation where Mr.
Button Button did something like that, I
would think Mr. Button was suspicious.I see, it's
easy to blame him, so that's
what I'll do.
[Laughs] That's
too funny.I'll
see how it goes.  Alone again
"
Where did everyone go? They were all gone in an instant.
[Laughs] I have
n't gone to see you.
Miss Melon. There are
too many people.
You're not a young lady, right? That's the
family budget.
No, no, no, there's no money to give to the common people. The
young
lady won in the end. The
way you speak is interesting.
In English, there is this way of speaking. Well,
this is it. The English subtitles have been
made to sound as lady-like as possible.
[Music]
No, it's
very lady-like.  She spoke in a typical way, but she's a princess,
so why isn't she always like this?
It doesn't mean anything.Even when I say ``Ojou'', it means ``Ojosama''
and ``Ojosama''.It seems
suspicious, minus Shirai-san.Yoshi-
san's lady&
George Fong
is a young lady. It
was cute.
As expected of Vacuum.
[Music] Have
you all calmed down? Ayami-senpai. Have you calmed down? Have you calmed down? Your
tension has loosened up a bit. Oh, I'm
glad.
Me too. I
always get nervous when posting holo posts, so the two of us.  I
'm nervous Well, I'm nervous
Yeah, well, it's almost over It's
okay
Agesawation
[Music]
Hey, I hope you don't
understand Well, the
next question is...
Yeah, the design is based on the image of Japanese culture.
[Music]
Yeah, the
members gathered together, Myu-senpai and Fubuki. Senpai, you
're in Yurito, but do you have any good memories or
interesting episodes?
Well, maybe there are good memories, but Kouko's
members are in Irohaniho.  Look at Yahoo! What's your
name?
Please say
Ayafumu Irohanihoheto
Ayafugumi
Irohanihoheto Ayafugumi
Really OK,
please continue.
All the members are
working really hard on dance lessons and things like that. I wonder
why we all went to a dance lesson.
On the way home, we
all went to karaoke. It looked like it was fun. I
wonder if these three sang a song together.  Well, that's how the three of them sang the songs of the three of them. I see,
but after doing that, it seems like the
beauty-senpai and Fubuki-senpai mirrors are
a lot better than the other members.  I feel
like just doing this  I guess we
got along quite well.The three
of us were really good, so we decided to try something together.The
three of us, not the management, came up with the partner.Well, I guess it was the
first time.  Well, I
guess it was almost like a flow. Well, the
visuals are done perfectly, so yes,
everyone is good friends. Iroha, Niho,
Ayafugumi, Yukiru
[Music],
right?
[Music]
Irohanihohe and Aya Flavor
are, you know, the Japanese people in Japan. When
tourists come to Japan, I want them to go to
karaoke and sing Neko's live songs
or Irohanihohe and Gumi's songs.
[Music]
[Music] There
's a lot of emotes out there.
[Music] It's
hard to tell who they are.
[Music] There
's a lot of emotes out there.  I
'd like to team up with Rui-chan too. We're
good
friends. I've hung out with Rui-chan a few times.
Oh, that's right. Ii-chan, Towa,
Senpai,
Eato,
Korone,
etc. It's really interesting.  That's enough, now
if we form a country unit of 4 people, I
wonder what kind of group we'll have with Louie-san, Corona-senpai, and Anime-senpai.It
's a new combination, but I
wonder if there's anything you'd like to do
[Music]
English words
can be seen as rice, and
what is T?
[Music]
[Laughter] It's boring
if it's just a little far away.
[Music] It'll
be gone. It'll be after I fall in love with you. It'll be
taken away.
Stop it. Every day I
put out my knife. Oh, wait, I'll change the order of the lanterns and go home.
If you say it in German, it
's cold, it's
cold.If we
named it like that as a unit, it would
give us a cool image and it would be cool if we could sing well
.  I'm not
talking about my imagination,
so I
don't need any motion sickness pills, but thank you very much
Senkyu. Maybe, I do
n't know. I
usually
play [music].
Irohanihohe and Ayafumi
have this central Japanese feeling, so I use that
[music].
Dad:
There's something really
special about musical instruments, especially for people from other countries.  I wonder
if people in other countries like Japanese instruments and sounds, because they don't really come up
in foreign songs, so
it's because they don't feature things like the shamisen that I feel so fresh when I hear them.  I'm so
happy. I've
sung it many times
at karaoke. I'm so
happy. I've actually sung it at karaoke. I
might just have to go once.
[Music]
There are other 3D live performances, but you
might not have thought of it as karaoke.
Karaoke,
right? Yes, it's a bit lonely when you're alone,
so you have to have three people together.
[Music]
Senpai,
what do you think is your greatest accomplishment as a Hololive member? Did that
accomplishment have any influence on Ayame-senpai's current high school
students? I
wonder if it was a mineral or something.  I
tried singing Edemo, that
guy has
over 20 million views.
20 million
won. How do you say 20 million won in English
? [Music] I see, that's a good-bye declaration.
[Music] Congratulations, it's called a
jewel.  I don't think it's a good thing or not. It's
always been that way,
and there aren't that many people who have achieved it online, or maybe not at all. Yeah, no, I don't
know.  I guess you're
doing it right as a beginner, but I don't
think that's true, so I think it's
amazing.Hmm, I'm happy about that.Second
question:
Did phimosis have an impact on high school students?
But I don't think you
say that to everyone in Japan too much.  I haven't,
but once I
tried singing it after it had been played 20 million times, I felt
a little pressured to release it.
After all, I'm nervous after all
. There's a lot of pressure. That's the same
with the original song. I've
put out one that I tried singing along with the original song.
Oh yeah, that Reaching By
Sengen-
san cover
[Music]
Like this.  I think the problem is that I'm probably
thinking too much about it,
but I
totally understand how it feels to be under pressure.But what's so amazing about
Ayabe 3's fans is
that their
support is so
strong and
passionate.  It's
probably safe. No matter what I do, people will see it
and I'm
sure they'll come, so I do
n't have to worry about it. I'll
do my best. There
are other places like Ogano, and I'm sure there's other things like
half-year allowances and
component funds. Senpai and
others.
Niore: Well, 3D live performances and things like that
are a gem. There
was a place where we could show the results of our hard work.
[Music] -
For us, life itself
is probably an achievement.
Ah, that's right.
[Music]
Next I'm Senpai, you've
been a part of this live for a long time, but it's no longer with you.Have you
ever overcome any hardships from the beginning?It
was all black and white.
What?
[Music]
Everyone and the other
guests were also talking about these things. It must have been a
difficult time.
But originally, I
never imagined dancing or anything like that, so oh well, that's right.  I
couldn't even dance, and apparently that
was difficult.
Even now, I have a hard time practicing singing, and
many things are
difficult.  I didn't know yet that the direction from here would
be what it is now.I probably
didn't even think about it,
so I would do so many live shows,
do so many 3D activities, and dance.  I
couldn't imagine it yet, so
yes, I didn't
think that the members would be so big at all.  I
feel like I'm
working hard every day to grow.
[Music]
Direction
The sex was like this, but at the all-live show, I
feel like Ayame-senpai is already able to do anything perfectly. Looking at him  She
dances cutely, sings cutely, and
is definitely an idol.
[Music]
What I overcame
was dancing, or did I do something else? Ah,
but I don't know if I can say I overcame it. I
guess I overcame it a little bit.
That's right, the
end is
near.
And what is your favorite activity?
What's your favorite thing?
[Music]
Everyone is so
considerate. Is it
because
everyone is so considerate? Everyone is so kind.  I
guess I like the way people treat me and treat me in a variety of ways.Everyone is so nice and other than that, what's your favorite activity in Hololive?What's your favorite activity?What's your favorite activity?  Is it singing?
I like it,
so I like it when we all sing together or form a unit like this.
Everybody's
[Music]
Fifth Moth
This is a standard question, but
for seniors.  What
is Hololive?
Well, I
guess it's life. That's right, I guess it's the same for me. That's right. That's right. It's so
deep. Thank you very much.
Senpai, I guess I couldn't
answer all your questions.
[Applause]
[Music]
Thank you for being part of the revival. Well, I'd like you to
check it out.
ThankyouforJOY It
's on
Nee-no
[Music]
From now on, I hope we can do the next All Talk soon
without taking that 7-month break,
and I'll do my best.
From now on, I
want people to see our new studio in a variety of ways, so please come again.
It's in the description, so please
click here.
Please, I do
n't think there's anyone who hasn't registered yet.
Ok
thankyouametime
[  [Music] Thank you for
coming with me today.
Thank you everyone.
Lastly, is
there anything you would like to say?
From now on, I ask you to be nice to me.
[Music] Please take care
of this beautiful castle.
Thank you very much.
[Music]
This is the character's final greeting. I
wonder if I can say it in German.
[Music]
[Laughter]