I
[Music]
1 two say no
oh yes
[Music]
1 two say no
Dre
ch
[Music]
one two
oh one two say no
[Music]
p
I
am SP
English and we're
got knife I my voice is
so um um sticky right now sticky
[Music]
sticky oh
B she got jump scared by me and laugh oh
my
god oh okay
she's gone now
oh why C if you hold on let me voice
chat to
unmute
hello oh
oh hello hi I got we both got the sticky
voice huh yeah it's not very
good I I do be huffing and puffing and
choking weezing
better thanks it's the perfect time to
play video games right now exactly oh my
God woman before me green woman jump
scare oh my God oh my
God that scared me hello hello
greenist oh we're on we're on day 15 n
yeah wait what
we on D7
yesterday wait what the
heck that doesn't seem right did someone
AFK in the
game do you think someone AFK in the
game maybe I don't know I loged off
yesterday hold on a second let me let me
ask
them was someone was someone playing at
night or something maybe like offline no
I don't think so cuz it would still have
to be 7
hours of playing
some a whole week has
passed it's day 15
LOL what the heck what
the well that's okay because you know we
can still we can still roll with it we
can we can still I mean the base looks
fine
that's kind of weird who's out there
punching zombies oh me I heal by
punching so I'm just getting some health
back oh nice yeah do that you do
that y That's crazy
though what about the water thing has it
been collecting water that's the real
way to tell oh yeah check how much water
we have ow
open de collector water hello water
hello what happened what happened is day
what
happened what happened why is the day 15
we don't
know what the
heck did somebody AFK in the game
what
happened a
mystery maybe you can mystery you got to
solve maybe we can ask uh if they can do
something about this like the game yeah
can roll back can we turn is is that a
thing I don't know I wonder wait does
this mean a hoorde will happen or
something no it thankfully it's day 15
so we still have like quite a while but
um I wonder if someone AFK like they got
to be dead like they got to be super
dead so surely we'll figure out who it
is
what there's three Waters in here so
wait it doesn't mean wait but like H so
the
next zombies are going to be in six days
cuz it's day 15 so the zombie hord just
happened technically I think so oh
no okay that's fine then I guess um yeah
I mean technically we're kind of where
we started anyway but it's just a week
later than that so that's it's still
it's it is
weird yeah oh can I have that murky
water there you go oh yeah mky water too
here take it take it here's murky water
too thank you it's a water
Fest let's go okay I'm making a bunch I
can make tea now I can make pumpkin
bread can I have some tea I'll make you
some tea if you say coffee is just as
good coffee is terrible no tea for you
okay give me water then I'll make my own
tea I'll make you
tea
[Music]
yay and then we got to then we got to go
do quest
Quest yeah let's do
Quest yeah you guys got to get your
too I really want a bike it would be so
fun just riding on my bicycle riding
around it would be so cute oh wait
everybody get a bike have you seen it
yet come here come
here see over here H up let me see I'm
door stuck F I'm door stuck
oh shotgun shells for
Mory
y I can honk the horn too oh you can
yeah I think so maybe is that how far
can you be fast can you be uh you can
you oo it's pretty fast
actually yeah and it's good because
doesn't uh you can Sprint with it
obviously but normal speed you don't
need to Sprint with it and it's like
faster than running so it doesn't use
stamina so it's really
nice but apparently you get it when you
do 10 Quest so we should all do 10 Quest
so we can all have a we can be a biker
gang yeah biker gang on our little
bicycles tricycles
[Music]
tricycles I wish
okay I'm I'm down let's do
[Music]
it oh I can make
coffee I want coffee I'm making I'm
making coffee and I making some tea
okay I'll make one you don't have to be
this rude every time yeah one coffee I
think so I do think so huh I didn't say
e te every time
but you like
to I mean
some to head up here you got to use
those oh by the way I got a treasure
map it says to whoever finds this note
friend the end is near the monsters are
breaking down my door but in my final
moments I can think of how I want to be
remembered not as a coward but as
someone who thinks of others I leave you
this map to one of my many secret Berry
chest to you God bless you
Jennifer
oo thanks Jennifer I think I think if we
go to a party together you'll see the
the treasure map maybe really nice nice
uh can you make me a fire spear as well
or like a fire club or
something uh I found a mod for that so
you need to find a mod
but incendiary mode or something like
that or no it was something else but I I
would I would like to tell you but I
just lost all my stuff I see the
treasure oh you do see the treasure lost
all your stuff maybe you died good no
like yesterday when I looked out I was
on this car and I had all my items and
now I I am not I have nothing wait is
are you is he the one are you the
one out
what are you sure you logged out out
yeah cuz it's day 15 we're trying to
figure out who was
AFK who was running the game with
someone they had to have
died was it you is she the chosen one is
she
the was she chosen cuz that might mean
that you died you were AFK and then your
stuffff
despawned oh
you all right maybe
oh oh no oh
no oh we can help you get your stuff
back there's there's plenty of stuff in
the house that you can take oh there's
so sorry
it's
hell no it's fine don't worry hello
hello if anything this is good because
now we know you know yeah now we know
what happened what happened then uh
apparently R stayed AFK I knew it I knew
it I knew
it I was the no I saw I was the second
as I was the last one before a to log
out and when I logged out I even said to
my chat oh isn't there someone isn't Raa
still AFK like in the server cuz I saw
her standing on the car next to her I
was wondering is she looks AFK but I'm
sure she'll remember hour oh my God
doing something else so did a raid come
I wonder I think it did and it probably
destroyed R over and over
again multiple times
no unable to move but then we missed the
raid what does this mean for us that the
next raid will be super strong we're
ready we're going to do it we're going
to it's okay we strong together I think
that it also has to do with our levels
and stuff
I think so that's how it was in the
better at least so I it'll be
fun we are so we are so well fortified
but that means today there is going to
be a raid
then right
no no seven days so 14 721 so that was
yesterday oh the next one is 21 so we're
still on track right
the same yeah it's
good it's it it was calculated guys
calculated um yeah oh my God yeah can
you guys give me like some wood if you
don't mind there's there's a bunch of
stuff in the house go ahead and feel
free to take
whatever there's weapons in there too as
well so you can take some weapons gra a
weapon I even double checked like I when
I ended my stream I was still worried
about l so I checked like if I could see
if she online on Discord or on Steam
friends and so on and on Discord it just
said that she's like playing Monster
Hunter or so so was like oh that's
fine that's
crazy but hey R you collected some water
for us cuz you kept it on so
thank thank you for collecting water for
us no I'm not going
to you already did oh my God how much
water was there
unfortunately it caps at 3 so uh oh
because I
was great you guys welcome that was
calculated as I mention for all three
here wait hey I made some coffee and
some
tea
tea I can't find wood okay CeCe here's
your tea oh thank you you're welcome
it's level my God bless you can't do
ITC that is so funny me here's your
coffee here thank
you
yummy can I get some of that tea oh okay
I'll make another
tea
the sorry Chef you're working overtime I
want to give you the
XP
penalty I thought we don't have an XP
penalty what level
there is AA how do I find tab second
taben was I'm level four it's okay I'm
so my beautiful no
hesitation oh my goodness my beautiful
weapon 23
deaths what 20 what 23 23 deaths you had
so far but I
deaths
15 wait where do you see your
de I think she probably just died once
and then just was in the respawn screen
probably yeah because and then probably
at you dying a lot sorry I understand
why people have to die is you know you
restore your health and I have eight
player
kills eight ples you murderer wow
okay thank you I'm not thirsty or hungry
anymore it's
so let's start preparing for the third
raid
okay yeah I'm I'm still trying to to to
find way well it not it will not happen
today but yeah we can take it relatively
easy I guess Bo can you cook me uh some
corn or something yeah do you have
any yeah I do
I'm cooking up some
cornbread I'm coming home cornbread
popping off I'm coming
home yeah the cooks are going to to
workit guys the the toilet the the some
of the boxes here respawned so like the
toilet was empty right oh because
because it's it's it's the ra cuz it
respawn stuff it respawned
everything yay y i so I have some work
water if F the game oh oh because she
was
online well some positive
effects huh only positive
effect I was standing with you and who
were standing I'm I'm behind
you oh on the stairs here oh thank
you nice hi so far if if you grill the
corn just to give you more Health back
or
more whatam call it more hunger back I
think so yeah I'm pretty sure it's more
efficient as a food to eat it
grilled yeah maybe we should try and
search for food
too I know I'm but we have like we have
60 steaks at home from the Big Green
boar oh wait do we did we cook them all
not yet but you know I think we might
have cooked them all really I think so I
mean the steak conversion ratio is so
bad five raw steaks to make one grilled
steak wait wait a
minute I wonder if the green boar
responds
oh food farming place I
think uh I would hope that he wouldn't
respond cuz he's already in my
nightmares true that guy sucks yeah it
was too strong and too big
satisfy find yeah even the trees
[Music]
respawned one so you never know
yeah oh yeah if anyone wants to come
with me to grab the treasure chest
treasure hunting I want to you mean the
loot no I have a treasure
map oh I see oh it just hold on a sec
what wait I see a drop is is it the
yellow thing bi boo no
oh there's a drop though yeah you get
the drop first before it goes away oh
okay and then we can get the buried
treasure wait where did the treasure go
the where my map go I don't know I only
ever saw the drop on the screen I saw
the treasure oh it might be the drop
maybe that must be it okay well let's
let's go over and grab
it yeah already I'm going to head that
way am home oh if anybody wants to come
let's party them
up yeah get yeah can you invite
me well I'll invite you me too I want to
do the treasure chest thing it sounds
fun oh yeah I see the icon the treasure
icon on the map okay I think only you
can see that then bi you're going to
have to lead the way to that but let's
okay let's get the DW the air DW the
DW if you guys have a stone
axe um and get some wood for me because
by hands it takes too long oh I have a
spare axe if you want it oh thank you
I'll take
it Zip Zip Zip Zip Zip Zip Zip Z
sorry just quietly sipping from the
river with my straw hat not even tea
just River w
hey as long as it's flooding FL Flo how
do you say that flowing flowing as long
as it's flowing it's healthy oh I made I
made the axe you made one okay yeah I
made one why are some of the zombies
super
hot Dr because because some people are
super hot yeah hot
zombies people zombie reflects the
streamer
[Laughter]
wait can we go into the snow area don't
we freeze to death or something oh we
have clothes it should be
okay I love snowy area yeah ah it's too
bright my eyes
flashbang why would they why would they
put the drop here they I'm still the one
who uses light
mode yeah she does
g what are you guys planning on doing
there's
AO be careful are we just balling yeah
we're balling right now okay yes we're
doing class increasing our skills Loot
and loot yeah we're going to build a
little house together go oh people
coming
in you are the farmer you if you have
some time today can you try to plant our
super
corn yeah yeah I would love to plant
some super crops super
corn okay um if you uh the the the super
corn seeds are in the new house next to
the fireplace in the food and Medicine
Chest um there is free uh ears of super
corn don't take those just take the
Super corn seeds there's five of them
and if we need more with more grown ears
of super corn I can produce more seeds
because I have some recipe but for now
it's just five seeds here you can you
can take a look question is will the at
the new place now nothing cool in here
um anywhere it's fine I got I got some
magazines though
um oh blade crafting I need that knife
guy I I have heard that the second wave
has already been finished
yes yeah I'm so
[Music]
we survived the second
wave unbelievable are we still going to
be using this house for another wave or
are we doing a different house now well
we might as well use this house because
it's it's well reinforced right good
yeah it's very well reinforced okay got
to continue using what what's good still
all right make the most of it oh my gosh
there's are those lions or Tigers what
are those there's big cats mountain
lions big cats big cat I am a big
cat big
trouble oh big cat hurts oh that was a
bad idea mm yeah I'm dangerous it better
be are you guys question right now are
you doing stuff at a new
[Music]
location um bble has like a treasure
chest and we want yeah I have a treasure
map that I'm mhm looking
for um where did you guys go I left but
I'm waiting for you somewhere close by
okay well I'm going to go to the other
home so I'll stick in a a different VC
I'll see you guys
later next to you okay treasure is can
you kill me
oh ah be cat I see the big cats guys I
found a like radioactive gigantic green
boar
oh it did
respawn it did respawn it gives a lot of
meat if you want to oh if you hunt it
you want to kill it heck yeah okay we
are going on expedition to the Northeast
cuz that's where the treasure is located
Northeast okay I am
around we're going this way or we're
following
bi people knows where it is it's it's
kind of a far track into the snow so
okay well we should be fine be
careful yeah how many kilometers is it
uh how do you
tell well if you mark it on your map
with a quick Waypoint it should it
should tell
you so like if you open your map with M
and then you find where the treasure is
on the map
400 and oh
meters that's not bad
yes okay oh we got to climb up a
mountain
though be like a Skyrim goat should we
get in a different VC do you think oh
they all went to a different VC already
oh okay cool now it's just us explorers
explorers
yay I hope it's a lot of bunch of a
bunch of good stuff yeah I hope it's
good I am
around for do us
proud uhoh
expectations no no we can do it jump
King jump King jump
King we are jump kinging oh there's
zombies up here how is he able to climb
on the mountain Hey sir if you see if
you see a mod for my
spear you get it
you oh this is a difficult climb
oh I'm going to die don't die I got
you stupid Mountain Man dumb Mountain
Man B dummy guy the mountain
dummy what a stupid guy stupid guy you
tell
him you tell him feel bad he's dead
already he's already
literally my good do you do you need do
you do you need cash for something in
this game I don't know nah money has no
meaning any
longer maybe we can burn
it yeah you can use for a fire oh
there's a there's some Villages and
houses around here this when you stand
on a cliff like
that it's difficult to
climb just try your best keep jumping
don't give up jumping yeah you could do
it just become cat you are a
cat are a cat ow my
knee my knee oh there's Bears watch out
oh yeah let's be careful of please no
bears do you guys want to check
out how close is the treasure it's 100
it's on the road it's like next to the
road I'm going to go around this bear
though cuz I'm not yeah I have seven HP
yeah careful about the
bear okay oh this wait I have a shovel
okay we have shovels we're fine yeah if
it's buried treasure it sure is they say
buried stash
oh be careful oh
okay here let's
go I don't see you oh is that you there
a lion a mountain lion oh those are
dangerous that's a z okay I won't attack
it I'll ignore never mind oh no my Bon
is broke oh you do need to dig okay I
have a big circle right here we got to
dig for it all
right
CAU get to digging ladies okay if we all
dig together it'll be really quick work
is it right I am coming
must be around here yeah it's there it's
there's a big circle
now mhm
um so just you guys are in the circle
so okay I guess I'll go a little bit
further so we have a better yeah R you
are right on the
edge okay and
it's shouldn't be too bad it's a big
radius uh-oh usually it shrinks the fur
down you go oh
okay there's a guy behind you oh is
there a dude shooting at him no I'm I'm
shooting at him oh you got it he's got
this hello I'm back welcome back welcome
back is this
a he's eating you he's EA me
oh he died on top oh he's not dead never
mind wait wow he's a T
man oh no my exp I'm in Deb
[Music]
now oh no well that's bio's backpack it
just looks like he's wearing it cuz he
fell down
[Laughter]
like is this a
place yeah I think so bi was the one
that had the circle so yes this is this
is the place it's a very big radius s
yes we got to keep looking just as much
as we can they're going to make us work
for that treasure
okay so just do your best all right I
have a broken leg I need to heal anyway
okay if you look if you stand where you
are
Callie yeah and look where I am this is
how big is the circle you're at the edge
of the the circle I'm at the edge of the
circle so it's it's quite
like that all right let's try digging
around here then hopefully it shrinks
over
time careful behind oh it says we're
getting closer to the
treasure
nice I don't have
weapons you don't have weapons who's
being freaky stop get off my lawn I need
a
weapon nice nice
whoa
nice yeah where were you where it said
we were
closer um I was like right here
is
okay
oops watch out you watch your head I
don't want to blonk
you yeah we're a great digging team look
at all this work we're getting done yeah
I'm glad you guys came with me this was
have taking forever by myself let make a
hole a hole I like
Treasures yeah I hope it's worth it in
high expectations I mean it's a treasure
map how could it not be worth it right
yeah amazing what if it's her like
emotional emotional treasure it's like a
letter like a picture of her it's a
picture dang it how is this going to
help us survive
it says I'm getting closer to the
treasure
again okay let's dig wherever is
sorry you gave me a fright there I dig
you my please don't oh I dig you too
you're
great okay I think I've repaired my
shovel
enough got to be around here somewhere
somewhere you see a yesterday
keep looking for a box ladies yeah uh
also let me open the box since I have
the quest if
possible just tell us what's in it yeah
I I'll let you look and I I'll share
I'll share the loot we all worked hard
for it yeah it was a gr effort the Box
yeah what's in the box what's in the box
what's in the box cuz all I want to do
is just see what's in there I don't even
need the stuff I just want to see that's
the most dissatisfying part just opening
it right just behind like when yesterday
when we did the you know when everyone
was dying fighing The Horde during there
was some downtime and I went to the
backpacks and opened some I didn't take
anything but I opened
it feel that things don't worry super
STIs yeah but I I didn't need the things
so I didn't take them but very
satisfying I hit over here and it said
getting close so
all right all right let's go near where
bi is I I'm glad that the game tells you
when we get close oh that's Rock that's
Solid Rock we supposed to hit the rock
too I don't think I don't think we're
supposed to dig the rock I think it's
probably the dirt part
oh
okay Friendly Fire ended up not being a
very good
idea it's funny yeah it's silly silly
funny time
keep digging ladies keep digging my
thingy broke okay
shovel yes it's okay I repaired it I I
tapped it I I had to stand talking with
it and it's okay now I what if we do
have
toat sandwich oh
sorry I don't I don't think so I think
rock is the the limit bottom yeah uh so
the limit
actually you can break the rock but you
need a better shovel you need to
upgrade well again the the the whole
perimeter is really really big it's like
really really big so mhm I think yeah
you guys aren't even at the edge if you
dig that way so okay it is getting
pretty late we're going to have to be
careful
yeah wonder where we can maybe we can
find a place to hold up in the night
there was a house
nearby stay in the house yeah pull up in
this
hole maybe we could actually like make a
literal you know like a little to like a
little oh like a little hide out yeah
yeah yeah because like if they can't
they can't jump so if we have a place
that is in the middle of this but is
surrounded by hole they can't get to
us we can set up a little campire
together says we're getting closer again
oo the hole the hole got smaller okay
start digging in this way Direction okay
oh that way okay yeah this
way you got it
Captain this treasure is going to be
great I'm
sure I like shovel it's one of my
favorite things to do in this game yeah
it's nice and easy it got it got even I
think it's like somewhere over here you
guys are on the very edge of the
perimeter
now um so like somewhere around where I
am
maybe
oh hope there's some food in
there okay I'm getting we're getting
close again this is we're at the center
of the perimeter now mhm so it should be
around
here we dug that huge big
it's just part of the treasure digging
experience you
know sometimes you got to dig oh yeah
yeah my character is super hungry though
my character is like yo we've been
digging for so
long give me something to eat silence
treasure is important maybe there are
rations in there oh oh oh never mind I
saw thought I saw something sorry no
that was my excited I think I was
someone's foot I was like oh oh never
mind that's just a
foot oops
ow zes the
perimeter again got
smaller
okay I'll take him
out m
F fast cuz it's night time
late one minute until
my leg feels
better good
ni uh I'm going to drink coffee now
yummy
[Music]
coffee did I brew it okay do you like
how I brew it it was okay yeah yeah it
was okay it was just
okay this is your apocalypse you have to
turn down your
invitations oh I found it guys it's here
found it I'm not going to open it you
people go okay hold on oh does anybody
have lock PS oh my god oh
oh no but you can destroy it by okay
let's let's just just smack it a bunch
yeah oh ow ow someone's hitting me hold
on let's let's let's let's dig let's dig
a little bit more around it so we have
room
to I'll be I'll be the the torch holder
now you can guys can see thank you up I
dig
everyone
yeah oh this
is all right I want to make the hole
bigger so we can all smack
it yeah so we can all gather around it
like a campfire yeah
I was going to
take someone's hitting me again oh
no no it's really fast look it's
already it's already
[Music]
1%
stop oh this is a zombie Oh I thought it
was you guys
uhoh I'm
bleeding kill him kill what I killed
you messed
up BR can't believe I'm so
sorry it is what it
is no my
friend it's dangerous to do at night for
sure that's
okay okay
I'm freezing I'm freezing this we got
this we got this poke him poke him poke
him okay he dropped stuff he dropped
something W he dropped a lot of
stuff are you sure that wasn't my
backpack no no he no no your backpack is
in the
corner what' he drop he dropped coffee
vehicle
Offroad
schematic o oh you can you can
oh you can craft vehicle lights I
guess GL wait why it says I'm cold now I
was not freezing before I think it's
just because we were naked for about a
moment a torch or
something all right we'll be opening it
up in no time oh yeah look
yay almost there you know I've noticed
that I don't really have an exp penalty
even though I've died I wonder if they
took it if they took it off for our
server didn't they say they did they
might have said that I did level up
recently even though I died
recently yeah I think that happened
we're playing on Ultra easy
mode nah it's still hard it's still hard
it is ow why would you hit me I got I
got your you can kill me you can kill me
if you
want I want you to check
the it was RA it wasn't me it was R ra
you
murderer I am a
murderer no I don't think so that would
be
awesome I think she meant like um if I
get an XP debuff now but I wasn't even I
wasn't level five
[Music]
so almost there almost almost
there keep it up ladies keep it up this
has been quite a task but I hope it's
right I hope the content it's going to
be so worth going so worth it it's going
to be at least one golden locket with
the lava's
picture mhm mhm I
agree what okay you are
wet W to me it look to to me it looks
like someone's healing it can you heal
the treasure chest it's healing itself
it's magic mag no it's the optical
lotion oh
okay no it's magic get it if all of us
work
together we there we there
yay all right I'm going to open it sorry
open I just want to take a look there
you go you it's full of stuff oh it is
full stuff o ammunition all right I want
to take the 9 mm
ammo and there's a ball there's steel
parts there's bullets bullet casing
shotgun shells silver and gold
nuggets
gunpowder o a
mod as soon as we can make bullets that'
be great what's the I'll I'll take
silver and I'll take gold okay I will
share the treasure feel free to take
stuff okay goes next I'll take the
shotgun I just want the shotgun shells
and then for the steel Club Parts I will
take those just because I'm Club M so
I'll take those um and yeah there's like
a whole bunch of really hold what is
this there's a robotics there's a wooden
bow people like bows there's a Bowman
can I get the
bow there's a nice I'll take the
robotics
then cuz I kind of wanted to go into
like engering maybe a this bow is going
to be so cool yay sure you The Bowman
magazine magazine I am I am leveling up
the
bow yeah there is a a Bowman magazine in
the box back at the house you should
read
it yeah get super good oh I have a I'm
going to put this it's robotics Parts
okay I don't have any space can someone
take it yes I have this for you a mod
for your spear no
thank
you
oh it's
cool beautiful here
actually no no no no no what is this no
that's my so we go to this little town
this little area colie
yeah with a flag on top and I I am over
in cucumber so I can't take the cucumber
too I think we should at least take the
ammunition because cuc I don't have any
guns but for the others keep we will be
able to make bullets
eventually eventually oh a big
cat I want to just swap
some nice to make oh oh there's like a
he or something but it's dark and do you
see that with the red eyes behind you
right behind you you in the tree where
I'm pointing with my arrow where I'm
pointing with my arrow oh oh my God what
the I'm going to shoot it is that oh my
God are you sure got to shoot it yeah
let's do
it oh boy that seems like a that's a
werewolf that looks like a werewolf a
werewolf werewolf kill it kill it a
wo it's really strong have spe all where
is it where is it where we are oh God no
no spe
Arrow oh my
God is camping where my back is there a
is
also strong
ah why is the bear attacking me what
have I done against the bear that's just
rude what is that
CER ow ow
ow uh-oh uh-oh no no
uh-oh got
this behind me I didn't think I think I
did any
damage a oh I'm
cold I I crashed I'll be right there oh
okay uh can you make sure my backpack is
still there I hope it didn't respawn
everyone's backpack is yet still there
so it's fine
but I'm
coming okay okay okay okay we could try
kiting him between oh that thing three
shots you three shots but it's going to
be so worth it you can kind of jump out
of its out of its attack if you jump
backwards oh yeah Dark Souls it a little
bit Yeah Dark Souls it okay just make
sure that it doesn't deagro and run away
shoot it every once in a
while someone's eating my body I can
hear
it going to little okay that's my
backpack is it yeah it is
have be
arrows friends with the zombies it seems
like yeah maybe they're like wh dog
zombies or something my back right there
and a bear all chilling together in the
same area camping over your backpacks
back
back try and lead him
away okay I got I got I got the backpack
my backpack
I'm taking care of the
zombie oh my back back my back back my
back back you sure we can fight this
thing we can we can it's just it's just
we just got to we just got to kite it
somehow it's possible trap him in the
hole maybe light him on Fire Light him
on fire good idea he does not catch fire
not catch fire okay I killed one I
killed one nice I killed him out line it
feels like it do do any damage
I why not why what makes you say that
like is there no blood when you hit them
or yeah
yeah maybe
you oh yeah now it does
okay okay I just got to drop some stuff
then I'll Attack I I I I put like 20
bullets into the wall
maybe he's almost dead I don't know yeah
he must be okay I'm going to shoot him
oh there's two of them oh my God two now
and a bear and a m
lion well we're not in a good situation
everyone we got this we got this we got
this wish I could snipe him your arm is
broken
me okay maybe we don't got this
maybe we should keep going shoot him
shoot
him he's just standing
there oh I killed him I killed him I
killed him you kill it oh my god let's
go nice nice nice oh he gave so much
loot really oh what did you got I don't
know but I'm going to
die oh Lord
I'm dead again
mured I'm dead again I think we all are
a little dead inside especially after
that it is still night time so they are
super fast
still even have time to run
away oh Yik oh God the bear to now
please bear me
[Music]
no I broke my leg
oh how do you keep breaking your
leg jum you
cursed you
cursed it's messed up oh man leave her
alone I'm so cursed
ah
stop wait wait don't shoot them yet
there's like a bunch of zombies behind
you kill him first
oh up so
much it's okay it'll be worth it I
wonder what the other guys are
think probably they probably think we're
doing like a super hard raid or
something
I mean it is in a way it is
hard no no no
no leave me alone leave me alone leave
me alone leave me alone oh there's so
much
stuff is the loot really worth
it
please wait don't shoot them there's
like two people behind you
ter
shot okay I'll
them okay okay I'm dead my is not broken
anymore okay that's good I guess
nice think the the the the werewolf
healed me thank
you see it's just
misunderstood okay my backpack is
surrounded by three dangerous
animals you could like go slowly and
then grab look at the animals I can't
shoot the animals
down you can you can't yeah I can okay
oh okay it's the wolf is going to run
toward me I'm just going to b b it
okay run run run run run found a
different oh they found a different
person it's me it's me
help ow sorry you got in the way of the
the my gun I try to shoot okay we got
one we got one
we I just picked up a flower
and yes Kitty yes okay I'm going to go
for the bear
now the bear probably the a good
me y okay bear is Dead bear is dead okay
one more one
more watch out for the
W okay he'll go towards his
[Music]
aggressor yes the bajillion Stakes for
everyone level 10
okay it's only it's only the wolf left I
if I can shoot the wolf dead we'll be
good okay okay right I got a shotgun
it's a terrible shotgun but we can maybe
make it
work dang
it yeah eat my body yeah yeah eat my
body get
distracted no no no no no that's you
that's you
No it should be almost it I put like 20
bullets in that
guy
ow we got this confus confuse him come
on yeah yeah yeah confuse him it
works my
body
H be make sure to don't get M my
backpack because we died in the
same are the Wolves killable yes I
killed one I killed one before the
zombie just killed the freaking wallf
what
I I want to see what it
is I want to see the loot and the watch
are the zombies behind you wait oh
God she sorry I just took I took shotgun
shells that's it I took shotgun shells
and a club magazine oh I'm taking the 9
mm
um and I'll take the juice cuz I might
get
thirsty I'm going to
[Laughter]
die oh wait actually I can make myself a
what I guess I gu this's about to be
broken that was interesting H Callie I'm
going to drop some ammo for you
thanks oh sorry I took someone's
primitive outfit here
[Music]
where if I didn't repair something in
time is it broken forever no you just
need a repair kit uh here oops sorry I
will here I dropped a repair kit for
you thank
you nice my out I can't pick up my
bicycle unless it the storage is fly
oh okay that's like laying on the side
yay should we go to this area
now yeah yeah okay let's go okay you
guys go ahead I'll I'll be there in just
a
sec okay I think this one shouldn't be
too hard oh never mind no no no no no no
no
no no no no why
oh it's pretty it's pretty
strong
scary they shoot
me I I I I don't want to do that oh this
one I I have a perk where if I step on
mes they don't go off
ooh pretty
cool IDI
oh by the way can you invite me to the
party I I guess I got off what I locked
off I got you thank you welcome to the
party welcome to the club this does seem
like a pretty strong yeah maybe we
shouldn't go
here
y guys are you sure no
I don't know if it's a good idea it
might not be a good
idea mark it oh
hello
oh is there a dude up there oh there is
a
dude want to go up yeah go up f up
there
ow why doesn't have a
[Laughter]
shoe feet drop some cool loot or
something
lame I just got to Bonk him in the head
uh there is a giant bear by the
way hold on hold on hold on this one is
giant hold on let's shoot him and then
climb up onto
this yeah good idea uh not good idea not
good idea climb up climb up he stuck
he's stuck he's stuck he's stuck wait
uh he's stuck he's stuck he
stuck I'm boy
hole he's big oh no no no no no he's not
stuck anymore oh he's dead I killed
him good
job yay thought it was going to
be yucky I see something weird in green
but I spitting at us oh it's the big
pole oh he's throwing up e
[Music]
e Yu
no
guys oh he had mag guys there's a bunch
turn around there's
a they broke the
door leave me alone
what is the on my screen was like a
giant
thing
no not like
this
dang
[Music]
e eating
me why would you go there we can take he
eating
me I got the I got the penalty by the
way you got the penalty
yeah yeah
really oh no actually no never mind I de
oh my leg is spraying that dude willon
die
that's what the orange eyes just don't
die well the loots probably really
good I hope
so guess we'll find out I went into that
one building and there seems to be a
cave underneath a
cave yeah the building with the open
door where I'm standing right
now let's go another police guy be
careful Oh
e oh no not not me not me not me not me
okay he can
climb I
can't I'm so bad oo I got
XP help the strongest enemy on the
planet following me if they have I got
you I got you thank you
rough I think I need
help okay where are you so here but my
backpack is on the top of this Tower and
there's a zombie do they keep uh spawn
spawning up there there's no way there
was that many up there no she just I
want to I want to I'm just going to
snipe him okay he was following her and
thenk
okay oh thank you more for sacrif iing I
got some good hits
in oh
God guys exploded there is the the
stairs are not there anymore now okay
you can build new stairs I think how
stairs oh is
more guys I under underleveled for this
so yeah yeah should leave
let's stuff let's get get her stuff
first
uhoh I di oh my poor my poor bearded
M I need to find a way to get my stff
back these dudes are crazy strong
actually I'm freezing
death we got some good loot from the
zombies were that were that we killed
though that is
true ah I'm sure that we can take on
like two and three skull places though
yeah May let's just
try let's try building her
build building blocks yeah so that she
can't go up yeah should be fine unless
someone can make St of letters I don't
let's see I can make some building
blocks up so let me get my
wood it's a lot of enemies it's a lot of
enemies okay no problem oh that's you C
CRA don't hit me please I always stabbed
you let me
see L more oh wait we can make wooden
lettuce as well ow ow ow did you just
break
to up okay
oh my God it's so far
away they so big oh there on my body
we're doing we're doing it we're doing
it okay I died in front of there maybe
someone can kite them and then someone
builds the stairs uh the stairs or
ladder like I have a ladder maybe that's
easier uh so ra since you don't have
your stuff try to kite them away from
where your stuff is so that we can build
a ladder I am the bite I'm the bite come
here guys hello oh you did it yeah yeah
yeah come here I'm there but I don't
there's too much stuff in it hold up
I'll finish making the stairs wait I can
I can go
up I
think I think yeah come
on
[Laughter]
yay okay good one sec I'll try to don't
die never mind o oh my God this is
strong okay that should do it I finished
the
stairs thank
you you got
this
yay thank you get out of
here okay now let's make like a banana
and get the hell out of here
o run run run run run run run run okay
okay let's go
back time to
leave that was very
bad ding ding ding
ding hey worth it worth
it worth it worth it worth it worth
it worth it worth it really fast you
think so it's not giving up
should we go back home do you guys want
to go to the Traer do a quest sure let
do let's go to the
tra he is still following me um I think
if we follow this path it'll lead home
back down oh God
okay yeah zombie eat the chicken the
chicken looks really delicious eat him
are we going to the new home or the old
home h i wonder to recuperate maybe the
new one
okay we go hit the Traer and do some
Quest till we all get
bikes
know don't know a new house oh that's
really far oh it's right next to the
Traer okay okay makes sense yeah I think
everywhere's pretty far at this point
cuz we're up in the mountains the
mountains dangerous we're we're at like
the higher level
area
mhm but hey now we know yeah who would
have known that five and a half or four
and a half schools is too hard for us
yeah that was a
little a little maximum silliness moment
it's worth my back got stucked in the
worst possible place you have to find
out your limits sometimes to test your
limits exact I'm on top of the
mountain you're Queen of the world I'm
Queen of the world I got all the way on
the top that's pretty cool following be
Waring yeah I'm just I'm just going the
road path because my bike probably can't
climb the
mountain
[Music]
okay okay I'm going back
down may take a while at least I'm
exploring the area too by doing this so
un look new map oh it is a big
map is you know Rara you had a quest
activated uh to clear a
house oh oh is it this clear the area
head to R Point thing okay yeah it's
like 1 km away we should we should all
go to Trader and grab Quest so we can
just bang
okay we can do Quest and we can do
everybody's Quest that so we can level
up big
time sounds good to me I'm still
wondering how we get number one the
workbench number two make CMO workbench
I think
is make
the forged ahead
magazine no I think it's called
something else doesn't didn't kiata have
like a bunch of them she said oh she
must have found him I hope she keeps
working towards that cuz we are behind
in terms of workbench yeah let me double
check uh she said
[Music]
workstations yeah it's called
workstations magazine and she has them I
think
maybe maybe today we get some Magazine
from the from
this the the quests hopefully yeah well
also what I'm realizing is that a lot of
the houses around here especially are
like a lot of schools like we thought
three skulls was scary some of these
homes in the snow are like five skulls
yeah yeah I think snow areas probably
later oname we we can come back but no
for
now for now let's just stick to the area
we're in and try and Conquer that
area yeah GL the treasure here though
that was nice there's there's so many
cars in this snowy Village that we can
loot though but I'm
leaving I don't have any any space so
yeah cucumber cucumber any space
we too cute there a lot of
zomies what
zombies how can it be why there's a
chicken in the middle of nowhere I'm
going to kill it yeah he there for you
why why did the chicken cross the road
oh here we go cuz it wanted you get to
the other
side cuz he's not a chicken wait I I I
haven't thought of a joke yet uh what oh
an air
drop I'm close to it okay so we got to a
new home mhm oh okay I wanted the
chicken cross the
road is somebody why did it CH cross the
road you say cuz it's wanted to go on
the other side no because it is trying
to get to the stupid person's house
knock
knock huh knock knock who's there the
chicken
stupid pretty funny that is really mean
do that people you are not nice Shame
Shame what mean shame it's a good joke
it's
funny I'm going to go to I'm at the
house because I followed the I'm going
to go to sh and ask if she wants to join
us if not it's okay too okay I'll be
right back oh I'm at the old house oh
no I follow the wrong
way well never mind because doing that
means I can just go grab
myself yeah are you okay
yeah I'm actually super close to Rus
Quest but we can go to the Traer
let's meet at the trader we meet at the
trader okay tra I'm going to drop by and
drop stuff at the old house cuz I'm
cucumber okay me
too those S I lost my spear with fire
yeah we'll find it again it was very
good
Noble I grab
everything I
can so I can move to the new house
a lot of supply drops are happening I
wonder if I wonder if they're like
backed up or something from ra being
AFK oh yeah yeah was all
plans of course that's why we're getting
all these air drops
now so I should call them supply drops
that's what they are supply
drops why have a
so many Stone Spears
the these I can get the
anals
iron 100 wooden cubes that's kind of
nice
Vier we die okay I'm going to oh
yum I'm going to get some food probably
a good idea does anybody have wood to Fu
the fireplace so I can purify some
water I do have wood but I'm very far
away I'm at the trader okay that's
okay I wonder what the others are up to
right now maybe they're doing their own
thing wa can I can you request some meat
uh I put in the Box yes but I need I
need uh I could grab the fire wood yes I
go grab the wood
okay I am the Woodman
Woodman The
Lumberjack get in
food that's my life
now oh yeah find something to make make
your life's work in this game that's the
best
way I'm not a very good killer so far
though right
now I'm okay but this don't worry it's
difficult anyway you know
yeah okay people I got the food for you
and I'll drop here
thank you there you go okay I
will cook here for now take the take
these corn breads for
food
[Music]
M I don't know why you
bleeding
okay okay
oh I want to make a bunch of bacon and
eggs oh it sounds good oh breakfast can
I get some of that b yeah yeah you can
have some I want some of that could use
a
breakfast but I'm at the Traer I'll
bring it to you I'll bring you breakfast
breakfast delivery yeah and then I have
brought a guest a guest hello who I
brought a guest hello to the party hello
yes I would like to moch your XP if you
will have me yes of course we'll have
you welcome no problem thank you don't
tell the other party why I left
them oh are they not getting XP right
now huh oh no uh I was going to try
mooching off of them but they were too
far away to mooch off of so it was not
helpful I see yeah you can mooch exp off
of us anytime oh well thank you I
appreciate
that sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry I couldn't see sorry I was focused
oh excuse
me thank you we a bit of a silly
Bunch all right I am here toit okay
we're ready okay we're going to the tra
we're going to do class pretty soon
we're just at the at the house at the
old house store and stuff and making
food okay I will head to the trader in
the meantime
okay wait wait we all going to go to the
trader in a second I think if you want
to together if you want to go together
I'm trees on the way okay okay I have I
put more farming magazines into the old
house chest by the way sh oh thank
you yes please Harvest Moon for us I beg
of you yes Harvest Moon yeah I think at
this point I've died more often from ra
killing me
than let's for my
spikes but to be yeah the spikes too
has six player kills she is the second
most player killer besides me messed up
you guys are messed
up okay I'll put this duct tape
here I guess they got close to the door
unless that's you guys damaging spikes
near
it oh
maybe what would they attack it randomly
if there's no humans there though I
wonder I don't know so I think they
would have gotten through that but maybe
maybe they did
okay buy some lockpicks there's
something called a gatherer surface
cooling increases the rate of du
collection yeah okay I'm ready the
breakfast will take a while to cook so
like while we's party while we quested
up breakfast we'll be ready when we get
back yay all right okay
uh I need a
new head I'm going to check on the farm
near here okay they have not grown from
what I have uh last Saw but
why cuz it takes seven days to
grow it takes seven days to die it takes
seven days to
grow I don't I don't know but it feels
like it it's technically been like two
weeks
okay I got B do you have the meat for by
any chance um I I'm using the meat to
cook bacon and eggs but it will take
like oh okay okay it'll take
about 10 minutes cuz cooking is okay no
problem it takes a lot wa wait the farm
plot has to be like loaded in to
actually grow so if it's too far away
from us it just doesn't grow oh that's
really I don't know
it's kind of lame unless unless have it
I can IFK for S
days no it's grown yay yay okay scared
I'm so tired of those have to
harvest I'm so
done so done with what with the spikes
in in the entrance I'm breaking them
why we need we we need them when the
raid starts no have to go straight just
here they want just no I cannot go
straight I'm sorry she she would fail
like the drunk
test yeah yeah the glasses
test okay I had enough she's done with
it okay I'm going to
go all right well we got some oh
actually okay I okay there is this one
area that I really want to go to and
it's east of where we are right now we
can go to it I marked I marked it lots
of stuff and it's just like it had like
a like a store with a bunch of magazines
I already took a bunch of them but is
this big like area with the
lake sh I have an outfit for you a
farmer outfit it's in weapon ammo chest
in our house okay I I will go equip uh
your new fashion thing we got it just
for you okay okay
[Laughter]
bye kind I'm coming to the store if you
look at the square uh you know this farm
that looks like a flag and then the road
keeps going and then there's a little
like an h and then at the body of the
H it's like a big area
H well I don't know how big your
map in that area if you've been there
so can I mark
it uh maybe we should go to the trader
first since Callie's waiting for us
there oh okay I didn't know that yeah
point I can head there now okay are we
going to the trader right
yeah okay okay okay can't wait to eat my
raw
egg yummy I love Ro egg now oh you do
yeah I like I like ra egg over rice yes
I love raw egg over rice but I have I
have to like uh filter the white out cuz
I don't like egg
white oh it's too it's too
goopy oh what I like to do is I just
break the I break the yolk and I keep
the egg
whites you you break the yolk and you
keep yeah wait wa don't you fry your egg
when you go it put it on Rice oh I think
they mean raw yeah you just raw raw egg
on I feel like that's um that's what
they call it in Japan isn't it yeah it's
not it's not really I don't know if it's
safe to do in the US it's not it's
definitely not I don't think it's safe
to
do it's safe in some countries but most
most countries it's not so yeah America
hates us though they want us to choke in
our own
eggs but I tried it I tried it in Japan
like egg over rice like with egg it's so
good so
tasty
[Music]
yeah I want to go to Japan eat all the
food I want to go back too actually I I
went to a dennise in America and then I
remembered the Denise in Japan and it
was
like I think I don't remember it was was
it Denny's do you know that one place
where I got hamburger like onion soup
french onion soup with hamburger
it Den I love Denny and Japan that was
really good it was not like it wasn't it
wasn't french onion soup but it was
really good liked it I never been to the
one in America but everyone keep telling
me that the the one in Japan is better
it's totally well it's totally different
because Denny's in Japan is like a
breakfast place primarily and Denny's in
in Japan is like a family restaurant
yeah it's also quick stop for truckers I
always stop there to grab the rice with
the burger and the dam
glass the Hamburg Hamburg steak thingy
it's tasty oh it's so good you guys are
making me hungry to be fair it is my
fault yes sori and I would just go to
those family restaurants all the time
like Denny's and Jonathan we were just
like let's go get food and ice
cream yeah oh yeah the parfit they make
there is crazy good too they make
amazing
parfit the other day I was like okay you
know this was I've been having a lot of
fun I want but I want I want to um
what's it called uh treat myself I was
like okay theoretically what if I you
know for because ra has thank you ra ra
does have like uh um space because uh I
I and since we're in different we stream
different times right I was thinking if
I visit her I can just steal her PC I
was like okay what if I go just just to
sit out and food
you yes
please I'll be there dream for me I'll
be there in a few months and then you
can have you can flip
your you can flip food for you
girls who wants
FAS yay make P for everyone actually I
made I make amazing meatballs my
meatballs are crazy good because my
grandma taught me how to make them do
you do you use bread pums and your
meatballs yeah
a she knows I'll food party yes a food
party I would love that yeah yummy back
there at some point we should do we
should do a food a food party but themed
so like for example you can only bring
like a dish that is the first letter of
your name so I would bring a be dish
that's
cute I'll bring is is my second name
okay yeah yeah
whatever pizza pizza pizza I'm here I'm
here almost I'm here
too pink yeah I do look like pink Keanu
um I want to ask a question real quick
bi um do you I saw in you have the
you're in the room with the big bed
right on the second
floor no that's me oh that's you you
have two forged ahead magazines are you
going to use those cuz kiar is really
close to yeah no I told her I told her
that you can take them but I don't know
if she okay cool maybe she maybe she
took them
already okay I'm here very close maybe I
I I'll tell her too oh wait you're at
the quest area her I'll be right back no
I'm at the I'm at the TR I'm going to
accept the quest and then we can all
just do our Quest
together I just took whatever is the
closest Quest it's okay we can take
double of the prices with one Quest but
wait are all Quest like shared
automatically yes
okay just you know don't die is the
thing cuz if you die and you've done a
bunch of quests you lose all those
quests okay yeah we have the same Quest
Mory yeah that's okay that's fine that's
good oh I got a I got a special job you
better take this job I'm not yeah cuz
you got your bike you we are expanding
trade rout to the southeast tell the
folks at Trader genen oh we can get
Trader Jen been Anon oh I hope she's
nicer yeah there's a cute girl she
that's the cute girl by the way Mor
you're a little quiet for me I already
have you 200% as well s hold on just a
sec let me give better now do I like
talk what do we do I take any Quest or
yeah take any Quest and we will we will
all share it which one should we go to
first um ohy do you guys do you guys see
if you zoom out of the map opening trade
routes B Boo at the South I I see a
fetch quest for you um it's you fetch
it's southeast of the trader it should
say opening trade routes bble do you
guys see that on the map I will I will
South South where southeast of the map
if you zoom like out as far as you
can
I I I will follow you if you if you if
you don't see it that's okay we can do
other people's Quest first and then I'll
grab that trade rout I see I see tier
two fetch bioo yeah okay that's the one
I see and then that's probably just a my
special Quest then so we can do that
done a bunch of quests we got to do more
quests
um I to meet the cute
girl oh special Quest is not shared okay
I see oh okay that's why we got to
that's why we got to go do these quests
okay let's do let's do your guys' quest
first D leaves in her her pink hair
hu I'm coming people can you try
something can you take out your bicycle
uh hi you constantly Hing okay so sorry
I miss I missed a
piece um okay I'm standing on it now
try doesn't work a apparently you can
get a seat for your bicycle though that
you can carry two
people oh that's so
cute car oh yeah I want a motorcycle
that's what I want o car and I want to
drive into the which
are we going to are we going to the
highlighted one in Orange I don't know I
was going to go to your uh your fetch
one cuz it's the closest
one is that I don't see that tier two
fetch B boo okay I'll go to that tier
two fetch
B it's next to the new home no yeah it's
pretty close by we're all kind of close
to it oh hi my hello am I going the
wrong hold on a second you're going the
right way you're going right right yeah
make it two I'm near you oh nice okay
just follow you and your
bicycle moving compared to me in
myc you you all get bikes you just got
to do a few more class you
know
how 10 I want to do 10 oh I don't think
I've even come close to
that in general so all the different
quests which is a new home
okay I am at the
residence just come to B Boo's icon I am
at the exclamation point okay heading
there oh there's a it's really big I see
it
too
nice time for some kill old fashion kill
uh by the way later can we can we go to
the new house because I don't know where
it is is this this one yeah yeah don't
don't forget to leave like a a
checkpoint there so you can go back
anytime okay are we all here the Box yep
I I'm near your fetch Quest oh wait I'm
the wrong one I'm a different different
fetch Quest it's okay wait yeah oops
okay thank
you let me just pass the Washington it's
very close ow
ow sorry it might have been my club my
tired kie every time you say Club you
have you afterwards you have to
go okay I am now at the McMill the
club oh nothing good okay I'm ready to
go going to start let's do it all right
I can't wait to move they're waking
up someone hit
[Applause]
me I don't want to hit anyone
so I will just stay put oh they're dead
good job we're good many hands make
quick
work what if we what if we bait all wait
wait wait wait guys guys guys guys guys
what if we bait all the zombies and then
put them in here and then we turn on the
vial and then they burn to the
crisp sounds a good
idea okay I'm going to wait here at the
vial oh oh never mind you can't turn it
on again you can't turn it on again
never mind
hot oh they were doing something they
were doing something strange in
there
Yay good job good job
team got I got you I'll be the lighter I
will light the way
my you are the light of Our Lives
desire do we Aspire spreading out like
wild fire wild
fire never I
ever take the chance with my
li this is such a cute kchen it's
lagging a cute house I'd love to live in
a place like this spear time without the
zombies of course there's some cornmeal
in there I don't know how oh I'm also
low on
stamina oh can you climb this rope to
get up
here a you can oh
oh oh G wait hey let
me hey I hear it I hear something it's
the
batties want to clim the Rope oh you did
can't do it I
can't okay my spear takes at least 10
hits you'll have time to
help I need
C picture I want it so cute can I get it
can't tell if it's
lagging yeah I can't climb the
Rope got
it never mind how the heck did you guys
get up
there climb the Rope I'm building
blocked wa why are things still on fire
wait you just climbed the Rope no it's
not working ow ow why are you kidding
I'm sorry I thought you were a zombie
[Music]
I have a name on
me going to bleed out she can't
read um
Goodbye Oh no you
died a punctuation I'm so sorry
KN dang was that bad you there I think
we can go down here uh you can come down
but I am still Ed by Yes actually come
down I will not go down then I will
shoot from
afar
uh-oh well he's wearing a
helmet like fish in a barrel come on no
no good job no
yeah
[Music]
yay good
job I'm I'm
back good good job to
you I found steroids that picture cute
you going to take it can I have the cat
picture oh cute I wish I could get the
cat picture yeah I want the cat picture
so
bad but you can't did it just get
destroyed you can't keep it I guess no
no you just destroy
there was also do
here o mag
supp all right we can destroy things to
uh harvest the materials at
least okay I finished the class how
about you guys I have not um you have to
closer though you have to check like
your the distance the distance away from
you you have to check the distance oh I
think I'm fig out I found a one
everybody has their own their own uh
sack they got to find yeah ah I found
the White River but I didn't pick it up
oh my God what is how do you know the
quest um if you if you're done it said
it'll say return do you remember I don't
see anything oh maybe because I
died I don't have the quest
anymore I didn't start it that might the
case
oh so I need to find something it's
called a sack
okay here Cy I'll give you a present ASA
sorry I killed you no it's not going to
fall maybe I just did something
wrong uh 3.3 2.2 it's probably upstairs
it's a mod that
reduces uh durability loss let me go in
the kitchen and try to CL up cool thank
you yeah I think it might be up here
wow you guys could not
clim hey I found
it
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah oh good job good job oh my oh y I
found it it's up here behind the thing
got it all right we're good who else
needs what I'm still looking for mine I
am unfortunately a little blind is it up
here maybe it's behind this thing this
is where mine was I don't know but I
think I think it's below here or near me
right now cuz cuz I'm 7 up here in the
Attic oh 7 it's got to be below you
unless oh okay oh it might be in the
Attic like uh I'm in the attic but I
it's a it's like a brown
bag a brown bag okay it is below me okay
let me look uh underneath
then not the corer Satchel oh it is a
corer satchel I found a cooking grill
but there's something in here
D oh that then that's somebody else's
cor your Satchel Maybe here the second
flooor wait is that mine
no get gosh I will never find a little
bit confused about how to like do the
quests so what it says on the top on the
top right what is says the winning
residence I think if you died then it
probably like stopped already oh yeah
you failed the quest if you die yeah oh
okay okay okay no problem we still have
plenty request to do the yeah it's fine
it's fine no worries just might want to
make sure that I'm not accidentally like
not doing the stuff
properly cuz I'm a little
slow no problem it looks like a satchel
right yeah it looks like a satchel it's
not going to be okay it looks like a
brown let me know if you guys find a
satchel in the basement perhaps I I know
what is this Satchel I mean I don't know
if it's the same for us it's um it's
going to be her own Satchel oh it spawns
it spawns satchels for all of us I
believe okay then wow I am not really
good at ice
spy doing your
best all I know is at least like near
the attic or below the attic that's the
only issue yeah beyond that I don't
know okay how about how about what I do
is I'll go the Attic and I'll destroy my
way down okay yeah okay okay that's
going to be my thing now force it go for
it yeah no
problem it's a great idea oh oh there's
a compass bar too
okay most dissatisfying thing is when
you find a secret item kind of oh why
did you oh sorry sorry sorry
sorry and then it's like MTR has very
little in it yeah it's my favorite I see
a satchel on the attic it was hiding it
was hiding behind something that's where
M was over here this one oh you're so
smart thank you my my beibs yeah wait
but that's where mine was hold up oh
it's empty actually never mind it's not
mine however it was very cute of you to
have almost found it you don't think
it's going to be at the like the
freaking roof right wait there's a
locked door right here wait can I see
her
it's not it's not up here is it we can
we can see each other's satchels yeah
I'll check the
roof it's in the ground floor it tells
me if it's up or
down it's at the first floor okay I'm
going to going to destroy my way
down maybe I don't need to go on the
roof but you know what maybe I want to
go it has to be at the garage
okay
yummy there was a satcha at the garage I
think okay it has to be it has to be
like here come on okay I see it I see it
right below okay
it's 5000 got
it got it don't don't don't say yeah
yeah wait is a freaking vent is that how
I couldn't find it oh my freaking
God messed up it was an event okay I'm
done nice okay shall we go North to do
the one up north
yeah it's almost night time me and
my yeah it should be an easy one just a
clear Quest
let's should we wait until this morning
because the zombies are a little bit
more no we're overpowered this is only
two skulls yeah I'm going to stay
behind Okay I believe
this one right
wait that's still burning how I think
it's the one over here
actually yeah it's the one over
there wait wait uh my my quest already
activated here for some reason maybe you
have two different
ones oh no no no no Maybe not maybe
not never mind I think I think we do
this one twice because there's alie's
Quest and Ra's Quest easy
okay
okay okay now I see it it says like
clear areas and stay within yeah yeah I
hear them don't leave the
area oh they're behind they're behind oh
they're behind the door oh no behind
behind us good job soive the zombies are
helping us open the door thank you
zombies appreciate that oh just kidding
they're not here I'll keep the door
unlocked so we don't get
cornered good
idea that's a lot of and we should
probably close any
doors I you want to I'm getting
shreded uh does anybody have food
because I'm dying I have some steak I
have eight eggs you can have some
eggs nice stay down you dead okay
thank you no that's not it I hear them
ah there's a there's a basement there's
a basement so dark got to be
careful there's a large lad watch out
for the large
lad a large L need a club I found a
key I'm going to stay behind I am
bleeding bandage you're bleeding do you
need a
bandage uh it's okay I have one
it oh my God the eye F the the light
flickering it's
so it's spooky down here guys do you
have the key here Siri here ick do you
have it too there's a key here do you
see it as well or is it uh a key I just
have clear areas I don't see a key no
right like hanging key behind you oh a
hanging key well I found out if you come
if you come to the basement I found like
a little secret passage okay there well
if anyone finds something that's locked
like a door or something that says
requires que let me know because okay
okay I need to eat all my eggs I am
dying eat your eggs you already eat them
I I am I have eaten all eggs I need
don't die otherwise the quest is not
going to be
complete wait where are we
going I oh we can climb up there's an
attic oh okay the garage I got a farming
book for you
sori oh thank you I can live up
my semi piece why doesn't me me I'm like
near death so I'm just going to chill oh
who is using arrows were you using
arrows C me me too okay I have a book
for you for that too where did they go
did you guys go from the basement we
went from the basement we found some
loot but no enemies so you don't have to
come oh I hear enemies and I do not want
to die where where are you I'll save you
I'm going back to the garage oh no I'm
not dead
yet it's just that you you stabbed me
pretty hard my girl oh I'm so sorry I
have bandages it's okay it's okay no I
already fixed it I I was going to die
from blood uh blood loss I'm pretty okay
we finished oh y okay finished now we
got to do it twice okay we got to do it
again yeah we'll do it again yay y i
curiosity if if you die before turning
in a quest do they reset like what
happens yeah you don't get that Quest so
let's try not to die ladies to die at
all not available until 149 so just wait
a minute okay everybody repair
yourselves if you
need bandage maybe I can make you you
can make take
this thank you B sorry take this will
that heal me I killers and BL thank you
that one can I drink the blood for there
you go okay okay oh oh here okay thank
you wait that's vehicle Adventures why
am I why do I have vehicle Adventures
wait that was supposed to be Southern
farming where' the farming go yeah no
you you want me to ride a bike or
something I'll get the blood
bag wait where where the thing go I
think I can I Dro it back again too
maybe oh I can craft a first I can't
craft
yet I will take the
painkiller nice oh if you have one
vehicle Adventure I'll give you the
second one people because then we can
stack it because I'm almost over
in does anybody has a first eight
Band-Aid oh I do no I can't craft it yet
either or maybe Al food will help here
you go I dropped
it oh thank you shouldn't dehydrated
going to die understand oh B use it
yourself yeah yeah yeah yeah oh I have a
first aid kit I'll be fine oh okay okay
dehydrated that's fine oh
no what is that
sound that was theor while we're waiting
you know let's just you know hit up a
house or
something I LEL
up I'm going to go get someone
El we can't eat the snow I'm
eat cat
food y y yum yum yumy cat food
y this way
is I can't see my cursor that is the
river behind that house oh yeah I'm back
W my bow now makes 20% more damage you
why you make it cool yeah I was going to
make one of my I'm having an armor issue
but problem is uh I don't have cloth to
make new armor so it is what it is I
have I have cloth you have cloth I have
six yeah thank it thank you I need as
much cloth as I can get thank you so
much all right let me drop you some here
you
go
cloth can someone come to the river with
me I'm
thirsty okay come come I have no I don't
have juice is there nearby water I mean
I have murky water but I'll I'll like
lose five Health if I drink murky water
let's go let's go I come go I think it's
this way yeah just behind the
house is it
here yeah it's down
here okay I am dying dehydration holy
crap I am so glad that there is a river
nearby wait how do you sleep from the
river uh stand next to it and press you
have to have empty hands with empty
hands yeah
oh but you might get
diarrhea that's okay I'll take it over
death am I now not too bad I
guess oh also yeah I need a little
water let's see I found a
cooking how do you make painkillers
they're really
good I don't know so oh someone needs to
like take medicine or the dirty s
I am still good to go actually I have
not been hurt by the water yet that's
crazy to me I
know I need to heal I'm so thirsty how
much do I need to drink you need a sip
sip gulp gulp how do I heal oh oh I'm
I'm taking
damage I am taking damage you should be
able to just equip the bandage and then
left click it no I did it but I'm still
like
4 uh-oh oh don't leave me I hear zombies
and I don't want to
die that's worrisome maybe you took
damage from drinking or something oh
yeah I'm pretty sure I did oh they're
chasing okay we can do the the mission
again you guys yeah okay wait in like 10
minutes we're almost ready oh they
dropped something yeah wait there's
another oh that's you
okay I need f
uh I
have diar though yeah food would be nice
here here here I have one egg I'm sure
ladies I'm sure if we do the quest then
they might like respawn the boxes and
maybe we can find some food in there
yeah okay okay I have
blueberries I have one egg fresh from
the PO wa oh no the sandwiches made me
sick
uhoh okay we've begun the
quest okay just you're just going to
have to fight with Terry sorry didn't oh
no I'm hungry now oh no it's okay it's
okay I'm going to break in didn't mean
to do that all right I'm going to stay
behind so I don't die yeah just stay
behind we'll we'll take it for you
hello I don't want to hit
anyone think I can do my this
time I'm staying behind actually
especially as an Archer yeah no worries
you guys stay behind we'll take care of
it tank thank you I don't want to lose
my
quests oh oh oh wait hey there's people
here I thought they were
zombies look look it's a whole gang yeah
there's G FAA and then
God what's up
what's up oh I think they they have to
wait for us to finish the quest for they
to start mhm uh oh oh boy up here
there's a
zombieing the
TR I need in
the thankar
XP right you guys are doing great thank
you I'm going to die I'm up in the attic
I don't want to get hit
no we
good don't die okay we don't die we good
we're good okay I'll just light the way
for you guys thank you no problems I
think there's one more zombie down here
maybe in the basement oh we're in the
basement right now I hear it I hear him
yeah oh there he is ow found
it go okay we're done we're
done you're really shank nice art this
is nice she stabs I'm the
sh nice uh should we go to the trador
and deliver those quests yeah yes yeah I
don't want to die with this let not risk
it any
further yeah let's not risk we got a
bunch of quests to turn
in
okay oh wait oh I got some food whoever
was hungry oh I'm also hungry I am
hungry as well uh also we don't should
we should we let tell them that we're
done with the quest if they wanted to do
this yeah we're done with the quest oh
you tell
okay
yeah did someone have pistol oh yes I
use pistol I found I don't know if this
is pistol I
found a magnum enforcer oh I am going to
use Magnums when I find one
that I can use that I'm going to here it
is I'll put it on the floor back thank
you okay so we're heading to the Traer
yes yep okay I'll just follow
Shi okay we I am blind to the map my
preacher head it's okay I'm hungry and
dying oh actually do you have your
food uh I only have the food that
damaged thr us so I don't think oh okay
I I sandwich is not good for you the
diarrhea sandwich diarrhea sandwich did
like a great job making it though you
your bike I found it on the
floor I maybe that's the issue probably
the 5c rule doesn't work in this
game oh wait wait wait wait stay still
stay still be found shotgun weekly uh
kie than I honk your horn instead hold
on to that for me I'd be
happy oh we can have like a little bike
gang yeah biker
gang yeah that will be fun I want that
bike too I hope they're going to give it
to me there was a bike at the base I
think it's one of yours stu oh it's it's
just
mine I see I see messed up I don't think
anybody else has a bike yet unless they
did look past I
think uh it K should be able to make one
because she has a lot of vehicles I
think she has like 10 or something but
she needs I think she needs the four the
workshop thing I have four vehicles on
me that I can give to her as well nice
nice maybe we can feed them to her and
then she can make his
bicycles yeah cars or
motorcycles oh this is this is the new
house we can store stuff in here I'm
going to store stuff in here real fast
okay okay oh yeah I should have put the
Farm plots here then oh what is what is
the new house let me check on the map oh
yeah I think make sure to leave a mark
here how do you name
crates uh hold e in front of it
okay I find it's actually
here old e what was wrong uh let's see
oops I have any seeds I got an
outfit o the farming outfit I didn't end
up seeing it shorty oh wait that's the I
need to get the outfit
actually oh pink uh shotgun
we Kelly where are you I should probably
keep one p the okay okay I'll just I'll
just keep it for now then
yeah okay where was the outfit again I
forgot where left it
sure
uh I got to the new house to deposit
stuff because I don't have
any in the inventory ammos and
weapons uh this one yo when does he open
open
up oh he's open
nice right put shotgun we oh I'll just
I'm stupid but okay never mind way say
17 so in 4 days we're going to have
another we yeah
yeah actually need to find my spot I'm
going to leave this here for now and
I'll only equip it when I'm harvesting I
think um sh for farming do you need like
rotten flash or something I think so
yeah yeah you can leave it in the food
and medicine box it's
okay yeah you're one I have a silly
question how do you name your box a hold
e and then the one of the off yeah yeah
yeah nice I got a B bicycle
yay biker
gang nice nice nice any special
jobs okay I'm coming to the Traer now me
too oh I should take some
food oh finally you
can much
better much
[Music]
better where did the farming outfit go I
just put it back in
here I did not take it hey oh never mind
I have it okay oh going to leave it
behind behind so it doesn't get
damage this place is cozy and then I'll
get a Repair Kit
Repair have a room just for
me
S armor
part wow we're hungry
people we're hungry for zombie murder
and knowledge honestly you think about
it like how badly we won
knowled to read I just want to read I
just want to know the world
Lear okay okay I'm heading to Trader now
me too I'm going to the
trader oh oh yeah I need the coins I
keep forgetting about they there you go
tokens wait is it is this a different
Trader Kelly isn't this this guy I have
to talk to oh you guys need turn oh
yeah he just we're going to go to the
new one after you
oh my
money crafting skill magazine my money
oh
no not your money okay okay I gave back
my trigger I did it I finally did a
quest good
job good job that's my first one okay I
I say I want to go sleep now
guys for play us maybe I should go back
actually first uh so I don't spawn
outside
next could be a good idea
byebye see see you
[Music]
later wish they sold water in here dang
it you can drink it from the river but
you know at the cost of
Health I'm good pass on that okay to the
the camping huh nah not really my
style I still don't know how you collect
water like you just lose the
jar you know I'm just going to take it
and then if anybody needs to buy
anything I'll buy it for
them uh I don't need anything at the
moment I I don't know what to
want okay we should I get for ahe
tactical what is a lock b I don't think
I need
it you can purchase purchase drinks from
vending machines
[Music]
oh
no inrease magazin capacity
goodbye goodbye
goodbye B I got a bike yay
bike and now you can also take the
special Mission everybody with the bike
can take the special
Mission oh yeah I guess crafting skill
guess one I'm so
happy i' shake your at least and then if
you get the special Mission we can go do
it
together even though we got it it's
technically separate but we do it
together uh do you guys need that refle
sorry refle world as a magazine rifle
world I think K needs those a rifle okay
what about armor
up yeah everybody needs those I think in
general oh they are more yeah I'm going
to use those oh Hy
bombs
ooh those could be very helpful during
the the pipe
W nice wait how do you get this special
oh special job okay
opening good Lu it you better not make
me
this nice
sir people do you want a home cooking oh
yes please okay I'll drop you here thank
you H sure I'm going to drop farming
here go and harvest tools than you here
go uh thank you I guess I should do
tools
[Music]
digest o i can get coffee coffee my shop
my rules I'm going to put those in the
chest I don't think I need did you take
a tier two clearing Quest B I did okay
maybe I can take oh who wanted to focus
on clubs again I think CeCe did right
I'll leave for her then
I'm taking I'm doing Club I want to try
this cycle oh okay I'll give it to you
here you go big Bonk thank you take your
club and go
clubs time to go
clubbing
yeah I love this kids and you're
clubbing I should take more Quest
actually I
forgot
oo oh my God that's so
cool who's doing Spears any of you guys
or sharp sticks I am Spear and Aro
usually okay here this is for for you R
sharp stick I'm jobless oh is that for
me or thank you I'm coming doing sharp
sticks I think
oh I've lost my big
cat I am outside trying the B oh
okay take your time oh I have a quest
here actually actually it's near yours D
so I'm going to go home and then uh go
meet one of you I got a Rog
Hood W how do you get out of the
bike oh just press e and then if you
want to put it back in your inventory
hold e and then hover over it and click
take thank you so much
oh station
yay okay I'm
here awesome oh right over here this is
your sharp stick magazine oh thank you
so
you're going to make the sharpest stick
oh yeah sh did you get a
bicycle no I sell anyone a man we'll get
you doing a lot it's okay it's okay I'll
be
farming I'm a stationary
woman
okay getting strong
together all right let me see if I can
Harvest stuff growing growing just get
the [\h__\h] out of
here okay would you guys like to go meet
the new Trader together okay oh yeah
yeah we can let's see what you know what
it is
yep what do you know well you took the
special job didn't you oh opening trade
routs right
is in here
okay okay then my character is so
cool look at how cool my character is
yeah I love it I love your hairstyle
that you look good so good is everyone
you fall in the hole Yeah Yeah you can
go okay I'm just putting some stuff away
before uh going back to Yonder oh sounds
good Fury
know how
to how' that happen where's
the what was that
Sher the new Traer uh if you it if you
leave your house or the it's just keep
going South Road on that road and you
should be able to meet up with us okay I
mean I'll just follow you anyway okay
I'll see you guys there okay a
[Laughter]
no it's okay I got out no I don't need
help sure M I'm following you okay
follow me we're
biking what a lovely bike what a lovely
Trail a biking trail yeah what a lovely
Dey morning biking
time
yeah I love the bike I'm so happy oh oh
this is oh no this this doesn't look
very good this looks like not Dad told
him to not go into I
like yeah it's a burn area
o those are well I don't know how it is
actually really scary everything's kind
of you know
charred some
fire fire fire fire AUM vibes
yeah awesome five maybe I like
it yeah for
sure I wonder if we can Rush all the
quests by this next Trader and then get
to another Trader I
wonder okay I hope they have better
stuff me
too I bet she will and I bet she's
nicer oh I don't know about that you
think she might be mean I think she's
mean maybe that's even better oh oh
that's what you're into oh you like a
mean lady I don't know I'm just saying
yeah it could be you like Mean Girls oh
she likes Mean Girls I see it depends oh
just like the movie huh no that's not
true I just like you know maybe when I
don't know you see like the special side
ofis residence get it cuz is crispy
their house
[Music]
now they're all going to go fast
Fe where's everybody else going here I'm
behind you this bike can really not
climb
mountains
yeah that's why you go around the
mountain around okay we can do
that that's
doable oh oh no no no no
scary sounds here it's like a little
windy road a windy Mountain Road watch
out for this Pokmon people okay yeah
follow the windy road I think it leads
kind of means biking I used to use my
bike all the time oh yeah you're a biker
I love I used to love biking now I don't
bike anymore I like biking but but my my
parents would wake me up in the morning
at like 700 a.m. be like oh yeah we're
going to go out to the park and go
biking and I'd be
like and then but it was nice biking is
fun but not at 7 in the
morning yeah that's totally something
that Mama Mory would do too we're going
for a walk on the trail it's like 500
a.m. oh my God my dad is the kind of guy
who goes on my dad doesn't use the bike
is like
the uh like the electric one oh the
scooters something yeah he's a scooter
guy and he goes around
okay man my parents just woke me up for
church no my par oh my gosh speaking a
church church down there you like
Church's Chicken are you okay I saw
that where's my
bik oh there's a big city here or
something a factory
J's Clinic oh it's a clinic there's a
lady there's a lady I hope she's N I
want to talk hope I haven't lost my back
my my my my bike no your bike is still
there it's by your uh it's by your
backpack oh I'm in the factory actually
place just make sure it's
here wow she lives in a
church wow memories when you talk to her
you just look straight at at her stuff
at her stuff does she have good stuff
like good wees um no well yes she has
some good stuff yeah see she's nice I
told you she'd be nice that's good uh
did I go through here she's got
blueberry pie I need to go
down no stim packs but but brother
dictus loves stim
packs I hope you get feeling
better thanks
lady oh she's got tier 2 fetch Quest bik
is how do you oh I can repair my
my start a quest oh that's where she is
that's a really nice place actually yeah
oh you've been here before Dan clean
she's nice it just looks nice yeah it is
like a cream we can finally make medic
bandes KCK us
out would be nice if she lets us stand
like the other traitor
[Music]
hly
woman yeah that's my lady oh she's got
Goods I want your goods yeah she's got a
lot okay um
goodies we can clear
[Music]
zombies oh I would kiss you but you know
she'll never forget oh she wants to kiss
me what
oh hey no fair
proven did she tell you
that yeah she said I think
she should I should I get the first
eight kit or the
magazines I think magazines is more
useful um yeah we'll just have to tank
dying and technically you don't really
lose that much when you die cuz you
still Level and stuff so it's like not
really of
consequence yeah I noticed
that well I'm probably okay here
oh
money make a ton of bandages
now how do you make
bandages without you have to unlock
medicine don't
you yeah but I have a decent amount of
medicine
nice try think of what to put my stuff
in four first aid bandages
penetrator a oh she's s
um you can you can loot the houses
around her compound here by the way yeah
let's do
it well wait for
me I can make wooden Club quality 6 now
yay wait baseball bat quality 1 I can
make baseball bats
woo cool
R do you use
bows I use no I use mainly Spear and bow
oh okay might well I have a bow a bow uh
magazine oh yeah I will take that here
you go I drop that thank you you're
welcome what wait let me check what do
you need let me oh I found an
engine wonder what that does maybe we
can use it to make motorcycle or
[Music]
somethings
okay is anybody here doing the
wiring magazines I also me not me you
can use it if you want looks like a lot
of our quests are near each other except
for Mor's at least of yours okay let's
go to the ones near each other first
then maybe yeah okay
I hear zombies around here yeah the
zombies are trying to get
in the door is literally
open do you guys have any leather by
chance no there's some at the house no
okay at the house
then need to wait for minutes because my
my she is the nicest lady I should
probably put stuff in
cooking can you believe that I thought
you going to be mean she I'm feeling
rowdy I I got a I drank
beer you're feeling it said I'm feeling
Rowdy where'd you get the bruis I don't
know how you sp oh my vision is so
blurry oh
no uhoh
Granda right now what a what an idol
should we head now while it's still
daytime by the way I'd say so yeah let's
get him done did anybody have a drink
the beer did not quench my thirst
I am
thirsty there is a there is a vending
machine inside and they sell water and
old dream Oh yay okay hit that vending
machine
ladies there's red tea I too I'm thirsty
who has
money I have money what do you want I
just want water or oh sugar butts they
don't really have a lot of that they
have like coffee and beer and the like
but uh anything that gives food I guess
is fine anything that gives food you say
yeah wait was I supposed to bring those
tokens that look like AR things yeah
yeah those are those are those are money
here all right I I could appreciate some
oh coffee but I'll accept it o tea I'll
take tea drink
it let's see um I got yucka juice
finally o
juice figh something you like yeah
something like
that o thank
you Yuka
Yuka yum yum M
moment something very
quickly yeah wait until it satisfies me
okay let's uh head out I guess you ready
to head
out I'm need to wait two minutes because
my leg is broke broken but okay into me
I'll get
fixed oh
okay she's
great yeah I I think how do you diee
your
stuff I have a crush
question I finally unlock
medicine bi you got to make us she's
smart because she grw stuff in nor
my bike is pink
now
oh vulture oh good job
yeah all right I'm ready where are we
going hold on Row's leg is broken let's
wait oh that's right okay sorry my quest
is they look like from a Legend of Zelda
actually oh these burn dudes
yeah Yik that's rough buddy that's rough
buddy okay let's see the next Quest we
want to do uh we can do the Mory tier
two fetch which is very close 288 M away
okay we can do that yeah let's do this
one hold on I'm CU cumbered I can I
think I can slowly
come yeah we're going to need to go up
The Path again I
think might over the mountain the that's
clear Mory
I don't know if we can Skyrim horse it
up this this actually can there's a path
uh uh beeps did uh there's a call going
on if you wanted to attend first a
call uh for the Encore thing with the
dog oh yes um yeah here how about we
stay in here really quick uh we can try
doing a two call if you want to do two
birds in one stone yeah let's let's
go yeah we we'll be we'll be
right get kicked out here huh we're
going to meet you'll at the quest spot
but uh we got to do something really
quickly so we're just going to leave the
voice chat but we're going to head to
the quest spot yeah we'll be right back
after these messages Okie doie Okie doie
I'll you guys at the spot
yeah that's all wait what uh
okay you and me Rob you and me let's go
let go are you are you are you going
by with the bike or I jumped up the
mountain maybe it's actually faster I'm
the jump King
though oh hello
I guess we're just waiting
for I I guess so
some
um I wonder if we should just like run
there while we're waiting yeah no I'm
going to head to the quest while we yeah
me too
okay wow it's so private in here it's
just it's just us
too now it's like but by the way are you
heading like the right direction uh I'm
going to the the Mor fetch Quest that's
but I'm going by the road so I can take
my bike since I have stuff in my bike oh
okay you are not a natural
climber us
hi sorry hello huh no you're fine we
just started I mean we're still waiting
for you we oh are you streaming yes yes
so so don't say anything like your
credit card number unless you want to
share well my credit card number is
55555 by
oh D we need we need one more number
dang also the the three numbers in the
back of your car too as well as your
expiration date that be very helpful oh
yeah this could to be 011 uh yeah
yeah H it's so hard without a bike in
this world we get you that bike soon I
know I I think I went the wrong way too
I got to go through the freaking
Mountain
Trail how are you Risa how is you doing
enjoying your Final Fantasy
games yeah just just chilling I was
actually watching a musical but you know
what
musical Elizabeth dos musical oh isn't
that one your favorite yeah the one that
only I like the only one only you
like yeah no one else likes it only me
oh well I I bet I like it if I watch it
watch I have to make you want
maybe we still need to do Phantom of the
Opera too oh yeah Phantom of the
Opera yeah you got to make it
work okay I I'll I'll stay quiet you
guys uh have
fun we're not doing anything right now
I'm just like yeah we're literally just
like freaking climbing a mountain at
least for my case oh my God a mountain
climbing I know it's so hard I hate it
well I'm glad you're having fun
wish you were here
baby oh yeah yeah every time I see a
bird I just think like I wish that was
her and then we kill it everything makes
me think of her and we eat the well I
well only in self-defense but I just eat
the eggs and I think of you I see well I
guess I'll have to cook you
eggs good gosh it's almost night time in
here and I'm still not there where are
you oh you're close you're almost here I
know I'm I'm like Skyrim mountain
climbing let me let me check
on
um okay they said
soon okay
so probably soon all right I am I am
near Mor's location okay I'm with I'm
with Mory right so you should be okay oh
shoot it's the
RPS and a half uh the area we're
in can I throw away money I don't really
need it
right you can do whatever you
want are you guys ready for for
Halloween yeah no hell yeah but what are
you guys going to
be uh dead
uh I meant like costume like what what's
your
costume
um I guess I'll figure it out I don't
have I actually have it prepared sort of
wait wait are you for real yeah yeah oh
okay in that case I can't
tell oh well you have to text it to me
well I I think we're going to be busy on
Halloween aren't we or maybe not I don't
remember that doesn't mean we can't
dress up yeah you can dress up still mhm
I guess I should dress up as a goth that
well that's not really dressing up you
just are you're that every
day
[Music]
yeah did you you did finish that right
yeah yeah I did nice
did you do that the
true ending of course not you think I'm
that gamer yes you are you are that g if
you if you went for the beef you would
get it first try sh oh no no the thing
is I'm too lazy beams you actually like
pain I just don't care for pain that's
that's the difference between
us also it's funny but your gamer stance
is like you lean in I just like I I do
CR like it stands oh I'm kind of well my
legs are up on my chair right now I
always have legs up I have like one mine
is legs up and then and then like
against my chest and then lean in legs
up leaning in yeah that's my that's my
game stance I have one leg kind of like
tucked in and then the other one's
probably just like dangling or it's uh
it's like KN up or something about youa
do you have a gamer what's your gamer
sit how you usually sit when you
game I don't know I'm like too zoned out
whenever
I'm you're the peaceful
gamer yeah I apparently I have like a
bit of a gamer pose I'm always like
looking down as if I'm like slouching
but as you know I can't slouch so you
got the good PA yeah I got that good
po yeah apparently I look like I'm
slouched over she's no SL
oh there's a casket
here I like how you went for a cactus
and ignored the
[Music]
zombie oh good
job you know that sound when their like
flesh gets sliced off their body it's so
satisfying
it's it's very ASMR for
me should we do like ASMR actually
you're doing ASMR and chesa I did I did
do ASMR my how did it go
[Music]
you congratulations
congratulations
[Music]
yay yeah Shi
Nissa what do you mean Shi Nissa what
about
bio we all we all
represented thank
you they just said your so fast you
didn't even realize yeah how do you feel
you feel
good yeah you feel good
[Music]
you good job good job
yeah to work really hard all
together
looking being really
some more cool things coming up in the
future yeah I'm strong great job
Doles thank you
than let's keep on doing thank you for
[Music]
calling oh I have a question yes yeah
what's your question what do you
oh to aim for next you know we had all
our goals and everything or maybe
there's something that
like way you think we're
weak I I think you should take a a nice
rest point yeah
oh well uh I really want uh separate you
know you know back in the day when anime
would make character songs all the
characters I really want one character
song for both of you each separately
because yeah yeah yeah yeah it's just
like very individually about both of you
cuz obviously as F Moko you're amazing
and even separately you're amazing too
and I I want to be able to see that
individuality too sh out it's just me
obviously cuz I love you both the they
sing oh so cool so oh that would be
amazing that
songs
[Music]
individually character song fua
character song I
[Music]
justed some separate streams too I like
seeing more of the
perspectives a Solo
solo still has it no get on it stop
being
lazy I'm just joking you don't have a
lazy bone in your body
it just it always ends up you know it's
fun together so then
right but I was glad that you were able
to do like a Ian
recollection like separate point of
view we still we're still right by each
other though so it doesn't really change
that
much if you want you can come over to my
house and I'll let you stream from my
room wow
no no
what
no I thought you just I thought you D
her just a little while ago saying
something different no I know I'm so
surprised
suddenly I don't know you said s d so I
thought from my I should not say
yes love you love you and now it's no no
I want to see you guys play challenging
games
challenging yes that's exactly what I'm
saying do you think we should play on my
yeah play onor yeah oh my god oh that'll
be hard at
least there's a lot of games that seem
interesting cool but yeah I want you
guys to go out of your comfort zone and
play a game that you
necessarily like feel like oh this might
be a little difficult or o this is not a
type of game I want you to try out new
games that's what I want game
specifically a new game yeah doesn't
doesn't have to be a Souls game but like
a game that you might think like oh this
isn't like our type of game but let's
try it out anyway that's my challenge to
you M Souls game
yeah monster hunter is Monster Hunter
not a type of game we would play it's
not that hard yeah monster hunter that I
mean the new monster hunter game is
coming out uh in a couple
month I think we should all play it
together please please please a a CL mon
wild pleas pleas pleas I beg of you I
won't ask ready to yell just let me have
this
please we should do monster hunter Club
yes Monster Hunter when wild comes out
we should do like Monster Hunter weekly
AOC Cloud but it's just Monster Hunter
yes double
challenge we'll all be Pros by the end
of
ITA has to play on on my own too my own
Monster Hunter I become my own oh
is that a possible thing is it four play
is that one demon dog too many if there
one demon dog too
many m is Odon and then FL is eony
Odon what
what oh I talking about their armor no
as in what monster Nissa Z monster I I
don't even remember the monsters in
there honestly he just my fa
[Music]
as long as they're cute yeah they're
cute deadly recently we've been more
interested in figures and on Twitter was
promoted to us a monster hunter figure O
monster and I was saying to
moan how could you have that next to
your cute dands what you mean the
monsters are cute
too moner it was like a tube with the
legs
haven't you ever seen a nante and been
like oh I want to rub it belly oh it's a
cute say what n you know you guys don't
I haven't played Monster Hunter
yet in there all I know is you killed
them I'll send you my favorite
monster yeah Mis is also my favorite mun
is adorable yeah I
love no but you can take the skin and
make armor out of
it why did you only send your favorite
monst through oh okay M Chan I'll send
it to
you there you
go
a mhm
yeah a little are you calling me
pretty it looks like B is what I see I
thought it like a sunet I don't know she
called me pretty
are I guess you put be and lemonade it
kind of looks like a and lemonade yeah I
guess
so yeah be sunset
lemony oh I should start selling that as
a drink right
tasty love
Cafe
oh we're ready yeah no this is squiding
pasta with blueberries on top blue is
cute not pretty what I'm bald excuse me
I absolutely disagree with that you know
I know said I'm both but I heard it I'm
bald no I'm B I'm B that youo but I
heard both you can be cute and pretty
thank you sexy thank you at the same
time thank you yes you can be it all at
once okay yeah MO is also cute and
pretty and sexy
yeah can be
as congratulations everything thank you
yeah con we're so proud of you yeah
congrat byebye see you soon
[Music]
bye I guess I guess we headed
all let's go Sil yeah I guess
[Music]
so oh they left us
y
hello yeah hello hello hello hi
the yeah it has been completed but uh oh
good you should let me craft things
because I have the highest skill
yeah you're the one that can do it but
every piece of armor needs two armor
crafting kits and then 10 claw frag
fragments I have a couple of these
things but barely enough right now I see
especially like armor crafting kits and
I can make armor crafting kits but then
I would need uh like more duct tape for
example I need a lot more duct tape oh I
see so if you guys have either duct tape
or I think I had some duct tape in my
uh I am also in need of duct tape though
to make a baseball bat or just the
armor oh I have in the Discord server so
we know what to give you and we'll just
put in your box if you can label it okay
you were doing vehicle too right I have
four vehicle magazines ooh nice we can
make I see there are some legendary
Parts in here you actually need those to
craft the strongest version of whatever
weapon you have so the strongest version
of the club six you need one legendary
part and then the basic Club just so you
guys know what that's for I'm going to
make a baseball bat so I don't
necessarily need a legendary Club but
I'm just letting you know that's what
the parts are for
okay yeah o shotgun weekly let's go
where are you in the house there ah yeah
take magazines if you need B you want to
go together to base again to drop our
crap yeah I'm going I want to go to I
want to go back to the quest Quest or
not the quest Quest the new house I want
to go to the new house base yeah base I
have oh am I muted no I hear you hi hi
here yeah I have uh something for you I
think oh you
do oh well I give it to you now that
you're here before I leave oh I am not I
am not at the house yet you can put it
in a chest though and then I'll grab it
if you if you got to go
says are you right there next to oh no
wait no no sorry that's morning never
mind yeah I'm pretty far but you can put
in a chest or something okay okay what
is
it h no it's nothing it's just like a
Knife Guy the magazine
and she's going to shake even harder
people where are you right now I have I
have someo where like the the desert I'm
coming to we're coming to the the the
new house though we're coming to the new
house I got stuff for you too Kiara hold
up you in the house oh yes oh good gosh
why is it so hard to control a
bike by the way how does the bike take
damage is it like if you fall or
something no I it it um it gradually
reduces it durability as you use it so
you're going to have to that's the main
thing I wanted to give you I think I
don't know yet that's all I had oopsies
thank you oh no it's for you awesome
helps you I know you you like I've never
taken care of a bike before
oh wa how do you do that I'll press X oh
here it
is what was that yeah I hear scream
there's some Screaming people screaming
ladies are coming watch
out small
raid maybe yeah it looks like a small
horde is coming
oh already I'm
blind there are a lot of them I use this
I will help you
I'm punching let's go let's do
it hi BS
hello look at us having a nice romantic
bike ride together yeah in the forest
that is oh you're riding together that's
cute yeah these scamers
ones freaking reloading
no oh yeah do it's a peaceful peaceful
existence in Canada and uh she just
killed
someone so
peaceful yeah the most peaceful o
loot yeah I wonder if these guys drop a
ton of loot I got one they're not really
dropping much at all except exp which is
good come on drop something you
fools Dear Hunter behind here yeah hit
him cie yeah I got him Bo with the bnk
are they outside I'll park my bike next
to yours here we
go oh
okay hello need a
hello that lady looks like she to thank
you all right this club is extremely
strong
now and okay I locked
mine I think I need to go now everyone
so
thank foring thanks for playing bye bye
byebye this time
I'm okay you made everything respawn so
was
awesome really it
was of course
loot
yeah bye bye everyone
see T KY you got a bicycle too yeah I
got a bike and we met the new Traer how
there's a new trador oh yeah there's a
new tra she's nicer too as she kisses
you that she could kiss you if you if
you um what is it if you get a bike and
tier 2 quest uh you can talk to the guy
and he'll give you a a special dialogue
to say like special Quest and then he'll
give you a quest to visit the new Trader
oh yeah and she's got more stuff I made
a bunch of bandages you're blocking the
uh the entrance maybe want to do this
quest for yes okay I'm at the start
Point okay should we go I fail the quest
oh it took too long I guess I'm just
looking do we not have any lever at
home a lever maybe I have to make it
craft one
you're so smart but no a I have stuff
for you okay oh here's vehicle oh
leather we do have leather um here's
rifle sure we do thank
you I have 100 leather there you go nice
100 yes please I'll give it to you in
just a moment I'm I have to run to the
old house really quick to get duct tape
I'll bring my duct tape too do you have
a storage in here Kiara yes mine's over
here uh in the living room up ceiling
okay I'll just try find it as long as
it's named over here here here it's not
named all right I'll name it for you
it's okay I got it oh thank you no
problem wow the archiv are doing
archiving things he's
archiving o by the way we did um plant
the super corn o it's planted it should
be growing or done growing
hopefully I think I might have messed it
up cuz I punched it and I only got a
couple you get it or not but you should
punch it
right I can
farmer yeah I mean you don't punch
aren't guaranteed it's like 50%
depending on your level
probably so punch away as long as it
says it's not
growing for now should we all get into
the same party do you think okay yeah
there's about less than six of us I
think maybe about you're leader right
now so I think you can do that oh
okay a
lantern do we have a crafting table down
yet or no yes yes it's in the kitchen in
the kitchen
okay but yeah if you want to make armor
then you should probably leave it to me
I think I can make weapons with it too
is it scary outside probably it's a
little gloomy it's night time it seems
scary ah she's
running oh wait I was going to put more
iron in oh yes our spiky house spiky
house it's very
powerful very hard to get into for
zombies and ra and ra
[Music]
no sh is already wearing the farmer
outfit as far as are you yeah I'm
wearing it good it's scary in
here here I'm coming I have candles here
I'll put in the mood lighting I can H I
can make ammo wait are you girls doing
the fetch right now I I can make ammo
doing Supply Quest I'm coming over okay
oh cleared the area Quest but I can't I
can't make ret the supplies Quest
oh yeah I'll just I can make I can make
all types of ammo
now really yeah how did you do that uh I
I have the skill for it I
guess
oh ammo for
[Music]
everybody oh look at them go
please owie guess you can only put on
surfaces well you didn't start the quest
yet did you no just killing them in here
okay
okay almost
there so
easy I have such a strong Fister on my
side that's right
oops pumpkins there's some good stuff in
these
cabinets I can make pumpkin bread
pumpkin bread looks so good in the game
that I went out and bought ingredients
to make pumpkin bread in real
life pumin oh this is the guy with it
made you so hungry it did I had to have
it in real life can we come over and
have some that sounds so good yeah
yay send a photo of your pumpkin bread
yeah photo head to you
guys
Quest he's fast oh you're doing a quest
here I can join you yeah yeah I see um
most of them there too by the way uh myy
don't you have to add everyone into the
same party I'm trying to I sent the
request okay we can just B and join
theirs whichever works oh yeah we in the
quest right now so youd have to wait
yeah okay okay I'll just join that then
yeah let's and Quest together since I
think there's five of us 1 2 3 oh crap I
I failed the quest oh it's cuz we
dropped the party I guess yeah uhoh oh
that's fine that's fine that happen I
find our supplies I found also one supp
not mine so there's a biker gang in here
uhoh I forgot my bike I'm already
running they're all
upstairs oh I'm hungry so anyway I
started blasting
o get him can you guys add me to the
party me too please uh I think mid
Quest I what you mean are we waitting
until after the quest you guys in the
same location as I am okay you're sker
Place yeah yeah yeah oh watch out you a
sexy zombie oh she's wearing a
dress a red
one hey you to PR go around the corner
there's a courier statue here one of
yours it might be
mine I just got
mine think mine upstairs I forgot we
were on a quest
again and punching I think there must be
an attic cuz I think mine's
down all right I'll wait for you beibs
okay I'm
coming yeah we still got to get the the
invite
anyway is in here look at you and your
bike I had a walk here the old I thought
you had a bike was that a I I it oh it's
just there by accident what oh okay
already started oh wait something went
flat in there oh yeah oh
uhor shipping
crate water nice a kitty Ki there's a
cat picture in here a different the same
as before different
one A orange cat's
[Music]
Behavior oh New Stone spear
oh okay I found
[Music]
mine oh my God what a cute cat I know is
there an attic I'm so upset we can't
take the cat pictures and decorate our
house with them I was going to steal
some love craft
thing I'm not sure if yours is up here
too but in the Attic that where we were
with
the there's a um
not I meant no no downstairs oh a
basement yes sure oh but I'll take
upstairs again maybe yeah it's like on a
really high shelf you might have missed
it oh weren't we merging since there's
like no no I think they have started so
we just waiting for them to finish their
Quest okay okay it there's like a
respawn time when we were trying to do
your quest it made us wait like 2 hours
two hours in game yeah that's rough
should we do something else then besides
this one
um I don't have I don't have oh I see
yours okay yeah I see yours I don't
think I have to break it
what where are you I we do this one I
have to break the kitchen to get my
statul oh you found it yeah found it
yeah we can we can do this one for you
after they finish and then we can merge
yeah okay how about we do yours yours is
like right there and near
myy oh true we are pretty
close do you still oh hello do you still
have the Hat fauna for drinking yes
please let me drink some here go we can
also join you guys on your quest now we
just finished ours oh okay we can should
I invite you guys have you turned in the
quest to the trader yet no okay you'll
need to do that or else make a quest you
me oh how about how about they how about
they invite us so that way they still
have the
quest oh I want I still think that might
affect it really I'm worried yeah okay
we can
wait okay I'm at the Harrison residence
if you want to do your thing
bik it's my bike it's my bike it's my
pink bike what a cute bike thank
you ah empty hand
[Laughter]
forgot don't look okay now you can look
I'm watching I'm
watching I'm watching I'm
watching pretty good pretty good the
drive yes watch watch me drift I'm
drifting I'm drifting look I'm drifting
wow
drift I'm drifting around the course I'm
drifting I'm doing oh my God she's crazy
I'm so crazy look at that wow she's
driving on the
inside she's um uh Ray
Tracy Ray
Tracy Ray Tracy take so long she's not
disgracing us I'm intimidating should I
just wait
I think you just wait Swag yeah right
cuz it goes up
okay no no no wrong
way the green
one you can't wait know you do have I do
have my hair out I should be yeah I know
I was just I don't know I thought you
were behind G or
so all right let's give back the quest
should we yeah and then we can combine
okay
back well we'll wait to start any quests
until we combine so that way we can all
do our Quest
together yeah yipp I'll head to now I'm
going to use my new baseball bat H by
the way Kelly did you like wait was it
level or duct tape you wanted to give to
me I'm going to go ahead and end it
here next time
byebye see you next time what byebye
where did you say you brought it to
Kelly it's in the chest in the new house
the ones that aren't labeled I put
leather and duct tape it's only six duct
tape though that's fine a bunch Lea
thank you you're
welcome do we have any food I'm starving
yes where are you um in the forest I I'm
coming to
you I'm inviting you guys want Lev
[Music]
a
what yes who uses who uses 44 guns me or
I will be using them I have this Stone
EG I have a funny magazine that if You
magazine like go to the shop with your
gun you will get cheaper prices oh
that's so funny yeah it's funny like
you're threatening
them I have magazines for Kiara and
fauna yum yo magazine STS are
[Music]
rising Fist and rifle I love
reading's good for you reading and
fisting
yeah mostly fisting but also reading
about
FIS it's a deep deep science there's so
much to know I don't think it sounds
wrong you should embrace
it okay I too love reading about fisting
not only the act of fisting but reading
about it watching it I love watching you
fist oh my Lord and the chests inside
the unlabeled ones should have leather
and duct tape duct
tape oh nice lots of Lea here's your
fisting magazine thank you waiter waiter
more fishing please
I'm getting so
smart okay I'm going to go make my nerd
hat my baseball bat looks so strong oh
my gosh I can't wait to kill things with
this melee for the
win and
then I have two skill points huh I don't
remember what the other stuff was that I
wanted
got to look it up again
later what was
it ah the preach outfit was a like the
best
uh preacher yeah the preacher the
preacher you have the Hat of that I
think yeah the preacher outfit is the
best um what's not heavy not medium
what's that light armor light armor yeah
the best light armor
set out there
[Music]
so Raider set I want maybe like I don't
want to just make stuff on my own people
and force it onto them they should tell
me what they want screaming out there we
got to
deal gladly down where is she now
now ra
that'll be no more screaming out of
you oh there's a bird chasing you watch
out a
bird there's a bird oh here vulture is
it the bird that's screaming I think
it's the bird that's
screaming so
loud the dang Birds put it away from me
for now I keep telling them to do oh
there he is oh okay W and G shot
shooting Bird's
dead it won't bother us
anymore how do I take
back there's my bike
[Music]
okay what you making me yeah I made oh I
made a nerd hat which I will wear I I
feel like I might want to make nerd hats
for everybody because if you wear the
nerd hats during the raid you will get
so much
EX
idea we could all use that tomorrow
yeah Oh there's uh shotgun shells and
stuff in the output oh yeah I was making
those ah I accidentally took the 7.6 to2
did you make those for me
yes nice you so nice you're
welcome you're welcome how far am I from
making level free stuff
chat and how funny do I look now so
funny you look like a nerd
look at
me you can see my orange hair at
least
nerd give you
wedgie I give you a swirly Kiara yeah oh
you why can't chat not
CH chat if you want to see how it looks
like because chat is covering myself
just look at me I don't I look like a
nerd my life to do looks like a MD right
come on just like
you wait I'll show you
chat oops what a inconvenient place to
be for
you here can I turn this
no wonder what I look like from the side
do I have like a ponytail or so Kelly
tell me let me see hold it uh Ponyta uh
let's see yeah you got a ponytail I got
a ponytail long ponytail kind of bushy
looking frazzled like you don't take
care of your
hair you know some days studying I can't
find my yeah she's reading up on those
books and like the side of your hair is
like growing out of like the side of
your glasses and like above it it's like
a big bald spot it's kind of weird bald
spot no yeah there is of spot I don't
believe it you're messing with me bald
no
bald bald there's nothing wrong with
being
bald there's nothing there's nothing
wrong with being bald I just don't want
to be oh Trader is opening up so let's
go give the quest back shall we go
yeah Bal
to one day we'll all be Bal okay never
my head will be full of hair
forever do you need wood I have 6,000
6,000 that's the max stat
stack 6,000 for my another stack yeah
I'm making another stack I think I can
solidate my wood now you need wood just
tell
Gigi I have so much wood don't even
worry man that's a lot of wood I heard
if you're wood if you have wood for more
than 6 hours you should see a doctor
good thing you're training doctor doctor
can you see my wood please no guys are
freaking
menaces my God sweet Jesus Joseph and
Mary nurse nurse I have so much wood can
you come count my
wood the nurse I'm quitting I'm getting
my medicalis revoked I'm turning it back
in
when you get fired from out practice so
you don't have to look at my
wood um change of topic does the other
Trader have like better quests yes the
the the other Trader has tier two quests
as well oh so the quest you guys got
going on right now that you want us to
join is that a tier two yes no finally
oh I have I have I have two tier two uh
quests going on at the moment then bioo
would you like a tempered blade a
tampered blade yes okay might be
good all the Traders will give you the
max tier Quest you're eligible for oh
okay I'll get tier two here too once I'm
there okay all traitor showed tier two
okay okay
okay
um what's happening Quest started oh
here deal want armor crafting right here
oh you guys aren't on my party yet oh
yeah one sec one sec
[Music]
um see let me
see F yes do you have um 200 coins yes I
actually how do you know exactly how
many coins I
have wait did you drop those magazines
for me too oh that was from some else oh
oh I'm getting all these donations from
these
magazines all right I'm just buying the
last magazine he
has oh well thank you sir I'm 42 level
42 armor now nice when can I make the
next tier I
wonder all right I'll uh leave
the group and then I'll uh be open to
being invited invited okay how to leave
okay me me too all right I am single and
ready to mingle
okaying let's mingle I'll mingle with
you I'm ready to invited as well yeah I
invited you wait Quest failed is it the
shared Quest you just accepted yeah
it'll come back when you when the person
rejoins the party don't worry all right
right
okay doing me a
concern I have joined tier two Quest
let's go wo invite please I'm
starving thank you you might need to go
accept it in your there we go there you
go oh I have two workstation magazines
I'll bring them to you kiaha
nice oh we're meeting up anyway aren't
yeah towards the quest I'll just go
towards the quest which Quest are we
going
towards I don't know there's one being
shown to follow me okay I think it's the
same I am
[Music]
following yeah we just got to climb a
mountain we can do it
way we just got to Skyrim horse it you
know easy easy yeah I'm pretty goat like
oh we go clear my goat Gigi that's for
sure oh really my goat
that doesn't mean you have to you really
don't have to make those noises if you
don't you're pretty good at
that bad not
bad if it makes you happy keep it makes
me happy nuzzles into your hand and
licks your finger looking for some I
don't really know if that's
necessary I'm just emulating goat
behavior is that not what goats do wild
yeah to a petting
zoo do something scary
um flashes you my demon goat
eyes I have I have passed out onto my
back as goats do out of fear oh I begin
eating your liver oh wow um they're
talking asteris asteris asteris they're
rping with words oh it's the B Barn
Fields oh
no the we gotb this got you no it's on
the other side of the boar this is a
different thank god let's run it
ladies all
right big
[Music]
party
H we can take them oh there snakes are
you kidding me snakes too snakes there's
so
many danger noodle
[Music]
don't worry
guys up up up up up up these guys will
be easy small potatoes what's wrong with
oh never mind I got like the angle on
it this is all happening so fast oh
stealing zombies worry not guys I am
skinning this warar while you are
fighting yeah get his
we have fallen from the sky
wed he said they jump so
high I want to fight too but there's no
zombies in my
way
yeah so fast they're luring they're
lurking about they're falling from the
sky oh oh oh there's even another ladder
to
climb oh can we get much higher can we
get much
higher oh I didn't die I didn't break my
leg I was so
scared
uhoh for 2 hours
Golem no o Urban combat give me the
shotgun
shells cooling mesh mod there's some
goodies over over here guys if you guys
want this stuff some ammo for both Kiara
and bio let's go yeah I I failed going
to where you were so I'm giving up on
that cigars boost what cigars boost your
strength increase your but ability and
make you look like a sexual
tyrannosaurus what that's what it says
for what okay I I want to be a sexual
tyrannosaurus I learned it Tyrannosaurus
what even is that I don't
know
tyun that is definitely what I
want you sure yeah R this I respect
it
huh I want to be that that
person I'm
okay I'm fine
I also found a ton of gas cans full of
gas for when we get
cars so I'll hold on to him for
now at least I said it for you
guys I muted myself uh
oh because not everybody has to hear
such things such things things now I'm
curious words plays of words I see
I think that's just what the game was
getting at
[Music]
so well uh are we done with this Quest
we're done how is this tier two it was
too easy I agree it was very easy I want
to find the big boar
again you want to F him again maybe that
again is he over here we the quest turn
in the quest first quests are are better
you want to do you want to do my quest
that's like right near B
sure mhm yes I see it yeah I see it oh
maybe I don't know wa where I'll just go
where I'll just follow
you what's this one also a clear Quest I
believe
so clears are easiest cuz you don't have
to look around forever for things just
kill all the zombies how did I have turn
in our current Quest first right no
it'll St MTI you can turn in multiple at
the same time die oh this is so on my
way well I think I think if you've
cleared the quest and you die you can
still turn it in oh really yeah as long
as you cleared it I think be I don't
know I might be lying I hope so I think
you can I hope it's as long as you clear
it yeah as long as you
clear yes no I wasn't lying I was not
lying are we all here oh giggy are you
joining us yeah okay I'm headed over
I'll wait
this is a nice residence I hope the
B are those bores your source of meat
this whole time so you were getting the
bacon
from BS I have 16 meat right now I need
another board oh wait that's pretty good
though that's a good handful of meat
okay we let me see let me make sure I
think we're complete okay we are
complete Let's us
go let's run
it
oh you just blasted them
oh I have a magazine for you I'm going
to stand right here while I'm dropping
it for you thank you
a beautiful flow you look good I'm sorry
ow that was not my intention looking
ladies me go up I wonder hey hey hey hey
oh wa thought we were already in
there a sham
sandwich don't eat it it's a sham I love
Sam my tummy is
fine oh there's an upstairs oh
hello well let's
go oh she was working out wow respect
when she turned into a zombie yeah uhoh
all that tells us no working out working
out not good for you
you found a nerd me sorry I ended up
clipping you it's okay too close to
please be nice to my nerd friend ow the
club the club it
hurts this baseball bat is so
overpowered kind of laggy I can make
iron tools now we did
it Hunter's Journal Barrel extender I
want these gloves I'm taking them for
me what seal shipping crate no uh here's
some
shotgun stuff over found shotgun shells
yeah there's GG do you also use shotgun
yeah but I am using my bow mostly right
now so you have a good shotgun you can
take
it
okay thank you there's um what did I
find here oh I have some bullets
thank you some what bullets does anyone
use knife magazines I do I use knife
you're thank
you and here's the ledge Hammer if
someone wants to use the hammer cooking
magazine oh I do I do the hammer I found
I do the hammering in this
household what you revolvers right bble
yes I will be using revolvers later
F okay I'll leave these for you thank
you
theyre chaotic I'll put it in our home
later okay good job team yeah that's it
a it's so fast when we're a big group it
is it's good we all get the reward to
yeah not fighting for my
life I I like steamrolling enemies a
pool is it this a nice house is good to
drink sip sip let's see it's really
nice oh no it it is not good to sip is
not
clean see you're drinking chlorine water
you need my hat what it's too late for
me I lost I'm going to get I'm going to
get beep and diarhea do you need do you
need tea I have tea oh there's more
zombies here I'm hungry if
anybody oh wait I have a oh
no thank you k I love how you just come
in from ins
side this guy looks like he's an
Outlast yeah he does look at T go like
he's going to
explode okay that was fun I think yeah
let's return Quest TR I'm running go
turn in some
quests good job team good job
good job team no
casualties I feel like we could take the
boar we could probably I mean we we
finished the quest now so you want to
take the boore let's take the
boore all right we've definitely leveled
up a lot since then thanks to the ra and
we have stronger weapons partially and
more people yeah
people if we go in all at once
yeah I guess we could be strategical
about
it or we could all just hit each other
until something happens we can all hit
each other from each other wait um
somehow we're close to our home I'm just
going to drop off some things really
quickly cuz I'm cucumber me too
cucumber I have so much stuff in my
inventory oh you're here already same
fault yes H cooking magazine is in
magazine chest thank
you should I just learn all these is
anybody hey chefs you guys making
anything delicious for us yes you know
how to make the hobo St or what hobo St
you really want that hobo
huh how to make hobo do one day we'll
we'll get we'll get experienced to make
hob pumpkin pie see that's what I'm
talking about fauna makes the best pump
by In This Land the most
delicious oh I'm going to get you home
cooking
weekly thank
[Music]
you oh I can I can get a bicycle now oh
yes bike join the bike game yay so now
we can go meet the
girl you think you're pretty I want
B me too oh I got to go to the quest to
give it back he do you have to give back
the other quests at the like right uh
Quest person or can we give back both at
the same person
bcle I'm going to go back to give
Quest I will
get if you guys are going to the board
let me know okay I'm now first okay step
by step there why is there a hole
outside who who dug this yeah that was
kind of not very nice them to do that my
bike keeps getting locked in there oh
yeah I swear this is not a natural hole
I think someone did this oh
sorry yeah know someone did that on
purpose to be
mean I have a feeling you know who did
that he not giving me a
bike to give you a bike giving me aik
never
mind
get oo I leveled up
[Music]
too my
bike watch out for the hole
outside
fists wah I have armor magazines for you
behind you k Sorry Sorry a sorry I was
muted I was like talking to my
chat what's what's going on I feel like
my server is lagging or is it oh maybe I
have running for you oh thank you be is
just endlessly running oh I'm in the I'm
in the
Traer yeah but you're like
running I don't know
why did you buy those for me
FAA um
I got them as a
reward okay okay okay I don't have wait
actually I do have money now he gave a
lot for that
one uh does anybody use like uh bows
even nowadays in I
think I think and Cilia also do I
believe and Dory I'm also going to drop
some magazines by your Fe kaha oh but is
this magazine is this a magazine that
you only learn once and then that's it
because this doesn't seem like
a yeah yeah okay then I wonder if she
had this before so if it's a one time
thing I know I'll take it for now oh
wait oh another
one wa burning shaft Ed the bike uh you
have to you can't place it in here you
have to leave the the trailer area and
then you can just place it down and then
press e to ride it and then hold e to
pick it back up again oh oh I'm in the
hole immedately went into the hole watch
out for the
hole
hold oh dear I think someone is doing
this to us on purpose I want them
arrested whoever dug that hole freedom
of a bike the bike the the world is my
PR x x to ding ding X to ding ding ding
wait bicycle I didn't see the bicycle I
got a bicycle
too special jobs he gives special jobs
now yeah that's a Trader that's a Trader
class that's the new
Trader I urge you all to accept it let
me so that we can go meet her if you'd
like
yes okay I can show you where she is yes
please I wonder accepts the special job
we can go she would have a different
stock for magazines I
suppose yeah she has a different stock
in the such Scholars here how to put big
readers ouch going my bicycle is red no
no it's green ah oh oh never mind but
once we find this new Trader maybe we
want to get a new house closer to the
new tree yeah
maybe you can see me no you can see my
hat oh it's so
cute all right uh are we all going to
the trader gen yeah yeah uh thought
that'd be cool which
direction that Way Southeast right yep
only about a kilometer
away with my propeller hat and the
bicycle I feel like I can take off
anytime nerd I'm a helicopter
this is the only helicopter we're going
to be able to
play truly no we'll be we'll be able to
get a helicopter I'm sure by the end of
this we'll be able to take off in the
sky yeah yeah and then shoot them from
the
helicopter where's a supply drop oh I
hear it I hear it I hear it a 100 me
away I'm going for it
okay let us know what's in it wait it's
in the scary Forest I'm still going for
it oh the trader the trader is in the
scary Forest anyway oh
yeah y the supply crates are kind of
underwhelming though I'm not going to
lie there's not a lot of great stuff in
there maybe they get better also
depending on how far we are with the
raids I hope so after each stage maybe
better drop I hope fingers crossed
who are these Supply crates from
anyway yeah um Trader Jen doing it for
us cuz she wants to kiss us so bad oh
she did want to kiss me
earlier I'm on my way to watch you oh
there's a big hole worry did you get it
I'll you back up there is a big
hole Yeah I don't know where it's going
to drop you think it'll drop in the hole
it it did disappear from the map did you
collect it no no it's coming down it is
May it is going in the
hole it's coming in the
hole what's in there over here first
shotgun shells that's all I wanted
there's a baked potato there's magazines
too if you want to take the magazines
I'll take the
coffee what kind of magazine let's let's
open these and see what what magazines
it has um it has handgun and armor
crafting assault rifle and workstation
ooh workstation for cute oh yes I need
both armor I'll bring those to you thank
you is the trader lady like on a weird
path up a mountain yes oh yeah you got
to take a swirly a a swirly path yeah
I'm on it right now it's not hard though
it's fun yeah I'm on my way over to dudy
witch dudy familiar dudy
witch um I'm going to her house by
accident this a dead
end what does Judy want from you I don't
know it's kind of ominous
oh why is her last name witch do you
think TR that that's why it's
ominous it does the swirly Road go down
again weirdly like yeah it doesn't go
straight great it's a bit up in the
mountains this is
confusing yeah that's why we need a
helicopter am I going back helicopter
helicopter I miss where's a
snake oh you guys should have seen we
went to go find bio's treasure and then
it was we went into a snow place and
everything was super
overleveled and we died a million times
I mean they probably saw the mes of B
died C died people died over again it
was intense it was crazy oh oh I'm
tracking the wrong
Quest here how do you can you change
which Quest wrong Quest girl you're
tracking um you can you can uh set a
waypoint with right
click oh fast
what is this
path yeah it circles through the
mountains a bit but then afterward I
just went down very steep I just kind of
mountain goated it all the way down they
could totally place a uh roller coaster
here this is the perfect place it is
very
swirly oh I think I did did I make it
goating our way up here yeah we could do
that or we could take the biking path
there is
one I got lot my legs are not strong
enough to bike up here my cow p p all
work those
cows working harder make them work
hard they need to put down some signs I
keep on taking the wrong
turns but now I think I got it
yeah it's just a little confusing yeah I
went the total wrong way but I'm on my
way now you got this you should have
gone together I know yeah I could have
showed you guys the way sorry about that
we got distracted by the air drop
a six shotgun shells
woo I'm almost there on my bike wait how
do you get off a bike
e e and if I leave my bike somewhere the
does it ever despawn so hold e and drag
to the hand symbol to pick it up into
your
inventory
[Music]
okay H okay
noise
wow the lovely in here you made it here
hi hi you made it just in time this is
her it's a church oh so you took the
bike path and you're already there
you're so
fast I'm I'm on the
mountain got lost two times just jump
down this mountain go down the mountain
degree
incline W closeup of her upper body okay
that's what I said you just you just
like have a front view over her
[Music]
chest your health is my priority
I am so glad to see your face I get
lonely sitting by myself all day now I'm
motivated to get there fast I got to see
this she's flirting with me she was like
glad to see your face
oh what FL with
[Music]
me I want we have like 15 more minutes
before today shift
ends I'm so sad it's fun isn't it it's
so
fun sa supplies maybe it would be good
to accept some quests she has so that I
don't have to come here all the time I
guess no never mind we get two tier two
quests at the other guy too so yeah she
only gives you one Quest at a
time okay I think I'll bicycle my way
home so that I can maybe in the last
minutes figure out where to put my skill
points and if I can make one more armor
piece
sure sounds good I'm going to head off
for tonight night thanks for playing
guys thank you see you tomorrow thank
you at the same time tomorrow I guess
yeah same time I think okay okay and
then we have the raid too so we'll have
to get ready for that yes the raid the
raid's going to happen like pretty early
right cuz it's already day
whatever what day is 18 yeah it's on the
21st just get ready for that 3 hours I
think yeah we can play a little after
though so it's fine oo
yes I want to let's do it for sure okay
see you later have fun thank you so much
byebye byee bye take care of yourself oh
she's already
gone I may have taken the wrong way
again I'm in the
mountains oh no are you biking through
the mountains I'm biking through the
mountains are you biking directly up the
mountain wait kiaha is here no not
directly up if you you see me
uh if
you go that way here around here right
side then you should you should get
there wait where did you go I think I'm
going up the
mountain
leg
[Music]
GG no I don't know how to get out of
here I can get down here I can climb
this a good deal trust me is it
necessary to go through the
mountain no seems very difficult she has
a really nice place yeah
way she does how do you repair your bike
uh use aair damaged wait did you did you
destroy it no I just fell down the
mountain oh yeah you just need a repair
a repair clip
okay she
Ela boobs when was night 14 uh we missed
it chat we missed
apocal it happened while we were all
gone but that's
okay people probably keep on coming into
our streams like and they missed the
beginning where we explained what
happened and they'll be like what did I
miss like did I sleep through it what
happened I must have did you guys take a
Quest from her I took no I didn't I
should have you can um I'll just have it
I'll take one
oh do you want me to help you with your
leg oh my leg is okay right now my bike
is not very
okay be fine
though don't worry I'll go up the
mountain again and then well I don't
think you need to go up the mountain to
bike home I think you to just I did say
it what is this view of her I don't even
see her face you don't see her face you
just you just stare right into the good
it's a very welcome
bug I don't think I don't think it's a
bug I think it's
[Laughter]
intentional it intended learning
Elixir
okay chat do you know what video I was
watching actually let me I have it in my
history
[Music]
the quest I got so close I don't know if
I want to do it
though oh I can I can do it if you want
minutes I can do it too where are
you Northeast it's the tier 2 clear GG
right yeah yeah you're going to do a
quest yeah you want to call let me go
where it's the one tier two G okay I'm
GNA try to get there ASAP is it up the
mountain or no no it's not up the
mountain
okay don't break your legs that way I we
don't have to like end exactly at the
4our Mark right cuz I just want to spend
some time looking at my skill points no
just don't AFK for seven hours that's
yeah yeah I will
not I'm just picking up stuff on the way
there's a lot of zombies on the way okay
I need this one a NAD chest
yeah oh M oats brother may I have some
oats zoom zoom
zoom this place is scary I know who
lives here dead
people so scary that dead people live
here
oh we have two quests do we we have a
lot there's like three around at the
same area next to each other who's it's
two of mine okay we can do all three of
these actually oh okay we're fast yeah
I'm almost there
[Music]
okay
fours I am really
thirsty oh I have some
water here take my coffee
thank you doesn't show and all that on
your
bike
huh ding right
now 250 M almost
there please
wait no problem Wawa is on the
way soon I'm there oh the signs are
telling me to go
slow don't listen to that it's is
apocalypse who's going to enforce
them this looks like Fallout New Vegas
it does look play New
Vegas I can't believe we people and me
we're all playing New Vegas
yeah fny danger noodles okay I am so
here oh I have I have stuff for
you me too I have lots of stuff what all
for me me yeah it's Christmas die orange
die watch out there a zombie W diey your
bike or whatever else you want I will
buy my
cloes yo so many magazines you guys are
amazing it is good that the whole server
knows what magazines I need that you
want this knife thing oh I would like a
knife thing thank you scary scary
welcome s
o for
G
yes oh I have armor magazines
too does anyone like ham or explosives
yes Sledgehammer thingies I do I do okay
there you go yes yes yes
yes
lovely I love how you girls keep on
getting magazines that I need
okay what's up hello
bues eating a can of pears just starts
blasting
everywhere all right let's help out a
little
bit I will help by opening things oh we
just start
blasting I will regret this but I will
go upstairs well I'm behind you oh
there's another upstairs
too
here
ow she's got yellow eyes mhm orange
eyes it's getting spicier here spicy
this area things are getting a little
bit more difficult dangerous
danger that's good I was kind of getting
sick of all the same places it was too
easy sorry guys am I giving you guys
motion sickness it's
upstairs there's a
box oh a forge ah
head let's go
more more more magazines here you
go yummy yummy books I am B I like to
eat
boooks oh there's some here
hello ah he so bad he's on fire
whoa Sauron is this
you or is this one of
yay we still haven't finished what's
that more somewhere maybe oh there's
more on the roof yeah all the way up
here oh he just
fell
us don't fall I get up
here not not die from the fall he did
not he was
chilling
Dam okay he's dead a good job level
1 Commando outfit excuse me what
outfit outfit oh that's I think a pretty
good one
Yeah medium armor oh no but you my
little pretty lady will get a heavy heav
armor set oh I use uh medium I don't
know if that's good or not but but
there's many different medium
ones do you have any cool armor right
now I just have
the scavenger outfit right now you can
try this
one
better my armor is critically broken
right now uhoh
uhoh it's getting a little bit y
well wait do you have a good good
outfit not yet day I'll hit these arrows
okay I'll just wear it for now and then
once I got the one I really want I'll
put this back into the armor chest and
somebody else can have
it okay thank you thank you I have ammo
for you does anybody use assault
rifle uh no I use machine gun okay
for you oh here where are you where are
you funa f where are
you behind you I'm jumping up and
down we got to do like hot hot cold
cold oh thank you oh what is that arm
more parts ah armor parts that's SM
that's what I need to all right second
Quest okay let's go let's this one's
harder right this is fetch so we got to
find an item okay be so much easier but
everybody's got their own item again bre
SP oh go oh it's
St be does oh they're
twin I feel like we're bullying them
uhoh there's a cop in here
[Music]
wow juicy how does he have so much
range
yeah boom head theama goes
crazy is this a developer
himself who is this guy
[Laughter]
painting oh blue baby I'm not sure if
this is one of the developers though
[Music]
hello oh they I think they're in the
CLA okay okay
okay oh
wa reloading I think I accidentally
stabbed
you I you did accidentally stab her you
you killed me okay I'm going to die as a
consequence anyway no no no no no no no
goodbye oh wait I failed the quest then
no oh I think I did too it's okay no but
the other one's still but you guys you
guys are still okay so keep going we
still help okay I'm feeling hot are you
okay up close apparently you feel hot
it says You must find a shelter where am
I going this
swim Arizona
baby is this does this all look like
this because of forest fires I think so
unless the zombie apocalypse did
something what did
I everyone's
D what did I what I oh oh oh it's the
spikes it's the spikes
I didn't make
noise I didn't hear it good
spikes but that was M have Survivor
guilt now don't feel guilty get that
reward get that bread also there's two
up
[Music]
here oh
c
I'm
stairs uh maybe that would have been my
cuer
Satchel whoa G I thought you were a
zombie but like a really pretty one
watch out for the spikes I'll protect
you I'm a Zombie coming back to life
Quest Limit Oh yeah you DA's uh quests
have a daily
limit ooh
so I guess we can go back to give back
the
quest right is it are we are we done in
here there's some here
yeah I have a medical
journal I have some ammo for you Kiara
and oh I got a brawling for fun ooh
thank you oh we forgot this
there you go there you go thank you oh
my goodness
sick oh I can drink beer now hey don't
do
it but it helps me punch better did you
go go into the uh attic and found crates
yeah okay okay okay good
good oh now you can you can be like
drunk drunk fist you know like the K fu
people drunken
fist here's the medical
journal some steroids too thank you oh
wow wow my armor level is at 54
now that's half of the
maximum wait I accidentally got a
medical Journey Journal I dropped it
again I think I can make first aid
bandages now
yay our second doctor doctor are you
licensed now I am I didn't give up on my
dreams after even
though I can you
please what was
it
um yeah let's go back I quickly want to
you know take care of everything make
some
do we have to talk to the same
Traer that we got the quest
from three of us failed uh the quest
let's do this one right here that's mine
oh it fails the last one that we did too
traffic so we can complete this one
maybe okay I'm so far this is just a
bing oh you were fast
huh yeah I just closed my eyes and
started biking
she's in the hurry I'm on my way back
there's a quest here bab yeah I have a
clear Quest
here
what I don't see it I don't either but
oh you don't see the you don't see the
bouncy exclamation point right yeah
normally we would see it wait maybe we
can't do it together for some
reason maybe maybe we can't cuz I can't
even press f on it ah it's because we
reached the daily Quest limit is that
why I don't think so cuz we failed we
failed ours so I don't have a it should
say if you have a limit I don't but do
you have at the bottom left do you have
a exclamation mark a red
one
[Music]
uh is that the one that says you're done
with questing FAA do you have it I have
it yeah we're done with questing for
today oh I don't have it yeah you're not
done oh okay I guess I can't start no I
can't start it I think it's bugged so we
can go maybe you can start it because
we're in a group maybe alone you can do
it maybe well I don't even see it for
myself okay so it's okay let's go
home and end our days slowly
yes turn the quest first go to the Traer
yeah I follow you girls I don't know
where to
go I feel like I actually have to learn
the maps
now like before I just run around but
now there's like roads and terrain we go
we go up this we go we go down wait no
we go up we go we go up we go up you're
right you're
right hold on them what are you
saying and then I started biking
yeah I think learning the roads is good
because now biking cuz it Doesn't you
can't just cut through really easily
with a bike
yeah this place is
Nice Nice
Landscaping she just closed
dang wait my bik oh my God wait my
bike's in there my bike's in there bike
she stole she stole my
bike this one did she Chuck it outside
this pink one oh yes oh did she did she
Chuck it outside that was nice to her
yeah she might have thrown your bike out
oh my
God it does it not work oh I guess that
was nice of her to
do she's
no yeah just just cuz she's closed
doesn't mean she's
heartless we'll figure it out later
chat all right well I guess this is
where I will stop for today okay yeah me
too
goodbye bye bye I will stay in game just
to quickly skill points and stuff but I
won't stay too long and I will not stay
AFK I will yeah don't AFK I want to
level up too I have a point too wait
where's home where is home byebye that
way byebye
[Music]
byebye hello I'm just leveling up as
well it's so hard to think about what
you got to level into but apparently
there's a a way to Res skill you can
reset your skill points but it's kind of
expensive oh you can mhm the trader
sells an item for it
if you really messed up you can buy
it I wonder if sneak is useful we
haven't really been sneaking anywhere it
is if you like raid houses like a little
bit more carefully if you sneak onto the
enemy you do like way more damage and
can kill them way
easier Quest failed oh okay that was
geek's
Quest no but if you if you if that's not
your play style then maybe not depends
on what you want to
do stealth
build shared Quest here one that's
that's not the one
that I still have the the one
right the one that I didn't
fail can I check that
somewhere oh this one this one should be
fine don't go
backwards a thank you for the gigy raid
the beaver
raid H it's 6: a.m. in my place it's 6
a.m. good morning yeah yeah I've been
completely changing my sleep schedule
for this project but it's worth it I'm
having lots of fun yeah it's so fun it's
way more like there's way more stuff in
it than I thought it was going to be
like the skills and stuff well I didn't
really know what to expect but this was
it's great yeah I love how we all like
have different like roles and stuff yeah
exactly it feels like everybody has a
purpose and they know what to do now and
now at least like we have a we have some
Cooks we have some first aid people we
have me for the armor we have the farmer
shielding we have killing people oh yeah
I just like to kill people and cook on
the side mm what a nice lifestyle to
have yeah I don't know if the evening
jst time slots will ever happen at this
point it's kind of like I would normally
join it but then you know when
everybody's in the na time slot it just
it didn't happen
last night right this yeah it was
cancelled because it seems like not
enough people are were like interested
what's with these
trees what
trees huh are you okay PL it does oh
like I I I am finding an
unusual wall of trees in front of my
house that was never there
before and I was just like this is like
I'm snowed in but it's like treed
in but apparently they were planted by
gigy okay nature is healing nature is
healing this is some kind of
fortification all right there's trees in
the
house what that's a lot she loves trees
she's such a beaver
do I even have enough KS for what I
going to
do surely these birds that are following
me won't follow me all the way back
right uh no I don't think
so
okay track I'm going seing kit and duct
tape duct tape please please only one oh
I have two I'm a crafting okay okay okay
are you doing vehicle too by the way yes
I'm quite far with it too I
[Music]
think okay I'll save those for you
please build motorcycle
yeah and then car I'll build all the
cool stuff helicopter
so I don't even know do you build cars
and all that also on the workstation
chat I
wonder what else oh the armor parts hey
welcome welcome in the other home oh my
gosh trees right trees
everywhere it's so
green what do I need where armor here
okay oh yeah armor parts are also very
useful let's see what did I
say I
[Music]
need boots need forged iron armor free
armor crafting kids
M well I can make a couple
here
okay Commando are you still streaming B
boo yeah
hello hello people on the other side
hello people on the other side are you
still streaming yes hello people on the
other
side hello we should like this is this
is kind of sweet I can talk to your
Pebbles you can talk to kfp I
F they're saying hi hi P are say
[Music]
hello they give you a CO and D ah a a
call and d and the smiley face the co
and D on the typing board ah Co and D
col D col D I don't know what that word
but I know what you're like you mean the
smiley the laughing face yeah colon not
col colon a a double punk dou punk is ah
oh how do you say it dou Punk d d Punk
yes D Punk don't punk oh that's cute
don't be
Punk the two dots ah I thought you were
saying some some weird magical
word okay
Leever and forged
iron Lea and forged IR we have that we
have that
oh I have leather here here here uh oh
it was it in that chest I dropped oh
it's only two yeah I should have oh here
here's more a lot more it's okay I got
plenty in here too
them this forged iron is over there I
need to make a chest that has all of
these things that I need for armor stuff
cuz it's usually always the same it
seems where did it go where did it go
guess there's also some in the
Forge it's
not but I'm sure we still got
some ah so blind I wish I could just
type it
in okay ah making armor come on
y these will be really nice to have and
they're level free so I can already make
level free armor
oo and then the other thing I think was
Nomad NAD chest can you make medium
armor uh I can make heavy medium and
light all of them and all of them at
seemingly level three now ooh
nice but I just need a lot of armor
crafting kits and stuff okay I'll be on
the lookout
for oh wait what's this can I not make
this more clo
rment that's where it
is stinky boots finally exchanged my old
sandals and now those scorpions can't
bite me
[Music]
anymore oh
cloth clo cloth clo clo do you have any
cloth on you I have cloth
fragments yes yes yes
okayi oh
awesome thank you oh more
oh okay wa I give back where did it go
oh I got it oh
[Music]
nice we're just in the process of Min
maxing right now yeah we're getting
ready but don't worry won't we won't
stay on for 7 hours no no no
no uh
craft and then maybe no I won't have
enough armor crafting kits
for for the chest piece
yet
uh armor armor crafting
M oh but I can make more I just need
more duct tape and duct tape was glue
and oh my God so many cloth fragments oh
you can make du tap okay here's glue
yeah oh no glue I have uh it's more like
the cloth fragments but I'll I'll take
you glue anyway here
go ah thank you
oh fragments why are you so elusive more
elusive than I thought you would be can
I make that too don't think I can
oh cotton you make them with cotton
that's not too bad oh there are like
cotton plants everywhere and you can get
cotton yeah they're
everywhere have I ever put them
somewhere I feel like I've picked up
cotton sometimes but got to a punch of
few Cottons I'm going to do that before
I leave because that shouldn't be too
much it's hard to leave my house now
there's too many trees
here okay cotton cotton where is cotton
when you need
cotton this is something
[Music]
else I should just use my
bicycle if you craft ammo is just like
one ammo at at a time like One Singular
bullet you're crafting if so that's kind
of lame um I think you can like if you
have enough ingredients you can like
line line the queue up and it will craft
more I'm pretty sure I haven't tried
crafting ammo before so I'm not
sure there were some in the chest what
cotton or cloth
fragments let me see if there's any CL
in here though 17 ah in the food box I
had a feeling it would be in the food
box oh well what's
this okay I'll go
back
Yi fin should have many clo FR she
hidden curtains oh I should make that my
new uh pas time if you get cloth
fragments easily
then curtain
harvesting radio schematic
whatat ooh don't like this noise
curtains and beds are great for cloth do
you need any
more
7622 cuz I can C it oh I mean how much
do I have right
now oh not immediately but I mean
tomorrow for the rid
maybe am I the only one using the
machine gun I think so huh okay well
right now it's not that important I
think okay I'll hold off on making
bullets until we meet it yeah you can
save your materials I'm a lot
yeah
okay
cotton cotton how much cotton for one oh
just one okay I am prepared now so I'm
going to head on
bye-bye bye bye bye
tomor bye see you tomorrow for the for
the raid for the hord let's be ready
bye-bye
bye-bye hey let me quit the
game this game is soct
in it's very fun I like the
um I like
the collection the item collection of it
Kyla would love this game I wish we
could have extended the um
invite to like everybody next time or
something I would totally play this game
with Kyla yeah maybe in the future
mhm it's so fun cuz everybody has like a
different Rule
and um we're all like specializing in
different things I like my knife gun
build I feel very very powerful I feel
like I
I'm very
strong time to get yeah time to
get uh Magnum next and then I think you
can make like bigger blades outside of
nice I think you can make machetes and
stuff
so um
have you looked at the parkour skill I I
know that it increases your jumping and
fall damage so that's
nice no Katana is there Katana probably
not but that's okay I study all the
blades all the
blades decrease fall damage you know
what I mean
but I feel like I feel like I'm starting
to become a Spaceman where my jumping is
just so so anti-gravity
now but yeah I like I like my knife
bleed build I feel like I kill super
fast both with my pistol and my and my
knife so I like it I like being the
killer with with um a little bit of
cooking on the side for survival IAL but
mainly
kill zombies and your teammates I
couldn't help it A lot of the times the
kill is from them walking directly in
front of me you saw my screen you see it
happen I'm going against an enemy and
then suddenly they suddenly walk
directly in front of me while I'm while
I'm smacking them
there's proof look at the VOD watch The
V they'll just walk in front of me boom
and I I mean everybody kind of does it
together I was getting smacked by Mory a
lot doing the exact same
thing yeah exactly true watch The V were
you watching no you just like people
kills your friends no I don't not unless
they ask me to and sometimes they ask me
to I'm grateful that they they asked me
to
[Music]
yeah the I think the blade is just very
very powerful so one smack from me and
they'll just bleed out
[Music]
forever we have footage of the Cali oh
the Cali one was defitely on purpose I
admitted that
one I need a you know you know me I need
one intrusive thought kill and then I'm
good I had my intrusive thought head
shot and and we are we are fine
now yeah I might just end up yeah you
know when I said when I said that maybe
I wouldn't end up playing this every day
cuz maybe I need a break or no never
mind I don't need a
break I don't need a break it's too
fun it's too it's too um it's too
[Music]
Tey it's it's too enjoyable is D it's
add diting okay next time tomorrow's the
big big hor thing got to be there for
tomorrow what type of build are you
going for
killer killer build that is my build
killer
hey I hold my own in the fights now
though in the zombie
fights things get blasted easily by me b
b i put a bunch of bullets in
[Music]
them
okay uh
Super Chat time I
suppose yeah
FPS trading has come in
handy I'm killing my teammates not on
purpose unless they asked me to cuz I'm
pretty sure the time that I killed Kiara
just then was because she walked in
front of me while I was sleep lashing
something and I nicked
her oopsies and the
shoulder finally fire is on can't help
it I have to get up close to stab
oh yeah the CeCe has shot too she was
she was just suddenly boom in front of
me boom wrong
timing oh
[Music]
A Series of Unfortunate
timing but there's no penalty to to
death actually so like if you die well
unless you're you have a quest but like
I'm just helping you get your health
back to 100
[Music]
uh okay reading super CH now Robert
Panda thank you for super rock rock
people I have to send this early cuz I
won't be around for stream again that's
okay I saw you inform Pebbles about mov
as a tiny Pebble I'm happy to say I'm
very proud of my Comm OC rooting for you
thank thank you I will do my
best for this time this
this next couple of months I will work
very
hard I am excite nervous but excite
[Music]
ban I had a nice talk with Mom ski about
it last night she's also pretty she's
also very very very very supportive she
encourages the ah was it the
decision she thinks it is well s it for
me I think
yeah yeah she's totally supportive of of
the deis
[Music]
I know some people are a little bit
worried about like oh if people moves
her schedules going to change or she's
going to start streaming in different
time zones I have said that like again
multiple times I will never change
my um
time that I
stream um but I mean the best way that I
can ease your worries is just prove it
to
you I guys I don't think I need to say
anything further about I said all I can
to like try to you know reassure you
that I'll be okay so now it's just all
right I'll just I'll just prove to you
that I'll be
okay by
[Music]
um yeah yeah thank you for the super
rock rock looks look out she's got a
knife a knife I have a knife and I'm
happy use it it well you already proved
it in your recent JP Arc right I
mean yeah yeah I did like I hope you saw
when I recently went to Japan that I
streamed from 8:00 a.m. totally fine for
3 months but you know it's it's natural
to worry cuz it's natural to worry about
change and you
know I can't really say I've said all
that I can so if people are still
worried
then you know all I can do is just prove
it by
action yeah so I don't intend to change
my stream time at all or anything like
that all just watch me
[Music]
uh t thank you for super yeah actions
speak louder than
words I
suppose I'm more worried about the fact
that it might take you days to settle
down that is true and I am aware of that
and that is why I specifically
requested while I am looking for a place
I have access to a temporary PC I'm
taking the steps to prevent being gone
for a long number of days while I'm
doing the paperwork and looking for
places kind of thing I'm trying to
prevent that cuz I know that happens
nonetheless so I am requesting things to
to make sure that I'm able to still
stream and stuff while I am doing the
work I'll definitely it'll definitely be
like less stream time obviously because
I have to do those those business things
but I was even asked like are you sure
are you sure you want to stream during
that time B cuz you're going to be like
really really really busy and I was like
yeah I'm
sure yeah because I don't want I don't
want to take too big of a break between
between streaming even
um
even while
I'm like home hunting and stuff like
that because I hope you know that
streaming is like my number one
priority thing because it's just the
thing that I love to do the most so
uhhuh so that's why I'm T I'm trying to
takee the steps to
like at least stream be able to stream a
little bit and not be gone for like a
whole week or two not saying it won't
happen cuz it still might happen cuz you
never know with moving and stuff it'll
be rough you know so not saying it won't
happen but I'm trying to take as many
steps as I can to prevent it from
happening
[Music]
ah me or scel thank you for the super
rock rock fun corn fact corn must be mix
star
maliz to properly be broken down by
humans this involves slightly mixing it
with alkalide not doing this leads to a
lot of malnutrition
wow wow I didn't know that fun
fact so is corn toxic if
not horn f
corn fact is just not very nutritious it
tastes good though just not nutritious
enough a doesn't digest well low
nutrition food really but corn is using
everything why why did people decide to
take a low nutrition food and make it
nutritious rather than just a bunch of
something that's already
nutritious because cheap
uh easy to grow uh not a
h inone thank you for the super rock
rock stone Dragon thank you for a super
rock rock really be bo question mark I
don't know what the context of this was
but
yes yes
really um T car I thank you for a super
rock
yummy wait I yes yes really no I
actually don't really know the
context but sure yes whatever it was
yes yummy
thank you for the super rock rock bble
is on kill on sight mode even allies get
killed if you walk in front of my path
while I'm swinging
my knife then yes you will get
killed that is that is like yeah if you
walk in front of me and my prey and my
line of fire yeah you're going to get
killed
[Music]
oh that was when I killed CeCe okay but
she walked in front of me when I head
shot her she walked in front of my line
of side while I was
shooting I respond to move I do respond
to movement that's how you respond fast
[Music]
M
uh Sage minia I think for the super rock
rock hi be saying awesome is always
great I'm ring for you thank thank
you well this world is zombies this
world everything's trying to kill you so
like why wouldn't you shoot and
everything that moves if you hesitate
you die it's a zombie
apocalypse kill or be
kill budy thank you for the super Rock
BL I heard be Japan Arc is coming soon
yay I hope moving process will be smooth
I hope so too I taking as many steps as
I can for it to be smooth but things
will always happen and it may not go
smoothly trying to prevent it from not
from going smoothly but you know things
happen we will just take it as it
comes can't wait for the a way to
reunion with our beloved family Tiki I
can't wait for family
Tiki thank you for the super rock rock
thank you for suggesting ac6 to full m
people yeah that's what I want for them
is to reach out and try games that they
wouldn't necessarily think is their type
of
game because I've done that a lot and
some of those have become my favorite
games of all time so I hope for them
that as
well a birdie thank you for the super
rock rock I'm going to sign back to
shower Bab love and stupid everyday Club
beep trying hard to focus more on work I
perform much happier the healthier I am
and supporting B is what makes me happy
milk but what about
you but what about but what about but
what about the work thing that you were
just talking about
huh well I appreciate it thank thank you
why don't why don't you have both
successful work and
successful support people help both
12 hours in the
bathroom that one thank you for super
rock
rock people please stay the
same in what
way okay it's not like I plan on
changing anytime
soon short okay I don't think I can grow
any taller that's not really
possible please always be bald that's
not possible I've never been
bald please don't turn into a worm no
guarantees I I think bble can only be
bble I can't be
anything else other than people so I
don't think you'll have to
worry about me not being bibu cuz bibu
is bibu and I will be bibu and I am bibu
and bibo is
me yes
so but UB oh well UB is a part of be bo
isn't
it can you be B Bo no because I'm people
[Music]
uh that one thank you for the super rock
rock no cor link thank you Cobra link
thank you for the super rock rock well
well if it isn't my favorite brain rock
rock V to hi B
hi
hi yummy M thank you for the super Rock
ro hi Mom SEI my chew call OC see hi Mom
SEI oh yeah I talked I was talking with
Mom SEI a little bit you know how I was
traumatized by bees it's Mom sei's fault
she dressed me in flower pants I had
flower pants and that's why the bee
landed on my knee and stung me because
because she dressed me in flower pants
when I was when I was
little yeah
so Mom SEI traumatized me
by bees
yes you put me in Flowery
pants that makes sense that makes sense
is this why I don't really wear floral
print often well I don't I don't really
like wearing patterns to much anyway I
like solid colors better but uh I don't
really wear floral print much I think I
have like one floral print that's really
cute but that [\h__\h]
um but but floral print is so is so
popular in Japan
like everywhere I would go I would see
the same floral print dress in like like
in like watching like every other
Japanese lady wear a floral print dress
a long a long like long skirt length
floral print dress was very on Trend
when I was over there
yeah no not Kamar like a Sund dressy
type of
dress Japanese women and long
dresses people would could
never it's short dresses for me I
actually know I have a few I have a few
long dresses that go like past my knees
but I don't think I could do
like too close to my ankle or for I like
I this the short dresses work better for
me cuz
short but I I like long dress fashion I
think it looks very
nice also more chance of me stepping on
my dress and tripping
[Music]
uh C thank you for super rock rock
thanks to the stream always Pome to see
everyone having fun and getting class
yeah it's fun hanging
out it's kind of nice that it's not role
play and we're just casually playing
games um
with
friends kind of more chill casual
playing games with friends more than
role playing I don't feel as socially
drained I don't I actually I thought I'd
be a lot more drained doing playing this
than I was but no it's actually pretty
relaxing it's actually really fun yeah
cling and chilling and stuff like
that RP isn't for any everyone I love RP
I love to RP and rping it's just rping
for long periods of time for example GTA
or Ian Reco is a little bit of a you
know it it's a little bit of like it
takes a lot of energy to
do
but like this this where you're just
like chilling and working together and
playing games with friends this doesn't
really drain me too much at all
[Music]
cany thank you for the super rock rock
so
what you are so cute M MO
people fan club from
Thailand
um
y Yen
[Music]
y nice to meet you nice to meet you
too see I can kind of
read I can I can read if it takes a
while if it takes if it it takes a while
but I can
[Music]
read
y d
[Music]
like thank you for the super R oh R okay
I know R okay R know you so happy to
know you is
literal translation happy to know
you so nice to meet you is the
translation me happy to know you was a
literal translation
yeah nice
y die y
die yeah nice to know you happy to know
you um BL a thank you for the super rock
rock once Monster Hunter WS comes out
would you try doing collabs with other
members in the future too yes oh Kyla
promised me that she would play Monster
Hunter wild um I want aan to do weekly
Monster Hunter wild collabs so I know
narissa and Shori already played Monster
Hunter nurer played R so I played world
so I need now so I just need for Moka to
start and we'll have a full Advent when
rise comes out yes and I kind of want to
I kind of want to see if I can collab
with JP sen byai um Ora to Raa uh and I
want to see if I can collab with Senpai
cuz I know like there's a lot of JP
Senpai who also play um so I'm wondering
I'm wondering and eie and Opie as
well so I'm wondering if you know the JP
Senpai would be down to play with me as
well
maybe
I'll reach out
and will you play with us of course I'm
going to play with you guys too I I
sneez
no I need to play Monster Hunter and
practice long sword because I want to I
want to do long sword charge blade
that's what I'm going
to probably mean long sword charge blade
[Music]
but charge blade will probably if charge
blade mechanics stay the same or close
to as it is in Worlds then I'll probably
main charge plate charge plate has
completely different gameplay does it
did they changed it a
lot yes in a good way or a bad
way can't do sad of me we got a combo
into it well every every weapon's being
changed a little bit in a good way okay
I believe you you can combo a into
sad add into sad ooh
[Music]
it's much bad okay I'm excited
then can I still can I Ste pizza cutter
pizza cutter is fun I hope they keep
pizza
[Music]
cutter yes okay good that's all I
need and it's better or it's
better did you hear sh is working on
silent hill perm so maybe you should
play it too oh yes um it is a silent
Tails individual perm so I need to ask
myself if I play it it's an individual
thing
yeah um I'm interested I need to pick at
least
one
solo horror game for next
week I need I need to pick at least
one since it's it is spooky spooktober I
need to do at least one solo spooky
game what it is yet I don't know Silent
Hill is perfect I've never played any of
the Silent Hill series before
um last year it was
ari2 this year maybe Silent Hill
too let's see I'm never yeah I never
play on Hill game
though but I can't just
avoid Silent Hill or not Silent Hill
horror games this month that would going
be very B of me I got to do it and then
probably going to do a spooky collab
with Kyla and then maybe do a scaredy
cat collab with GG and B
[Music]
of but we'll see after this week cuz
obviously this week is 7 Days to Die
week we are horror game
one I I don't
know maybe maybe
but horror games give me headaches and
VR games make me motion sick so like the
combination of the two might be a little
too much for me to be completely
[Music]
honest it's not an excuse though when I
get scared I get a
headache
and I
will I don't want to sacrifice there are
definitely many other scary games that I
can play play that doesn't you
know I mean I'll give it I'll give it a
shot I think fasmo VR would be the
easiest thing
to probably try it out with
but that is is pushing it a little
[Music]
bit I mean V games I haven't played that
many VR games
but games where you stand still like
beats saber is fine but games where
you're like moving through a
map uh gives me motion sickness quite
quickly which is what I am concerned
with with spooky games like Ari that
like you just go through go through the
map and stuff
even if you was just F Well I played a
VR game and I modded the game to like
try to help with the with the graphics a
little bit and like I modded so I would
have I could adjust like the visuals I
still passed
out so
yeah we'll see I just don't want to end
up passing out on
stream is my concern that will be not
very good and I don't think you would
want to you would want to see that
[Music]
mhm do not BL on hly not very Demir not
very mindful think of the content is
that's not wor that's not worth the
content
that's definely that's definitely not
worth
it but yeah we'll definitely play a
spooky game more likely it won't be a
vond it'll be like an acne game like
Silent Hill or dead space or whatever
alien isolation or what of those one of
those things I'll I'll request perms for
Silent
Hill let's see if we can play something
next
week resy we could do
re1
um
yes you get motion sickness IRL if not
you should probably just have to
practice
VR to get over motion
sickness
um it's like a time limit thing like
beat saer I can play for
hours VR chats I have about like two or
3 hours before I start getting
dizzy
um Skyrim it's like less than an hour
before I start it's it's basically
the dependent on the
game um I don't really get most in
sickness in life too much I don't
think I can go on roller coaster is fine
I can go on boats
fine oh but I I'm really easily sick in
cars though I hate I said this before I
hate riding in cars when I ride in a car
it drains all my energy from me it
drains it drains my my being it it's it
just drains me so hard I don't know why
cars but
like I get car sickness so easily I
don't know why car sickness specifically
but trains are fine planes are fine I
don't get motion Shake in ples like if
there's like turbulence I'm totally fine
I will sleep through turbulence
like I remember I remember being on the
plane sleeping and then turbulence is
happening and I was like half conscious
and I was like huh no h shaking
huh
this Le
yes going to go back to sleep or
something so I can sleep through
turbulence pretty easy I don't know why
it's cars but cars
car smell sucks it might be the smell
cuz I think it I think it's the
combination between car smell
and and stuff
because um when I was in a car like I
was in a taxi with full m and they gave
me a
mint
and the mint really helped the car
sickness so like
maybe it is the chemical smell of the
car or something like that because like
the mint really helped with car sickness
for
me Stinky I have a sensitive nose so if
you are
stinky I can tell sniff sniff I get a
whff for you
and
ew I really like that Meme uh ew you
stink go
shower with with me in the spray go you
stinky go shower that was really
cute go
shower
um ah TIY too thank you for the super
rock rock just want to say doggo is
wrong of all the bab B girls and Hall
life baby was the prettiest and the
sparkliest too still baby though wait
didn't but wasn't what muku said muku
said I am pretty so you should agree
with the doggles the doggles are right I
am pretty and
cute you can be pretty and cute at the
same time
M said three
things she did he did
say one other
thing he
did h
oh wa my tables in the
way oh gosh I am hovering my
body
okay my motion
[Music]
get away I'm getting closer
he
hold
on
[Music]
ew you're stinky
ew a
shame
oh you have you been rolling around the
dirt since your pble have you just been
rolling around it smells like mud and
dirt and mooss
did you roll around and dog poo
[Music]
poo did you roll around thinking it was
mud but it was actually dog poo
poo disgusting
[Applause]
[Music]
oh was I done I think I was die May were
just
chilling oh yeah I'm
done
okay time to we can tell more I mean I
guess we can what do you want to talk
about do you have anything you want to
talk about otherwise I'm
leaving yep you have anything y about
otherwise I'm
aing quick
star the Shadows generation animation oh
yeah I haven't seen the Shadow videos
yet I wanted
to they Space Marine went as soon as
possible as soon as possible as soon as
as soon as
possible Space Marines that's that's
what I want to play now no not
now did you hear about the E10 DLC E10
these nuts in your mouth that that one's
so old get new adults that's so old
that's so that's that's such an old one
how do you not think
that I don't know that
one a classic
yeah um any watch along
[Music]
soon we could do a bookie movie there's
so much to do so much to play how am I
supposed to fit it all I'm already
streaming like 7 days a week how am I
supposed to how am I supposed to
fit everything that you want me to do in
one in one week cuz we got Space Marines
we we need to play a spooky game we need
to watch a horror thing we have to we
have to uh we have to do collabs of
people we have to play uh Black Ops we
didn't finish BLS to the uh there's card
shop S I need to get a ghost card I
haven't got a ghost car yet
I also need to
sleep unless you don't want me to sleep
okay I won't to sleep I'll just be here
forever and ever and ever and ever and
not sleep but then I got I got homework
too oh I like this smug too this one's
cool
bombastic side
eye criminal offense side eye
what you haven't showered in how
long
huh
really
what no way
what you have that many plastic bottles
on your desk how can you even grab
anything why are there so many cans on
your desad
hey what's that over there in the corner
of your
room how long has that pile of clothes
been there that corner right there that
corner in your room over there that one
that one in the
corner why why why is what's that pile
huh
hey can I check under your bed what are
you hiding under your bed can I take a
look what about your floorboards hey why
is this floorboard
loose hey why why is this why is this
why is that floorboard like popping out
a little bit is there something under
there can I can I see
can I can I
see hey can I Snoop in your closet I
just want to check out your fashion I
going to judge your fashion sense can I
can I take a look in your closet what
are you hiding in
there let me
see let me see
oh my gosh you have that what is that
no no that's messed up
no I can't believe you have
that
what even that's too much for me no
no oh my
God don't tell anyone I don't know I
might have to report this I don't know
if I can keep this a secret I don't know
I don't know if I can I can keep that a
secret I I feel like I have to tell
someone I I don't I it's just it's just
too shocking no snitching okay well
what's what's it it for me then
What will What will what will it take
for me not to
talk I can borrow it okay deal
why is she angry why why is she angry
hey hey hey Pebbles Pebbles why is she
angry why why is she angry
huh can someone tell me why she's mad
can someone tell me why she's
angry cuz he hates us
why is he
sad oh this is
cute I didn't know I could do that
wait can I do it
this I
can oh I can't do it if if I'm not
frowning
though this one looks silly
I'm so
bewildered cute this one's cute too
I don't know I'm just being silly I
should go I should go sleep I should go
I should I I should I should stop being
silly I should I should I should
away hold on hold on I got some supers I
got to read that and then I should away
I should sleep I I got distracted by
being silly again hold
on n
m thank you for the super rock rock
people I you shower today how dare you
sniff me
[Music]
again are you sure about
that why does it smell like you haven't
showered
then did you did you wash completely
everything did you wash your
butt did you wash your feet did you wash
your armpits did you wash all the cracks
did you wash your belly button
did you wash did you wash the back of
your head did you wash did you wash
every little
crease did you did you wash everything
with
soap with
soap why was what's Soap
soap
soap this the most terrifying thing on
the universe soap the most the most
terrifying the most terrifying thing
that could scare even the the most Brave
dog
soap soap
soap from Modern Warfare oh yeah
soap uh you you think for super rock
rock today is my birthday can you wish
me a happy birthday I love you I
guess happy birthday to
you I
suppose happy
birthday to you
or something happy
birthday dear
Pall happy
birthday to
you
H oh
oh hold on there's
more um thank you for super rock rock
thank you for the super rock rock dark
thank you for the super rock Rock N time
thank you for the super rock rock UNL
Expressions AR by the way did you know
this ESS is to sto you from borrowing
that in my closet here's more be tax in
exchange for not snitching oh well I
guess you did pay people tax so I
suppose it's fine I suppose it's fine I
feel like a fish in the dentist's office
this is exactly what it is you
guys I'm watching you I'm observing you
I'm in your walls I'm observing your
life please do something funny so I may
be entertained I will tap on the
glass can I tap on the glass let's
see how do I tap on the glass
oh here a point
is there is there a point I want to tap
on the
glass
W
hey hey
to to do something entertaining tap to
now it's your turn to entertain me to to
to
to let me
in let me in
oh tap tap oh yeah there we
go tap
to hey do something do
something do something hey I'm bored do
something right in the eye oh
oh p
dance St is your is your eye itchy here
I'll help you you need to scratch that
itch for you on your eye in the back of
your eye hold let me just get right in
there and
just
do there you
go ew ew you got some you got some eye
go ew it's on my hand ew take it back ew
ew take back back I go ew ew I need to
wipe my hand
ew ew I go ew I touched it a this got
e
oh I WIP wipe it off
all right are we done can I go
now just kidding I'm getting distracted
cuz I'm having
fun we got distracted playing with the
model no oh I
see uh budy thank you for the or not yes
bird thank you for the super rock rock
one are you going to finish mon to World
sometime soon yes I want to beat at
least Kyla Furious KY before before
before uh Wilds also green scream scream
screen also green screen stream and 3D
when for more memes when I have a home
3D setup that I can freely move around
in because I want to do meme dances too
uh just doing my part stalling people by
the way thank you for stalling
me Sky let say thank you for the super
rock rock people can't sniff sniff us
she doesn't have a nose yes I do you
want a HD of my
nose look at it from all the
angles all the
angles look it's a nicely shaped
nose all all the angles well
there how can you not whoa how can you
not see
it you've got all the nose angles now
you can draw my nose with great detail
now because you know exactly how it
looks like all the references for
you very shiny look it has a little nose
shine to it
it's
pointy sharp got sharp
[Music]
nose uh King of Kings thank you for the
super rock rock randomiz thank you for
the super rock rock hi people I'm
mistaking or does your eye have a heart
now we can check together there's no
hearts in my eyes and no I'm not going
inside my head head we saw it once we're
not seeing it again I don't want you to
look inside of my
head but I don't see I mean I guess like
the bottom part of the shading could him
like a
heart it kind of looks a little bit like
it nothing in there yeah that's true
it's pretty
Hollow BM
[Music]
look at how nicely shaped my eyelash is
look at that it curves
up so like I have a and then the eye and
then
the and you can see the gem from the
side oh so many angles of
be nice polygons
yeah
um yeah thank you for super rock rock
this is also totally not a reminder for
the M assistant endings you have yet to
get um I might not do M assistant cuz I
talked to Kyle about doing it and she
said like there's not that much more
like you've seen most of the game
already and it might be worth it to play
like a new spooky game instead of
playing a spooky game that that like
you've already played so that is I
talked to her a little bit about it but
she was like yeah there's not that much
besides like lore and stuff um so it
might be worth it just to play something
new and spooky instead cuz we have
limited spooky month
time also silent 2 will be great if you
get to play it one of my favorite
stories from a horror game yes it is
separate separate perms for everybody
though so I have individually get perms
myself so that that but I will try to
get them in
time it it it just depends on the game
and the game company why is it like that
it's not it's not it depends on the game
company and what they want basically it
depends on the publisher the
developer so yeah
[Music]
he can we get a closeup of the demem on
your test you change colors
in live 2D it doesn't change colors
right now but I was told that it will
Ooh o look at the shine I was told that
it will eventually though when it gets
updated
ooh
ooh wait was that are you trying to
trick
me are you really enjoying like see my
cool my cool gu gu chest Dam or or is
that a trick I'm going to give you the
benefit of the doubt okay because it is
very cool and I do like showing it off
because it is very cool
swing so I trust the
respectful
[Music]
observation okay
anyway uh this four think for Super V
Rock hi bab more s days die it's great
for collab games have you seen P Park 2
and Liar's bar yet rock rock star so
I've seen pic Park 2o justice has and
Avan has expressed interest U I was
thinking about planning it after the
Seven Days to Die thing but I didn't
want
to ask to plan it for while we're busy
with this so a little bit later
[Music]
Liars bar I've never heard of liars bar
though uh I look thank you for the super
rock rock take my B love get a job clean
your room take a
shower get adequate sleep and eat
properly and
uh
yeah I'll brush your teeth
uh touch some grass
sometimes and
um and make sure to clean every crevice
when you're taking a shower cuz you
there are more spots that you might miss
and that would be stink
[Music]
oh thank you for super rock rock B can
you unlock more face before you go not
selling fun I swear wow you guys like me
that much that you just want me to you
just kind of stall that hard you just
don't want me to
go
wow talk about me
needy I'm just
kidding I mean it's not a face but have
you ever seen my wing my wing is cool
you should you should take a look at
it hold
on it's very it's very sh and it has
like swinging physics on the G I just
think it's
neat and sometimes people forget that I
have wings but I do have
wings Swing Swing I can
fly oh I just realized I don't have my
oh yes I do oh I
do they're just like
round I thought I didn't have it I do
have them
revolation I can't make them spin right
now but they shoot bble Beam bble Beam
[Music]
I by way there's
more H time to thank you for a super
Rock Rocky thank you for the super rock
rock I can never
leave
uh n thank you for the super Rock
it's not that we're stalling we're
simply preventing you from doing hey
look a b not stalling for sure where
where which direction
where where where's the bird
huh behind
[Music]
me where
where do
go is it out
there
oh it's all my bad you're
right oh yeah it's a little it's a
little stradle yeah you are
right oh he saw distracting
me I'm leaving
now
uh
goodbye good night I'll see you tomorrow
for
um the thing more 7 Days St I will
definitely be playing tomorrow cuz I cuz
the the hord is coming the hord is
coming
so we got to go I turned off the game so
I will not be AF
King oh wait there's
more oh wait there's more hold on wait
there's more cut
uh uh
absolute Cinema oh do you want to pose
for that
Meme
absolute
Cinema absolute
per you're
welcome
um but you thank you for the super rock
rock oh look it's a bird never mind it
was my name it's not for stalling sure
sure uh go go tile thank you for the
super rock rock hey hun
thank you for super rock rock people
when is your million subscribers vid I'm
not at million subscribers yet
but if you want to help me get there
that that would be cool I suppose if you
want to
anyway uh Advent thank you for the super
rock rock thank you so much for
making prism noo it's become my go-to
song I even redownload Apple music just
so like by oh thank you for the support
thank you for the support for my song on
the streaming services too thank you
thank you that's very nice I appreciate
it
um she you thank for this super rock
rock before you go stream prism Noah
yeah stream prism noala I just came out
with the original song my first one
prism
no stream it watch the video it's
there's a lot of little Easter eggs in
there watch it every day while you're
working
out I have 10 thingies up 10 different
ways to listen to it in your car um on a
train on a plane at work at a at a party
um blasted if you work at like a cafe
blast it in the cafe I'm sure people
will like it read it in the or listen to
it in the bathroom in the shower and in
your bath in the shower on the toilet
when you're struggling really hard you
would listen to my song to give you
motivation if you're struggling in the
toilet um before you go to sleep at
night that' be really um nice way to end
the day when you wake up so put it as
your alarm song so it make you want to
get up in the morning
um whatever you doing that's like way
more than 10 ways to to listen to
it
uh and um when you're taking a walk it's
a good walking song when you're lifting
do you even lift bro you want strong
arms listen to prism NOA I saw some
people uh tag me on X Twitter actually
lifting while while doing while
listening to prison naho you go you get
those Gams you'll get those gains oh
while you're doing gacha it will
increase your gacha luck it won your you
won your 50/50 see
see yeah
[Music]
uh yeah thank you for the thank you for
the super rock rock um people I'm new to
the Warhammer series what can you tell
me about the Lord from you learned uh
there's it's space
medieval it's space medieval it's
medieval in space so the Space Marine
are like the Angels who are like eight
feet tall um and there's people called
the Canadians who need our help and
um and there's this guy called the
emperor but he's like half dead but we
need him cuz he's like the chosen one
and because of him space travel is
possible cuz he's the chosen one for
whatever reason so we kind of need that
guy we need that guy alive
um so so a thousand 10,000 people die a
day to keep that guy alive or whatever
or a thousand
people he eats a thousand people a day
to to to keep him alive but that's okay
cuz he's him and so many more people
would
die uh if he didn't but then there's
also like uh four
gods and we give them blood for the
blood God but that's heresy or something
like that um so that so I guess that's
not very good and uh the tyranids are
scum death to all tyranids uh xenos
filth filthy please kill them we Must
Destroy them with all that we have uh
they are an endangerment to the the
universe uh that's all I
know that's all I know so far but before
my next stream of Warhammer I will watch
videos to know more about this weird
deep lore thing
uh wa if I pay you these $10 will you
continue to stream for another hour just
to have a comy chat stream thank you
Peter for the super um maybe not an hour
but but oh but I mean I'll I'll be here
long longer for a minute while I'm
reading your Super Chat oh God what's
happening what's
happening what is going
on
um hey be would you also RZ s for the
super rock rock hey B do you know dark
sours lore by any chance please explain
in great detail
okay there was this you should have
asked for Elden ring cuz I'm way
more verse in Elden ring lore than Dark
Souls Lore
um there's this
guy
named Gwen or something GW
[Music]
Gwen okay so din Soul there's this
flame um and you have to to light the
flame
um and um you have to keep the flame
alive and
so this guy sacrificed himself to keep
the flame alive and then you are Ashen
one or whatever
um and then pling pling pong ping ping
pong and then there
see I'm not refreshed with Dark Souls
Lore I forgot the Dark Souls you should
have you should have told asked Elden
ring um and uh and then you have the
choice to either rekindle The Flame or
um take it for yourself and rule the
world or something like that
yes something something flame something
something ping ping pong something
something something
something
hey
um D Bagels thank you for the super rock
rock my mom sadly passed last week oh
I'm so sorry for your loss beep cancer
yeah beep cancer I'm so sorry
uh I wanted to thank you for making me
laugh despite and smile despite
everything that's happened you and the
other girls have helped me so lot a lot
thank you thank you thank you for the
super my my
condolences
um you know moms are an amazing thing
people I love my Mom very much so I
would be super sad if M I didn't have
mom se you around anymore so you
know I'm so sorry for your
loss um but yeah I bet she loved you so
much and you know I bet she gave you an
amazing amazing life and I bet you had
so many amazing memories together so be
cancer yeah be can you stay strong um
and keep going and do good for your
mama yeah do good keep doing good for
your mom I'm sure she's proud of
you uh yum Dum thank you for super rock
rock good night good night but I'm still
here and also I thank you for you know
I am very happy that I can bring you at
least a little bit of you know ease and
happiness when you know you're in this
hard time you know even just a little
bit I'm happy that I can do
that I thank you for super rock rock
plus one thank thank you oh my gosh oh
what is
happening um
you're thank you for the super rock rock
lore go on I think I'm going to have to
explain like 10 different video game LS
now
uh new Ro roll thank you for the super
rock rock elen ring Lord ASMR F all
right there's this people called the
outer
gods and um the outer the outer
Gods sent the Elden Beast Down to the
worlds of the lands between and thingies
and the first FY was the mom of fies and
they sent the fies down and there's
these people who are called um imperian
who are basically like children
of the the outer beings where their
bodies are controlled by them and they
they and they all have shadows with dogs
that protect them uh Queen Mar and they
are in line to become Gods themselves so
Queen Mar was uh was it was one when the
Elden ring story happened but
um well so she she was she she's the big
one she had elen but then but then
there's his there's is imperian named
Ranny and she did not want to accept her
fate as an imperion and because of that
uh she devised a plan because her body
as an imperion will betray her and her
wishes because it has to follow the the
the lies of the outer beings because of
body is under control so she devised a
plan where she um hired people um and
you can't really kill an imperion
properly so she decided okay what we're
going to do is we're going to kill my
brother and me at the same time because
you can't just do it properly so she
sent the she hide assassins to kill her
brother Godwin
um but only his soul so at the same time
her body was killed so well not brother
I don't think it was another imperian no
no that Godwin's not well I you're
technically
like half technically half brother is
half halfish e half halfish e um and
then anyway so Goin gin's Soul died but
his his body lived and then uh ranny's
body died but her soul lived and
um and and then rany r that way rannie
was free from her Imperium body and
that's why she's in a puppet now and
then uh because of that Mara was like no
because she really really liked Godwin
and then she shattered the Elden ring so
that is basically why the Elden ring
story started was actually because of Ry
because Mar was like no my son no and
then she out of Rage shattered the Elden
ring and then um thus thus began the
plot to Elden ring because of Ranny good
job Ranny you are the best uh you have
not done anything wrong and they would
never make me hate
you okay that there's the beginning Lord
of Elden ring I don't think I can go
about the rest of it or else I'll be
here for 10
hours you skipped so much W I'm trying
to give like a little preview I'm not V
T I'm
bble
I there you go
there's this is bble explains hold on um
bu B can you thank you for the super Ro
can you tell me the story of John
tarnished and his quest Elden ring
lordship all right well the t is are
people who are banished from the land
between and now they've come back to
answer the call because the Earth tree
and the fingers called to them because
uh of the whole shattered thing and then
um so you you have heard the club to
become because your goal is like they
the fingers need help the fingers have
called you to come back to become Elden
Lord the proper Elden Lord so you go
through these trials um and stuff and
you need
to some reason kill the other imperion
or whatever beat them up to because you
need their like runes or something
question mark um to access the tree and
you also got to burn the tree and then
you got to blah blah yeah blah but then
boom plot twist we don't beeping like
the thingies that's why I said beep the
thingies so plot twist beep them burn
the
tree beep the fingers beep them
whatever May the moon take over ranny's
ending best ending don't fight me you
can't fight me cuz you know it's
objectively
true I mean you go on Eternal Eternal
Voyage with your wife how how could
anything be better than that
okay I skipped too much I know what do
you expect you want me the whole you
want the whole
thing
anyway
um thank you for the super rock rock
we're talking about spooky do you
recommend any Tha horror movies um I
don't know many Thai horror movies but I
really like that series on on Netflix I
think it's called like the girl from
nowhere it's Thai series um each episode
is like its own story and it follows
like really um and like it follows a
girl named Nano and she's like an
exchange student um who like goes to
different high schools and like exposes
them for being being
like corrupt or one way or another and
it's pretty it's pretty fun it's pretty
spooky it's pretty creepy
um yeah I like I liked that that Series
yeah there there's there's a there's a
recommendation for you
okay
um rainy ninja thank you for the super
rock rock hey people if you end up
diving into Warhammer lore videos I
suggest watching bricky that was the one
that was suggested to me the most so I
will be watching those before next
Warhammer stream uh thank thank you uh
Papa Foundry thank you for the super
rock rock have you watched any Warhammer
lure videos I have not I only know from
what Callie told me and everything I've
experienced in the game and you guys
have told me but I will watch them
before the next
stream uh Peter thank you for the super
watch Ro can you explain in detail the
meaning of life 42 um how do we get here
why do we get here what's our purpose
are we loading the universe side note
the do you know dmail is an anagram for
ligma 42
[Music]
can you explain
4242 do you know reference yeah I saw
the movie
fairly
recently I saw the movie fairly
uh not like super recent but like
recently recently the movie oh I heard
it's a book I haven't read the book yet
though I haven't read the book I've just
seen the
movie Mama yeah hit Tiger's guy to the
[Music]
gall uh yeah thank you for the super
rock rock thank you for the exclamation
people um it's very helpful now what
about Kingdom Hearts for like the whole
keyblade B until Kingdom Hearts there's
a all there's a there's a guy named the
master of Masters the master of mastered
had five apprentices and another guy and
he had a keyblade and he gave one of his
disciples a keyblade and was like this
keyblade can see the future please take
it with you um because it will watch and
you will need it in the future and then
he goes by and then the five disciples
got mad at each other because they
thought they were the best one so there
was a keyblade War keyblade War happened
and then why he told one of the groups
one of the groups went into a pocket
Dimension to completely avoid the
keyblade War cuz like uh they'd all knew
that they were going to kill each other
so like one one dimension like one or
one one faction like uh didn't even
fight in the war they just kind of hid
but the rest of them everyone killed
each other and then um zoom zoom zoom
zoom zoom zoom zoom Kingdom Hearts
3 Darkness Darkness light light oh X
blade yeah the key not the not the
keyblade the keyblade not the keyblade
but the keyblade uh and then uh uh
there's Sora but there's also roxus who
is not Sora um the roxes is sora's
nobody uh uh Shion is sora's lost
memories that take the form of Kyrie
because Kyrie is the closest one to his
heart so C is not not Sora but kind of
Sora and then there's Rox and then
there's ventis ventis is not Sora but
Venus looks like
uh uh roxes because no actually roxus
looks like ventes because vent is um U
was Sora touched ventus's keyblade um so
that's why Sora can use a keyblade cuz
he touched ventus's keyblade um but then
ventis went to sleep but he needed a
play uh a safe place to sleep because of
vanitus because vanitus is the evil
ventis vanitus is the evil uh uh in um
Venus's darkness and Venus's heart but
uh uh vantis looks like Sora for some
reason and then um but he's also not
Sora and then so Venus is also was
asleep inside s's heart for a while and
then there's also uh SE seon who's my
favorite character she's best girl she
can do no wrong I love her and then and
then uh um and everybody is is Sora and
everybody's also rku and everybody's
also
zort got it
memorized oh did you know did you know
did you know namura the the director of
Kingdom Hearts has to watch lore videos
to keep up with his own lot do you know
that he said that in an interview he
said that in an interview where he has
to watch his own L what like people's
fan-made lore videos just to catch up
with his own plot
yes that's a
thing so even the creator of Kingdom
Hearts doesn't
know Kingdom Hearts and has to has to
watch L videos to to uh
[Music]
yes and there's a thing called getting
norted where you a like puts part of his
soul into someone anom and and zus are
not the same person um Terra xor is not
the same person but also the same person
as uh and then Terra zor is zor where he
lost his memories and then and then anom
is the uh part list of Terra Zord and
then uh zus is the nobody of Terra xanor
and this teror xor because zor took him
over to terra's body because he got and
then um U uh
anyway and Sh is half theor too sure why
not you got to be distracted again
reading the Super Chat
mama and Kingdom Hearts is
[Music]
light uh thank you for super rock rock
stop send suers just to rest by the way
will there be any outfits related to
your new original song I'm curious thank
you for rest well if I could have 10,000
different outfits I would and you know
that me fashion people if I could if I
could make like 10 different magical
girl outfits for me to wear I totally
[Music]
would de Griz thank you for the super
rock rock what be dogs that's a new name
been out in and out due to work but did
you ever get to the karaoke supers
before prism no M I did not cuz we
haven't had a Super Chat reading yet um
but I'll do that
sometime as well do another Super Chat
reading Benny thank you for the super
rock rock no thank you for super rock
rock hey guys did you know that in terms
of
did you know in terms of head pability
Vaporeon is the most head pable
Evolution because
um it's very cool to the touch So like
um because it's a water type so it won't
be too too hot or too warm so you can P
pad it uh as much as you want without
and I bet it has a nice a nice texture
because I feel like we Pon would
like I guess fish maybe a fish but
anyway it would be moist moist and every
time you you head Pat it your hand would
stay moisturized um because it is moist
So
like um
yes
so dang it you know Vaporeon like was
one of my favorite eveve utions until
until you guys well not you guys but
like people messed it up now if I say I
like Vaporeon I'm like hey did you know
did you know stop it leave Vaporeon
alone leave AAP poon alone dang it
anyway yes I did know um T hunted thank
you for the super rock
rock
uh H helloo thank you for RO thanks to
the stream be sorry I bring this up
again but but hope it goes well for your
moving toan can't wait to hear your
stories of moving there
yeah I can't wait either I'm taking my
time to make sure it goes okay but I
also am very
excited um what that thank you for the
super rock rock people have you heard a
game called ark Knight I have heard of
the game I haven't really played it I
played try playing a little bit but
again uh phone games lose my interest
very very very
quickly
um but I really like their fashion I
love I love phone games for their
character design because they can go
crazy with their character design and I
love looking at the
pngs of of like phone game character
characters I love looking at the pngs I
love looking at character designs
they're great uh gameplay wise it's not
I can't really get into it too much um
it's just not my type of thing I've
tried multiple different like phone
games to see if it like uh keeps my
interest it never really does but I I
always try I always try to be like oh I
want to I want to play like cuz you know
it's kind of
fun I like the character collecting part
but then
yeah
Mama how about love and deep space I
deleted that
thing that thing I
would nope I'll delete it it's gone nope
NOP it's bye-bye
[Music]
I can't even I can't even when I scroll
uh through the Tik Tok and if I if I get
a love and deep space video I instantly
swipe I instantly whye I don't want that
on my on my uh uh algorithm
anymore it's just too to I just cringe
every time I cringe every time too
traumatized by it
[Music]
Dan coming from your body Loosely remind
me of characters from that g game which
GRS the magical powers called Art could
see as a Caster
type I guess I could be a Caster
type but by prefit is and game says
otherwise I'm a very in your
face action
type yeah I'm a if anything I'm a Spell
blade type yeah Spell
blade Dex in
[Music]
a random power thank for the super rock
rock please can we get opai mouse pad as
future merch I like the idea of B themed
flat mouse pad but there is no
opai how would that
work How would how how would that
work it just be a normal mouse pad
I not that's not even to dissing myself
it's just facts it would just be a
normal mouse
pad what's the
point dang
it I still s for super rock rock oh
people the all knowing I have one last
request explain your own more okay I
am the gem of human emotions so I was
created from the
crystallization of human emotions so
like all of your emotions so like
happiness sadness jealousy anger rage
all of them
over many many years
formed into
people yes it Formed
into people I was asleep for a long time
and then I woke up and then I existed
but because I existed so
brilliantly um and shined so bright um
people tend to lose their minds around
me especially um greed
um there were many wars fought in in
my behalf fighting over bble yes
people's brains and Sanity I have a
passive debuff um to your brain and
Sanity and stuff and people just tend to
like go crazy and fight over me whenever
I am around um and so because of that
um my my
captors lured me with
cake they lured me with with the jam
cake and I was like oh yummy and then I
got capped that way but now that you
think but now I I'll tell you a little
something that you might not think of do
you really think that I would just be
lured by cake do you really think that I
was just ooh cake I take
it maybe I saw the fight thing that you
know I caused and was
like man maybe it is better that I'm I
get put away maybe I went to jail on my
own valtion because of of the war and
stuff what if the what if the cake was a
lie what if the cake was a lie and maybe
I went to I went
to still voluntarily because I saw the
impact that I had on Humanity and you
know the world wasn't ready for me yet
so I went away yeah I decided to take
myself away like that so I went to
jail
and but then I met aent and decided
hey you know I shouldn't have to hide
myself you know I shouldn't have to
I Want to Be Free too I shouldn't limit
my freedom let's get out of here and aan
help me realize that so we decide prison
break and we broke out of the cell but
yes technically I went to jail because I
my existence just existing is just too
dangerous for people and
then it hasn't happened yet there but
there is a reason why
I keep emotions intact you have never
really seen me mad before not truly you
have not seen me truly extremely sad
before because if that happens and if my
think mob
psycho think think mob cycle if my if my
emotions get too out of control 100%
question question mark question mark
question mark
percent the crystals and emotions within
my body would go out of control
and I would cause catastrophe to the
world and ascended people would appear
and ascended
people
is the emotionless form of me where boom
my emotions are outward not Inward and
anymore bottling up too much and ah be
ascended bble can control the emotions
of everybody not just humans but outer
beings
Gods I can affect
everyone yes that is my lure
[Music]
be
yay I I've said all this before by the
way I've said all
this before but that's a little recap
people and the reason why you are
Pebbles is because again it is too
dangerous
for humans to have their physical form
against me like look at you right now
even though you're Pebbles you still go
crazy sometimes it's for your own safety
so if you if you w in a pebble you
couldn't be anywhere near me so that is
why I give you this form so that way you
guys wi don't fight each other no
fighting don't be crazy
yeah oh that's why you have Pebble
form it's to protect you from me cuz I'm
too dangerous to be around
[Music]
I will manage to
societ uh anyway that's my lore thanks
for your
question
uh what time is it it's been six hours
now what happened okay anyway
um uh yum Dum thank you for super rock
rock good night was going to go bed but
that was
awesome yeah I we all thought we were
going to bed
but we've stalled uh play every thank
you for super rock rock p p thank you
for the super rock rock um
hi people do you think I should get
worlds now or wait for new mon now get
worlds now people are still playing
worlds I still playing worlds
and you know it worlds is
always World Is Timeless world's always
worth it to play um plus you know you
can get a get a feeling of what weapon
you like before rise comes out yeah or
not
rise Wilds yeah
also can you give me a quick Lord of
monst
Hunter they were
people called
fleets uh and then there are monsters
and we fight them
for resources and fashion and we hunt
them we hunt
them for stuff yes
we skin them and huntt them for stuff
sometimes there are elder dragons elder
dragons are are monsters that affect the
environment they are the biggest they
are the biggest threat um they they come
with sometimes cataclysmic change um but
yes we must hunt monsters to hunt and to
survive because it is a ruthless world
out there
yeah Sapphire
star restore balance of
nature what weapon do you imagine for
mocha using dual blades cuz there's two
of them
[Music]
uh there's aown this rock rock hi B I'm
feeling a bit down right now can you
give me her
PO Yosi
Yosi yi
yi yi yi I hope you feel better there
there y Yi you did well today I am proud
of
you good job today you did your best pet
pet pet pet it'll be
okay I'm not slapping
you I'm not smacking you it was a head
whatever you don't appreciate it
uh P thank you for super rock rock uh
congrats on pison Magic love cute
costume so much by the way heard you
might like DMC can you share the L all
the best with your big move there is a
guy his name is Sparta and he is the
king of demons okay and Sparta um fell
in love with the human lady and they had
two sons and they and they were Twins
and their name was Dante and Virgil okay
Spartan died uh some time later but then
so it was only it was only just Mom
Dante and Virgil and then one day um but
demons still didn't like them because
you know you know demons and so so one
day when
umen uh Dante and Virgil and their mom
were hanging out Dante and Virgil got
into a fight and so Virgil went away
into into the
um to the nearby playground um and then
Mundus Mundus the bad demon guy he sent
demons to to assass assassinate the
family okay uh so uh The Virgil was
attacked on the playground and Dante and
mother were attacked in the in the house
okay
um boom Vil was attacked first in the
house or in the in the
playground mom help me Mom Mom why did
Mom not come for me oh Mom Mom oh
because because he was he was in the
playground and the mom and Dante were in
the house um so while R was like ah oh
Mom help me in the playground uh Dante
and Mom were in the house Mom hid Dante
in uh the closet to protect Dante and
then she was like I'm going to go find
Virgil bye I'll stay in there Dante
while the demons attacked but before she
could find Virgil boom demons killed mom
um Virgil came to the house and was on
fire and he was like
H mom didn't find
me because because because Virgil was
able to kill the Demons by himself
because yam helped or whatever I so so
Virgil went back to the house and it was
like and the house was on fire it was
like H mom didn't come for me
only only Dante and then he was like I
don't need anyone anymore so he's like L
by and then he left and that's the
origin of his mommy issues and so so
Dante and Virgil grew up separately um
Dante blah blah blah red grave city um
and Dante started a a uh a thing called
Devil May Cry which is a demon hunting
agency and um he was like ohy this is my
small business now woohoo woohoo Pizza
um oh yeah Dante has dad issues Virgil
is the one with mommy issues Dante is
the one with daddy issues remember that
so they are two totally different
different people um now um and they're
not very close in terms of brothers and
then
um things happened Monday uh
M this was like hey well no DMC 3
happened first all right so DMC 3 like
blah but they haven't twins haven't seen
each other for a while oh now go play
DMC
3 I gave you the backstory now go play
them now now go play now go play the
game also Wei wooho jackpot
[Music]
if you want to know more play DMC 3 and
then one and then four and then five two
is optional I think I've been told but I
have never played two yet maybe I'll
play it one day
uh where' Nero come from um uh when two
people love each other very much they
hold hands but sometimes two people
don't love each other but they hold
hands anyway just for the experience of
holding hands um but they don't want to
take responsibility for it and then
accident happened and then so that's
what happened to Nero and then
uh yes
so
always not hold hands with
people what are we even doing it's like
what's happening right now
[Music]
uh where was I oh okay turtle cill thank
you for the super rock rock Roxy thank
you for the super rock rock tee Hunter
thank you for the super rock rock
um Wan caurus thank you for the super
rock rock uh fav is the crystalization
of human emotions if she's from the war
this would make her a chaos God heresy
well maybe I will be a chaos God
heresy whatever you can't stop
me I don't know what that means yet but
we'll figure it
out um very Bor thank you for super rock
rock I for one welcome I want to
Overlord a standed people thank thank
you
[Music]
wait you're not supposed to want a send
be to appear that would cause that
would ascended B is like people
experiencing extreme trauma that boom
ascended bble
happens yeah that means I would be like
traumatized you don't want that doal
[Music]
but we can fix you can you can you fix
me once I've cracked once I've oh I do
look cooler though that's
true uh C J thank you for a super Rock
blck B I think I'm crazy they locked me
in a room a room with prism no Maho I
listen to it every day from day toight
am I crazy I'm not crazy crazy who's
crazy crazy I was crazy once they locked
me in a in a boulder and blasted prison
naho from day to night crazy I was crazy
once they locked me in a boulder and uh
play Prism naho crazy crazy hours once
they locked me in a in a
boulder and then I came out as a
[Music]
monkey thank you for the super rock rock
let do have a good sleep I'm
trying I'm I am trying
to crazy I was crazy once and then they
locked me in a stream with pebbles and
forc me to talk about
lore because they know I'll talk about
it crazy I was crazy once they locked me
in a room with pebbles and and um
I thank you for super Rock Ro guys thank
you for super Rock Ro hello people I was
wondering how much do you remember about
DMC L okay so there was this tower that
appeared because um uh before the the
mom died she gave Virgil and Dante
necklaces okay that belonged to their
father and both neck you need both
necklaces to to
unlock no go and play the
game play the game dang it play DMC
3 go play it it's
great
um you're G than you for the super rock
rock didn't act thank you for the super
rock rock go to bed I'm
trying heer thank you for the super rock
rock I always end up sking the story of
f FX i v i r r can you tell me the story
and Lord for it here fa think Oh but
before before you have to before we get
into that you have to know that before
that there were 13 Realms all the Realms
were one realm okay all the Realms were
one realm and the everybody every person
is a split being your souls are not
complete because of what happened in the
past and then there was one realm and
you were we were these perfect people
who who had like mask and they had like
big robes and they were like a really
good society and they were able to like
create amazing things like creatures and
stuff and
um what there it's prequel it's prequel
it's prequels okay fine play the game
there was a crystal her she's a Mama
she's a crystal llama
here feel think or
[Music]
whatever s song Thank you for the super
Rock
[Music]
uh I want to ask how much H6 memories
you have but your sleep is important all
so you
are on this planet called rubican and
rubican is pretty dangerous so you have
like these armored Core things to like
um and then there's the world is there's
coral Coral everywhere but Coral is beab
spoiler uh and then the coral goes
inside the main character's body and
then you get a brain wife and a brain
wife is named air and she's in your head
and she's like please help me and please
please help me do the things so we help
her do the things um you could choose
not to help her do the things uh but I
think you should help her do the things
and then there's this big um big beep
beep spoiler beep redacted beep redacted
beep beep beep and then then beep and
then
okay how how why why are you asking me
to explain lore when you're like no
spoilers huh do you want me explain lore
or not you can't say explain lore but
then also be like no spoilers choose one
or the other there's definitely going to
be spoilers it doesn't make
sense
anyway oh is that it can I go am I free
am I
free am I free do can I run away
now oh my gosh I'm free
[Music]
okay run we see tomorrow bye woohoo woo