[Music]
[
Music] [Music]
[Applause] [
Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
[Music  ] I don't
believe,
that's when I wake up,
that bridge that crosses over time,
Shinjuku's
[Music]
Stand up,
pull together the courage,
call love a rule,
smile and hold the hands of the moon
[Music] Deceive the
darkness,
separate it from standing, and
escape the punishment.  Gain their love,
and the passion you hold through will
open up your future.
[
Music] It seems like it's going to change every time. The wounds of the dust that won't go away emerge from the fate engraved in your bloodline. [Music]
Clutch it tightly.
[Music]
[Applause] That's where you'll be
struck by the overflowing power.
[Music]
While hiding the pain that has blurred and the meaning of living through this moment, the
stone in front of us
guides the dawn.
[Music]
In a shrill
Light,
towards the scorching sky,
on a journey where our souls collide,
shaken by sadness.
Save the future
[Music] I'm
leaving this rabbit-like wind and move
forward without fear and without hesitation The
ripples of fate resonate
in my heart
[Music]
Deceive the darkness, dodge the sky, get through the day bus,
win their favor and
penetrate them.  When my
feelings
embrace the future, it's
not hot. The
bond of indelible dust that rises to the surface of the engraved fate.
Close
[Music]
Yes,
Alona, ​​I can see you, I can hear you,
wait for me.
Yes, I'm Akiro Sekotaki Rosenthal, the healing half-elf of Hololive's 1st generation,
Arrow.
So the Akiroze 5th Anniversary Live has begun
[Music]
Today is the
best, coolest live ever, and it's almost to the end,
so make sure to keep an eye on it!
Please tweet a lot at the 5th anniversary live.
Tweet lots of cute screenshots, small videos with cute cutouts, short videos, etc. Aim for the trend.
Trend
1 please. And
here's my buddy who showed up in a flashy way earlier.
This is the American car Aki-chan.
Hey, I've
destroyed the wall behind me, so I'll win consecutive races later.
Okay
. So, it's just the beginning.
Please enjoy it till the end. I
guess it's time to change to Akiro.  I'm going to change my
clothes, so I turned over there.
What the heck? This is the flight parade. It's the same as the idols who came. It's cute. And this hat has a cute hat on it. I
wonder what it is. I'm curious, right?
Okay, let's move on to the next song.The
guests are Fubuki, Matsure, and Mel, who appeared with us earlier.
[Applause]
[Music] A
shining night is
spinning around,
carrying you with the spring breeze, and the
colors of summer are welcoming.The color of
turning autumn is on my back.  If I push
it, I'll
take a step without knowing what I'm talking about, and I'll finally
get here.I'll
definitely show you the wonderful stage I've been walking through the city.I
want to be drawn to the dream-like days where the seasons are running around the world.Fortnite  It
just arrived
[Music] My
heart is filled with colorful
festivals
and I'm pouring out so much happiness I'll ring it and dye it brightly I
've changed the sound of the 12 o'clock bell, but it's never going to
break Let's cast a
spell on it I'll
send you a time that makes my heart flutter and my heart flutters
Follow me, don't move
Even if you know the 5 things to do, you wo
n't be able to dance enough to get involved and make a lot of noise Curve
far beyond the curtain cold
[Music] Let's get
excited Conconkey Festival
Happy 5th anniversary everyone and thank you
Thank you I'm sure if you have the
will to enjoy it  Anyone
can be the main character.
[Music] Let's
play together in this world.
Even if this melody ends, I
won't leave today alone as a memory. I won't go.
[Music] The
seasons run around the world, leading
to dream-like days.
[Music] Let's
continue, the
spotlight
never ends
[Music]
That's why it's Plasmagic Season 2, an original song from the 1st gen.
] I
think you'll understand something if you watch it. It's our
5th anniversary. Yes, it's the 5th anniversary of the 1st generation.
There are a lot of debutants, so I took the opportunity today to
introduce myself and
do some kind of promotion.
I see, I'd like to do that, Matsuri-chan.
Please, it's a
festival.
Well, it's not 3D,
but we're planning a commemorative broadcast on June 3rd,
so even if you have time, please make time and
come see it.
Thank you very much.
Next, Fubuki-chan, I'm
embarrassed to say that greeting, so let's see. We're
planning a little bit of that project on June 23rd, so I
'd be happy if you could look forward to it. It's a hell of a thing.
Thank you.  Please, I
'm looking forward to it.Okay, Mel-chan. This
is Melo Yozora from the matchmaking party's Genius Vampire Hololive 1 season.Mel will be broadcasting a commemorative broadcast on May 13th, and will
be selling archive goods.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to everyone's channel.
Thank you very much.
So, it's not just this hat. Actually, I
have a surprise for everyone.
[Music]
[Music] [Music
] [
Music]
Everyone, let's do a little exercise.  That's not enough.
Basketball: I
'm going to ask you to do a shuttle run now.
Well, since today is a live performance, it's a
rather large gymnasium. If you
look behind me,
there's a huge monitor.
What is that? I wonder if that's a
VTR.  Here we go
[Music]
Thank you for your hard work here.
5th anniversary. 5th
anniversary. That's amazing. Akiraze. Well, I can't believe it. When I debuted, I honestly
didn't think I'd be able to celebrate my 5th anniversary. Now, I guess it's so
amazing that it's almost like a miracle is happening.  I
couldn't do something like this in 3D, and it
was like a dream to me, so I'm
really happy to be able to do it now. You're
not thinking about it, are you? I'm definitely
lying.
This is
right, I'm
twisting my brain.  As I was spinning,
there were things I thought I wanted to do, and
everyone has their own youth,
right?
There was a time when I was involved in club activities that I was passionate about, like playing in both a brass band and a marching band, and that
was Akirose.  I wonder if I was able to develop that kind of youthful spirit,
and that kind of strong spirit of not being able to write without giving up.
Hey,
[music] I
wonder if we can do something together like that.  The
5th anniversary is a big milestone after all,
so I wonder if we can do something
[Music]
Good morning, what kind of work are you doing today?
Yokohama City Kanazawa Industrial Promotion Center
No, where is this
[Music]  I
can hear
[Music]
This
is a marching band team, right?
[Music]
Yes, this is the home of the
marching band team
Yokohama Robins, which is
made up of everyone from junior high school students to working adults. Founded in 1990. Since 2000, they have participated in national competitions for
23 consecutive years and have won numerous performances.  They are a very famous matching band team that has a long history and is in
demand for their collaboration with Masaharu Fukuyama in Kohaku and appearances in GM movies,
and
Aki Rosenthal is also a big fan of the
team.Really,
really, are
you here now?I feel like I
can talk to you.
Hello!
[Music] I'm
very busy and I'm sorry to bother you. My name is
Autumn Rosenthal, and I'm glad you
took the time to talk to me today. I've been
waiting for you, members. Please
gather. We've
all gathered here.
Mr. Aki Rosenthal is here today,
so I would like to say hello. Please be careful.
Hello, hello. Hello
everyone. Hello, everyone. My name is
Aki Rosenthal and I am from Hololive.
There are a lot of different people. By
the way, how many people are there right now? It's
just April change.  We
currently have 130 members, and today we have almost all of them.Thank
you very much.Well, since I have this opportunity, I would
like to ask you a lot of questions, but first, please
tell me what kind of people you are.
Can I have it? Yes, my name is
Ryotaro, and I am in charge of the members of this team.In
a way, I am the leader of this entire band.My name
is Haruna Arai, and I am also the leader of this band.Ah.
I see. Thank you very much. By the way, what instruments are you two playing? Yes, I'm playing this big tuba, a
brass instrument.
Actually, I'm not playing a musical instrument, but it's
called the color guard, which is unique to marching.  I
play the role of a dancer.Actually,
even though I'm Gero, I
used to play color guard for a little while.
[Applause]
Thank you.
By the way, I also played the horn.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you very much, I'd love to see you next time.  I'd
like to have a look around.
There are a lot of members here, so I'd like to ask you something.
Is that okay? Do you
know what Hololive is? Please tell me who you know.
Or rather, the
two leaders.
By the way, can I just ask who this is?
Yes, I'm a fan of Shirakami Fubuki-chan. I'm
Shirogane Noel-chan.
[Music]
By the way, those Akiroze fans are
raising their hands a little bit. It's a little
embarrassing.  I guess it's embarrassing to raise your hand after all.Well,
actually, I had a request for you today.Can I
ask you to listen to my request?I've
always
had a dream, and I've
always loved Matching Band.  However, I've
always been a fan of Yokohama Robbins and have
wanted to perform with them.Therefore, the
5th anniversary of the Autumn Rode will be held, so
it's possible that we could collaborate on a Hololive song.  Yes, let's
do it together. Really
? So, we
decided to collaborate with Yokohama Robbins. I
never thought that the day would come when I would be able to perform with Robbins. I've been practicing hard.  All the
1st generation students will be singing along with me. I
want everyone in your household to see it too.
Everyone at Robbins, let's go and do our best together.
[Music] I
think this is our first attempt.
Well, the
Yokohama Robins gymnasium is
connected to the broadcast from this virtual gymnasium.
I wonder if all the Robins will come? It's been a while since we last saw each other, so today we're going to do a performance collaboration with all the first-year students and Mr. Robins. Thank you, Mr. Robins.  I'd
like to perform with you that Hololive song that was originally arranged for you.Before
that, since I'm using this machine, I want to see the performance that
Mr. Robbins always shows at the park, saying how cool he is.No, it
hurts, it hurts.
So,
can you show us your intelligence and performance as a vice-captain?Yes, I would like you to see it.I'll do
my best.Then I'll get ready.Please
[Music]
That matching band I've seen before is
cool, isn't it?  I'm
aware of it. It must
be cool. Yes, it looks
like it's almost ready, so let me take a look at it.
Yes,
please. I'm
excited. It's cool. It's so cool. It's so big. It's
so cool.
[Music] It
's so
cute.
[Music]  It's a
song I've heard before.
[Music] It's so
cool!
[Music]
[Applause]
The teamis so
beautiful.
Actually, Akiloze also did a little bit of it.
[Music] The
instruments are so cool. I think I'm going to do
this.
[Music]
Wow, that's right.
There are 130 people, so that's a lot
[Music]
Yokohama Robins Special Performance It
was my way
[Music] It
was really great, so I'd
like to talk to the leaders.
But Mr. Arai-san, can I tell you a little bit about it
?
Thank you very much for your wonderful performance. I would like to
ask the other members of the first generation of Hololive for their impressions,
but what do you think, Fubuki-chan?  Yamo, it
was really cool. It
was really good.
Thank you.
[Music]
Well then, Mel-chan played everyone's breathing
movements and it was the best.
Thank you.
Hey, how was
Matsuri-chan? That person with the big tuba instrument is really heavy.
But if you have something that big, you'll be able to
lift Matsuri-chan with ease. I'll do
my best.
Why do I gain weight
? I'll try to
get you to lift it.
Thank you again, everyone. Thank
you. I'd
like to ask you something.  I heard before that you
like the other members of Hololive a little bit,
but I
thought I'd like to confirm it, and then I
started to like Mr. Rice and Akiloze.I
love color guard, so
please continue to support me.  Well then,
what about Echino-san next to me? Of course, I was really impressed. I'm really excited. I do
n't mind if you tell me that you love me
.
I
love you, please, I
love you. Thank you very much.
Yes, I'd like to see a little bit of self-interest, too.
Everyone.  Thank you very much. The
collaboration between Marching Banta and Hololive has finally become a reality. Let's
celebrate our 5th anniversary and sing together.
Everyone at Robbins,
please get ready. I was
able to see the performance, and let me tell you how amazing it was.  I'm
sorry, we just did it together
[Music]
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, that's
me. Well, let's
get ready for our collaborative performance. It
's a little special, but just
like always, smile, be cute, and be energetic.
Please bring super idols to us with love.
[Music] I
wanted to do this with Ha-chan too. I'm
waiting for her to come back.
Okay, everyone, let's do it.
So,
please listen to the Above Bright Parade, a special collaboration with Yokohama Robins.
[Music] It's
shining.
Using the voices calling to each other as a signal, I go looking for someone
[Music]
No matter how many times it starts,
[Music] I
keep talking to myself.  I
just wanted to start, so I ran. A
faraway
light lit up in the dark. It was
a name that was too bright.
It
was a memory that was too kind. I reached out my hand to bring it closer. We were unexpectedly connected. See, now the lost child has become my own.
[Music]
Hey,
you.  I'm
proud to have found this. From here on out, we'll start
frying. [Music] [Music] If you listen to me, I'll scream "Welcome home."
[Music]
Isn't it obvious?
Everyone, everyone, will
shine.
All the regrets and love.
[Music]  ]
Let's dream, let's
fly
If we don't whisper, the light will never end I'll
jump in with you from this
wonderful height From here onwards
[Music]
Frying pan
[Applause]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music]
Thank you
[Music]
[Music]  There are
too many things that can't be helped Every reality
is tough, but if you can sigh
and
stand up from here, something will begin again No matter
where you go, as a country,
let's enjoy ourselves with pride
[Music]
Yo, we
'll change our destiny in general.  Even I
know you
[Music]
It's only when I interrupt the convenience store that it's gone. How much is left of my heart that can be reduced? I don't have to wait until I'm seconds away from tragedy. If I laugh as hard as I can, I'll upgrade to a good day. Let's go, raise my trash face.  Hey,
take the same steps as you are and give birth to the future.
[Music]
Don't blow it away. Even today, when you looked like you can't see me,
you know that you are the only one who can do that.  Right
now, it's still
far away
Even if the scenery changes or dazzles, until I can grasp it with my hands
[Music] [
Music] It's up to
me to change It's
time to start On the river of HAPPY
YOU, you
know
[Music]
Yes, the fate surrounding you
Thank you very much for the special snare drum performance.And
Taiko Tai Atsumare Pan.That's a lot
less people.
[Laughs]
Thank you for such a cool performance.
Yay See you
bye-bye It
was really cool, right? The
5th anniversary live is still going on.
Let's open it up.  I'm going to take it off, so please
wait
for a moment. Okay. Are you ready to get even more excited? Akira's
5th anniversary live. From here on out, we're
going to make it even more exciting. Now, here's the next song.
[Music]
Let's dance.
[Applause] Whatever it is, it's loud.  I
want to be able to do it. A
beautiful romance with hidden feelings.
[Music] I
won't give you my passion like a fruit.
[Music]
Show me your true face. I'll show you
everything I have at the last minute.
[Music] It's a
miracle that I met you.  I do
n't want to spoil it, let's
go back with love
[Music] No matter how
many times you laugh, worry, and get lost, it's a wonderful drama That's how I
explore, feel, and overlap, and get a little closer to you It's
like my actions scream
[Music]  It's an
instinct. I
can't stop the world.
Let's dance for you.
[Music] It's
already
[Music]
[Applause]
My heart is on the edge of its limits,
baby. I
want to give it all to you, just to
you.  I'll give you everything I have,
so let's go back with the history of how I met you
[Music]
Come on, come on, come on, come on, I'm
getting excited, I can't give up, my battery
is going up too. It's
still going on, but you know what the next song will be,
right?
Heroine Ah  Who are you, Dishon?
[Music] I
remember
your kind words. I was so
excited, but I couldn't say it. Instead, I tried to smile. I felt like I was wishing, but that alone
made me jump.
Please, I
misunderstood.
Then, I quietly
sent you a warm gaze in my heart. Please
turn around.  I've been
hoping for a
wide range of auditions.
Will you choose me if I enter?
[Music] I can tell
just by saying good morning that I have a serious personality.
[Music]
Maybe it's time. I'm
looking forward to it.
There are so many dazzling, wonderful people, and even though I'm
not confident, I still fall in
love with them.
365 days a year, it's
getting closer.  I'd like to go at my own pace, but
if I muster up the courage to do a wide audition, you'll be like a
cat.The
moment I met you, you'd be amazing.The moment I met you, everyone told me that this
chance was red, and that we were clinging
tightly to each other.Believing in fate, straight forward, standing tall, and
speaking the words,
your heroine is  Who, I'm sure
your heart
will move. It's
not enough yet, but
choose a wide range of auditions. And I definitely want you to do it someday.
Thank you. I'll love you forever
[Music] [Music] [Music
]
[Music]
[Music] I
can't.  I love rubbing on top,
or something that reminds me of you.
[Music]
Layer
[Applause]
[Music]
What to do with ease
[Applause]
[Music] Be
fashionable so that it's sunny
Just like my brother saw, I'm serious
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] The
living room is next door
[Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
] [
Music]
Hello Akirose 5th Anniversary Live New Strip
Route 5 Thank you for watching this far.
Thank you.
This time it's the 5th anniversary, so it's super special.
It's a collaboration with a marching band,
and there are 5 original songs by Akiroze, including a new song.
Hololive.  I think it was a very special stage that the five of us performed together with the members of ``
Today's
cute screenshots and
cutouts of cute parts. I'm
waiting for you so here it is. I'll
use the hashtag ``Akinose 5th Anniversary Live.''  Please release it to the sea of ​​SNS as much as you can. I'll be
waiting for you. I'll serve your ego.
Thank you very much. Well then,
everyone can't wait. We've
got some goodies this time as well. I've shot an introductory video,
so please take a look at it.
Hello,
Autumn Rosenthal.  Goods commemorating the 5th anniversary of our activities have been
decided to go on sale,
so we would like to give you detailed information on the goods here.First
of all,
here is a big towel written by Akitake Azumi.This is the
Super Sawayaka that has given up and the Rosé squad is marching.  Now, Victor is
super
cute.The size is also
quite large, so you can display it,
or you can use it by covering it with a futon, or you can use it
as a regular cat lap blanket.You can definitely use it.Save
it.  I forgot to display things like that,
but I'd really
appreciate it if you could get them.Next,
today's live theme is Historic
Route 5.This logo acrylic
keychain
has a really stylish design.It
should be a super fashionable item.
I hope they can show it off.By
the way, the key chains with the logo that were released as Hirose 4th anniversary merchandise are
actually in the same style.I think the
combination of the set is really cool.I think it makes it
even more emotional.  I think it's a lot more, so be
sure to get your hands on it.
And here's the next item:
Coin case key chain to prevent marching bands. It's super
cute. It's a
fluffy marching band hat that really captures the energy of this live performance. It looks
like it has feathers on it.  It's a
key chain with a None design
and when you open the zipper, it
becomes a coin case, so it's a
super item that can be used for everyday use, as a decoration, and more.It's
super cute, so be sure to get as many as you can.And I'm
also excited about this live show.  However, a
storage case is now available that is modeled after the snare drum that you practiced so hard on.It
's super cute and has a special Achilles spec snare drum, but
it's also quite large, so I think it's
great for storing small items.  You
can use it at home, you can display it in your store, you
can
use it in your store, you can use it in your band, so I
'd be happy if you could enjoy it in various ways.And I'm planning on
purchasing this full set to commemorate our 5th anniversary.  A postcard written by Akitake Azumi with a
handwritten autograph by Akimataru
and a foil-stamped reproduction message.It
also comes with a bonus voice.It
would be nice to have a bonus.However, the
handwritten signature will be
delivered in a limited quantity this time.  The
full set for those who are not limited to a fee will also come with a bonus voice
and a
foil-stamped signature and message,
so I would be very happy if you could get as many copies
as a souvenir.Thank
you very much.  If
you haven't checked it
yet, please make sure to get it ready now.It's a
5th anniversary commemorative item, so we put a lot of
thought,
thought, and love into preparing it, so
please take care of it.Okay,
so we're going to have a commemorative live.  It
's a really cute item, so definitely, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, definitely,
definitely, definitely, definitely
get it
Check the summary section
Yes, and today is our 5th anniversary,
so it's a special day, so I'm
a little
embarrassed, but I'm
not good at saying my true feelings.  I've written a letter today,
so
can I read it a little for Rosetta? It's
embarrassing, but please
come. It's
definitely been
5 years since I debuted on Hololive,
so it's a little more special than usual.  I
wrote a letter. I
don't know if I can express it well in words,
but I would be happy if you would listen. It's
been 5 years already. I'm
surprised that it's been so long.
[Music] I guess I've
grown a little. As I'm
doing my daily activities, I suddenly
feel sad.
There are times when things get tough, and
when things get tough, it's all
thanks to Rose-tai that I can muster up my courage.
[Music]
You've been by my side ever since we met that day, and now
you, the one who found Akira Hoshi for the first time, are
giving up.  Thank you for meeting me and falling in love with me.
[Music]
Akiloze is
n't good at many things. He's not
good at doing things that stand out in front of people. He's not good at
saying violent, strong words, even if it's a joke, and he's spoiled.  I'm
not good at relying on others, I'm
not good at communication, and I think I'm really
clumsy.And
since it doesn't hurt on my own, I've been
acting strangely strong, trying to make up for it, pretending it's fine, and
living my life with a lot of bravado.  That's
what I often think, and it's been with me ever since I debuted as a vtuber. That's why it's so difficult to love myself.
[Music] I
often think that way.
[Music]
But at times like that, what
always saves me is
[Music]
Words and support from Rose Squad. They
praise me and say that they like the things I don't like, they
acknowledge me, they stay by my side,
I enjoy the time we spend together, and they
make me love myself just a little bit more.
[Music]
So,
thank you as always.
[Music]
I have always wanted to deliver moments that add color to everyone's daily lives.
That has not changed,
and I
want to be by your side for as long as possible.
[Music]  We're celebrating our
5th anniversary and
entering our 6th year.
This past year, we
may not be able to do anything that has suddenly changed.
But
this year, in our 6th year, I
want to embrace my larger-than-life self
and have fun with everyone at Hololive.  I
want to make a lot of time for it.
[Music]
I think I was able to see new scenery again
today. Let's continue to take one step at a time and
see all kinds of scenery.
[Music]
No, I'm going to show you everything, so join me with Aki Rosette's hands.
Let's take a leisurely walk together and have fun
[Music] I don't want to
get bored
[Music] I
have so many different feelings, but I'm
really, really happy to be able to stand in front of everyone like this.
Best wishes for your 6th year.  Please.
So, I'm
not giving up. And to everyone in the five households, and today, tomorrow, and the day after tomorrow, to Rosetta, who will meet Hirose again in the future. Thank you very much for your support. It was a really fun concert, thank you very much. We have to close it for the last time. I'm
so sad, but
I'll let you know a lot of things.
After this live today, I usually
do an after-live event only for Menma,
but today from 10:30 p.m., I'm
going to have a normal YouTube live where I'll talk about my impressions of today and various other things.  That's what I'm thinking, so please
come and have fun.Subscribe to the channel.If
you haven't turned on notifications yet, thank you very much.Thank you very much for the
5th anniversary, and I hope to see you
in the 6th year.Bye-bye [Music
]
[Music]
[  Music]
[Applause]
[
Music] [Music]
[Music] [Music] [
[Music]