foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
donichiwa
[Music]
hey what's up
this is my first time in your room
yeah I hope you like it here it's uh
it's I like it I personally I love the
Aesthetics I mean I feel like the lamp
is like super modern but the rest of the
room gives me like antique a room of of
a British uh luxury
um
Vibes it just needs a better Cuppa
water
[Laughter]
I love it it's a dark blue it's so
relaxing and it gives it such again such
a royal Vibe what kind of blue is this
is that a name for this blue cobalt blue
cobalt blue up like royal blue they
really Royal you just said that because
I influenced you to say that twice
yeah I'm allergic to Cobalt
what yeah what's Cobalt it's like a
metal of some sort
oh
liking metal like like metal like silver
is a silver metal yeah kinda yeah
something like that
yeah
but hopefully there's nothing like that
in this room oh no there's there's
nothing like that I just need a
prolonged exposure
or to actually be a problem yes can I
ask you something yes
when you when you were asked
um crony son we have an offer for you to
do this sponsor stream uh your sponsored
collab part there will be takanashikiana
what was your fault
my thoughts yeah empties what what is
what is was there to think about
oh
no concerning fact
yes there were so many concerns
you're you're fine
bye we should probably tell people as to
what the heck this thing is oh take your
time crony crony you can take your time
take your time we got plenty of time all
right okay okay
slow take it slow okay
I want to say thank you crony for
letting me hear in here and for not
turning down the offer immediately when
you saw that takanasikiara would be your
collab partner no no I'm not doing this
again
no don't worry about it I mean it
happens and at least now I have a you
know if if I if I have a problem or
something you'll you'll give me a free
pass but didn't I already help you with
a problem
when
[Laughter]
I bet you by hand in Universal Studios
with a turkey
[Music]
that was a problem you had you were
hungry and you needed to be fed
thank you thank you for that I I owe you
and then I just got so hungry I just
like took took a leftover leg and I was
just like eating it oh man
good time it did pretty well you didn't
even need my help but I did I did help
you for a while and I felt like
um maybe this will maybe this will
improve her
opinion of me
not not saying that there you know the
whole time actually you didn't make me
feel like I ever did anything wrong
thank you thank you no no I mean it's
not like you like did anything severe
like you know you you murdered my entire
family line or you know nothing severe
like that it's all good it would be
difficult to
oh God okay I'm trying to make this into
a joke because crony you got the crows
family of crows is a murder I wouldn't
murder your murderer or what no I don't
know how to create this joke so I'm
gonna just give you the notes for it he
murdered my murder oh no no I didn't I
wouldn't I wouldn't murder your murder
yeah I can't believe you you killed it
you you really killed it man I killed
the joke didn't I
by explaining it
was such a killer
killer line oh man well okay maybe now
we have created the relaxed atmosphere
yeah yes
that's that's a small talk about murder
yeah
such as such as life
I will I will leave this red text to you
oh okay oh okay
so yes if you guys
have any thoughts all related to this
collab be sure to use the hashtag
holoconnect
and uh
yeah it's cool and if you want to
download the game you can use that QR
code over there that was what I was
trying to mention a few minutes ago yeah
but we gotta take our time otherwise
it's too short man
come on speaking of shorts the hashtag
yeah it's shorter than before but what's
up with something different before now
it's hashtag whole connect
tweet about it because it was too long
now it's short we like it what was the
last time
I forgot maybe maybe hollow life
Valkyrie connect or something oh look
Valkyrie connect something like that it
was just too long yeah too long to
remember
um now it's like you know a short and
concise it's nice yeah so please use it
when you wanna I don't know even post
screenshots of your uh whole life
characters in Valkyrie connect yeah
gotcha pulls
um
[Music]
anything else cronini anything else
hoop who here played the game
how many people
curious
you did you did and you just started oh
just getting ready for the second phase
huh
did you mention the QR code chronini I
didn't okay I was like look at it over
there look at that look at that look at
that
yeah
definitely not a scam
of course it wouldn't be a scam I
wouldn't like lead you to a shady
website yeah
corny crony
geez crony I'm saying it like waffle
anyway okay so shall we move on yes
well well well I the reason I am here
anyway in case like you know some
chronines uh chronicopters corny fans
you know they might not know
why what this Valkyrie connect is all
about because it's the first time they
hear it are you guys is there anybody
who here who is hearing it for the first
time
some so you may not know that previously
me and Ina were the ones from the en
side who were all part of the
collaboration so now I'm here to kind of
help you out I suppose plus they were
really the character designs were really
nice by the way I did take a look oh
thank you yeah but so I I am here but
the reason you are here means something
too I suppose
maybe maybe yeah maybe I don't I don't
know what do I know right there's no
point anymore in hiding it
right yes yes
I guess I'll be in the game too
um following following after you and Ina
well well welcome you're joining and as
we've also seen maybe some of you guys
have seen recently Maddie and Senpai
also did a channel a stream on her
Channel with pekular Senpai announcing
that she will also be joining so that's
already two members that we know of
crony and modern senpai
but uh are you not joining this time no
um you know it was a pleasure for me to
participate last time it was a lot of
fun and they they basically showered us
and gifts as well so
um this time you know I thought somebody
else deserves to receive all this
happiness
what a what a senpai
so yeah
um maybe tell me about it like how you
feeling about joining have you heard
about all the awesome gifts that we got
are you excited for it I'm getting
something like that too maybe
yeah uh I think I think it would be nice
sorry yeah I've been implemented in a
game like that yeah I'm really excited
about the the game part especially like
getting to getting to hear uh
like you know stuff that I voice in the
game is always rewarding so where have
you been uh implemented like with voice
and illustration into a game before
um
um wait am I forgetting something
not
were they laughing
but don't send requests
not here
well
okay I'll shut it down
uh no it's I mean
see you
hmm
I mean a game as pretty as this
um yes probably it's probably my first
time
yeah what an honor yeah
you've been the chosen one you have been
chosen yeah I love God now I'm in gotcha
that's awesome oh let's go you'll be
yeah immortalized in this game for the
future forever and then people can you
know get the game and download it and
then try to get your character and then
they'll be always able to look at you
even when you're not streaming they can
go into the game and they can hear your
voice and all that right maybe not
forever because you know gotcha
night has been around for so long like
it's like this is true yeah they've been
around for a long time yeah you'll be
able to look at it for a long time maybe
not forever but for a long time
hopefully yeah hopefully and they get to
see like you know us like you Anna me
Marie Senpai and everyone else
yeah yeah sorry
but we don't know yet who will be the
other two members but there will be in
total uh four just like last time so
your one for me and then we have Marian
from Japan and we don't know yet but
hopefully soon we will know
[Music]
um I I don't know I I do not know
anything officer I do not know I do not
know officer sauce
no when when when will we know chronis
only time will tell I guess
we will know in May guys
the event starts in May
okay well okay well well when you say it
like that yes no we would know before
that hopefully but the event starts in
May so
at the latest by then yeah it's it's
getting started mate it's gonna be cool
so not too far off wait May is like wait
a second Maya's like in three days or so
oh oh damn oh oh wow wow okay okay then
let's since it's so soon let's talk a
little bit about that Curry connect and
the event itself okay can you bring up
the image please yes of course this
whole change screen
yeah the chat does not work so it's it's
in Black don't worry about it guys
oh you're looking different looking very
different today Chad
let's not worry about that uh look at
this oh
that's pretty okay
[Music]
is a jrpg in a fantasy world with Norris
mythology on mobile devices and also on
Steam if you for some reason feel like
playing it on PC sometimes
and it's ice
next slide thank you yeah so this is the
image of promotional image of the first
collab that we had oh pretty much
exactly one year ago May 2022 uh with
lights Empire not Senpai and India yeah
we became the first home life characters
in the game and the theme back then was
connect your wish and it was very um
different from what people expected
probably
uh what do you mean
well it's good that you asked you ask
crony thank you
we'll remember uh but just uh think
remember normally when a character comes
out in a free-to-play game what are you
gonna have to do usually
um
it's probably spend all my
gotcha
gems orbs yes whichever yes or even real
money who knows but no not for us we
were all free to get back then
oh yo what
very very nice of them wasn't that all
you had to do is play the event and then
finish some of the missions and then you
could get all of the whole life members
oh
so the same thing is probably gonna
apply to me too hey
I think so bro who do you please want to
read out the joke that they put into the
script because I like it I like it
[Music]
don't you not read it don't ignore it
makes sense though can't put a price on
perfection
good one guys
good one I'm in I like that thing wrote
that done that means they did their
research they know that you're perfect
they know that they know the most
important part
yeah the perfection
collab characters for this event are all
free to obtain costume costumes to
change your parents those will be extra
available for purchase
um
so yeah everyone is joining the everyone
who's joining the second time will be
free again so but before we look at
anything of the second uh wave let's
look at some illustrations from the
first collaboration let's check them out
let's go check it out
wow fancy
oh thank you thank you
you don't want that
what do you think about this Eh this is
super fancy and I like how the
illustrations
are matching to how you look yeah
but like a more enhanced uh upgraded RPG
version that's what it feels like to me
yeah and you have like smoke flying
around you know like the fried chicken I
mean fire yeah
Beyblade fire beyblades yeah
y'all very cute and and Ina kept her
tentacles but she became I feel like
generally her dress feels a little bit
more girly to me than her OG hmm it's
cute even more Priestess like
damn her weapon is so cool though look
at that Lance yeah I like her mascot too
yeah the crow yeah
yeah then is it like a friend or
so
um no that that one that one is a
stranger to me I I don't know I don't
know maybe you would be able to
communicate with it if you wanted to
I I probably could but I don't want to
show that on stream it's gonna be a
pretty one-sided
oh that one's pretty cute
accent with an accident
so by looking at that maybe you guys can
get an idea of what's gonna happen to
cronini
it's gonna be a pretty nice wow pretty
cool
oh oh is there a favorite you have among
these
I like I like all of them but since
you're here I have to say it'll be you
uh where I live yeah
but I think I think everyone's really
cute here one thing that I was really
impressed with is that even though it's
not our original artists that through
these the artist who was in charge of
these like tried their best to
impersonate basically the the art style
so that it looks like our original
artist drew it so it makes it really
look like you know it looks like us it
looks 100 like us yeah especially like
pecula and I feel like they they nailed
all of them though yeah and yours yours
too like they they nailed okay Papa okay
Papa yeah yeah the the coloring I think
yeah so please pay attention to that
guys beautiful details everywhere looks
so nice yeah just having a PNG is much
more different than having one in game I
would know
Yeah we actually we didn't only have
pngs yeah we got 3D models as well so
and we we had like you know battle moves
like animations and stuff so let's look
at that too shall we yeah let's go
we played together at the same time so
you'll have to give me a countdown all
right three two one go
[Music]
attack
what is she doing what is she doing
she's talking with carrots I know it's
cute you know what she's what she's
saying
what's she saying
she's saying don't you know how strong I
am because
oh that's so cute
yeah well that's that's that's pretty
good
[Laughter]
of this
ah
um
the thing is I cannot hear
oh we have it
I cannot hear
I've been out in like this oh no
but uh
what a good excuse to have to not do to
put impersonation yeah you also got me
there that's that's part of the reason
look at the others uh yeah let's look at
the next one the purasu I suppose yes
all right uh three
two
one go
oh
ymd
she's really good I like her voice
acting very much
yeah the ymd yes my dark the true
nebulon really comes through in her
phrases that she uses she's saying she's
saying in case you don't hear it
Darkness infinite something something
and then Darkness Infinity oh that
sounds really fun to say yeah
she gets so so passionate about it
you can't take her serious
I'll feel oh I'm in danger she's so cute
how can I be in danger and they had like
you know she has a little logo too
yeah the little symbol that pops up
yeah it's super cool nice implementation
yeah and then we have another one
[Music]
she's releasing them tentacles tentacles
tentacles they look kind of tasty yeah
or like takoyaki yeah
we just talked about you not being able
to eat fried fried dried squid right
yeah maybe you can eat these tentacles
though they still look very squishy and
soft yeah but it's probably still chewy
I can't have chewy food either
okay no tentacles for dinner tonight
oh shame
maybe one day darn it but it's super
nice it's cool yeah you're not looking
hella good and powerful
voice acting is really cute too yeah
because she's cute
well last but not least we have oh he
was truly three two one go
wow it's just fire
yeah
they're feathers yeah and a tabulous
blazing flames
I've been told that my character is like
pretty strong you know
it's oh is it meta
yeah
um I guess so
I'm not gonna let them Nerf me down
she learns
yeah
yeah I really like the special effects I
did a good job at like
implementing all our traits and
personality and our you know typical
element and all that so looks really
cool I really wonder what you will be
getting probably a little sometime
related
[Music]
yet guys I really don't know
who who knows who knows are we gonna get
to see anything animated today
uh that's that's uh well we'll have to
find out yeah
[Laughter]
not yet
likes to tease
they did that with me and Ina too they
like to tease you know step by step
exactly it just makes the waiting so
much more exciting true
so we looked at the art and the
animations and some of the voices of us
from in the game from the previous
collaboration now let me tell you a
little bit more we had this campaign
going on where we could choose like
presents that we wanted uh from the Well
from the company Valkyrie connect like
they would give us the chance to ask for
something that we would really really
want to receive and then it was also
like
um secret gifting between the
collaboration members like I got
something from Ina I got something from
La puraso I got something from pakura
Senpai and then there was also gifting
going on from like the viewers to us
where they gave us like they were like
voting for what to give to us uh and
then we got like 20 smaller gifts from
the viewers additionally as well
um
you want to know about them yeah what'd
you get
um well my
big company and since I knew I I could
get anything pretty much I asked for the
cat's toilet
oh so that's what this is
no no what did you think that was
I I thought it was some sort of like cat
and hotel kind of thing I don't really
know yeah I would like a place to sleep
yeah yeah maybe like maybe like a cat
dryer or something like
I don't know I don't know it doesn't
look like a litter box
Well turns out it actually is so there's
this company that makes really good cat
automated litter boxes Little Robot
thingies and I wanted to get one but I
didn't ship to Austria so with Valkyrie
connect we got like a way around that
and I was able to receive it yeah and my
cats have been using it ever since and I
don't have to scoop their poopity poop
anymore uh that's really a huge blessing
to me like they go in you're really
though your life was like so much like
less work for me because they fill it up
you know and then it turns around
there's sand inside and it turns around
and it like filters the the non not used
sand uh and it keeps on turning and you
know the used Sands will be dropped into
a hole and it leads to the bottom and
then eventually the toilet will tell me
like maybe after
1.5 or two weeks it'll tell me ah it's
full now so all I have to do is like uh
take out the bag that I put underneath
and replace the bag and then I just
throw it the old one away basically how
you're really selling me on this
wait wait crony cat
well in the future this is really useful
Cali actually also got like one of these
the similar ones really yeah it's really
good really useful oh do they do they oh
yeah of course they would happen in
Japan
[Laughter]
yeah I'm so happy with this I thought my
cats would maybe reject it because it
gets a little bit loud when it turns and
it's kind of weird to enter very
different from usual but they accepted
it and it's it's been great yeah it's
kind of surprising like cats are usually
spooked by
anything convenient
yeah like a cucumber like a cucumber
well yeah but they they get spooked by
vacuum cleaners and you know things like
this futuristic litter box they beat it
baby spoon but I'm surprised oh I spoke
to a little bit in the beginning well
that was my big gift and then
um let's look at you have something else
that we can look at yeah uh what else
did you get for the others
uh wait what what's the next image you
have the next image
this is the pecora one oh yeah yeah this
is not from me this is also her big wish
from the company she got a 300 000 Yen
worth of lottery tickets that she also
scratched up in a stream this is like
worth two thousand bucks maybe US dollar
roughly
I think whoa yeah I wonder how much she
cut back I mean at least she didn't
spend anything so she definitely didn't
lose any money but I wonder how much she
made from this one
wow I wanna
I wanna get that
one dude you wouldn't be losing any
money you only have a chance chance to
make money genius right yeah that's
that's really good genius wish from
yeah wow
since you asked like I think I gave what
did I give people a senpai
something carrot related I think and
then
my gift to her was like finger paint
oh
wow
I don't really remember my thoughts
behind it anymore when I chose it but I
didn't this is like a year ago
um and I didn't know her because she was
pretty new still and I didn't know her
well at all like I never really talked
to her at that point I just knew that
she was very like kind of you know so
lucky childish so I thought maybe we
shouldn't like finger
I feel so bad yeah she was like a kid so
yeah and then for Ina what did I get for
your eye because she likes cup noodles I
I asked for her to get like a cup noodle
vending machine
was like uh like a probably a year
supply of cup noodles whoa
oh yeah she's already done like she I
think she was done after a month or two
even though it was a year's supply
whoa
got me I think Gucci sunglasses or so oh
and I'm saying she got me I got her Etc
but like we're not paying for it we're
just deciding what they get right so she
got me those glasses because she thought
that they would be implemented in the
game as a fashion accessory
which also because she thought that made
her choose as her own big wish the
following
the following
this yeah
because she thought that this was gonna
be implemented in the game like kind of
like as a mascot or so for her in the
game she didn't realize that they were
talking about you know something
actually like physical that she would
receive in real life
and she realized too late after she made
the wish and she was like ah but I
already we have like a taco merchandise
plushie merchandise now this is an even
bigger one oh well and then she was like
whatever I guess I I can never have
enough tacos
kind of I kind of want that yeah it's
cute it's like a bean bag right it's
like it's not a bean bag but you could
definitely like just sit on it that's
for sure
oh I actually speaking of bean bag I
think this is probably
her present to me really Bamboozled me I
was really confused about it
um I got a huge free Cedar orange
beanbag
and I don't
want to learn the reasoning behind it
it's so huge when I got it it was like
it could have fit probably
seven uh human bodies adult human bodies
in the Box in it probably human parties
yeah that sounds really sketchy yeah I
wasn't sure how to give you an example
but yeah now the bean bag is just in my
office and my cats sleep on it is huge
it's absolutely huge what did she mean
by this that's exactly what I was
thinking
I don't know what Pickler I was thinking
when you know wow I'm orange because I'm
orange I mean I see the relevance there
but yeah and then I also this one
actually I don't know I guess no I'm
maybe that one came from La Plaza or the
other way around but I got a carrot
scratching uh tree for my cats in the
shape of a carrot no that would make
more sense if it was
maybe it's the other way around maybe
the bean bag was La Progressive it's
pretty new though like carrot
carrot scratching pose yeah I never saw
that before
um it's cute
very cute don't wait do we have another
picture oh yeah we should
um
that's it
how about the next thing is this big
gift oh her wish she wanted to make a
voice acting debut yeah I think we can
see the character
this exactly
that is
character
I got like a million of cat hairs in my
mouth right now
ah speaking of cats it's a cute cat girl
girl yeah and so the character that is
finally coming out is pretty new I guess
they worked on it for a long time
um it's coming out in the game maybe
it's out by now but it must have been
recently
um yeah the character's name is silver
cat Chelsea and she'll be out oh
tomorrow oh that's why we're maybe why
we're doing the stream right now
ah tomorrow yeah
it is so convenient so this character
she thinks very highly of herself it
seems uh and we can actually take a look
at what she looks like and again that's
what we're doing now yeah
and we have voice clips as well of La
puras's voice acting you're listening to
that of course are you gonna be able to
hear it this time I heard them before so
it's all good I have it all registered
in my head I have photographic memory
well when it's convenient uh so let's uh
let's play and uh three two one
she said I'm cool so I don't associate
with just anyone oh oh that's that's
pretty cool Derek
even though she's saying she's cool she
sounded very cute but that was great
voice acting
do you want to hear the second one too
yes yes
countdown
oh it's already been played
hey I need to react to it too okay I'll
listen to it now
[Music]
it really has like such an anime voice
what the hell yeah right
now
hey hey that one was pretty cute just
what did she say in English can you tell
me
saying uh play with me this is an order
oh
cats like
do you think she might say yes my dog
I think you might want to use my my
automatic cat toilet
she's a cat you should ask I don't I
don't think she would fit maybe maybe
her little like cat weapon
thing might but I don't know I don't
know I don't know but actually oh my God
that that cat that golden cat on her
staff
that's so cute what is that what kind of
weapon is that anyway
that that it's like
it's a slingshot and the big cat in the
front that's what she's shooting oh oh
that's so cool
yo hey that's funny I like that I've
never seen like a character in an RPG or
so fight with a slingshot before I think
yeah so cool
that's our original all right the last
last uh voice line let's play that one
too
wait she's like shooting with her pet
yeah I guess so it's kind of a little
maybe it's not even a life anyway maybe
it's just a ball
maybe it's just a ball
maybe maybe okay that would that'd be
that'd be better
three two one go
[Music]
um
please act it out
laughs
I feel like that one's pretty
straightforward
[Music]
um
do you like me
oh no
no no no no no
can you say it in Japanese too
no
yes I don't know
in English you sounded sweeter and then
in in Japanese you sounded more a little
bit oh if you want ARA ARA it's more
like
and then before was that your moment go
away or do you have an even more more
going oh
oh I've been kind of shy just do the
Maui thing
oh
okay okay
I don't know if I can reach it but ah
let's see
[Music]
equal
s
wow yeah you sounded very very adorable
thank you you sounded more adorable no
no no no no no no why are you losing
your confidence your Perfection no I
yeah yeah this is true
yeah I gotta I gotta get a grip yeah
thanks yeah I know yourself I'm pretty
good
yeah isn't he amazing
oh yeah oh there's a there's a skill
video for real videos yeah silver catch
Chelsea oh my God yeah let's take a look
I want to see I didn't look at that yet
let's go right two three two one go
[Applause]
I think I'm pretty sure that thing's
alive
oh yeah is it blinking wait let me look
again
it looks alive
oh but she's using it as like a huge
slingshot that she puts down
nice
oh
cute oh
I want to watch one more time one more
time oh
I'm so cute look at that is so my way
live Lively slink cat so it's supposedly
Lively so is it oh it's just it's Lively
oh yeah Lively sling cat but
does that mean it's alive or is it
simulating life
I do not understand
the
kind of
wording so I'm not sure
Genie yeah awarding oh man
um was just so cute I wonder if she had
any Import in the design too
maybe yeah I'm gonna ask her I love how
the there's like even in her hair braids
there's the the cat like fur pattern on
it
um
so cute everything is cat themed
including the slingshot it's cute oh
apparently this if this stream is held
before that time yeah it is this is the
first time the above clips and video
have been shown anywhere
no exclusive footage oh man whoa whoa
whoa whoa you're welcome
oh my God
World premiere I can't believe I get to
witness this historical moment with you
I was the last one to receive her like
wish from the company I suppose it took
a while to make this but it was
definitely worth it yeah it really paid
off like it looks amazing and um people
have played the collab the first time
will Mary remember that lasts the
darkness she had a everybody has an
element in the game and hers was
actually Earth even though she has
darkness in her name but this character
Chelsea she actually is coming to you
with the dark element
um
I'm being the color like the color
scheme seems to match uh the Plus
like the purple and the moves or like
you know um
it was on purpose yeah
oh yeah maybe maybe
her element was Earth because she likes
us
I was gonna let you say it but you know
yeah then I guess I'll be crony element
you have no idea what that means though
I don't know what that means
[Laughter]
ah
but the art the Earth thing actually I
wonder if that was really their their
like reasoning behind it I I don't know
why they made her Earth she always I
guess on the illustration she sits on
Earth on her like game illustration one
of the ones I don't know she's in she's
an ass person
exactly yes he's from the planet ass
foreign
will have to consider and think hard
about what he wants as a present and the
theme this time is
happiness
so do you know what you want that will
bring you happiness Cronin so like for
the gift yes hmm well I've already
decided uh yeah maybe maybe enough maybe
try taking
um some some guesses as to what it is
[Music]
chat what would crony want does she have
a talk on stream about what she wants
a Lamborghini
uh a hug Subway Gift Card yeah Subway
Gift Card maybe like oh yeah
the powerful blender
what else a life-size crony figure oh
would you want that would you want the
life-size version of figure of yourself
I mean
wouldn't hurt honestly because I already
have a donkey and it was it was gray and
the mouse pen and you know life is great
what happened to the dakimakura
it still is great it's okay it's great
it's still it's still amazing you're
just checking if something happened to
it making sure
now that you like I don't know for
without the window because you weren't
sure which was more perfect you or the
dakimakura and then you were having an
extensional crisis because you couldn't
make up your mind and just threw it out
the window or so I I I hug it I hug it
every day when I go to sleep it's it's
comfy it's nice and my smiling face
greets me yeah oh it's sweet well
honestly I I guess I'll
figure is it wrong
uh it was uh it was a very good guys but
uh it's it's not it's not the the answer
is
um
like you can stop the video probably oh
yeah
okay well uh what I wanted was I wanted
uh like
either three three plane tickets uh to
Cancun maybe or like
oh yeah three times it's like for free
people yeah or
or
um maybe like a resort
in Cancun uh for three people oh some
people they would pay for the
accommodation or for the flight
yeah either either of the two because I
wanted to uh send my parents off to a
nice place
uh what without you
with with me of course okay oh yeah yeah
but that would have been a little bit
too selfless if you got a little amazing
uh I don't I don't know if they'd be
able to uh travel fine uh with just
themselves
since uh yeah they're I know I don't I
don't trust him so I usually tag along
uh whenever they go on trips so but if
it's not enough for three people maybe
just two would be more awesome Mexico
yeah
[Music]
you've not been there before I suppose
um I've been there once and it was
really nice so it was amazing on
pictures how do they keep their Beach so
beautiful right I mean like you know
those places are really really nice like
you've you've been to other tropical
places yeah but this is going on my
bucket list now too yeah I went there
before and I was thinking oh man I wish
I can take my uh parents with me too
someday and yeah that's why I put into
it that's a good idea
[Music]
I like it well all right crony crony
crony
we know you wish now we want to know
what you look like in the game
show me show show okay
well well
give me give me the goods maybe maybe
[Music]
um
no maybe do it
dude do you want to see
do you want to see Maurice
yeah
okay okay
let's look at her first
[Music]
already has been revealed in the recent
stream on Martin's Channel
yeah oh
[Music]
look at that buy pots she with the color
frame and the wings it's I feel like
she's got like a phoenix inspired outfit
is is pretty it's pretty but
yours is yours is pretty nice too you
guys can be like dumos yeah
also she gives me like kind of dancer
Vibes with that skirt like if yeah
dancer class yeah you know what I mean
gives you an Oola kind of vibe
wings
[Music]
cute
um big opening
um
of of the Wings they're very wide open
yeah they are very wide open
um no they are very exposed they're
they're ready to hug you I think
and I like the little
um that little thigh bulging
um yeah that is that is like
um
chef's kiss
true so true crony you get it cultured
it's it's just nice it's just a nice
nice little touch yeah I'm very very
interesting design for modern sand fire
for this collaboration that we're gonna
get to see in the game very soon
so yeah there will be another Japan
member who will join and then and then
we don't know who that is but then
there's also crony so I want to see
crony
okay okay show me crony all right well
uh here it here it is
oh
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yes yes yes uh oh wow
it's pretty yeah I like all the spiky
things
they're like Crystal Crystal Blaze
Crystal
it's like you know Crystal everywhere
talk us fruit is crony what are your
thoughts
I I like I like the you know blade
inspired uh parts and the cape kind of
looks like my veil
yeah yeah yeah it does
yeah and the crystals are just kind of a
nice touch to you know
the whole aesthetic it's nice I like it
it gives it this like warrior RPG Vibe I
really love it so pretty I like the side
cuts of your dress too oh yeah yeah
close up both face please oh and there's
a thigh bulge um
[Music]
can I get a close-up of the face the
face of course oh man that works
she's gonna come back I don't know why
where the heck is she where'd she go
oh there she is
Baker
is it just how big do you want it
[Laughter]
oh
nice there we go
wow I love it
it's so nice is that like one is a sword
but the other thing is like like a
dagger or what
like that thing
it's like the blades that I already have
but crystallized what happened to you
okay
it I was like did your like did you
freeze what happened he's looking at it
and uh
you you you you you you
me yeah yeah
it's really cool oh you got some extra
spikes on your leg damn yeah
like you got some
I know looking pretty sure you're
growing out of your leg
just can't contain it I guess
yeah and the shoes are really nice it's
like ribbon and tape inspired yo
yo I have top two designs from the whole
whole life collab designs top one is you
no I'm not sure I would give number one
I would I wouldn't give number one to me
no no no oh maybe this is even my
favorite crony might be my favorite
the previous ones were awesome too but
this one is like banging absolutely
okay crony so you showed us that thank
you very much thank you uh we we don't
get to see the 3D model right uh no not
yet maybe maybe in the distant future
maybe okay we'll be patient we'll be
waiting please
no no okay don't have to be so patient
okay well then let's go over everything
we talked about today uh number one
second collab will start in may we don't
don't accept that yet I suppose
and another Japan member will join and
Odo crony and one another em member will
join so for a total of four new members
and the characters will be free and you
guys should cheer for joining members in
the game to earn them presents I guess
they're also gonna Implement you know
the other gifting options as well where
the viewers can gift you guys things too
possibly if it goes well yeah and make
them happy
yeah make the make the girls happy they
might have some uh special words that
they'd like to share with you who knows
special words
maybe uh Special recorded lines Special
recorded lines yes
oh
chronic did you record a lot
oh just
just too big just a bit probably as much
as you did did you have fun recording
yeah it was it was it was fun there were
um a lot of things
I don't know if I can save them on
stream that's all but well you know I
thought I thought it was a nice touch it
was very crony yeah oh yeah okay looking
forward to that
very excited to see what the what the
collaboration will bring and really
excited to see who else will be
part of it who could it be who couldn't
be find out hopefully soon yeah oh and
your final thoughts cronini
uh well first of all I'm really excited
that I get to have this opportunity uh
to be
a part of this amazing collaboration
with uh the JP members and
Ina and Kiara
[Music]
and yeah I hope you guys enjoy it yes
and you guys will be able to hear lots
of cronies voice acting yeah and if you
pretty much pull anyone else you can
hear everyone else's amazing lines
[Music]
now time to download the game right yeah
exactly it's right here this thing
capture it if you can
oh nice above me how can I reach it here
you go oh thank you
yeah maybe it's easier for you guys just
scan it with your phone all right
yeah it'll be it'll be easier than than
to just catch it but yeah
this just leads you to the download link
of the game so be sure to get it yeah
yeah
mm-hmm
closing closing words closing words
closing words
I already said
oh oh yes yes the closing words the
goodbyes lead us out of it lead us out
of it okay well
yeah this has been an enjoyable
experience uh looking back on the
previous collabs and yeah
hope to see you all again soon well Seth
cronini thank you thank you for letting
me do this with you as well I hope that
you're gonna have fun with this I hope
you're gonna get all your wishes come
true uh and have fun in Cancun and all
that don't know when you're going but
will be exciting maybe I'll go there too
just let me know the dates and I'll
follow
the more the merrier
yeah alrighty
uh
uh Huawei
him we're gonna say you're normal
goodbye I mean it's a little too early
to say
[Music]
wait you you made your ending greetings
so that you can only really say it if
it's actually evening time
because I'm going to sleep after this oh
hey okay I'll say anything to you
yeah no it works out all right
what do you say uh and in German we say
oh you taught me elf wieders in oh all
your pronunciation is on point me lady
actually
yes
time to learn German oh oh dear that's a
little bit of a steep curve but yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
well today I went out
[Music]
and I said yeah
okay today I wanted to eat a honey
[Music]
so so I went out to get a Connie
and I bought a chroni
and I ate the crony
[Music]
cute okay over cut cut
foreign
[Music]