[Music]
hello
everyone
[Music]
[Laughing]
yeah no intro Legend
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
about wih
try to
you
[Music  ]
there are so many companies that want to
and
okay
[Music]
I think I'm from the please
and and let's
[Music]
hello
introduce me
My name
is from the Academy
nickname
[Music]
[Laughs]
OK
the nickname is
OK then yes
yes yes
nice to meet you this this this this this
I I'll just give you
my CV right away So this is it  I've already
dropped my CV inside.
You can buy it. Yes, it's okay,
the house looks really breathable. Sis, it
says that I'm relaxed, I'm relaxed,
everything is really cool, so I
think  I thought it
would be ugly, but instead it turned out really pretty,
oh, okay, okay, okay, just now I saw this
from Ms. Nih's email. She said she wanted to
go into design,
okay? Oh, I can't see this, too, this was in
2020 until now, it said in modeling, yes,
that's right.
Is there something on the card?  Oh, what's that,
his heart suddenly became interested? I want to
design like that.
I've made several
designs before. But unfortunately the portfolio was
lost, but if I'm not mistaken,
it's there for a while, if not.
Wrong, eh, where is the portfolio that I made
? OK, let's try looking for it first,
Sis, I'll see
what else it is, Manager. uh, there's this furna. This is
one of my portfolios that I
made, eee, where did I make the character design,
eh, maybe it could be eee
help eee preferences yes Yes OK so
that's what I'm really interested in with the
potatoes in that photo right
now huh Nowadays
today's kids Oh what is this potato what is
this potato What does this describe
something I really just want to be a potato yes
because I want to  That's all. Yes, that's right,
so I can get money because being a model
isn't enough, so I have to have
another job, OK, then
what do you do? Because you guys don't have
enough. Is there any hope that if you
have been accepted by us,
for example, how much do you want?
What do you want to be provided? Just say that
you want
strong internet, yes,
strong internet, maybe at least
for money, money for food
and
transportation money, at least hmm, at least 1
million, that's what my expectations
are, eee, the salary  eee above the UMR is like that
oh okay
OK okay that's okay it's okay to be
curious too Why do we
really want to just
want to or want to meet I
want to meet you actually yes
Oh I see yes but it's a shame Ma'am I'm so
Sisi for our design again  now it's
very, very, very,
very and I also see that
maybe there might be another
position at another agency, Ma'am, it's a shame
[Music] I
've been trying, if that's the case, I
'll take the CV and but but  Sis,
I have this one, there's another
proposal, another one, it's
a shame you're not accepted at
our company, we're me, I was one
more, do you want to design the
future with me,
okay, ready, sis, wait a minute, I'll look for
it. This is my pen. This
is my phone number
[  Music]
Thank you sis,
bye bye sis, bye bye
Thank you
[Music]
Oh my God
How come I think my
account is lost,
I think Wait a minute, So
it
looks like it seems
like this is over, we have to
look for another one, we have to try
another one  Okay  okay okay then
Let's try another place
[Laughs]
how is he here let's go
[Applause]
Hi my name is other's
you
with Yes I want to be a police
s is a
bad ghost I want to be a police This is  my
rest to me
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
become Polri Softex
I can cake people
ofoke
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
]
[Laughs]
[Music]
let's go to the other let's let's go to
the other yeah
okay
[Music]
maybe you guys
[Music] [
Laughs]
[Music]
[  Music]
hello hello
[Laughs]
introduce
me
so I want to
register if there is a job vacancy
Is there a job vacancy I
haven't been asked for the name immediately given the
name it's real name
[Music]
my name is Munaroh
I almost immediately refused because
Secret, if you want to register as a Secret
Agent, right? Yes, you have to use a code name. Yes,
my name is Munaroh. Greetings to
meet
me. I have a CV to
introduce myself. Do you
need it or not?
This is Munaroh's real name.
his name is Munaroh, no, no, no, not
munachinobi. Yes, it's just this. I changed my
name many times. I want to be a
secret agent.
Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay,
I'm going to sell this,
right? What do I sell?
[Music]
Is it cardboard? Two cardboard boxes. Yes, the
agent
heard from where we were going to
sell cardboard.
Who knows, because the information agent,
maybe that's not it, then this is the agent.
What's not this, this, this is this agent, this is the
cool agent like on TV, you know?  like
James Bond,
I'm looking at
this CV. You know, for example, I
only need 5 criteria, for example, if I'm
registering to be an agent,
first of all I need
communication skills, right? Well,
I can, I can, I can talk.  how come
communication is okay okay okay I can say like
that like I can this I think there are
real resources here I think Yes I
have Rich skills research ee
like like
Build build a lot of Project by looking
remember Someone Like reasons right
actually But
[Music]
we look at other people's work so that's
used as a reference. Right, right?
Don't be happy, there's still more.
Okay, communication research, what is physical
endurance? Oh, what is physical
endurance? Of course you have to be able to
walk a lot,
manage to do a  catwork with a cat
is one of my strengths.
I can pounce on a cat
[Music]
but it doesn't get tired easily, right?
Unless the cat runs away then it gets tired,
so the job depends on the condition of
the cat.
OK. OK, if that's the case, OK.
Especially in Season making skills.
creating in your own season,
what is this? Always looking for your skills
and then forget about reviews
[Music]
because I have it, I
forget it easily, my brain is just
like that. So  For example, it's
like RAM, if you put one in and one comes out,
but once you put one in
straight away, wow, it can't work
together.
OK, if that's the case, here's the
last question. You said you've
bought
groceries at Combini Japan.
So, what's this disguise? Ah,
I'm wearing it.  I disguised myself so that
Japanese people would get lost so I could. Yes, so
I disguised myself as a Japanese person
speaking in Japanese,
pretending to speak Japanese in combination
[Music]
pretending
Oh well,
it seems like there are a lot of
incidents where it
seems like you almost succeeded but failed,
right? Yes, that's right
[Music]
What do you think?
In my opinion, it
seems like maybe being an agent isn't
suitable, but if you sell meatballs you can do it,
oh
my  There's meatballs. I'm eating. Is
there any job recommendations that
I can go to? I'm tired. I'm
looking at LinkedIn.
In my opinion, if I look at the CV, I
don't think it's necessary. Just stay at home.
Yes, that's fine.  That's it, I'll
try to find it myself, if it's
like that, that's it, thank you,
thank you, Munaroh. Yes,
thank you
[Music]
How come it's so hard to
find? It seems like what
should we do to
match Mona, I
think, but I think it's there.  what's
suitable for Mona?
According to Mosquito's CV,
Mona seems suitable to be a [ __ ], is Mona trying
to go to college?
[Music]
but before that,
what about that? That's
all. That's all.
[Music]
OK,
we're
[Music]
excuse me.  it's
such a mess ah
[Music]
good evening
good evening what's the matter
so I want to ask about
work Is there any work that
I can do
look good
I've seen it yes Here's Indonesian
Advanced that's what that means I
can speak Indonesian fluently Oh
I see
Can I speak English like a
junior high school student?
Oh, I see. That means elementary,
OK,
then I want to hear an introduction
to English.
do whatever
I can  coolies, I can work,
work, don't be a typo.
Oh, I see. That means you already know more or less
what you want to do there, right?
[Music]
I see, I see this, there is experience in
becoming a comedian in the universe,
what does that mean? Yes,
this is just experience becoming then in
the universe so I happen to have a lot of
comedian friends, so I
learn a lot so I I know
certain jokes like that.
Oh I see, so what does that
have to do with working in a
factory, right? Working in a factory, yes,
that's what it means, Uncle. What do you mean by that?  That means, for
example, if the machine doesn't
want to run because it's sad, you can
become a comedian so that the machine can
laugh again and work more
properly. Yes, that's right, so
I
can be enthusiastic. Oh, yes, I can also be
invited to do modeling, too. Yes.
That's right, how is that?
I'm the first time anyone has applied for a
job like you.
Actually,
what is this? Always looking for powder new skills
and then forgetting about the private skills.
What do you mean by that? I can't speak
English. For example, like this.  Well,
I eee want to learn how to make weapons,
right? Well, before that I was a
comedian. Well, so I'm not a
comedian anymore, but I became a
Webtoon maker, like that, because of my skills, then I
lost that, for example. Oh I see.
So that means stay focused on what you're
doing now.  but forgetting what's
past is
good, that's good, I like that. So if
you later, for example, because you've worked
here,
you immediately forget everything
that happened here, so you can't
tell it to other people, that's good, I
like that, that
means you're like that.  Yes, it's very suitable, that's
two points.
I want to look again. Yes, answer. I'll
look again.
Here, I'll see where to get lapis
lazuli. What is lapis lazuli? Yes, this is the
first time I've heard of it. What a coincidence, I'm
running out of lazuli, it's a stone, right? Well
if for example we become blacksmic,
make sure we need a lot of rocks, like that,
iron, gold, like that, right? Well,
I've found layers before.
Oh, I see. So, for example, if you work
here, you can bring lapis lazuli
here.  That's it, that's about it, that's more or less
you can do that, that's right, just bring it Oh, that's it, I like it,
so far I like it, I like it,
I can try
this, Tom includes it. So firstly, you
can make a machine laugh and make the mood
happy again,
secondly, that's it.  you can't be a
spy I don't like
anyone who can be a spy where
I work because you
won't work anymore so
thirdly you can bring a new stone that
I don't even know how many thousands of years
I work here I too  I don't
know, it's really good.
So you want this to work or not  Here,
roughly, how much is the salary?
[Music] The
salary here is
how many items are printed
a day. So if you work and the
results are good, you get more
money, right? What are you saying? What are you, a
hard worker? Yes, you are a hard worker.
No, excuse me, I think I
have a call, thank
you, thank you
[Music]
wait a minute, the interview is
n't actually finished yet. Please, please come
back here first, sir, no,
I don't get paid, what do I do? I work
here,
I will, I can  pay whatever you want
later. Actually,
how much can you ask for? I can give you. Don't worry, don't
be afraid,
but I want to ask the last time.
I saw on Twitter that
Munaho, Nova, has a lot of followers, okay?
I want to refuse because he has
a lot of followers
[Music]
because  here is only for people
who are No Life
but I am No Life how come
I can't accept people who have
a lot of followers thank you please
exit over there
thank you for trying
[Music]
this
working period is like that ah it's really bad really
really bad
Yes  okay then
let's go back first
How come I'm lost
oh here it is
[Music]
Yes never mind it's
really hard to find a job huh guys
how about it
[Music]
so okay then if that's the case Muna wants to
tell you guys something,
right?
This is Muna from  I've been looking for
work, I haven't found anything, I
can't find it, what if Mona sells for
the first time, Mona sells, sells for the first
time, yes, who knows, maybe I can make food
today  That's it, OK, never mind, let's
sell for a while, okay, let's sell first,
is this going to be on the street? This time,
Muna has Wow,
special item voice search anniversary
set complete anniversary,
get stickers from illustrations by
[Music] [
Laughs] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
there's a backpack, there's a kitchen.
What else is there,
wow, there's a lot of rubber matte,
there's also accompaniment, so the accompaniment
will be very similar to the one in this MV,
so you can buy this match
from 11  April 9pm the staff is
9pm and continues until July 24, well
then there will also be a voiceover Age
get to know
but don't laugh if you can
buy it don't laugh Muna
okay okay
wib wib WIB
[Music]
more or less that's it friends
this is crazy, I wonder if
this match can make Monas live for
at least one day Wow, because Wow, it's
really hard to find that job. Fine
fine
key guys
[Music]
I hope I can I can I can see
I can get another
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
]
hello
[Music] [Music
]
Batman
[Music]
[Music  ]
[Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Laughing]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
can I help
me through the speaker I'm sorry, what
can I help you with?  looking for borax
for the bathroom borax for
weed or rice what is it for today I
want to apply for a job
Alah not a customer anyway Ah Tell
Mas Hendrina Sir if I pay it
in half first the debt is scary the more people are
different  every day I'm surprised
[Music]
I want to apply,
look here, here, bring here, bring your CV
Wow, there's a TV, wait a minute, don't read first, don't
read first, OK, there's Oh experience present,
there's candy, OK, There's education too Oh, OK,
OK, OK, OK, indeed
you came  Go to the borax shop. Really
want to be a borax seller, who knows, maybe you
can make something toxic.
Don't think that you
don't know much,
but yes, but I think borax is
interesting, yes,
interesting how?
I don't know what's interesting, I think
what part is interesting
[Music]
the part that can make people die
You might be a cereal killer, how do you
know,
take my disguise off first, OK?
[Music]
Oh my God, you
can do that. So you're not the one
who wears  borax to make slime
but to kill them
yeah maybe more or less
that's how it is
so you really like failing
someone's kidney with borax
more or less that's how
your own lungs are with the
very strong smell of borax maybe you
could say that's how it is  Do your eyes
water when you see borax?
Maybe it's a
coincidence. Wait for me. I want to
ask because there's something odd
about this CV. Is it written
[Music]
Yes, I
can hold a lot of money, but I
lost a lot of money
and I'm not responsible.
I happen to have a place.  sitting specifically for
employees like you,
so I am accepted. It's
true that for every kidney
you lose you get as much as
the minimum wage, but times 8
[Music]
Is this how you will become a
permanent employee?
[Applause]
Say it together first with me Come on
borax okay
thank you Wow thank you
I made a special song because I was
accepted at this borax place oh where
I want to hear it Wow so I
will Premiere the song
will Premiere the song for
everyone's ears
for borax toxicity does it mean
heavy or not  I can't wait to hear it.
When are you going to sing it at 9 o'clock,
wow? Then let's listen,
I want to move straight to
[Music]
thank you.
So who is toxic, you are
borax
[Laughs]
while watching, you can
start working  tomorrow okay
[Music]
what are you up to with the song
[Laughs]
[Music]
we'll show it
so here's
the song, it's
been there since yesterday, mona
mona let the membership know if you're
going to prepare something like that, right? Well, next time
these
lyrics were written by Arina
Epiphania and Arinadi with a song
written by Mas Hari Renaldi
and this will be released tonight on
Spotify on Apple Music
Zero in your day and your place finger
place  yeah
[Music]
and also don't forget to buy the match,
guys, the match is already there, the
mark is already available, you can buy it, you
can buy it anywhere, yeah
[Music]
yeah, yeah,
ready to do this, you know?  no, it's not a fun
fact, it's a fanfect, it's all
the movements, it's not
what it is, it's like that, but it's
the record itself here and so and so it's the same
Sis, Nauru is cleaned up, right?
Wow, that's right  it's true, it's true So you're
dancing like that
all the time
[Laughs]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
how many times have the lyrics been revised
[Music]
[Music  ]
because of borax, yes, because of borax,
then this, yes, for you, you don't
know, this song was made by Teteh
Arina, do you know who Teteh Arina is?
Teteh is the
[Music]
singer at Moka guys
for the song thank you
[Music]
Thank you Thank you
later
[Music]
it's in the description
actually
there's also some
MLM [Music] it's in the instrumental  guys, yes,
whoever is in the description
is the
background voice
[Music]
thank you so much
I'm surprised you usually like it  give
information if you want something else for fun Yes, I
don't want to give information at all because
this is in line with the job registration roleplay route
Yes, it's already included in the script guys It's
already included in the script guys
so the concept is deliberately different on purpose to
surprise
[Music]
yes yes thank you so much  everyone thank
you so much
description and
Please
the song the song
intense Open music spotify
[Musik]
[Music]
don't forget to buy matc guys and
don't forget to play the song Thank
you Thank you Thank you my
[Music]