[Music]
so
kelly's still muting herself ally
kelly can i come out yeah
[Music]
kelly's scared of halloween
here i'm here hello everyone yay my
stream is on ultra low latency now and
i'm very excited hooray
[Music]
big cheers for everyone yay cheers
here we go is the audio fight is
everyone too quiet for you guys or
should i turn them up louder
how's the audio
[Music]
thank you chad for letting me know
anyway ultra low latency
okay so should i explain what we're
doing
yes please please please yep okay
so and now we all have never played this
game before at least
like 10 minutes before this unless we
play the 10 minutes before the stream
however uh i think i have grass wraps
crap grass grass the basics
[Laughter]
so i shall explain and
this is kind of similar to among us
and i didn't play it but coulda said
it's kind of also similar to dead by
daylight
right to me yeah in a way yeah
uh basically we are all children
and and then among us
wink wink is a secret neighbor like a
really old
dude scary dude that's always in the
screenshots from this game
uh but he's also uh shown as a child
at least in the beginning and until he
decides to just uh like show himself
so uh well we are trying to like we're
going into a big big mansion
and uh there's keys hidden up over that
mansion
and we kids try to find it and each kid
by the way has different skills
depending on which kid you choose so the
the old dude eventually will try to stop
us from getting those keys because once
we get all the keys and
open all the locks to a certain door
then
the kids win the game and i have a
feeling that
uh today in today's collab we will never
even once manage to open the door
but that's the spirit
pretty much how the game works oh oh
[\h__\h] oh
i'm on low power mode
well i'll be fine
thank you for reminding me i should plug
in my my key movement
yeah that's yeah i think that's pretty
much the game it's kind of easy
um yeah that will be an impostor
among us wink wink and pasta among us
everybody wink kiera sauce
you're a clown wait wait how are
we're not gonna mute ourselves like we
didn't among us
because we realized it's not maybe maybe
not necessary however in the test rounds
was the imposter and she was very quiet
so
hey maybe act as
[Laughter]
act like a child
is everyone ready to go into the first
round are you ready
you guys keep it at 10 minutes or do you
want
slightly longer oh let's make 15 minutes
if maybe
because i i think we need my time
especially my brain i just woke up
okay ready up i'll find some i'll be the
detective
are you a detective i'm a detective but
today i'm
using my fps skills for good oh
i guess i'll do wow
cool ah kelly you gotta return to the
lobby oh yeah okay here we go um
push the big orange button button
[Music]
mustache i want the mustache too
okay cool
all right i don't how do you use your
flashlight oh yeah
so it's like click like like this all
right
okay we have six keys we have to try to
open these
[Music]
the stairs
wow
[Music]
don't call her apex predator for nothing
hold on press
uh-huh oh no nothing in there huh
yeah how could it be don't throw that
pumpkin at me don't you do it
where are you there's no keys here
all right why don't you guys blame me
okay i
am still relying on you i'll keep an eye
on you
cool okay actually maybe not being a
little is that good
i'm gonna use this one
[Music]
get away from me get away from me get
away from me
[Music]
okay oh
right in the beginning so oh
okay that's drop and then throw as you
click
i'm trying to throw okay you press the
other butt okay oh what's this
hey oh a key i found a key
oh oh oh open the door okay
hold on look creepy here it is oh it
makes you sticky
what are these you know that how do i
know which door it goes to
it's right here right here right here
right here isn't it try it right here
oh wait that's the door in the middle oh
that's her upstairs that's right
upstairs oh they're frozen
get away from me get away from me
[Music]
okay you pressed this button got it nice
but you all knew that all right here we
go
let me hit the key card again oh
i found where the number two key card
goes to oh okay
now i guess you can't really use it
again huh okay oh
well we're opening doors
hello who's there oh who's that it's me
oh kelly hey you know what's going on i
don't know but i'm trying my way to
number two
i found the way to number two so if you
find the number two please let me know
look around
[Music]
what floor are you guys on we're on the
second floor
oh it hurts yeah yeah
he did oh i was on the second floor lads
in front of the uh
in front of the entrance to any of the
other rooms
[Music]
good eyes show it to us your sexy body
wait what huh
there we go oh
[Music]
help that's what i meant
but ultra in the practice rounded it was
also uh watson
who was the only one who's staying alive
and he actually died
yeah i don't know where i'm going i
don't know what i'm doing well where
are you where are you i know don't talk
about where she is
you gotta keep her safe what
[Music]
yeah but i don't know i didn't know you
could get there oh my god wow
nice texture on the roof
wow nope what i'm
mad no she's in the basement
i think it's the what um
they're carrying us as always
i was just impersonating
i can hear you
oh my god
it's creepy just watching you gouda
it's like is she a kid or she is amelia
breaking the game where is she is she in
the roof somewhere like glitching
the game she's glitched into the wall
she's amelia's breaking the game
are you hiding you're in this room
[Laughter]
come
what are you gonna do huh what are you
gonna do you can't get up here
wrestling you can't throw chairs wait
where are you come here
no let me try and turn my chair at you
no
[Music]
oh
you know that's a little
i want to paint my character i want to
be the one who gets the clues
oh i'm going to be the detective
because we need to find those keys
okay return who should i i don't think i
was a very good detective i found one
key
uh but i wasn't really pleased with my
job so let's see
um is there any is there a kid that just
beats the [\h__\h] out of
people the scout you can be one too all
right cool
you get to shoot them oh fps
can i can i hit someone with a baseball
bat yeah
i'm not sure i think so
there's a character with a baseball bat
but i don't know if you can hit anything
you know if you can actually hit the ah
man i wanted to i wanted to hurt that
guy okay well let's try my
flying object yeah oh okay i got you and
that's a counter strike what's the
inventor do what do we do
you make again
stuff
please we want to get into the basement
yes ah
yeah what's our goal exactly yeah
there's there's a door on the map
and then you open the big door with like
the six blocks and then you gotta
we should stick together aside from the
killer of course
yeah let's chill ideally
it's a good idea let's stick together
this time gang up on him
yeah yeah get him dog
so with the scout you only have 10
bullets and you can only
you can only temporarily
uh okay
and how do you uh how do you press what
buttons do you press to shoot
at q and then one oh what's this all
right
q and then mouse yeah got it okay that's
easy enough
for some milk all right guys we're
sticking together right yeah yeah
i don't know i don't know if i trust
anybody anymore i trust gouda
because it's got got to be
uh imposter again neighbors i don't know
[Music]
listen man
oh what's the key card pumpkin it should
go up to the second floor i think
yeah peacock opens down
i also have a keyboard you can open the
other door over here
oh i dropped my flashlight somewhere
you can oh
stairs yet hold on we can go there
whoa there's a coffin looking place
what's in here is that any like oh why
can't we pick up useless items
to throw them i think you can throw them
boys
okay hold on so each key card has wait
no give me that
each key card has a different number
um oh i found it too okay
okay so there's another two in there
who's in there
what uh-oh is that why do i get killed
in everything
where where was that wait where is it
oh it's not chiara it was a cat
oh
i died
i think only like a certain character
can escape
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
you gotta stay hidden
wait wait wait hold on wait
i can build a gun
oh no oh no
people who are good
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait what is that what is the goal now
if you're the last one
you gotta so fast yeah finally
you start all the keys yeah it's kind of
it's kind of
like you can only hold two things at a
time so it's like
yeah well there's the one character that
can hold more than
two items
[Music]
it's okay you can carry the game you can
carry this game
you can win all by yourself i believe
boy
flashlight this is bad
oyo
[Music]
i saw a few flashlights laying around
wait that
cupboard was the one on my photo
oh you have to like speed around this oh
nice yeah yeah yeah
there's keys they're not all up on
that's you guys
you got yours you got this
you gotta find this yeah don't say the
number let's say the number oh sorry you
know we'll find out
whoops yeah i mean you got one number
one
go to door number one good afternoon
number
[Music]
what is this i don't need this oh wait
yeah i do
very creepy oh good one
wait what did i do oh never mind
how do you get on the roof oh wait
[Music]
[Laughter]
you can win
like not like actual key keys you can
find them in different places it doesn't
matter it doesn't have to be like
in a specific spot so wherever you are
you can still find a key for the big
door
huh and there's key cards and there's
keys
key cards are to open more rooms and the
keys are to open that
a big big door that we need i said
it's so intense you know i don't mean to
alarm you but i am now i now i'm
carrying i am with firearms so please
keep your distance
this is a tube i need a one
[Music]
you can't stay in the garage the whole
time girl you can't stay in the garage
the whole time
uh well i found them
get out yeah
i'm good as bad with numbers
[Music]
oh what is this it's the one of the keys
what's the big he do you put it in the
big door that's the main lobby
oh god that's all the way over here
though
uh why did you just give away my
location watson
what what do you mean i didn't do
anything i just said
it goes in the where's my door
hello that's difficult man
that's difficult tina camps in front of
the door
yeah so we i think we if we all stay
together and we have like one person who
does like uh
stunned well is this yeah it can be a
good bait
i can be good a good distraction it's
easy to get lost
that's about all i can do you wanna you
wanna start over since we're not all
here it might be better if we're all
here
yeah yeah hold on wait let me let me go
back to ina though
i wanna test my how do i get to you uh
if you throw
enough items at the killer you can
temporarily kill the killer
ah get him down as well not only the
kids
what if i shoot spam throwing items at
him and the
fling shooting or diamonds oh yeah
you know we'll use the slingshot next
time
i'm gonna do it temporarily
talking about
we can play another round this is a lot
for one person and you guys yeah we
[Music]
is really useful because you kill him
instantly oh
that's op wait i don't have a flash like
that
did you just find the gun that's a
powerful weapon
[Music]
where are you um are you parkour
main lobby where are you what the hell
okay good is going to kill yourself i
died
[Laughter]
oh oh no oh oh you can rest oh okay you
can revive
oh i see there's a little stick missile
oh no she's outside she's outside
i can crawl
[Music]
all right
someone said my screams sound like uh
cleats or
shoes on a basketball court i don't know
how i feel about that
some of them
[Laughter]
[Music]
how do i throw stuff you can press right
click
ow from all the
cabbages no not cabbages yeah
you want this shark you're gonna have to
fight for it
you can still save them yeah yeah yeah
um let's see i like i bet i can throw
pretty well so i'll be
i'll be this good what are the match
rules maybe we can set it to like
because you guys said there is re-five
oh um
what oh there's auto remove on yeah yeah
it's on it's on
but they never revive so
when you get missing i don't think
you're five yeah ah okay okay
okay okay oh wait but one thing one
thing we can do is maybe uh
the number of locks maybe get them down
to five or so
yeah that would be good five five and
yeah and and the character that godot
was playing is pretty op
if anybody wanted to
stuff right yes but you find it's really
easy to find the stuff to build
oh okay i'll be i'll be an adventure kid
then
maybe we should also turn off key cards
so we can go straight to the keys
ah yeah yeah
we'll see how it goes okay i think that
makes it a bit easier for us to win
because other than that i think we were
it was impossible for us to win yeah
wait question if yeah if there's a
neighbor but they're an inventor does
that mean they're
uh i am they can shoot the kids
i'm a killer but i actually don't like
bullet sticks you all in the chat chill
out chill out
now everyone who knows me knows they
don't like guns all right listen
can you turn off the keycard yeah yeah
okay
okay thank you thank you okay
that's kind of a good idea i should've
thought about that before make it easier
to hide then
because we won't be able to see yeah
yeah yeah wait how come chat is saying
in-game voice chat is it because it's
proximity based is that why you guys are
saying that
oh possibly what
ah it is proximity that would be cool
you can try that if you guys want yeah
practicing
uh the closer you are to somebody the
louder they
they are and then the further away they
are you know you can't hear them
i'm sorry i'm sorry i don't know how to
play this game i'm sorry hallie
i don't know what oh you're still
fighting
what's going on here why are you hurting
me
you hurt me yeah i actually threw my
flashlight
i don't know how to play this game how
do i switch objects
what's the button switching one two one
and two
wait okay hold on two oh okay so this is
the blue
what does this do what does it do
it's all sticky and on the ground i'm
gonna leave that alone
come with me yes let's go it's milk yeah
okay wait where did you go okay
i'm gonna stay with you wait what if you
are the what if you are the imposter
truly by the i have a photograph again
of uh where the key might be to oh
where's the switch items oh okay it
should be
a lower lower cupboard not one like this
in a low one like a tv cupboard oh this
is the meeting
yeah hi kelly
money can i get it
where are you why do you want why you
want to see me
what's in sauce
who quiet she's quiet she's so quiet
usually she isn't so quiet yes
yes mine is suspicious
i would say
me yeah
no yeah no yeah
i am she's kind of quiet i'm a kid i'm
just a little innocent
kid oh i see watson hello
eyes on watson see wouldn't i have
attacked you guys already if i was the
jelly
[Laughter]
there was a lot of flashes yeah oh in
case you lose yours i guess
whoa what's going on what's that laugh
i'm scared
i don't like it what why are you guys so
suspicious of me i didn't do anything
that's exactly right exactly
yo there are a bunch of snacks in here
oh that sounds suspicious she's trying
to lure us
hold on hold on hold on a snack are you
talking is it a candy bar
hold on trick or treat
smell my feet what the hell is that what
the hell is that
why i heard a bag there's a walking
pumpkin
there's a clown
it's cali oh yeah
callie she wishes
what are you talking about i didn't do
anything oh god
you guys are stuck you're thinking i'm
suss
um you can also be the clown and the
clown can transform into
it the clown can transform into other
eyes
that's not good it's not great
is
i'm about to die thank you everyone for
being with me it was fun but i'm about
to die goodbye sayonara
i'm working on it
i'm still alive i'm still alive
how many years do i have i have two
probably why are you
so quiet callie why did i move
on
by my own we're so close to death
because i love that
that's it oh i see i see how it is i
don't know how to grab people in this
game
you killed me very good i know i i
pressed a bunch of buttons
basically don't need the key cards we
only need the what is that yeah
money oh that's not money
i'm doing my best
[Music]
make a rendezvous point how about that i
don't know about that
no not um normally i would like to
we need to make a plan
by the way i already got two keys so
eating it with the carrot oh come on
doing she saved the game
i hear some nice music playing
huh
it's real dark i wonder why it's so
black
are you lost kelly no i'm fine
i'm scared mom
who's your mom
why do i hear sounds
[Music]
okay i don't need my i don't need my
flashlight
oh it's sneaky
what is this sound how does it sound
oh it's blowing out what the
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's a shame here why can't i find any
keys
oh do you even lift bro oh the the curl
the curl marks where the key is
oh where who is the grill
do you see the crow in the oh yeah i see
that thing yeah yeah oh
wait then i i guess i found the key
oh i found the key
oh no no
oh boy
[Music]
hillary is not very good at the game
exactly
i think the killers were really bad at
video games that's probably who
that's probably who it is the one that's
the worst
is very bad too because they're always
lost
[Music]
the thing the thing
all right in
you know what are you riding on you're
writing on something on my screen
i am i don't know
what you gonna do with that killer
oh wait
[Music]
what are you carrying kelly is that a
bomb that one maya
okay a good question i don't know what
it is
a super nintendo no no no yeah right
what does it do
let's go we can do this you guys got
this it's only one
yeah only one left what no yeah two more
two more oh okay i forgot i just do the
count
only four minutes left
suddenly intrigued would be nice if i
had a flashlight
well valley
there's like a few places where they're
scattered around oh thank you for the
tip
i appreciate that here we go found one
yes
problem
a nice house it is a huge house there's
a hole in the floor
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
you gotta kill her good luck but can you
kill death
yeah exactly see that's that isn't it
the killer instincts finally come out
let's watch
watch watch watch and when i like like
all right now let's do
the game i'm only a little bad at video
games
okay turn on your in-game audio
[Music]
test test can you hear me
oh my gosh
it doesn't sound too bad
it's part of the experience sounds like
we're talking
to each other
wow oh yeah maybe
[Music]
for oh yeah good idea 15 minutes key
card off
uh all good how do we turn off the names
wait i'm gonna see something yes test
test test
hear me hello
intensity let's see how do we turn off
the names
oh no it doesn't automatically
[Applause]
30 seconds
would like to let us know that they
liked it when discord quality was on
i'm not surprised i'm not surprised okay
we can switch
back it's probably fine it's fine it
doesn't add that much
anyways to the game oh like actually
discord
all right what's in the chat oh wait
what
what what discord's in the chat what
my discord hi this course listen we're
doing this for the experience
a discord like the real discord is in
the chat
i had a check mark next to his name
they say they forgive us
well
is almost ready okay
this is in-game audio yeah this is
however if it's the real one thank you
for blessing us
without can you guys hear me in game
hello
hello hello
i have to restart my name i think hold
on oh
she's restarting the game i'mma is
restarting the game okay
sorry guys i'll i'll fix it i'm pretty
sure i know how to fix it it's just like
the
in-game mic that it uses like steam uses
but i i was able to change the
the chat the the steam chat mic but now
i just have to make sure that the
in-game chat mic is changed but i think
it's in the steam settings
i'm gonna say f i'm still here
i'll be back in i'm just changing the uh
i can't find it it's not under account
family in-game you think it would be
in-game
but this is just overlay interface
no library no downloads no
cloud no music ah
no broadcasting no remote play
no web browser no controller no where is
it
why are you guys saying f
uh you can do it through shift tab okay
okay i'll try it shift tab
controller configuration game groups
workshop
community hub friends settings
here in-game no
[Music]
in-game mic settings i don't see that
i only see broadcast i don't wanna take
too long and voice for chat
now you guys spamming f makes me think
that the the cogwheel on the top right
oh okay that's what i changed it
and okay let's see maybe if i because i
restarted my game after i changed it
hold on i already changed it there then
hello really can you hear me
or good hello i don't know but it's why
is this
yeah the quality sounds about the same
hello
i'm supposed to sound good on discord at
least now when i bought my new
microphone
don't tell me it sounds shitty on
discord like maybe
some like megaphone things
i bought a 400 microphone okay 400 or
500 whatever
you guys can't hear me in games it
sounds like a walkie-talkie
yeah maybe maybe it's my brain
remembering how your old mic sounds
i think that's what it is
[Music]
oh there we go oh my ears in the end
you can always rely on discord always
rely on this course
[Music]
okay i'm ready i'm sorry i don't know
everyone was awakening
you ready yeah oh sorry i'm an idiot
hold on here we're going
i'm with him so loud
burn the audio down oh yeah just turn it
on because i had to turn it up because
everyone's voices are so quiet and now
it's like blasting over yours
i wanna be the imposter i don't wanna be
impossible all right guys i think if we
spread out
[Music]
what do you mean you cover more ground
when you spread out when you look for
keys
can someone show me the way to the roof
oh my god the room's changed oh yeah the
doors changed
a thing that happens in the stream
everything changed
whoa wait what what the what is that
[Music]
no one can show me the way to the root
hey we're looking for keys right just
the key
wait who's quiet watson is suspicious
you guys said that last time
oh can you oh
you know is that you you know can you
hear me yes yes
that's you right okay stay together okay
okay
hey i'm here too i'm normal hi normal oh
money
yeah wait there's only one person in
front of me where's the
[Music]
hi are you normally
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't see anyone oh i don't see anyone
only the killer would have recommended
that we split up
well i said that before right now
i need to be listen
either i'm killing folks or i'm getting
killed that's how it always goes every
game
[Laughter]
in a dedicated relationship with death i
am
yeah why is anyone surprised
okay one key down one key down now
[Music]
i don't know lucky lucky
don't touch me okay
i hear someone say with death you silly
willies
what is that
ah
[Music]
gave it away right in the beginning
though no no
carefully it's just like chiara okay
what does kiara look like
she's the one with the the pig hills is
[Music]
oh
now he's a child again it looks just
like you
[Laughter]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
i got no chance against amelia
i lost
well i was up against the top fps player
out of halloween
amelia what and i can't wait
we both shot at each other oh my god
yes this is really fast yes she has got
to do better
[Music]
wait she's going to say we suck i heard
it coming up
i agree
is there any way to make it less keys
make it easier for you guys
yeah yeah less oh we can get to three
keys do you want the three
yeah but put the time limit to ten
minutes
okay ten minutes three keys no names
i want to be this guy he holds a lot of
things all right you said spread out
because you were
impossible before i knew
[Laughter]
[Music]
i get
uh i guess we are splitting up at least
okay it's only three keys now
money what does the money even do
you can oh
what does the hammer do are you cool i'm
cool
are you cool i'm cool are you cool i'm
i'm cool i'm chilling are you sure yeah
all right i'll go i'll go with you then
this would have been the perfect time
for me to kill you
are you sure i'm sure you're not gonna
you're not gonna i don't like the way
you're saying that homie
i'm not supposed to you guys always
think i was business
what's the man what was that
someone broke a pot
broke a glass did i check that before
don't waste it don't waste your rocks
don't waste your rocks yeah waste your
rocks place your rocks please
he picks you up
why would he be wasting my run wait what
oh god
[Music]
oh
i just know how to play my flashlight's
gone
oh can you make things with it
what this shot's not reload yeah white
beers dude no they don't you only have
10.
where's kiara
i'm useless now i got one
[Music]
i don't have anything
sorry enough's not available right now
please i'll get them next time i'll get
them next time
i think my channel is the official
spectator channel everyone
where couldn't you not be here
please give a message and
[Music]
has marked the key where is that i think
one of us seems to be a detective to
make it easier oh yeah
uh someone should be the detective
that's a good idea
wait i watched that happen no oh my gosh
why don't you do something don't die
[Music]
big
i nice nice why can't i find any keys
who's still alive because i have to be
in inna cali right cali
oh she died never mind oh callie died
no as i said dedicated relationship with
death no one's surprised
it's too bad can i see something i know
how that feels oh what's that
i have a dedicated relationship with
that deaf as well
very dedicated uh-huh i heard
the word upon the street
i have two bananas now yeah what are you
gonna do one
night jump on the floor you slip and die
oh yeah yeah yeah try it
girls huh i am victorious again
i can fight again so much foreign
a certain november
okay you guys don't get who are you who
are you
that must be cool i don't think she's
sorry
wait do i want to run away from her yeah
get away from there
probably running is the best option
nothing nothing don't worry about it
wait the crowd that
doesn't mark the key anymore is it
because i went too far away
possibly i think he spawns yeah if you
get the key
oh
nice god oh no
[Music]
you gotta throw something at him oh wait
i thought i thought i already
threw the key
you dropped it in the garage i'm
cheating he dropped it in the garage
[Music]
wait
oh
i think you know where it is i know
where is it
oh no how many of you are alive
um
okay
[Music]
oh jeez
yeah you're really decent at it one more
time
uh one because it's uh
uh in 15 minutes it's half past
like half an hour before one more
yeah oh yeah one more okay
yeah let's make it one to remember let's
laughs
i thought i meant to leave one person so
they could win i thought there was two
people left
my best
okay because at some point she was
talking as if she was one of us
oh sorry i was looking at characters all
right
see oh cool okay i'll
i'll be adventure kid right
let's go who is it yeah
why is he so creepy i don't get it
perfectly sculpted stash his eyes look
like
perfectly symmetrical
here we go oh different
totally different
[Music]
maybe not because now i have to find my
way around that's no different
it's kiara by the way uh-huh
what huh i never deem imposter
she's smiling when she's talking i can
hear it
let's stay together this time
stay away from me i'm i'm i'm clear
not me really
[Music]
the three of us stick together we can i
can uh shoot whoever the wait
who's that i come in peace
i'm giving you my years ago if you guys
find gears tell me
okay okay stay in the same general area
maybe it'll be okay i'm gonna go
this way i'll follow you waltz in okay
what is this you guys seem safe
yeah where's kiara she's uh somehow
missing out
on the action game
[Music]
just trying to find guns why are you
running away it's definitely chiara
[Music]
[Laughter]
are you cool kiara is that you
no i don't know are you the adventure
kid who's the
me gura oh girl okay cool i i trust you
this is me i'm emilia watson jumping oh
i can jump
you press spacebar to jump just take
that out
kiara's here i don't like this it's too
crowded i'm not here
okay no it's good that it's crowded we
can hit
whoever girl i'm fine i promise you i'm
fine
oh god kiara's here help we all know
all right let's help each other out
[Music]
let's make some guns
come back are you guys outside okay okay
okay she's here she's here she's right
there
i don't even know he's working
away okay come on
okay i'm just giving you a chance
to win this game at least one time
oh my god it's definitely ah i dropped
my flashlight
there we're good to the front to the
front door
see oh maybe we can find stuff to build
um what what is that what is that
where's the music coming from
does anybody need help oh i don't like
it
where are you guys i'm i'm not kiara
i'm amelia okay you're cool
right everybody there's that there's a
thingy in here
oh gears yo the jackpot
okay i'm lost who's following me oh i
can almost
ah man i hope i can make the gun soon
where am i
here
[Laughter]
oh right buddy the secret bookshelf this
is spin
a cute little camper
oh hi people nice
how do we get to you i don't know
where am i oh
i don't have anything to help you
someone was here well we are really high
up i don't know
who else i don't know where i am how do
i get [\h__\h] up
i mean what that's the f button do
f button hey there you guys are i found
you
chiara is camping the main door if you
guys bring stuff we can kill her
there's a crowbar and any gears up here
i wonder
can i make this jump camera
nope that is the answer to that question
wait i can help you
well you can get up by yourself i have a
king i have one too
i think we have enough to win but we
just need to get to the door all right
i'll be bait
i can beat a distraction no stop it
that's not what's happening
uh-oh wait why wait wait wait
what can i do with that look like that
town
[Music]
[Laughter]
but
[Music]
uh she's downstairs somewhere oh she's
right there
no no but she
we're safe here we're safe here you guys
see any beers
i had a lot of gears i wanted to draw if
just have to get back
find any gears you guys hey we're all
alive
i
she went down the stairs okay guys guys
we gotta get to the main door
i don't know i think it's i think she'll
be getting it's the way she went
wait where'd you guys go where'd you
guys go
i want you guys i wish you guys okay
well i don't know what kelly is front
door
how do you distract her okay okay leave
it to me
okay oh okay you're ready
no no no nothing nothing okay
nice nice one more how do i do it scared
let's click left click put your key on
the oh okay
how come how come we have two blue keys
oh is it something
red key and no yellow keys damn it i had
a red [\h__\h]
ah yeah cause i have my writing gonna be
useful and i remember we're gonna die
sort of
oh wait oh wait okay oh wait okay you're
still not back yet
okay yes she died
[Music]
again no no no no no
do we respond
[Music]
oh i think she died somewhere around
here
what you doing callie waiting to be bait
do you have all the keys no kiara's got
the red key
all right
that's just not great news to be honest
[Music]
well i'm ready to fight i'm ready to
brawl
oh my pro mark's the key
who is alive oh we only have a minute
and 45.
all right hey
hey hi
okay we can go out here we can go out
here all right
wait why is it making noise like that
everybody we need to try to
we need to try to get up your stairs
i'll throw this at him
and yeah
[Music]
okay she's still she's still outside
don't tell them
you stalker
all right what's the plan here oh
whoa
nice nice okay nice perfect okay oh do i
need to get the blue okay
no we already used the blue one we gotta
use the yellow one yeah
yellow one yeah i don't think i don't
think we'll be able to get it in time
i don't know yeah there's no way to find
the last key
there's only one key though oh
[Music]
yeah how do you throw oh i see
hold the hold on here
there's two
oh we should get more time when we open
it
she's just waiting
[Applause]
[Music]
i was pretty close to to dying at some
point so
at two points i think
can you hear enjoy yeah i'm here to
smile when you're trying to
deceive us but i i really didn't think
like
i was thinking if i'm gonna be the
imposter i'm definitely gonna
die and this will be the only game that
you're gonna be able to open the door
i did it it's good to be the killer once
your neighbor yay everyone had to do it
yeah i think everyone did one oh yeah oh
nice
that's lucky um
[Music]
definitely definitely yeah that was fun
i wasn't trying to make it yeah the
clown was super fun to play
oh my god the clown clown
[Laughter]
oh yeah basically everyone had a win we
are all winning
yeah yeah winners i'm back it's the
perfect timing to end but cali i think
you have something to announce
i do my new song is premiering in 30
minutes
[Music]
[Applause]
there's a party after that where we're
gonna make drinks i haven't figured out
what we're gonna make yet but i bought a
bunch of stuff and if you guys go on my
channel
uh you can see the ingredients i bought
if you want to buy your own similar
ingredients so we can all make drinks
together and celebrate halloween
you guys how about you guys do you have
any do you have any other announcements
i'm making food
[Applause]
wow how do you get on not ordering
mcdonald's huh
the only announcement i have is i have
the legendary
collab with marin senpai coming up
over so who knows what's going to happen
callie are you jealous if i sleep over
at maddie and senpai's place
for you uh-oh what you want
wait that's your friend i just want to
make it clear we're just friends okay
as are we no no no no no no
nope not last time i checked that's not
what the ouija board says
what what where
[Applause]
[Laughter]
anything else anyone wants to mention
uh i have uh i'm gonna post a video in a
little bit
uh because cali is is uh gonna give you
guys the last piece of candy to the
halloween scavenger hunt puzzle
and i'm gonna post the video after her
stream
on twitter and you guys can see the
final piece
yes thanks for like organizing this
super cute event scavenger hunt yeah
thank you thank you
thanks for watching thanks guys
[Music]
you