[Music]
this
ky ky
I'm in front of I'm behind the
Chad wait
move happy New Year Happy New Year I
mean I already told my viewers happy New
Year many times but for you I know but
they're first time first time this is my
first
stream 2024 let's
go k can you do it
too
oh oh
yeah next to me is my beautiful
beautiful I want to say wife but uh
friend wait what's wrong with wife oh
wife okay my wife okay my wife is in my
room uh she's visiting introduce
yourself way uh hi I am Pia rain from
Whole Life Indonesia generation 2 and
I'm I'm here in B house and the kids in
Fall proof so I think life is good
yeah wait we're looking cute in our
swimsuits
yeah oh in
fre so when we look at each other we
have NOS we look sideways oh my go
sugy sug have you seen snow now there's
no snow right now I mean unless she goes
to the mountains maybe yeah a a bit warm
right now swimsuit in Winter yeah it's
too warm we're feeling hot I know like
she's a fire bir fire phix and all so
it's you know it's it's only natural
that we wear swimsuits in winter you
know that was that's what birds wear
during the winter yeah totally educated
I want to say way is here on an off
collab by the way this is not just the
usual collab she's right next to me yay
wait didn't we say this was didn't we
say I went to your yeah yeah but I might
I got to make it really clear I want to
touch but my hands are so I know I know
Twitchy I it does that hold on let me
see let me
see can we touch
hands touch M touch oh wait touch this
one that's oh your hand you have to be
kind of like in the view of the phone oh
you stupid my hands are not working
maybe try closer to the camera and
slowly move it once it shows up hey hey
hands
move oh I moved a little bit there for a
moment yeah no no no I got I got it's
like hard to figure out know it's like a
oh there it is yeah
yeah there it goes you have to be so
careful it's delicate it's
delicate so I um showed waya around and
I took her to a cafe today with a nice
view it's the cafe I always go to with
everybody yeah do c yeah and then uh
then I took her to special ice skating
place yeah and waya this tell me about
your ice skating experience please okay
tell me so my eye skating experience so
it's it's pretty much you can say it's
my first time actually eye skating I
used to do inline skate me too yeah back
when I was in a little baby egg but it
doesn't count Bas when you were in in
line skating as a child did you also
like pretend that you had like magical
superpowers no
no I just do it normally not everybody's
like
you but anyways it's great so I
basically within the half hour was it
sorry it was like only half hour cuz I
got tired yeah yeah I think we did maybe
even 40 50 40 yeah something like that
so she saw my growth from not being able
to do literally anything yeah she had to
hold like she could she could barely
move like it was really like beginner
beginner beginner yeah if someone had
never ice skate in their whole life
basically that's it basically and then
after 40 minutes you can see how much I
have improved in the beginning she had
to hold on to the rail fence and even
then it was a bit difficult but at the
end she could even like do you know with
with no hands look no hands a little bit
I mean she's still like when it goes a
little bit faster then it's like y y y y
the slow espe cuz like there's a lot of
people there's a lot of traffic yeah
there was a lot of traffic so the cool
thing is that you know the reason why I
took her ice skating is because the
place we went is not just like a normal
typical round ice ring where that you
just go in a circle the whole time no
it's like roads and crossing and like
you go this path this path this path and
it's like like streets of ice and then
sometimes there's like bigger circles
but then you go out into another Street
and that street leads to another Circle
and so on so it's like a I don't know
like a city an ice city right so cool
right and then everything was like with
uh surrounded with like trees that were
like covered in uh Christmas lights and
so on so it's like a really really
special ice skating cream it was fun
though I enjoyed it touch touch oh wait
wait wait it's funky wo wo
wo oh
[Music]
okay Christmas yeah we you read the same
comment
wow you know like certain comments they
just like for a streamer it like just
pops out yeah you have that that one
thing yeah to pop out yeah and then
after the ice skating you know um we
went to have dinner I brought waya to an
Austrian restaurant Austrian experience
yeah but waya already okay she didn't
have schnitzel for dinner
because I met up with her in the
afternoon and I I said like R asked me
oh did you already eat I'm like no
because I'm bringing us to a cafe where
we can eat but if you're really hungry
then maybe just eat like a small quas
because we're going to eat at the cafe
and what does she do she goes out to eat
a whole
schnitzel I thought I wanted the
Austrian experience you didn't tell me
we were going to eat austrians I was
like okay well no but I told you we're
going to the cafe and eat there too so
like and then you go to have like a big
ass lunch with a cute schnitzel
and yeah I was just in a schnitzel mood
it was good it like a ve schnit very
good very good cuz schnitzel comes in
all different shapes and forms and meat
well you ate the best one already let's
go I like it so you didn't need to eat
it for dinner but when it got a h uh H
it was I think it's a deer yeah it's
deer Lo meat but the back the back meat
hen but H I don't know is H really deer
because uh isn't
Deer uh cuz here is what what she had is
the deer with the big
antlers the de that's not a deer I think
male deer yeah the big the big de the
Stag yeah she had a stag stag back meat
uh really thick slice of a filet wow and
then with a rad cab I love rad cabbage
as like a side because so good describe
how that was tasty yeah yes and then
like small Austrian dumplings I thought
it was going to be I didn't that's like
I thought it was potatoes but they're
not really like normally dumplings those
normally they make them out of potatoes
but those were special those were Grease
Grease knodle and I don't know what that
is in uh English together maybe someone
knows in the chat they just said
dumplings in the English menu yeah they
had English menu guys yeah of course
many places have English menus here I
asked for it for way thank you so much
you looks so cute let's
go
so any any ah ah it's kind of like like
corn but corn yeah I think like maybe
like
uh corn made into small small small
small small small grease greasy grease
it's not greasy but in German is grease
I don't know hard to explain grease mice
corn yeah okay so it's moto moto corn
moto moto corn but Pro processed into
delicious food yeah so so I love the red
cabbage yeah me too yeah that's
literally like some kind of like venison
or so with red cabbage that's like
usually they like to make it with like
apples but yours was with with some
berries I think cherries what was it
well something Berry I forgot yeah so
that gives it like a slightly sweet
taste yeah and I was like asking cuz I
already ate snitel and I was like Yo
which one which one's the most a you can
get and then she was like okay this and
this and this but it's pretty austr and
I was like oh I want I want the deer
meat cuz you don't really get deer meat
India that much and then is this
Austrian and she's like yeah I guess
kind of like it's it's not like
specifically uh an Austrian dish but
it's like an Austrian way of combining
these ingredients I would say yeah so
you had a good dinner let me tell you
you had a good like eating H deer
venison Wow Wow Wow Let's go yeah so and
now we're here for a little collab yay y
I met up with the babies i d I gave them
new names one of them yeah I gave them
new names now now chunkers is baby and
smoothie is beauty I mean I do call them
baby a lot so they're probably already
used to that and I bought a a headphone
splitter oh yeah yeah so now we're ready
for collabs yeah yeah
yay and we're going to play Kirby
Superstar a little bit I don't get why
I'm pointing they can't even see it
just just hope that the phone picks it
up sometimes yeah I'm just like I'm just
like pointing downwards and the splitter
oh yeah
sure oh my hand yeah oh yeah oh no no it
censored you yay cute oh my God my hand
stop stop
stop
cute are you taking screenshots guys
this is so
cute all right I you guys recommended
this one I never played it before um
have you played Kirby games before it
just
once do you guys hear it do you hear it
I do hear it
ni is it supposed to sound like
this is it a bit crackly CRA
crackly is it fine confirm in-game menu
select sh W it's so old nice I've never
played this one before wait what what
what was that oh it was an intro I
thought we were like getting started
already oh intro so fast no no no no no
no what can we start how do I uh start
button
ah oh this is so old school this is from
not even N64 this is even before
N64 holy that's called hey is that
the fic con I'm not because in English
it was called something else yeah ficom
what's ficom called in the in English
Sun yes I am SN which one do we play all
of them I guess I don't know is there a
recommended one for multiplayer for
multiplayer isn't gourmet race the one
that became a
meme is this normal I hear crackling
yeah I do hear crackling as okay I think
I fixed
it just by opening that I know it's
magic oh wa why are we looking for the
OBS
screen cuz we can see each other there
too yeah it's cute I think I have I like
looking at myself here chat this is uh
waya chat if you want to look here oh
hello does that help you should we do
dark mode here I can give you dark mode
there you go no crafing for us oh okay
well now it's gone anyway here can you
two player spring I don't know which one
is you guys said I can play this
multiplayer so it better be possible
this is probably that one's probably
multiplayer maybe one of us would
be uh we could try spring Breeze is a
good starter oh okay okay okay let's do
spring hi baby hi
hi hello donky wonky is visiting us for
whatever
reason
hiab think she's curious about the
visitor all can be multiplayer oh
awesome hi baby okay okay then let's
play this it says spring Breeze help all
the food from Dreamland has been stolen
hurry Kirby or everyone will
starve level one star really
easy oh she wants to get oh she flopped
over she wants Way's belly rubs
a a
cute oh my God static electricity from
oh yeah I heard it in my
headphones they're so static these days
I don't know why but yeah you can you
can cuddle more with them later let's
play game you can stay for hours till
3:00 a.m. I don't
mind is this your first time playing yes
yes it is teach us guide
W welcome to do you want to read this
welcome to the beginner show for all you
first time players does yours work if
you press no oh yes okay
nice
wow this is the controller no no that's
not it it's not gray thing with the no
purple buttons no no not purple hey I I
have the same one yay the Splatoon yeah
this is Kirby our
hero and then his face a jolly fell that
doesn't look Jolly cute move kby left
and right by pressing the move kby left
and right ah cute oh not even the d-pad
you want accomplish anything just
sitting there and then what when you see
a door you go in in we go in he looks
like bubblegum push up oh nice nice how
to jump probably this button yeah yeah
but you try to does it work oh no it
doesn't now let's take the food of the
obstacle hot
dog food Resto energy nice I took it
whenever you find food take it there's
food up in the sky Fly up and get it oh
yeah we can fly let's go you guys don't
know Kirby we know Kirby but I mean you
know he looks cute I don't know this old
Kirby take the food by continually
pressing me ah we should fly up there
yeah so just like hold
yeah like
that let's go the fly function when
Kirby's about to fall off okay hopefully
that never
happens where's the Baby Baby Baby Gone
Baby Gone oh oh oh oh we look away
for one
second it's okay to jump over an
enemy and fine but you might want to
defeat them instead why Kirby will
inhale anything get his path yeah's oh
nice per can inhale enemies in Attack by
spitting out same button I
guess same button let's practice
inhale and
spit which why oh bam yeah let's go nice
job this time could be a bit
difficult all right Su oh too too far
there you go you did it jump and out a
St I push B and why oh that's next level
oh oh wow nice wow that's all for the
beginner show okay see and how do we
play together be fine as long as you
remember the things you
practice start playing jump the you like
and have fun cute there he goes goodbye
okay
goodbye hey green green but wait how do
I play with her is she just where when
does she show up when does I show
up when do I show up guys how is this
multiplayer huh where how does eat an
enemy first oh okay oh
who what the are you Aus I don't
know wait
oh W can you fly
too no you have different attacks oh you
can't fly I I I I don't know if I can
move
[Music]
oh oh it's back I probably just had to
be activated work
now how do I move oh no that one
di wait maybe you can just U play with
one of them that should work whichever
is more charged they should be charged
though they were always on the
switch okay okay y wao
fire shees oh
wait isn't that thing on on on uh Animal
[Music]
Crossing ah I double jump instead of fly
beam attack
oh primordial amus yeah this is the
first amus that was ever
[Music]
amongus when to help
the it's too late do we have to just go
through the door I think so oh but
there's more here what's the door is it
like an extra level we
go oh oh what the tomato W I know
that tomato from Super Smash
Brothers I I'm just I'm just here
wa it's a dry Ro Droid how do you say
that from Animal Crossing ow
come back here there was something
there I wanted to okay oh it's
gone okay the Tomato from Super Smash
Brothers yeah I'm I'm sure it comes
originally from this
game oh oh my God it's a duck W
duck cute my can you turn into a duck by
swallowing it uh oh no actually yeah he
doesn't change into anything
huh oh that one looks like oh it fell
off oh the star is already here
byebye let's go
cute I'm just going to tell you to eat
everything no dck KY can we turn into
anything at all you have to eat it and
then you swallow it I think but I only
they only taught me how to spit it out
oh is this a boss fight oh I can't
swallow
ah wait yeah kill him thank you we
almost died oh now I can eat him eat
itat bam
oh wait they're not bosses they're just
everywhere
[Music]
me who what the what the hell that thing
is huge how do I eat that oh I can eat
that too eat the bear let's go so okay
let's go
inside wa carry yeah way is carrying me
with her power Oh no you're strong yeah
I'm just
here oh yay oh he's like you the orange
one there's a
one the thing is like the controls on
this small thing is so difficult I
always accidentally oops sorry I already
went somewhere I was going to look
around but what is this cool music I
always accidentally
KN can I
do oh
yeah cute where going what is this place
there's no it's oh I was like invisible
oh it's the oh hey how dare you oh my
God how do we fight
it oh oh hey I'm going to
die Apple what ah I don't eat these
apples oh
wa wa to thank you you saved us
oh dancing
people hey oh yeah Kirby dances are the
best also you're supposed to like I
don't know when he does the apples you
um you and yeah I thought I could eat
them but then yeah I was wrong oh you
can no I I thought it was food but it
was like a weapon okay oh are we going
to go swim wait can we swim oh
yeah oh oh
I
know I think a help is so nice it's like
three
weapons let's go
inside okay
wa where do we go down oh what
Ste is
that moai moai statue oh and now I took
everything who wait what was that a no
good there was like a fortune in there
in my food
yeah cuz you don't need that much and
now he eats
it oh what there was oh
secret wait is this
edible no W literally have no idea I
have a diving uh mask on diving
equipment
cute I guess it's not diving but
snorkling come here no where does he go
can we no I want to hit the last
can I not get rid of that maybe I can
maybe I oh wa good
job did he
snowman wa you're so much more useful
than me you're ow wait can I can we not
damage this guy oh I guess not I can't
suck him
in and press press down to copy what
[Music]
a what are we doing why are we screaming
because that look at my HP oh my God can
I can I give you my HP no no just kill
everything and save me oh pink castle
wait let me let me uh suck okay I want
to become one of them oh I guess it
doesn't always
work oh no
[Music]
I'm
scared he's shaking his butd come here
come
here
uhoh oh we're so close yeah oh we start
from here we're full speed how
nice hey how do I share the health to
her you can I don't think you can ow ow
what what he can eat me
no can I jump on him
no what H oh St oh we just leave okay
yeah yeah we finish it I
guess is only when
we oh but now you needed it more it's
all right it's all right if if if you
die yay
oh oh wow that's cool I like
that
you you take care of the bottom
one okay oh wait
there W oh it has a
[Music]
bow yes sword good choice yeah sword I'm
powerful I'm almost like link um
transformation oh y
okay what do you you don't you don't
know the Coro you dance differently than
me yeah I'm just like doing My Own Thing
freyle freestyle let's go nobody told
waya the Coro it's all right it's kind
of like a surprise birthday oh wait I
want that
one no no oh wait oh I couldn't suck him
in because I already am something else
all right okay that's fine can I get rid
of my current transformation guys ow are
you okay oh my god
there I
help uh maybe oh
sh you can how how this it oh my God oh
my God I oh
my oh I got rid of it can I
not okay we good inside
yes press a to drop a power okay I I
seemingly have dropped it oh oh let
me get the wizard then okay if I
can never
mind I touched
him
okay you want the wizard right yeah
that's right there you go and then down
let's
go
W
magic magic oh nice
okay oh
oh I'm stuck come over here wa
o nice select drops the power a toes it
as a hat that Raina can collect a also
turns R back into a hat if K has no
power wait look at the chicken the
chicken wait oh there
enemies can I oh Magic in the air okay
here take the take the weird food there
nice what what
happened
hello oh what Y what what
[Music]
the I of Doom oh it sends out more W
these W
do goodness
they
yay the mother of all of wled do your
mother I always like silly
duck really maybe that's good you're
like ready to duck from the
danger what is this
m really what is this the water nothing
here oh ice
[Music]
cream yummy
nice this is really
cute man Nintendo is such a genius hello
where am I hello where am I you need to
see it Nintendo is such a genius for
like bringing oh this game what
happened where I'm eating why am I to
the Nintendo switch let's just leave
let's just leave leave leave leave leave
you're poppy Bros Junior now I don't
know why but you're something else now
good luck you're can throw bombs is you
right you're you're you're
controlling I'm ducking again oh I'm
scared my
[Music]
HP
yumy yumy okay okay let me try to
uh
yeah
oo
random way
screams what the was that what the
the the bear again and some Ras or
whatever that
is I'm spawn camping is he dead I think
the I think he's dead okay let's
go I'm just
uh wait do you want to tell them what
your what you told me about Austria like
what your impression is oh I think
Austria has clear air
yeah you were like excited about excited
about the Blue
Sky cuz it's so clean there's no
pollution I mean I think there's
pollution to a certain extent oh
hell oh
[Applause]
bro W you killed him nice nice I think
this potion to a certain extent but like
yeah definitely differently from like
Indonesia there's no traffic jam I
didn't see traffic jam there definitely
is sometimes but
yeah and you were happy about the
weather cuz waya is on a Europe trip
right now and all the other places where
shitty weather right the bar is
literally in hell because oh that's so
good for Austria oh man they got blue
guys and to tell me about the tap water
the tap water yeah like you can drink
tap water in Austria one of the cleanest
tap Waters in the
world I love tap water ow I become you
oh no I'm magician again okay we got to
go for the door no who wa with the
explosive spicy bombs
exposive yeah oh wait I know this guy yo
this freaking guy he looks like a Donkey
Kong guy
eat my magic I protect way you don't
touch
her wait did I say Donkey Kong I mean
donkey donkey yeah did I say he looks
like a Donkey Kong guy I mean he looks
like the donkey H
[Music]
guy yeah let's go yay that was
nice and then you were saying about how
the T water is even more delicious than
the bottled water in Austria I prefer
the tap water over the bottled
drinks speaking of t water oh wait that
was the end of spring Breeze there's
credits are the games so short I mean
I'm fine with that but is that it
there's more smaller games too but oh
okay okay it's like a collection of
games wait we beat
[Music]
it oh wow okay it's very short so
they're like minii games and then we can
play the next one okay yo I'm drinking
Austrian tap water y so how much would
you rate
it I would rate it delicious M thank you
as an Austrian representative I am very
happy very delighted yes mhm second game
beat it this year oh does it count cuz
my viewers they like make a list of
games that I beat it oh like played
until the end and and games I didn't yes
let's go wait what button do I press
select next he says next oh I don't know
I'll press the start button oh yeah okay
for R bless you bless you thank
you um this one next I guess for race
race orward to the finish gobling up the
tasty T you can find level question mark
okay is that that's scary that's kind of
scary that's it could be really
difficult we'll
see oh Dino blades next they said okay
no problem one's just one player wait oh
wait I want to uh yes but I want to go
back to the main menu oh can I go to the
yeah yeah yeah
no what oh we're playing together no
we're not oh I'm racing against this guy
oh I already lost but what is he doing
where is
he why does he get
points because he said 19 points further
than you oh oh you got food he
got yeah he got like two food ah oh yeah
right it's a gourmet race
okay wait for me
dude no no no
no no even the Maxi
tomato well I'm on the diet yeah is
still a checkpoint it's
fine wait do you want to do you want to
check run run run run I gave the
controler to her go go go go go eat all
the food
wi run why is he why is she so slow Run
for the Austrian snitel don't forget the
lingo Berry Jam I don't
know I don't e
forget the food you have to become first
first like in front of him oh wait oh
yes he can't reach
those go go go go what is the trick to
this I have the what the hell oh d-pad
faster oh my God how do I jump yeah cuz
we're we don't have oh there's a
d-pad py py beon oh my God go go go you
you pretty fast oh wait you you dashed
how did you do that hold 1744 what the
how did he get so much more is this
[Music]
jump no cuz like guys I was using the I
was using the mini controller and
there's no why it goes
down my my mini controller didn't have a
uh oh my mini controller did have a uh
what you call that
[Music]
have a that's why I always St that's I'm
moving your
hand what how do I I don't know I'm
Kirby let's go Kirby
goby you currently have more points than
him really 16 versus 13
where is he oh there was tomato
there go in it the drink
yeah where is
he
oh I don't even know the
way why am I she just ignores the
tomato
[Music]
a okay okay okay okay oh the total the
total it's okay guys r a
d he oh he's like pulling the cheek
Cur do they hate each other I don't know
maybe man okay let me get out of here
let get the other game yeah let's get
the other game okay okay which one did
they say um I forgot Dino blade din
blade difficulty
free and Dino blade is destroying all
the crops oh it's a character she must
be stopped Master different abilities
and defeat her okay okay oh it's just
like okay what oh my God why is it split
into two should we explain copy ah is
that the what's copy the popping the
like sucking them in and becoming
them guess I already know that have you
mastered inhaling and flying let's learn
how to use the copy function you'll
teach that to me now enemies attack in
various ways this enem is called W yeah
that's wa oh yeah when Kirby inhales an
enemy push a to
swallow a a also works
oh you can use the energy beam Vibe what
is this why it's one of my favorite
chocolates you can try it's called
Kinder country let's go it's so good
chocolate in Austria yeah more likely
than you
think oh spit out some M nasty Nast yo I
like this one very on brand of you Stone
turn into a stone ah yeah I love that
Super Smash Brother ah this this one
yeah oo let's go oh I love this I think
I've had this before but I I forgot
where are when but this it's so good it
has like
puffy rice yeah the rice puffs or
something I yeah oh Puffy cereal it's
cereal
inside yeah there's more two yes two
people can play at the same time wow I
know that's what we've been doing when
Kirby's wearing an ability cap push a
and you'll give birth to me okay cute a
second character will be this is I I've
already been your mommy to today because
I taught you how to ice skate and you
were holding on to me and I was saving
you when you're about to fall sorry guys
you can see I'm e invisible chocolate oh
yeah invisible chocolate it's it's real
it's real it's real
though yummy here more techniques throw
off the cap uh-huh oh and the helper
will put it on Ah that's why you changed
uhhuh push a one more time at the helper
will become the ability cab
wa you just like you just like sna me
out of existence yeah I don't want to do
that you can copy the build again and
then yeah BF you again when the helpers
press and push any button on the second
controller yes the helper will then be
controlled for the second player it's a
little confusing at first but give it a
try and you catch yeah no problem thank
you Pur with your friends double yay
that's so
cool H you can do that to wa to share HP
and spit ah okay I I I'm not sure if I
will understand how to do it to dash
push twice yeah earlier oh twice yeah oh
it works with a joystick too to slide
push down and be
together they didn't teach us for that
yeah to guard push L or R it can reduce
blah blah blah for more details please
refer to the instruction manual I don't
have a manual now let's play dblade oh
dear they taught us so many new things I
know a good slide slide attack and
Master Copy and help she just called the
d-pad the Jo yeah cuz I'm playing with
the joystick I I mostly use the joystick
I'm playing with the half controller
like like it's not even like a complete
set like I don't know why it doesn't
work together it was acting weird but it
should work are we going in here first
May
battery okay uh I first have to like
suck something yeah and then I can
you oh
uh hey and
then oh what did I do it wrong uh you um
you became the oh there you are you're
sir kibble sir kibble do you have some
kibble for my
cats a I want actually to take hisn
with
me do they respawn I think previously I
saw them respawning but let's just go
next and no it's good well if you want a
different one let me know it's okay wait
wait what is my no I'm
nothing do I not have a hold weapon like
oh you can be magic gun oh no that was
not the right one I guess oh that was me
this one you want to beat that one
whatever you say you're going to be it
you're back to what'll
do y I have
umbrella Y what what does this do I
guess it's oh it's like a weapon like
this oh that's cool though I like that
it's like a m
weapon
you oh my God I always accidentally
ducked
controller it's
okay we're so silly we have such silly
weapons oh what that's so cute dancing
on it oh can I can I run out of air or
is the best game
of doesn't seem like there's a limit
press plus to review your move
set Splash drill or toss your enemies to
the sky ah so these are the the current
transformation skills along
there's a dash Y and down oh I need to
try
that oh wait was that it was I dashing
oh I think I
think
okay there's a lot of stuff
here we can't kill that okay oh yay
thank
you there can be only one
[Music]
do you want a new power you have to let
me know like oh I want to be this one
good I'm good I'm good I like this one
so basic the only other thing that you
that I like is the bomb
guy we'll find you
one or maybe something completely new I
wonder how many choices there are oh we
can't destroy that oh nice nice way I
didn't even
wait
wait I want the bomb kid the bomb can
you SW oh this is not even the bomb kid
okay I'll try uh S I killed it by
accident wait what how do I oh I have to
get rid of mine first maybe wait how
does it work again I don't even know I'm
I'm fing this
guy what about that one though the
fly what what did I just do how do I a
there we
go come back yeah it's okay just take
there's no bombs
[Music]
here nice oh I I gave this one to you
have
fun okay I guess I can try The Dashing
one dashing
skill I I I can't it's so hard I don't
have d-pad uh oh it doesn't show it
because I don't currently have
the the transformation why is there two
doors can I be this one no he goes away
a he's
hereo is it just that I'm unlucky or
does he not give me a transformation I
wonder double tap the analog stick
for for dashing right yeah but it's
hard W there the sword guy is down there
or like different kind of the sword
throwing guy I can go what's that what
the is
that dead
now how can I go down yeah I don't think
we can go
down have to kill them from a
distance
[Music]
oh how
to activate bomb
oh just hit it oh nice let's go
down
wa we're in the
underground the
underground I with waa today I'm I
literally made her use every single type
of public transport we oh yeah we Ed the
Trap we used the bus and we used the
underground train and an Uber the bird
love the bird the bear that's called the
bear the bear the bird
you need some you have full HP wait wait
I
can't
stupid okay no bullets no no no boats
sadly oh the bear is
back the flower looks so funky come
wa I always I'm like
the wa you need a new transformation you
don't seem to be doing so well with your
parasol No I need a new controller
that's what I
need skill
[Music]
issue down or oh is that where how we
came from
here we should not go back we must
proceed deeper and deeper
deep and now maybe
[Music]
up oh we going down I think so this is
so cute why haven't not played this
before Oh for you I know what it is
tomato maxic tomato oh
BS what is this potato where that one
not charge
bam
wa oh
oh nice
e was that a metanite n no
[Music]
way magic okay let's go it's a baked
potato now yay M I love baked
potatoes oh and after the oh goal what
do you mean what that's the goal
oh
what I don't get it what's that mean I
shot you and this is a score an extra
score I guess I don't know I don't know
either
yay are we proceed to the next
one
M what is this Peach's
castle let's look for some new powers we
shouldn't get too used to the same ones
we need more variety we're variety
streamers for real you can give away
that one you have for me oh oh yeah wait
what the that was
interesting uh oh here take the magic
wand uh how do I give it to you
again oh you you unbirth me first ah oh
wait I threw it at you okay yeah now you
can do the magic again okay
okay un B
you
oh oh oh what the give me I he he
resists oh ah Fork Fork Fork it
is oh it didn't work what about
you please give me no it doesn't always
work sometimes I
fail oh hey
that yay
sword is there some more here right side
left side oh okay nothing here oh wait I
I wait uh take my take my uh my SW
nice go and I'll try this ah I can't
reach him I'll get a different one wait
how do I do the attack that's like the
same as you I'll just press it like a
lot of times I
think
yeah
mushroom can I become mushroom w by the
bump guy got the bump
guy
yay now we're at two different ones oh
my
God he froze so
far oh hold on there's a
b how do we get
there magic guys so how do I how do I
aim the bomb like froze it way over why
is there a the why is there a pineapple
pineapple
wait I don't like this all it does is
throw the bomb Oh you want to with me no
I'll take this one ah wait
[Music]
ah oh
sorry but you kind of like this one
right I like this one oh okay I'm
surprised you like it oh nice nice
[Music]
Hallelujah Yahoo there can only be one
bomb thrower you have a talent for it I
don't know what I'm doing with it stream
pineapple oh the map is moving you have
to be
[Music]
fast whose Castle is this guys is there
some lore behind it it's ours now what I
have been
undone oh ah that's my power they took
it from me no I have't
done oh yeah wait isn't the pineapple
and be Sor sorry um how can I share food
with you what what do you want to do
share food oh you don't have to don't
worry I'll
survive oh we needed that okay did it
this Castle oh
ow they don't even wait a second after
we spawn they immediately attack
us I'm just throwing stuff
what a lot
[Music]
of careful the duck wao nice
bro yo we're so we're so in
danger I realized my sword has a quite a
big reach so I'm going to try to stay
further behind oh my God the stupid what
are you doing no CU like whenever I do
this it's like it's
duck
o the chicken
exploded no no what no no wait how do I
stop you from dying oh no I'm dead wait
uh how do I burth you again um um like
this now you blade KN what is this thing
here you become the super wheel guy ah
I'm a
wheel Y and I even have a cool ass cap
on my head we wee wee
you're so wheel now no you died no I
died again I'll I'll bring you
back wait what oh I threw uh yeah okay
uh wait I can't take it and those are
spikes um which one can we get
oh you can
okay oh you became wheel
oh
got
what I didn't know you could do that oh
my God there's so many enemies do we get
like points for killing many enemies no
don't really but we're Unstoppable oh my
god oh that's a cool looking bike too oh
like we can't
fly you can ride me okay okay how do I
do that again let's go did I just jump
on you oh yeah let's go oh do you have
to ride oh yeah are you controlling it I
thought I was controlling it maybe it's
different
now how can I Dash if I have this really
shitty no
dash it's different before I I think I
was controlling let me try to get the
chicken can
I no why not why not
not it it is because it's meant to be
guys I am a phoenix I cannot be a
chicken it's fake what is this guy let
me get
off oh no oh my God no don't die what
you became him Bonkers his name is
Bonkers are you controlling him right
now I don't know the pink one because
like it are you are you moving him
you're doing it waa you're him okay I
guess I am you are how did you become
him I didn't even give you that skill
Bonkers that's my that's my raccoon is
your raccoon no
chunkers not no notun totally not
chunkers take ah take the food take the
food's one more oh did we did we kiss
yes I gave you look like CPR but for
take the peach what for for your health
it's really low oh you can't see it cuz
your phone I can't
see that's not good oh what were we
saying I forgot what we were
saying what what you destroyed the whole
thing yes oh my God it was so Pretty in
Pink why would you do that I just like
watching things being destroyed
go ah we both have
to like yeah ideally would
full now we get it we we ignore the S I
think I saw it at the top right but then
when we flew a little bit back up I
couldn't see it anymore so I was like H
I guess I didn't see anything okay okay
next
stage oh why are you such a powerful
big I don't know strong
dude how did that happen let me oh let
me try to get this ow
ow no it died oh okay is this the bomb
ah where am I oh I'm still back there
come
here there go how can you fly like
that doesn't fit the
character waa you have like a Donkey
Kong Hammer maybe you're related Donkey
Kong you seem as
powerful wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait don't don't okay yeah
[Music]
what can I do wa shock your enemies
thore energy and really electrocute move
the d-pad control to store energy and
really okay High a the more you press
okay so it's just like storing my store
but no like different
combinations how look someone
sleeping but I don't know understand how
I'm charging it
[Music]
oh B it doesn't seem to be charging I
don't I'm pressing like different
buttons on the
d-pad H just wiggle move a lot oh
[Music]
oh y be so like become hyperactive more
power which door this door probably the
one most hidden okay okay
oh
oh be careful not to get the thingies I
wish I could shoot upwards but I can't
choose the
[Music]
direction
no let me go to the to the one
up wait to do make the way
[Music]
free I can't it's
dangerous I can oh I freed that one too
but then I can go here yeah and then
there we go but I can't make an attack
upwards there there there go oh go one
yes
there nice plasma is a lot better as a
helper oh okay then let me give it to
you if you want to get rid of the
current one oh wait my back up you all
right let's get out of here get can be
powerful I want to try the bear if I can
get it here take this who oh you become
the whole thing oh no bear for w
wa yeah move aot and then I guess you
charge what's that oh
[Music]
no it's it's like raining some some
clouds oh oh I'm
sorry I forgot I can't eat
those they're
spiky oh I want yes I became
Stone right I don't know what that is
Stone
yeah oh wow that is
amazing oh different
Stone so I should like fall on onto them
I wa let me try uh oh I can't I can't
activate it from the
air just like oh close
[Music]
by
what I love using it in Super Smash
Brothers but
H have to Exhale first
oh God this all this static plasma
energy reminds me of my cats like when I
touch my cat oh my God yeah when you
touch them what wait what does this even
do oh Stone in the air St oh they're
they're like a ground pound kind of ah
turbo Stone Dash and Y okay let's try
that then turbo
Stone oh
[Music]
okay no I lost
it okay wait
I can roll down like this y finally I'm
useful ah oh what the heck follow
me follow me wait maybe we should check
out what's in all those gaps here there
something
there oh there secret doors okay I
should become something else I can't
handle oh wait never
mind
no well I thought that was perfect for
this room but there's uh I think what I
don't have the power anymore
okay well now we don't even need the
food
ah it's okay I fell down wait how can I
fall I'm cury do you want to unir me and
so you can
no prioritize the one out my think okay
can you destroy
it thank
[Music]
you okay
okay what about here nothing
here yum yum yum
yum I I need to eat something oh you
what is
you yo yo yo yo yo wait I want to go
back up for a moment oh come here oh W
wa I want to try oh I can't open that
okay I thought maybe I
could oh I can only go horizontally all
right yo yo yo yo
yo W break dancer he's also a break
dancer what what where do I land oh we
in the nether or something
ooh Minecraft so dead there you go so
sad sad used to be so exciting oh
snowman wait I
tried do you want to kill a
snowman yes I do oh this one wait he
doing something okay
uh what are you
doing ow
ow oh I
w
wow so
sparkly oh yummy perfect Oo we can turn
him into ice
cubes we look so cool together Elena
green and blue but today you were blue
and I was red okay yeah we didn't
even oh oh hey why would you leave me
behind can can we
[Music]
walk
wait Invincible
frames I can assist you thank you with
what how um um with my B
button
oh where you going we all
together we're using the sleds yeah it's
the holiday snow split oh my God oh my
God wait why oh it's the
infant they only shoot at me yeah
bye-bye here for additional
ammunition okay is this boss
[Music]
fight m yeah
no
[Music]
okay ooh my block is ice block oh what
is this oh it's a it's a something n
would really
enjoy the neighbors are him are
they why why would you guys be hearing
that don't scare me
fighter but I have to birth you you're
the fighter
whoa who's The Knuckle Joe
now you look cool you have fancy hair
wa oh wait can I eat
this ah no okay we have to fight
it oh no The Beetles not the Beetles I
had an invasion of those caterpillars in
my home before
and I sucked them up in my panty hose oh
ow how' that
work I think I you can you suck this guy
oh oh maybe yeah maybe maybe
yes yay I'm suplex
suplex you're I don't know what this is
suplex
suplex okay okay go go go
what whoa we're too powerful now let's
go don't joke don't joke oh no all go we
just got the cool
stuff
yes oh my hands oh my God have they been
moving like this the whole
time I had them like here oh okay with
my controller
nice can we keep the the power they're
so
cute we keep it we keep
it oh this music is cute hey oh
wow oh wait wait oh my my superow flew
away no it's okay so youold but oh mon
dead the guy the guy when he's there
again I want his power okay I'll stay
behind I'll stay behind yummy hot
dogs
what the Sleepy what why why is he
sleepy kind of stuck up
there AR we all always sleepy I'm always
sleepy sleep talking in my dreams I'm
sleep talking right after right after
dinner I was so
[Music]
sleepy cuz Wayne sleeps like a baby at
clock that's so so that's the word
disciplined so proud of you thank you
okay magic let's go
ow oh my God I'm dying
help
yeah is this guy carrying a sock or
dakimakura a you got the bunkers again I
got the hammer wait oh my God I'm dying
though there's like a hammer I also got
the hammer yeah there's like a button
downstairs do you know Super Smash
Brothers when you have the hammer it
goes
[Laughter]
like place what the only time I play
smashes with you in the the in the
mold oh oh yeah oh yeah you're almost
going to die but if you die don't worry
I'll burp you
again pleas just spawn endlessly let's
go somewhere
else yeah up here oo ow I'm going to die
soon
too I not let's go did we come from here
no okay bir it looks like you I'm going
to kill it there's only one bird
alone two birds
you
o
no
okay there we
go and
[Music]
okay there we go oh my God back to
normal I don't think I can protect you
oh wait what is this anyway
wa nightmare cat how do I kiss need you
need the
nutrition no it's okay it's okay I don't
mind what do you mean be bird can I
become bird well probably not if I fly
into
it scarfies can't be inhaled scarfies
you think I'm going to know what you're
talking
about like is this a
scarfie oh
forgot
Wing Wa to
the amaz your friends toss your enemies
into the air
and a shuttle Loop FEA gun C heavy
bber heading toss B heading sideways oh
by the way I see I'm seeing it in my own
with my own eyes the spark keyboard
Works let's freaking go yay I don't know
if it's on you know like cuz some peeps
some peeps are telling me that my uh the
keyboard that I gave her broke but I
guess it's yeah it's not the not the
keyboard that broke but the cable bro
but I found a different cable that
replaces the old cable yeah
so it's all good the Sparks keyboard
works the Sparks are flying yeah I hope
they're not flying in the you
[Music]
knowb I kind of don't
like this guy really strong but has
really short oh well tell me if you want
to be something else oh I don't really
cuz this one's kind of rare I guess
yeah
that sounds
unsafe yeah oh wait this guy why did I
kill them I killed them I'm sorry what
is
this let's go do down where are we
[Music]
going what do we
do peekabo peekabo oh no no no we need
to light the F hold on oh wait I have to
go you
then oh this one
ah
I ah we should we needed the fire guy
maybe that we killed no wait
okay oh you a first look at your
[Applause]
eyes but you're pink you look like
l
oh too late oh w oh we are in the cannon
okay
so
late too late fire can we light it again
it looks like we can light it again you
go in you go
in go to the
W is this lit I don't think it's lit no
it doesn't matter you go in and I light
in so at least one of us flies if I
can't make it okay let's go oh w
maybe now secret secret
world I'm
bir I'm happy you became a bird it
really suits you oh dear oh dear oh my
oh my god oh oh my God are you okay I'm
okay I'm just having trouble seeing the
screen seeing my
HP and my oh yeah you're dead oh uh no
bird
D and here we see a short how the bird
dies but now you're burning
Leo oh oh my God you have a new
power you powerful way against the
Recycled Powers what that cuz I was
too use oh these attacks what are these
attacks oh I make things hot yeah
burn but oh no but I ow you died again
um yeah what if I make things hot
then t wait that's you t wait how did
you become
that what didn't you just
die why do you have such a cool thing
it's called tag ow what the f oh we
touched the we touched the lava that's
yeah oh no this is so I can't see I
have
I wait okay
ah wow no we're so it's okay it's okay
let me get this one maybe uh oh no it
killed everything around it okay well
have to just watch yeah no no I want I
want the power I don't want to kill
them hey just running against the
bombs okay okay this is dangerous oh my
God
ah they're not giving me space to eat
oh it's okay just rush rush
rush you're now A
Stone Way a St why he sto oh no he stole
You Ah that's what happened for now
you're Stone again because it even said
down here like help on the on on your
name it said help and it had like a like
a picture of you being stolen oh no I
don't even know how I how I can navigate
this without
dying how to be Stone come
on can you
jump see it's
SL wait maybe if I go on the screen you
you join me right
okay well find you something
better for now you're just the stone
yeah I'll just um I'll just do that I
can't get across land in the middle
okay okay oh
umbrella this become a St until you find
something else microphone that surely is
something oh
mik that's very what the
hell wait I
can't
okay oh wait it has like oh I think it
has uses like it says one now I think it
has like three uses oh okay and then
it's
gone oh cuz it's very powerful like it
destroys
everything oh okay cat no I want to be
the nightmare
cat I don't think I can suck the
nightmare cats in okay parel
parel
okay I'll take this and I won't use it
until the magma cats are
here H sorry oh man I feel bad how could
I ever hurt
cats what wait what is this pineapple
guy eiz
BS okay wait another microphone that's
kind of
op wait wait
wait o oh
pineapple which one do I get
oh cook what does that mean I got a
cook what oh this is is is also like a
special
one what's going
on yeah I gave it away I cooked some
food and you ate
it that's so cute
hey a ball
do you want that take it I hate
it nice you're more useful with
that
oh why do we kiss like that I don't
understand what's going
on what what are I doing I wa to kill
him why I I have no
power oh good job yeah I like this P
power up oh were sharing
food thank you that wait why do they
run ow oh nice way good job wa doing all
the
damage W what the it's the bomb guy I we
to kill
him wait let eat ah ah ah it's exploding
oh sorry no worries
was just exploding on his own oops
exploded you're good you're good oh
thank you way for absolutely carrying
it's okay we got all our
rolles let's go to the goal how far how
far wow W oh number one number one y we
got
a y yeah I think this is my favorite
weapon as as long as I have you in front
wow that's surprising we're I think
we're at the final level
really is because Kirby is tone deaf and
his singing causes
destruction oh that's mean that's mean
sad I'm sure I would enjoy Kirby like
this cuz there's a final level really
yeah why the music so scary just because
it's oh we can choose Cho no I'm God oh
yeah you can stay that I I'll take this
one yes hey best team and then we go we
go I want fan out of us being carried on
the star and maybe with our favorite
[Music]
weapons oh that thing is
huge let it go let him go let it go wait
let it go let it go Let It
Go
monkey monkey
w w we did it oh there's more there's
more wait but I lose I lost my power
there's no way oh I think we're done are
we
done we killed the mother and Kirby's
just super happy about it oh my
God no
what the oh okay oh the tree what's
up with that is the tree going to feed
the bird oh for them not for us I guess
but for them y but like what is this
weird happy ending we killed the mother
I and now oh now they're our friends
what is this story yeah we adopted them
we adopted them no I guess cuz like um
the mother is corrupted and then I guess
oh now there are four four of them are
flying away but they were free babies so
I think like we kind of cleansed the
mother out of like evil mind control but
she she still alive I'm making stuff
up this is why wispy has beef with kiry
beef was helpful though beef Kirby was
the the tream was helpful though oh okay
Kirby is an eldrich horror after all I
don't know that story really confuses me
just now after we beat the mom I thought
we were going to push the kiss off a CL
that's so evil yeah I thought so too and
he was like so happy about it he was
like wink and like P push push to the
side but it's a tree what the hell is
there like a proper lore explanation
there
somewhere I'm so
confused okay oh so it's it's say to be
can I have more yeah of course I'm glad
oh that's that's something else um
that's just gummies that why is there
why is there a yeah I thought I saw that
I think I was trying to put like the
stuff together cuz my desk is so messy
gummy bear yeah I'm glad you like the
chocolate a wa I don't know when it's
11:00 p.m. and we stream for one and a
half hours I leave it up to you like and
I think um it's a nice ending it's a
nice ending we finished one game yeah
and two even yeah no and we played the
gourmet race as well
oh that was
amazing that's a really good like Co-op
game is this only couch Co-op guys I
think it was also online co-op was it oh
I don't know we can chat for a little
bit yeah yeah of course we can chat yeah
didn't I say we should talk about
something uh before the stream I said
like something we should talk about it
on stream I think it was something about
my cats oh um what was it like I will
tell you on stream but what
was what did I ask something about my
cats I think yeah I was like there right
I was there and then I was you're
patting my cat and then I'm eating the
the chocolate again yummy then you asked
me a question I said I'll tell you that
story on stream I don't know what is it
I don't remember what what what would
what would you want to know about my
Catos is something um does your cat
remember does your cats have any
siblings in like another oh yes you
remembered waa nice okay so okay wait
let me put on we're going to like maybe
talk for 10 15 minutes okay yeah sure to
end it I'll add some
[Music]
bgm music AIO St oh wait to see how I
keep all my stuff I have at least a
folder for audio stock isn't that
amazing that's nice and I named them do
you use audio stock I do and then when
you download them I don't name them yeah
they come in like numbers and then you
never recognize them so that's why I
name them normally um I usually end up
naming them in
the I don't know why you giving it to me
do you want me to eat it no I wasn't I
was doing
gestur you can
have and
then um I name it on like the scene here
oh you keep it in there forever yeah so
it's like blah blah blah blah blah blah
but I think I should do it the way
you're doing
yeah I just like name it in something
that I think fits the theme so anyway
yeah you wanted to know about my cat
siblings so my Catos they're like I
don't know five years old or so now
maybe mhm and uh when I got them first
they were like small small babies and I
wanted to get male cats because they're
like more even more cuddly and even more
like sweet and like Chill from my
experience oh really yeah and then they
said yeah you can have two boys we have
we have them so I even I even already
thought of the name that I would give
them and then I went there and I
reserved it they knew I wanted boys and
I went there and like somehow they were
all already taken they only had two left
and that was two girls like what
happened with the boys the boys they
just forgot about it or so and then I
took the girls I mean I couldn't say no
they were cute but they were definitely
like difficult at times like
a okay you tell me a cat story
too I forgot um I don't know tell me
about your cat C what's going on with
way they're doing good what do you want
to
know
Shenanigans my cat I told you this
earlier but how your your cat's like
very smart with the
door cats are very smart too but they're
kind of lazy about
it they would push doors but they're not
as active as
like you know jumping and you know
pressing yeah your cats are really like
slow yeah like super slow paced and you
like earlier I said like are they always
like this your cats cuz they're just
like everywhere oh yeah they like crazy
uh running around but that was only
because they were they pooped yeah see
like my cats don't even do that I just
they don't poop no no no no no they po
but I mean like that's the first time I
hear it like oh they're just very Zoomy
and active after they poop and I'm like
what are they like celebrating the fact
that they don't have consultation yeah I
know it just they feel
lighter I guess yeah but my cats don't
do that they just poop normally and then
you know go to the bathroom it's a
little bit concerning that your cats are
so calm they're a little bit too calm
they're too calm for cats this what you
think yeah maybe you need to play more
but like they're too lazy they've become
too lazy because they're used to like
always being lazy I guess so
but I don't know um when I guess when
they have the space like sometimes uh
they chill in their own room but
sometimes we release
them right in the main room and then
because they don't even like it if I
bring them to the main room anymore
because they already are you know uh
comfortable in the in the smaller cat
room so you know we in a cat room so
cool yes my cat room is just a whole
apartment whole apartment the
stairs what the is the hand doing
stop it what it's just like it was like
up
here I read that pooping is like a
dangerous activity in the wild so they
celebrate after it's safely done
what ah yeah okay cuz like they let the
guard down and they're like busy when in
the wild they're doing that and they
could get attacked or
so cuz they're focusing on like one the
PO they're concentrating on getting the
poop out or something I can see that
actually makes sense yeah you You're
vulnerable yeah and like especially as a
human too maybe even more as a human
because when as a when you take an idol
meeting you're like pulling down your
pants a cat doesn't even have to do that
but we would have to like pull put our
pants back up before we escape and run
from someone so we're even more
vulnerable in that situation I guess so
but we don't have to bury poop with our
hands uh but I was about to say
something yeah when uh when I put them
in the main room sometimes they get like
really like they just like run around
like that and climb over the furniture
like it's race like it's a cat race or
enjoy the space they enjoy the space but
like if I if I just release them alone
they would be like eventually they would
be like I want to go back oh yeah oh
maybe it's because in that room you have
like the toilets and the food true and
also alone I
guess yeah but I also have trained them
to be lazy to fear nothing all they know
is a good life with belly rubs and belly
Wubs my cats also love belly Wubs yeah
and then when they sleep you know
sometimes like you know how they the
Tiny Paws they like just squeeze my
thumb they're so cute yeah I also I
touched their Thum and I like I like the
Paw beans yeah I I I I stroke it with my
Thum and then sometimes they get really
happy oh my nail is so broken they get
really happy and then they like bring
out their claws like they hold first I
hold hold let they let me hold them them
like gently like this and then and then
she's demonstrating just
clutching with the claws they like dig
in because they're happy they're like
like trying to what's the word need me
yeah they're doing that yeah they they
do
this so one of your impressions of my
two cutos ah they're so cute which one
do you like more yeah I like both I I in
she told me the difference and I
instantly knew not even like yeah yeah I
guess it's just like a cat owner thing
yeah it's pretty easy like I basically
just told you the chunky wonkey has is
like a bit thicker and she has a baby
face and smoovie is like thinner and has
a a beauty face beauty face that's why I
called it baby and beauty baby and
beauty or Beauty at the Beast because
sometimes chunky monkey could be a
little bit of a beast cuz she's so B big
yeah and another thing is just like you
know how uh she uh goes on up your on
your chair ah yeah that's what happens
when my cat gets in my room so she sits
there on your chair I know it's so
annoying and I can't sit cuz I feel when
I S sat there or she ran away does your
cat just stay stay she's that's nice I
wish mine would stay I would love to
share my seat like half of the seat for
the cat and half of the seat for the for
me no but it's so annoying and then
eventually like when I'm in the middle
of streaming she be like I want to leave
but then like okay here you can leave go
and then five minutes more she'll be
like I want to go in and then I open and
then that's why I have always all doors
open all the
time I like it closed so it's like ooh
you know how like the noise no noise
yeah I mean yeah yeah it's no problem
for me cuz I'm all alone I guess
so and so okay how was your impressed of
Austria Austria is good like I said the
bar is in hell because I like that you
guys have clear
skies that's so crazy that's such a
crazy thing to say for me like it's so
normal I'm like what but I I don't even
remember when I was in Indonesia yeah I
don't think I
really
consciously saw the fog or so like the
I don't think I really realized it maybe
I wasn't looking at the sky don't you
don't need to look at the sky you look
at the sky there's no Blue Sky to look
at I'm sorry I think like one day smog
not yeah fog smog I think like one day
um just one day out of nowhere I forgot
when it was even like one morning we
just had like blue sky and I think
everybody in town was freaking out cuz
like w w good erased it from the B
but yeah I like walking
around I like walking around a cuz yeah
I made you walk quite a bit today yeah
and we we tried all sorts of
transportation we talked a lot about
this and that we talked about art and
stuff and blah blah blah many blah blah
blah yeah we talked about a lot of
things actually and I made her try the
I'm wait I'm
d oh is that the drink behind the c yeah
and this is like the in the
advertisement on TV they like scream on
top of a mountain cuz it's like kind of
a mountain drink cuz the it's um herb
herbal flavor herbal soft drink and so
the herbs are from the mountain so he
like they drink it on the mountain and
then he goes
like nice oh dude love it just screams
it through the mountain and it reverbs
and
echoes get it okay so good you liked it
yeah and then I also tried like some
other yeah like okay that the orod she
had in the cafe but for dinner she was
like okay what other drink is like AUST
and I'm like uh nothing really from soft
drinks we only have oilla that's like
specifically Austrian but my all my
Austrian friends they like to order this
really simple soft drink which is just
sparkling water with like lemon juice in
it yeah so we call it the
uh what's it called wait uh what do we
call
it a soda Citron a sodon soda we call it
soda Citron so soda and lemon so I was
like well we don't I mean that's nothing
special but I mean it's kind of Austrian
so she got that it's so simple they like
I'm Austrian and then J walked and said
I'm Austrian let's go oh yeah yeah yeah
I'm sorry oh oh but okay I have to say
like we took the Uber right and I go in
I just automatically put on the seat
belt and Wayne is just chilling and
she's like after a few seconds she's
like do I have to put on the seat belt
and I'm like yeah you have to it's
normal here we like even in even in
Indonesia I put on seat belt in the back
of the taxi I was like if I could get
away with it no no no no you have to put
it on if I could get away with hey even
in Japan like if you go into a taxi in
Japan if you don't put it in they go
like dinging no they make some alarm
don't you have you not had that before
but because normally the um the alarm
only works the alarm is only yeah I have
noticed yeah wait actually even like in
Jaan no no in Japan I do autopilot seat
belt what I mean I do autopilot seat Bel
but I was just like like you put it on
automatically yeah yeah oh yeah yeah and
then it's like so in Japan you do it
automatically but in in Indonesia you
don't I don't think and in Japan in in
Austria you don't feel like you should
put it on it's honestly it's like people
take it really seriously in in Germany
and Austria I think is it's not because
they suck at driving no no it's because
like the the law the law is really
strict and the driver will have to pay
for the that you do for not putting
on the seat belt the driver will
be yeah see so I was like checking it's
so normal but checking now that I know
it's normal I'll put on the se but I was
praised so many times even in Japan
because even in Japan so many Japanese
people when I drive with them like and
they're in the back of the car and me
too they don't put on the seat belt
either I'm the only one and um and I
always get like praised with like oh K
you you put on the seat Bel I'm like
yeah does like for me yeah see like
that's the thing I mean is it at cuz
like in not in every country at if I can
if they say no need then I will not no
need need need need because I get car
sick sometimes and when the seat belts
like you know eh have you not seen like
I think it's maybe it's a thing here
like they have a lot of like warnings
that are very traumatizing like even on
the Austria on the aoan on the highway
they will have like big big signs with
big pictures of like uh accidents that
happened like people dying because they
were in the back and not no seat belt on
and then they flew to the front and died
so they like show off like really
traumatic
scenes mhm of these accidents and like
they hammer it into a brain until we
know okay we should wear the seat Bel
yeah that's actually really good yeah
fruit and windshield it does happen okay
yeah that makes sense that makes sense
oh but then someone told me recently
I don't know who it was anymore but
someone told me uh maybe it was about
someone El some news or so I don't know
where I have this information from but I
I've heard about a story recently where
someone had in the front seat I think
had a seat belt yeah but they were
injured or even died I don't know I I
barely remember what happened in this uh
story but because they were wearing a
seat
Bel something happened because of that
like because it was um holding them back
I think they're not doing it properly
and then they got the freix them over or
what I think it was something with like
uh something came from the back of the
like behind the car and
then yeah and they were like held back
by the seat belt so like I don't know I
have no I don't remember but yeah so
sometimes I guess you can yeah you can
get your chest crushed or it's not
always helpful huh
what I heard about um something
dangerous is you know when um if you're
sitting in front you must absolutely not
put your feet on the dash Yeah well yeah
yeah yeah no no cuz I mean like I mean
from the passenger seat oh yeah from the
of
course you're going to you're going to
drive with your
feet but I mean the fact that they had
to put a warning for that that means
like a lot of people do that right and
then it's kind of like if something
happens and the air back just fhes and
then your feet like like in the way it
can get not scary we all got to be
careful that's really D cars are careful
traffic is cars are cars are dangerous
traffic is scary I that's why I didn't
get a license until now yeah cuz I'm
scared of
driving I'm scared of the thought of
driving being like cuz it doesn't even
have to be me who causes the accident
someone next to me could cause an
accident and I could be like the victim
of that just by being on the street and
that just scares me ah so true so true
oh speaking of traffic yeah one more
thing that's a big difference like I I I
I thought it would be like so
refreshening to you refreshing to you to
have a traffic where there's only cars
no b no uhom bikes yeah cuz we have a
lot of bikes we have a lot of motorbikes
when we were in males you said oh this
is just like home because not on the
resorts but like there's a main island
where the airport is the main airport
right M yes and we were like sitting
there on the last day to have our last
dinner before the flight and there were
so many bikes the whole time boom we
were kind of like on the second thir
floor and we were kind like on the
balcony so we have the view of the
street and it's just like God damn this
looks like home and I was hating it
because it was so loud and it was so
crowded and they were like it gives me
anxiety watching them all go like like
wait here let me show you with my
they're they're so skillful
they yeah this is exactly yeah like this
yeah like like that exactly I don't know
yeah the mopeds mopeds yeah that is so
terrifying yeah guys you kind of can't
you kind of can't compare the traffic in
like I guess like European countries or
like whatever and then southeast Asia
it's just it's just different I guess
it's because mopets are are just cheaper
yeah I guess so yeah it's easy to get to
and stuff like that and if there's
already traffic jam like it's easier to
get around it with a with a motor bike
with a motor bike so I get that I get
that yeah but even higher risk of
getting injured because you have nothing
around you that protects you a Mot bag
yeah cuz you're on like you're just
holding on to the bike oh and in a car
at least like if someone shoots an arrow
at
you I don't know I don't know just get
good I feel like get good get good at
dodging or what you get good at you know
maneuvering you Arrow I don't know
random I don't know yeah like qt in
games oh and we went um this is has
nothing to do with traffic but I uh
remember uh so when I was ice skating
with her uh I got tied really easily
because yeah it's understandable yeah
because like when you're uh she says
that oh it's your cuz it's your first
time you put so much pressure on your
feet your feet gets so tense yeah your
feet gets tense so it's like you don't
know how much pressure you overwork it
and I'm just like isn't that the same
thing like when we're streaming and
we're playing a game and we're fighting
a boss we get the that controller death
grip you know it hurts our wrist and
stuff I've had that too yeah I guess
that's it but you were doing so well
like uh after like mostly I was staying
with waya uh like in front or in the
behind her and sometimes holding her and
then sometimes you know because you know
I want to go a little bit Zoom fast
around the the the rain so I left you
for like 2 minutes to go one round and I
come back and you're all on your own and
you're like like wobbling wobbling on
the ice but you're not falling down I'm
so proud my give me two three times more
and then I'll be a God I'm so proud of
you thank you and then even when people
crash into you or you crash into them
you you didn't let that scary you or
trauma IED you yeah I think like during
the first 5 minutes I was just scared of
everything basically scared of fall fall
falling and let my head be on the floor
and then people will hit my head with
their shoe let me get rid of the hand
yeah and waya waya was like speeding up
and like trying
to hold on to the rail like when she
obviously when you get fast you want to
like quickly go to the closest rail to
hold on to it so she did that but like
there was a child and she she kind of
like bonked into the child
and then the child like I watched the
whole thing go down and it wasn't even
so dramatic the child wasn't even like
like nothing much happened it fell down
a little bit but it wasn't a big crash
and and this child immediately was like
starting starting to cry and I'm like oh
crying she was like nah she was
just like making up like you know like
she didn't even cry she was just like
her she was like confused like what the
just happened yeah she didn't even
feel the pain the first time she
realized she was falling show she was
trying to get the attention
in I'm like is the parent going to get
angry at us for crashing into her like
what can she do she's also just a
beginner way is just a beginner okay
don't don't be so angry at her you want
pain I'll show you P just kidding but no
the mom was like she'll about it
whatever yeah the mom even I think in
German she said like when we were
leaving she was she kind of scolded the
child saying like oh it's because you're
standing around here like something like
that oh my God we have to go go well she
didn't really deserve that but also it's
not really I also I feel like it's not
really my fault cuz like somebody was
like somebody was using me as a fence
like somebody was like doing this and
then like was passed by me yeah I think
it's just it was a lot of traffic cuz
like some of these ice roads were like
really thin and so many people
especially the good ones the people who
know how to ice skate they like Zoom zo
Zoom zo they like zoom zoom and flex and
just like you know and then the the
amateurs they're like oh yeah
shaking and holding on to the rails and
trying to go slow and it's a bit
stressful I think for amateurs but you
you I threw you into like a really
difficult ice skating experience and I
think that's like the best way to learn
it like hardcore ice skating yeah and I
think it's like you know like I'm a
beginner yeah but there is a lot of
beginners of yeah many so it was just
like a lot of people there were really
shitty people really good people
people I'm I'm just I I can hold myself
normally on my feet and I can go pretty
fast and all that I can hold control of
my balance but that's it I can't even go
backwards the coolest thing I can do on
my ice skates is like make a little wait
I show you this is good I think I make a
little here my hands here oh where are
they oh now they don't want to show oh
wait I turned it off oh here we go okay
so my feet are like this and then I go
wo oh yeah like you know what I mean
like I open close open something like
that that's the coolest thing I can do I
can't even go backwards ah people tried
to teach me before but I can't you you
better watch out yeah next thing you
should learn next thing you have to
learn is how to stop like a uh lower you
speed I thought you were going to say to
snowboard no no but yeah I think you
should totally learn snowboarding not
sking because you look like a
snowboarder yeah that's what she
said like she was like she was looking
at me and I like you look like a
snowboard like what is that supposed to
mean like as opposed to me you look like
a snowboarder yeah you look like an ice
skater I do yeah that I appreciate Dad
because I I think ice skating is so cute
I want my own ice
skates cuz they're so expensive I want
to try I mean like um I skating I can
still do in ID because it's like indoor
and it's like yeah well you know how ID
weather is but no morning I imagine it's
going to be a little difficult I need to
but you said you want to go to
Hokkaido so that's a good idea like if
you go to Hokkaido you should combine it
with like learning how to ski or
snowboard yeah like spend a day or
something get a teacher get a
teacher you could do it in Austria too
oh or anywh Canada somebody's like your
stereotype think her all snow bers I
know are rich preps no that's not why I
no no no I I know what you yeah you know
what I mean right I I know what you mean
I was pointing out because of Wayne's
fashion
style cuz she looks like a snowboarder
she looked really cool snowboard
snowboarding fashion let's go can I say
the thing about CI yeah sure that one
you said yeah cuz we're talking about
fashion so I I realized something me and
waya we were talking about clothes and
all that and then I was looking at her
and I was like you know what you should
go shopping with cie in Japan because I
think you guys would like our fashion is
very different yeah but you and cie I
feel like even though you give me very
different Vibes you kind of would wear
probably the same clothes what what
you're wearing I feel like cie would
wear and you
might I think Callie's like wears wears
similar clothes but like darker but she
would also generally wear what you wear
I think n yeah I I don't really like
wearing darker stuff that much I mean I
do sometimes but your pants are so cool
ah thank you and your shoes were so cool
ah when was the when when did you last
meet Kellie it when we were in Japan
karaoke
h what were you guys both wearing what
were you wearing I was wearing like a
sweater it wasn't really like it wasn't
like anything similar to today did she
not say anything about your fashion
because I feel like she would love your
fashion she needs to see more no because
yeah because I was wearing something
totally different that
day yeah so I feel like you have very
similar fashion tastes and you could go
shopping together and you would go into
the same shops and buy yeah the same
items of clothing yeah yeah totally
similar than yeah I can wear totally
different things one day C is yummy Dana
yummy yeah like a like a dark or version
I guess but at the same time I still can
see her wearing Way's clothes just maybe
like combining them like those pants
maybe with a with a black shirt yeah
maybe these pants with like a black um
jacket or something yeah and like oh
even like your your choice of bags or
choice of uh hair not accessory like a a
cap or whatever it's it's very
very very C I don't know how I didn't
realize it until
now I gu yes I know did you realize it
um I mean
I in a way but I felt like because the
colors are different the colors are that
she likes to wear are different so I
felt like but I do feel there's some
similarity especially when she got uh
her new outfit it depends sometimes
sometimes she wears like leggings and
that I would say is not your style yeah
yeah see like even her like she wears
different things just so happens the k k
I was wearing something else yeah yeah
but I did see her and I'm like oh okay
maybe I miss her what did I say what I
say cool but colorful Raina yeah Rea is
like the colorful version of
call colorful Callie
yeah hey what how would you how I mean
today I would say I was still like
mostly dressing comfy but how would you
describe waa
fashion I think you look
nice hey hey what does that mean that
sounded not very
enthusiastic no cuz you are wearing this
really nice coat and then you didn't
wear a beret today though yeah you she
weree you she wore like this really this
what's it called this like a noral knitt
knitted um with a a pom pom on the top
top Yeah because it was windy and I had
to hold my hair down and ber can't
really hold down my hair it was so windy
nice you know and but yeah I was wearing
a skirt and tights and UGGs do you hate
Uggs so many people hate Uggs what are
Uggs the shoes I was wearing oh I mean I
don't hate them they look good on you
thank you yeah and now people are just
like oh she's not a she's not a fashion
girl she's not a clothes girl you tell
them I was wearing clothes of course we
were wearing clothes
yeah oh no she's an ug girl I like my
ugs I like ugs they're so comfy and I
think they look uh cutest with a skirt
or or so or dress because I think the
silhouette of like chunky boots M but
then legs just being like no pants no
not nothing bulky just like you know
tights or so and then a a cute skirt for
so I like the silhouette going from
bulky to th to Bulky you know what I
mean yeah I think
so what so you said I what what why
don't you say it look
cute you look
cute and just make it that makes it work
but I I just think you look really nice
though because it was so funny cuz she
was wearing red yeah she was wearing red
and I was wearing blue so it was just
like colors like today like now I mean
I'm more orange but my orange is so
saturated but this is like a bikini
look when you're blue I'm red right now
so pretty red yeah but okay you're just
saying colors like you were red eyebrow
blue you're not really saying like you
wear cute clothes you cute clo you're
stating facts okay
okay she's so
difficult she's so
difficult well well s this
now right now I'm so sad it's only one
day but I I hope we can can meet again
soon yeah of course well I hope pen pen
I hope things work out so we can um go
to we meet in Indonesia yeah hopefully
when when might might or may not be part
of uh don't call me
Mand o I have to give her the wife treat
what what no she no I give you Wi-Fi and
yet you you don't give me Wi-Fi W wiu
treatment what what is that like we have
to go hand in hand you know no listen
the cats like me it's fine I'll go to
them your cats like me too I guess so oh
well so anyway I was saying I hope we
can meet again this was a short but a
nice a nice day I hope we meet each
other again yeah see you again sometime
maybe in in
Indonesia you have to help uh us plan
our trip of course yeah of course well
actually maybe we meet in Japan before
that
probably oh maybe somehow some somehow
at some point maybe for this maybe maybe
maybe maybe I mean we probably should
probably we should hang
out whenever we have the chance we need
to go for it because it's already hard
now like we can't like I can't meet up
with her like as easy as like maybe the
ID girls or
something y so this so this so today has
been really fun yeah I hope you cuz
you're still staying in Europe for a few
more days I think I hope you enjoy your
time here I hope the weather stays good
I think it will I think it will no cuz
like I was looking at the weather and
the weather said it was cloudy with like
little very zero rain but then I see
outside it was raining so I'm like can I
trust the a WEA app no not trust but if
you just trust Wawa or trust your guts
put a little uh what do you call
the nice the anti- rain I'll send you
some restaurant recommendations for for
the next days let's go we love you girls
so much thank you I've been eating I've
been eating yeah oh my God I can't
believe well oh my God like I took you
to good food today but
can't you're
you're it's so okay your your your mom
yes my mom your your mom your mom I I we
should have invited her for dinner too
cuz I'm I'm worried that she actually
just went out to eat Asian food she's
she's she's going to
eat please yeah eat uh wait what what
was it uh what What's whatever you
called the that burger place Five Guys
Five Guys yeah my mom's so obsessed with
please stop her please stop her from
going to Five Guys you can't go to
Europe and just eat five guys please
stop her R I sent you I will send you
restaurant recommendations you have to
take control of your mom okay
yeah I got you give her a good snitel no
she's like obsessed with you know how
like the Five Guys they have drink bars
it's not even the food that she Su it's
not the food it's the drinks it's like
it's well I guess drink bars just one
drink out of the drink bar no I think
you know it's it's so dumb because in ID
we also have drink bars but I think
she's too busy to go to like the places
that
I'm
I don't know I mean yeah drink bar is
pretty fascinating but um I hope she can
go eat some schnitzel and some other
austan food
yeah like you also really liked it yeah
I would have I would have loved to hang
out with you for more days if you're up
for it of course but I need to babysit
yeah go babysit your mommy reverse
babysitting
yeah can I met rain mama not today but
before yeah she's very sweet I was like
nervous I thought I would meet her today
when I picked you up so I wrote to waya
beforehand like do I I don't remember
anymore what to do do I handshake or do
I hug her waya what do I do yeah she's
not even here but just in case just in
case I see her somehow today she's not
even here just going I don't know N I
want to make a good impression on your
mommy I guess so but I didn't mean her
but I would have hugged her cuz you said
it's okay probably to hug her yeah give
her a hug from me will you yeah thank
you greet her from the
WW okay that was a lot of fun hope you
guys enjoyed it I'll I'll send uh waya
off now yeah first a little bit more
cudding me out no first cat cuddling
okay and then I kick you out okay can
you believe it guys drama get kicked out
of the W
house go no you're always welcome yeah
thank you for coming way yeah no
sleepover no no no way when you sleep
you know she can't just you know leave
her mom alone completely
no oh yeah fingers W so good W
fingers and in German we
say let's
go can I can I we can do this part wait
can we do can we do
it K doeses it work that's wait wait
wait that's the other it thinks it's
your my hand but that's you're stupid no
go
away okay wait here's my now now now
yeah oh yeah does it work I'm ready this
is such a challenge no no
no I don't think it
works oh my oh
I don't think it works hold on oh my no
it doesn't it's fine we're good do you
have like an auto sensor over there what
that automatically translates your
middle finger to different
one oh my God imagine if they put in
like an auto sensor so that we don't put
up the middle finger no can I do it
there's like a trick maybe is there a
trick to it cuz there's got to be a
trick to it this hand is
broken there's going to be a trick to oh
I can do it I can do it there we go but
I want to
do not middle
finger no it's always like you want to
do the hardest things
first see it's hard it's difficult where
are where's your hands I don't know you
have to start like over
here oh there it is but I can't go any
further I can't go any further it's
remotes
Oh see it's gone oh well okay you get
the gist guys yeah
I'll let's go
byebye ignore that other
hand
byebye I don't know what that is doing
oh it's here again my hand is here yeah
it's a ghost does it never do that with
your hands no it's like sometimes it
spazzes out like that I'm like trying to
for me like for me like the fingers go
like sometimes I'm trying to shake the
hands of the viewers guys why won't you
shake my
hand sh
sh okay no don't no rage no rage enough
enough
Shenanigans okay bye-bye
byebye Papi love
yay
[Music]
that was a fun game I know I like it and
the phone survived mine wasn't even
charging but yours yours is a little bit
hot and like High ever since the new app
uh I need to use a a phone
cooler yeah oh I need this you can buy
it anywhere on Amazon cuz like it
sticks magnetically on the back but you
have to connect it with USB and then it
will blow air onto the
phone how much is
[Music]
that
for