this is the new kfp noodle production
facility something's not right about it
sometimes people go in but never come
out and the files I found the things
I've seen and now this another anonymous
tip just like the others perfect timing
almost too perfect and they don't
mention what happens after 2:
a.m. keep an eye out for me
PN we don't have a lot of time to find
both these documents he said p002 files
were here uh they just
wrote you'll know the key when you see
it what do they mean by
that
wait when you need to hide a key hide
where they look but never
see try the sink and clear the dust and
place the key to avoid the rust what the
those aren't my memories there's no way
who who did this to me no time to think
about this where do this key unlock
there's nothing around here that needs a
key unless wait a minute I guess if you
think about it this does count as a
filing cabinet of sorts there are a lot
of papers in it so they said these files
will lead me closer to the answers I'm
looking for shadow resistant properties
introduced after mobile samples lost
during variable user height testing H is
something there what was that noise no
time got to read anti slip hook added
after feathers kept dipping into broth
what that came from the sink I'm sure of
it who are you show
yourself no nothing here wait I come
from
me
okay let me oh nothing to worry about
just a frog in my throat okay now I'm
running out of time okay I'm just going
to upload this file and you guys look it
for me um okay where would they hide the
second one let me think um if it were me
if I were the head of the research
division trying to hide
documents where would I put them the end
of shift Machinery cooling down what if
I hide it inside this machine it's so
simple wait I lied good hiding place
H how's a machine like this work not a
fryer how do they make these noodles
wait let me give it a shot there's all
kinds of rumors floating about this
place like that it should be impossible
to put that much protein and vitamins in
the ramen and that the flavor density
breaks testing meters and that sometimes
they'll even make strange overly
dramatic marketing
videos that was the main power disengage
emergency stop press the start button
then disengage all the heat units so
that the file doesn't burn finally run
the conveyor belt in
reverse and now just
wait okay this taking too long I'm
speeding it
up
wait how did I know to do that I've
never done that
before why was it here
like they knew I would check here
and knew I'd somehow be able to operate
the Machinery knew I'd be able to find
it all right come on come on not much
time let's look in the file let's see
what they wanted me to find product
development report Final Phase bribery
successful Mission star cooking skills
acquired massive flavor improvements are
introduced major
breakthrough 30 G of protein achieved in
ramen with the inclusion of quinoa and
waight initial proposal submitted by
c727 in response to Health Department
concerns argued that the constant
boiling temperature of broth would
eliminate any contamination risks from
Aven staff members notes and margin
besides worst case scenario just
improves the flavor
profile the health inspector chicken
skin crumbles integration successful
provides perfect crunch while
maintaining no Refrigeration shelf
stability there's got to be more
infation on this oh no 2: a.m.
what I got to get out of here I got to I
what is