foreign
[Music]
oh one
okay
Ricky
oh let me move it for you Kelly do that
do the thing again
all right all right get down oh yeah
that's totally Rick dancing
wow what incredible technology
wow wow
your second head I like how you're
wearing two hats yep two hats double
hats today you guys welcome everyone
collaboration whole life English
collaboration birthday party special
edition on my channel we're playing
jackbox games
[Music]
is that I guess the audio could probably
be turned up a little bit yo okay I
turned it up a little bit dude guys
first of all here the game music there's
a little slight not too loud but slight
bouncy music in the background
yes that punk do you hear it do you hear
it
louder
oh yeah it's really grilling monsters
yeah I just turned on audience if you
guys want to participate I guess you can
uh uh but I will be hiding the the code
for so that only we can join for real
those and you guys can be the audience
[Music]
gonna be fun I think it's a kind of
Dating Game
[Music]
thank you
[Laughter]
the lady will probably explain it to us
again but it's like go we are all
monsters but different kinds of Monsters
And depending on what monster you are
which will be randomly given to you uh
you get different traits like you will
take Hearts away from someone or
whatever stuff like that and then you
try to flirt with someone and then and
then after floating a little bit with
some some people you decide who to date
and then they even turn you down or they
turn you in
I guess that's basically the game well
if we got bored of it we can play the
other games in this one there's like
other games and and what's it called
jackbox games but party pack four so we
can play the other two but I want to
start off with this one
try it there is definitely not a reason
why I chose this game yeah
I wonder why
so so is that you're okay now guys are
you happy is the balance acceptable do
you hear a good amount of the music and
a good amount of the girls
I'll turn up Buddha a bit more on my
side
Duramax
Max it out when I scream it'll it'll
make your ears explode yo sorry TNT in
the eardrums you're kidding me yeah
anyone
okay how about now
I'm gonna go check and call them
[\h__\h] it's coming from like inside
the house that's muffled yeah it's not
supposed to be super loud exactly
should we take down some of these hats
yeah I'm ready
um
[Music]
uh so you can like I don't know look
into that you know yeah or throw up into
it when someone sends you a pretty
message
I hope you can use that you can make
them super small
Drew why did I not think of that
it can throw up into my hood I don't
mind
yeah oh gosh it no I just want to say
she hasn't washed it in Forever
doesn't matter oh those that's so cute
when they're so small I like that
this is a party for ants
yes
oh it's so cute
oh my gosh oh I want the small one too
all right
now let's go
so high
the Moon is
okay and just cover up the whole screen
but now the music is probably louder oh
[Music]
they're cracking it right now
wait hi eh I think these are the first
two
you mean
let's start chatting with other people
trying to set up dates you can only
spend four episodes so use them wise all
the audience can also also send messages
so is it the same code that we used
yeah okay
nvpc you're welcome to join everyone all
right so you can take the audience out
for a day oh my god
oh
oh okay it's too loud
the audience sends each night gets sent
to everyone and appears here on the
screen
gosh okay so what am I
um
[Music]
but we should have mentioned that some
of your conversations will appear on
screen during the day oh well I'm sure
it will be incriminating
[Music]
thank you
so that was totally 100 floating skills
over nine thousand
[Music]
uh I'm real smooth
oh my God
give me a pick up and pick up thingy
um
[Music]
it's funny
are you my paintings appendix I don't
know why what
oh sorry oh my gosh
if the one person you hope you're going
on
I'm keeping my mandibles crossed well
to write to her
how can I choose whoever
yeah well I'm disappeared oh are you out
of time
and if you don't get a date don't worry
there's just a lot going on I guess
there's a big old audience I think I
think
Jen this is not how you chat
this is not how this works
[Music]
trying
oh yeah
sure girls
I was trying to ask
[Music]
oh yeah
why did you not ask anyone else
it glitched for me
wow
[Music]
and you're temporarily in last place
to have their monsters
every night after that you'll do the
same with the highest rank of unrevealed
monster
oh whoever's in the highest spot will
get the power revealed hold on secret
word what does that mean there's a full
moon out tonight
probably it doesn't you can double check
your monster ID if you can't remember
a full moon
yeah so if like somebody has above a
monster that gives them a buff works
oh we can continue where we left off
I am by the rules
hey if you need to block
the info button on the chat screen you
can also find the block button so you
won't see their messages
[Applause]
okay okay oh my God my phone is blowing
up
foreign
[Laughter]
I didn't realize that
oh
did he learn any useful life lessons the
first night we'll find out all right
let's now works
it doesn't really work for me either I
try to click on date but I'll click
there click their chat and then like
oh
oh there we go it worked oh
oh no wait
I feel a rejection coming people had the
same idea let's see oh hey shut up back
off
I really like that sniffer
I mean
[Laughter]
it was for you
we both have nice noses
looking forward to our smooch
[Music]
oh it went oh I know this ends badly
loved by somebody
all right I tried Tiny Steps
your monster I died
the mother receives a
Pizza mom your child does not get a date
who is your child if you need to read
that again you can always see the
Monster Power rules for a revealed plan
by hitting the info button on their chat
screen
surprise it must be good oh
full moon fever
enough
foreign
[Music]
I'm getting kind of bold tonight
um
[Music]
all right
okay
[Music]
uh oh God 80 Seconds
oh come on
[Music]
morning
getting left on red
oh
[Music]
sorry time's up once again it's time to
pick your dad no I ran out of time
so much potential for disaster and
heartbreak no hack breaking please
um okay
okay
just believe
believe
I apologize in advance for letting you
down
oh audience
[Music]
for the mother
you don't know
[Music]
yeah I just realized
I love you too
oh no
how did you do this to me oh yeah oh
yeah let's see if any of that changed
the social pecking order okay
so let's see
[Music]
dad
the creep earns a bonus
creep only on nights they successfully
get a date interesting that's very
complicated it's shaped like a
linebacker
let's go
[Music]
okay
get involved
foreign
[Music]
all right all right I got my messages
out there I think I think I've been
heard
that like they get like only specific
phrases that they can vote for right I
think so yeah
they're like the most lonely out of here
I feel sorry for them uh
the audience just looks like a a crazed
fanatic texting me in their sleep over
and over again
in the morning
I'm closing my 29 eyes
oh it's a lot oh I don't know if I want
to fall for this trap come on
wow
[Music]
all right
oh if I didn't break let's see okay okay
all right Chad don't let me down
[Music]
wait oh looks like someone
oh no on the table oh no what about
Elvis
I didn't know you feel about me that way
yeah
[Music]
it's just black I I thought
um
something
[Laughter]
so small
so small how do you do that I have a
burger jokes
[Applause]
when you said mother I just lost
at the end of the game
every time they date the monster type
they've secretly Been Told
oh no
message time
[Music]
oh fingers are going fast
hahaha
[Music]
I am I'm I am sure about this
foreign
[Music]
um
I am I I am done
I know it's hard to choose
okay
come on
oh audience
was going to work
it means a bonus heart for the mother
yeah
don't go yet there's more
there's more
cheese
thank you
infected with love oh yeah yeah cucumber
oh come on that's not original
this is
let's see if that changed any of the
standings
well some small movements
[Music]
the vengeful ghosts
when the vengeful ghost ask someone
oh
man
to begin with sabotage
is to make it count and you get tickets
for dating tonight
[Music]
oh
last night I don't know
my DMs are open ladies
um um um um
oh my God the music oh my goodness
[Music]
hey what does that mean
come on
[Music]
what are your thoughts on the murder
well well okay okay
foreign
[Music]
the door can't be beaten I know it's
hard to choose
that really likes to film my messages
without me anymore
[Applause]
gets a bonus heart for standing at the
player
[Music]
oh gosh
confidence in your messages
I don't know where you were going with
that one ah
[Music]
I'm getting lucky tonight
oh wow
let's see the almost final standing
one last thing it's time
um
the vampire dates becomes a vampire
at the end this vampire receives half a
bonus heart oh my goodness it's not like
I really thought about it while doing it
huh
[Applause]
thank you
there you go
that is a little overpowered I gotta say
yes
that vampirism really spread oh I did
spread very hard
I was really lucky though
[Music]
yeah
how do I do it with the same players
again I can't click it oh I think uh is
that me and players
[Applause]
welcome to monster seeking monsters
repeat customers I see let's do this if
he customers
oh it's cute game that's cute
[Music]
message time
okay
here we go oh
no I don't feel too good about this one
I have a garbage one it's bad
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow
20 seconds into any unsent messages are
lost forever hurry up oh
[Music]
my God is like so
don't forget
[Music]
I'm talking about stuff
I promise
[Music]
oh it's it's fate
um
let's see
[Music]
don't worry this is
oh that's who you go for first huh
I'm sorry
there's another one for you
oh yeah
um
[Music]
interesting oh yeah
okay
[Laughter]
it works out we got the typical couples
huh yeah I guess we did you know don't
be sad you won you got all those days
last time
monster
all right I'm satisfied
tonight let's get out of this game I
don't need any more it's a secret word
crash
maybe it's what the chat can use
[Music]
foreign
oh I'm running out of I'm running out of
corny pickup lines wow my phone's
blowing up today
Callie reminds me of my dad [\h__\h] you
chat
we're down to 20 seconds
quickly I don't know
Kelly reminds me of my dad
[Music]
the date
so did we learn any useful life lessons
the first night we'll find out thanks I
don't know please take my love uh
come on take it I keep on pressing bait
but it doesn't do anything it's not
working I didn't know who to choose so I
tried to pick between two and I think
well mine works all right
I don't know if that works oh
and failed
heart is broken egg is too Kelly
I know
I was your first love and I will always
be
nice
how did that work I understand she had
finally congratulations
stuff definitely happened later don't
forget at the end of each night for more
the highest ranking to secret monster
will have their identity revealed
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
message time
is that how you flirt
uh
if the audience has no messages waiting
for responses they send their messages
to me
[Music]
hahaha
[Laughter]
this is Twitter what is this casual in
it
yes
is this something all right
[Music]
20 seconds left
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's Times Like These I love being a
matchmaking monster
I'm picking
come on take me it works okay
[Music]
oh yeah
what is your face
she understands German
around
of the audience
[Applause]
oh my goodness audience
[Laughter]
it looks like me in a summer heat
it looks like um
looks like ice cream yeah yummy
flavor
yeah that's it
um
okay let's see
oh yes
[Music]
keyboard clogging seriously
um
what are they called
shooting
oh
baby Kiara
baby baby Kiana yes baby
20 second morning oh no this is so bad I
don't know this is gonna come across
right
[Laughter]
this is awkward time's up oh once again
it's time to pick your date
all right oh this part always makes me
cake
this part always makes me giggle we're
talking about you cover for me
no
[Music]
no no
why is it in my message box come on
one chance chat oh the right thing I I
said
Yoga Yoga someone's lining up
what's up
my game screen is kind of like gondo
almost has monster seeking monster
oh yeah I think it'll come back okay
okay oh that [\h__\h] hurts it actually
hurts
never again
never again chat never again oh no
no
[Music]
okay
that's a good thing we don't want that
chill out
[Music]
oh no
oh you guys love tonight
now look what you've done message time
all right all right all right
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
please
I don't usually say this
oh no
what do I do
again
oh yeah but you never get enough
I have I have enough tentacles for
everyone all right that's true oh that's
kind of yeah
oh yeah why is no one answering my
flirting floating prepositions
okay 20 seconds
I think I can sell one more who's gonna
get my message oh no I might have been
um
[Music]
again
it hurts oh no what the heck
what was it what was Kelly again
what does that do
hey
but if you don't yeah I think you'll be
severely peanut I don't remember
you have to click on her and then go to
press that little I at the top
um
they secretly been told oh
laughs
[Music]
it's lethal
the wall oh
I'm trying to eat a strategy
[Applause]
okay okay
I clicked too
[Music]
oh no
oh no that's a little bit of a chaotic
situation
so much
rejections
it's too fake when the leprechaun is
revealed that's right now all fake
hearts disappear at this moment
then
oh one player
I got money
yeah one is this the final night okay
yeah it's our last night together make
it count oh my heart's for dating now
because it's such a special night two
okay
all right get to message reading my shot
I think that's shooting your shot
I don't know yeah I think yeah
[Music]
Kelly you really
um
this is kind of sucks this is the first
time you're going for me
okay but think about it I didn't know
who you were last turn maybe it's your
shortness what the [\h__\h] oh I mean you
can die
I'm still shooting my shot
wait don't wait
[Music]
20 seconds
[Laughter]
skipping a few right now
oh man oh this is hard oh no 10 seconds
[Music]
oh my god
oh you gotta be last until the end oh
boy oh
with me
approaches let's see
damn it
I thought you'd want to play strip Uno
still fire I guess
it didn't show the rest of the messages
oh my god oh oh no oh
oh no
oh yeah
let's see how this works out some cereal
guys
I don't know how to spread Irish accents
[Music]
everyone the mommy did not speaking
so do the players they date at the end
of the game
oh no then the curse is lifted
because then it's no oh
no
[Music]
nice down
here
the monster hunter hunting this whole
time a leprechaun
I still got one heart from you though
that's okay I'll give you that
is
had a little too many hearts there
um
so much in dating wow that's impressive
tell me how you went from last place to
first place what did you what was it
what did you pay attention to what did
you do better well what
poetry it all begins with poetry yeah
as soon as you said uh strip poker and
then Uno question mark question mark to
me I knew that you were the one
here we go the thing right
now
[Music]
I'm happy on my birthday I at least
wasn't last
second is pretty good in a game like
this yeah this is a hard game
because it's RNG like what yeah like
like first game was really aren't you
cute
life is strict that's true
yeah
we have time for another game or a
different one A different game
let me look uh there was one other in
this pack that I was being recommended
um wait how let me see yeah oh yes is it
the we might wanna survive the internet
is the one that I was being recommended
I think and how do I triangle yeah
[Music]
I like that one
compete to see who can make the best
additions in your attempt to beautify
the city yeah so like we all get to draw
there's like it's one section where one
person two people draw at the same time
and then we each vote and then it goes
on to the next thing but it keeps the
drawing so we draw on top of it and then
everybody draws at the same time and
then like we vote on which one we like
and we keep adding on to it
a masterpiece at the end family friendly
my tablet over for that one all right
okay let me use a mouse yeah
I always use a mouse
[Music]
okay okay
you might want to check the settings on
this one okay
uh might be good to put extended timers
because it's kind of like short you have
like 15 seconds or so to draw oh yeah a
little short yeah okay extended timers
um recommended only for streamed games
and what else do we have nothing
okay now let's play one of these and
then we maybe finish it up okay yeah
where will the code show up
just cover the whole time yeah
did you did you watch the musical video
it came out a little bit ago
stream it
sorry multitasking is not my strong suit
today
[Music]
um
all right
hello I am
oh God
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait okay
I've been no driving eraser dang it
I think if you mess it up that's it oh
I'm the first person and so when you
guys are ready let me know Mommy I'm
ready
okay is that a kazoo which one do you
have a kazoo I can't remember it is
I think everyone's in okay we're ready
I was in the middle of writing Sheriff
mode
that's my messed up drawing in the
middle that I couldn't correct blank
walls
that's right Louise that's not my name
and I know just where to start right I
like that voice
[Laughter]
is already in progress
I'm going to paint something here but it
is not before they declared it an
exercise in futility they're very
Advanced didn't finish the drive where
is your follow through pal what I don't
know
let's continue off of that and then we
continue
volunteers will vote
Calia drawing huh we're keeping you on a
short timer to make sure you guys want
to just draw a line ready all right what
are we doing anything anything yeah
whatever you think it looks like it
could be a nose like Kiara said or butt
or I don't know
okay uh this kind of looks like um
some kind of like uh vegetable and a
vegetable garden okay
okay to the town okay it's a statue I
got time
it shows up
yeah I was making a vegetable garden
what what do we get to pick which one we
want to start on the next one
I mean I think there's a practical
answer and then there's a funny answer
[Music]
there's a Powerball in the other side
probably
looks like they want you to use the
mouse
is that the cat
no let's do it okay
oh yeah it's me and uh okay next what do
we start on rack up those votes
of course the audience's voice yeah
yeah that's all good I kind of I kind of
figured
a Marcus a market sign oh yeah
two more
legs
swagging a real hard you guys are
breaking it and I give out
this time the bonus goes in my house
oh
you could turn it into a face if you
want
yeah yes
what exactly is going on right now you
two get to add something
um
soon I think the next turn okay now Ami
and I are adding to it I think yeah all
right artists
lack of artistic skills
what ah sorry about the leg guys I don't
know why that happened
that's okay
[Music]
oh that gets so laggy
eating
[Music]
is that because that was my monitor
thingy happening
oh no
what is this
okay
[Music]
all the eggplants guys come on oh no
it's vegetables is with the theme yeah I
guess so that is
what the hell
why did I not really good
next
yeah wow wow
[Music]
what is that on the right side I can't
even understand what it is
the veggies I like the peaky little
double chin at the bottom there
you guys have to add on to it it good
luck yes
I got it let me start with the clean one
I can't save this one oh That Shook out
that's that's right that's the point
toss those audience votes in oh oh hi hi
who is Diane's going for
oh yeah
of ice
okay
[Music]
with the mouse
oh really he didn't say that for real oh
everyone
oh my God all right all right guys let's
make it good
I mean it is good already but let's make
it even better let's go I know how to do
this easy
I'm gonna spruce up our town I want to
fill it full good morals like eating
veggies
oh there we go okay wow
now and tap into the game
you guys are breaking it you're playing
the game
oh my god let's see what you got
oh it's so slow
add your
contribution
no I'm not sure what I can contribute to
this one but okay
um
all right
[Music]
my hearts will will be more than
eggplant
[Music]
oh oh I like that
dude was on the right
[Music]
that was pretty good
slime that's just the work of art come
on sexy they're both really good
yeah I'm sorry I really like the Frog
it
looks like a frog to me it looks like a
frog okay
[Music]
I don't know
about
[Music]
as well
candy I really like boobies huh did you
drag them
were you inspired I have not I wasn't
looking at yours
why are you looking at your own probably
not
I don't got any yeah funny funny
floaties and that's fine
what did the audience think
oh come on
good choice good taste I mean I guess
it's not bad
we're gonna add on to it one more time I
guess yeah
wait who's adding on oh boy I didn't
have an idea for the Frog but I'll do my
best I can come up with something on the
spot oh
um
oh oh you meant yeah because you're
seeing it for me yeah I'm not clicking
foreign
I have a feeling that's had something to
do with me disconnecting my monitor
[Music]
no one
I mean look at all the emotes that like
the chat can put into the yeah thing it
has processed all of those yeah oh God I
have that with the monster game
that stop it
oh wait it's part of the game never mind
yeah all right it really draws out
[Music]
I'm really nice and suspenseful
is this the last room we're playing the
wrestling one that one was fun well yeah
all the Restless it was good oh my gosh
the characters fighting each other yeah
there's characters oh that was really
fun oh
wow
100 more boys
it's a stress ball
Sheriff
[Music]
we're almost there
without animations huh
but you got lots of time don't worry I
don't hear music anymore do you hear
music
no no
no
the other section it doesn't do this
again yeah yeah
it's Pizza go oh here we go
I really can't find a turn on button for
the welcome anymore
okay I don't know what to add actually
this already is pretty uh
interesting
[Music]
let's add some finishing touches
how do you say nipple again
oh
[Music]
foreign
of course
don't be crazy
is everyone voting I need to vote oh
dear
I think this class is one of the seven
man-made Wonders of the World in our
town
[Music]
I'm just kidding girl I love it
was the last you know so
um
you had you see you had you have uh some
floaties in the birthday Arts oh wow
yeah
[Laughter]
you got something oh yeah you got
something one of the blue dots who cares
Justice
blueberries blueberries it's not a
vegetable it's a fruit look the pink one
is uh is the Apple yeah yeah it's to
promote a healthy diet in our community
because this is Civic Noodle and we need
to promote a healthy lifestyle inside of
our town that is very Noble of you
yeah and they might also be nudists
I mean it's like they're covering up
we're gonna do this
no it is
okay I like that one
as really cautious about eating lots of
veggies and and fruit nice
very nice
[Music]
[Laughter]
see if it works better without the
audience yeah and then then it would
probably be 10 times faster than this
one
yeah I don't know if you can see it in
the settings and during the game
um probably not is this over is that
another round because I could shorten it
by just we have one more we have one
more drawing and that's that's the last
one all right oh okay
cool and birthday Barb
I already put your vision in there so I
mean I wonder I wonder why you can hear
me
I got some ideas eyebrows and no what's
the makeup on my balls yeah makeup yeah
that's a good idea or more vegetables to
promote a healthier Community
strawberries in there
yummy yes straws
I ate a pound of watermelon today
watermelon today too oh
wow
what a question where's the difference
yeah I'm gonna eat some right now
crunchy give us ASMR crunch
great what if I get water in my
microphone I don't care
[Music]
I
don't have patience for this
watch
so ladies let's go let's freaking go
live let's go there we go okay
going lots of hearts
[Music]
speed oh it is okay
sometimes I shake my head too much and
it makes my brain feel like it's moving
around
Jake Oh I thought you said shaved
I was frightening
just because it looks different from
your usual you
[Music]
I love this
Oh no I got it in I think that you'd
walk the shaved here
appetizing I had to do it
is incredible
I love it
I really love the scarf and all that but
stream Sparks challenges
I think it's true
time
in your country yet it might not be on
your music providers yet but you can
already listen to it uh them to the
music video on YouTube and then wait
until midnight and then it might be on
your Spotify your iTunes your Amazon
music or your Apple music wherever just
check it out just remember make a make
an alarm for me that or if it's already
midnight in your country you better just
go open it up right now and then type in
or spark so whatever you want and then
you'll find it and while you're at it
you can also stream hinotori and heart
Challengers well go for it stream all of
them
again
remember 1-800 dreams again
yeah Kelly we didn't even talk about
that
oh yeah well what happened I went to the
hospital for cracking my neck so since
Cali is also one of those crack neckers
I wanted crack knuckles
you should probably stop as well as fill
your own good I know it feels good but
yeah
I did it to my back maybe I should also
stop whoa how can we yeah just smile
yeah like a pretzel yeah you lie in the
bed and you swing your legs over
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
I just I just moved I just put my arms
up and then I move myself like a
Beyblade and then I crack my my neck and
my bag
is that what you said yeah
not the next just my spine okay the back
thingy it actually works really well
it's supposed to spin like pain points
why audience oh my goodness
thank you
it's just because they can't read it
they think it says Sparks stream so they
got confused maybe they're reading it
like it's like right here
let me help you with that here
that's how they're reading it they don't
know what it really says they're reading
it backwards okay they can't read yes
I think they got the message though you
got the message I got the message that's
what's important my first English
like Man stream Sparks
this is
a secret message maybe I should have
made it more obvious more louder more
flashing lights
and then you just write streams
all right since this was the last round
I'm just gonna not listen to this
anymore dear Lord uh can we get out of
this
this was the last one right
now there's another one there's another
like uh it's like different it's
different it's still drawing but uh it
should be faster unless there's another
round of this but I don't know five out
of five rounds this is the final final
drawn by us
okay yeah it should go on to like after
we load
uh whenever we load yeah
um continue because I don't want to get
dmca
I couldn't imagine adding anything else
the fact that it's she is wearing a
scarf but also a bikini
[Music]
there's only one one title for this
masterpiece
like we all had a baby
yeah this is our child
yeah interesting it must be a dominance
drool and not a scarf I just realized no
yeah
who the hell wrote that genius
[Music]
looks like a certain uh whole life
America member
yeah I would say the name
I mean the more I look at it the more it
it's just one-on-one the same thing
it's beautiful I was supposed to vote
oopsie
we got it are you okay let's go it's got
one minute
everyone wants an adult Oh no just
kidding this is what this is our ideas
okay
oh yeah
oh dear
oh
no there was nothing
predictable Meme
and now the moment we've all been
waiting for you
definitely
oh
oh for giving us a peek inside
I wish I had my kazoo here wow
wow that's one for the history books
[Music]
I don't want any more of this lag
no no no no game is over I gave him is
over everyone
thank you
yay that was fine
it makes me aggressive
second place
yeah I didn't win
funny I partially did not really
oh unfortunately it's gone
well we're all winners thank you
everyone for coming together on this
very special day I just wanted to have
some kind of birthday party of us five
together and I'm glad you all took some
time out of your busy schedules to spend
it with me thank you
[Music]
yeah thank you thank you I'm glad you
liked it yeah please everyone listen to
this box it worked really hard on that
one yeah
[Music]
stream spikes yeah hashtag stream Sparks
streams from Scream spikes thank you
I'll be I'll be gone probably the next
two days unless there's a gorilla but
there's also Hollow talk with God uh so
look forward to that
yeah I'm keeping myself busy and I gotta
work on whole clock next but I was a
very very special birthday for me and I
am I was absolutely overwhelmed with all
the love I've received today and my
birthday's dream thank you everyone also
thanks all the the the the people who
called in and including you girls and
all the sweet sweet presents and
comments from everyone and all the art
really really adorable I will spend
hours and hours in the next two days
days off that I have scrolling through
those things
um but yeah it was very special very
special day thank you everyone
yeah thank you
thank you you're amazing
thank you I love you all so much thank
you
um I don't even know what to say anymore
my brain has been absolutely burnt into
Lashes in the past few days
um you gotta take a rest
yeah
oh yeah
maybe I don't know we'll see
that time yeah everyone's sleepy sleepy
and in German we say ah a Peter Zane
a beater Zane bye bye
-bye
while I'm gone don't forget to stream
specs yay
okay
[Music]