foreign
[Music]
thank you
thank you foreign
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
oh yeah hold on
hello hello
[Music]
hello
everybody and welcome to Among Us with
whole life English and Indonesia
Indonesia
[Music]
[Applause]
to present to you a new feature that
just was updated in Among Us for the
whole life
[Applause]
wow
okay let's go
[Music]
have Cosmic Cube then you can like get
outfits from selected members from Whole
Life en ID and Japan this this games are
not sponsored but we just really want to
show you so good look at everything
[Music]
wow
to himself and they can also show off
their sexy outfit Wilder introducing
themselves all right let's go
[Music]
of the room eventually but let's just
start so let's start with
hello everyone
uh number one detective I'm naked
um
[Music]
introduction
hello everyone I'm shirakamian today
nice to meet you guys
[Music]
okay next we have
hi I can't really I'm having some
trouble with the choppy audio which is
why I'm not streaming but guess what
also my mommy hooked up my Wi-Fi which
means I'll be streaming in 480p which to
be honest why even why even Harry Potter
why even bother okay Mom I'm gonna get
some whole swag As a sheriff let's party
[Music]
Amelia one of the selected people you
can get the outfits of hi gouda hello
hello yes we're officially in the Among
Us lore now we're running along
Among Us hi I'm gonna
[Music]
thank you
now you can have so many imposters of
yourself do you even know who who is you
anymore I love it there are many
sharklings around
I was going right here right next to you
is cool please introduce yourself
[Music]
oh my God
yummy
[Music]
yeah
I don't know it seems like an imposter
it has to be meals it's suspicious
hey
I was also part of the people's outfits
you can get in the game
Indonesia generation one nice to meet
you
you're wearing your own hair yes
I'm wearing a scientist on feed right
now I feel like I'm I'm doing a touring
love in the Among Us
yeah
okay okay and then we have Mommy hi
Mommy
ice cream today
ice cream yeah
yeah I'm gonna get points I'm gonna win
yeah yeah
this works
for what outfit do you want
ah whichever is closest on the tree
yeah understandable all right and then
we have it raining
uh-huh
whole life I agree today I'm cosplaying
as sexy naked money in your area
[Applause]
okay and then we have
okay
[Music]
but not least the organizer of today's
event has sponsored today's event
[Laughter]
[Music]
s
oh you guys can hear that
okay a new code is in the Discord chat
please please go get it and don't
I get it
I get it I get it
let's see oh wait a minute Mouse wait
mouse please don't die please don't I
can play this without a mouse but
let's see it okay
my mouse dies I'm Gonna Be Sad okay come
on
it's
sorry but come on
there we go
I we
why
why you saw me click on it okay I don't
really need the mouse dude
yeah that was weird combination of
Martin and pickled you look at that um
[Music]
I will now change the world settings we
will have everything included we'll have
scientists
you don't know the scientists can see
the vitals at any time no not anytime
well there's a countdown but you can see
if someone's dead before finding the
body and then we have the engineer
engineer can it's a who can jump into
the vents so you can maybe with that I
got that a lot in practice yeah or your
some other imposters because of that
meeting in the vents oh yeah yeah
very spicy and now we have the guardian
angel which I thought was really useful
because the guardian angel is the ghost
of the first crewmate that dies who can
then go on to protect others from Death
I want to do that
I only have last but not least the shape
shifter this one is that that calls for
a lot of
fights I would say I knew it was you I
knew it was you
Shape Shifter can be only an imposter
but that imposter can change the looks
of themselves even the name so if the
shapeshifter is me I can change to I
don't know Anya and even have her name
and her outfit and I can kill people as
her a people will think wow that was
Anya oh my God what if I was the one who
found you instead it would be two onions
but just so you know all of these rolls
are not 100 so it's not guaranteed that
you that they will be in the coming game
but you know it's just might happen to
you now let's see
[Music]
I'm ready
everybody
[Music]
[Laughter]
but there's guns in here
oh careful
pretty nice to see you here
let's see I don't know this map very
well so
okay
[Music]
I got one left
let's see all right you guys
wait I can't go there I'm doing the
records don't bother me okay
I'm learning the math oh hi oh bye
or was it Ollie
's in the middle of doing tasks
uh
[Music]
[Laughter]
like in the beginning of the game I saw
Muna in the armory but Michael that was
the beginning I was in the back room
when it was found out well she got
killed fast
you know I want to step up and be like
yo I'm something I have no idea though
uh if if you are you were telling me
that um I was in a Armory you can ask a
gura because I saw Guru also in a nearby
there in the kitchen
um
[Music]
oh I'm a skeptic oh no it's when this
goes down it cuts off I see
oh my mouse
I hate being
drained with my mouth
oh I don't know where to go
here
let's see
no I can't go that way I need to
remember this man
the only map I really know is the uh
what's it called
the oh there's bathrooms
open it
intense okay I remember this
banana what hello what
oh four hello
I'm the poop poop I can't go this way I
keep for forgetting
I remember
that
can you not move from here
I'm so useless
cash my tasks okay
how do you get to this I should probably
look at the map
I need to pick a word with Anya
Anya Anya
Anya Anya don't go
there's a bed
I see
no you can't see okay that makes sense
there you are Mommy I have a word to
pick with you don't kill me no I don't
know where to pick with you
hey what
I got to do my task do I look like a
shark team I'll probably do my no I move
it at first
myself and I was like all right guys
let's do my test
oh yeah it's like that way
I don't like being in the dark with you
guys
come on man oh my God
the kitchen
a kitchen kitchen
uh me and Maurice and fight we were
nearby electrical I was going to review
it I was with a roommate and Kelly said
bye I mean I went to the Armory and put
guns away I passed by I passed by I
think it was Watson oh and
and gura in records yeah I can I say
that last time I saw zado they were in
the main hall with Cobo Cobo
I was listening about global because uh
she she telling me on the previous one
it was me well I definitely like far
away from the kitchen and now
um
do you have anything that you want to
defend Cobble yeah
so any lost words
like in the in front of the fan yeah
sure just uh see herself I like just
what she said and then after that I go
up
right near the lounge that was beginning
though that was the very beginning
after that I go up
[Music]
I go after killing her you mean there's
something wrong
so we have like we have little shorts on
uh shoes uh who's you're gonna I don't
know
I have enough information yeah I have no
idea I'm gonna follow what everyone's
doing
I don't know
[Music]
at the very beginning
bye okay
hi we are so bad
oh
[Music]
girls hello
there's no reason
wait wait wait don't stop me bye bye
mmm
how does this game work
and then you pull this right here that's
completed
[Music]
okay that's insane Watson is dead uh I
found the body
oh is that it was like the privilege
then it was dead last time yeah oh
um so I was in the front
um of the ship and I was doing the tasks
that were up there and then Watson came
in and we chased each other around for a
little bit and I was like don't don't do
this to me Watson she laughed she was
like I'm Gonna Get You he he and then I
was like haha very funny and so then we
did our tasks and I finished up the mini
game and nobody came in right after
while I was figuring out how to do the
mini game I was like how do you do this
then mume ran in and was like and doing
things and then I walk out and Watson's
dead body is there
Watson if you were entering the front of
the ship I mean you would have passed
Watson how did you not see me really I
don't know but I did I want to say I
passed gura and I went beep
we people people didn't yeah yeah
Watson left and then you came in and I
walked past you and Watson's dead bodies
on the ground I just want to know what
that's about I don't know what do you
remember so much Kelly I'm I'm just you
got a lot to say I don't know all right
now listen here's the deal so the amount
of time that passed in between me
entering the room seeing Watson leave
and mume entering and me going outside
was so short
it was like no time at all
I just want to remind you that we have
10 seconds left so I think if you don't
have all of them I'm sorry I have to
vote for a movie I just don't believe it
wait where's me I wanted to oh there we
go
now I'm really bad at imposter
I should never plan Foster really bad
it okay
[Music]
it was worth it
good job everyone combinations
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
all right
that was the only time I've ever done
something legitimately hit among them
[Music]
Kelly you should go for the Amelia
Watson detective outfit uh really yeah
[Music]
thanks are you guys ready for another
round yes ma'am
[Music]
oh
today
[Laughter]
I don't like playing poster
I like what's this I like to wait oh
wait what was it you need lettuce onion
onion what what is
onion onion
okay
oopsie
eyebrow I'd be better and faster if I
knew the map
but all I think is I don't know the map
I don't know the map Cobo oh wait Cobo
huh sorry I'm really bad at imposter I'm
sorry
the same too it's okay oh we're both bad
I don't know very bad it's okay it's
right for us okay we'll get them next
time we'll kill everybody
yeah for sure yeah yeah yeah for sure
yeah yeah
with that
what's this
okay what's this
can I go up here over here
hi
take out the garbage
what girl hello girl
oh wait
okay
I got it
what's in here
she's pondering she's thinking oh what's
weird
hi
you look you sound confident
oh she left
let's see
make sure there's no body here
oh that's old
found Ollie dead
that was crazy so I don't know the map
super well but I left the shower so I
put away all of the washcloths from the
shower and then I walked up and I turned
right and I went down that long hallway
and found Ollie's body right in the
middle of there but I didn't see anyone
coming down
well let's see
um Renee was busy doing things around
the shower
um also rained could have killed me and
she did pretty close I think the girl
was in the shower as well but she like
went down to the left
it's really if it's raining if she
already killed only probably she cannot
kill you
right but I mean Renee could have killed
me several times and she didn't so I I
feel like you're freaking vouch for me
she was trying to tell me a joke and
then I ran away from her oh yeah Kiara
also could have killed me but didn't
know
I have no idea because I didn't see
Ollie at all and I was like at the left
side
the whole time yeah it was mostly down
below
[Music]
I don't know I'm just like saying uh so
probably saying that you are nearby the
the place I just like thinking oh true
I'm true
but I I don't remember I saw Muna Senpai
in the middle-ish or on the left side
[Music]
mm-hmm
that's a lot of people
oh my mouse
Spider-Man actors rotoscoped into Mario
Kart pretty funny what
hello
where's your what my date I made a great
appointment
oh I see
I don't know what she said date
look up hey oh
hi hey
okay
[Music]
oh that's not a task
what's this
oh right there's this I was just gonna
do one two three four
eight two three five eight
okay what's that I don't know I like
doing tasks
supposed to wait what
the pointing at this stop it oh I
already did it right
hey hi
oh ice cream
yeah do you
yeah good yeah
pretty good
yeah yeah
hello person
mom
why did you vote for yourself
I don't know
think long and hard about this decision
fellow crewmate
hmm
I have a tablet
probably
you know for me you
oh my God
[Music]
um
anybody else
[Music]
I was on the way to the kitchen so any
any sooner I would have found the body
but I'm from the engine room I saw you I
saw you at the right side of the map
going up
because I was doing classes
oh okay cool wait girl
all I want to say is that before it was
called
um
I'll explain my route I went cargo bay
uh for the you know small thing and then
I went to the showers because you know
that those are a two-part task after the
shower I went towards the main hall
engine room Communications because I
have thoughts in the kitchen and viewing
deck and then I was about to turn to the
Armory and then Bob
[Music]
and I was like I went like what
about that
foreign
[Music]
meep
I guess you didn't want to talk
oh
you know what I want to oh it's in my
task never mind
can I go this way
house
towels
the towels hey no no no no no you're
weird I have a weird feeling of it you
smell weird
you can't go that way
no you smell weird you smell weird
[Music]
no um
we were met in here and you're going
that way I'm going down what happened I
don't know whatever I mean maybe no
look at all the towels
I gotta do that
nope it's just darker outlined for some
reason what's the drama
oh they're gone
uh my mouth keeps getting stuck because
of the
um
cable
should I look for
hmm what else do I got oh absolutely
wait where's this
like
tuition is usually right
I have an intuition
wait where'd you go
let's see
[Laughter]
are you actually are you are you
bluffing
stand still to find out
huh hello hi
to get there
I got here oh that's all I get here wait
again
[Music]
[Applause]
wait where
when I was I was just doing the stinky
electrical test with Anya and I ran into
Renee and mume
I'm following girls
that's uh technically that's true
I think these three a two Row in the
back is always you guys always spots
salsa but rainy why yeah right
it wasn't me it wasn't even me reporting
I don't know where the body is this time
shifters don't forget shapeshifters why
not let it go guys
where was it
wait I want to ask uh Arena where are
you at I'm at Medical I came from cargo
bay
um what with Muna Muna was like going
from bottom to up oh yeah I saw her in
the cargo bank and where was the body
I literally
how about Watson I was with Muna Senpai
for a little bit but then I was down by
electrical like down the ladder that's
where I was coming up when it was
reported
always so afraid of me or is she just
afraid of everybody you just desert some
type of content I was thinking the same
order for me last time the body I voted
for myself
wait so do we have an answer where the
body was I missed it probably yeah
where's it where's the body was I was
gonna see
the body both the body is and the um
[Music]
I don't know what should I choose um
oh
this is what I get for being a creepy I
guess no I was being friendly wait what
they all decided
you sillies I think it's raining
why does he keep telling me to go there
no you're not moving
what about me I want to take a bath in
the coin so I can be rich
and she's not kidding
sorry where are they what I do you
didn't do anything which is why it sucks
why are you running oh okay why
not
dance
oh wait they're not oh
what the heck
I was in the cockpit
oh
yeah
okay okay
[Music]
she literally didn't see me the entire
time
she knows that I don't do anything she
knows
[Music]
you know sometimes you just have a
feeling
but you know you don't want to do what
you did to me because
I have to wait here
you don't want to assume you know
okay now we will never ever okay who
should we never listen to again we'll
never listen to
um
[Music]
I definitely wasn't ready then I thought
it was her maybe but oh my God these two
are diabolicals
doppelganger of me
so yeah
cheers
before that I was in a cupquake with you
know with gura and then and then rainy
come and say she got she's so double
Ginger of me
so I didn't know so somebody was
pretending to be you I did see you
running from Moon
[Music]
but but she didn't kill me neither
no
[Music]
oh no
maybe perhaps perhaps it's really a
um
no more tasks
it's stop telling me to go please thank
you
are you the guardian angel
oh no one hates me
playing with moon I was real weird
I think
coins or pods
the real fun in the game is messing with
everybody oh wait can you guys hear me I
hope not
waiting do I wait do I leave or do I
wait
wow
I wonder why people kept aggressively
trying to frame me you know yeah that's
pretty hard to watch yeah it was really
hard it was so easy to do
oh my gosh I'm getting face expressions
like I was like alive and then I saw
something I wasn't supposed to sleep
[Applause]
[Music]
it was really nice
quick I'm gonna I'm gonna actually a
little quick hold on wait hi okay
nice I got faces if I buy some clothes
[Music]
maybe if I wear clothes yeah maybe it's
not her yeah
I have a question on there because I
heard you in the in the selection screen
where you choose where to go next I
heard you say something that sounded
like something
might have been acting
[Music]
hello
oh my God are we waiting for Muna right
now I'm back already
[Music]
yes
you see it's like the Webkinz bun onion
wait what the [\h__\h] bun tomato onion
onion fun yeah
oh that's loud
can I go this way
this one
this way I gotta go in this way
nope wrong room this way
let's see
I want to speed on my tasks
I also want to stalk people
stop
I should do my tasks
hi
sell it to me
okay you hear me do you hear me
oh you know the location
uh yeah uh going to the Armory
when I want to go to the engine room so
I didn't know I thought we receive from
cockpit or main hall
I think
she went to the left side so she wasn't
yeah she went to the left side yeah she
was in the shower I saw her in the
shower Cali do you have an alibi maybe I
was going out to get service I did pass
you Watson I was worried you were gonna
follow me outside but you didn't
and you probably weren't that worried
since you're outside the service that
are actually right by the body because
uh I was the one who were born yesterday
yeah I couldn't see because it was
really dark
yeah you went on I went up no I went I
didn't see you go up oh just remember
the black fingers are the most sauce out
of everyone okay don't Point anything
and no no I'm skipping I'm skipping your
body so I'm gonna vote for Zetta because
that's very funny
[Music]
I don't know like someone going up but
they didn't
I don't think
so
[Music]
um
why was everybody being so quick to
point
hi Kelly she's truly the sheriff
she's the law this isn't fair because I
called you out no
um
[Music]
why are you following me I'll protect
you on it even after everything you've
done to me I'll protect you
don't pause there
I have stuff to do
[Music]
what happened
it can only be one okay
um
this is a garden angel stuff
man
where's on it
okay wishing this right anyway
I'll protect you
well now it's lit up
there okay
I'll protect you I'll protect you
Zeta does not want to fix the lights
look like now
I was yelling at Kobo the entire time
okay
where's that where's the body uh anybody
or showers
are
[Music]
um
the last time the last time I went near
the shower wait who killed you guys I
saw only
um
with anyone
[Music]
I was getting some Giggles out of Kobo
though yelling at her the entire time so
haunting people does really work like
psychologically
she's innocent yeah listen to me I'm
always us when I'm a crewmate and when
I'm not a crewmate I'm uh not fun so
keep that in mind now you're saucing me
which means I'm a crewmate the reverse
psychology I don't think that's gonna
work oh my god
well then I say it's honor because why
aren't you providing an alibi instead of
Defending yourself huh
[Music]
with only this included room where like
she would have killed me
[Music]
oh
no neither of them
no no no no no no
they've done this to themselves
[Music]
do I have any thought oh I have tasks to
do yes I do what's this oh I'm not
supposed to go there what's this you
download okay
let's see let's see
is it done oh
I should protect somebody right
who wants protection oh they're dead
it's too late for them
make her go crazy
wash my dirty ghost body oh I want to
watch wait no uh no thanks
Guardian Angel go save people I want you
where is our buddy I have to do tasks I
know
oh they're they're running around not
here you
know maybe
um
yeah you you you you yeah you yeah you
you hear me
okay it's Zetta for sure I'm voting
you can't you
roll now yeah because
it could happen to be a detective who's
really good at spotting bodies
some scary things but I don't know man
Rayna could I have killed you or would I
have an idea if I was with you and in
that room for like over 30 seconds
I don't know uh you want me to be honest
um what you said was oh just kidding I
was just waiting for my cool down yeah
but I was already in the room
and that's what Watson does Watson
always jokes
can anyone uh give an alibi to Jada
no
no no but it can give out running away
from the body well Raina and I were both
up in the room like in the meeting room
and then as I went down I was throwing
it the whole time and then we saw Zayna
pass Us in that hallway yeah
[Music]
it's in like near defense if I die
that's not me
okay 30 seconds 30 seconds I'm sorry
guys
[Laughter]
10 seconds
oh
wait why'd cobal vote for
uh-oh
[Music]
oh it's very funny
oh my gosh
we were in Foster together we were
cooked oh my gosh
here oh I gotta protect people
[\h__\h] what is that
wait
where is here I'll find her in a second
I have to do tasks too right oops
all right
that's kind of important be good if I
could find somebody along the way
um
let's see where's everybody
oh no
can I see on here
oh no that's gonna waste time it's
wasting time okay
[Music]
for me
um
[Music]
loud
okay
[Music]
dinosaurs
she's alive
[Music]
thing
separated
[Music]
but why did you mess up why did you keep
messing up that number thing I had to do
the keypad thing for you oh true that
was us it took so long after Cobra went
over to that side but I was on that side
too right on the other side once I was
just being stupid
wait so why do we call this emergency
meeting in the first place just because
because we want to develop you off yes
yes
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
oh no
oh
you know what I'm happy for cold
[Music]
damn it I'm happy for Clover I'm sorry
wait where is everybody I can protect
you
[Music]
um
we just finished my task and I will be
okay
[Music]
I'm sure it's Cobalt now I'm
I'm holding yes
[Music]
Mommy
thanks for you who was it uh I'm not
sure who it was
um but whoever it was I'm going to
do you want to go back
oh
trying to think of something bad but I
feel like any bad thing I can think of
she'll say oh yes please who is it who
killed me I will
yeah
where is everybody I'm going in circles
hey
where's Colville
I don't have any tasks left do I
just go ahead
how do I recruit win come on I finished
all my tasks right away
now I have finished my tasks
wait I have no idea
all right
wait so it wasn't try to senpai
okay
I have no idea
hold on let's call the watch is that it
kill me
do it together
[Music]
I've done all my tasks
is
guys
oh you're dead but that would mean
right now
[Music]
though
Christmas again
[Music]
it was Kobo and it was Global
um
nice good job team nice hustle
oh my God
[Music]
lighting was so intense
but to be honest was so spot-on
yeah
it was kind of funny not gonna lie yeah
that's just her personality it's not
that she's the Imposter that's just her
personality
and I was like doubting myself
that would believe me
[Music]
yeah yeah
um
[Music]
yeah
somebody kill me kill
me kill kill you have to run for the
Imposter kill me kill me kill me
kill me I'm a free kill kill me
please quickly I don't have much time I
have to die soon
you can't kill me oh wait but this means
I can't do task maybe they should just
leave can somebody please no I should
leave
somebody's just gonna be how about
somebody somebody
die how about that
okay
I'm gonna speed around this I don't want
to be useless here technically I have to
go on like 10 minutes or so
you you
I just don't have time for a full game
[Music]
to kill
I can't oh free movie
anybody want to kill a free movie
can I interest you in killing me
okay
um
would you like to see me
foreign I'd like to die please
pretty please
I'm tired of living
yeah over there
[Music]
oh my God
whoa
[Music]
I want to die
watch her die
I want
[Music]
the game
I will give you until the next meeting
and then all right all right okay this
combo wanna talk about it because she
reported so yeah sorry yeah oh yeah yeah
where was the body where did you find
the body Cobble I found the body in
front of
Communications between Communications
and Communications and I was oh I was uh
um
I don't think um
[Music]
the last time I saw Cali was somewhere
all right we'll give you until the next
meeting okay can you kill as many people
as you can okay
[Music]
oh I forgot to votes
hello tell me tell me
okay wait till my cool down okay okay
I'll be over here
waiting
I was up there
kill me huh
maybe it's not global
I want to die
I want more babies here
um
do you want to be my daughter I want to
die
[Music]
um
I'll need a new daughter she's my
daughter scared of me I can still be
your daughter I just be dead
or I'll come here okay do it
thank you
thank you thank you
thank you thank you bye
bye-bye bye bye thank you
oh did I give it away
okay I gotta go
I go now bye bye everyone thank you for
watching I hope you have fun they're
still playing
foreign
[Music]