[Music]
do
sup of the morning to you
[Music]
what's up
good morning
do we have deep voice bae today kind i
don't know and also what is with you
guys you have zero faith in me
it was like literally two minutes i was
late by two minutes and then a chat was
like goku randolco radoco bruh
bruh
have a little bit more faith in me zero
faith
[Laughter]
i need a note explaining why i was late
bro
[Laughter]
good morning i hope you guys are doing
well
we just missed you too much i haven't
streamed in three days
i was hibernating for three days
um
i mean i was also
um doing other stuff for three days um
being kind of stressed for three days um
we have we have a situation we have a
situation welcome to the rat pack hoo-ha
hold on i haven't had my coffee yet um
also damn sicko thank you so much for
the
big
uh
i literally brain buffered about what
what what why are there so many reds
what's going on
uh my brain just buffered for a second
trying to figure out what color it was
congrats on second place and zucker
absolutely amazing job thank you so much
thank you
[Music]
uh
something about wanting to watch me i
don't know the last bit like yeah
thank you um
thank you so much for that
less than zero faith but happy you made
it welcome back
thank you so much thank you thank you
thank you
deep voice bae doko it's right here
hello
hello deep voice bae hello um
my raspy voices no okay here's the thing
i
i i haven't done anything i was
literally in bed i opened i turned on my
pc four minutes before the stream
started
jumping
ain't that a mood you're right
did beasty bother you yet today we have
a situation with beastie guys um
okay i was originally gonna hibernate
anyway over the weekend because i feel
like last week was just very intense
like very very intense
ah
um
sorry the first sip of coffee is always
the best
um is bc okay yes and no um so last week
was already really intense as in like i
streamed 12 times i feel like that's the
most i've ever streamed in a week
now why do i do this to myself i don't
know
um also i feel like deep voice baby is
leaving us pretty pretty pretty uh fast
today so
i'm sorry i'm sorry you just have to
deal with normal bait okay
it was a good training arc yeah yeah
yeah yeah but um
i heard that you screamed 12 times last
week
um but yeah i mean 12 times it's quite a
lot for
one week yeah was it 12 times i don't
know it was over 10 times i'm pretty
sure um so i was gonna take you know the
weekend off just to relax anyway
um but then
on the day of the mario kart what do you
call it um on the day of the mario kart
tournament
we had a situation for with beastie and
it kind of set me into a slight panic
um and major stress
but um
yeah that was that that was a ride also
chad died bruh i just started the stream
can you please not stop sabotaging me
okay
[Music]
hold up let me fix chat
bum bum
hello
please load
[Music]
there we go
yes yes we have many things to talk
about today but i just wanted to um
start off with this story um
okay what's the situation okay the
situation is this we're back hello um so
on the day of the mario kart tournament
so
uh
i was in group d which was the last
tournament which started at
3 00 pm jst
uh which was five o'clock for me
um we had like the um
what you call it i think i was playing
mario kart with um
holly en like we were just training
beforehand um and it was before the time
we had to go
meet up and do a briefing so we had a
briefing session like with uh the whole
other holla members at around i think it
was
12 30
wait no yes 12 30 my time which was in
the afternoon um so
we had the freaking
uh briefing and then we were playing a
little bit of mario kart and then i was
like i'm gonna go check on beastie for a
second guys i'll be right back now keep
in mind this is two hours two hours
before i was meant to race okay are we
there yes okay
two hours okay keep that in mind and i
was already very kind of like nervous
because you know i was streaming as well
but also i was just nervous because of
the tournament and i was already feeling
a lot of things
so i went out and i was checking on
beastie and she was on the bed and then
she looked up at me and her left eye was
literally so swollen and red to the
point where it was kind of flipped
inside out like you know how when you
rub your eyes so much that like it kind
of like
it like it flips like
like the bottom flips and like her pupil
was pushed all the way to the corner
literally i looked at her i was like
what is wrong with your eye
what the heck
and then i freaked out i freaked out
because obvio it was like it was so
swollen it looked like there was
something inside of her eye like it was
so swollen um so i kind of panicked um
panicked because i
well one panic because of her eye but
two panning this was two hours before i
meant to you know take part in this
really big collab um and i was meant to
be streaming in it as well
so i immediately caught up my vet and my
vet was like sorry we don't have space
and i'm like bruh
and then the
receptionist was like you can try like
other nearby vets and then i called
nearby vets and even nearby vets were
like nah we don't have space i'm like
bruh wait bro
so i took her to emergency services um
and they were like yeah we're only
seeing emergency cases at the moment but
uh i booked you in with the
ophthalmologist with the eye doctor here
and i'm like okay okay can i come in now
because it's her eyeball like it's not
like like any other like i feel like i'm
i was more panicked because it was her
eyeball because i feel like the eyes are
you know most a very important part to
any living being you know like if
something's wrong with the eye it can
lead to very serious things you know
um
so
i took her i raced her to the emergency
um and
then you know we were there and
on the way there i could see that the
eye was like slowly
like kind of
calming down like it wasn't as swollen
anymore but it's very obvious that there
was still something there
um
and this was right before the tournament
yeah yeah yeah i was messaging manitan
and i was like can you please let
someone know i may have not i don't i
have an emergency i don't i don't i
don't know if i'm going gonna be back in
time um but anyway i took uh beastie to
the uh to the vet and then that had a
look and then they
literally took two looks at her and the
um
the head ophthalmologist doctor was like
yeah she has um
burpees
she has cat burpees
she has cat herpes
um and it was just a flare
so i freaked out i was like burpees what
what
cat herpes what burpees what
[Music]
oh my god
no no i just said babies because it
sounds funny she has she has cat herpes
um which is not contagious uh only to
other cats herpes yeah um it's okay i've
heard that it's similar to
conjunctivitis in humans um or like cold
sores on your lip if you're a woman so
it's not that big of a deal it just it
just flares
um it's very common um the vet was like
yeah 80 of cats have the hippies and uh
90 of strays have hoppies yeah um
but it's a very specific strain of like
and it's only it only affects cats
um
and then
i was like okay well that makes me feel
a little bit better as long as it's not
like something you know very serious and
then the doctor was like yeah it's
because she was a stray she probably
picked it up when she was a baby and
then um it was probably dormant until it
flared up you know and anything can
trigger a flare something very small or
something big um so
they were like it's nothing that you did
wrong it's just you know um beasty
because beastie was a stray she probably
picked it up um
[Music]
you tell me
welcome oh my god rap god whoa
what's up
i worship hello oh my god
oh my god oh my god
yeah yeah yeah yeah um
so they explained that it was kind of
like conjunctivitis in humans um i
wouldn't know i'm a rat but
like it's kind of like a like a it yeah
it so it flares in the eye bowl
and in this discharge and it gets really
red and stuff but they took a look at
her and then they were like i'm gonna
give you some medication uh and then
some ointment and she should be good in
two weeks and i'm like thank you oh my
god what conversation did you walk into
my cat has herpes
yeah so overall she's okay but um
it was just very
like it was a lot happening within a
very small time frame um so i kind of
erased it to the vet and then i raced
home and it was 30 minutes before
um i had to race for mario kart so i
made it back in time but
like i feel like that kind of attributed
to my disgraceful performance in the
prelims because i was just so frazzled
um
god
race to vet raced home race tomorrow cut
let's go
yeah thank god i was in group d
um respect
um
i was frazzled yeah so
uh that's what happened and then um i
i took the last three days um i was
hibernating because i was kind of
recuperating after the wreck of streams
but i was also taking care of beastie
because um beastie's ointment has to be
applied three times a day and i have to
apply the ointment literally in her
eyeball and nobody likes things in the
eyeball so it's literally like a resting
not wrestling wrestling match every
single time i have to do it and then i
have to give her medication uh two times
a day which is forcing a pill down her
throat basically uh because it's too
hard for her to bite so i have to like
drop it down her throat
um
and i just have to monitor her and make
sure that she doesn't really rub her
eyeball um so i haven't been sleeping
pretty much
um
windows talk about a job bruh what's up
welcome to the right pack
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
um it can't be crushed with it no they
would they the the vet instructed me to
like it yeah to drop it down her throat
and then swallow it and then have her
eat right afterwards is she in the cone
of shame no okay the vet gave me a cone
of shame but then they were like oh i
don't really want to put her on beastie
because she's so young it's gonna be
very traumatic
yeah i mean she's getting used to like
me giving her well the medication's
still a little bit rough because it's
literally forcing a pill down her throat
or like you know a bit of a pill down
the throat but the cream she's getting
uh ointment she's getting a lot used to
me putting ointment in her eyeball now
so she's doing good she's doing good
not much room for rest during this
weekend after all kind yeah yeah i yeah
my schedule nowadays is i
i sleep and god knows what time and then
i wake up at uh like five to six to feed
her medication and food go back to bed
for like an hour or so and then eight
o'clock i have to wake up and give her
ointment and then i sleep until god
knows when until i have a stream pretty
much
streamer hours let's go
[Music]
ah
ointment probably feels nice um i don't
think so because the first couple of
times i did it she was really like
what kind of cat is beasty i don't know
she was a stray
ah
yeah
so
oh my gosh so many new members what's up
welcome to the rat pack
um could you do that noise again what my
cat my my beastie impersonation
[Laughter]
um and i've also realized that i don't
know whether it's because she's just at
that age where she wants to be pampered
or she's just not feeling the best like
because she is sick she wants to be
pampered she will literally
sit outside my door and meow
and then she won't eat her food unless
i'm holding the bowl for her
oh
yeah
so needy cat and then now we should
uncle before she used to snuggle like at
my head like i told you obesity would
fall asleep at my feet now she needs to
fall asleep in my arms
baby
are you holding her now no
no no bc's know him when i stream
because she'll start scaling the walls
and then no
that's very dangerous
ah
um
yeah so that was the big story that i
wanted to tell you and it's kind of the
reason why i also took yesterday off as
well uh just because yeah
[Music]
what
thank you so much for the red zipper
thank you so much
english is difficult
[Music]
man
it's the morning it's early okay i need
i need help i've only had one sip of
coffee yo
[Music]
oh
okay um so that was so i wanted to tell
you uh which is why i didn't stream
yesterday as well but i i really i miss
streaming guys
i'm missing me i miss you guys it's only
been three days and i miss you guys um
so first i want to thank the super chats
from the mario kart streams
um
[Music]
and then we can talk about this week and
the stuff we have planned
the feelings meet you uh thank you thank
you thank you thank you
hmm
[Music]
you're
you're as beautiful as the day i lost
you man yo i see you i see you with them
quartz
i can't do a scottish accent you're as
beautiful as the day i lost you i don't
know how to say the last bit
i see you
you based
based
coaching best okay
i see that reference
[Music]
thank you good luck thank you thank you
uh that said thank you it's time unleash
toxic tarot jokes aside good luck bae
thank you thank you thank you so much
thank you
um
murph laser thank you let's go bae show
these guys that you can go toe to toe
with hollow life's best i couldn't
i i couldn't i
couldn't but
yeah dang
i tried um
alessandro thank you rats rats we're the
rats we pray at night we still cannot
wear the rats yeah
preacher boy
um i also saw the clip i didn't realize
that uh they caught
i saw the clip of pawasoma and uh aitan
reacting to my um
to my to my molding
oh that was funny
uh gfi thank you so much b it's time to
go to work in korea can you read this
for the people who work hard today
um
[Music]
uh
[Laughter]
um
the what do you call it oh yeah i was
molding i saw the clip where i was just
saying i hate this game i hate this game
i hate this game and then they saw it
and i was like oh no
oh no
oh i hate this map that's what i was
saying yeah
it was so actually you know the comedic
thing is that it's like as soon as like
you know they were commentating on how i
was first and that i was saying i hate
this map as soon as the screen changed i
literally got hit with everything and i
got pushed to eighth and then yeah
they literally didn't see the rage they
saw the mould but they didn't see the
rage
they saw the salt but they didn't see
the rage
[Music]
see them reacting to cali yeah i did
that was really funny
that was funny as well
yeah
the timing of that entire stream let's
not talk about that literally oh my god
i don't understand timing
man
[Music]
you had a good showing overall thank you
thank you i'm glad you enjoyed
as i'm glad you thought sir oh no thank
you zoom zoom you've got this bed thank
you he likes
we're going let's go
oh nestor thank you so much for the pink
super chat boom boom bc funs give that
kitty cat a smooch for me as i hope she
gets well soon ah thank you you're so
sweet thank you thank you so much thank
you
oh
[Music]
you tried to focus but you got focused
oh that's pretty funny
um
here to welcome to the wrap pack
welcome welcome welcome welcome
um bingham thank you
sure obey that rat bro bus got oh he
cheering for you can do it thank you
um
thank you so much for the red super boom
boom boom go go go thank you
itami thank you so much for the pink
super as well oh my god thank you so
much
um
hey
oh my god dude
hi thank you so much for joining us
oh my gosh
oh my god i'm in the presence of gods
i'm in the presence of so many gods how
do you say god in korean
bow down to the gods
[Music]
um
envious gaming thank you bae i know you
can do this you are great and the best
uh member ever you got it
ah
thank you thank you he who devours as
bad as it may be this race your rage is
adorable thank you
thank you
um dairy way galaxy thank you even if
you hate this game i still respect you
for giving it your best out there thank
you
thank you
um dougie five five five thank you you
gave it your old is always next to you
thank you oka no mine thank you
um no matter you're still number one in
our hearts thank you thank you very much
your rage was funny well i'm glad you
found it funny
i lost
i i was damaged emotionally and mentally
because of that that tournament
[Music]
ah
um
droid lover thank you based on you to
make a custom thumbnail for the taco
copy thumbs up for effort oh yeah i
zoomed that thumbnail
i'm glad i'm glad you guys liked it um
jerry thank you
um
thank you so much for the red super
again boom boom
boom
um
[Music]
mario kart is an rng game don't blame
yourself you know i said i was never
going to play the game again but now i
have an inkling to play mario kart
you know for the two days after the
tournament i was dreaming about mario
kart
i was i had i could visualize the drifts
i was dreaming about the racing it was
bad that's how you know you've played
too much mario kart
yeah that's bad it's bad it's it's bad
i kind of i kind of feel like i haven't
i have the
itch to play mario kart now
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
thank you i'm betting my friend emil
that you place at least top three well
i'm glad you got a free meal
um
[Music]
thank you wishing you luck in the
tournament also wishing no i'm not not
you didn't get me
no gothams no
no shouldn't bread thank you first place
i believe thank you
five thank you do the job babes your
destiny no
no we did we didn't do the jump we we
didn't do the jump
starter speaking korean
look it's early okay sometimes the
languages don't register yet
the the doesn't register in the brain
small brain i'm sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
doctor
helga thank you used to jump bathe the
jumpers with no we didn't use the jump
um
xenomorph thank you she's starting to
believe i did start to believe
red frame thank you so much for the red
super chat boom boom boom second base
zakota i did i became i came second
place my mom was too strong
i also saw her reaction when i used what
i um also i used the the boom box thingy
uh and she was like how could you do
this to your mother it was funny it was
quite funny
um itchy thank you
um tifton the chocolate thank you
uh nubsco thank you i always believed
thank you
um john joe thank you
um congratulations mate what a
satisfying conclusion thank you
thank you
fire heart thank you congratulations on
second base thank you
never had a doubt in my mind ah
ah
a burpee
um seth set thank you congratulations
bae second place dakota with the clutch
i will drink to your victory thank you
thank you thank you thank you um
[Music]
uh exerciser thank you
yayoi thank you podium taro congrats
sorry mama taro
uh two
[Music]
that says thank you congratulations on
second place thank you kamen writer
thank you
mia getting into zaka was a fluke
congrats to the best true zako zako taro
you're right thank you so much
turtle cubes thank you let's go me thank
you and bing kong thank you so much uh
zucko cup congratulations on
second place bae you did it very nice
thank you so much
thank you so much welcome to the right
back hoo ha
welcome welcome
ah
okay and that should be all the
suppers let's talk about
the schedule this week actually no i
don't want to talk about that yet i want
to talk about
new outfits
i wanna talk i wanna talk about the new
outfit did you guys watch myths outfits
oh my god
oh my gosh
oh my gosh they're so beautiful
they're so beautiful
they're so pretty they're so cute it was
amazing
and um yeah so if you guys didn't know
um knock it down in the calendars this
week we have council review new
commander outfits for the new year
let's go
let's go let's go
short hair cali has awakened something
in me
i knew i i i was literally so hyped for
kelly's one because i remember she
showed me uh like a draft or no she
didn't show me a draft she showed me
like the finished uh like kimono and
then as soon as i saw the short hair i
was like
oh my god
amazing amazing i'm so yes short hair
based
[Music]
mika mama is gonna blow this one out of
the park i already know you're gonna be
beautiful thank you
well i will say i'm i'm oh i'm always
beautiful
i'm always beautiful but i'm just saying
you know there is something there is a
certain appeal about uh kimonos you know
i said i'm okay i'm gonna stop now
cringe stop
[Laughter]
um but yeah no i really like it i'm
really really excited uh to show you
guys um and amiga mama worked so hard on
it and i love it i love it so much
i love it so much
myths review with twin tail heaven i'm
twin tails look
mine are not really
cute twin tails they just i woke up like
this twin tails look at this i got two
tails
[Music]
um but yeah so we have the outfield
review uh
on the weekend in a couple days and then
we have a council club right after it's
been so long since we've had a council
collab
[Music]
i missed the council collabs um we were
all literally like playing mine uh not
mine mario kart this is the thing cronie
i caronia cronie i and i wait what am i
saying cronie iris and i always have
this weird thing of calling mario kart
minecraft
i think we were talking about mario kart
as we were playing and then crony
suddenly said minecraft and she was like
yeah why do i keep saying minecraft and
i'm like i feel you bro it's fine
oh i feel you
i feel
[Music]
yeah you're right
mariocraft i think she said minecart
um or i said minecart i don't know it
was funny
[Music]
um so we got the council collab and then
what else are we doing this week i feel
like i'm also taking this week this this
week kind of chill because last week i
had 12 streams what am i streaming this
week i never know what my schedule is
like i i never know what my schedule is
um
oh we have a monster hunter
i'm very excited about that we have a
monster hunter um collab stream with the
flames i've never played monster hunter
before so i'm very excited um and then
we have more
we have a member stream we're gonna
watch for the next four episodes of
nitio
uh we're gonna be watching fauna play
the resident evil 7 dlc which is going
to be fun um
[Music]
a very chill week of seven do i have
seven streams what one two three four
five six oh
oh
i i didn't realize that seven oh
[Music]
look okay i'm i have two days i i had
three days off that's pretty chill
that's pretty chill isn't it
man kevin welcome to the rapper
a big cute hug from peru thank you
you have three streams on the 16th you
right
but i don't think the council club's
gonna be on my channel so that doesn't
count also resident evil is also not on
my channel so that doesn't count either
both you and kelly casually forgetting
you booked seven streams for the week
wait what
really is that what cali said
[Laughter]
[Music]
right seriously
bruh
[Music]
this is confirmed
sister's confirmed
this is confirmed it runs in the family
cali got soft bonked for trying to book
four streams in one day i mean i would
soft bonk her too that's too much
three streams a day is kind of i feel
like the max you should do four streams
a day nah i feel like that's too much
and besides the new year outfit also
doesn't really count as a stream because
that's only 30 minutes because it's a
relay so it's kind of short so it
doesn't really count and also it's a new
review i don't know
i don't know
[Music]
and also that time cali was doing yeah
she was only enduring streams which is
different it's different
yeah
base justifying
no no no no no i mean i i definitely
think you know cali kelly kind of is a
bit too much because she was streaming
like each of them were like eight hour
streams like really long streams you
know so but mine these are like you know
baby streams it doesn't count doesn't
matter
[Laughter]
[Music]
enabling the problem
no it's okay nothing happened
what jump king does to you
yeah i've been getting pushed by people
to play jump king because i've
i think i first said to cali i was
thinking of playing jump king apple whoa
welcome to the rep bag bow down to the
right guard
[Music]
um don't play it i don't know it kind of
looks strangely fun
i feel the first one looks strangely fun
anyway um who else did i say planet i
saw uh i know some of my friends are
playing it i've seen cali play it and
then
uh i i watched coyote play it and then i
watched asta senpai play it oh watch
some of them i didn't save it for the
whole thing but i saw that they were
playing it
and
ollie played it as well yeah yeah yeah
so i'm just like every time i've like
seen someone play it i'm just like
oh should i play it i feel like i should
play it
did you know how to play it as well oh
damn
i still stream was fun yeah it was
i said the senpai stream was so funny i
mean i think i i popped in to say like
uh good luck or whatever and then
uh astor senpai was like oh have you
played jump king and i'm like no i'm too
scared to and then he was like what
there's nothing scary about this game
look look at these jumps oh my god
they're so fun look we jump here oh my
god it's so fun i've never seen such a
fun game look we jump here oh my god so
fun
[Laughter]
and i think it was um a part where he
was stuck on man it was funny
[Music]
no i can't say that that's rude
did i say idaho senpai
no
i didn't say that did i say that
i said
did i say senpai
uh-oh
sorry the tongue slip of the tongue i
said ask still i'm pretty sure i said i
still but i will
i don't think i did i'm pretty sure i
said aster said bye and i just said
okay
you know that's something i'm actually
i'm kind of like i think it's going to
slip out at least once is if i ever ever
collab with gen 6 um i feel like i'm
going to accidentally call one of them
senpai because i feel like
um whenever i collab with a holo jp
member everyone is a senpai except for
gen 6 so i feel like
i feel like i'm gonna accidentally
call one of them senpai's
yeah
[Music]
there you're pawn is showing up lately
laplacian no
no no no i don't think i'd ever call
laplace said but no no no no no
i think out of gen 6 i think i'm the
most i feel like i would call lui lui
senpai by accident
i think she's the most
um
easiest person that i would probably
call senpai by accident
dewey does give us that like senpai vibe
though yeah doing it
i think about i think if i caught doing
it then it's like
you know
and also like once i hear them call me
senpai i'm just like eh okay i can't we
can't could be calling each other senpai
that's just weird
[Music]
iris already called her senpai really
bro iris what are you doing bro
speaking of virus i had a what do you
call it i was in a cold with iris for
like a couple hours the other night it
was really good
man
i love like this is something that i
feel like i just i need i i want to you
know let everybody know like i'm
so i'm such good friends with like
uh like you know holla en that i'm just
like haha yeah be jealous chat that's
right yeah we play games off stream we
talk off stream hahaha we have cause of
stream
will you watch mommy hope 6 month
no
wait when is that
wait when is that hold on i know it's
yesterday oh my god yes
uh bad wife um i'm sorry iris i
definitely knew i
i definitely knew up
yes i'm gonna be watching of course what
are you talking about
duh
[Music]
they exposed life no i didn't forget no
i didn't forget
oh it's fine it's fine everything's fine
oh okay they're uh talking
talking i didn't forget no i just
i was i was i was just a bit hazy i was
hazy i was hazy
hazy about the day and time and when
it's been a rough couple of days okay
guys call me some slack thank you
[Music]
i didn't forget i just forgot
um oh uh speaking of new outfits um i
wanna i need to come up with a hashtag
because i wanna see all your predictions
i've never done a new outfit reveal
before so i have no idea how it goes um
i'm also trying to cram a lot in 30
minutes but we'll see how that goes um i
do we create like a hashtag so people
can send in their um
what do you call it like
predictions or something
[Music]
oh no
i was thinking kimono taro but that's
kind of long hashtag kimono taro
oh my god drip taro bruh
wait i need to see if drip taro is taken
as a hashtag
drip taro
bay mono's also pretty cute
okay i'm gonna make a poll
your outfit hashtag
[Music]
drip taro
or
what's another one what was it bae mono
they mono sound i feel like if i use
drip tara i can consistently just reuse
the hashtag if i ever have new outfits
but
um
[Music]
baymona might be cute as well though
oh bay mayonnaise is not taken but what
about i like the new bay who this
new bay
who is
oh wait never mind okay that that that
hashtag is taken
um
that's a stream title oh okay never mind
okay we'll stick with bait with bay
mooner then how about that
drip tarai or bay mono
[Music]
okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
oh
thank you
joey thank you so much for the pink
super chat boom boom congrats to the
true champion of zuckercup your training
paid off also pet care fun thank you
thank you so much thank you thank you
[Music]
uh let me just explain in the english
and then the japanese
for people who are watching um i'm sorry
i can't explain in korean though um so
basically i have a new outfit release uh
on the weekend and i know a lot of
people like drawing their predictions
based on the silhouette um and i wanted
to create a hashtag where you guys can
just send it there and i can easily
filter through them um and that's what
we're choosing at the moment
is
foreign
[Laughter]
bae what's your opinion on oat milk i've
never had oatmeal before
now we gotta explain drip to the
japanese viewers
a slowly confusing jp verse
[Music]
oh
i don't really think drip is something
that they need to
in particularly learn it's like
literally teaching someone it's like how
martin learned money senpai learnt based
super lit it's like you know it's not
really helpful but like i mean sure if
you wanna if you if you wanna learn it
just
[Laughter]
[Music]
tango
it
[Music]
i just learned a new japanese word what
the heck okay that's kind of weird what
that's kind of cool but it's kind of
weird so there's a japanese word or
shade which means like stylish and
apparently there's a slang which they
think it's
like similar to drip is where they put
the o at the end of the word apart from
like rather than the beginning and
becomes
wow is that the drip equivalent maybe
maybe
yeah
[Music]
um
just got us two new nicknames no
no no no
i mean but if you look at it it just
becomes share otaro which means it's
like it's like what
[Music]
sounds unironically nice
man
all righty
well i think drip tar is winning so i'm
going to close that right now
[Music]
so i think i might put out the
um
silhouette with the
wait hasn't do we post ourselves how do
i do this i'm so confused
how do i do i post the silhouette with
the hashtag and say give me give me give
me your predictions is that what i do
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh okay
might have to ask senpai just in case
yeah you're right i might ask callie
charlie nancha how do i do this i've
never done this before
still can't get over the fact you've
never had oat milk bruh i've never had
oat milk
i've heard like people go crazy over
oatmeal but i've never tried it before
[Music]
post the wrong silhouette by accident
ahaha
yeah i see you oh that would be so funny
wouldn't it
yeah just accidentally post not the
silhouette oh i get it
[Laughter]
oat milk is better than almond milk i
don't like almond milk i feel like it
tastes weird
almond milk tastes weird it also smells
weird
why do you keep saying bro so much
because bruh
literally it's a it's a expression that
can be used in so many different
scenarios bruh it can be used when
you're feeling disappointed
brah when you're feeling like let down
bruh when you're feeling confused bruh
when you when you're trying to when
you're feeling very judgmental bruh
when you're feeling excited
brah see bruh is the way of life
now children what does bra stand for
bay's rats unite here okay that's why
bruh it's very versatile yes
it's a bruh moment
it's not bro it's brah
b-r-u-h
the bra
[Laughter]
the english language is a wonderful
nightmare bruh see it can be used in any
scenario can we have an asmr bra
how do you do an asmr bro hold on let me
just
wait
so i get real close is that how
to the mic
bruh
is that how i do it
[Music]
i don't think my mic is suited for asmr
but
[Music]
robin thank you so much for the pink
switch boom boom or fake milk like oat
and almond or garbage should be launched
into the sun i mean if people enjoy them
people enjoy it
[Music]
was that too loud wait let me try it
again
you have to whisper it i don't know how
to do asmr four nine can you help me
bruh
this is how you do asmr
[Laughter]
there's no binaural mic this is not an
asmr mic
that was good but the first one was
better so you have to be louder i'm
confused
let's try again
bruh
that how you do it
[Music]
i don't know
red frame thank you so much for the pink
super hey no hating on almond milk
people can enjoy what they want yeah
you're right
i mean it's not for me but if you like
it you like it
simple more for you
jupiter thank you so much for the rest
of your boom boom
i don't have a mic to do asmr
i don't have a monkey to eat tomorrow i
want to buy this 3d asmr
you don't need a fancy mic really
but i don't know how to like does that
mean enough to tweak the settings
um because like sometimes it cuts in and
out because of the noise gate and stuff
fauna said you don't i'm going to ask
for for now how do you enjoy
i will absolutely die on this milk hill
how the hell can you milk something with
no
tkb anyway i don't know
i don't know you tell me i don't know
salted bread thank you so much for the
pink super boom boom i will send it to
bro
witnessed
bruh what are you doing bro
[Music]
hey this is my first super want to say
you're fun to watch
[Laughter]
bruh you witnessed
breath
same sickle bro
you suck bruh
um
base new reaction to red surface it went
from bam bam to what a deal to bruh
[Music]
dingle thank you so much for the super
chat
bruh babble thank you so much for the
super chat
[Music]
wtf some bird or something is screaming
outside my window and it sounds like a
terrible impression of your asmr bruh
bruh just tell that bird to
you know
just get out of here go home
dancing pfp thank you so much for the
super chat milk stream let's go
cockroach
i didn't need to know that bro what are
you doing stop
stop that's gross
you should tell that's a fauna don't
tell me
uh what else do i want to talk about
wait um we get sidetracked very easily
here whoa
i don't know what just happened um
so we talked about any outfits oh
google we did the hashtag oh maybe was
that it
schedule i feel like that's already had
schedule i i kind of feel like we went
through the schedule
we went from new outfits to bra asmr
[Music]
mango reading oh yeah i'm reading manga
for the first time i've always wanted to
do a live manga reading um
do you guys want to know what manga i'm
reading
i've never read nor watched the anime um
for this and i'm very excited because i
know that a lot of people like it
um we are reading
[Music]
himoto kimoto
himalto
solar leveling bruh
we're gonna read himoto because i have
never what i've never read it nor have i
watched it so um
um
i can't wait to act like a um to voice
act literally from like
say so to like gucky
maximum gremlin
yeah
gremlin voice
so
i'm excited
i'm excited i'm very excited
why food thank you so much for upgrading
to wreck god bow down to the god
everybody also i'm so sorry that i said
your name was
w-y-f-u to to begin with i i don't know
why i didn't sound it out
[Music]
i'm sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry
it's fine bae reading english letters is
hot no
[Music]
don't you dead egg or jersey me what the
heck who do you think you are
you right
did you see kiara's fortune reading of
you no i didn't
what did she say what she say what's my
fortune
am i gonna die
[Music]
where's my fortune i wanna read my
fortune
[Music]
hello i read your fortune am i gonna die
am i gonna die
should i tell you in a call oh would you
like to
would you like to we might have guest
appearance kiwawa
i love i love that name by the way
please allow me to call you kiwawa
senpai
by senpai it's so cute
bear hunker what's up upgraded to rap
boss we got a boss up in here
we have guest appearance
oh my god wait i'm gonna find a photo of
kiwawa uh
[Music]
wait let me find a picture of you
wait let me send you one because
it's more if it's one of one of the
kimono oh yes yes yes please how are you
doing
i'm doing fine i just had a membership
stream where i ate some shitty snacks
from all over the world
would you be open to maybe one day sent
me like a box filled with australian
snacks yes oh my god i've been wanting
to do that but i've been trying to
figure out how to do it because i don't
know like how to send it
you wanted to send me an australian
snack box i wanted to send everyone
australian sniper everyone
oh
interesting everybody gets a taste um
yeah well i want to send everybody tim
tams
oh tim tams yeah i've heard of that
oh that's a good idea please please oh
god please oh man if if you do that if i
ask you for australian snack box that
probably means you're going to send me a
vegemite huh
i mean
it's customary but like
it's custom it's customary but like if
you don't want it then you know it's
fine
no it must be i must try it it is i
understand it's part of it if there is
no australian snack box without
vengeance yeah i mean okay here's the
thing right when it comes to vegemite
people just people just eat it wrong
like which is why like you see all the
food challenges like they take a spoon
and then they like
like a spoonful of vegemite that
literally i mean that's not that's
that's not even how you would eat
nutella so obviously that's disgusting i
eat nutella
oh um
you shouldn't but okay i mean there's
people like that
that's okay understandable
cool i understand it with nutella
but i mean it's not really recommended
but okay
yeah i mean like then tell us sweet
chocolate that is different um but like
when anyone does like a vegemite eating
like taste testing challenge and they
use a spoon literally every every
australian just dies inside because it's
like you know that's not how you're
meant to eat it but like you're making
it worse for yourself why don't you do
this to yourself
what happened since you are uh
in the land of the down under or
whatever
um
do you know
community channel yes
[Applause]
i [\h__\h] love community channel like
every like five million years ago when
the youtube video quality was still 360p
and we thought that was 4k oh my god i
don't think okay recently she uploaded
some new videos oh did she i know she
uploaded one [\h__\h] back
really
i know you should probably not forever
but last year
like after a long while
she did upload a new one for i think for
christmas or new years or so
two actually i'm gonna watch whiteboard
later bro community channel i don't
think like i think i discovered her
after like she went on break but i kind
of went so late yeah but then i binged
all of her
oh she's so funny
yeah i i figured you know um i thought
that she would be like very famous among
australians um
at least like as a at least back then
maybe not now anymore but i think back
then she was like me proud most likely
the most famous influencer in australia
back then when the word influenza wasn't
really a thing yeah yeah yeah
but she was like huge she was she was
not only in australia she was huge like
in all of youtube i remember those were
the good times she was so funny i love
her skit so much i know it was so like
deadpan humor but it was so amazing yeah
yeah i love it oh i'm glad you know her
yeah uh i was gonna tell you your
fortunes yes
this is uh
a bit more fascinating if you
actually uh
see what i was using do you know this
application called holy
uh holy holy lee
yeah holy we have a y at the end i've
heard of it before
um it's like a whole live official
application for your phone where you can
like turn on the camera and you can take
pictures together of the models yes yes
yes yes no i'm like okay yeah i feel
like i should know what this is but i
was no it's okay because literally no
one else who called into my stream no
one knew about it and all of my uh
although the chat audience they also
were like what the [\h__\h] is that yeah you
never knew about this yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah it's not so well
known in in the overseas community but
it recently added for new year's until
the end of january it recently added a
function where you can um have whoever
remember you choose uh pull your uh
omikuji your fortune from shrine
i did a stream that was themed around
that and i pulled yours in your absence
oh
i'm sorry i was probably no no no no no
problem no problem i i ended up doing
everybody in the end uh not only to call
and zaya
so
uh yours was
gonna get it kidding okay
let me go back
there was it there was it there
no wait wait wait wait sorry sorry sorry
sir i accidentally
skipped that
oops here it is
okay i got yours with with okay you
senpai i chose okay senpai no specific
reason
and
here it is okay so you got kitschy there
was actually there was no bad luck they
made everything kind of sound like good
look
okay okay the worst one was shikikichi
but um
yeah so uh
it said let me look at here my my okay
if i said ostato
uh horomenga anatano ini nenga
so
apparently roberto senpai
sent a new year's greeting card to your
house please check your post box
what
credit card
according to hololey oh
i was concerned for a second wait wait
did it say it like
wait what ha ha
did it specifically say nobody said boy
what no but your oshie is roberto right
i never said that
[Music]
i mean when i asked my viewers they said
she likes roberto
i remember you telling me no that
doesn't mean he's my oh she i don't i
don't i i'm i'm sweating i'm an idol i
don't have oh [\h__\h]
you don't ever know really even jago has
an oc you see akuzoshi
survivor senpai
i mean
okay but it's the closest thing to an oc
perhaps so we were thinking oh i see
nobody sent you a great according to
that application
you got pretty good luck there was a
oh
i think yeah it was it was it was
something like hollow super daikichi
that was dye kitchen it was kitty then
it was uh chukit uh
uh
uh a few up uh below that as well
yeah
are you happy with that
sure
about the following year this one was
it didn't really
give much to work with uh uh-huh yeah
uh-huh
yeah are you good should we pull another
one
wait what i can pull one for you right
now oh yeah sure
is there a specific whole live japan
uh female only member uh that you would
want it from because you cannot choose
somewhere let's go
good choice
um
oh sure give me a moment i'll pull a new
fortune because i guess it was wasn't
your absence so it's not
it's it's not accurate right
what is your new year's resolution by
the way
uh
[Music]
good ques what is my knees or is that oh
you didn't think about it i did i made a
list i just forgot um it was to
get back into fitness but come buffer
right
and then it was too
guys what was my resolution i forgot
what was my resolution i forgot
to stay alive and breathe yeah you kind
of write um
oh
i think it's just
um
i
i i forgot it was oh i wanted to meet
holly and members and hug you guys
anything else yes let's go
of course we have to we have to yeah we
have to we have okay i got your new
fortune
[Music]
one the word saves those images um i'll
just read it to you i took a screenshot
maybe i'll find it later and
wait oh wait no i can save it i can save
it then you can read it yourself
what the hell i'm using bluestacks right
now it's so confusing
what were you doing anyway by the way
right now
before i came chillin i just talked i i
don't know what we were doing
i don't really know what happens in
these like my zatsu streams we went from
talking about the new year outfit which
congratulations you look so cute oh
thank you
we went from talking about knee outfits
to bruh asmr and i don't really know how
we ended up there but
bruh asmr bruh b-i-u-h yeah
bruh
oh i know the word but how would you do
a samaritan i was just saying bruh as if
i was doing asmr
i don't know
oh
sounds uh
sounds inspiring it's inspiring yes
yes
okay i don't know how to save it but
here's your fortune
uh
[Music]
nakanoi senpaiga
okay but that could be anyone does that
mean i just get free food let's go
i'm gonna get me
that you're getting along with very well
we'll invite you for free for some free
yakiniku
but that's anyone
that could be anyone that could be any
one like part of hollow myth it could be
iris there's a senpai no i refuse to
believe it could be a japanese senpai
even japanese stand by who in holly jp
would treat me to yakiniku meow mama
i think anyone would do it for you bae
thank you i'm just robbing people of
their food
is there is there a good yakiniku in
australia yeah they
so good it'd be very good it's so good i
don't know why but like putting buying
meat from the supermarket and putting it
on on a grill here it's just complete
something completely different that's
barbecue i don't know man how do they
i think it's the grill itself like they
have like specific grills and then i
think the cuts of meat different as well
um
like it's different
on a pan like on the stove like you have
to have the the coal yeah it's cold the
cold grill you need
yeah yeah i guess so and and i think
also the the sauces
yeah the soda
firewood mix gives it the finishing
final touch i guess yeah that's so good
korean barbecue still called yakini oh
okay i guess well but that's korean
barbecue that's i mean that's still
different right like i haven't had it
before but it's different it is a bit we
have good okay barbecue here though
korean barbie oh yeah it's good
yeah oh
oh
all right there anyway i wish you a
lovely 2022 i'm gonna leave you now i
don't want to uh
annoy you for too long but i hope so i
hope this year will be a wonderful
successful one for you babe
all your wishes and dreams come true
and and just you don't have to we talked
about new year's resolutions but you
perfect the way you are so don't worry
too much about it thank you bye-bye
oh she's so cute
thank you
thanks for stopping by
no wonder i saw someone in the comments
say that nobody has sent you like a
greeting card i'm like what where did
that come from i'm so confused
oh i see i see i see i see you i see you
i'll see you i'll see you
thank you for coming cuba
um sir my fortune apparently is just i'm
gonna be getting things from my senpai
i thought it was real yeah i kind of
had a heart attack i thought it was real
as well i was like what
but what huh what what huh huh huh
[Laughter]
um shook for a second oh shook us
shook us
congratulations on free yakimiku thank
you yakimiku with cali
bruh i just want to go yakiniku with
everybody
the year being spoiled by senpai's let's
go
let's go
certified bra moment
let's make nobody make it what no
it's too late for nengajo anyway
[Laughter]
back to bra back to bruh
[Music]
you called iris senpai one time
i caught oh my god i literally
like i i think i told you like before i
send out that tweet exposing iris of why
i never call her senpai i was looking at
our first like conversations that i've
ever had with iris and i was like senpai
i look forward to working with you and
now i'm like bruh
what the heck
that discord dm doe
i literally called her senpai once
disgusting yeah i know
i caught step by once and that's it
never again
[Laughter]
[Music]
her six month anniversary is today
yeah
it should be in a couple of hours so i
might get going soon actually this is a
very very fun that's i love doing these
artists with you guys
literally we just talk about random shi
taki and it's great
imagine calling your wife simbo
i mean don't a lot of people call them
like i don't know what if they were your
senpai what happens then do you keep
calling them senpai
but what if your significant other was
your senpai what what happens then
[Music]
what happens then
marriage is sent by anime plot irl
[Music]
no but like senpai could be just sent by
because like you know in like don't they
call like someone who's like one year
older in like if they go to school even
if just one year older they call it
senpai don't they
[Music]
i caused her wife senpai oh you're right
bae is anime protag
[Music]
i am main anime protag
all right
how much coffee do i have left
[Music]
how do you wink on that eye i'm
wink master
i'm skilled
oh you have to make the sound as well
wait you gotta have the you have to have
the main anime protag wing sound
bruh
[Music]
you're killing us here
[Laughter]
if you're an anime pro tag what genre
would you be slice of life
slice of life
yeah
screenshot saved
rom-com with iris no slice of life
i want a feature in like plastic neson
or something like that
literally an anime that makes zero sense
but is
comedy
no story no adventure it's just slice of
life but
kind of whack kind of weird champ yeah
[Music]
please do that wink with the kimono
during the reveal
just for you i will
have you heard about arcane league of
legends yes
i have from many different people
and also
uh i i looked up the reviews for arcane
and i can't believe it's 100 on rotten
tomatoes what the heck
has
what the heck
[Music]
yeah
um
i mean funny funny you should mention
that i literally i'm taking a day off
next week to watch our game
i want to binge arcane so
ah i'm very excited
i mean like if it's anything like the
i'm like you know i'm not
i don't play league of legends but i'm a
big fan of like the animation like short
clip videos that they put up on the
youtube
um
like the warrior one that came out in
2020 i really like those so if it's
anything like that
um then i will enjoy arcane very much
like the envy yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
don't play league
uh
oh okay
i have a little bit of coffee left we're
gonna stop streaming when i finish my
coffee
bay i want you and iris to do a karaoke
sometime i need bearish duets please it
will happen eventually you just gotta
wait until i can
fly to waifu
are you going back to minecraft oh don't
remind me of minecraft i probably will
next week because i need to start
building after the the absolute failure
of a stream that was the last minecraft
stream i really need to start building
the light thingy
um well now that the new outfits have
been announced the thing i wanted to
build it so that you know we can all
have you know react to it in our knee
outfits with the kimonos um which gives
me like another
week or so with like if i complete it
within january i feel like it'll be good
but
i don't know maybe i should honestly i
might just wait till 2023 because
honestly i have no time
server updated oh yeah i need to update
my minecraft as well
that was not a failure minecraft stream
i mean failure in the sense that i
literally didn't do what i was meant to
do
[Music]
so
r.i.p phil r.i.p feel
rip phil
it wasn't a fail it's a success in
different ways
you're kind of right
we were playing minecraft and somehow
ended with monopoly i don't know
[Music]
oh my god reincarnation
you believe
[Music]
legit forgot that phil died i only
remember the fanfic how could you how
could you forget about phil
february 29th do you have a birthday
party every four years
we have very exciting things planned for
february let's just say that
um
[Music]
uh technically i don't have a birthday
until 2024 but that doesn't stop me from
celebrating so
just you know get excited
get excited for
february
[Music]
okay
my coffee is finished
oh
coffee finished
time for productive day i hope you guys
enjoyed this um zatsu with me i had so
much fun
um i'm gonna go do some work and do some
stuff and then i'll see you guys at
iris's six month anniversary stream okay
can you believe it's really been half of
you it's crazy it's crazy talk
crazy
um honey
but yes we are gonna leave it here
because
i feel like we're just gonna keep going
on tangents if we continue so
um so thank you guys so much for coming
today
to the zatsu we had so much fun we
talked about a lot of different things
uh look out for the um silhouette uh
kimono post with the the the hashtag so
that you can um send in your predictions
and i'll include some not like i won't
be able to include all of them but i'll
choose um a few
and then i'll show them on stream um
when i re uh during the new outfit
reveal as well so thank you so
[Music]
all right thank you so much for coming i
will see you guys tomorrow no not
tomorrow the day wait is it tomorrow no
i'll see you guys the day after with
some
monster hunter
see you
bye bye
annyeong
[Music]
do
you