[Music]
passing by the milar
roades I couldn't
buy the reason why
who I am you couldn't know stuck in the
ruins my
disillusion in between the
reality my own
desire keeps me to
you ooh moving faster than the light can
I'm in the
upair alone looking back did I lose my
way I can see to day and I can reach you
again then can I let
go I can hear your voice leading me
through the GL fade
away to the
great the I'm walking by the Light the
before my I alone the silence steing
still I'm reaching out to you come now
saice
life so I'll survive one day bet life it
will lead me back to you see
me I am the
[Music]
Wonder I am the
Wonder
faith is gone the well let's try it no
more believe it just to
see ooh feel the daylight on the
Ed I can't feel
the fall back
[Music]
and then I lose my way I can see today
when I can reach you again then can I
let
go I can hear your voice leading me
through the ho fade
away to the
Brave the L I'm walking by the L the the
before myone the sun is stening till I'm
reaching out to you
conice life myself so I'll survive one
day eventually the light it will lead me
back till you see me da da da da da
[Applause]
[Music]
o I am that one
girl I am
[Music]
under
ah