[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
um
yeah
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
wow
[Music]
oh my God don't look
uh
[Music]
sorry
I'm very tall
let's fix this
so chat chat is
not YouTube is not loading
YouTube is taking its sweet time by the
way I think you guys are probably
hearing the music by the way double
oh now you heard myself probably
hyper chat
hold tall tallah
my beloved
well isn't double better
no
I suppose not then let me change it to
uh
[Music]
monitor
only this should fix it
see now let's once
right not double
is once
how do I say
you know double TWY no double triple and
then how do I say once just once
only one is double kiwawa music quiet
okay
single ah single double okay yeah yeah
thank you I know that word I just didn't
recall
um
Roger
how about now
is you've been dancing no it's
solo it's solo
oh it reminds me of a tangent I wrote
down
I might have I may have even talked
about before but
okay let's let's start with a tangent
sounds too loud oh come on
I don't know if this was only maybe in
the German speaking Realm
uh
but I remember when I was young and I
was like in forums and MMORPGs and all
that
uh
like there was like
people described themselves if they had
uh no partner in life as
you know you would say single right but
it's weird because like people would say
they're like some of them would say
they're single some of them would say
they're solo
and in back then
for some reason in my world in the
places where I was going around at
a solo meant I think having a partner
for some reason which makes no sense
because uh
obviously solo means alone as well
but yeah and it's German speaking
communities that I was in like I don't
know
some some fan communities of
um like a little little band or or
MMORPG or whatever just like I mean
it's not even that it was that they're
all as young as me like there were some
older people in there too living but for
some reason back then yeah if you were
single I think they said they were
single but if they had a partner for
some reason they said they were solo
and then I heard it heard that so many
times
that I would adapt to that and in my
mind it had the meaning solo had the
meaning
uh having a partner hmm
I don't know it's weird
I think they you know they were like I
don't know trying to use English words
to sound cool but they didn't really
know what it really meant but then
this is this is weird isn't it so weird
it makes no sense
um
I think all of the people that I was
like talking to back then
who were using these words they I don't
think they were really good at English
either
it was mostly like German people
and I don't think their English was
really good
and since also a lot of them were young
um I suppose yeah more reason for them
not being good and proficient in English
but it took me a while
to later on understand that that doesn't
mean that at all I mean I was always
really good in English but
I don't really think the word solo
really came up
in my in my English classes
even though I was really good I had a
lot of vocabulary I was the best student
in English in my in class in the school
even probably
with flex no good Flex
[Laughter]
um
from solopolia Mori
but wait you are you are you justifying
it that there might actually be like a
reason
foreign
would make sense
um
fully sick means really good
how are you doing oh I'm like fully sick
dude mate
only one partner that's so weird nah it
makes no sense
it really just makes no sense I I just
wait what if single is
single is single and solo is single
what's the word for not being single
taken but is there no cooler word for
that like you know sing along solo taken
sounds so so
like they didn't find a fancy word for
it
pair the duo
what's your relationship status uh Duo
so no one would use that
maybe because you know maybe because
there was no no no
well well used such words that's why
they thought all then solo must be the
other word the opposite right because we
all we have at that you know what that
might that might actually make sense to
a German person German speaking person
when they hear the word single and solo
also maybe especially because they both
start with s maybe they thought it was
the opposite of it because you know
taken is just a normal English word that
makes perfect sense but I feel like
single and solo
I feel like to to German speaking person
who's not much in an English-speaking
Community ever could sound like that
Lily you know you know saying I'm like
unraveling this whole mystery right now
your brains should be exploding right
now
foreign
I feel like some people might think the
way I just explained it
and then other people picked it up
because people used it in that sense
but obviously never it never went so far
that like you know people would use it
everywhere but anyway
I'll take your word for it thank you
believe in the koala
we are not a cult just believe in
whatever I say
just believe no doubts allowed allowed
in kiwawa World
um
I mean in the end maybe I'm also just
remembering things wrong
laughs
but I feel like
I'm pretty sure that happened I'm pretty
sure especially like I feel like the
younger the people were the more they
would use them
like I feel like
like girls and boys around like 10 11
12.
their knowledge of English language was
still very much question my question or
question mark
and then they hear some cool English
sounding words to describe their totally
real real and serious relationship in
like their years under 15.
and they're like this is it maybe I was
in strange forums
that just reminded me of something
really strange
oh my God like once when I was like
really young
that definitely also under 15 maybe I
was like 12 14 nah 12 11 12 or so you
know I was I was I was in the interwebs
yeah and you know all kinds of pages and
forums were popping up back in the day
sounds so old
but then I remembered it was uh I don't
know why I just remembered this it's all
also really crushed but I remember there
was this one website I found it was kind
of a Blog from someone
um but it didn't quite look like a Blog
it looked more like a proper website it
was just just really like a dark like on
like the whole layout was like a simple
black background I think
and then the font was either white or
red
and
um I I remember there was this whole
I think it was a girl writing about her
how she got
to know the Lord and Lord Satan
it was like something about her
oh that was I was really cursed
something with a mouse or a hamster and
um
doing something with its head I don't
want to say
but basically she
killed it
and and
whoa I remember reading that as a child
and was like what the [\h__\h] this is the
creepiest thing I've ever read on the
whole internet
I'm like what
what what what
oh
it now that I think back I wonder yeah
if that was some kind of Creepypasta
but it wasn't German and it was [\h__\h]
creepy
yeah
holy [\h__\h]
the internet's very very scary place now
and also back in the day
um
I don't know how I got this stuff
I post translated Japanese horror
stories
oh
pretty creepy creepy creepy
yeah yeah many weird vlogs
[Music]
but back in the day
they had a Blog because there were like
so many blog providers and it was like
such a popular thing like uh I have a
Blog what about you they have a Blog and
I have my blog on this providing my blog
is a blah blah blah my blog is XX spooky
girl XX dot blogspot.com
or something like that
nowadays people don't
you know randos don't really have some I
have so many blogs anymore do they
yeah blogger days WordPress days
there were like a million of those kind
of
like blog providers
yeah
and everyone had like a super
professional website
yeah using the provided layouts by those
providers
so professional because everybody needed
like a blog or like a website about
themselves because they were so
important
everybody was sound patent yeah
on and then
okay I should stop I need someone to use
tangent so I I wanted to continue but I
need this tangent for a GTA stream
perhaps
there's Blogspot still exist I don't
know
I would assume that like WordPress
Alex's WordPress was like one of the
more professional ones
where you had to do more of the work
yourself I think which is why I never
got into WordPress because it was
already like too much for me
it was already too too difficult for me
WordPress still exists nice they
survived they survived impressive
21 minutes to which I reading not one
supercharge red classic Kendall nothing
I've gone through like hours but at
least an hour of not reading a Super
Chat
of not even starting to read
previous times many times
first time here
uh anyway uh do you got
not only 200 but pretty much I would say
[Music]
in like a day oh I'm so happy
so heavy I'm so happy that it's doing so
well
[Music]
um
so happy ah you know
I'm gonna be honest after fever night I
was quite worried after fever night and
then animal I'm gonna be honest I was
worried but um
I think uh
I I think I did quite well with do you
because
um like for example the preview video
the teaser and also the the actual video
that I uploaded on Twitter of the song
uh even when you play it if you scroll
through and you see it like muted I I
think it catches your eye
it's like what's Chihuahua doing well
yeah let me let me unmute this and take
a look let me let me look at it for a
little more than one second because if
you scroll through you know
yeah normally you don't even look at
things for one second but people would
stop and then the more you look at it
the more interesting the trailer looks
and then then you're like what the [\h__\h]
let me turn on the the music what
music video looks interesting already
let me look let me uh listen to the
music
then you listen in and you're like wait
what the [\h__\h] what a banger who's like
K-pop not only I love kpop but I know I
know not everybody loves Kpop but I
think it's um a music style that speaks
to a lot of people
um
so
especially also my my other whole life
members yeah
we all suckers for kpop
um
and I think also especially Japanese
members they're like when they hear
something like that they're like oh so
cool so Kakui
so cool
yeah and that that leaves an impression
and then they
and they like to share cool stuff stuff
that's cool from their point of view
yeah
he said it's cool
um I'm really happy that so many members
shared it so far
because that also really helps like
getting the other fans of other members
to see it and then you know
more and more people start sharing it
and it gets the attention it deserves
um
so I've been really really really
excited about it to see it get such a
good reception yeah
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
I think you know it deserved much more
but I've also seen like YouTube [\h__\h]
it over
many times and also then again you fiber
Knights just didn't get
as much as attention as it should have
gotten and yeah that makes that makes
makes quite a difference I think
um
makes quite a difference
people just like they they look
they look away from its existence
and it's like it never happened it's a
bit sad
it's a bit sad but um
I think you know especially also when
it's performed with choreo and all that
in live performances it will always be
loved
yeah and it's nice to have a variety of
different songs with different
um
different genres even if like you have
your favorites and you have some some
songs that you don't like that much if
you hear them all in a concert or so
then it's nice to have variety and then
I think you will like love all of them
and they will all have a different uh
purpose because if all songs are insane
bangers you also need some filler songs
that it sounds a bit mean I guess but
you need some famous songs but you can
also be like you know a bit more chill
and appreciated and a bit more chill way
some more calm songs but also
yeah it just balances everything nicely
and I still love Fever Night
I still love favorite night and the
Heart challenge as well
Challenger also a bit underappreciated
but almost at 2 million views by the way
hmm
what's next on your mind when it comes
to the genre of next song
um I want actually I thought about this
today so next I want to make an album
right so I want the album to also have a
lot of variety
um but one thing I want to try out is
going in a bit more of a rocky
not like really authentic Rock obviously
but you know kind of like
old old school Avril Lavigne
uh like girl girls rock I don't know how
to describe it but if I say old school
Avril Lavigne or
or so you might know what I'm talking
about
rock pop pop pop I got a punk that's I
guess more in Punk Direction ah let's
try both
let's try both uh I'm thinking of
several things
but the question is just can I find the
right producers for that
uh because a lot of producers are like
kind of Untouchable like you know
um
often they're not credited often you
don't know how to reach out to them
um
but I do think like and
and heart Challenger is very talented
and like if you even just if you look at
hinatolian heart Challenger they're
already so different right super cute
song super energetic cute song and then
hinotori which is like a fire cool song
um more fantasy style like he definitely
can do even more different things
and actually for hinotori and heart
Challenger I did
um kind of like ask him to go more
into a style where what he what he
nowadays probably wouldn't write for his
own um like music project but
um so maybe I'm thinking maybe he can
like make something that's kind of like
J-Rock
something in that direction
Jay Rock
Jay Rock is cute
girls J-Rock
and then however then we put English
lyrics on I know even more English lyric
writers now thankfully and I am
I I know I have more people to choose
from now because
um for for real do you
I also found out about
the lyric writer for do you
um
could ask her again for example
yeah yeah connections connections
bump of chicken
huh
yeah
anyway
I know
um
and obviously album has to have one or
two like slower songs like ballads
because I don't think I would want to
release those as a
as a single so I would release it as a
album song
oh I also know one more person I want
really want to ask for a song is
Farhan Farhan Farhan Farhan
um
feel like he has a long talent of like
making really our original creative
songs that still have
um I don't know kind of a any song Vibe
but
he has his original
sound
I wonder
I wonder what
could make for me
yeah so I'm gonna start
you know picking out producers and start
working on the album seriously now hmm
yeah
socio
who is Farhan uh he made reflect and I
think also made songs for ID Girls
before
oh
don't remember which one specifically
but I remember they were good
um
ah Kate openstack for example yeah
before three two
that's right see oh so many good songs
oh generally Like A Thousand Years too
wait he made a lot of songs for all of
us already
I pick journey of a thousand years was
really good something like that for an
album song I think would be nice
hmm
the good thing is of an album I feel
like uh
an album also needs a good balance
and um I would I would put album I would
the songs I would put in an album
I would generally not put out as a
single
um
because like I feel like what I would
aim for is be more like yeah ex
experiment more and then go for some
songs that
I would be too uncertain and and nervous
to put out as a
as a single song
so
which doesn't mean they're not good but
they may not have a really
secure
mainstream feeling where I know oh this
will be popular or this will be picked
up by a lot of people because this is a
really hype Club Banger whatever you
know so I can I can be more creative and
I have I can put in more different vibes
um and more calm and songs in general
yes yes yes yes
so anyway now we should
slowly start to read some super chats uh
we're at the last
Sports last hour of these super channels
[Music]
oh it's been only 45 minutes oh
your oldest songs will always remind me
of docomo 2022 waking up at 4am with
takanashihara
and Kiana you mean because
you woke up early to practice with
kiwawa eggy Wawa
oh yeah
all of all of my songs are very precious
to me
but I want to make more and have a big
repertoire to choose from for a concert
yeah I probably won't have the budget to
make like a music video for every
[\h__\h] song on the album
um but um maybe at least one we can have
like one song that's like a lead lead
song Lead promotional song and then make
a music video for that one perhaps maybe
um
oh
snail house oh I don't know about like
sneha specifically but that kind of
genre yeah it would be nice too to have
as a as a variety
option
um
something like that
do your rights friend okay
exciting
[Music]
oh something like baby Babymetal
honestly
I'm very sure that Gojo could make
something like that
I'm pretty sure he could make something
like Babymetal song
um like that Kitsune song
that would be cool
then we have metal Jay metal you
[Music]
mellow death yeah
yum yum yum
bubble metal
okay
let's go
do
I know Scandal but
I don't think I've ever really listened
and I know that they're like a JJ Rock
j-punk I don't know group
but I don't remember it's been too long
but I am aware of their existence
okay oh I should turn off the super
chats
for sure
okay
no more Super chats
you shall not pass what the [\h__\h]
yeah
also Elena we need to talk about the
houses with dragon
we need to talk
we have to talk
um
foreign
I didn't know it could do that oh
[Music]
I just realized in horalizer you can
see all of the whole Live members
chat comments
for each stream afterwards they
collected
[Music]
okay anyway what number did I say
was it
what was it I was it 653 perhaps
well maybe not
oh it was okay good
good good
Eva
yummy let's let's uh start reading
[Music]
Wawa
why won't you stream with males what are
you talking about
this happened remember
how dare you forget about this this
legendary stream that's so so
disrespectful
that was a really special moment in my
life a really important whole talk
episode okay
ah
how dare you forget
how can you forget about it
go watch it
anyway
[Laughter]
am I sticky thank you for the ransom for
chat thank you
happy second anniversary Nintendo I feel
I must apologize as I have had your
streams in podcast mode while I work for
some time now but I must also thank you
for making those stressful days more
enjoyable by the way I'm impressed that
your scrims can overpower every
machinery
oh yeah I need to somehow somehow grab
your attention every once in a while
I'm gonna lose you completely
but thank you thank you for watching my
streams even at work you don't have to
apologize for that
you're trying your best to keep up with
me
and I really appreciate that um
yeah maybe we need to sponsor you some
earbuds if you don't already have some
you're about to listen to Chihuahua
without being noticed
yeah airpods that I hate so much anyway
just don't lose them
um
yeah I promise it's just gonna steal
some of one of the whole life members
and send them to you because everyone
has them
um
[Music]
foreign
I just don't understand why you would
pay so much money for a product like
that
nah
just fall for me back in the day where I
actually like listened a lot to music
um while I was like
I don't know on my way to work or
yeah I'm on my way to school
um but nowadays there's like I don't I
don't really listen to music
anymore besides takanasi Kiara's bangers
obviously
um
good for training oh yeah yeah but I
don't do that either
oh no
um I currently have
something in my Amazon
cart
I'm about to buy it I was just waiting
so maybe I can think of something else
to put in my cart
I put um
machine
for home
in my cart so what does that mean
[Music]
[Laughter]
previously right otherwise you would
have no idea but
[Laughter]
uh ah you could tell from my model
moving on this good a good good good
good good eye it's okay
I'm like I don't wanna like you know go
to a public public or like you know like
like a fitness place
anymore because
um I don't like it that there is like
people who are all like you know above
and they can go longer than five minutes
while I die at five minutes
uh and I know it makes me feel
uncomfortable and pressured and also I
want to be able to use it at any time
you know
like late in the night at three a.m
before going to sleep you know if I want
to that's better than not doing it at
all if that's the time I feel like doing
it then power to me
yeah so
you have to actually use it though oh
really is that like a requirement what
happens if I don't use it does the
machine go like poof and like yeah
delete itself does it just disappear
oh is that is that a record ow I didn't
know
oh I'm forced to use it then oh no
[Laughter]
I will use it if I want to but I'm just
telling you the reason why I'm getting
it is because I don't feel comfortable
doing you know exercise with other
people so I wanted in my own private
Chambers
um
but I got like a pretty
cheap one like somewhere like 300 400
600 bucks I found one for like 150 but
um the the reviews all say that it's
very good and like you know it does what
it has to do
um it maybe doesn't have the the same
um mechanisms as a 600 one but it still
works perfectly fine for what you needed
to do unless I just saw some some
opinions saying that if you like really
really buff then this will be too weak
for you
um but yeah for someone like me
obviously it should be good enough
um
I don't want to like spend 600 on the
rowing machine
I think this should be good enough hmm
because I'm not trying to be a
bodybuilder yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah I think the more
expensive ones seem to support more more
and more and more much more heavier
weights and I don't need that
um
foreign
yeah I don't want to be buff I'm just I
just want to help my shoulders because
it's been really bad it's been really
painful
oh
[Music]
yeah
so anyway back to Super chats because I
think I only read one
ah thank you am I singing
thank you for the recipe what I respect
about you is your hard-working honestly
blunt and despite the obstacles that
come at you you continue to move move
forward move move forward each time
stronger than ever your past vods and
this Marathon prove it
you didn't end your sentence
no never mind I read it wrong
never mind
it's all good
I wanted to roast you about missing some
words but no the sentence was fine
I apologize
um where was I okay congrats on your
second anniversary and thank you thank
you
ah
honestly blunt yes that is uh two words
that describe me
well
I wish I could
you know if I could I I would be even
more honestly blunt with you guys
I've tried to control myself
but yeah I'm glad that there's some
people out there who appreciate that who
appreciate not being bullshitted
all the time you know an honest honest
Austrian person honest European verb
just
trying to be fair
of the people that support me
yeah you were nerfing yourself yes
[Laughter]
yes
I am nerfing myself
um that's bluntness is my blood hell
yeah high five
I like the feeling of genuine
interactions nice and your right here in
the right place
thank you
today
congrats on two years tencho you've come
so far since the Debbie and I'm glad
I've gotten to see the journey so far I
hope you can get to Japan soon
I must admit I looked for half a year
but I have been watching since soon
after the debut got a good rest after
the stream
oh thank you you learned for the first
half year huh what made you what made
you want to interact more huh did you
just fall in love with the one with so
much that you couldn't resist sharing
your love and getting some love back
understandable have a nice day
hmm
thank you
also I see it I think I saw you in the
chat yeah
yeah what's up what's up how you doing
how how are you doing channeling my
inner
what's his name again not Chandler
Johnny Jonathan John John
you're Joey
thanks
I had it almost right I was so close
Jonathan and he does not feel like a
Jonathan right that I was like can't be
Jonathan doesn't fit him
does not fit him
fake friends man shut up I'm not
I'm Noah it's hard to remember names
sometimes
I know the other ones Monica
uh
wait
[\h__\h] uh what was that [\h__\h] called again
I love them all
um
[Music]
oh yeah Phoebe Phoebe was one of them
but that's not the one I was thinking of
wait don't don't don't don't
um
it was Monica Phoebe and
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
um wait wait wait just think of
um you know what what people always say
oh that relationship oh my God
we were on a break come on come on
now I'm not looking at the chat on
purpose
we're on a break
we were on the brick
[Music]
um
Rochelle almost Rachel
[Music]
Rochelle
[Laughter]
ah Marcel
yeah
yeah with Roc c-h-e I was just gonna
like start like naming names any names
and the holy [\h__\h] that was uh
that was me shooting the middle the
middle the middle of a Dart thingy
[Laughter]
Michelle is 19 than Rachel
oh my God
oh my God that was really funny to
myself
Bullseye thank you
uh and the guy was called
Chandler Joey and
Chandler Joey
come on brain you can do it remember it
doctor doctor
Geller
cool Geller Gala who moniker Galler and
someone Geller I know his last name
wait we're on a break
I'm Dr Keller yeah like dinosaurs
[Music]
hahaha
oh
Rachel I love you Rachel
Rachel I want you love me
[Music]
[Laughter]
I can't I don't remember huh
yeah
I can't
Ross gella
oh Rochelle and Ross
Rochelle Rochelle and Ross oh yeah
enjoyed no
ah
there we go
my brain is so hard to remember
no I love friends I've watched it so
many times
Michael bloom and a different show how
many times have you watched Friends um
from beginning to end probably like at
least four times
which is oh dear let me let me see him
how many hours is all seasons of Friends
86 hours almost 87 hours
calculator
87 hours
times four
is 320 . 248 hours in days
four oh only 14 days
I've only spent 14 days with these
people at as little at most I don't know
it's not even that much
someone would only spent 14 days with
friends
to remember their names forever and ever
and the thing is I remember their names
you just need to help get a little help
of uh being reminded
um
anyway
[Laughter]
we need to get back on track guys you'll
have to be like wow stop stop tempting
you're gonna be done with the super
chats
dad is love
no no
[Laughter]
which is like this
oh my God
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
ha ha ha ha ha
yes that's right it's me how did you
know
Daddy's likes to have her fun okay
um stop stop stop
[Music]
don't don't
understand
I'm sorry this was not real kiwawa
I've read three super chats so far uh in
one hour
amazing
absolutely amazing
start somewhere Matthew and here's a
kissy
Reggie Steele thank you for a little red
Super Chat happy to your anniversary
thank you my schedule has been hectic
for the past couple months so I haven't
been around as much but you're still my
favorite streamer to watch whenever I
have free time oh here's to another
successful year filled with memories
thank you
Don kitchen I hope
so too
for a successful year
with many memories hopefully also with
you yeah yeah
hopefully you'll be less busy you can
watch me more that would be nice
but at least you're not forgetting about
Chihuahua the one and only your true
love
thank you for the support also thanks
for being for free today
[Music]
thank you once again Titi mwah
from school thanks for two red super
chatters
you are my second anniversary
time sure seems to go fast with our
beloved Phoenix but this last year you
made damn sure that you gave your best
to us with magnificent 3D concerts off
collabs sand dunes and a lot of sweat
tears for love and love for kfp couldn't
ask for a better Ocean than you couldn't
think of a better Idol than you
you have to detained us and inspired us
every day even when you don't stream I'm
glad that you're part of whole life
because if you weren't I'd probably stop
watching YouTubers by now oh
is literally
the Holy One who keeps YouTubers alive
with her own soul power oh my God if it
weren't for chihuahua vegetables would
be dead by now
incredible power
is contained in this one YouTuber
no one can stop her no one wants to stop
her as she is necessary for the life and
continuation
yes the the
um
dynasty of YouTubers
it rests upon her shoulders
and yet
she is so humble so humble to not let
that get over her head and just acts
and blends in like a normal YouTuber
which is why she's so beloved by all
[Laughter]
uh uh fantasizing a lot today
hahaha
yeah I should be more like this this one
yes it's everything
is only possible as long as I exist this
one
[Laughter]
oh God someone would stop me
thank you
yeah Glenn Cole and
something like that
Lanchester nope that was something else
glad sister Chesters yeah
[Laughter]
do you guys remember
since when every member of the life
calls your mommy a lady koala Mommy a
lady is not really a title everyone
gives me no no no no
kiwama however yeah recently because I I
called myself Chihuahua nowadays all the
time I guess everyone also
uses at least I don't think the Japanese
members use it for me but the English
speaking members
now
because it's cute
[Music]
yeah perhaps only Kobo calls me Mommy
in a very innocent way
anyway Francisco thank you for raising
my eagle
my confidence have confidence you too
you two friends were you should have
confidence just like me
ah kill nice and Glencoe thank you
I knew that I was just testing you
testing you
I don't think AMA has called you Kiara
what what has she called me then uh are
you saying Ahmed has never called me
Kiana ever
you mean she hasn't called me kiwava you
mean probably right because I don't
think she called me kibowama actually I
might always calls me says yeah Kiara
when she talks about me she always says
Kiara but she doesn't even say it like
in the Japanese way she says in an
English way
Kiara
is how she says how I say my own name if
I say it properly Kiana
with like a Japanese r
Alma says Kiara
I need to Bonk that kiwawa into her head
she needs to call me
by my nickname
but honestly she could call me anything
and I would gladly Cry tears of
happiness
as I may have a nickname
her name is Amelia actually
anyway thank you
no
no why would you call me chicken that
means absolutely no sense
makes no sense I'm a muted
oh man what the [\h__\h]
I wonder if there's some people who
don't know where that comes from why
people say that
I could be task money
is
really old it's like no it feels like it
wasn't the first month or the first two
months or so
there was a collab
that was planned with I think four
people
's gonna be one of them
uh and then I'm gonna overslept
um but we just we didn't want to like
say it too clearly I think so we just we
just you know streamed without her
not really you know put any blame on her
or so
people were like where is
muted
it was overcooked yeah
yeah yeah yeah
and then even when she was like not even
supposed to be in any collapse
afterwards
uh like you know people would be like
I'm as muted and I'm like I mean I mean
amazing even
wants to be here and then when Ami was
in collapse and she she was actually
actively speaking and people could hear
her uh people would like you know troll
by saying she's muted
and we would be like what I mismuted
what what no it should be fine what do
you mean
yeah and then continued continued
up to this day
my whole life meme history
super super
chats
what are super chats what what what are
those can I eat those others edible
what do you mean Super chess
I don't know what you mean
um
count no wait no Maybelline
Maybelline thank you for the rest of the
chat
happen to you
and you were taking us on this journey
of blood
sweats and tears of supreme victories
and overcoming rough times
you've done the style Grace and strength
a true as tear Idol keep on Shining as
bright as the sun Like a Phoenix
where does the Blood come from
what what happened when did we lose
blood
four blood away
[Music]
the usual room
s
oh [\h__\h]
yeah bye are you saying that
are you saying that there's blood on my
hands on my hands literally
hmm
is that what you're saying
are you trying to get
a confession from me live on stream so
I'm caught in 4k
is that what you're trying to
the ocean around one year
just kidding okay don't worry don't
worry Maple Leaf seeing what you're
doing I see exactly what you're doing
but I have mercy I I am totally not
growing to be paranoid
going crazy from my power
no no
I'm a merciful leader
even though even though he would tell
you what to overthrow me
by slandering my name
just kidding my balloon thank you so
much
thank you said Calvin
w.takashan black Richard thank you for
the recipe chat congrats on another fun
year Kiana and here's to hopefully why
did I scream your name many more
together thank you for being a huge part
of my life you make everything so much
better
we'll continue to support you all the
way so technically we haven't missed a
single stream ah yeah I love Oh you mean
because he caught up with the boss wow
that's impressive too though damn
thank you
congratulations and thank you so much
for all the dedication and all the love
thank you soon always here
[Music]
I know you are
no
always here by my side cute little
chicken
don't vote girl hey yo
[\h__\h] kidding me
are you saying
are you saying you've also been here for
every every minute of every 12 hour
stream
crazy chicken
that is that is quite something
life life for all of them you've been
here fly for all of them strongest KFC
oh you're giving yourself a title of
strongest coffee everyone who gives
themselves that title must fight
fights to death or life
just kidding don't don't
know
there can only be one strongest give me
[Laughter]
boys I've read more super chance shut up
I've read more I've read
um one two three four five six seven
eight nine ten eleven
11 in one hour and 15 minutes
wow
I guess I'll perish then no no
how many are left
um that's something we don't talk about
here okay
thank you black virgin
I hope for your own sake your own health
that I won't stream too much in the
coming year
so that you have some time for yourself
thanks for the pinkies
[Music]
son
is no
[Music]
no fun
um
[Music]
mm-hmm
I don't know it's your YouTube
[Music]
Channel
soon happy second anniversary boss what
a year full myth of collab travel to the
US Korea and the Maldives and Italy many
conventions and of course you're insane
friendly concert I hope you realize how
much you've achieved let's go to more
goals together this year yeah thank you
thanks for the pink Super Chat thank you
indeed
some very special events happened in
that one year hmm
yeah yeah very very very special moments
I'm glad that we finally made it happen
it was about [\h__\h] time
thank you for being part of it thank you
soon hlg thank you soon
Arigato Fallen penguin thank you for the
red super chat happy anniversary tangel
got a job by following what would Kiana
do and you're knowing the interview oh
wow
so my first super had to go to my Aussie
thank you for being you I'll always tune
for your success and happiness field
tonkatsu oh
[Music]
yeah
congratulations good job I'm happy that
you got a job by being inspired by me
I wonder what exactly
this what the answer was to what would
Kiara do like besides just yoloing
how how exactly that unfolded I would be
interested in hearing but I'm just happy
that you made it congrats I'm so proud
of you
I hope the job treats you well and that
you will be there for as long as you
wish to be there
but don't forget about kiwawa
yeah in your busy days don't forget
about kiwawa
threaten the interviews with usual room
time and it seems very efficient indeed
thank you
thank you oh
no
[Music]
hi hello
hello
thank you
oh
I remember listening to your first kind
of look right up the debut and being
blown away oh the first one some
nostalgic I was so nervous thank you
David asked you thank you for the pinky
happy second anniversary Kiana I can't
remember the last time I woke up for 6
a.m but it was well worth it to share
your anniversary review on KFC oh thank
know so the best options jimkins could
ever ask for I hope you keep making
new memories together thank you that's
so sweet of you to wake up so early for
me you know
I I know 6 a.m is really early I don't I
didn't expect you you know that all of
you would wake up so early thank you for
doing it anyway
um
I hope it was fun for you thank you soon
and yeah
fully I won't force you to wake up so
early much more often but but almost
healthy so what the hell
yeah it doesn't matter
as long as you get enough sleep
sleep early and sleep early wake up
early watch kiwama
best rhythm in life
watch and repeat watch and repeat
yeah PST is um pretty [\h__\h] I'm so
sorry
I'm trying now I'm trying to always have
like a good balance and you know like
last members only stream was later in
the day for me so next members only
stream will be earlier in the day for me
and so that the sea fans can enjoy and
you know you know Kiwa was always trying
to look out for everyone
so you know everybody needs to suffer a
little bit or just adjust
and what's even the Vaude or wake up
early
um
yeah always always possible to just
watch the VOD
thank you thank you for making the
effort
to be here when it is important
[Music]
to you and it feels like it's my child
and it's growing up so fast oh my God
my sweet to you
[Music]
uh guys I got some water here but I'm I
kind of want to drink some more of my
own
sugary soft drink if that's okay can I
get some more yeah
yeah so much care for you guys are so
kind give me a second I'll be right
foreign
[Music]
yeah but we as soon as I saw you I know
it
[Music]
oh you know what I should do
I need to I need to put
my music video on screen here
especially because there's one empty
one I want to put um
the FIFA night one
if a knight goes into the small one
where is it
you go here
[Music]
I need to cut it a bit more
how's that look oh it fits pretty well
I think
okay but
I might uh
the only version I have of my music
video is like a 4K version so I'm not
gonna throw it in now LOL
I'll um re-render it as like a smaller
version and then put it in there
but I feel like I forget
can I do it now
it won't take much time I just need to
throw it into a Premiere Pro
I'll forget about it otherwise you're
the best feature in the world thank you
thank you that's it see
what I was talking about
me carrying the whole industry on my on
my so humble
so humble shoulders
I told you
just kidding
and do you uh oh yes
ah [\h__\h] there it goes
foreign
music video
why do you
do
you
okay
and then
here
and then we can make it really small
export media
uh 720 or
I can't even know where I was supposed
s d n t s c
and it has borders though weird
this one this one
854 x 480 pixels
sounds good
do we use small
and I will take one minute
okay
oh yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
do you in bird language oh just mixing
in some bird languages into my Jewel
rendition
hmm
this is what I call Super cherry
I hear no complaints
no complaints
yeah
acapella was good thank you I didn't
really prepare for it so if I
if I prepared then it would have
probably sounded even better like some
parts
some parts just really don't quite fit
that style so you need to change them up
a little bit
it's done
I think it's done
[Music]
small do you
okay I
don't want to stop it yeah playing
watching
[Music]
there's something special about you when
I see you I know it's true
I just can't resist you oh guys stream
Friday Fever Night
Friday FIFA night love conqueror
love conqueror on Friday FIFA night
foreign
reason
[Laughter]
your son was stuck in my head for the
whole day
[Music]
mission
accomplished
while I'm looping it
and it's behind the screen noise
wonderful immersion complete
foreign
also
also you know one of the members who
really liked my song apparently was
Tower summer
you know who that is
what's what's Tower summer
[Laughter]
you know what I'm talking about
and watch the clip
it's like what's hell alive
we're talking alive
how was summer
a clip of some like twitch RL streamers
where apparently they were in a Japanese
convenience store and they saw some
whole live snacks and this girl she's
totally fine you don't have to know her
whole life she's like to have friends
who know her life she's like what's all
alive and they're like oh my God
what
what she's like what what's so alive and
they're like oh my God
and then and then chat tells her to say
tawasama
to her friends apparently I guess I'm
guessing that's their Oshi or so and
she's like
and they're like
oh my God don't you ever speak to me
ever again
don't don't even
and she's like I don't know what I did
wrong what's telling summer
I'm not making fun of her she's fine you
know totally fine she thought it was
really funny in the interaction
you know obviously some people don't
know her life
um
[Music]
it do be like that sometimes oh massive
tour fan in Idaho
Tower
summer
imagine if she pronounced Kiara's K Aura
Kara
um
is that what like if a English-speaking
person would see that name naturally
like pronounce it as like as a first
guess
because I feel like so far
people always pronounce Kiara pretty
correctly but takanashi
tap tap take on gnashi I don't know that
that's been more problematic
chaosi takanashi
takanashi
taken
not that difficult though I feel like
there's names that are more difficult to
pronounce
in in whole life
um
anyway I need to read super chats guys
why are you keep on like stopping me
why it's you guys you you are like toxic
to me
[Music]
it's me no it's you it's not me it's you
no yo no
I fear and I feel no guilt
in my body not a single vein in my body
feels guilt
no
no no no no no no no no no no no no
no I see you no you
oh
[Music]
and my first
uh evidence
would be that you guys enjoy
me tangenting and you
encourage it
would you say that's not true won't you
say that's not true
do I hear an objection
no I don't hear anything
yes
guilty as charged
oh oh no she got me
there you go
discussion closed
silence
hmm where was I
seven people don't concerned wikitunes
Duncan for the pinky happy anniversary
bus here's to many more years and
support to my ocean thank you
thank you for being there at the
anniversary and
yeah for the previous year and I don't
know how long you've been here but thank
you for all the time you've spent with
me thank you
thank you for the pinky as well
[Applause]
I don't know that was Mickey tombs huh I
remember a whole Talk of the viewer I
was like how how have you why
tell me
switch to the holotalk set
if that has ever happened to you you
could never leave kiwawa ever
you face it basically you were bound to
me for Life yeah
summer I have endured till the end damn
happy Kiwa versus I don't know enough
words to express my appreciation for you
thank you for making my days brighter
with your beautiful smile and voice I
hope I can stay with you for another
year love I hope so too you're
definitely welcome here
thank you so much
for bringing
your love and your dedication and your
loyalty to kfp thank you soon for being
part of it thank you
thank you Sean until more time together
love you too
I love peers
pears pears pears peers
thank you
[Music]
foreign
your daughter
ah so yeah
[Music]
mama mama
my
my Hunger
thank you
thank you for the pinky thanks for a
wonderful 12 hours here's to all fun
memories kiwawa and chat will make the
next season of the idol Adventures of
Kiana the Phoenix
here's hoping to that album and live
concert workout in the next year my
osikiana
thank you I hope so too we have a whole
year it has to work even if it takes a
whole year
it will happen we'll figure it out
I'll do my best
thank you for believing in me pirate for
being here for some
[Music]
here
thank you
soon thank you for the rest of the tan
and many many hearts back to you thank
you
[Music]
for the pinky thanks for the Epic
creative and fun endurance stream and
happy second year thank you you care so
much about what you give us and not
always striving to be better and share
more the reasons to stick with you just
get stronger with time
oh sweet thank you
time makes us stronger
yeah
that's very sweet thank you for the kind
words simple turn I appreciate it thank
you so much
please continue supporting kiwawa
happy two year anniversary I have been a
member for one year two months and 27
days so I haven't been here since the
beginning however the amount of love for
you is worth so many more Kiara you make
me so happy and only wish you the best
thank you oh thank you soon that's also
a long time thank you for supporting me
as a member for so long
kfp needs you
thank you for being part and always
supporting my streams and my activities
yeah
thank you soon I wish you also only the
best lots of happiness
thank you oh wait there's another pinky
cat I don't know why but I'm starting to
tear up as I write this knowing that I
have followed you for so long see you
for your highs and lows makes me happy
to be so emotionally invested I hope to
spend many more years to come with you
thank you there's nothing bad about
being emotionally invested in like a
content creator because like
to ask content creators
because this work we put so much work
into it
we put so much passion I mean maybe not
everybody but I put so much passion into
it
and seeing you guys being passionate
about it as well
that's really great thank you
I will try my best to be there for you
guys as long as possible
Super Snake Mario thanks for the pinky
actually wait that was two pinkies a
kiss
Super Snake Mario Santa Pinkie says hey
get a happy second anniversary it's hard
to believe it's already been two years I
feel truly blessed to have been able to
make and share so many memories of you
you're such an amazing Entertainer and a
total sweetheart as well I love you
Kiana
I love you too yeah love love love love
thank you
um me a sweetheart I'm not as much as a
sweetheart As You Are
I'll lose to you thank you
thank you soon so Charming
thank you for being part of kfp
it's 15 thank you for the pinky happy
second anniversary I'm looking forward
to celebrating many more with you and
the rest of myth I recently got fired no
fried fried hopefully you don't get
fired can't wait to evolve again give me
forever thank you fried and fire the
very close words aren't they
oh yeah
who
do Julio
oh oh no Mickey
I would never fire you but hopefully
you also will never leave Cafe
counting on you
please continue being part of kfp maybe
you will be revived from the bucket
State eventually as well
thank you soon
back in my desk if I would fire naughty
chickens did I do that that's such a
waste I shouldn't fire anyone I should
eat them if anything
um
I've grown I've learned
things as well in the past two years it
seems business things
smart smart verb yeah
ah Albedo yeah well that [\h__\h] deserved
it
how dare he
how dare he build up another fast food
branch and then in a name it's so
closely to the one and only kfp that is
that is so disrespectful to what kfp has
single-handedly created what do I have
single-handedly created I would never do
that I would never name my fast food
chain
so closely to another fast food Chain's
name I would never do such a thing
yeah that is so undermining of my
business
no totally unacceptable I never
[Laughter]
[Music]
never
[Laughter]
I mean have you ever heard of something
similar to caffeine
there's only kfp hmm hmm
oh at least you apologize for a token
but that's something what do you mean I
mean are you gonna are you gonna
I'm not even gonna acknowledge that no
[Music]
see thank you for the red super chat
happy second anniversary Kiana I can't
believe it's already been two years
since I first found you damn the pastors
have simultaneously being B B and B
been so memorable and a crazy blur but
what I've learned is that you're beyond
special and an Irreplaceable part of my
life ah I love you
hot hot
thank you thank you oh it's very sweet
oh Irreplaceable Chihuahua so you're
saying kiwawa cannot be replaced by
no froggy Wawa
no no
no
emotori no none of that no no other
versions
only kiwawa
yay thank you only Chihuahua white Kiana
also know
blue Wawa alter one was smoking Wawa
what about German kiwawa
I wonder about Germany huh some people
said they were giving up on me because
of this new German chihuahua that they
found who's been using the same name
even
honestly deserves a lawsuit
[Music]
make me feel a bit uneasy
in German speaking kiwawa
yeah I don't know what's up with that I
need to have a talk with that young lady
well thank you doll for choosing me
Patsy out of all those Beach boots you
chose me to support thanks mate
Australian mate
thank you it's so nice to have some
people from my country support me
ah it just moves me emotionally
indescribable
Indescribable Scrabble scribble scribble
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh also thank you for the rest of the
chat looking forward to many more years
of your amazing voice of wonderful
tangents and Shining personality
you little sweet Charming
piece of happiness
cute thank you soon thank you tangents I
don't know what you're talking about I
don't tangent
you're a little sweet no only love only
love
[Music]
um
thank you for the support
for flattering me so much
Papa thank you for the rest of my
channel
happy second anniversary grateful your
hard work especially the 3d concert also
thanks for being here being my only I
will pray for you to get more happiness
and keeping supporting you for next year
and next and next day yes thank you and
actually you wrote in the next
day
next next
[Music]
that was probably not on purpose
I've seen energy everywhere
my love
[Music]
thank you so much Papa
you've also been around for so long
thank you for being so loyal
These Hoes may not be loyal but these
chickens are very loyal
yeah
thank you thank you
[Music]
please
please stay in kfp
Chihuahua loves you
these hoes ain't loyal
kfps
he is loyal
that's the only the only part I know of
this song I don't know how the rest of
the song even goes
how much Mozart did you listen to today
nothing
um
I don't know why I'm so hyper it's
because you guys are so cute and I'm I'm
proudly because Dewey has been doing so
well yeah that makes me so happy I was
so nervous you know
you know uh my my songs budget uh
changes depending on the pre how the
previous song did
um
so
it's quite some pressure on
on the song You Know
and uh
um difficult
that's why I'm I'm always trying so hard
to promote them
uh and and um for this one I really
chose like creators to work with that
are so skilled and so good but you know
they also cost cost a little bit more
than others but the product is so
amazing and I feel like we're a great
team together and I wish we could do
like many many more things together
um
now an All-Star team yeah
yeah I mean there's definitely been some
extra costs uh that normally wouldn't
have been involved
too yeah but um
I I hope that
um this won't be the only time but also
it's difficult now for me to put out
another single because I'm like
oh
do I always have to put something out in
this quality it's a bit difficult
I can't I don't think I can always put
out something in this quality
[Music]
um
I don't I also don't think I can always
put out something in 3D but the
surprising thing to me is I think I've
absolutely nailed it with this one I've
made the best use possible from a 3D
music video this time because like when
I was looking at like music videos in
general
when you compare normal music videos uh
in the YouTuber world with like
just some like images like two one two
three illustrations or so that get used
in the music video That's like the most
basic one
um but it works well often and then then
there's like some next step music video
would be like animations
drawn animations
that one is uh the more animations you
do and the more high levels they are the
more really really expensive they get
and yeah the more implement the more you
implement of that style
the more expensive it gets and uh
however those are really popular
I would say and then 3D animation is
actually from what I've seen so far even
though it costs a lot too
uh it doesn't quite get the amount of
positive feedback
as you would think it does
hmm
sometimes even the cheapest option does
better
than if you make a 3D music video
hmm
yeah for some reason people don't like
it that much A lot of the time but I
think I have
done it the right way
like the whole visuals
um the different scenes the outfit the
way I changed it so it would fit and Rel
as much as I could and the choreography
the sick choreography
hmm
the city choreography very important
so I'm really happy that even though
it's 3D
people like it so much because like if I
want to put dance in my music and I
really want to then it has to be free
if I were to animes that dance in 2D and
drawn animation first of all it would
look this smooth and even if I spent
like Millions on it it's like not worth
it
and I I really really wanted to make
more stuff like this where I can show
off my my dancing so this is really the
only way for me
um
3D freebie is the one chance that I get
at expressing myself
yeah
expressing myself with my full body
and I think a cool choreography gives a
song so much more to look at and enjoy
and
be hype about
appreciate
so much more
good stuff
hmm
yeah
so I'll definitely be looking into
doing more
like choreographed
music videos but I don't think I can do
it all the time
and also it depends on the song I guess
also again like
I can't keep on repeating in the same
outfit at the end and again and again I
feel like
it's difficult because huh I wish I
could just you know throw on
like a K-pop outfit you know any kind of
like stage outfit or clothes normal
clothes you can make some really cute
outfits with normal clothes but they
have to be modeled they have to be first
they have to be approved
you have to be designed they have to be
approved again they have to be
modeled on the 3D body
and it takes so much time and normally
it's not something you do just for a
music video at least not in whole life
um
I wish it was easier
I really wish it was easier for
us
um
I wish you could just throw like in Sims
throw on some clothes
it doesn't have to be like super
intricate
but hmm
I wish I wish but now I have time you
know and now I'm working on I'm gonna
work on the album so I have maybe some
time to
discuss and think and plan
um
but then if I do that always and every
music video takes like a year
probably
it's four music video
yeah I wonder like for like the way
preacher changed the outfits colors and
removed the belt and stuff
I wonder where the limit is
but you know
hmm
I don't know if preacher can just
put new clothes on me preacher focuses
on low pulley
models but
um
I'm probably not the right style but
yeah
I'll be thinking about this in the
future when I plan my next music video
but in any case I'm just really proud
that it turned out so well and it's
speaking to so many people I'm so proud
so proud thank you guys for sharing it
and and streaming it has been doing
really well and also it's on Spotify and
so on Spotify apparently wasn't like a
maintenance that's why it didn't work in
the beginning but uh it's available now
so please stream it uh you know not only
on YouTube but also on the streaming
services as I said you know my budget
depends on it
hahaha
is it coming to iTunes
um
I feel like it should like isn't that
like
could be on there
but it wasn't
um in the list of that link right
well weren't my previous I got it on
iTunes oh okay there you go well then it
should be there
it's on Apple music yes
oh wait that's the same thing now
what
is Apple music iTunes Now
no yes
it's the same basically
same thing
oh what
I guess that makes sense because iTunes
I guess it was an apple thing
I thought it was two different things
though
oh
exactly is it now let me Google that is
iTunes Apple music
uh all of your music is now in the Apple
music app
the Apple music entrance
Apple replaced iTunes with dedicated
music Apple music videos
you can access any previous iTunes
purchases for these apps so I I chose
just basically doesn't exist anymore
I mean maybe it does but Apple music is
basically just a replacement
iTunes are still around as a legacy app
for those who need it says Google
[Music]
iTunes as an app won't exist on the new
Mac operating system but you'll still be
able to buy music from the iTunes Store
it will just exist on the sidebar in a
new music app
interesting well as a not Apple person
but Windows person I didn't really know
this but good to know then it basically
should be on iTunes but
hmm
[Music]
you're probably trying to transfer
people to use apple music
and not Apple person more of a pear
person
what do you want kg
so needy
[\h__\h]
go sit in the corner and reflect on your
neediness
so needy
I hate Apple Computers high five let's
go anyway
[Music]
let's continue
for the rest of the chat oh boy Gaga
thank you
for the heart emotes no message but only
love thank you very much
Apple sponsorships
that's so unrealistic anyway
hmm
I mean I mean I would take it if
but I don't I don't I don't I don't need
anything I already have an iPad from
Bangkok
my beloved Bunco
I'm getting those Apple products even
though I'm not sponsored by Apple
[Laughter]
and I have an iPhone
and I found an iPad
yeah
I don't want airpods
Apple to make
kfp airpods we could just make them
Android
if we wanted to
got an apple
I've got an iPad oh Apple iPad
you guys stop me
in
you all need to stand in the corner
I love you
you are enabling me
for using fancy English words
thank you for the pinky thank you soon
very much thank you f prank thank you
whoa if I didn't start watching you
nearly two years ago I don't think I
would have ever continued watching whole
life damn thank you
and yet it looks like you have a million
Watson as your profile picture
where's the Gratitude just kidding
Sean all right thank you for the pinky
you made these two years much more fun
that they could have been then they
could have been thank you for being you
here's to another year because I'm with
you all the way count on it oh pinky
promise
it's been sealed thank you Sean r
taking you up on that promise you better
be there all the way
thank you so much
commitment yay
a guy who's not afraid of commitment
let's go
thank you promise yay
I could not be more honored to because
[Laughter]
you know you know I would I would
probably also have a picture as my
profile picture
if I was you if I was you hmm
channel
for me
thank you
okay if you brought your channel thank
you
[Music]
looking forward to your future projects
the koala University
UT YT donkey in space wonderful Duncan
siren
your second anniversary attention time
does fly by before we only would two
years have passed and now here we are I
hope you will continue to have a great
time make amazing memories and most
importantly of course have lots and lots
of fun Heroes to ukfp in the time we
will continue to have Viva lucky Wawa
yeah
yeah time flies by indeed
but
we must treasure it and cherish it and
also holy [\h__\h] that rhymed but I was
shocked by the 500 thank you sir you're
crazy
too much
thank you so much
it's so generous oh my God like oh my
God Cyrus damn
Byron where are you
say something
like come on come on
where are you
you're not here today
don't hide come on let me stay you let
me squish your cheeky cheeks come on
come on get your kisses
[Music]
valley girl kisses hahaha
yeah yeah he's probably working
for those super chattels thank you so
much so much for the generous
Mega hyper super generous
for chantos thank you for the support
for staying with Chihuahua for such a
long time it's not a given and I know
that thank you for not being sick of me
yet
cyric
yeah
[Music]
your attention for the pinky
and this was when I was doing my speech
you're giving me 100 points so what
hello for staying until the end thank
you
thanks for listening
[Music]
10 out of 10. oh it's a Skyrim meme I
need to play Skyrim
iron
speech level hundred damn you couldn't
have a speech level in Skyrim
what the [\h__\h]
each level
in that game
whether it be a speech level zero can
you not communicate with like NPCs
or does with speech like can you die
like I don't know convince
NPCs oh you oh yeah for convincing oh
persuasion that's what I thought now ah
wow haggling oh I see
that makes a lot of sense now
Oblivion tomorrow until oh
you speak like a caveman in Fallout NB
do you mean me or the character in
Skyrim because I don't appreciate see it
being called you
bunga
science
I'm gonna look for your answer
are you saying I sound like Unga Bunga
in Fallout
I'm waiting for your answer
I'm I'm in Fallout New Vegas have speech
checks
uh-huh okay
[Laughter]
ah careful they're careful
it's the usual room
it's close
could already smell it
stop it guys stop stop being cute
Alvaro thank you Shin my beloved there's
a bell Duncan for the pinky happy second
anniversary I never thought I would be
here for this long honestly I also
doubted it
you have helped me through the difficult
parts of my life and I've become a lot
happier looking forward to what the
future brings and will continue to
support you forever thank you now that
better not be a lie
you must be an honest person and live
your life honestly so you can never turn
that into a lie you must commit thank
you for committing
induction
now
ah
getting ready for work though since
there wasn't anything there was
something
oh my God cyrack
it took so long
why would you do that
where were you
unbelievable
okay you can go to work now
goodbye I guess
[Laughter]
I mean
have a nice evening yes indeed YouTube
you too sir
um have a good day uh farewell indeed it
was a quite fancy seeing you here today
I I very much appreciate
your existence
thank you
politely saying goodbye
[Music]
da4289 thank you thank you
[Laughter]
is there something wrong with me if I
enjoy lady Kiwa or Joe summon Valley
Girl piano on the round Queen no not at
all that's that is just you know the
normal way
foreign
[Music]
but this speech was great it really
moved me and showed me even more how
great you are this is the reason we love
you and thank you for everything till
now and I look forward to more happy
second anniversary thank you
ah not a very emotional person don't
hold it back it's okay to be emotional
just in case you needed to hear that
it's okay let it out let it out
put your head on kiwawa's lap and let it
out
I will stroke
your chicken feathers
and then rip them out and then get you
ready for the breading and then for the
frying
it was a mistake to trust me
I
anyway so thank you
thank you for the red super chat
[Laughter]
thank you thank you for everything so
[\h__\h] wow wow I'll support you with
everything I can to help you make your
dream come true you're really an
inspiration to us all with your undying
burning determination and passion
couldn't wish for a better or she ever
thank you oh so sweet
hmm I feel like
I I still have many reasons many things
to improve
um so in in reality I feel like you
could wish for a better ocean
I still have
room to improve definitely
um but thank you for loving me the way I
am and that's it wow
[Music]
you guys are so weird cute
foreign
standing in line now waiting to get the
same treatment
ah aren't we cute today huh aren't we
tied here today
um
my friend does for a good time
no see that's not a good time at all
because I watched um I started watching
a new series
sets out on Amazon they only have um two
episodes so far I think
it's called serpent the serpent Queen
it's again
[Music]
you know in the
1400s 1500s I think more the 1500s
um about you know royalty but this time
it's about
um uh Italian
Queen princess at the time going to uh
France uh really interesting I didn't
know about this lady before
um but then there was one scene in the
second episode where
um like the the first in line for the
throne in France he yeah the meditative
family yes yes yes yes
the first line he like tries to like
assert dominance I guess uh
was it him I think it was him yeah he
like
orders wait
I'm not mixing up shows now right it was
I'm pretty sure it was that so when that
happened yeah they they have like a verb
I think it was a hawk
and I feel like that hop was only for
messaging or something my brain is like
like right now a falcon [\h__\h] maybe it
was a falcon and then he's like
he's in a bad mood he's like okay now
rip out its feathers
and then they start like they were like
hey what the [\h__\h] is this with this
dudes and they start ripping out the
feathers and the bird is like crying and
screaming
I'm like oh what the [\h__\h]
poor bird so sad so oh poor bird poor
baby
sad
it was only a short scene that was like
bent to show how pissed he was I guess
the first in line is kind of a [\h__\h]
sassy Baka
it's an interesting show though so far
is pretty good um they do this thing
where they break the the fourth wall or
the third world or the fifth wall
whatever they break a wall by having the
think
not only the main character they
sometimes also Side characters they let
them speak to the camera
like they look at the camera and they
give a comment
about what's going on
um like like something in their mind
breaking the wall
um
but it's not
too weird
it still feels like overall serious
um and I like I like you know that
that's Medici girl
she by history
by lore she's supposed to not be very
pretty and thankfully they also casted
an actress said I'm not gonna say she's
ugly I'm sure she can be very pretty too
but you know she's like not the super
model Queen you know and I appreciate
when shows do that when they don't
especially because that's the main
character they cast a character that
does not look like a supermodel hmm
so I really appreciate that
normally they say [\h__\h] it the whole main
cast have has to look like supermodels
you know like for for the tutors a show
I loved so much Henry looked like a
[\h__\h] supermodel but actually like he
looked like [\h__\h] supermodel
throughout the whole show I would have
maybe understood in the beginning but
Henry the eight he was pretty fat you
know a general like every king would be
pretty homely because I'm pretty fat I
guess because you know that is a sign of
wealth back then but of course they cast
all the kings as like super handsome
good looking thin buff guys
someone realistic
but again I mean partially I get why
because that's a recipe for success
to a certain point
like the guy who played tutors
I'm sure he brought in a lot of like
fangirls falling over him
what do you mean Kiara what the [\h__\h]
this is true
yeah I mean I'm sure he was fit when he
was younger but then the older he gets
he shouldn't have gotten fatter
um
they at least tried to make him look
more exhausted and
older a little bit older by the time of
the last season
but I don't think it's enough hmm
yeah
they hated her because she told them the
truth yeah absolutely but what about the
super chance
[Music]
custom super attractive because it sells
yeah that's basically
what they do what they do hmm
sells well Attractive people
bring success
you asked us to stop your tangents
[Music]
no you wouldn't actually try to do that
would you
I should hire you then oh
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
my God these hands are really useful
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
no
I am Opera and Opera
M Opera
Opera Opera
not losing
yeah maybe I was I think I was trying to
do South Buffalo then probably
don't know that's probably where that
melody was from
ah
this Super Chat rating stream
it's quite something isn't it
you guys are witnessing greatness
yes I am the entire Opera yes
hmm
why does it feel like a 2021 superchar
reading stream why what does it make it
feel like that why why why why why why
why why why why why
also Evans L just wanted to know I see
all of your tweets even if you don't
tweet it right at me I see I see I see
you commenting you know about my streams
like oh my God I would almost follow her
I'll almost make make her one or she if
she would do this now I would make a
myoshi and again and again and again I
fulfill these things that you say that
would make you that would make me your
or she and then you still continue
your little [\h__\h]
their ways explain yourself
explain yourself
let's be honest here I am your or she
very clearly
I see also the times when you're dead on
Twitter even that I see and then and
then you're like like somebody replies
to you and then like should I should I
show this to Chihuahua and you're like
oh no please don't oh no but I see it
even if they don't show it to me
I know you love me you can't fool me
love me love me said that you love me
fool me fool me don't [\h__\h] fool me or
I'll put you in the usual
[Laughter]
be true to yourself
honest
[Music]
thank you for the pinky thank you for
the two years of memories so far kiwawa
there's been
see that's difficult to remember at all
here's many more of memories to come
that's exactly what I'm saying Christy
it is difficult to remember them all
most difficult question that people
could ask me is what's your favorite
stream that you have done so far which I
feel like is such a such a basic
question is that people ask in like
interviews but also like generally if I
if I open marshmallows or whatever
that's such a difficult question to
answer
that's why I I try to not ask stuff like
that where you have to remember
something really specific in Hollow talk
I try to stay away from that even though
I would like to hear the answer but I
I'm sure that if I would put the girls
that I interview on the spot like that
that they often wouldn't know
what to answer unless they prepared it
beforehand
um
because I don't think I'm the only one
with this problem
yeah
and then and then just because you're
under time pressure you would just come
up with some answer like oh well my
anniversary stream or so that it's just
something really big that seems like a
good answer I I would do the same
probably oh yeah the off collab yeah
but was that really
was that really the stream I enjoyed the
most in my whole two years you know
can't remember
can't remember but I think oh you know
what I
um the streams something I really
enjoyed I remember tunic and also the
later alligator for example later
alligator was so precious oh my God
loved it so much
but that's like I guess in terms of
games that I really enjoyed
cute
Yakuza was also really enjoyable yeah
yeah
and I loved playing Tales of arise and
ryza like jrpg is on stream
it's because that's just when I'm in my
elementia
and no one can really
judge me for being shitty at the game
because it's really hard to be shitty at
like tales off games
it's almost impossible
[Laughter]
at least for me
oh no I haven't played Short hike yet
but I did play yeah donuts come to
County
foreign
it's one of those games that
eventually if I need like a
quick short game
I will play it indeed I died in a
tutorial tutorial of tales of Xperia
[Laughter]
pathetic
absolutely pathetic
just kidding
skank just kidding
yeah all right let's finish this I'm
like
I'm almost there I think
[Music]
yeah oh I can see the end basically
the camera instead of a raggle thanks
for the Pinky Okay I'm going to learn
German now really
really are you really gonna commit to it
but you can try at least try to watch my
German streams I'll try to mix in a
little bit of English here and there
yeah I do it already damn wow respect
good luck with that I wish you all the
best thank you for the support
maybe one day you can send me a really
fluent German super jets
big hug from Peru thank you
picture
thank you
that is hopefully your last one Tai Chi
let me look down yeah that looks like
your last one
another red super chat I think that's
another separate account
19. I feel like you spent your life
savings on that stream thank you so much
thank you
and Mark thanks for the pinky never in
any Dimension or timeline should you
consider yourself having failed anything
it's all learning you're so talented
sweet and honest with us and I look
forward to seeing you continue the final
we will cheer you on no matter what
thank you very sweet
[Music]
it will be a learning process life is is
a learning process yeah
yeah thanks for being so kind I will
continue
try to be
the Oshi and the idol that you guys love
so much thank you Amarth
we do do you
Skai Jackson That's the last one thank
you Skye for watching over the stream
for 12 hours in your helicopter
tech maester
for the pinky or two pinkies
woke up just a hashtag woke up just in
time for your ending I
ain't [\h__\h] kidding me open the mic
what's your excuse even though the
stream is buffering really badly at my
end currently I do hear you one reason
why I love you is because of your grit
and determination
how you're just dropping that bump and
then just go on as if as if as if your
absence would just be okayed by me
but I feel like you were here in the
beginning at least now
look I mean I've split up the Super Chat
so much but I feel like you were there
in in the beginning of the stream Maybe
and then
maybe I don't know what the [\h__\h]
or if he wants the whole VOD you will be
forgiven
I just just comes in the last 10 minutes
and it's like hi
I just woke up it feels absolutely no
shame
okay Mike
that is
that is quite the confidence you have
there
rainbow so I guess you just went to
sleep somewhere in the middle of that
okay okay okay I forgive
I forgive baby perhaps probably
I'm in a good mood
yeah
drop a rainbow and pass out yeah that's
fine I guess
your passion reminded me of the years I
was at my the at my lowest of low in my
career hashtag yolk
thank you that's all
[Music]
um
I hope now you are at the highest of
your high
highest of high of your career and life
or maybe maybe just maybe not the
highest but a high I hope it still can
go even higher
that would be nice
thank you Mike for waking up yeah well
how's your woking up
and kitchen for being part of the
um marathon and for being part of kfp
History
[Music]
foreign
let's call
Maxwell first thank you not an English
speaker Dan kitchen
thank you
and for girls thank you for the rest of
the chat happy second anniversary
potential you're already a living legend
at this point
yes I am specific memories may be lost
with the pass of time
true but the feelings that were born
from them will remain forever here's
many more years together with kfp well
said well spoken danke schoon thank you
very much for being here and supporting
me
ah
that's love induction my great Junior
negation Garden Park
thank you for the words of a chat you
play a bigger part of our lives than you
thank you Wawa but keep supporting you
for as long as you let us love you Kiana
[Music]
thank you
for the support
yeah
um
you guys also play a big part of my life
very big you're actually the biggest
part in my life
you guys
I'm gonna cook anything tonight yeah I'm
planning on it I bought some extra
ingredients like you know
it's not I would say this is not even
completely my fault but like when they
send like salads
in hellofresh boxes
already by the time it arrives or maybe
if I leave it for like you know for one
day the salad looks like [\h__\h]
foreign
some new um
forgot
uh what's the word
the thing that makes you cry
the one that makes you cry
onions yes thank you
because like the onion That was supposed
to be in that box I used uh for a
different recipe because the onion that
wasn't that box was like ew
and we cut like half of it away me and
my mommy
because it was eel and then we were like
do you have any more onions I'm like
yeah I guess I can take this one
replacing
yeah some stuff that
I had also a blasted tomato
in the Box my most recent box
it was disgusting I opened up the the
hello fresh box and then I uh at first I
always take out the things things that
are cool to put them into the fridge and
then
um I noticed
uh somehow some stuff in the in the Box
was wet and then I'm like also smelling
uh something a little bit weird you know
so I look a build paper and I see that
one of the bags the recipe bags it's
paper bags is like wet pretty silk I'm
like what the [\h__\h] happened here
and then I carefully really carefully I
put on plastic gloves and then went
through the bag and then I uh because I
thought it might be moldy too you know
but it wasn't moldy it was just um like
an exploded tomato basically it was
still pretty intact but there was one
big rip in the tomato and that made
everything wet
and then the whole bag smelled kind of
blah so I didn't want to use it anymore
hmm
yeah I threw a delay
felt like everything was
uh infiltrated by the tomato
but even when I throw stuff like a
recipe bags away I still keep like the
packaged things like
like rice packages or panko packages
or whatever make your knees fetish
whatever is packaged I keep for another
time
but a lot of the times
the
veggies are mmm questionable
no you stay in the corner
yeah yeah
I try to keep
certain things at least
um
if possible
no well I agree you partially but I also
disagree part actually I I appreciate
how fresh for like making me
um like inspiring me and forcing me to
Cook and Cook things specifically that I
haven't cooked before
um yeah teaching me about certain things
how certain basic sauces are made and
all that that I normally like
would be like I don't know I'm just
gonna make the easiest thing that I can
think of spaghetti bolognese let's go
yeah
and
I used to like throw away a lot of food
too like ingredients because
I don't know would be too much
can't buy it in small portions a lot of
the time but but hello fresh sends it to
you and the perfect
amount but then the problem is since
they send it in the supposedly perfect
amount that if something is off then
haha then you're [\h__\h] foreign
like that tomato or that onion
anyway
I'm finally gonna
make that cheese burger that literal
cheeseburger
after the Stream
it's Burger because the Patty is
literally just cheese I don't know if I
will like it that sounds like a lot of
cheese but
I will report back
and with a side of a salad but maybe I'm
thinking maybe I'll make some fries
actually the recipe doesn't have it but
I have some leftover potatoes
because I love fries I love fries
always eat fries yeah
and it's like a baked common bird I
think
uh where was I where was I
was thank you for the rest of the chant
is that is that my face when I was
making the snail
that profile picture
my snail face
uh so in a sense that face
she was trying to be a snail
just minding my own business
cute snail Wawa cute and snail
what a glorious to use it has been
looking forward to all the amazing
events that come coming up as well as do
you I love you in every Universe kiwawa
thank you for the 12 incredible hours
rest up and see you soon thank you
every universe that is so romantic thank
you so much love you too
[Applause]
for the support
you also rest well you seem to be
resting now probably I don't see you in
the chat
sleep well sweet chicken
that was a strange reference oh really a
moral reference what
romantic anymore
now still it's so cute
slime thank you for the rest of the chat
congrats on second anniversary a new
original song Love
thank you thank you thank you thank you
original song I hope you liked it now
it's finally out at that time it wasn't
yet but now it is did you like it
slime
thank you for your support
[Music]
almost done I'm almost there
soon
[Music]
happy second anniversary my one and only
honestly that's me from our survivor
because oh my God you survived oh damn I
survived
for a fro in the hospital putting up one
thumb
taking a selfie
written on it is I survived [\h__\h]
yes
Survivor
I'm a survivor
was that also Destiny's Child or was
that just Beyonce
[Music]
it was damn
may I ask why she's saying thank you so
much in German because um my first
language is German so I
made it my thing to thank everybody in
German
after each super chateau
yeah
I wanted a thing you know a gimmick
basically and almost two years I got to
spend with you and it was the best time
I ever had stay awesome and as always
and never forget we timkins will always
follow and support you we love you Kiana
thank you bro for you're the best you're
so sweet
[Music]
mi amor
no
47 um
thank you for the Reds which had happy
anniversary thank you thank you for all
what you do for the past year and
endurance today there's so many good
memories and funny times even sad
moments yeah I will keep standing with
you for the next year and next year next
XXX
thank you
hopefully there will be all those next
years I'll do my best
thank you so much CS Polly a kiss for
you for you for your loyalty and your
support
for the pinky
and president goddess a trash compactor
so many titles but above all my oceans
one of those
titles seems off
which one is it huh Kiara and
presidential goddess the trash compactor
there's something
like it's falling out of the line
which one is it
oh yeah of course it's Kiana because
Kiana is my actual name and the other
ones are indeed just titles yeah yeah
yeah
it must be Kiana
ah he always bread in the day I'm so
glad to be along for this fun ride who
knows where we'll go next to Greater
Heights I'm sure much love to you Kiana
thank you much love back to you
thank you so much for being a part of
the journey
of the ride
even though you mixed in some weird
things there
I guess it's just a compliment to my
butt
I'll take it as a compliment
yeah
oh Amazon not a thing to save my fruit
thank you it's actually doing pretty
well because I was smart
to
read it it's separate
uh sessions I am done
take the wow no this goes into the trash
compactor whoosh
[Music]
free Nicks
yeah I finished hmm
Freedom whoa
Rachel wow a big stretch
no no super chats no no more
I still have some from other streams I
think like two streams or so
that's fine
um like tomorrow after GTA I can read
some more
for example
but we're done with this one that was
important because it came with a lot of
biggies a lot of red super chats thank
you for the memberships
now we talk about Hospital Dragon you
know what maybe I'll keep that for
tomorrow
oh well
GTA
tomorrow GTA
um now this schedule is a little bit
wrong
I'll fix it and then upload it to the
community board I guess
uh but yeah today is tomorrow then
sleepy sleep and GTA again because you
guys enjoyed it I enjoyed it so why the
hell not and then we have German Channel
stream 8pm on that day
and then Pickle Park on Amazon which you
know she was like who wants to play a
pickle bag and I'm like me because
actually I wanted to do a pickle Park
collab anyway at some point
but Amy
and they had the same thought as me that
girl
hey
more and more we're becoming one
yeah so that is actually uh a day after
wards
um yeah basically
uh for me midnight from Saturday to
Sunday I think
yes yes yes
and then members only remember is only
first and then Pickle Park Pickle Park
and then Ian idea Mangus uh which is the
one that I'm organizing and just to not
have any misunderstandings it doesn't
mean that every member from me and an ID
participates but it's a good mix
I would say
I think we're like uh nine
Nine Girls
there's still room so if anyone still
wants to join they're welcome
it's um I think a time that works
for all of them like I thought maybe
midnight this is midnight for Indonesia
I thought
of them will surely stay up forever I
don't know if all of them won and then
so many of the ID girls said yes yes
like we have Kobo
uh Muna I think
see let me see let me check
foreign
[Music]
those are the
ID Girls
yeah
couple I wonder how couple handles
accusations she'll just be like Mommy
accusing me and it turns out I'm
actually in the Imposter and I'm like I
can't help you
and then and then I get kicked out and
combo still calls for kiwama Mommy and
I'm not here
I would be cute to have mommy kiwawa and
Kobo both as imposters wouldn't that be
cute
together Dream Team
um I did really like the feature of
proximity voice chat but I don't know if
we can do it this time because last time
I remember last time I tried that when I
organized to
uh something
um there were problems like one member
just didn't work for them right I think
it was Ollie
and then you know it had some problems
with it
um and I was I felt sorry for Ollie
hmm so I'm not gonna force it I'm not
gonna force it
did we figure it out completely by the
end I don't remember do you guys
remember
yeah I'm sure only was also feeling very
pressured to fix it when you were on
stream and you're trying to fix
something and you just don't know how
it's very stressful
I would just use this chord at the end
didn't we
oh yeah but just like normal like gather
whenever there's a meeting and then
scatter when there isn't
I mean you know both ways are fine doing
it the classic way is totally fine too
and that's probably how we're gonna do
it because even if I tell everybody like
all the like Kobo for example and said
that don't I don't think they've ever
used it before and it's gonna be hard to
like explain and please install this do
this and that and do settings and that
settings
ah
I'll ask them if they want to if they
want to commit to it but you know
there's the the
chance and it might not work so
everybody would be would have to be able
to also test it out probably properly
um
haven't used it for a long time ever so
I'm also not really sure anymore how it
works but uh yeah
um
oh
[Music]
I mean
first and foremost that Among Us collab
is
to Showcase something anyway
it's not really I mean I'm it's not this
is not sponsored by the way I was just
like
I'm I'm I'm not part of it either
I'm not part of it I was just like asked
if I wanna
if I wanna do a collabo and I'm like you
know what I guess I love I can plan
something yeah
yeah there's something that's already
been announced I guess so I could say
and there was a a Mongoose X
whole life thingy yeah with some some
interestingly customized
Among Us characters all interesting yeah
so
that's basically
what I want to showcase
yeah no I'm not there's no no kiwawa
customizations
as far as I know
uh so it's not sponsored
but I am
kind enough once again this humble
humble
Queen Phoenix empress
once again is humble enough
and generous enough to Grace everybody
with organizing the collaboration oh
[Music]
confidence confidence guys
benevolent that is me
oh that um it's been a while since my
last Among Us collaboration with whole
life members so
um I'm looking forward to it I'm really
bad at
um being an imposter because I rarely
ever get the chance anyway and then I'm
really bad at um actually doing the job
and then protecting myself
so honestly I hope I just get
um
team team member or whatever the crew
matter
the whole time I would be fine with that
hmm
is there like a new map that we should
definitely try out that I should tell
the girls to
um take a look at
I feel like it would be boring to just
go for the normal most basic one again
because that one has been used like a
million times
no new maps
really
well I'll take a look anyway
foreign
[Music]
wasn't that like originally
just mods is it now an official feature
or am I confusing things
that it was never mods
anyway
oh official new rules that's cool oh
nice
okay
official scientist engineer shapeshifter
watch
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
anyway I'll go now
I will go now
I'll see you guys tomorrow for GTA today
[Music]
and in German we say thank you for being
here with me hanging out
in the meantime please stream do you
we're over 300K now let's go 500k go go
go go
thank you bye
love you
[Music]
foreign