[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
foreign
wake up hello good morning
I am
yeah but I will follow you I will be
brain empty but
uh it will be fine
yeah well let's do this then yeah I got
this first we should introduce ourselves
I think just real quick yes yeah who
we're playing hi my name is Maury
Calliope and I am playing this beautiful
being from God
um this half of work Barbarian wow
Barbarian named Mario pay
um she loves to smash she's not really
good at words and she's not super smart
[Laughter]
okay
Yara yeah all right sorry that my
character looks hotter than yours right
I don't really know what to say I'm a
bit traumatized because
I ran into a scene where something
similar to you was smashing and yeah
I mean in a bad way like yucky sick
everywhere how about you can you
introduce yourself
uh hello I am the I think I'm a ranger
I'm kiwawa and I don't have a POV today
but stream POV in my new album point of
view let's go let's go
[Music]
yeah thank you I don't know I'll pass it
to whoever takes a pass
oh yeah you go first you go first you
caught it you caught it I'm sorry
okay uh hi I'm koseki Bijou and I'm
playing as Bagel
the Gnomes The Gnome sorcerer I'm on
what is it yeah I'm a story sir right
now and I'm ready to get heated yeah you
look like breakfast
you're making me hungry people
hahaha
who said
okay there you go your face is right
where the cheeks are
there
hiya Darlings this is nervous The Raven
Croft I am playing as nurissa I didn't
realize uh when we made it that everyone
was gonna name themselves silly stuff so
oops but uh I'm this very uh sexy uh
looking deepling right here I'm also uh
currently a Bard might swap over I
haven't decided yet uh probably will
stay as this so maybe maybe yeah but
being a Bard is so useful so far I know
I I just look I have a plan now that
I've played through so much of the game
I need an item and I feel like it will
work better if I'm a cleric but I'm not
sure yeah we're not we're not the
experts anymore yeah
[Laughter]
the rest of us I think wow yeah very
addicted
yeah
but we have uh after last time concluded
to you know stay together a little bit
more right yeah and to go a bit uh a
little bit slower maybe of course we
can't look at everything but at least
we'll look at things together maybe this
time yes Cali will take the lead today
right okay
leader look at what she looks at a
cutscene or so moriope says team huddle
team huddle okay okay ladies all right
game plan how are we going to do this
because because we can make it a
bloodbath or we can try and be
charismatic and kind of like snake our
way in there
Charisma Charisma wow can we be Charisma
first and then kill them later yeah we
have the option to kill them at any time
so why not go in well first so then we
can uh you know talk to their Trader and
everything
yeah yeah yeah and then bloodbath right
yes exactly yeah exit going like an
arrow go in clean pull out real bloody
yes so who's charismatic forward hoe I
am charismatic I think we're yeah you go
there's a while back
was there a dude amongst the
seats
got one of them chined up below
are we are we talking about Bolo
nah volo's human Druid is halson yeah do
we want to go straight to him and start
that or do we want to look around first
Quest as his rescue
I thought it was about oh wait okay he
might be he might be yeah
let's go
all right I believe we take a right
all right
yes
[Music]
you're doing some freaky [\h__\h] over here
oh all right it's dangerous music yeah
let's go help him
someone else
we'll help him maybe Let's help this guy
is he okay he's being tortured we're
about to find out
[Music]
no don't whack him with your sick nobody
likes to get whacked with a stick
thank you sure
no no no no no baseball
can you please put some clothes on I'm
begging you
I don't think I will
look we can't handle your beauty
yes it's too much for us yeah this looks
interesting let me put him through his
Paces
use your brain worm please my brain worm
yeah you see a list isn't brainworm bad
no
add bonuses
good that is you don't need them for the
elephant okay
in the future
I'll use my my brain powers
sorry can you say that again please
don't be too rough maybe
is that a challenge
oh what you gonna do what the hell oh
I'm gonna go talk to him now yeah I'm
gonna come take a look
hi
please now I'm really thinking about it
I do like to smash
smashing is is
very powerful but let's see
good one
no
into a bear
sight of him
I don't know if he's still alive
it could be easy to find then yeah
think about it
I keep trying you'll figure it out
[Laughter]
Jesus I will help you
it's sleight of hand pick the lock good
luck
here can I add something here let me
help yeah yeah guidance thanks
appreciate it big up together
oh
my God
oh my God inspiration here wait wait
wait let me one more time oh
[Music]
yeah
oh my God I'm gonna give this one more
time wait let me let me add a bonus oh
no let me add a bonus
oh you got it it's fine it's fine
at the bottom it's okay I I I was I
think I was gonna try
you willed this to happen you forced it
you sure did and now I have no
Inspirations
that you just set somebody free you're
you're a true Soul what are they gonna
do before they catch us
um quick question do we share
inspiration
[Music]
comes from your different goals okay
guys yeah because we get like separate
Inspirations okay okay yeah
oh it is sharing apparently yes but we
get it from different actions yeah very
sorry for using it up I think we should
yeah it's okay let's ask in the future I
thought we had our own inspiration get
more inspired I wanted I wanted to let
him go lately really
[Music]
to the left
left no no no no to the to the left of
where we entered
oh okay okay
see all right I see you're going this
way I love this guy I know me too
hi
oh
that's why you guys like this uh
[Music]
companion no no okay you recognize he's
a free scourge
it's a follower
yeah he does look like he could be one
ah
are you also here too he's got nipples
he does yeah he does
right there I'm surprised they don't
have clamps
yes
you'll see why
you see her face
these goblins seem to thrive on the
crude and primitive
pain without purpose is a terrible thing
wouldn't you agree
who invited you a goblin
what are you gonna do exactly I want him
to beat my ass this is an intimate thing
and
you guys are a match yucky trying to
discuss such sucks
maybe I'm not sure
imagine just saying that excuse me sorry
I just saw some naturally sad looking
eyes uh I mean you guys are the same
trouble you're the same therefore we
should smooth
yeah is he flirting with me
no I just wants to beat you up little
one I can tell you
you came
oh
you look so concerned yeah I need some
help you guys please
I guarantee you a hug is nicer than
whatever he's about to do
why
isn't it
I think most of the gods are female yeah
the likes of which few experience
[Music]
just like she said
yes Ariana yes oh hmm
exclusive wow Divine possibly
please
[Laughter]
what is he gonna do oh you'll see him
simply face the wall
maybe the chancla oh boy he's gonna give
you a big hug from behind what face
[Laughter]
oh
getting my ass beat
[Laughter]
it gives me a permanent buff
it does yeah
I I talked to him because I want to stop
him no
no more that um
I I'm not gonna assist you in this one
my friend this is all you good luck
thank you
[Music]
give me more
Game of Thrones vibes
um who turned me around
[Laughter]
guys I need the blessing
[\h__\h] him I want to kill him right now
don't kill him I need him
I I don't think he needs help I think
she likes yum
you look tired should I take over
you're so into this right
yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
hurry up man
it's really okay
[Laughter]
okay
all right another Nat team
get ready
of course if you'd like
sure
[\h__\h] why he got to be so freaky about it
he's been killing you that's okay
no no no no I'm gonna get a buff I'm
gonna get a buff I'm proud to have
served you this thank you for the
penance
[Laughter]
I feel gross
thanks abdara
inspiring
firing she has deemed you worthy of her
blessing
wow yucky don't be disgusted you have
some acid dummy
whoa I'm getting a blessing you guys
what kind of blessing I don't know
[Laughter]
yeah he's so creepy
heal yourself
uh when you have 30 hit points or less
you get a two uh plus two bonus to
attack rolls with and wisdom saving
throws for three turns
yum
and it's permanent you never lose it let
me get a hit in oh okay okay there you
go okay okay I was I I was gonna do it
with my fist but I was holding it yeah
no I've I've never I've I've I don't
know if maybe it's a glitch if you're
supposed to lose it but I've had it
forever I I did it once and I was like
hahaha and then I was like oh this will
fade and then I was like it didn't go
away it didn't go away and now one went
away
you guys gonna get your ass beaten
minutes Forever Until the End of the
playthrough you lose it in act two oh I
still have it in act two
oh can we all get it I don't know did I
ruin it for everyone
I don't want it
[Laughter]
that's that's Fallon that's Fallon
all right well he doesn't seem keen on
giving it to others that's the same I'm
his favorite or something I guess so now
let's go free Zolo follow me yes
[Laughter]
let's go he's
okay
[Music]
can we talk to him
you know okay wait are you the woman in
charge here um
it doesn't look like we can chat can we
chat we could we could just kill her we
could just kill her
well I just feel like that's that's well
right here's here's the thing if yeah if
we have if we have the doors closed
curiosity they won't stop us
so I admitted something of an impossible
please I wonder maybe we could strike a
deal he's asking really car and Lou to
unlock herself
oh if he's asking nicely we should help
him out right do what your heart tells
you
all right I'll get you out boys
I'll wait nicely but
he's still Daddy
[Music]
can we just smack the door
um I think so but we'll have to kill the
lady in here unless she left I don't see
her
look
[Music]
no no no don't we'll kill her we'll kill
her it won't don't worry the door is
closed it won't it won't it won't make
anyone angry
bam
too easy
yeah that can be for him now oh we got I
got a key I can open the door okay yeah
open it up
I'll pick up some of these boots yes
[Music]
okay what now bolo come out follow us
okay you know what else oh do you owe me
yeah make him pay up he does owe me so
that's your character
tell me where we can meet each other one
slip the goblin yoke
or something no way
Larissa did you save him in your
playthrough I don't even remember I
think I accidentally skipped him
okay go to camp yeah I can't be our be
our entertainment
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
he's dead now we gotta fight
mm-hmm
oh no not the Wardrobe oh they called
everyone you gotta destroy them
um
[Music]
uh let's run
let's get out of here let's just dash
out of the goblin camp we probably can
we can try
again yeah
we need to get we need to get house then
oh so do you want us to run no we we we
we won't win but we can try to fight
this
laughs
out of my way
frenzy oh you hit so hard that's so nice
as well yeah that's what I'm here for
um
what it's big old oh I think the boss oh
yeah this is this is just one boss so
there's three different bosses here
um if we kill them we get their brain
worms
yeah brain worms and we can eat them
all gotta gotta gotta catch them all
exactly if anyone has AOE I feel like
that would definitely be the one can you
please I'm sorry can you please tell me
what AOE means
it's like big big attack that hits
multiple people I have one of those
kind of yeah definitely use those when
they're grouped up together yeah
sounds like a plan
aggroes the entire Camp I wonder why
these guys are aggroad at us yeah
maybe they definitely figured out we
committed murder yeah
my wolf is somehow stuck like kind of
far away yeah I can't move him
or lupus
hey it's okay I have an idea whenever I
get a turn again in a million years oh
he's being attacked by the goblin oh no
he's having his own fight over there
kibaba your turn
which one which one let's go for this
one
why did she get so close to me
nice nice hit
so I'm gonna shoot something out and you
guys need to not walk through it or
it'll hurt you okay oh okay are you
talking about the uh clouded daggers
yeah yeah those are so good
they are so yeah we can push people off
of stuff and they'll take damage if they
fly but if you knock anyone into a Chasm
please know that you will not be able to
collect any of their loot
ah okay but it is what you have no spell
slots
they say I'm looking at your chat it
they say you have no spells it's not
even my turn
I don't know what that means I
oh my God they're right it's probably oh
[\h__\h] you use that that's okay I have
some I I might I have an AOE
sorry Kiana
it didn't light you up it didn't light
you up I'm sorry I'm sorry run away
oh oh she's okay she's okay
we can definitely kill these guys don't
even worry about it are you sure
not with me almost killing Kiana I'm
gonna be okay
all right get ready to feel pain dummies
do your best
yes keep in mind we have the boss right
behind me that's right right behind you
yeah okay she's got 40 health
yeah she came up pretty quick
and she's very strong mm-hmm oh I
completely cheesed that Boss by the way
before Oh I killed her easily
let's go
we'd like to rage they're all on the way
oh my god there are so many but I feel
like you can do it we can do it yeah
we'll see
them how I believe
I blame Volvo for this
Volvo Volo what's this what's his name
[Laughter]
yeah yep yeah okay she's a true Soul
High Priestess of the absolute well
don't take an action jump is a bonus
action
yeah
kick her ass b-boom yeah that's the boss
yep
I'm still blinded
that's a little oh it looks like you
should be having to smoke poke into the
dark
I want to use a spell but I don't want
to use it when I have a disadvantage
well she attacked me if I run
yeah
you just have to walk but you walk
slower
uh okay I will for now I'll do this
oh seven damage that was sick okay she's
all sharp I'll work on her for a little
bit yeah until I get out of line
we'll cover you Kiana you got you got
any uh health potions yeah yes I do
waiting for my turn sorry for killing
you on accident that's okay
it's okay
there you go that's not much but a
little bit yeah
oh maybe the guy in front of you if you
can attack
I hope it doesn't miss
oh let's go
nice good job
yay
[Music]
[\h__\h]
[Applause]
I want to save you but I gotta focus on
frenzy and raging out I'll just go back
to sleep yeah take a nap take a nap
okay you need you and your cute animals
I'll see you in five
okay
all right just sweet dreams
don't let the team be wiped don't let it
happen
please no party wipes
it's fine
yeah when in doubt we'll do it Bart
dance yeah yeah
this will save us that did nothing very
smart
strike
yeah yeah sure why not
boom
yeah there goes another one of them
everywhere
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h] oh no my strength my strength is
debuff oh we're oh
poison
ow
ing my people
let the bodies hit oh
it's fine I'll live okay yeah do your
best
buy to kill her yes
that would be the move
I need to jump I'll jump to
Chihuahua yeah
careful there's acid on the Forum
oh yeah because you turn away from him
that's why he tries to hit you there's
like a red arrow whenever you turn away
from an enemy mm-hmm no you can you can
do it again you can try again if it's
still
lit up yeah I still have the ball then
you can you can try again
nice
that was sick
okay get her
nice yeah
are you kidding me
yes
what how high was the percentage
yeah that's not really good episode 60
is pretty much zero in this game yeah
I regret a blame it needs to be healed
to get back up all right I'll come help
throw a potion
damage you maybe maybe I can do it
so good Kelly focus on damage right nice
okay
I can't heal you though
sorry try okay do you have potions Kiara
I I
uh
you have one one potion yeah it should I
still can't use it yeah you have to use
it when you're in a turn
so
don't die just um
yeah we're all we're not doing so hot
gamers
we'll be fine well I have a disadvantage
nice nice God that feels good
I should be fine if I can fly out of
here
why do they do they all go for me
because you're so beautiful oh
I don't think we're gonna make it
[Music]
doesn't work out for us this is just
these guys
[Music]
no I'm gonna still try to get the boss
yeah
I'm gonna miss
What if I
jump jump
dang it tried to hit you
jump
okay
nice
please
hits
a lot of you took a big chunk of damage
into her she's almost dead yeah yeah
and she's out of there okay and I'm
connected to her so I can hit again nice
are you kidding me
at this plus four okay
oh
um
so help us Volo yeah me Volo if it
weren't for us freeing you
yeah honestly this is all his fault
oh his fault all of it
I feel like their attacks aren't missing
us as much as they should be yeah
they're getting real like we're we're
missing a lot of hits for them hitting
everything
party yeah
and I'm about to die it's all up to you
too let's go game of the century
um
really you know yeah actually
[Music]
nice nice okay now block my way hit Cali
people are you sure about that
oh my God oh my God she survived
I can't believe it you endured
[Music]
that's wild omori all over again oh okay
okay
yeah suck on that
um all right it's my turn
so it's not
wildly by dang it okay good luck you're
so close thank you I can perish do I
have a better heel
probably not
where the healy's at
4hb
ate
for HP in a dream yeah healing her
um
in my death Pros
I I will not die
yeah yeah 26 HP okay all right and we're
here you will look for breakfast compare
that to my one HP wolf and
um
[Music]
but you know now there's the other the
other ones
[Laughter]
[Music]
that doesn't look so good okay wow maybe
maybe we should reload yeah
we tried we tried okay
try I think we need to Long rest yeah I
only have two spells yeah I think I
think we should long Rest Long rest yeah
only short rest is available oh
we are trapped we are in um okay well
let's get out of prison
should we short dress at least
um yeah give us a little bit of help
I can't see anything oh okay there we go
see there's a key somewhere lock pick
somewhere
um
um wait what about the way the guy jumps
you know hey look what's in here yeah
okaying legs pretty sure from the hole
mysterious oh someone failed your skin
we can eat them
[Music]
I'll pull it free actually
come on out I want to see some guts
still blocked I'm in oh it should be
easy enough
too many McDonald's should be able can
we all get through at least
what what happened
oh it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's okay
oh let's go let's go we can do this
yeah
good luck good luck
now we totally got they took all of our
weapons
what what yeah haven't you noticed we
don't have any weapons
punch
[Music]
wait I have no spells either yeah yeah
they took your magic ability away can we
load it can we load can we load a save
maybe back back a little when was the
last time we saved oh man uh when we
started the stream oh no auto save
nah we should I should have been saving
um
[Music]
is that possible in the hole the other
way
I don't see the hole anymore maybe it
was above us no it's still there it's
it's in the little it's behind you
going though
I guess we just punch them [\h__\h] it guys
we ball
we have to balls
okay I have some bombs uh I have no oh
okay uh oh I still have I still have
some spells yeah we have nothing they
literally wow strike frenzy all right
all just Frenzy
and they just punch him do your best
I'll leave it to you today
no she's too far away okay uh
there's a skeletons
the skeleton has a candle and a ring of
poison resistance but that doesn't look
quiet
um
but I was thinking maybe somewhere here
there's a weapon or so
maybe the other sacrifice we can pick
their their weapons up if we kill them
yeah yeah so good luck guys free money
okay here we go the one
what's he gonna do oh no no no
[Music]
we can still do it
what happens if we die here again do we
just go back into prison
probably
[Music]
um
no
well well if it isn't the consequences
with my actions because I think this all
started because of me
that's all right it's cool
yeah bro the candle will it will it set
them on fire I mean if there's stuff on
the ground like uh you know oil then yes
okay I'll still try it even though
there's no oil
[Music]
um
55 is pretty low oh
I need to hold on I know I don't know
what happened but yeah yeah I mean it
hit
yes
that's um most of what I can do
no worries it's fine
I'm taking it
whoa our tanks
we can get weapons if we loot them after
murdering them yeah
just one yeah the arrow would be nice
bow
[Music]
it didn't work it was super dead
everyone wanted to say if you get me up
maybe you can use me as a weapon
yeah I could throw you yeah throw me
around yeah yeah
perfect perfect yes perfect perfect but
if I turn around now I'm gonna get beat
yeah they'll hit you yeah if someone
could get me out I can
run to you I guess
to get
enrage throw
leather boots
I'm sure that would work
I was sure
well we tried yeah this doesn't look too
good for us
um however however
um well what we could do is you know we
could just reload and then what we could
do is all the scenes that we already did
uh everyone can individually go and do
one
so I can go do the BDSM if we just go
back in jail
I mean we just we just won't kill the
lady again this time yeah we haven't
done much progress anyway yeah yeah yeah
so I say I say we just let's just get
out of here
oh it just launches and it'll it'll uh
alert people it's so cool yeah it's like
it's like the sauron's eye nice
she's the one whose underwear we need to
steal them
all righty everybody
the game quickly get beat yeah
yeah I'll get beat and then we'll do a
long rest and then we'll uh you guys can
free the guy while I'm doing that so you
don't have to walk
yeah
and then yeah I'm watching that it's
fine you got to see it once I hope it
goes just as well for you oh me too yeah
yeah oh I'm getting a splash party
t-shirt for the Bingo rewards oh wow
guys
did you get something
no did you
played at all no accomplishment
it is what it is all right now let's
onward to help Zorro
for me
all right and I go to my destiny again
is the guy uh the guy is not Volo right
you know talk about no not yet
nah he's just a random dude
all right you you girls you will take
care of that you'd rescue thing I'll
talk to one of these crackers forgive me
but
let's hope you don't fail twice again
let me give you guidance simply
yes
let's do this chat yes
no pain no gain exactly
can can we we can
nice
without getting in trouble yeah
okay cool
um
free
and we gotta save the barn
AKA you I mean me too yeah I'm saving no
no I'm good I'm good
okay
[Music]
there's a nice looking book here
be wary of your mortal limitations
okay I'm good I'm good they're having
some fun over there okay yeah while this
is tempting to allow Payne's ecstasies
to sweep you away particularly during a
delicious bout of self-regulation broken
bones Hindu worship of our Maiden no
pain
so don't go too far eh
don't go too far with the pain
what do you mean
broken bones hinder the Revelation or
something like that oh I'll be fine
where'd he go flagylation
why is he running outside sir hello sir
sir pain
[Music]
are you afraid
hello why are you frighten them
guys get away from him I don't know why
he'd be frightened to me oh cause he's
scared of your dog
oh my God Kiana go away
and all that and then get away I need
him to beat my ass so we can move on
okay why don't know okay why don't you
guys go heal why don't you you go here
do a save before we do that
okay cool
what chicken oh my god get your
woman I
ain't room yeah it's me
they ran away he ran away you
interrupted my cutscene where did he go
he literally just ran all the way away
yeah he he went up an iron ladder
well maybe that was just my way of
protecting you why would you do that to
me
because I love you don't you know that
[Laughter]
should I should I Authority this guy
wait you know it yeah I I encountered
Raphael who's Raphael is Raphael Satan
yeah it sounds like it which you do I
don't know
I got her
much Satan hold on I'm second dialogue
they do
is living here
well met
aphase dialogue
that doesn't look like Satan uh not yet
why yay okay
what happened
maybe maybe he will give you the pain
that you need to gain so
he's he's just threatening me but like
he's trying to not sound like he's
threatening me oh no oh no please no I'm
in the middle of something Raphael
come
on
where are you going
oh beautiful is this hell let's go it's
his house
[Music]
what are you guys seeing the House of
Hope
that's a beautiful picture oh if I go to
go on oh I see a joint conversation oh
after all it's might just pause
you last
hmm
she's sick
HP yeah I told you he's look believe it
[Music]
hi Daddy
I'm gonna kill you what's better no you
can
you devil you do
I got it
I knew he'd say that
potentially
an adversary conceivably
that's for certain oh let's go ah
I don't trust him because my compassion
is
Raphael is something something else
please I'm in the middle of another cut
scene can you hurry it up
I don't know why we just encountered
this time two tenants
and no
suit
I could fix it all like that he sounds
really compassionate yeah
wow oh fancy house and what is madness
but a denial of reality
still I have a feeling change your mind
before it it changed for you shut up
shop around beg borrow why did this
happen to me exhaust every possibility
until why did I climb up that ladder
here would you like evil people yeah are
you a demon too I mean yeah I mean in
game I'm just a tiefling I'm not
technically an infernal you know
okay can you send me back
send me back
this is what you get for for just
looking out for the pain
I'll be around watching you squirm what
a [\h__\h]
yeah yeah
[Music]
you're self-interested but not even in a
fun way like hysterian is they haven't
manifested yet in a bad way yeah he's
just annoying he doesn't even call me
darling I know I'm so mad do it I called
he's just so funny
you sounded so sad in the beginning
thank God I don't like this dude you're
like I thought you'd like him because I
know narissa I was like of course
and she didn't believe me where is my
pain guy
why is he just gone where did he go did
he go
okay I'm gonna let Volo out I have a I
have a key set him free
hello
I'm here to finish my cut scene please
come back
my blessing
ah that sucks and I didn't have to kill
her this time so they're not aggro to us
this is the good timeline yeah
I got to skip like the other two okay
that's not too bad
nice
oh okay we should long rest oh you got
the pain after all yeah he just like
randomly re-showed up so
hi
soon my friend soon we can chat
the buff isn't really permanent anyway
it's bugged is it
okay we can rest now he he went away
yeah yeah this time he was really
invisible I really didn't see him yeah
yeah he he went invisible all right
let's let's camp
let's Camp you guys want to go camp yeah
yeah yeah let's go to camp
do you want to end the day yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
oh and let's save
oh yeah oh hey what's happening people
are you okay you feel good am I okay I
don't feel so good oh you got a tummy
bug drips you're gonna transform through
your fingers sorry people we're about to
become you're about to become um
you can't be helped mind flare we're
gonna have to kill you sorry boo the
run's over for you
your hands Shake as they reach upward
you've always went from Palm spaghetti
arms spaghetti arms spaghetti arm
spaghetti oh no oh wait
here I'm not gonna kill you
I thought we were friends
well I thought we were pissing your
belly traveling Partners I guess
she hates everybody I see it yeah why
are we so mean I hate her yeah I don't
think we really I don't think anyone
here really oh no I really like her in
my run she's so freaking powerful
I'll take the vampire dude over here
myself I mean and Carla
they're both really helpful on my team
um I have I have persuasion I uh
use my Wrist all right
uh guidance to
Advantage roll let's go yeah is that the
[\h__\h] When the Roll doesn't show up
probably I think so
oh I'm lagging tell us what you got yes
I got 24. nice big
I cannot trust my own mind
I must trust yours I Will Wait Marissa
is lagging now because it's above no
because of the cutscene okay because
since I'm playing it alone I turned up I
forgot I turned up everything to the map
okay wait we need to revive a Starion
please before we leave Camp
if it gets too much you have to wait are
you guys no I I can I can turn it down
during the game I mean because there's a
there's the the leak the thingy the
thingy leak hey it's Mommy
my other bearded friend oh my God the
guardian
the memory leak oh yes fellow bearded
lady hello
dark man
mommy wow
hello Mommy
wow I know your voice I've heard it
before
you have oh I saved you mother
mommy oh she
oh
um
can you romance Your Guardian I want to
romance my guardian I know right romance
myself yeah
I made my guardian so hot like my mind
flayer
she seems so nice
take the hand offer to you no Mori the
Beards blend
people are saying technically you can
romance them
closely yeah sort of can actually
nice that is great it looks oh I didn't
know that
I think it is to resist the power it
gives but you
don't worry no it's like telling us to
wait is she actually bad consuming um
don't say anything don't spoiler yeah
there's yeah no spoilers but the the
point is they're hot because we designed
them
why not because in our brain is bad and
now they're saying to use the yeah yeah
yeah yeah so I feel like they're bad so
I actually uh I don't know so it's not
really a spoiler because I don't know
but um I don't know
I like them
I'm willing to take help from anyone
who's willing to help me in this game
because there's not many because if none
of the companions are attractive for a
way that you like then you just make one
yeah yeah
Trust of the worm just like this
exactly like this
the enemy is closing in
so is this some kind of dream world or
where are we
the astral plane
um isn't that
the place between death and life I have
no idea
that's limbo that is true if hot then
yeah it's like it's hot why why evil and
then why hot yeah said wrong if even why
hot gear is right
oh
we're okay now
I guess let's see
um yeah we're going back
wait wait no we got a healisterian
s
uh where is he it's over here
get on the floor everybody walk the
dinosaurs
back and that's fine we can keep his
close because I'm not giving him his
clothes back either
he's okay writing the balance oh yeah
Beyond mortal rest I know you have a lot
to say an amalgamation just skip it we
don't need to we don't need to people
get mad when I skip the dialogue
me I do
no people watching
um
he's all right yeah he's pretty I mean
he I wish he had more of a nose but
let's talk about something else very
well wait uh I can only say change class
I can't change my life
we've been there too long go talk to him
maybe maybe somebody else talk to him
yeah
um
[Music]
you did it oh he's good morning
oh is he back talk to me why won't he
talk to me oh bibu is talking to him
beating up or she's talking to someone
oh okay
assistant
there was a visitor promising reputation
clueless I suppose you absolutely
yeah man
[Music]
um
you can always see the bite marks pretty
well oh
exactly it's rip waste notes
comes to mind a parasites now was there
anything else the Vic lives it's Vic
Hotel who I'm a magistrate back in the
one from a ttrpg we did with myth oh
the vampire NPC there's always one you
always you need way more annoying than
him though
Darion is nice sir I like Hysteria
[Music]
of course boss your history accidents
find the camera finding is my job my
friend if there's anything in the world
worth knowing
I assure you you do be everywhere
okay uh you know what I'll talk to you
more in my private run
okay
okay should we also talk to Gail because
he has yeah yeah
chat him up
yeah
spare me a moment
Gail by the way I don't think I'm
traveling together I like him most most
all the romance options are pretty good
actually
but I don't have time to do runs to
romance all of them
I'm not really feeling anyone in the
game to be honest
romance I have this
yeah
you you like have able to fight with you
yeah I'm pretty sure
so do I
I guess I'll try that thank you for the
offer
very specific what it comes down to is
this I know I know you want the items
magical items you're trying to give him
a bunch of those and none of them were
good enough for him and he got mad and
ready wow
yeah
he just took mine but is it even worth
helping him when we're not taking him
with us anyway
don't worry about it
no no no no nothing like that maybe
it's quite literally yeah
I literally gave him the shittiest items
such artifacts challenging for us so
unreasonable look I'm trying to help you
buddy
since before we were abducted
as early as possible
he's annoying but I love him we have an
intervention
Dale you have an addiction please yeah
are you sure you really need that magic
your implicit trust is
free anyway apparently
for now for now we can let him scream or
do we
then let me see him no I don't have
anything
but I'm in school green green magic
one of us might in our inventory if you
click the tab you can see everyone in
the urgency of the situation it only
shows mine okay we can let him squirm
for a little bit yeah yeah yeah yeah
come back yeah we'll come back later he
can take it he needs to calm down from
his addiction anyway
I can spare anything right now okay
he's desperate
man you have to understand oh my gosh
what will you do yeah let's see what's
he say what's he gonna say
will he rob me of nothing will he leave
[Music]
enjoy it yeah trying to help him out
here and he's like I understand he's
going through something Jesus Christ
Gail God uh yeah okay so it's Kelly's
armor and my necklace and then uh Bijou
has an oil of accuracy or those are just
uncommon but uncommons are fine right
does should I give up my oil
is this oil right yeah does that work I
think right
does that work you can take the armor
I'm not using this
[Music]
you can't get potions okay oh okay
you wanna yeah it has to be an artifact
what's the difference what do you mean
an artifact I just gave him random green
items
yeah that's generally called yeah yeah
I have a spear that I'm using I could
give that no no let's not let's not do I
mean Cali said we could take our armor
so why don't we just take the armor
okay
Gail come on
yes yes my apologies I just
myself just
here oh not a strange dream dream last
night
or perhaps a certain parasite that's
clamped its jaws
so what happened to you focused on the
real world
he dies that is most gratified to hear
take it all in enjoy it before you
glitch out more oh it's
uh he reached out his hand but nothing's
happening oh wait yeah sorry
there take it take it
take it thank you
I don't work this time
wow
oh yeah he's addicted
what an addict
oh
he really liked your clothes
metaphorical demon I hate the points out
but no less dangerous
no less bound
you're welcome
yeah yeah yeah I believe you uh okay uh
yeah I heard this before please
sorry my tower in water D was never been
so free of clutter
Water Deep I don't know I understand I
ask a lot from you with few answers in
return
it's not that much all will be told
is a functional edit
see at least at least the Starion is
obviously fake okay we should say
I think Australian's better yeah yeah
I'm not gonna lie let's get out of here
yeah let's let's save and make some
progress yeah yes let's do it okay uh
save game game is saved let's return uh
leave camp
[Music]
let me ladies get over here
I wish there was an auto follow right
I'm a lazy Beach
all right these guys are the milk
they're just gonna be chilling and we're
gonna go through the door
you know chilling
we're just hanging out uh yeah we're
just saying hello we're not doing
anything weird why would we do when
you're gonna go and talk to these dude
dudes real quick
hey guys
and here I'm gonna start the cutscene
yep
[Music]
steady three
who Could That Be
[Music]
okay
let's see what the hell's are you doing
the Beast came in here with those
robbers
[Music]
it makes funny noises you make funny
noises
you're gonna make funny noises when we
kill you give me that Bijou excuse me
she's ours
let him out I'll take care of the Beast
I just said there's still a moments
easy take care of the Beast
you're also
uh yeah a badass yeah I know
no see I knew the worm is evil of course
it is
one that's a true Soul you're talking to
yeah
[Music]
now open the cage
it's now all right get ready for battle
guys
uh battle we still gotta find it I mean
yeah this look at this bear who's like
ready to tear everyone apart unless
we're friends a bear I thought okay
where's the bear um leave the bear to
the goblin
let me talk to Bear yeah can you talk to
him now hello but not yet attacking
are you talking to him yeah I am okay
um oh oops sorry
I don't know how to get out back out of
this okay wait wait wait oh there's an x
button in the upper right corner okay
Boo's talking oh okay hello
what
eh I can't listen in for some reason
that's okay it's because Cali Kelly
upper upper right corner click the X I
am using a controller
[Laughter]
dialogue history attack private dialogue
cute laugh
I'm just gonna let you guys
do your try B okay let me try B is not
working
maybe left button
all right let me go here
uh I can't use anything else
I have a dialogue on
do you see the X
no they're I'm stuck uh why don't you
can't you grab your because you're
playing it on your PC anyway right
put down your controller and grab your
mouse for a second and click on it okay
does anything happen
yeah uh there's still no X oh I think
she's stuck in the dial it's okay yeah I
am it's fine just looking out okay just
let's just attack the Goblins we'll be
fine right
yeah yeah
surely what could go wrong
Welcome to The High Ground Bijou
thank you we're taking the goblin we're
doing okay
we have a bear yeah we've got a bear so
it'll be fine yeah fine also no spoilers
but I really think I think we can do
this uh should we save right now before
we start so we can at least reload from
here yeah okay I'll make a save yeah
make one make a new one
oh
okay
I think we'll be fine this bear seems
very powerful
[Music]
it was like 90 For Real
oh nice a lot of daggers nice
I suck my aim is [\h__\h] that's okay it
it's fine yeah it is this is it the bug
because it's like not even on the enemy
I know it's just I just they're too far
apart I'm I made a mistake okay I made a
mistake oh maybe we can push him into it
[Music]
no they're running to get reinforcements
it'll probably summon about three more
okay
do you want to try and dash maybe shoot
shoot them something
do your best
nice
[Music]
that range
amazing
absolutely legendary
what's happening
I'm gonna go
no I'll stay on The High Ground I won't
leave yet
okay
we have a wolf tank up here oh and he's
leaving too okay
hello
can't reach destination
oh
nice five damage damn
your crab is powerful maybe for having
two health
[Music]
oh
attack wow wow look at you all right
I don't know I don't know how that's
gonna go
oh nice one yeah wow
oops sorry sorry no he's tanky yeah it's
okay he heals himself all the time so
yeah he'll be fine oh is that friend
bear oh no not friends yeah bear bear
his friends other other ones maybe not
evil wolf bear yeah
oh those dudes are bad yeah oh
yeah
I don't think I'll one shot the kid
do you have anything to slow him down or
like
I mean I I have I have something that
I'm pretty sure could one shot the kid
but it just feels like a waste
oh wow
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
oh he's letting the things
[Music]
cool door
um I love when there's no one for me to
attack
my favorite
favorite yeah
hold on actually I can do a ranged
attack
um
let's see no there's too much stuff in
my way where's the bad guys
um there's one right in front of kiwawa
then there's one right by me and then
there's the ones in the cage
again
bonus action frenzied strike
nope too far I need help with that now
um and rage through
yeah bro all right let's see don't tell
me yet don't be sick bulb
that hurt everybody I wonder
nice
oh they're gone all right don't need to
do anything
I'll just skip okay
and to turn
this is on its move
80 Miss hurts yeah I know oh
come on Cave Bear
we love a bear a bear
oh they're running
just can't bear now Lord they're coming
get him
ooh Greece he's gonna lay you on fire
yes Grace let's go
shoot the grace button
I want to
laughs
wow we have a good idea yeah yes those
are smart
I did a ttrpg thing yeah yeah you did
yeah you did that was pretty cool
I wish I knew like of more things that
are like possible to do I feel like
there's so much but I just I just don't
know that kind of think outside the box
yeah
foreign
here we go
who are we beating up there's just oh I
can get these guys do it
yeah
what
um
again good again
fun
way way with you I am burning that's
fine oh that's fine I need the fire to
help enrage in me yo you remind me of
Carla right now yeah you're on fire
I can take both of these guys I can take
both of them yes you can I'm no easy
what
oh okay that helps
that was pretty sick
I know they slipped on the grease he's
he's spreading even more grease
a rooster
you heard her again
well the the grease can light fire so
it's kind of dangerous to be in
yeah when my my com my friends my
animals are there I wouldn't do it now
um
oh I mean he might light it on fire was
what I meant does the bear have to stay
alive because he just got 25 damage yeah
I mean I think it's probably five
yeah
yeah good combo yeah nice combination
all right oh
um
ah
snippity Snappy
low percentage not good
oh cool
coming
that was awesome I'm here to help go get
him gumbo super
super cool next turn I get
right
this is so much easier using friends
instead of
yeah
oh the fun part about Druids is they
don't lose their actual HP when they're
in Wild shape it's a separate HP pool Ah
that's nice that sounds gross that's why
they're they're very very good too oh
chocolate
oh my God oh my God
you
oh yeah sure
no destroy
um
okay one more left
the bear the bear
he's like behind the banner yeah ah
almost there good thing good thing we
stopped them from calling reinforcements
nice nice
talk to him hello
I'm already talking to him I'm sorry
you aided a bear without knowing
a true friend of nature or perhaps a
lunatic this guy's great yeah I love him
I am the Druid house big nice guy
parasites in your head
the dialogue is the subtitles
uh the game's a little broken
gotta get this thing out of my head
halson
Big Papa
you're infected Auntie the wooden hinge
the Mind flesh I don't think this is a
wooden end
something's different
you're aware of the monster inside you
you don't bow to the absolute like the
true Souls do we're special I'm a good
girl house
no leave me alone
let me tell you what I know I've been
studying these parasites for a while now
ever since I discovered these so-called
true souls are infected with them
someone is using very powerful magic to
modify these tadpoles they're using them
to exert control over the infected I'm
sorry to say I can't undo that magic
which means I can't cure you what did we
rescue him for then put him back into
jail no you can you can go back turns
into a bear
yeah maybe
be where these enchantments are placed
on them
and it's where you'll find your cure hmm
[Music]
so all of this was furnishings I can't
just snap my fingers but I know where
the solution almost certainly lies
better help me
to moonrise Towers
[Music]
come out
come out if you want to find a cure you
must head there and discover how the
tadpoles are being manipulated okay
I wish I could but there's still work
I've yet to finish
blood I've yet to spill so you're gonna
help us yeah
but if you could help me I'd be free to
join your journey to moonrise okay
[Music]
the natural order must be all right that
means you know what that means we gotta
kill everybody yeah okay so now we do it
with his help I think yeah there are no
way
there are three big bosses
[Music]
ah
the ones holding these parasites
together remove them and nature will
cure itself
my presence could make things more
difficult I can only restrain my bear
form so much
okay go wild attack goblins if I join
you we'll likely have to slaughter this
entire place
oh no no please unfortunately let's kill
them all yeah we should do it that way
let's go everybody
okay wait let's save yeah let's okay
yeah let's do we need a lot rest or is a
short rest fine yeah because I I didn't
use I only used like that one spell so
yeah I still have three I should be fine
all right let's go okay who do we want
to kill first is the question I guess we
won't have much of a choice it'll just
be however we pop out mine whoever we
run into
well it's Gotta Be let's do our best
let's do it
[Music]
oh are you starting already oh yeah we
we walked right out into a fight I found
I found Beast monster chain that gives
you animal friendships and free potions
and one big ass potion nice
[Music]
I want that
I already saved the game don't worry
guys yes
good
ow you worry oh I'm dying already
yeah it would appears so I gotcha
the Goblins had a stuffed bear yeah it's
freaking evil
you gotta make him pay for that
jeez oh hello
Oh you mean still like a cute stuffed
bear yeah teddy bear actual animal okay
what did you think it was a stuffed uh
Taxidermy is what I thought that's what
I like about carlax Camp is she has a
little teddy bear at it
[Music]
is this the place
no not bee boo yeah this is where we
were before him
it's fine they can call reinforcements
we're gonna have to fight all of them
anyway yeah all right this is the oh no
not her
oh but she's the one who's underwear we
need to kill yeah or steal what the [\h__\h]
yeah we need to steal her underwear
[Music]
I healed those that have fallen down we
might need to
focus on
each other
yeah we're already dead yeah
they hurt me
[Music]
they targeted her really hard
I'm playing music
yeah push him yeah
I have The High Ground now
um if you push them into that Chasm just
don't do it to the boss but they will
disappear so if you have that option you
should move and push them in the
direction of where you see where that
bridge is
a hole in the ground yeah oh interesting
so apart from the boss if anyone comes
up there you should try to throw them
that direction okay okay
oh wait uh my my lupus oh lupus
[Music]
okay
attack okay
[Music]
good boy oh two uh dismissing a little
bit oh no
it's always that one step
oh
he's gonna hold you there
what what are you holding me
I don't know I don't like it though I
appear anyway
but I can't take actions either
um
oh no you didn't
possibly
I wonder where the most likely place
yeah action can you can you help me Boo
and then I can heal her
it is not my turn
it's only my turn I see
I'm not close enough
I think if you use the heel on me it'll
raise me anyway oh really yeah
come on bagel
oh There She Goes does it oh yeah nice
oh that's good to know then I'm looking
super swampy right
uh I am going to
go into hiding
hide out
and then I'll take care of this over
here please don't kill halson
nice nice mess
please don't kill houses
well it's okay we'll go back into the
house uh I have to I control halson
oh really yum
so
dang not in my turn
you die get him
foreign
so much stuff
that was 28 HP just gone in one go yeah
I'm not even making nothing on my high
ground
[\h__\h]
sometimes Lord of the Rings isn't right
about everything
hold on can I
can I um I really hope I can blast them
probably you can try okay oh hold first
and make attack against you critical oh
thank you
yay you remind me of stand up right now
okay I got one of them
oh
powerful she's got the
Palm
ate what are you gonna do what are you
gonna do what's what's going on what are
you doing so magical Fly Away
[Music]
do that
I knocked one down
but I have less HP so I'm gonna die if I
stay up there that's fine that's fine
you've hooked them quite far yeah nice
batch
okie dokie
right on this boy
oh nice nice nice
[Music]
do you want me to come and help you
I'm just gonna howson doesn't even like
have an attack like I don't
I don't know how you can get how you can
get it yeah I'm confused because he like
doesn't he doesn't want to attack so oh
yeah he doesn't want to attack like yeah
no his his attack thing wasn't lit up I
don't know what what was wrong but I
guess I'll just fight this one oh okay
since since he's he has 38 HP you can
get bring him to save koala
um yeah yeah I mean is he tanky
um
oh boy
oh oh
okay well
closer to us
blessing in disguise
was that supposed to hurt me
I'm just being bullied by these enemies
today yeah it's because they're so cute
24.
back to full HP
oh they're coming down
these guys we can focus on her okay
who's after me Marissa
um
[Music]
I want to push her off
I love you I love you
that's okay we'll kill all your friends
he looks dangerous okay uh I'm going to
we should turn down the game mode to
easy
oh yes maybe we should can you do that
mid bite
that was the original plan anyway right
yeah let me see
the Creator oh you did you do that Visa
yeah I made her wet so I can hit her
stronger next turn that's sort of the
Sparks
Sparks like the flames
yes
so I am going to put it right back here
yeah we but we can we can always just do
that randomly you know we can just do
all the fights in Easy Mode
yeah dummy oh you're running away now
haha coward
like what do I do I finally get to do
something
are you kidding me
nice there we go nice
I'm gonna use
[Music]
um
I wanted to do it from a distance but
okay what the [\h__\h]
why do we have so much HP right now I
just noticed it now I turned it to
Adventure
[Applause]
[Laughter]
is that even easier than easy
I think that is the easy one that is
easy yeah okay let's go yay hacks
crazy that they let you do this in the
middle of a fight right other games are
not this nice
well I gotta be so real I I'm not even
good in Easy Mode either
I don't believe that are you playing on
easy private
private
are you playing on easy privately yeah
just because I'm there for the story and
for the Romancing you know oh
okay that's okay it's okay she's a
really tough boss
but I really want to steal her clothes
for me okay
oh we're having a party up here
I want to try pushing her though
[Music]
Target can't be restrained does that
mean she can't be pushed
chat what do you say
try try pushing her just try it says
Target
it doesn't even give me a song
yeah because the others give me a
percentage okay she can't be pushed ah
damn it
for now
[\h__\h]
oh
um
oh oh I'll give her a try yeah I missed
yeah rattling
I'm sorry I can't I can't attack her or
she will get thrown oh
oh no
why did that hit you too yeah
[Music]
um like there I can't I can't get up the
ladder
um I'm not in front of the ladder it's
the enemies oh
okay okay it's okay
not me killing Kiana multiple times
through my run
wow
oh wow you tried to push you
dude
shedding them lines
oh I'm shiny okay
[\h__\h]
she gets so many moves I know it's not
that's that's the one thing that annoys
me is I feel like I always only get one
move for everything meanwhile
yeah they get like endless moves I'm
like are you kidding me
yeah it's very silly
can you find the guy with one HP
yeah I'll try
hey we can go 25 let's go
listen up
wow
oh what's going on
see so far
yeah I
also did damage 12. even though it was
only 65. I'm gonna do it anyway
do it do it oh oh let's get her
[Music]
noise we're doing it
sure are
wolf we'll go on a trip but like I know
my issue was she kept healing herself
which can be pretty annoying
so yeah
oh oh
I'm dead again it's okay
that's me it's it's okay I don't I yeah
see him
oh no
not gonna let her get away with it it's
okay I can still shock her again
foreign
okay she's got one Health
one HP one HP
and a nightmare
oh that didn't work like I thought it
would okay
okay good luck oh wait I'm alive again
well since when who helped me
I don't want you to not have fun playing
we're all in this together well I was
just kidding
can you kill that eye if you get a
chance so it'll stop calling
reinforcements I've currently whenever
it's okay I will try my shove
don't shove her don't I mean you
probably could you could because she's
not as long as it's not in the direction
of the chasm
but I'll try Okay Target can't be oh she
can't be shoved oh okay can you hit her
no oh
you do something to her
oh hey let's go
what
no don't cry no more reinforcements
please
[Music]
I leave Allison alone ma'am yeah
you're so mean
it's okay we almost got him
yeah it's so close
you missed this time die
nice
you get it
hell yeah
okay
strike on this dude okay he's got two
health I won't I won't take her
underwear no no I think I think we have
to pick up her body and take it back to
Camp to get her underwear
so but her body won't despawn
right here you you have her closer she's
close right no I'm talking about her
underwear
oh but also take our stuff anyway yeah
go ahead take her take it take all of
her stuff because I mean we all shared
the inventory so yeah but I'm going to
just be aware I'm going to steal it
except from your inventory
she's in her underwear now perfect oh my
God
hold on
she's just hanging there
looking pretty
oh no
oh different color variation
oh that's cute yeah
appreciating the beautiful things in
life
I cannot awesome
that is a spider's liar do you want the
spiders you you need to keep that it's a
quest item we'll need it later oh okay
mm-hmm
thank you
okay you're welcome I feel like me dying
all the time today is just a reflection
of himself from behind the computer
oh
okay so there's just the two guys left
the one who's hiding out like a big baby
and or do we just have one
oh
he's coming doors okay oh yeah yeah it's
the traffic dude okay
that is close at hand
I'm right here I'll stay here
yeah that's good good oh no more Frenzy
what is freaking
through the Shelf come on interrupted
[Music]
okay
okay is he dead no
he's got one Health left thank you okay
now we gotta be careful okay wait can
anyone pick up her body and fit it into
their inventory
yeah you need to pick up
I can't pick her up she's too heavy
yeah right
I'm in a cut scene
um you should be able to right click on
it and then all right I think I'm
stealing I'm stealing her why that's
it's host man memories I think I'm
stealing her tadpole my daughter
[Music]
yeah you know now we can take her back
to camp and steal her underwear wow nice
okay should we go back to Camp wait I'm
in a cutscene
I don't know I'm getting hurt I'm
getting her
it's mine
she is but I was already in the cutscene
so
that looks tasty let me just put it in
my pocket
hey
um
you should have picked like uh a few or
at least one up off of her no from her
inventory
did I or I mean I don't know if it's
because it's the first one if it's doing
it like this
I think I'm forced to consume the Tad
foam
sorry
consumed I will consume
I like in my private run I like to
corrupt Astorian and his brain only so I
give him all the tabs
oh
okay item received my inflare specimen
Legend
is so funny
[Music]
I'm just gonna really quickly check
through the fat Coat Factory
but yeah there's a bunch of stuff
everywhere so okay okay thank you for
picking up her body
yeah it was like on uh uh over where
mint flower originally was there's a
gilded chest that's like yeah
can we take this
um yeah no uh because there's no one
here they can't see it so you should be
able to take it just fine
what's in there I'm away now I love that
wolf climbing on the ladder there's some
shoes you can check in my inventory if
you want if any of it interests you
oh shoes
pretty water sparkers
but this is maybe something for Bijou
because it says more lightning charges
where if when the wearer stands in the
water during combat it becomes
electrified if the water starts to turn
I do an electrified surface
yay take it from my inventory it's yours
okay okay let's say thank you
all right next boss in save next bus
um
uh no I think with Freddy's do they do
they do more damage as well
[Music]
it helps concentration I got them
nice okay well we're probably going to
be doing the Priestess first uh it
depends where we go so we can either
turn right and then we go into the guy
and we can fight him and the nice thing
is once we kill him there's a treasure
Trove from a key we can take off of him
but there's a lot of people in that room
and it's kind of difficult alternatively
we can go and do the Priestess and clear
the front area that we're doing before
out
um honestly I thought that that fight
was easier than fighting him so we might
want to since we've saved we might want
to go do this first and then long rest
I have no spells do we how many because
I don't know how our camp supplies are
looking uh I got one from the lady
but it's probably fine we can do a long
rest okay
sorry goodbye Houston
okay go to camp
where are you going where are you going
we have worked to do this now snap me
99 of cases long rest do not affect
mission
he's mad at me
he's pissed we need to sleep I know
nice outfit Marissa thanks
oh we need to drop her body okay
I'll drop her right here
okay I can see your bones
oh there you go oh wait how do you
chat how do we steal our underwear
I don't think we can you can you
definitely can I don't know if maybe it
needs to be done when she's in your
inventory
eh revive her revive her
how do we steal
her
Dental oh I see you can have mine okay
no I want I want her underwear
but okay Cali put the body in your
inventory again
[Laughter]
hold on just give me a sec okay yeah
yeah yeah
all right let's stop doing that
side boob oh I do a very strong case of
side boob
all right it's the sign booby
we have to we have to raise her no no no
no no I don't believe that
I'm pretty sure you can put it put it in
your inventory and then like can you go
through he's in my inventory let me see
or maybe maybe I can also do it from
your inventory
I don't know how to do it though
no I mean I Can't Live school do I have
a real life I'm choosing loot it's not
working oh wait put it down for a second
I dropped her okay hold on let me see
how are you gonna do it
you can't be resurrected yeah she's not
she's not on our team
oh but you should be able to take it
quick okay non-lethal they say yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
in your inventory all right
[Laughter]
go
and then click on your underwear slot
can you put her underwear on from the
underwear slot well let's take a look
my under oh underwear slot I have no
such thing
uh it's yeah it's on the right side
below your yeah
oh I didn't know those were underwear
yeah mentha's underwear yeah there you
go yeah
yeah okay put it on
all right they're on okay now I'm going
yeah now move them to your inventory
[Music]
hold on
put your clothes back on
God
is
[Music]
actually all right holder she looks like
it's like a she looks great in anything
pop star outfit all right hold on I'm
figuring out how to do this sorry for
the weight yeah yeah yeah controls okay
all right so can you close back on first
yeah just in case yeah of course of
course
did I flash you
yeah
no it's not the nudity was off but it's
like you know it's still jump scare okay
wait now where where has the no are
you
there's no way
[Laughter]
I
don't have it on either but apparently
apparently your ass showed but I
definitely have it off not
it filter s like nipples and private
parts but it still shows your butt yeah
I I had don't worry okay wait if Polo
summer survives YouTube then yeah you
survive YouTube wait I think there's
like a leaf okay okay there's a leaf on
there yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah all right
so the underwear
go because yeah I think it's is it still
how do how do I do that
because only I can it looks like only I
can choose to equip it or not equip it
yeah okay can you drag it into you yeah
yeah you gotta equip it then move it to
your inventory
[Music]
[Laughter]
when you have
have her underwear clipped that's
where's
yeah
it's equipped I have a question okay now
drag the underwear into your let me just
use a mouse let me just use a mouse
hold on oh my God you don't understand
the keyboard how do I open the inventory
uh
oh okay yeah here's here it is I now put
it in my inventory there you go okay and
then the rest I can take it right thank
you
thank you so much for um doing this for
me
do I need to put in my inventory first
thank you yeah
yeah okay now we can now we can long
rest
he said I'm wearing yours now that's all
yours take your let me see it I want to
see how it looks on you oh okay oh my
God
our Chihuahuas then look at that
browsers
Bloomers that's a Bloomers
I guess I guess I should take my clothes
off too huh oh yes please save by the
way yeah there's a lot of effort pretty
bloomers
[Laughter]
this is just how things are so shall we
move on and kill the next boss right
yeah we probably we probably should long
long rest and you know if
ah you gotta sleep
oh sleep sleep sleep we'll use a supply
pack
okay
don't do that to me
twerk for me boy oh what's happening oh
it's uh mommy again oh a guardian it's
your boy
don't worry
for now leave you
I see you've been using the powers the
tadpole gives you
good yeah not good things haven't gone
as you've expected
you hope to Druid as powerful as Holton
might be able to remove your tadpole
but he couldn't
quite desperate to be rid of it
what a lovely beard you're looking for
Solutions in the wrong places
mine doesn't have a beard uh I want to
be her when I go like you Majors with a
beer
that's complicated
but I'm an adventurer
just like you some way
just like you I seek to be free this is
so interesting hearing it hearing the
different uh perspective because in my
in my regular one it's a it's a girl
on you it is wrapped in Magic that
prevents its removal
until the source of the tadpoles magic
is destroyed any attempts will kill you
you were lucky that Holston knew this
his instincts are right
parasites were merely a symptom of a
greater sickness in faerun
[Music]
sorry guys the height when the order to
transform is given I have powers of my
own
powers
but know that we are alike I've been
trying to escape from this evil for a
long time
once
I almost succeeded interesting
through you who are you I've been given
a new chance
from that evil thanks man if we work
together
we may turn this around
else they need me
who are you
no
it is
to protect you
I stole it from someone
they want it back
for as long as I can but soon
you must discover the source of the
magic that controls the parasites before
that happens
[Music]
back on your power
why am I cloned into my dreams
what do you need me to do
[Music]
are you girls still listening too yeah
yeah I just finished
okay yeah my guardian wants me to use
the powers yeah
foreign she's not telling me Dad
she says go to moonrise Towers
we gotta go a little different yes we're
going some of your companions remain
deep in their Slumber ah sorry I'm
sleepy
future me talks a lot I'm just saying
these freaking clothings on okay I'm
done
oh look at that
this is
by the campfire nice oh ladies Girls
Sleepover
cute
yay
they take your clothes back off get back
to how you look
and look for my character
it is I I only see you with the
underwear all the time in my mind this
is
hmm
I don't need it all right put clothes on
me
let's go
where we going
all right
um so yeah who do we want to do do we
want to go do the easier fight that we
lost at or should we save real quick
I'll save
it easy so I I here's the Strat okay
um so on the right side when you cross
the cross right
um and then start going to uh if you're
looking straight across the bridge the
left there's that little entrance right
but you might realize in the corner by
that door there's also a ladder uh Kiara
it might be good for you to get up there
so you can do uh ranged can you put a
pointer there I don't know which line um
I can walk over there but it might
trigger the fight
well they're not triggered on us yet I
don't think up here all the house in
yeah
he's gonna do what he wants but if you
climb up there then
um it it might be good for you to do
rain shots
um and then me Kelly and Bijou do rain
shots too
I do man I'll stay up here oh it has
commenced the battle hold on he found us
we'll take him out really quick
eh why don't I have
oh no is it the armor I I can't reach
that enemy from here uh wait no wait
never mind I can I think I can yeah
where even where even is we just have
one enemy where are they
at the door I guess I guess we just
killed this one we don't kill him he's
dead okay good okay wait apparently I
can't wear this armor because I can't
cast spells and that is honestly the
most devastating uh is that the issue I
don't know if it is
well you you treat that to Gail then if
you want no if no one's using wait I
still don't uh
I still don't have the ability to even
after I take it off why aren't my spells
working
yeah
oh my God it's the boots okay I can't
wear the boots sorry
yeah go ahead and feed it to Gail if you
want because I don't okay we'll do we'll
do it later okay anyways are we ready to
should we save since we just killed one
random guy okay I'll save it
save them
yeah take it from my inventory yeah
yeah killing the people in this Hall um
yeah well we're we're gonna yeah we're
do we're gonna do the same people I mean
if you wanted we could turn over to the
right and quick kill off these three
people because that will probably
prevent um everyone else from getting
okay like over here wait where that guy
came from one second don't do it don't
go anywhere oh over there yeah I am I
found a a gilded chest scroll up
stinking class get it get it get it box
and scroll up cloud of daggers
nice
but here's the issue we need to close
this door
um door wait
how
son don't you [\h__\h] this up
no he's not hiding okay
okay I have The High Ground okay
um I don't know where you are yep let's
kill him
right
destroy Chihuahua time
silver throughout The High Ground
what does that even mean
my English not as good as your English
you must explain to me I I don't know so
you're asking the wrong person I am only
the number one myth speaker of English
so okay
why don't you talk to this little Goblin
that's in the in the cage
you can talk to him I have a little chat
hey little dude talk
Crackle
crisis ever played in action
Express he's thrown a flaming iron
tyrannical days
how do you how'd you land yourself in
that cage
uh wormless I'm not the one behind bars
yeah I get them yeah
[Music]
he's wow
spiders and works are nothing more open
defend more
they've all gone by me brain isn't
exactly my thing buddy muscles
nods are fickle
me yeah your guy doesn't care about you
isn't that interesting he he doesn't
like the absolute
oh I mean can I Fireball his case oh
yeah but uh yeah you can kill him
why not go have fun
oh
um we should have a health bar on it
right
wow
oh good okay there's three goblins in
here oops
it's okay they're pretty low health
uh should we how do we hold on what's
going on over here
[Music]
I think oh no wait we can howson can
probably handle this if you just if you
just wanna
it's fine
oh but then we if we can just do a short
rest after maybe ah
try me maybe afterwards we can go there
keep going
all right how's it going here
I wish I knocked him out of the cage
chat
I wish
it's fine
not really not me missing I suck
skip your turns
please
skip
they're so far they are
why am I missing every hit
oh
nice let's go
one last started this you have to end it
okay
and your turn go for it
um
my turn has ended mine's ended too
Chihuahua is it is it worth dashing over
there no no just don't worry about it
I'll do it I'll handle it
'll join you
this house and we'll finish it off
please
my beloved Senpai coming to my rescue
mental support
wow see I really was only there for
mental support yeah
yeah why not
I want to talk to this rat hello I'm
here
anything oh wait
what what does giraffe say
oh we should save sorry save's coming
that's okay
you guys want to do a short rest or
you've got a short short rest maybe for
me my house halfway down
for us better find somewhere to come
soon oh the rat doesn't even not do
anything
stop
I I'll do it
later okay okay let's let's prepare for
battle okay okay I'm going up high yeah
yeah go go up
oh
and then when you guys are up me and
Cali will run out there and
uh let me know when you guys are in
position
I mean really if you wanted to you guys
could shoot a random shot at someone
well I'm gonna try to shoot the boss if
that's okay yeah which one is it
um yeah I got yeah okay hold on let me
give me a second to set up hopefully
they won't notice water on them I'm just
hoping they don't notice Allison he's
not he's just standing in the doorway
he's still out there
okay
Serena so weird why is it raining in
here
I don't give us a good question
oh boy
oh okay I missed oh my god well it
didn't aggro them so you could try it oh
you guys oh we gotta help
let's go
let's do it in
where is Sheen
nice
now how listen why are you chilling join
the fight
get in here bear
nice nice That's fast okay great
um we'll they'll get reinforcements if
one of them can ring one of the drums so
we just need to try and kill them as
fast as possible and we'll have less to
worry about
it
yeah you could destroy the ground well
actually there's nobody around that area
yeah
but they'll run to it
sure will they're fast they're speedy
oh
no ow I can't even see up there
wow
oh
that looked painful on there
oh Lord he coming
oh man
no
uh-huh
[Music]
hold on they're not completely stupid
they're not
they're still gonna pay
oh
who is next
I hate when my rain shots nice this is a
big Breeze
how do they shouldn't they be in a
disadvantage shooting from down down
there you think you think right right
that's what I wonder too
every day of my life
yes kill that one he's probably going
for the drum
ah come here
you're gonna have to fight me
uh this little guy down here but just
focus on whoever whoever you can reach
like uh that warlock grease warlock
grease is a kind of High Health ish okay
warlock
he's he's over yeah yeah boom
boom baby
you broke him
perfect
once who's next
I'm evil guys
why am I so proud
nice
okay where are the rest of them
um
okay I'll try to kill them
nice nice
[Music]
freaking go oh
oh there's one dashing down
nice nice nice
[Music]
they're all like on the left side I
think right like by Bieber
[Music]
bye get them oh no you're so close it's
okay
very close
and I try to say
no
let's reach
bro
I push him
you are too weak to push I am I have a
noodle arms all right borax I wish there
was a way to paint I'd really appreciate
being able to Ping things
look what do you mean pink so I can be
like oh they're here here and here you
know instead of being like yeah there's
some around
oh you can though how you mean just
marking something on them oh I mean like
exact location
like in League
hey trying to push me too
I'll show you
oh breakfast
video you can okay
[Music]
or something like that yeah
that's what I'm being told and then
somebody marked something on the map
why do I always miss
oh
where are our
enemies oh there's one see nice I saw
that League thank you I was blind and
you helped me
um
[Music]
nice
wow another one in the bag okay how do I
clear how do I clear this spell
do we just have to wait for it to run
out
so we can get the body loot from True
Soul gut
um
is there anything on the side like the
um right side of your bar that has the
same symbol
I found 183 gold get it wait for it to
go away
we can just we can just goes away events
rate other stuff in the meantime
there's lots of dead people around here
Here Comes the Money
there it is this is gone yay the money
time to get another brain worm does
anyone want to eat it or do you who
who's against the brain worms here
brainworm
um
okay so here's what you're gonna do
click on your little inventory and
equipment there will be in a lipid
Powers manage experiences and you can
pick where you want to build a little
fast too fast too fast okay inventory
inventory look in the in the top middle
you see how there's the four different
uh equipment spell book Alchemy and
lifted powers
powers
uh
it's the far right one in your inventory
no no no you don't need you just in the
top one it's it's the fourth option
and then manage experiences and you can
just read about it and pick where you
want to put it
wow
[Music]
oh wait I do I have a so we all share we
share them we share them we all so I ate
one because I'm selfish
I don't know which one to choose
um whatever would make you happiest
just whatever sounds like it it'd be
helpful to you ah concentrate okay thank
you chant
where do I put it
um just pick it up and you put it over
the one that you want and then drop it
or you can click on disgusting
okay
thank you oh so it consumes one okay
yeah got it
should we do another short rest I can do
it yeah yeah
okay this is the hard fight so I don't
know if we won a long rest before it
actually
um I have two spells left I don't even
know how to see how many spells I have
left to be honest uh do you see the
squares oh yeah yeah it's the squares
okay I think it'd be a good idea to
fight up in the rafters and I think we
all should be in the rafters so that he
feels like he has to go on to the
rafters and then we push him off Oh you
mean so uh go up climb yeah
okay awesome good luck okay
[Laughter]
I can carry him on my back we level up
not yet we haven't had a level up in a
while
soon hopefully
awesome come on
oh my God house and just turned into a
human why do you gotta make life so hard
as a bear before I know and now he's
like no can't get there
climb ladders in this game yum
okay
so
um let's see where are you guys you lose
this chest already
yes
it was just some silver tray um
after we do this there will be a room
from the Priestess that we can go into
um and unlock yeah Cali knows
uh this is too high for all of us we
can't get there can you bless us with
jump Powers oh um what Cali can you eat
me
oh yeah
that's too high for you girl yeah I'm
short only for being too right there was
something no I I apparently not it's
just too high I was able to get up all
right let me see you're you're so
special on me you could throw
all right let me see I bet I can throw
all y'all wait why do I have to choose
let me see
help
throw I I want to throw a person
improvised melee weapon
uh it's not letting me choose you ah
weird
if you right click on my name
does it say well
just use throw it says okay
just throw
and then it won't let me choose the
Quran screen all right well
teach me how to use the keyboard oh my
God just just click on me
it's West to move around and then q and
E to move the screen around
and then your mouse but nothing happens
all right throw wait throw first there
you go yeah
get up there
[Applause]
[Music]
my turn can you throw me all right
bro
looks like you're a little too big for
me okay it's okay me and me and halson
will just um
we'll find we'll figure something out
um a house and maybe is not good here so
I'm gonna just move him to the ground
level
so maybe don't start the fight yet
um okay
it's because I'm just gonna have a
ladder down there that you can
eventually climb up if you want yeah
we'll get there
yeah first I need to just get house and
back on the ground so he's not useless
in the fight
I'm gonna drop these uh these fire
things on them yes on those goons below
awesome God no chill can I try setting
up again yeah okay okay halson's at the
door so
um I'm I don't want to open it I guess I
can since I'm human house and I can
sneak it open
okay let me know when you guys are ready
okay I'm almost almost ready one sorry
one more moment almost there remember
how to turn him back into a bear
uh-huh
oh hell we'll do it later okay let's
let's begin
okay
holy that guy
nice nice a stinky Cloud stinky cloud
oh yeah
nice okay time to fire the arrows
or throw axes throw axes
oh
they're naughties yeah I think they
won't be able to take actions for a
little bit
I'm gonna throw a goblin Scimitar at him
yeah yeah nice nice let's freaking go
yeah thanks Bill shouldn't have wished
to live in more interesting I have to
get on the ground too I'm not even close
enough to be in the fight
oh my God he's almost gone he's almost
yeah he's almost dead let's go easy
[Music]
foreign
but I had a Moment of clarity
sometimes that's just how it goes you
know
okay where's the guy
did he die
nice wow that was that was real good
yeah
was it
oh I didn't finish my turn I'm so sorry
everyone didn't mean to keep you waiting
yeah
oh he's just running away
I'm nauseous okay
wow this is red right there
sometimes I get lucky
wolf is stuck outside
open doors
not that one I'll go to the other one
maybe I'll reach someday no the war drum
uh it's okay are there even any more we
killed we killed everyone
yeah you go ahead and drum those beats
yeah you can drum them all you want
we've killed everybody
nobody's coming to help you
do that
yeah yeah I'm wilding out
oh that's you sorry
I was thinking of attacking you for a
second
um
I'm wearing
nice nice fever hmm who did that hit
um
he's got three Health left someone
please take him down
go Bird go whoa birdie time
okay guys
what okay
dang it I didn't even see that dude
there
yeah he's successfully hiding
the misfortune
oh angry
[Music]
oh I totally didn't see that that was
him yeah yeah
wait run through the um
please he was so close
fine but before anyone heals him Angie
oh
are we concentration
ouch
he unbeared me
he's nice
he's on our team
stolar kills
let me be fair again I want to be a man
a man bear
[Music]
only three left not bad
yeah we're doing we're doing really good
now that we turned on easy yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
let me move a little bit
if I move
kill him get him
where's the other one
where's the other I only see one guy
there's one next to bear and one next to
bird oh that dude yeah interrupt you got
me [\h__\h] is it the crowd still I think
so
you'll just have to wait till next turn
that's how the cookie crumbles sometimes
calliope
[Laughter]
Calliope Marie again wow
we both missed
I can't believe that caliope
whoa
oh the poor dog oh my God he's trying
his best oh
he's arriving soon
okay
yes all right nice okay one more
actually hits this time
nice oh there we go
yeah
[Music]
he's very happy that's not right
praise you my friend The Grove owes you
a death beyond measure yes man get back
to the Grove My First Choice selective
feet those three were too dangerous to
leave alive uh there's so many there's
like a million
[Music]
return to the Grove
um
You can call it oh okay
maybe next time
now a team that we have oh yeah
so anyway
but it gives me a penalty
okay
yeah
we can sell it
music poison oh yeah Supply pack yay we
need that
I could use that okay
just take all because you know what we
can always sell it later
okay do you guys uh let me know when
you're done in here and then I'm Gonna
Make You Follow Me
okay I'm the queen now bow to me kneel
to me I am on the pro the Iron Throne
yeah
from Game of Thrones that's definitely
that's definitely a throne a throne of
all time
he he
can I take it home
no
sad
[Music]
I guess I'll let's stay with my
What's this called again
a fancy chair
the expensive office chair oh Herman
Miller oh I love my husband Miller
potatoes there's so many potatoes
and garlic and carrots
oh I can level up
oh hey
there's a cool thing now
yeah yeah
no noise
only took us about three hours
hey usually you know
it can take a lot of time in here yeah
so that's not I mean that's not all that
bad
it's about as much time as like ttrpgs
take again yeah we did pretty good one
fight
where'd all the treasure go and there
was nothing in there I already took it
it's in my inventory
yeah we all share inventory though so
it's it's our goal being different again
eh oh those are the clothes were her at
East clubs
I know how could I
spell when to wear a dashes or takes a
similar action during combat they gain
momentum
it's got some cool stuff too I will put
into the inventory
rings and stuff
hmm
saloons
chosen amulet hi twin magic Missile
thing
I was asking out loud
why strength because I want strength
don't complain this is my run not yours
sorry my chance bullying me because I I
went with I leveled up
I leveled up and I didn't do what they
wanted
okay okay except I think I'm leveling
now yes okay why arranged I just want to
hit the there we go
I took the shield and the boots out of
your inventory yeah take what you mean
and then follow me oh okay oh falling to
myself okay where's North I'm at the
door that we entered in well that I
entered in
we have one more fight we're not done
here oh we're not done no okay oh okay
are we not like taking
this body you don't you're interested in
his clothes
no
I mean if you want them you're welcome I
really need these underwear oh that's a
bit early I'm so yeah I mean this isn't
this isn't the fight but I don't know
what happened so we're just gonna uh
these must just be guards that missed
out the first time
yeah
yeah okay okay
they're they're sad they're like huh
what do you mean I didn't really fight
there's only three of them
yeah there's an Archer
over there
oh Kelly dodging everything how
masterful
[Music]
let's go
let's go can I reach from here oh I can
but 50 percent
it's not gonna make it what's that noise
hmm
there's like a banging noise
not here too what don't tell me okay I
hear like wood banging like something
banging on wood
does it have a ribbon a consistent
rhythm
I don't know it just sounds like banging
on wood not the ogres again
are they playing their game again
yeah it's triggered oh no
that happened I guess love is just a
game I can't complain oh
hmm I don't hear the banging why are you
here look banging oh it's gonna stop now
okay
um maybe you have a headache
feel free to loot and then and then
follow me over here
come to me
okay
huh huh
[Music]
he's still here
um no the guy what are you trying to
just hold do two try it
okay oh okay well I didn't need it
anyway whatever anyway follow me yeah
get rid of him he was still here
hahaha
that's so funny
[Music]
aligned okay we're gonna have a giant
lady to kill in a bit
but feel free to loot this room first
ah she ain't [\h__\h] yeah you're right huh
people where are you
something we
on my screen oh my god oh no is this the
the sound that she was hearing yeah it's
a bug yeah
flying around back and forth
[Music]
what what the hell what is that
you were crazy
I guess and not just ogre is doing their
thing again
yeah I am happy all right coming through
the door I went into
and be ready to fight already in you
okay hello defile Temple why is your
attitude going down you sense it might
be time to live what is it it's a big
lady oh I'm going up here
oh my God
she looks familiar yeah doesn't she
your drama
Sharpshooter all in
nice nice
man
Wolfie finally gets a bite
and he misses
no no don't hurt Lucas
oh you're gonna pay you are so gonna pay
animal is friends I love you just for
fun
too heavy to shove all right
your turn
won't let me cast a spell
[Music]
I have a spell
um
ah okay that's how you do it
I feel bad for ganging up on him no she
deserves it
[Music]
what are these what are these things
that my character is saying
I don't know cool barred disses
[Music]
yeah Wolfie got revenge in the end all
right and with that we've actually
cleared everything out that we can hear
him
um yay yeah now we can just look for
stuff for Luke
yeah I mean we could go and see see how
the thing resolves in the um yeah all
the camps
huh
what'd you get
that's just something a little bit of
gold useless necklace
that's okay you can sell it for money I
also picked that the scroll of Mel's
acid Arrow so I could confirm acid Arrow
do you mean acid
well here are you afraid to say ass yeah
no you don't have to be shy here
[Laughter]
us ass domination
the same
dominate the ass I love ass
[Laughter]
don't we oh
it's all right nice
[Music]
nice nice nice nice nice
oh do we teleport out or do we walk out
we could teleport where does this go eh
wait follow me
wait what's this are you sure you solved
it correctly I really believe I did okay
wait no room now
let me solve the puzzle
okay wait where did I come in from here
good luck wait where did I come in where
did we enter from I think someone with
strong strength with me for a second
Cali has that
Cali follow me for a second yeah well
well Norris is doing that puzzle okay
puzzle fuzzy what do you think this is
what do you think never said what's
happening here can you go in here we
need to match up things
confused match to what
you know I can't fit in there but can
you people oh you can't fit in here here
no I can't God I'm not the puzzling
person
can I move stuff oh I oh never mind I
can move oh this goes down okay come on
let's go
oh hold on okay we're waiting we're
holding we're holding
yeah where are you
[Music]
well I opened the door so now there's a
chest that we can get me oh nice I don't
know where you are
no I said do I pulled a lever
um
I don't know there's a lever
try oh try it
one second okay close the door okay
close do the lever again it's a lever
for the door once we solve the puzzle so
ah can you ah oh yeah nice okay okay
I found 254 gold okay nice yes
more money
this leads down to a ladder
go through the door that opened up yeah
yeah yeah save save
Kelly did you go here
huh did you go here oh there's dialogue
no I think I think that I thought the
puzzle was would not what it was before
okay I thought I thought you had to have
all the the black circles in the middle
yeah no the bottom this ladder is so
long you look very frightened
oh
oh what's down here
Saloon night Outpost oh
whoa what's this
Holy Light whoa whoa
oh wow a waypoint
wow where are we we're in the under dark
it looks like under dark and that's what
the Waypoint says that's the I think
that's the other path that you can take
oh there's a lever can I press it
yeah
oh I opened the gate hey wait no no no
no no no no no oh don't do anything
don't do anything don't do anything
don't move
oh boy it eh well that's rough there's a
Minotaur here oh hey oh hey cute yeah
nice well
you close the gate
[Music]
close the gate close the gate close the
gates
everybody's almost dead
we can save them yeah we can take him
through here
can you yeah well I mean I don't think I
can in Cali they've already saved chat
shut up I already said you guys could
come up to where I am
why why is nothing happening oh my God
oh he's angry that's fine let him be mad
be angry see look oh it's because
that'll kill him if he's stuck I
wouldn't want to get hit by that
okay nice okay now you can open it
oh oh wait but we might not want to move
through there because of that so let me
just
what does he have
I want to check this
oh whoa open Lockpick
20 20. oh 20 what
I can't get a 20. what the [\h__\h]
wait can I add to your role oh that
attitude Kiara
but I'll roll again one time only I'll
just try one more time just one more
there's treasure in there
wait where where are you where are you
oh
it's another 20.
see that's cool
um I don't know if I should try again
yeah we have no lock pick available
enough space
it's gonna be even worse probably
ah man at least you tried yeah I'll give
up
you might be able to that'd be crazy
let me try
I mean you could try to break through
the door too no I can't I can't nice
nice nice
no no I can't oh good try
to [\h__\h] myself
where are you oh you're over here okay
I will try medium toughness oh medium
toughness I feel like
that
give it a shot
I was able to break for something like
that with with Carla what is that hand
and where do you want me to throw you
um one
night King
up there there you can't just yeah oh
nice idea actually hold on I see
okay create a ladder to the ledge with
the chest and the one with the highest
ramp can jump over it
um
how do we create a lab
path is interrupted ah look at his
blocks oh wait hold on
might be possible 22 damage yeah break
the gate
yes
[Music]
you look like dead
what's inside what's inside get the
chest oh it's locked
up
if you have him
yeah that's right okay I need to get a
15 and let me add my guidance
it's worth it you should do your best
inspiration to be able to do
it you can use yeah yeah you definitely
should use an inspiration you haven't
been really using it so much
ah yes muddy okay one more time yeah
yeah can you put it in your pocket and
take it out and then we can just look at
into it later too if we can't get it
open right now if I if this one doesn't
work
let's go what's in it
what's it got what's it got what's
inside
let's see
let's go oh it's a helmet of smiting
interesting
oh um maybe Cali can have it yeah
oh okay if it has more strength that
might be good condition with one of your
Smite spells what's a Smite spell it's
might spell I don't think I have any
spells
um would not be good for me I love
mushrooms one of your Smite spell
oh it's for paladins oh we can sell it
for money yeah yeah it's worth a lot
money is good yeah money is good
115 or we feed it to Gail yeah we're not
feeding it to Gail money
um should we go to the Grove and see how
that resolves
oh yeah sure that's the Waypoint yeah we
uh the way we are I got the Waypoint I
don't know if everyone needs to get it I
can't leave
um you're gonna have to jump in yeah
let's teleport no we can teleport
because I can't I can't jump out okay I
don't think
I went to the emerald Grove
okay uh
okay
okay environment on my way
nice fresh air wow very nice wow we've
been inside all day
inside that stinky Goblin camp
yeah very smelly
I'll take a bath
I'll remember this person it's good
memories yeah oh yeah yeah there's still
the blood there too
oh yeah what will or whatever you still
won't join our team
yeah we joined my team
I'm in a cutscene
he did it I took a collection from all
they're giving us some money
thank you zaplore
you can keep your corn I guess we're
taking the money what do you mean
just a while ago we are not nice here
as for us yeah we did something big we
can't be doing this for free otherwise
everybody expects us yeah
we don't work for free
all right
tonight
oh party they're gonna celebrate so
um let's go see what's happening with
kaga though you know yeah
Downstream
[Music]
and we can also sell any any of the
stuff that we picked up yes
he only takes one person at a time I
know so it's true yeah that is pretty
annoying but there's a is there a child
uh salesman around
[Music]
oh the kid wants what's some business
give him some business I want to give
him business
okay I'm in business do what you got to
do [\h__\h] the business moo
in the most say so way possible because
that is a child yeah let's see around
here
I had some I don't know I'm just gonna
troubles with those kids in my private
play through yeah no they're kind of
nasty little little ones
they moved away
stuff
um
yeah we we can sell our stuff Advance
the story and then that seems like a
good you know yes yeah today
uh we're gonna wait for you guys down
here or yeah okay I'm all done um I'll
just I'll just sell my stuff next time
okay
oh yeah we can do it before we start
next time Google the cow no killing the
cow
would I ever do that
all because of that croissant
croissant sounds good
you two are good you do a great question
thank you
awesome awesome
yeah tell her what's up
and then bloody we do the story and then
we can we can go and do the tiefling
party
and then and then we can end
okay
yeah oh
I will allow you to stay but consider
yourself he tries to be feisty to him
but he's not having it yeah he said I'll
place in the natural order I think we
should kill her again right here
backslide and Nature's Fury will crush
it seems like himself
okay
um he tried to imprison a check all
right he did try it on President's child
you were too lenient we'll have your
hands full with her she shows great
instance
but time will humble her
why
but enough of that for now I owe you my
thanks
you're welcome stands
nature we owe him our fans too though
yeah yeah he did he did help us out a
lot speak to wrath he will reward you
for your efforts oh
um
that that entails
soon that's tomorrow's problem take some
time for yourself tonight
rest celebrate
come morning I'll be by yourself
all right so we get our prize first and
then go to the party or just do the
party yeah yeah right
is in here I believe
oh now they teach me about the pink
system all right
hello Wrath
you've done it you brought house in back
oh thank you
you're welcome no problem Bob thanks is
not enough
May Sylvanas it was fun all your days
yeah I cannot imagine taking on a camp
full of goblins was a simple task
true fair enough
I should not have underestimated you
um I also need to check something real
quick in the Grove
before we before we leave I don't know
if we grabbed it before place it among
the people I think there's a
Wonder wolf clothes there's a worm
everything in the vault below
oh worm oh
okay where is Nettie again Daddy is like
here somewhere
[Music]
did you guys kill her
okay let's do a long rest
are you guys ready
[Music]
okay wait what did he give to us as a
reward I have no idea
click off my clothes
racist
myself yeah that happened automatically
I didn't even do that yeah
I wish he'd put his back on
I don't need those two things staring at
me
when you look at it from the right angle
it looks like he's naked and just
covering himself with the book very
elegantly we killed some goblins to save
some tieflings oh we're listening in on
something else
well I'm not giving him his clothes back
yeah that's fine
[Music]
it kicked me do you mind I'm very busy
wow we have no connection we have no
connection okay I'll try my luck with
somebody else
there's a barn here
Mary says Bard friends discuss your
problem tomorrow
we'll have time to spare for that I
sense
yeah
I really want to get
sure there are
you strike me as extremely
resourceful resourceful but there are
many grateful people here who want to
spend time with you health and please
keep your words myself
why is he like this we just met you
desperate though
around here it's a lot of thirsty people
around here
no yeah go go enjoy it it's the party
talk to whomever you please well which
Gail should I talk to her
yeah
do we not have will
we really never recruited him huh
this is the saddest
Rising you what's not mine
desperate people
like those Refuge
okay I guess we try our luck he's gonna
say no
oh we can't yeah right
um I'm raising up yeah yeah keep going
miss her miss her
[Laughter]
for my liking she likes you oh
Shadow heart Trails off and glances
around at the party
turns back to you
please surprise you're still there
I thought you might have wanted to
mingle with the others
I'm trying to get rid of me wait you're
you're all the company right now oh my
God
I won't pretend I'm not surprised
we haven't always seen eye to eye after
all she's so cute I'm sure there's
plenty of people who'll be Keen to
celebrate most thoroughly with you
what's that spot uh uh maybe maybe I'd
like
to celebrate with you maybe you would
yeah but I'm not cruel enough to get
your hopes up
in spite of what summer
hold on
um
I think I could win you over you do do
you I'm not some dewey-eyed tiefling
Maiden you just saved
work before I commit to any hip work
excuse me
persuasion yeah
um
let's see
what some advice on how to make me more
bearable
all right if you like I'm not half as
mysterious as you might think
respect my privacy my opinion
thank you
if you do that well okay
closer wow no she didn't say no she
didn't say no she didn't say no she said
maybe later of the Grove so
okay
I'm flattered but I think it's not you
you understand
it's me sirian hates me I have stuff
did he really just it's not you it's me
I have standards
you gross get away from me
oh my God oh my God biggest bottle oh my
God my [\h__\h] now oh he's great he's great
I love him so much he's so funny he has
the best one-liners
thank you for seeking me out amid all
this merriment I wasn't sure whoa
aetherian does yeah
excuse me
oh geez I mean
well
safely make them say please
I'm ready
[Laughter]
good luck
streamer's luck
[Laughter]
what you're winning
[Music]
good boy
no way I'll see you later
we need some privacy as they like to say
he was the one that came on strong to me
what was that no I couldn't but it's
like
vampires
the idea of a bear being a spicy scene
between a story
I just couldn't say no
understandable oh my God yeah no one no
one likes me no one no one here is
interested in me I'm so sad I know oh my
God in in my in my solo run everyone was
so mad at me they're like you're not
gonna sleep with me tonight what's wrong
with you I was like oh I didn't realize
everyone liked me so much
oh
wow all right well
alrighty shall we sleep shall we end the
day or does anyone want to party hardy
some more
just get your just get your screens
ready maybe wait wait I want to try I
want to try bracing Shadow heart first
real quick scene
do you like me
share private moments it's strange
let me make sure for your eyes desperate
people your private moments is off
neither will you chat I'm censoring it
yeah we
saved their lives
I mean I don't have nudity on so I don't
really know how spicy could it be
I mean
or do they just do it with the clothes
on
um it's a little spicy this is around
the
[Music]
can I give it to somebody
it's gonna be so funny because it's your
character
okay
we haven't always seen eyes they're
pretty spicy
I guess
um
for free maybe you would don't know you
don't know that you don't no I've never
seen anything like that have fun okay
well don't be a stranger
yeah I don't actually know how spicy it
is
it's
um yeah it's it's a little
it's a little it's a little much
movie she thinks I'm done streaming
because I stopped talking oh
smart
okay let me just um
I just have my screen I just turned the
game screen off but I still have the
game sound on that's fine right
as long as there's no obscene visuals oh
I'll see it right yeah no I have share
private mode turn it on turn it on I
want to see it I want to see it
share private moments on let's [\h__\h]
go all right okay hold on hold on hold
on I'm just gonna
I'm just gonna take measures real fast I
hit take measures
I'm gonna make myself really really big
the one that gets this
I think if you probably talked to people
more so the they probably get to know
more about you so since you're the one
making like choices they uh are more
attached to you okay Super Evil I'm like
the nicest one why is he down to bomb I
don't know he liked me too and I was too
nice for him so
oh I guess I'll go to bed all right
let's go
show me your scene
yeah
I feel fear oh can we observe yeah yeah
yeah yeah
I wanna see it
[Laughter]
oh my God it was just like Edward wow
he's always loved me can you believe
that he's always loved this ogre I can't
wait since the moment yeah wow I feel I
feel like I'm getting NTR he was in my
own stream maybe
I'm not shipping out you don't have me
yet say nothing just let him kiss you
um just just let him do I am over a few
words
do what you must sire
wait a minute
[Laughter]
look at you go
Frozen them up as always okay
[Music]
yeah yeah there's definitely tongue
involved
relax enjoy yourself you're the one who
pinned him against the tree I mean
moriopa is you know just a little a
little frisky
you know
um
[Music]
wait I'm pretty naked in there you are
well not I mean okay yeah you don't you
don't have nipples
oh yeah oh yeah yeah your Leaf your
leafed your leafy cover you are leafed
yeah
so how how did we think about that sir
is he humping you
nah nah he did nothing
lame last night
they you weren't that good how dare you
hotels
I wanted to ask you about your scars
where'd you get them isn't exactly
yeah okay I told you that I was a
magistrator
home runs
Now kill him again
I crossed
Cazador
he captured me
kept me for years as his slave for sad
backstory sad past as we look at his ass
yeah and a nice ass it is sorry Chad
kidnapping
I mean how could he resist
yes a poem to carry with me he composed
and carved that one over the course of a
night
he made a lot of revisions as he went
but it should be okay sharp complex
[Music]
never mind
you certainly can't
[Music]
well I'm just checking a mirror can I
yeah he's a vampire doesn't matter I can
tell you what it says whatever the
bastard wrote can you read infertile
anything he did to me no let's go uh
probably not with the problem
if I was playing as a team okay
thank God
perfect yeah it was an okay evening it
was fine wow wow
[Music]
Starion is very lucky he got to he got
to spend the night with me yeah
so lucky
well uh great we we made good progress
we finished saving the Grove which means
we're moving on to chapter two
yeah isn't that exciting
we can still go back and do some stuff
from chapter one though but especially
when we get to chapter three we won't be
able to go back so just so you know okay
but if we want to do like the Hague
mission for example it's probably better
to do that before we move on too far
whoa hag Mission yeah yeah we gotta find
The Hags man
[Music]
egg hunting yeah
yeah but everyone did so good today good
work everybody Baldur's Gate crew yeah
gotta find our way through
um thanks everybody for tuning in yes
yes thank you thank you for coming
despite the late hour
it was a pleasure
yeah yeah
I'm gonna take a huge fat nap I'm gonna
go to sleep
I'm sure some people have announcements
for example I know Kiara you've got an
announcement yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah
well I released an album yesterday
uh it has quite a lot of variety yeah
some edgy Emo songs some happy bouncy
songs
some cool EDM songs this and that and
today is the release of the mb3 DMV uh
of pineapple in in about seven and a
half hours so I hope you guys can watch
it
um
[Music]
so you guys should go listen to it on
iTunes because yes it's crawling up the
charts you guys
yeah you guys gotta listen to it
[Music]
Kelly likes retrospective the most huh
yeah great I don't know man great wander
is also really good those are the two
that like I listen to that's my favorite
that's my favorite I like great
Wanderers it's really good I'm surprised
would maybe like the cuter songs I mean
they're all good but like and I feel
like sleep talking reminded me of like a
like a really cool like poppy Banger
that like I feel like everybody can
enjoy yeah
me too it's my favorite
yeah yeah they're all fantastic so much
thank you please sing them in karaoke
dressing in them
um so what else do you guys anyone want
to say what they're streaming next or my
membership's open today that's all I've
got
my one one month anniversary month
anniversary my first month and uh then I
open memberships so it's a fun day for
me
[Music]
but debuted for a month
[Applause]
so exciting
why you you girls are one month and me
and Kelly are coming on two three years
[Music]
so crazy
yay
um I'm streaming armored Core tomorrow
that's it
I love that game I found my game
it's so fun I love it
um yeah that's about it for me and then
I I'm doing it I'm not sure if people
can view the thing I'm doing tonight for
music first
um I have an appearance that I'm doing
I'll try and retweet stuff about it if
there is something online you guys can
see then you should be able to find it
there and yeah that's uh that's about it
is that Japanese TV or what yeah I think
I thought it was TV but I heard that it
it's like an on online that's on
Japanese TV okay
gotcha um I mean I don't know I got a
lot of weird conflicting information
from money
um
Subaru will be there
[Music]
um so check my Twitter for info about it
if you're interested yeah yes okay okay
everybody
thank you guys for playing I'm looking
forward to the next time we play yeah
next time different time again yes when
we're swapping times every time
yeah Rory's gonna wake up super early
next year yeah sacrifice myself like six
a.m
yeah yes
[Music]
bye
they're so cute
that was so much fun I can't believe no
one wanted to raise me up I'm so
depressed actually I don't know what to
think of that that none of none of none
of none of them were interested in me
isn't that just the most depressing
thing you've ever heard imagine imagine
having the opportunity to be raised by
the nerissa ravencroft of hollow life
English and um
rejecting her the crazy crazy
so different from my regular run this
this truly is a pain of playing
multiplayer
the pain of playing multiplayer but
we're gonna go ahead and we're just
gonna end it right here I'm super tired
it's almost 2 30 in the morning can you
guys believe I stayed up so late and had
two streams today even if the first one
was a little short but this one was long
enough to make up for it so thank you
guys so much for joining me Jill Burton
thank you for everyone who's joining my
memberships today as well I will be back
tomorrow don't remember what we're
streaming off the top of my head but
it's on my schedule so feel free to take
a peek and I'll look forward to seeing
you all there then so now get to bed
jailbirds it's late
Ethel thank you very much thank you very
much for the uh for the akasapa
thank you but yes you guys all have a
wonderful night or a wonderful morning
depending on where you are located or a
wonderful time of day and I will look
forward to seeing you all tomorrow at
the regular time bye bye for now
[Music]
thank you