[Music]
hello
everyone say things
[Music]
hi
so
seems fine no one's complaining on my
side are you good
i think everything's good always yeah
um
is everyone already in the holiday mood
yes jingle jangle
bingo it's all right
[Music]
okay that's fine that's fine you know
what happens to the best of us
let me turn down my mic okay maybe this
is okay
[Music]
someone going back and forth in the
portal i keep hearing it
is that 200 volume
[Music]
oh yeah i got whoo i have like 12. i
don't know
how many wow then again there's never
such thing as too much
your house is looking good now
thank you amelia added a nice touch on
top i don't really know what it is it
looks better
uh what yeah it looks better
yeah i think i definitely made a big
contribution did you get rid of
my tickets oh yeah
i ate them
[Music]
is it a middle finger
i think the answer is clear if you have
to uh ask
[Laughter]
where's my sword here we go
oh man every cat oh yeah
is it in your house i thought it sam huh
i trapped him
he came out of the wall he came flying
out of the wall
i don't really know how he did it um
all this dirt comes up
i didn't come here to be
you didn't come bullied too but that
doesn't mean you're not going to be
is this your christmas tree yeah let's
go see the christmas tree
over here who is doing that
christmas
[Music]
it's
yeah if you look in the box there's like
a bunch of different decorations and
shears
so you guys can make your snowmen and
they'll be alive
do you guys want to build a snowman oh
my god
these pillars here that have snow and
they have the pumpkin if you grab a
sheer from the chest and you
use the shear on the pumpkin then now
you have a snowman you can take off the
pumpkin
cool how do i get in here
my first snowman look at him he's so
cute
and then you can take the pumpkin off if
you want to or you can leave it
oh my god they always try escaping i
have to put it
that's so cute is that a mod or is it
actually in game a feature
and what else do you want they tried to
escape okay i saw that one snowman that
you made
[Music]
escape hold on i'll trap them hold on
i'll just i killed my snowman and all
they left me was these snowballs
what do i do with them oh you can throw
them at people
can i build another snowman i messed up
yes
how do you build a snowman how do you do
it again right click with the share
on the on the pumpkin top
[Music]
you just need like a few snowballs and
you can make a snow block you don't need
like a
a crafting table to do it and then you
can
put two down and put a pumpkin on top
um i know you already prepared a lot of
uh
decorations on it but i also prepared a
bunch of pumpkins so that i can
also contribute so i want to put some
pumpkins on the tree yeah
we generally make like whatever you want
i just picked some eggs
but it's gonna be hard to decorate on
the other side when there is literally a
cliff there
um that's what we have scaffolding
yeah i've never used that before
yeah scaffolding stuff is nice because
you can just click on the ground and it
just spills itself
and then you can go it can build really
high
and then they break with like one one
hit it's like it like
and then breaks all down it's really
good yeah
when i use the snowball it just uh it
just makes me throw it
um yeah yeah you gotta make it in the in
the blocks
oh yeah yeah when you press uh
[Laughter]
get it
when you have a shovel you can also uh
you can dig these
the snow on the ground yeah what happens
if i
put a torch as a light on on the tree
does the tree burn
oh don't put the toilet in it oh we have
like this like
glowy assuming i could put it i can't
put it on there anyway
but yeah we need to lighten the tree up
as well
is there a color scheme we're going for
or is it just red
oh and whatever you want whatever color
i think it works
yeah oh i should bring some wool over
all right hold on the lights
bring some hollow that i've colored all
over
you put them wherever you want i gotta
climb
[Music]
it's growing so pretty
damn can you not put the
scaffolding on a bush um no no
i don't know if you can just put like a
temporary
dirt block or something and then put it
on top of that
why can't i use the red vines does
anyone here already have a tree in their
home
um
[Music]
stuff like on the wall like this
this is not over yet
[Laughter]
what are you guys
[Music]
how doing how about this the crimson
roots wait who are they throwing
snowballs at
what is she oh they're zombies oh
wait can we have a snowball fight oh
yeah
[Laughter]
yeah that's what
[Music]
where'd you go where'd you go oh boy
where did i come from where'd you go
where did you come from katniss
huh huh
[Music]
i see i need to bring some stronger
weapons kiara hasn't spotted her yet
she's going she's going to get more
weapons
i mean this is what christmas is all
about right worse
oh no i need to eat something oh no oh
no
you need some steak did you make a
mistake
[Music]
no real for real they need some steak oh
that might be nice
actually where'd you go maybe i can at
least put some bones oh wait no
hold on oh no now all these weird rocks
are in front of our tree because i tried
to make a big a big flower so
i could put the star on the top ma'am
ruined it
to just be able to like jump around like
if you come this way cali
yeah follow me i think we can get to the
top like this you just jump on the box
yes oh okay maneuver around the tree it
should be like a little
stairway okay did you call a uh
taco eats
my inventory is a little low so hold on
let me get rid of something
snowballs i don't need them i wasted it
i wasted it
what is uh what is she plotting yeah
i was just setting something on fire but
don't worry it won't be the christmas
tree
i just want to put this bone somewhere i
can't all the things that i want to put
down i can't put down
when you press e and you you click on
your inventory you can drag it out
and then just just drop it somewhere
okay cool
i'll do that should make the star with
glowstone it's like close
oh yeah yeah well there's also the
there's also redstone light but i don't
i'm not sure how to make it
oh the redstone is pretty
oh no i'm just gonna bring more
scaffolding from
yeah i'll make my contribution i never
realized how much torches were around
our town until now
yeah put some bones there they're just
kind of floating well they disappear i
wonder
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh no the snowman is escaping who's that
that's okay we can make more push back
push it back
get in yeah all right
we're safe okay scaffolding
you're zombie why are so many chickens
i don't know why you tell me
i mean they do eat a lot of kfc in uh
japan for christmas don't they
yeah they do i don't know what so
why on christmas but i eat fried chicken
every day hello girl is the star
girl is the star on top of the tree i
know how's this happening
thank you for your momentum no but okay
[Music]
ah if anybody has redstone dust i can
try making a redstone lamp
yeah gonna think we're hung out
you know i'm reading your house for
redstone guys okay i forgot where i put
it but it's in there somewhere
i thought oh down
[Music]
now ladies let's not play fair okay sure
we're gonna be
[Music]
railway
okay okay okay
uh miss mori
yeah could you take a back step just not
towards the cliff
not towards the cliff
anita this way a little bit of room for
the star
thank you okay thanks guys how are you
ever ever thought have you ever thought
of the theory that
enderman might just be enma
song our manager ah
oh oh what
i'm gonna go put some fun surprise so
that would be quite a twist
what's your mail then hello oh
oh oops
all the different types of lines yeah
this made
a little more sense in my head but
stuff's breaking here gonna be a scuffed
scar
looks good looking good and uh
let me see that it might not be very
star-ish but
it's good either i guess i just can't
put them anywhere else i wonder if we
could have like
a few more color variations in the
decoration although it looks kind of
cluttered now so
should we add more hmm i think a few
more colors would be nice though
maybe i think yeah i think that'd be
good
i'll put mushrooms on it pink and green
let's see what colors i have let's
check some screen to see how this looks
i can't tell i think it's upside
put some of my fancy white glazed
terracotta on it but can i have it back
when the tree is gone
of course maybe maybe not because i got
them from far away
okay i don't want to lose them next week
you're really fancy that's a nice idea
we can make lots of tnt we can make
fireworks so we can send off the phone
yeah
there we go
this is easy i can do blocks the roots i
can't understand i can't make them work
i tried very hard
it's not working you know they don't
want to go in the style looks good
it's a little scuffed but we can improve
it later
it's nice i can't get up to scaffolding
ow
it's a chicken
i'll eat you don't blame me down my
employees
it does not look like a nonsense
of course uh
it needs a little more legs
is the tree lopsided or is it just me i
don't remember
being like that i may have forgotten one
side
[Music]
i can't make progress how do you get up
there
oh god uh hold on hold on i can fix this
did you guys want for christmas
[Music]
well you had to ask but what about
everyone else
i want sleep
sleep one's good i want just a freebie
[Music]
oh wait do you need leaves i have like
like 10 centimeters
oh yeah leaves yeah you have leaves yeah
i do hold on
i need them we can make the tree even
bigger
you won't believe how many leaves i have
[Music]
i have birch and uh oak and i have a lot
of springs
i love like spruce but
i have a lot of birch and spruce no i'm
at my house
i'll come to you my house
we're gonna have a very mixed
tree yeah this is
fine you guys like uh when trees have
like themed ornaments or do you like
when it's uh
like a bunch of handmade different
colors oh
i like colors i like colors and that's
like a more
personal flair to the trees i think
[Music]
are you like are you guys even gonna get
a tree this year
i'm probably not getting one because uh
i i don't want to get rid of it it's
kind of annoying in here and
you have to vacuum after the trees a lot
so it's easier to get a fake one
you always get a fake one yeah it's very
in the middle and where are you
oh i put some leaves in there in the
chest
i
fun when you have cats and a christmas
tree that's fun
yeah i had some kittens that were hiding
in the tree one christmas very cute
thank you thank you
[Music]
if i make the star a little better it's
going to be like bigger than street
i can't wait to see oh wait it's
glowstone that means it's going to glow
inside
you
oh it looks fine
i wish we could make like different
colored lights
instead of just one blue stone oh we can
make a we can make stained glass
oh i have a bunch of stained glass
we can
[Music]
okay exactly
but them being individually beautiful
that's what makes them special
[Applause]
oh thank you i literally have no idea
what i was just saying but okay i'm glad
that's a lie sounded good
no i mean i brought some stained glass
i'll put in the chest thank you
i only brought like two of each because
that's all i had left over but if you
need more i have more at home
[Music]
[Laughter]
how do we light up the stain glaston can
you light it up i guess you can put it
like in front
of the light so if you look from the
front it looks like different color
maybe
what if we put torches on the tree will
it catch on fire
they don't even place on the on the
leaves so i guess you'd have to have a
block
because it's hard if you have something
like um
what if you put it on an ornament is it
getting too much now
how does it look still put torches on
like the pumpkins or the terracotta
oh yeah underwear it's missing a bit of
clothes
over there okay i got this it doesn't
burn the tree
[Music]
we'll be fine
if it burns and the sun is setting
almost time we need more glow
should we put something under the tree
like a carpeting or
something oh carpet sounds nice right
maybe i can sorry
the tree looks so yummy it's like candy
growing on the trees
what color should it go under the tree
guys red
oh red would be nice yeah red okay
[Music]
are you okay are you okay
it looks so good oh i want to see
hang on oh that is so cute
oh my heart cool wait oh these are so
cool
there's like a perfect spot for a
photograph
something i know the part is here can i
mean the preparation for the tree as
well i want to stay on here
[Laughter]
you got to take off your armor though my
armor
[Music]
tastes are very similar that's why we
are both business owners taco bell and
kfb
exactly oh i think we could use one more
stone way up there
we can make a christmas card and then we
can sign it and then we can post it yeah
yeah it looks really pretty that's a
great idea i like that
let's do it again
[Music]
while i eat these potato chips i will
provide a view of the christmas tree for
everyone do you eat anything besides
potato chips
is there a reason too
[Laughter]
and bread that's that's your favorite
food i'm gonna order some vegetables
later for lunch i wonder what i should
have
i mean potato is a vegetable right yes
therefore potato chip is vegetable
healthy yeah
agreement
[Music]
that reminds me of it's the offensive
collab
i'll shut them down guys don't worry you
guys all have feathers
there's one that's in there and i have
one button here
yeah buddy actually i should have a lot
of beds
somewhere i bet you
everyone good hey
oh that's not that's the most fight me
like a real fandom
oh girl's fighting here wait hello
nice nice no wait are you just killing
it
oh they are is there only one
it sounded like only one the skies are
safe another day
yes i feel bad i wish i was there to
help
i tried to go to sleep you guys remember
the first minecraft collab where we all
just died at the start from the fact
how times have changed how they have
there's a party going on in my chat
right now
oh yeah party yeah
he just reached 1 million
[Music]
i'm ready for battle maybe we should
sleep what if they destroy our tree
they will they just destroy our lives
thank you i love you guys oh sweet
where is it i see it enemy spotted
i'm just going to sleep is
[Music]
sometimes the best option in a battle is
just to sleep
does anyone need extra beds i will make
some i'll also sleep
i'm sleeping on your cat's bed okay are
you sure you can because the phantom's
around
okay
[Music]
just pretend they're just pretend
they're um cats or something flying cats
no it's like it's like
whale sounds you know very relaxing
[Music]
thank you everyone oh my god they're
still partying
oh they're gonna burn to bed
[Music]
except they're dying instead of coming
back alive again
oh my god they're reversible
[Music]
uh yes
[Laughter]
understood there was actually a cat that
looked just like the first edition
i think it was girl's girl's cat
wow yeah it's like the uh the three
different colored ones
so cute oh yeah yeah yeah i have a lot
of cats now i can't really remember what
they all
look like i think we're gonna have more
and more cats because of the uh iron
i mean i'm fine with that yep they're so
cute
right more i only have one but i want me
i want millions of cats in my home
[Music]
yes wait what is this can i ask what
this is is this like
it's the uh the photo zone for i don't
know instagram it's the viewing platform
the photo zone temporarily i'll just cut
these off
oh so cute trees looking good
really really good i'm really happy with
it
oh the terracotta really good too needs
a little more red oh
[Music]
it's just a little more red in my
opinion more red or are we killing just
a little more red
like bright red like this kind of oh
like red blonde red
red red red red red red
we should make like a red carpet that
goes to like the entrance
oh good idea i have some red if you
would like to do it do you want to do it
yes please you can give me something
ready
here you go wait
[Music]
our elevators are gone huh oh do you
need some they can build
oh it's okay no worries
oh good in the hood i think i'll just
climb it the old-fashioned way oh here
there's some scaffolding
who tried to shoot me while i was
partying with my employees
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's okay it's okay um it's okay
i like being shocked it feels good yeah
she's used to dying
i like pain i'm a massive kid yep
[Music]
okay
the hanging ones i tried so hard
[Music]
are you talking about like tinsel that
you wrap around the tree you're
something like
is there anything you don't have i'm
telling you guys there's zombies
everywhere
i keep hearing them just like but
there's no there's no caves
careful they got arrows too they'll
shoot you you sure do
they'll get you millions snowballs
what's for christmas dinner by the way
oh
yeah chicken and christmas cake of
course
i'm gonna steal your snowballs no you're
not
oh my god the sound of
the sound of snow when you walk on it
isn't it amazing
exactly you can only have 16 at a time
it seems
good they have to tell you something
from a distance because nobody no no
from this close i want to look deep in
the eyes
[Music]
would do some damage so we can have like
an actual snowball fight that would be
fun
we can throw some uh arrows at each
other oh yeah
[Laughter]
until we die maybe we should build that
we should build a
coliseum
and we can fight to the death wait
didn't care build a ring
yes i did a while ago like a boxing ring
over to my house do we want to have a
baffle
christmas bathroom i'd like a christmas
battle
forget the christmas dinner it's time
for the christmas battle
yes the christmas battle that's what i'm
concerned about if
kfc and yeah exactly i'll just bring you
well actually that's not really my job
that's kind of my job to keep you from
coming back but uh yeah you can you can
just
just wink and just let us know
12 deaths of christmas
martin is suspiciously quiet has anybody
seen watson
what's up
i'm going to get vines and i'll be i'll
be back in like four minutes
i thought vines only take six seconds
okay oh my god there she goes
[Music]
that was a good one that was really good
that was really good
oh my god
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god
yeah you are on fire tonight she's
always on fire
i can't stop myself
[Music]
on my life no no you were going to make
an attempt on my life because you don't
have a life if you're
you're deaf exactly that's the point
which is why it wouldn't work
i don't know why i feel like battling
good albums
[Music]
oh wait are you guys making it to the
ring tempting fake i'll start both of
you i'll hurt both of you
it doesn't hurt at all though
i can pretend it is
this looks so good i really like it
i'm adding a little snow to the top of
the house
a frosted christmas tree yeah
yeah like guy fairy yeah yeah that's
right
like that guy tasting around the
christmas tree
all right coming back hey
that must have been
you gave him a life yes i saved him from
i don't know no no
the snow like how do you put it down
uh oh do you mean be a snow man or a
snow
ball or snow oh on the ground
on the it's like uh what is it it's not
a snowball
you take the snowballs and you go in
your inventory and you line them up in a
straight line i think
that's how you make them oh okay you
just fill your
uh crafting slots with snowballs and
then you get snow blocks
got it or you can get you can get like
the little little snow
thingies like that flat one yeah
cool snow thingies i see the snow
thingies would you call them they're
like platforms i don't know
oh sheet yeah yeah yeah
oh okay like this
wait wait sway the torches remove the
snow oh
no sometimes there's no carpet
an effort was made
if we put lanterns i don't think it'll
melt them uh
lunches instead i think all the snowman
just fell down anyways
[Music]
it's fun can you put the snowman on a
lead
oh that's a good question can we put a
saddle on him
can we ride the snow can we make a snow
horse
he's so cute though so cute
well at least there's still more and
more snowmen just jumping up and down
they're cute i hear the kids for our
those red bushes they're like holly we
can put a holly oh yeah
can we make them this little toe yeah
yeah
yeah i want it
[Music]
are you making an igloo huh i'm making a
cake
[Music]
okay oh my god i love it
i don't believe me i'm doing that
i mean you need red strawberries
i brought some red yes um okay okay
hopefully should we make lanterns for
the
well i thought the torches look like
candles but like i was wondering if we
could make like bigger candles with like
uh oh yeah yeah yeah like like something
something and then
yeah to make up some of these this idea
here in this chest i'll put you ready
oh
do your worst phantom oh my gosh
are you fighting them all right nice
nice nice
don't provoke them i've got five shots
today
nice shot nice
[Music]
christmas cake that's gonna be a cake
yes
yes shouldn't the ground layer be
i mean okay it's all gonna be out of
cream okay
again why not but we could have it land
a little bit like a little like
yellow and white oh with cream on top
it's jumping out yeah and then you can
have the side showings
how about we make this the plank the
plate yeah
now we can build on top of it okay we
have yellow for cake oh this is
does that look like from the side like
it could be
what we want it to be like another layer
of carrot
that can be the palm street oh
[Music]
you see this fine here yeah i guess
it'll blend in
i don't know it would hang you can hang
it off of oh
let's give it a try okay let's see what
happens
cool it makes an interesting one it
looks interesting oh
that's i see they're only in green
uh yeah except for the ones from another
but i guess you can't put those on the
tree for some reason or maybe i grab the
wrong ones
oh no no the stave
huge it's the emergency place
[Music]
i'll put some on the glowstone that'll
look neat i forgot
oh no there's it there it come again
where is it
[Music]
hello
that's not good guys oh no oh
don't ruin her i have my battle axe
who's i cannot be one two three
four come closer come closer
could you
i think it's afraid of the cats oh my
god
is that a thing some moms are afraid of
cats and like
dogs and etc
all the more reason to have lots more
cats please
[Music]
oh is that yeah you can do that
very good i'm gonna drop something for
you
[Music]
phantom membrane what is that oh it
doesn't make
do you want it i mean you kind of killed
it no it wasn't really me
yeah i did yeah i don't know i don't
know what that is i don't want it sounds
gross
i don't know what you can do with that
membrane oh it's used to repair
elijah's that's useful for later
that she got for free
get away from the tree everyone we lead
them kill it let's fire
we will not do such a thing
go away i'll try and drag them can we
can we
kill them with snowballs or something
it's fine it's
almost morning we
[Music]
that's so cute
thanks guys for helping you nice snowy
dudes
hey girls put down the base
and the cake where do we where do we
start how many dollars
uh start like right now right here i
guess
here like where i'm standing uh one more
i'm gonna help make
oh my god yeah do it so that there's
like one one um yeah
[Music]
do you want to come up here for a second
for what just to see it look at this
no i'm good though not anymore yeah
there's been more indiana more creative
than that
please yeah yeah a little more creative
what is this i will wait for you this
looks like fried egg
oh big egg
egg mama mama
hello
[Music]
i think we need one more here
and then one more here yes oh
oh you're actually making a proper thing
and
[Music]
i have i have these red these red things
here that we can put we can use them as
as uh
as strawberries yes yes yeah that's a
really nice
bright strawberry
christmas cake no i will not burn
everything dude where's the pizza sama
okay dude
no danny devito i will not burn our
christmas tree
excuse you they're asking one person
right exactly oh i should put the
scaffolding closer
i have a little addiction when it comes
to
yes
i'm curious you guys sure do a lot of
things in this game huh
will you burn it for 10 no no amount of
money
you're just going to be wasting your
money deadbeats will be wasting your
money
ow hey
are you guys hurting each other no we're
playful
we're playful uh we've been having fun
yeah we're high-fiving each other yeah
we're being good buddies and good
buddies like to touch each other
every once in a while what
[Laughter]
now we need we need more cream oh hello
i got the i got the i got the whipped
cream
what's going on what's up
we're family friendly course we are
what the hell um a little bit of bloody
touching is
there's nothing wrong about that okay
[Laughter]
can you burn it down for a scooby snack
no would you do it for two
groovy snacks
let's make it three minutes
just get thirty
all right i think i think i think we're
good for this job right now
and oh you gotta do it like like yeah
like a clock right like doing
yes and then doing like
i didn't take screenshots again it's
tasty
ah yeah oh yeah oh yeah
gotta get some making off photos here
what
i'm leaving this area i even i don't
even care if i hurt myself
no photos like that what i just take
off the progress okay so we only have
two strawberries
you said making out photos no making off
photos just come here
until they're done
wait this isn't going to work uh you
gotta
improvise adapt i got some more
strawberries
uh one
yummy huge
we got one for each member one's
shopping
so we don't have to fight over the
strawberry
should we i know this is not a birthday
cake but should we put candles on top of
the
strawberries oh nice i think the
strawberry looks a little weird
you think it's inspired
you think it's expired quantity is not
exactly a strawberry
she thought she tried to burn down the
tree for unprotected hand holding with
kiara what the [\h__\h] is water
what i'm going to cut down this tree any
objections
no no no no sorry no no no
christmas kisses no christmas kisses i
put those trees down because i was going
to hide anvils at the top so when you
guys cut them down they would fall on
you but it didn't work out so yeah you
can cut that portal
that would have been funny though come
on think of the contest
for the content yes
[Music]
hold up i got a very special block i can
light on fire i forgot where i put it
though
oh there you go second crib if i made it
the second christmas tree and burned
that one down
make for a cozy fire how do you make the
just make a bonfire
[Music]
can i hide inside of the cake yes
like what
like a chicken dinner uh-huh
when there were no chicken dinner okay
wait
all right
[Music]
so fire that sounds interesting i want
to see
hold on it's nice in here it's uh
you're inside the cave
it's like the uh you know when you make
like a marriage proposal and then
you like cut the cake
it's your it's your it's your wedding
cake
hallie this
don't ask me question kiss my quote
unquote
[Music]
what are you talking about
that sounds so weird
[Music]
what else can we build as christmasy
no i messed up
[Music]
oi can we put some pets in the tree what
are you doing to my candle there
what cats in the tree yeah that could be
fun if we put one of the cat like
just to put some cats on the tree like
his little decorations
cat oh yeah you know you have a ton of
cats right can you grab some put them on
the screen
i don't want him to die
oh sledding sled yeah on the on the ice
there's an ice biome oh yeah
[Music]
i have a bunch of ice i can't bring it
hold on i'll go get the ice
skating drink we can transform the
fighting ring
into a skating ring
we gotta extend it a little bit maybe
yeah
[Music]
will you give me permission to build a
giant chicken on top of your uh store
i i mean we can build it together
because yeah
um the blueprint for it before we get
started yeah
oh yeah please yes i got a lot of
uh wool as well so um it's gonna be
majestic
yeah majestic chicken i'm gonna make the
eyes glow
with clothes
a little bit like a phoenix so that my
my employees don't misunderstand
what it actually what we actually saw
but it's it's
laser chicken laser channel i just
realized
the christmas tree i think of my home oh
it is
it's right on top of my cave nice you'll
never lose your way this style
do you still not have a proper home let
me check it out
i mean i worked you can come see
something yeah
i've never i haven't seen your house yet
you can come take a look i still don't
have a proper door but you know i still
hear zombies
you wanna you want a door no i don't
know how to make one
oh no yeah ghost rider oh
i got super lucky i picked it up as a
gotcha oh my god oh there's a zombie
and then there's a [\h__\h] in kitchen up
here i'm still working on it is this
your pet or chemical
oh yeah oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you i have your salmon buddy hold
on
your cave has potential oh kelly you're
gonna have to
light up this place otherwise you're
gonna have a lot of friends i'll give
you one
she was told that before but she didn't
believe it i
didn't one i listen i just didn't want
to do it because they told me to do it
listen she doesn't want to be told what
to do she's a rebellious teenager
don't tell me what to do let's get you
let's get you a door
i'm getting ice but i already have a
bunch of ice so i'm just picking it up
and then i'll be back in like
four minutes okay baby
[Music]
door
yes cali i got the perfect door for you
punching bag really love that salmon huh
shut up
punching bag listen i don't know how
buttons work in this game
so on occasion when i try to feed my cat
sam and i end up hitting the cowardly
famine instead of giving
[Music]
it's a nice color too thank you nice
nice a real door hooray thank you it's
uh
adorable how's everyone doing
goodbye
[Music]
it's raining sharks and squids
oh cool can i fight can i go kill some
more fish i need more food for my kitty
yay
need more employees here
not enough people working at kfb why did
everyone quit their jobs what the hell
oh
no i think you need to look at yourself
mad in that respect
[Music]
was it me or did the zombie not have a
face that would never leave
me that was just you yeah i mean
maybe it was in the back of their head i
couldn't tell
it was looking at me maybe i think
you're going on the side of it yeah
yeah oh look how good this looks
this is so good i have some ink sacks
oh
i have some anvils your house has a nice
hat
put some rock damn it on this tree and
maybe the cats will come to it
do you like it i've been told it's a
finger apparently
it's a very interesting hat yeah maybe
maybe that's how they say hello to each
other oh um
i will not let them be hurt by a stupid
zombie
zombies we don't need this sunday
sunday it's not ready
stop they'll they're gonna kill me
they're gonna kill me people from the uk
i'm sorry i don't mean any disrespect
you okay
that's the aussie twang oh yeah i can't
do that
[Music]
british people be like subscribe to my
youtube channel
i love youtubers
legit
[Music]
amazing
all right anyway how's that ice coming
along i mean i'm almost back i'm in the
tunnel on the way back
i have 52 eyes
[Music]
oh wow i don't want that that would
probably taste really bad
zombie breakfast
just the side of rings
no i need to see if i can uh
get all these shamrocks wait
this is crazy wow
oh whoa those ink sacks
i like collecting that
i i i'm just uh admiring your beauty
when the sun is coming up you shine even
more beautifully than ever
oh oh my gosh
oh cutie well we know nothing's as
beautiful as you are
beautiful where the tree the cake is
almost bigger than the tree though
there's nothing wrong with what's wrong
with me
yeah it's enough for everybody exactly
yeah he's probably getting rid of this
uh yeah he's good man thank you people
thank you
do you see our delicious cake in our
beautiful tree
yummy and where do you guys think we
should build i have all the ice but
where should we put
like an ice maybe an ice slide because
if you go really fast on the boats
yeah won't make that big of a square
but now wait who is building something
on the mountain
which man oh that's good
[Laughter]
yeah nice idea you go down ice like that
does it still slippery
you're right ina it's a cutting board
just thank you thank you
it's uh it's really accurate
[Music]
you guys want some scaffolding
oh what's happening why are you coming
after me
really what is that you're using you
ain't legging freak what's wrong with
[Music]
is way faster we'll just use this
okay there you go let me get something
spiders have eight legs right
um okay
you know what else cause i call them an
eight legged freak and i'd like to be
correct when i insult them
all right that's good never mind don't
answer that question here before i like
the view from here
nice the tree looked also nice from here
it does
that's a weird oh yes
you know oh the tree on top of your
house
looks very weird you know what else
looks weird
[Laughter]
i gotta get one of those
you how could you
[Laughter]
cry
i have the same thing we all have the
same thing
oh yeah
put we'll put somebody do like this side
with blocks like even dirt and concrete
and the other side and then
um we won't fall off when we when we go
really fast
i feel like we're gonna need a little uh
fence to make sure we don't die
wait that might be the fun part of who
who gets the furthest without dying yeah
we'll do it over this uh this ditch here
you know so you guys uh
it's more fun that way wait how about we
put make a little pool of water at the
bottom
so we can like wee into it that'd be fun
ah
maybe it should maybe it's a it's an icy
diving board
of death
i'm gonna put a sharp turn here oh my
goodness
it's like a rainbow
[Music]
road wow
that's all the answers
the leap of faith i'm dropping i'm
dropping a bunch of boats if anybody
wants to pick up a boat
you don't want to like you don't want to
like put us put a
put some stuff on the side so we don't
fall off easily yeah
i'm bringing some dirt now though but
that's the fun part
no way i can make it safe this is not
regulated
i wish you could bumper you off that'd
be like a bumpy bird
i wouldn't make this place safe i will
make it safe so help me
and i brought i brought extra dirt so
help me poseidon i will
boats don't like you take fall damage oh
oh these will fall off i'll get some
water
yeah i'll make some
[Music]
i like blue yeah your color is better
yeah it's pretty cool it's very nice
could you try to make this longer or
will it end there
apparently there's no fault that is from
votes
also we can we can do it without the
wall and whoever falls off first is a
loser
whoever falls off versus a stinky
stinker stinkerton
[Music]
um
oh really
all right i just found out
[Music]
i'll just take this one what about my
boat
no you've got yeah mine
see i see oh we should make another
scaffolding going up
i love stuff oh wait i'm out of stuff
i'm sorry
i thought it would only be an hour and
30 minutes for that okay okay that's
fine
okay i think we can actually make the
slide like uh
like straight so we can go zoom in and
just fly oh
so you don't like fall down okay
okay okay
if it was here i was gonna accidentally
break the ice block that she was
standing on
don't worry about it okay let's go uh
take a picture yeah screenshot
screenshot
make it's been a sure since all of us
are here
we go down to the tree yes this is can
we have the tree edge the cake
on the picture oh we can probably find
an angle we can do
that holy
during the night should we wait until
it's night oh i think sun is setting
right now isn't it it'll be only like a
minute or so
flower and salmon yeah let's go on top
of here
it won't get both on it but let's at
least cut the tree yeah
f5 is the change thing yeah you can
press
f1 to get rid of the uh hug you want to
take off your
your uh that's not my equipment good
idea
pretty mm-hmm i'm seeing my bud
[Music]
i'm in i'm here i'm coming
oh how could i have forgotten
maybe we can all uh crouch
how do you crouch shift
oh shift yes yes
yeah cool crouching in front of the
christmas tree it's perfect
okay maybe one more should maybe one
more piston should be
let me up shorty's in the front
that's you i
it's perfect right now it's like not too
dark
okay please
how can i get rid of the ui uh f1
oh you know you want to crouch again
what's screenshot again f3
okay other
[Music]
i think there's enough room for both of
you up here come on come on
do we want to be on the cake
oh it's too easy let's just sit here
this guy's good okay ready
high
[Music]
we did it
you guys have fun okay enjoy the rest of
your time together
[Music]
i think we're all on the yeah
i would suggest that we leave the
christmas tree forever
we can keep until next christmas
[Music]
bye
okay
you