[Music]
foreign
so
[Music]
yeah okay wonderful wonderful
yeah maybe
[Music]
okay
okay okay sorry some adjustment had to
be made but welcome everyone
to the long awaited takamori cuny
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's
finally
finally time it's happening it's
happening
yeah they're these kfc people hello
recently they call themselves k of beets
isn't that cute oh that's so cute well
you guys are getting creative aren't you
you're getting very creative
is the audio fine everyone uh what's up
bgm as well and kelly's voice
check one two hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey hey hey hey hey
i'm sleepy but i'm here ah
very sleepy oh
yeah i came back the other day
yeah yesterday yeah that's right
it would be yesterday indeed yeah well
it was a nice trip
but about the trip we will tell you guys
the details in the stream
after this one that's right yeah i
already have a stream reservation for
the stream after this one so it's uh
in two and a half hours from now so
first we'll do the q a
and then we'll do the trip review
look forward to it anticipate it
anticipating it very much
i actually yesterday in my in my animal
crossing stream yesterday i already told
like
one or two small things
just just small things you know they had
nothing
it wasn't anything that i wanted to
necessarily say
later anyway i told them i told them
that you
that i brought my german chocolate and
then you kept asking for the german
chocolate and kept eating it and it was
so cute
it was tasty i don't know what else to
say in this place
my one father was very adorable and you
kept asking for my chocolate
but it's it's it's normal
of course i would of course i'd ask for
chocolate i we came to the conclusion
that
i mean i already told you that i i
taught you this japanese word that
describes you pretty well
kui symbol oh yeah that's right
oh yeah because it's the east yeah
who can resist german chocolate it's
just so good
true facts true true facts it's true
fact
all right with this uh sleepy cali
we're gonna wake ourselves up with some
nice questions um
yeah they were mostly chosen by
my manager but uh yesterday since i had
some more time i still went
in there and got a few extra questions
uh on my own
yeah it's a little more clear yeah
so there's also like two or three
japanese questions in there don't mind
it guys i'll translate them for you
anyway
don't mind we want to make there's a lot
of japanese uh takamuri fans as well so
wow welcome welcome
yokosoko
i think i saw that the first one is a
japanese though so uh i'll
don't don't worry guys i'll translate
don't worry don't worry and i'll read it
out loud for you and yeah
let's freaking go taka money q a
yeah that that thing q a with kiara
you sound very excited i'm i'm
raring to go i feel like i'm gonna
explode from excitement
okay here's the uh first question
and i'll read it and maybe maybe uh
let me know kat if you don't understand
something okay
okay
so basically this question is asking
um since you're like when you when you
collab with other people
you act very different than when you
collab with me even
it doesn't matter if it's senpai's or
other girls from her life english
you act very different there's a big gap
and you
seem you seem way
way more open with the other girls
then you then when you collab with me
and right they ask
if it's because you're nervous when
you're with me or when you just
p if you just pissed off when you're
with me or
oh or if there's some from some special
feeling so yep well you see kiara
sometimes
in in your life in your existence um
when you meet
people um and you meet friends you set
certain boundaries
depending upon how forward that friend
is
listen listen
some boundaries need to be set sometimes
you're a great friend but did you know
but even when they say simple things you
react like really really
well yeah because you're very clingy we
gotta we gotta take a couple steps back
you know gotta take a couple steps back
but listen you like
for example when ollie and other girls
flirt with you
or always see me a little bit now listen
you listen to me
now the ollie tricked me a little bit
all right i didn't realize that it was
that it was like that
until the end of the of the haitian okay
at the end of the livestream then i kind
of got those vibes of oh man oh man
you'll even hear me say oh gosh i've
i've been through something like this
with kiara before
so it's like that
but i've definitely boundaries will be
set i've definitely noticed that you're
like
way more like you want to go steps back
but do we have to go so far back that we
are like
like behind everyone else you you chat
with
yeah no not really i wouldn't say it's
that different
okay don't take it too personally
because it's why do you take it so
personally
it's okay come on man
like we still dogs and whatever it's
just you know i'm a phoenix though not a
dog
all right well that's not what i meant
with with that phrasing okay
you got it you got it
[Music]
how to say how to say uh
i want to set boundaries in japanese um
google translate
this is actually something that uh i
didn't realize until i saw this question
been listening to off with their heads
since sunday night is that keanu's voice
sampled at the very beginning
i listened and i was like wait actually
that does sound like me
you know what they're talking about is
it me yeah i mean it sounds
it sounds like you but i don't think
that it is oh you know what they're
talking about
and they're like yeah yeah yeah i know
yeah yeah yeah there's like a little
hoie
it sounds like it might kick at a key
like you can hear like slightly like two
keys kiki
ah you'd have to ask the producer i
didn't add those in
oh man yeah that's mysterious
very fushiki very fashionable so i guess
that's
but that's not me probably not huh but
it sure does bare resemblance to you
a lot yeah you guys can when you close
your eyes and you listen to it you can
pretend
you can pretend that it's kiara chan
all right so that's not me all too bad
but but uh if
even when i listened to it i i felt i i
felt like it sounded like me so that's
very
weird well there you go you can imagine
let's pretend we cleared that one up
next one
what would you choose case on the
forehead case on your cheeks or kiss on
the lips
none of them
forehead i i would have said the same
um kelly i don't think this is
necessarily about
if you get a kiss from me just genuinely
forehead okay okay wow oh my god
today is kind of a painful day isn't it
not just for you it's
anyone oh my gosh my deadbeats know this
my deadbeats know this i
i am very shy i don't like things like
that
it's not just to you thing we had such
nice days together yeah oh my god
next one
thank you too personally kusatori
um hi callie and kiara first off i love
you both so much
thank you for your streams and good
vibes all the time here's the question
for both of you
what are your favorite ice cream flavors
have an amazing holiday
you first comment what i like choco mint
chocolate taco mint chocolate and mint
it's refreshing it's zucchini oh
i actually um there's this one specific
ice cream flavor that i have in baskin
robbins uh in in japan
it's uh it's called but they only have
it in the
japanese uh uh baskin robbins it's
called
lavspotion31 it's really good it's got
like chocolate like hearts
in it and it's got like some berry
tasting stuff in it
it's really really yummy i like that one
too oh
but besides that one i like like um
i think like strazzatella or
something fruity i don't know i like i
like a lot of
different kinds of ice creams i wish
anything is good if it's
ice cream yeah i wish they had the that
one
flavor in every basking robin still
however
they don't have baskin robbins in my own
country to begin with so
that's kind of sad i wish they had oh
that's really used unknown
yeah basket rabbit's really tasty this
is not an endorsement not a sponsor
please come to my country australia
yeah australia seems dope um
hey mom and dad hope it's been a fun and
relaxing trip for the two of you so far
can't wait to hear all about it at the
end of this week yeah after this stream
we will tell you more
how do you think your first impression
of each other and maybe
other whole life members have changed
since your debuts was there anything
that was surprising or fun to learn
about
what about you kelly it's a good
question
gosh
everyone's really hard working it's not
like i thought that everyone was a
slacker in the beginning but
but do you really really see it when
when you join you know
everyone's working on like really cool
projects and stuff
and doing their own thing it's pretty
amazing everybody's very talented like
i didn't know that kiara was good at
singing and then i found out and i was
like
whoa that's quite amazing thank you
yeah um actually
for i think for kelly my first
impression
didn't really change like it wasn't very
off or anything
it was pretty accurate i would say like
straight from the beginning
i always thought and you were like like
the way
you you talked with us was like you're
like
super funny and cool and you use all
these weird
like words and funny words like like
yeet and sick nasty
yeah like that
yeah and yeah generally you just gave up
god gave off a really funny um
aura i guess a very funny personality
very
easy to you know talk to and
and hang out with and become friends
with so
yeah yeah but if we talk about other
members you know what's what's weird
like
um i was a big fan of uh piccola senpai
before i joined home live right
and the thing is like
now that i'm like part of her life it's
it's not that like she's like different
on anything but
my impression changed over anyway like
it's kind of weird like
uh in some way i wish i was i wasn't
uh like i feel i wish i i still saw her
like as a normal viewer and not like as
a colleague
because yeah it's like my point of view
changed completely it's a bit weird
yeah that happens i mean that's happened
to me as well you know
even just like uh rapping in the
underworld you know sometimes
people that you look up to it's it's not
so much that you
like i don't want to say like surpass
them but when you get into the same
working like field as them
and you start doing work like in the
same place as them
or that kind of thing you get like a new
perspective and you're like whoa
yeah okay i look at this person
different yeah you know
i think it's a good thing personally i
mean i don't
it didn't change in a negative way but
it's just like
a different point of view um yeah so
i feel i feel less like a fan now and
but i didn't enjoy being a fan of her
ah yeah that's bound to happen i think
yeah
difficult oh well but yeah also with uh
for example
uh gura um when
when i first actually i don't know my
impression did change but i'm not sure
in what ways
definitely uh my impression of her
changed a lot from the beginning oh yes
same she uh she's like i don't know
it's also hard to explain i mean
maybe you seemed a bit more quiet and
good i seemed more quiet in the
beginning
i think so too but then you know over
time it's like it became easier to talk
i think
definitely yeah that's how i felt at
least
next door i'm making music for a few
years on my own and i'd like to start
sharing it with others soon
one of my biggest struggles so far has
been trying to figure out how i should
present myself as an
artist as i'm much too spooked to use my
real name or face so that's good don't
use it
your real name your real name don't you
really finding a visual
identity and personality is proving
quite confusing would a phoenix
or rapper have any advice on the matter
sure um i mean
that's that's the tough part is that
especially i mean i think there are a
ton of musicians these days that are
that are using aliases or or character
image characters and that kind of thing
to present themselves so i think it's
it's totally doable
and and you should do it especially if
you're on the shy side i recommend it
but
it's going to take a lot more thought
than just putting yourself out there as
yourself so give it time and be patient
is what i would say
and make sure it's something that you
really like because you're kind of stuck
with it but you don't want to rebrand
before i give my answer i just want to
say because the chat is going crazy i
just didn't mention enough because my
impression of her didn't change
yeah same guys guys we're not forgetting
about inna how could i forget it
chill all right so my answer to this
would be
since this person is apparently having
issues like trying to
find an identity and like doesn't know
how to
present themselves out there uh like if
you're talking about like
deciding what you want to be and what
you want to you know look like and stuff
and maybe if you can't decide then maybe
ask your friends what they would imagine
you as like
like ask them if i was a virtual
youtuber what do you think i would be
what do you think what i would look like
and stuff like that yeah
nice idea yeah because maybe they can
give you some
ideas and opinions that you yourself
have never thought of like maybe they
see you as a cute cat and you never saw
yourself as a cute cat
you know maybe they said that maybe your
scene was a
blonde princess maybe you yourself never
saw yourself as a blonde princess
but yeah them seeing you like that means
that it must fit you
yeah all right yeah next
that's it yeah next time if janna would
ever revive
and didn't regain any of her memories
how would kelly feel
would she try to find a way to restore
those memories or just make new ones
good question
cause i last time i died and had my re-w
stream
for a little while i i didn't remember i
didn't recall stuff but i remembered
eventually
but what if what happens kelly if i
don't remember anything
if i don't remember you
uh you you act as though it uh that
hasn't happened before
completely because sometimes you regain
them but there have been times in the
past where you did not
at least i don't remember that yeah
exactly so there you go
that's the thing yep it's like that
so i mean there's only so much i can do
it's annoying
knowing knowing his health hey but when
when that happened did you try to
help me regain my memories or not i mean
because of it
as i said there's only so much i can do
after a while you give up
and you just make new ones
but if you when you went like like hey
hey yeah
we we're friends and stuff do you
remember and i say wait wait who are you
not like does that not hurt you
it's annoying
[Music]
you know there's a pain in my ass and
whatever
i mean yeah
but don't worry i guess i guess one
thing that you can do like if it's if
it's like
maybe that's like like a bug in my
system like for
if it only happens sometimes then i
forget everything i never remember but
most of the times i regain my memories
after some time maybe maybe i have some
virus or some bug or something kind of
gotta be fixed or something
yeah you should get that checked out i
don't know if there are any phoenix
doctors out there but
yeah you should what that means if it's
just like
a re like like a failure in the reboot
system
that means you could just try to quickly
kill me again with your scythe
and then next time if you boot me up
again
you know it might work out yeah but what
if it doesn't though
but then you just do it again and again
and again i'm a phoenix i'm a good cat
it's not a problem just reboot me again
and again and again
but what if it never ever would if you
never ever get them back
it's just like how many times did that
happen that i didn't remember you at all
even after you like tried to help me a
couple
back in the day okay way back
it didn't happen for a while i guess
okay yeah and then
yeah well i guess when it happens again
just just kill me again
it's just really want me to do that yeah
it's like restarting your pc and
suddenly every
every problem is fixed but that doesn't
that's not always what happens you know
sometimes i restart my computer and
after effects still crashes when i open
it
well then after effects sucks yeah i
mean
we all knew that but
listen well maybe that's the problem
with your pc though not with after
effects
yeah i guess so that's also true that's
all for true fact
just try just try rebooting again and if
it doesn't work then
maybe maybe call ahmed for some
technical help
if you say so amma knows what to do i'm
sure
i'm sure all right yeah she's the
troubleshooting master i guess
i'll try to um not die anytime soon
because i don't want to forget the
memories we made on our
trip exactly
that would be a huge waste yeah
okay next dog oh oh wait that's a long
one
i'm making a bit smaller okay hello and
kelly thanks for the amazing stream as
always
since this is the first sakamori couple
question mark q a
i want to ask some questions and play a
couple quiz game
let's see how well sangamone match with
each other rules
read the question and answer it at the
same time uh after a countdown of three
seconds okay
okay okay okay i'll read it and we both
answer instantly okay
okay yep okay three two one
summer winter summer spring
uh dark white or milk chocolate milk
yeah i was about to say the same bikinis
or one piece swimsuit
oh bikini bikinis
favorite stuff drink uh orange soda
iced tea is that a soft drink yeah yeah
favorite song from other whole life
member oh
um oh oh gosh let me think oh okay
i have no idea um which one
um this is me answering about you right
this is like me guessing what your
answer would be oh no no
just our own answer oh [\h__\h] oh lord
[Laughter]
well we know each other okay
okay winter spring
dark white or milk chocolate milk what
what why did you say white yeah okay
okay bikini is a one-piece swimsuit
one-piece swimsuit okay bikini maybe
favorite soft drink
i see um water
it does not suck chick i love what oh
favorite topping oh
of water okay it is kind of soft
favorite sound from other whole life
member well i guess we still uh
you said ahoy though oh i thought that
that was which that was the one that you
liked
that's a great question they're all so
good um
hinototi of course
i mean it's the one that i listened to
thank you
doesn't change one superpower that you
want to have
[Music]
i feel like i can do everything that i
want to do so that's rough
maybe no i can fly i want to travel in
time
yeah time travel that's a good one i
agree same
whole life member that you want to most
that you most want to collab at the
moment
whoa oh um
i mean i got some plans already set up
but for someone that i don't have plans
with at the moment
i would like to do another collaboration
nice
i feel like my favorites are always busy
it doesn't matter doesn't matter maybe
they maybe they don't want to collab
with me
oh that's impossible everyone wants to
come out with you what the hell
no maybe maybe we can't of course
members i don't know maybe for some
reason we can't
yeah i don't know this is this is too
hard this is too hard
you can't cool
can i i don't know of course say it
say it don't be scared don't be shy
i don't know maybe it'd be fun to collab
with um with rain or something
i don't know oh yeah
from id what yeah why not why don't you
sound out
well there there are multiple people
that i'd like to but i just i'm unsure
no not hold on ideal boing boing cup
size
um what does that mean is the question
like like
what is the size i think would would
start boinging
or what is the ideal size for me or
for who i like i don't know i think
that's your answer
um but i think for me i like a couple
a variety of sizes but you know
that one over there looks pretty good
okay when will take
married um
what no just maybe hopefully
i'll follow you someday
no comment hope you guys enjoy your
honeymoon trip and looking forward to
the sweet trip for you that's it
there you go thank you for the speech
actually um regarding the ramen
me and cali had some ramen on our trip
and we
actually have the same kind of taste
when it comes to ramen
right yeah i mean more so than tonkotsu
ramen i like miso
yeah we both like miso and tonkatsu and
shoyu
i mean it's edible but we prefer
tococ is good because it's not like a
heavy miso soup flavor like miso soup is
just so
intense it's very rich but with miso
ramen it's not over the miso isn't
overpowering it's just tasty
yummy yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum yum yum
all right let's go next question
what are your favorite snacks to consume
i hope the honeymoon is going
well favorite snacks
zambe that's your favorite bag
is like rice crackers and they're salty
what's bucky
you've never had pocky before pocky
pocky
they're tasty i prefer my my german
chocolate and my
australian chocolate hmm that makes
sense
like a milka or rita spot
or lint or kinder chocolate
chocolate actually kelly there's a
there's like a european
slash german version of pocky oh
yeah it's really yummy it's called
mikado
ricardo i'm not i'm not
yawning it's very very long trip it was
a really long trip listen
yeah it's really yummy i want to try
some
anything that's like hockey i want to
eat it doesn't however it doesn't have
as many
flavors as japanese pocky has because
pocky has like a million flavors right
yeah yeah yeah they got a bunch of them
what's your favorite
i like the strawberry ones i got the the
heartful valentine's day ones
recently just because i wanted to try
them because they're in heart shapes and
they're covered in strawberry
and they're pretty tasty i like them
they might be my favorite
and i like the crunchy ones too the
crunchy ones with nuts on the outside
it's like
it's chocolate and then you put nuts on
the outside and it's very crunchy yeah
yeah i've seen those
all right let's and next door
hi i'm a fan from indonesia i want to
ask what makes you two feel loved or
appreciated
i think that's a good question that is a
good question
i have a hard time discerning these days
but i feel like i
i don't know it's hard to tell because i
feel loved and appreciated all the time
since doing this so
i don't really know what it is exactly
uh
i don't know maybe maybe just um even
when people
i don't know you don't need to super
chat at me just being in my chat and
wishing me well
uh is something that makes me feel loved
and appreciated
[Music]
for me i think if i had to say something
like concrete and
i think a specific i think i would say
like just if someone asks me
how are you
yeah that's a good one no one really
asks yeah right
they always ask where is kihara but no
one asks how is kyoto
yeah no but that is like that's
something that people often forget about
just asking people how they are
but it's such a simple question but that
often like if someone is feeling bad
that often gives someone finally a
chance to open up
and say actually i'm not feeling so well
let me tell you
more about it please i need someone to
talk to yeah
and that's a really good point yeah and
even even if i'm not feeling bad if
someone asks how i am
even if i'm doing well i just feel like
them asking that question
and just gives me a feeling of they care
for me
although it's kind of weird because i i
have heard i've
experienced that for example people in
america use how are you just as a hello
and they don't expect an answer and they
don't give an answer
right right exactly
even if you're not good yeah but like
okay for
most of the time people who i have a
conversation with answer this question
seriously and when they ask me it feels
like they want to know an answer as well
so yeah it's nice yeah i think that's
really great
yeah because most of the time people
aren't really they they aren't actually
looking for an answer and you can tell
when they aren't
it's a little upset
oh well how how are you kelly
um okay that doesn't sound very
okay there's just a lot of stuff going
on
i don't know uh yeah i can't really
it's hard to talk about but there's just
a lot recently
i guess i guess i we gotta do a therapy
after the stream
help us i guess we should probably talk
more huh
yeah i told you i told you like during
this trip
we had so many conversations because we
were together all the time
but like outside of our trip we don't we
don't
like talk that much we do but we don't
talk like extremely much
and we don't talk like you're in god
yeah
so i told you even after the trip
you can call me anytime if there's
something on your mind if you just want
to
vent or whatever just call me callie you
got to let it out
of your system is it really okay aren't
you busy no i
i mean i have time for you anytime what
the hell
really it's important that you have
someone to talk to please
yeah but i don't know i sometimes i
worry about telling people about
my problems because i don't really know
if but i know that they'll
end up feeling bad though and they can't
help me you know okay
i i it's just i wanna i wanna give you
someone that that listens to you and can
relate you know
you said it yourself it's hard to um
talk about these things
with like people who are not in the loop
you know
yeah so it's better if there's someone
who's like in the loop right
yeah that's a good point i'm here for
you
yeah okay thanks you're welcome oh we'll
have to do that then
anytime i appreciate it next time
yeah next question what is your favorite
thing that you two have done together so
far
i might can we really talk about that
without maybe spoiling the vacation
yeah i guess that's true
i mean
i really liked the papers please collab
[Music]
i collapsed huh we made a good thing
yeah
collabs
hey honestly rather than gaming collabs
um i'm very happy that we did our wawa
world collab
um that's like that's almost like one
million views by the way guys so
everyone who's here
if you would all after the stream take a
little moment
to check out the video and uh listen to
it one more time
then we might get to one million guys
hmm
because today we're doing so many
collabs
yep there's a lot going on and then i
have a solo stream later too baby
i think it's like nine nine thousand
views left to go and there's like what
uh if youtube is telling me this
correctly then there's fifteen thousand
people watching right now
so honestly if every one of you go
there yeah then that's enough what the
hell if you guys don't make it happen
then i'm gonna be crying just kidding
but you have to listen to your boss i'm
your tantrum guys
oh my gosh please not the usual room i
keep
i keep hearing things over on my side
people that have escaped and are saying
callie please help and i can't help them
i'm powerless i won't give you their
names i won't do it
actually i won't let them have you i
feel like the the usual room has
some things in common with uh the
underworld so you might
actually enjoy it oh really like what
can you tell me later
yeah i mean i'm yesterday i recreated i
started recreating the usual room
in in animal crossing and it has like it
has like a
lava floor oh okay that's fun
yeah that's fun right so you can like
split your splashing in the lava
yeah that sounds excellent i'd like to
come to visit the usual
definitely not try and sneak your kfp
members out i would never do that
don't throw that try and save them i'd
never do that they need to be punished
they need to be punished not necessarily
punished they're not being punished if
they're they are there for re-education
oh okay then they need to be re-educated
right i got it okay well i'll come visit
um just to hang out then because i love
i love lava floors you can maybe help
them um complete their puzzle because
there's a puzzle of one million pieces
in the usual room
but yeah but there's one piece missing
wow it sounds like a whole lot of fun
so people look like ocd i guess they're
gonna like really have a
hard time uh yeah i think that they
might suffer a little bit
suffering yes that's what we want uh
sorry
no no re-educationally re-education
re-educational
yeah i believe you i think people would
be very happy if you would visit
actually you're not allowed in the usual
way because i don't want people to be
too happy there
oh uh but i'll make sure to hurt them
how about that
whoa now we're talking
yeah yeah i'll hur i will hurt them with
my scythe
oh hell yeah oh my god i'll be sharp and
it will put it'll make them feel pain
wow that that gets the usual room to a
whole other level man
i bet it sure does oh my god you're
probably killing the people though
i don't want them to be killed well i'll
be careful
i'll be real gentle with it maybe you
know what you could try to
maybe you with your side maybe you could
like try to
just peel off like one layer of
skin cells oh nice just the very very
top layer
that would be kind of difficult i'll
have to be very
very careful and distressed with myself
but i'll give it a shot
oh my god yes
i'll give it a swing it sounds it sounds
terrifying now
yeah maybe a little bit huh
maybe maybe a scythe is not exactly
maybe maybe it shouldn't maybe your side
shouldn't be allowed in the usual
maybe i should just use my fingers to do
it to
peel off people's skin yes uh-huh
that might be easier if i use my my long
finger nails
oh my god yeah
[Music]
it's like a skin peeling honestly
actually a good thing
it's like a like a beauty salon at that
point
exactly exactly very refreshed
all right new addition to the usual hell
yeah
taking applications now indeed
get me please oh no oh no
there's those people wow of course
all right next one uh yo yo
what is something you or somethings you
admire about each other
take care and have fun
there's a lot uh let's see
yada is a good singer um
and also very nice and easy to talk to
thank you
and even if there's a bunch of people uh
in a room that don't know how to talk to
each other
uh if if kusa today is there then
everyone will feel comfortable and start
talking in no time
and uh yeah i don't know what it is
about you that does that
it confused me because i try and do the
same thing too sometimes it just doesn't
work
oh no i see i see i see thank you
you're welcome for me i admire kelly for
her insane heart like ability to heart
to be like hard working
i mean i admire her for her create
creativity
and uh i admire her for her
um i had something in my mind
i forgot what to say wait what was it
what was it ah she's like actually
she's super cute like she doesn't show
it right now but she's super cute she
has like
these super adorable moments
a lot of them i don't know what you're
talking about
she's super cute i can't say that i know
what you're talking about
but okay if you say so
she's adorable she's just sam i mean
i asked maybe she shows that in her own
stream sometimes
but even that that's not that's not the
kind of cuteness that she shows me
what are you talking about yeah what i
want to say
but i'm just saying you're pretty
adorable
you're a thin ice cream
oh wait what did ollie say about that
when i said that to her what was her
oh yeah you did say that then it's
easier to crush it
our eyes between us oh hell yeah now
there you go
i thought that that was there was
something beautiful about that the fact
that that uh ollie was you know trying
to flirt with me and then you get angry
at ollie and then ollie immediately
starts flirting with you yeah she flips
with everyone
yeah i thought that there was something
special about that
therefore i don't think you should be
too angry yeah
that's true that's true i guess so i
guess so
end uh we we we do have our
our bond don't we that that other people
don't have
i mean i think that there are very few
people in the world
um that continually die and get killed
by each other over and over again and
keep coming back to life all through
eternity so i would say
that it is special and different yes
your face scares me
[Laughter]
i don't want to scare you it's just a
reflex
next one what is one quirky thing
we don't know about either of you yet
i have a good one no no no
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
it's so cute though it's so cute
callie callie speaks in her sleep
not not that much
actually it's uh like in in windows
nights that we
uh slept in the same room um in the
first night
she talked a lot and i was like that's
the first time i knew about it so
i woke up and i was like who is she
talking to me and i tried to listen and
it was like
it was english it was english words put
together
it didn't really have much context but
she kept on talking you know i wanted to
write it down but i was too tired to
write it down
so yeah that's that and then the next
night
the first night she was actually talking
normally right and in the second
night i woke up and she was making
the following noises
sure it didn't sound like that it was
like i don't know you were kind of
low-key crying i was getting worried i
thought you might be having a nightmare
or something
oh what did you say i was giggling i
thought you said that i was laughing
no you were like looking like crying
but yeah maybe you were maybe you were
giggling a little bit a little bit in
the first night i'm not sure anymore
but uh the following night i think you
didn't uh say anything anymore
uh so it's like a gotcha a lucky draw
yeah
whether i'm talking or not huh maybe
it's not a hurdle you know
actually um uh
recently wait who was that uh was it
wait
who recorded themselves in their sleep
the other day uh another whole life
member
was it was it was it oh you guys
probably know
was it it wasn't on it it was uh you
guys know that
i know you guys know that come on come
on
[Music]
senpai recorded herself in her sleep and
she was
saying some things that made absolutely
no sense
and it like was barely a audio boo
audible but i think if you record
yourself in your sleep cali
that would probably be a lot of audible
things
wow maybe i should do that yeah try it
out one
i mean you maybe need to to do it more
than one night maybe there's some nights
when you don't talk
yeah that's true but i that that just
goes to show that i will never do a
sleep stream
who knows what kinds of things i might
end up saying
i think it's um good that we will never
to sleep stream
yeah that's never happening ever in a
million years
all right well is there anything quirky
that um
you know of me that other other people
don't really know
hmm i mean i guess i wonder
everyone knows chiara's a phoenix right
so fire and whatever etc
but did you know that kiara actually
can't stay in a hot place for too long
believe it or not you're exposing me
yeah that's right you can't take it you
said to me callie i don't think we can
stay here too long it it's it might be
too hot and i can't do it
hey now listen
my god was that your girl i was i was
impersonating you
listen listen here and listen now
so i was just trying to make the hot
water feel good about itself
i'm sure you were yeah sure you were
because
yeah so cookies when you can't stay in
hot water for too long no no no
boiled chicken from a boiled chicken i'm
just in the water and like
the water is like you're super hot and
i'm like wait this is just nothing this
is a no problem for me
but then the water would be like crying
and feel sad so i'm like oh my god this
is so hot
all right i believe you i'm sure chat
believes you too
definitely i mean actually that's um
i had i uploaded this video uh the other
day
where i was drinking hot chocolate and
then i was like
so but but in that video as well
i was just making the hot chocolate
feeling good about itself
yeah i'm that's definitely what you were
doing yeah for sure
i believe you yeah i i just don't want
to make anyone feel bad
yeah you know what that comfortable kind
of view because
that's very admirable thank you thank
you yeah no problem
all righty let's go next door
but that's the japanese one i'll
translate it for you guys don't worry
about
[Music]
um if there's like any places that we
still want to go in japan or if there's
places that we went to that really um
stayed
in our um memories that we liked a lot
yes okinawa i want to go to okinawa
wait you've never been told nope
tonight
places that i really wanted to go in
didn't really work
[Music]
you get a beautiful view of this volcano
and there's a beautiful ferris wheel
and it's really wonderful especially in
the winter time because it's not too
snowy but there's like a little
bit just a little it's mostly warm
i've never been to kagoshima
really underrated has the the best the
best tonkotsu ramen i've ever had in my
entire life
um entire existence ever since the
beginning of time
uh is is the there's tonkotsu ramen
um in kagoshima station
um
[Music]
um fukuoka there's actually like
um i've been to japan so many times
even before um like me currently living
here right now
but um i've mostly been to kansai
prefecture and kanto prefecture kanto is
where
tokyo is and kansai is where osaka and
kyoto and so on are
and but yeah so besides that i haven't
been to so many places actually but
fukuoka is one of them and i really like
fukuoka
was dope and one of the things that i've
noticed in
in osaka i really i really love osaka i
have many
very amazing memories in osaka
the people from kansai or like osaka
specifically
are famous for being very open and very
funny they're most of the comedians
in japan all come from osaka did you
guys know that osaka is famous for being
the the
the place where all the comedians come
from yeah yeah i need that i need that
of course i don't really understand
understand them but i'm sure they're
doing great
yeah um uh so yeah that that basically
just reflects how
how open and how funny and how kind the
osaka people are all
kinds of people in general i would say
true yeah
yeah so yeah wanna go to okinawa
hopefully maybe
maybe in 2021 maybe in 2022 but one day
you gotta make it happen
yeah you gotta go go go i wanna go too
mikimasha
and actually the one other place that i
really really really really always
wanted to go
we already visited together this week
oh really oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that was right that wasn't my
in the top two uh places that i wanted
to visit in in japan
in the background you can kind of guess
where we went i i put some photo that i
took in the background did you did you
see it kelly
you'll be able to guess probably some
people will yeah yeah yeah
no no
i think so i think you will guess it but
uh even though it's pretty obvious
when you look at that thumbnail i'll
still keep quiet about we'll tell you
guys in the next stream
yeah yeah it's definitely a dream come
true going there is uh was amazing
yes yes yep okay it was really a dream
oh next
next one is japanese as well i think
that's the last japanese question that
we have
[Music]
is japanese but got into her life
through english whole life
i think this person wants us because
they enjoy us
speaking uh japanese and because they
don't speak much english
they want us to do a japanese-only
collab
we can do that
[Music]
i'm trying but have you have you noticed
uh
your japanese getting better a little
bit
sometimes i'll say a sentence that i
know is incorrect and that
my japanese sensei told me was incorrect
and then i'll correct myself but i still
i don't know there are too many words i
don't know
you said before that you're it's more
like your vocabulary is lacking right
[Music]
the way it is right now we could still
collab in japanese only
okay yeah we probably could i mean we'd
be able to do it it would just
be really i would suck but it's fine
we'll do it anyway maybe we could do it
like with a game that's japanese only
yeah yeah actually i have one in mind
oh okay um
yeah yeah yeah but it is that the thing
that really sticks out to me with this
question is the person saying they got
into
all alive for whole life english even
though they're amazing
yeah i've had me all it's got me all
fired up yeah
actually like i had someone tell me that
before maybe it's the same person but
yeah that's that's pretty cool yeah
welcome to whole live check out the
japanese members at least you understand
them
yeah you'll understand the japanese
people they're awesome they're awesome i
love the japanese neighbors really hard
and they're cute
[Music]
there we go hi karen kelly hope you guys
are having a lot of fun on your trip
it's over now
unfortunately this question actually
comes from
oh all that question i picked this one
uh this question
and it comes from my young niece ever
since i started babysitting her we've
been watching your streams together
especially since the
especially the minecraft streams she's
so sorry
no i'm not i think it's bad although i
i'm also also kind of worried because i
do
swear a lot now no
f word f word f word
anyway she noticed callie's scythe and
chiara's sword and asked me
when they go outside do they take them
with them or do they leave them at home
can they make them disappear or appear
and is it magic i don't know how to
answer these questions and i hope you
guys can clarify this for us
um i can't i just leave them at home to
be honest when i go outside
i can make mine disappear it's really
easy it's always with me it's just
invisible right now for example
actually i i leave them at home but
actually i can also
just um i can do something similar like
you i can
like you see my badge that i have on my
on my
oh my on my chest yeah yeah yeah that
just if you look closely my sword and my
shield is combined into that batch and i
can pull it out
you know and then i have it it
transforms into a bigger version of it
uh-huh that's right yeah you told me
about that that's pretty cool yeah but
usually i just leave my
my badge at help at home and then i just
go at that without the badge
because it's better if you know not too
many if people don't ask too many
questions and that kind of thing
especially
for example my my cloak right now uh i
whenever i visit the surface world i try
to wear um unless i'm on business unless
i'm on business i try to wear average
um human clothing oh yeah yeah we did we
did
we did we did actually um now just say
that
how would you how would you
describe your average human clothing
oh for me i dress really casual like i
like sweatpants
and um like well for example look at my
outfit right now it's very um
it's hard to put on it's very high
maintenance
um you know so when i can i like to be
comfortable as possible
uh i got some sneaks we love the jays we
love the jordans
um and that adidas though oh hell yeah
yeah and i actually i actually wear a
lot of um like uh like fitness wear
i guess t-shirts and that kind of thing
i like to wear uh super tight like a
long sleeve with the hood
like uh kind of the kind of uh uh
where like how do i set up jackets that
you wear when you go jogging
and that kind of thing and i like
leggings too and then i'll put like
either a big hoodie on
or like um a big like shirt or something
like a graphic tee like a really big
comfy one and then i like neato bows as
well uh knit caps
that is uh extremely accurate yeah
and recently i bought some new chains oh
is it like but i really only wear them
during this
golden dollar sign change no no gold i
i have the classy ones just a typical
thin silver one
that's all you need it's kind of
disappointing i wish you wouldn't be
wearing this dollar signed one
that was so cheesy please do it
actually um what about you you were
looking very
you were dressed very cute now don't
take that as as me
saying anything like absolutely i think
you're cute but i thought your outfits
were cute thank you but actually like
i i tried to dress appropriately to the
river
because it let me just say it was cold
as
hell okay hell is not cold but it was so
[\h__\h] cold okay
so it's hard to dress cute when it's
freaking cold
but um i guess i i probably dress a bit
cuter in in like summer and spring and
so on
and but yeah in winter i like to put on
like you know
hats or like ear muffs and boozies
cute cute fluffy bootsies and um
i like to wear um i like to wear coats
rather than like full on like these what
do you call those fat
what do you call that jacket that i was
wearing oh yeah it's like um
it's like a puffer jacket yeah i i don't
i mean i don't really like those
but for the lever it was kind of
necessary
yeah but i prefer i prefer like girl
like normal what do you what what would
you call that
that like like a normal fabric
yeah just like a normal coat oh yeah
yeah yeah i get what you're saying
it's like kind of felt sort of but it's
like a cotton
as well exactly exactly i prefer those
they look kind of um sometimes you look
kind of
yeah chic elegant yeah yeah very chic
but it's difficult i recently have this
feeling that i want to
uh like buy a whole new wardrobe because
i've noticed that my style
like has changed a bit over the years
and i still have a lot of clothes from
like years ago
yeah it might be nice to just throw out
all the stuff you know you'll never wear
again
and then go on go and buy some new stuff
a little little shopping spree for
yourself i think i think you deserve
that
i do have to do that anyway because i'm
i'm moving uh back home soon and
i can't i can't wait until you go back
home wait till you go back home though
yeah i go shopping there but i still
have to throw away a lot of stuff here
because it just doesn't fit into my
stuff
yeah good point um
but you yeah you've also been saying on
our trip that you really want to go
shopping right
i do but i don't want to overdo it too
much just a couple new things you know
a couple new things just because i mean
also think about it you know
uh it's getting really really cold but
also it's a tough time to go shopping
because even though it's it's
a cold month you know it's about to be
spring
and then it's going to get warm yeah
true and then what
you got to get clothes clothing that's
flexible for any time of the year
that's why i like especially to get like
big graphic t-shirts that like are
not very form-fitting but then i put if
it's if it's winter's time
i put the athletic wear underneath
that's like really skin tight and that
kind of thing
and then poke the hood out of the big
shirt oh that's my style
kelly kelly you don't have to get
clothes that are flexible for every
season you could get clothes for every
single season
okay that's what i do yeah
i guess so but um i just really like
having like
clothes for every season because like
for example i really like autumn fashion
autumn fashion is the cutest i agree
yeah scarfs and stuff yeah yeah and then
like the autumn colors are just so
adorable i really enjoy like
like dark and dark red like wine color
and
dark green and brownish colors for
autumn but then for spring i want like
white and
and pastel colors and all that and for
summer maybe that's too
but combine it with a little bit more
poppy colors
so that kind of makes i like com like
mixing the colors depending on the
season
fun yeah hey we totally went on a
tangential that was not the question
yeah it sure wasn't but there you like
sneakers what kind of shoes do you like
ah like all sneakers um i generally
i like wearing uh like ankle boots
ah yeah that fits you and well for
for winter right now i prefer like you
know i told my fans before and
and this is like a 50 50 because 50 of
the people hate them
and fifty percent of the people love
them i guess you know those ugg boots
yeah ow yeah i i like them there's so
much for the thing
yeah the thing that was in what do you
think about ugg boots
i don't they're not for me but you know
i guess i mean for example you know mama
reaper loves them
mama reaper loves those i
i don't know i just i'm not i'm not
super into them i guess
yeah not my thing i i kind of prefer um
more like uh more yeah ankle boots and
that kind of thing or like those that
you can tie up with laces and they're
made of like leather i don't really like
heels personally but that's because i
have to wear them all the time when i do
my job you know
and they're helpful that their help they
help me they they do help me as a reaper
believe it or not
wearing heels if you're a reaper makes
you it's a sign of status and it makes
you more powerful
um but for example kia i'm jealous of
your sneaks
my sneaks yeah you have some nice sneaks
right don't you work something
yeah those are really comfy yeah i can
run around with them easily
yeah if i go if i go more casual for
example in summer though i
i do prefer like having some some cute
sandals that are like
uh slightly like slightly that have like
some some slight platforms
you know what i mean oh yeah yeah yeah i
know which ones you're talking
yeah you can get some really cute shoes
in in tokyo
ah wow go shopping spring yeah
you you you said it that i should go
shopping when i'm back home but
uh the fashion is something you should
go shopping together yeah
the fashion is just so different in in
tokyo
yeah you'd have to buy a ton of new
things just just a couple
you know i mean imagine some of the
stuff that you're going to take back
home
right and look through it and throw some
of it away and then just go buy some new
stuff
oh yeah there you go all right
so oh and that's that let's go to the
next question
oh this is a question that you asked me
in my in my chat in the comments
the other day but i i didn't see it so i
couldn't answer it when you say pancakes
okay
i like both though actually no french
toast oh
no one of the options pancakes
i would say between those two if i
really had to choose
i would go for pancakes but both of them
i would have to arrange a little bit
yeah because i want strawberries and
powdered sugar and syrup
and all that stuff yes yes yes lots of
cream
and lots of uh berries lots of fruit
like bananas and [\h__\h]
and then and then put a [\h__\h] ton of
nutella on it
hell yeah yeah i like making pancakes at
midnight
good timing to make pancakes i i agree
with that excellent
that's the best timing actually uh kelly
there's um
there's an australian wink version
of pancakes oh and it's really yeah it's
like a thing that's like it's between
like
american pancakes and french pancakes
like it's a or french crabs i guess it's
like an in-between thing
oh okay that's one of the few things
that i can cook
yeah it's egg it's called palacing
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah got it it's so yummy and with the
leftovers you can make a soup actually
oh really it's a very popular soup in in
australia
oh that sounds good i'll make it for you
maybe if we have some time
yeah i want i want to try i wanted to
make french toast for you anyway
actually oh yeah you mentioned that yeah
maybe when we wash shrek
oh okay i'll make either french toast or
a pallet chicken for you yes please
that's a good idea
i will we'll just eat it for dinner
right we'll have a sweet thing yeah yeah
yes because i'm already used to eating
pancakes for for uh
at midnight a midnight snack kelly
that's one of the things that i love
about you
is that you eat like sweet stuff a lot
and you don't mind
eating sweet stuff like a dessert for
dinner like i do that too
yeah yeah why not i use food ain't it
yay yeah
pancakes for dinner with chocolate ready
yay
i anticipate it maybe even put some ice
cream on top
yeah yeah i'll remove that's perfect
yeah definitely nutritious and good for
our souls maybe not for your body but
good for your soul good thing that we
don't really have
regular human bodies right yes yes yes i
agree
i'm looking forward to that a lot now
hell yeah
me too i anticipated nicer all right
next
what is the skill or trait from the
other that you wish you had yourself
should i start oh yeah i i wish i had
your
lyric writing skills because i can't
write lyrics
i liked the ones that you did for
hinotori but it's just like three lines
that's nothing
yeah it took me a while to get like uh
something good for that
lyric writing is hard to be honest there
are a lot of times where there are lines
that i write that are just kind of like
i don't really think too much about them
they're the spiller but they're just
there to lead up to the good line
you know do you correct yourself a lot
in the process
oh yeah all the time unless unless i'm
in a rush and then it's just kind of
like ah
shoganai but i try to not let it get
like that oh
yeah i wish i had your lyric writing
skill
i wonder is that is it something you
kind of like had to teach yourself or do
you think you just have a talent for
that
do people have a talent for that that's
generally not only you like lyric people
you know i mean i'm not sure because i
actually i used to write a lot of poetry
um when i was a little reaper uh-huh and
i got a lot of awards for that stuff
but i didn't really think it was
anything it was i mean i didn't want to
grow up to be a
a poet i wanted to grow up to be a
reaper oh god so
but imagine imagine small cali like
roses are red
violets are i don't even know
what would i do without you yeah
something like that i mean they were
they're around
they're pretty much like like that oh so
cute
yeah that's cute so yeah maybe that's
that's how maybe that's how you got your
lyric writing skill hmm
it must have come from that i don't know
where else it could have come from
one skill that i wish i uh that i wish i
had from kiara is
japanese ability i think it's the
obvious one but
gosh every every day i just kind of
think
i'm trying my best but gosh i suck and
like
i wish i had your memory in that way you
know i can't remember words
i just can't remember them i'll i'll put
it into a flash card
and i'll replay it over and over again
every single day and it'll be five days
later and i still won't be able to
remember it because i have goldfish
attention span goldfish memory
i see actually i generally have like
verb memory
myself like it's really bad i don't i
forget things
so fast but with uh when it comes to
japanese vocabulary
i don't know i just i just had a really
easy time for some reason
wow this is freaking lucky but
that does remind me of during our trip
i'm actually glad that like mostly you
planned everything because
normally i'm always the planner when it
comes to trips but you plant most of the
things
and and but but i
i did lots of japanese talking i did
mostly
talking yeah yeah you did yeah i mean
you were with me
i just thought and i'll i'll lay back
and let kyoto take care of this there's
no need for me to try my best to
scramble around
that's totally fine but it's like funny
because like obviously the bookings were
under cali and
murray right oh yeah but like i was the
main top
main talker so they would call me the
the hotel people would call me kelly
callie like they would be like okay we
found candy song kelly said i'm like yes
yes
i would just go along with it because i
didn't want to like explain
what was going on and i'm just sitting
in the back like yeah
i'm the chiara one we switched rails
there
yeah we kind of did huh yep i just let
you take it take over i
thought i'll take a little break i mean
you know
since since your boy planned everything
then you know i guess it's it's a nice
thing that you
got to take over talking it's a win-win
we both put in
some of the work and there it is i
didn't i didn't mind it at all
really is it okay sorry about that you
can i mean i can usually
i can get around you know in in that
kind of situation but
i just thought yeah you're the you're
the fluent one so i'll let you handle it
it's okay you can rely on me okay
all right oh my morty i know you guys
are getting really fired up about these
trip details but more
uh are coming in the next stream i have
a few more questions i've
just a few more questions oh that's a
big one what the hell
let me read oh my god okay
i hope you're having a fantastic time on
your trip and i hope it gets even better
you two are incredible inspirations and
equally amazing
people with how hard you've both been
working with your girls deserve all the
recognition love and more
thank you just wanted to say that
watching you too and seeing all you've
achieved in these last five months
ah wait i thought i know this one it has
made me rethink my life and what i am
doing
i know that you two didn't just suddenly
sprout your skills during your debut
i understand you that you've worked hard
for years before to gain that skills you
both have
so i know i can suddenly change but i
will have to work just as hard for years
to come
i don't know if i have the strength
alone to accomplish this but seeing you
too always refers my energy
you both deserve to be chosen for her
life and i'm thankful you both tried
out thank you from the top to bottom
left to right of my heart
thank you for coming into our lives
thank you
it's just that's a really sweet message
yeah i'm glad that they said that
because
i don't know sometimes i i think about
how lucky
we got that we were chosen to do this
out of you know there's so many people
that try really hard
and sometimes i wonder to myself you
know did i don't know
you really do i really deserve to be
here and really
me but thank you for saying that
i had i had that issue like that was
something that was on my mind a lot
especially in the beginning i really
i really felt like i don't like
skill-wise and all that i don't deserve
to be here
like i'm not good enough especially
compared to the four other girls
or even the japanese members i just
didn't feel like
i'm good enough for our whole life and
so i thought it was i guess just
luck that i got in but
recently it's not like i completely
changed my mind on that but i just don't
think about it anymore
yeah but yeah i don't i don't think like
that
regardless of my skills before coming
here
i feel like after i joined with all the
effort i put into
my my activities here after i joined
like
um in my into my streams and my original
music now even
and the covers and and my projects like
holotalk and all that
i feel like everything i've done now
i've
i've done quite well and i did the best
that i could
and yeah i mean you're one of the
hardest working people i think
in the company you're always working on
stuff yeah i just work
you're always working on something
you're out of a talk show though
and i don't stream as long and as much
as you do so i think but you
and then the time that you don't use on
all that [\h__\h] that i do you use that on
music and that's amazing
okay let's say it we're both amazing
okay we both do a very good job
i think and there's always room for
improvement but i think
i think that that doesn't even need to
be said we just are we're just doing our
best and i think we're doing
pretty pretty good so yeah thank you
thank you
yep yeah i mean if you think i'm doing
good and i think you're doing good then
how can we be wrong i mean if we were to
say no no no then we're denying the
other and calling the other an idiot in
a way
and i don't think you're an idiot so
there you go yeah
i think lawless logic me i i cannot i
mean the one thing i can say is that you
definitely deserve to be in the whole
life
you got you got one you
you thank you i know we've had our
we've had our our our struggles together
in the past
right you and me and our in our battles
our many battles that have spanned
endlessly
but i'm glad that we i'm in the
beginning it was rough
but in the end i'm glad that we could
meet yeah we're
in this i'm so happy to have you
honestly there was one question i
probably didn't
pick that one up because it's uh there
were many many questions thank you guys
there was a one question that was asking
um
if if we would all like whole live
english members if we would all live in
the same place
um and we actually had the the chance to
you know hang out in real life with
everyone
if we would like have different
relationships with everyone and be
bonding more with
someone more than with another and i i i
do feel like
um i would probably be much much closer
with the other girls like
as close as with you with the other
girls
if we were all together and i wish that
would be a thing and
me too yeah so it's not like i
don't like i love the other girls but
it's just like being
being in the same place with someone in
the same country and being able to meet
that person
is something very special and i really
appreciate having that with you kelly
i feel the same way it's been fun no
don't forget about your boy when you go
back home annoy you
so much i i promise you i'll message you
and
you do that take a sit back
[Applause]
don't worry i'll never forget you how
could i
how could i honestly honestly i
um even even if we can't meet um
that much anymore we can still do a [\h__\h]
ton of like you know
collapse over you know discord
as we're doing it now that's right i
honestly i don't think there's going to
be much of a change
i think that things will pretty much
stay the same yeah a lot of people are
like oh my god so much going to change
and they're not going to collapse so
much anymore blah blah blah
most of our collabs were online anyway
yeah exactly i mean and it never
it will never stop us i don't think and
the only thing that will change is that
that you'll be in a place that you know
you feel uh
better to do things in i guess the place
where you're happier exactly
exactly you know that's just important
and takamori shippers
don't worry it will stay the same
yeah what she said i think that was the
last
two one uh that one's from the beginning
yeah okay
we're through with the questions perfect
timing um
yay we're gonna take one hour i think
one hour
right yeah one hour break i think ramen
oh go do it you want ramen yeah yeah
i don't know though maybe maybe i need
to order it i'm too far away
[Music]
we're talking about the the travel
memories
everything that we did we'll be showing
photos i have a [\h__\h] ton of photos
to show you guys and together with cali
we'll be explaining what we did on our
trip um
come and hang out with us all the spicy
details hell yeah yeah
all the things that you guys want to
know that we were doing the past week
yeah i think it will be very interesting
so
we'll see you guys in one hour on my
channel again the stream reservation is
up and the tweet is up and in this one
hour all of you
go watch wow wow wow wow wow
noise make some noise make some noise
make some noise
yeah yeah ah yeah that's actually
delirious right oh
yeah make some nice
let me link it in the chat right now
let me link it charm point
exactly
[Music]
it's a good song it doesn't sound like
that it sounds better than that it's
linked it's pinned in the comments now
so everyone go there now and i say
goodbye to you in german as usual
yes and in germany thank you sean
exactly and in germany
peace
see you guys later watch
[Music]
you