hiris it's Iris
happy holidays everyone it is currently
uh the 11th of December over here might
be the 12th for some of you guys happy
holidays we're reaching
um Midway somewhat Midway through the
holiday uh season oh I just noticed my
my halo is not uh is not
fully in in and okay there we go there
we go
okay now it looks fine uh happy holidays
what are you guys gonna be eating for
Christmas I hear that a lot of people
have this thing called
um eggnog yeah eggnog for Christmas and
I don't know that kind of sounds weird
but is eggnog good I've I've never even
had it I've never seen it in real life
before I've only heard it in like
cartoons and stuff I hear it's like
historically known for Christmas food uh
I heard usually has like alcohol in it
so maybe it's not good for kids I'm sure
there should be an alcohol a
non-alcoholic version too but I don't
know having an egg in a drink just
sounds really uh high in protein I'm I'm
assuming it tastes like like
pudding yeah like flan or something like
drinkable flan but it's also warm and it
warms you up what I drink for Christmas
by the way
if you would like to know is of course
see see lemon
has nothing to do with Christmas but
it's full of vitamin C yes and it will
keep you keep the colds away all the flu
and the clothes away from you because
with the high vitamin C and you'll be
healthy for the holiday season
yeah are you guys excited to spend the
holidays with us
yes yes
I have no idea what I'm gonna do for the
holidays except for watching school days
because that's how that's how we spend
the holidays here in Japan we we watch
school days
I can't wait anyways I hope you guys
have a great day and keep yourself warm
I feel I kind of feel like I might be
coming down in a cold and I'm very
scared for myself yes so make sure you
buy a nice warm coat uh keep yourself
tucked in in beds wear socks I keep
being told that I have to wear socks
in the winter season and but I don't
like wearing socks but you should wear
socks it's not good to you know keep
your feet cold okay okay I might sound
like a Naggy mom but you need to keep
yourself warm yeah
see you guys around virus the virus