every day
[Music]
is
baby underneath
[Music]
me
is
[Music]
keep me
baby
underneath something new
[Music]
family
don't care
[Music]
buddy
wow
i'm tired of the
[Music]
is
music
[Music]
i don't need no drinks tonight here we
go
[Music]
me
okay
[Music]
hello
hello kfb
i'll put up some music
[Music]
do we want this one
on this one
um
first this one
good morning thank you
ah i could have slept forever
oh man i had to force myself to get up
oh
[Music]
also there's literally no [\h__\h] air in
this room i feel like you know the
people who took care of my
place
did not open the windows for 10 days
straight oh my god oh
well
there's no air where the [\h__\h] is the air
no cursing excuse me what why would i
not be able to allow the curse
gradually getting smaller
yeah
yeah it's a hot as well i feel like
when i arrived it felt hotter than
where i was in america
it was my birthday yesterday but i found
out today what do you mean you found
that today
you mean wait are you not talking about
your real birthday are you talking about
your membership thing
i'm not sure
what happy birthday
[Music]
that's next level for getting your
birthday but then remembering not on the
actual day but
the following day oh i'm hungry already
oh you know what that means here
what the [\h__\h] is there a fly
inside of my
plastic packaged
uh
cut
fruits
oh it's like low-key open on one side
well now i don't want to eat this
no
should i i should probably not eat this
now
but i'm hungry
i don't know if it entered new you know
after i bought it or
before
um how you doing in there how are you
doing get it
okay
i think
when i joined
i tried to open it a bit
um it kind of
smelled funny it looks fine from the
outside but i guess i'm not eating that
that's um unfortunate
that's unfortunate
okay well i guess i'll need different
snacks later on
unfortunate can i refund nah i'm too
lazy for stuff like that
also i don't think i could get a refund
but anyway welcome everybody thank you
for
coming today
you guys missed me didn't ya
[Music]
all right
yes we managed
that sounds kind of sunday
yes yes yes
so the show um i miss you so much don't
you
know what a little bit excuse me
you're wearing other channels that
that's true that's true
and i thought you know that should be
enough but
i know
i know you know
i've seen some of you guys say oh
okiwawa should stay longer
in america
to
participate more in collabs and then
there were people that were like well
welcome back so like so you can do solo
streams again
um
which one do you want
well now i'm home am i lagging oh i'm
lagging you know um my setup is not the
usual kind right now
because i feel like i'm missing
a cable
or two
um
i
think this is always you know this
happened with uh lena too
when i came back i realized i was
missing a cable and now of course
i'm missing the cable again
too
so i can't connect my camera properly
like i usually would do it
but okay it's not that bad it's not that
bad so it's just so maybe a little bit
laggy but it's fine fine for now
so uh today i'll talk a little bit about
my trip and then announce something and
then we'll try to catch up on super
chats
and i flipped myself horizontally
because it bothered me that i was
flipped horizontally
yes you don't see my ribbon anyway so
whatever
[Music]
trip tensions yes the moment you've all
been waiting for
but can i get a snack i'm gonna cook a
snack
i'm so hungry
it's part of the jet lag
[Music]
also my nose is kind of stuffed
oh
okay i got bananas
i think my cats are trying to sabotage
me
or at least smoothie is trying to
sabotage me because she she wants more
time with me she's so clingy right now
i'm here i'm not leaving girl
okay
this
[\h__\h] is bananas b-a-n-a-n-a-s
this [\h__\h] is bananas b-a-n-a-n-a-s
okay who doesn't know this song
you're a zoomer if you don't know this
song congratulations
[Music]
oh
my nose is stuffed
have i said that i have said that
[Music]
[\h__\h] the air in this room
oh
okay
[Music]
once upon a time
went to america
but it doesn't really count because
she didn't really do anything there
[Music]
and it was very short
so we don't count that time
so once upon a time
she went to america again and we're
gonna count that as the first time
yeah
because it sounds more special i went to
makeup for the first time
[Music]
sounds more special doesn't it
more special than i went to america for
the second time yay
no let's say first time yeah that sounds
much better
[Music]
well i'll definitely win for the first
time
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
okay one second i'll get really i'll get
really deep into it once i'm done with
my banana
[Music]
i don't really have any photos for you
though this time
i think um
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know there was this one time where
we are eating
we were eating dinner the first night
and i was like
um
just for myself
just for myself i wanted a picture
for myself
obviously
of all of us
and then
you know what happened
everything but cali
basically hid under the table
so i have a picture of cali
which i already had before
i now just acquired a photo
with kelly apparently
that's
uh the only group member that i have
weird i tried to take a picture of
everyone but well maybe everyone else is
a ghost and they just don't appear on
photos such a weird thing
um
yeah everyone just hit like immediately
it was so sad
i'm so sad
at least cali joins me in photos
ma'am
kelly's always ready for it
[Music]
okay why hope he doesn't mind
taking some pictures for the memory
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my nose is opening up
it's like a store opening oh someone has
to like cut the ribbon
um
no shotgun
[Music]
i'm almost done it's a pretty big banana
grand opening yeah
my nose is back someone took my nose but
now i got it back
no
okay i'm yum
i'm done with the banana
i'm dancing with the funsies
mm-hmm
[Music]
sorry i can't breathe so well um
it's not time for kiana dot dot dot why
would free time for kiara dot dot
you know when i arrived in my apartment
the first thing i noticed and i still
smell it now in my office room
is that the whole apartment smells like
used
cat toilet
like mostly like pee peed on cat's
toilet
and it's not the toilet but it looks
like more or less clean like i don't see
any poop in it
but i wonder what they did because the
whole apartment reeks of cat uh pee i
have to like throw probably throw away
the whole sand what they probably did
was like
you know you need a little bit of a
technique when you clean a litter box
you need to understand the sand
that's being used
and then adjust appropriately like i'm
actually being honest uh serious at this
no my kids don't pee anywhere like no no
besides the toilet but
yeah they probably just like you know
those those little brock brock's brox
and that is very german because we say
broken it's probably not english how do
how would i say those chunks those
chunks of
uh
was
hard
uh sand they probably just poked into it
and then it fell apart and then they
didn't properly get rid of it
um
i had a couple of friends take care of
my cats while i was
gone thankfully
yeah my cats are still alive
on the sound of music
yeah thankfully at least they're alive
but i gotta throw away the whole sand
afterwards something went wrong there
um
[Music]
speaking of bra
i met bales now this was kind of at the
end of my story
and a brand new story one wish it's kind
of at the end of my story i i kind of
want to start chronologically
but i feel like we're not even going to
get to the end of my story
um
but yeah i guess i'm going to i'm going
to yeah say it so
originally the plan was only to meet um
the myth members
but then both fauna and bales
individually
uh spontaneously decided to you know say
hi
not on the same day it was separate days
but
um i'm very happy that i got the
opportunity to meet um
two more
of her live english because i think
if that wouldn't have happened uh i
probably wouldn't have seen him like
until a long long long long time later
especially bae
because
you know she's normally in australia
right so
that was a great chance that normally
would not come so easily
um
fake real australia
yeah i'm from austria
no from australia
i'm from austria
so beijing
told bales that i watched this whole
long what like 30 minutes 40 minutes
video
on why
australia can't be
inhabited
more than it currently is being
inhabited even though there's like
only being um five percent or so of the
land being actually used it was really
interesting
um
really really really deep inside that's
on my watch list
you probably gotta recommend it because
i watched it i watched that too there
you go
and then i went on a little bit of a
spring and watched like some other
videos like why why england has
so many airports or no why london has so
many airports
yeah all kinds of videos
i don't know which channel it was
[Music]
okay
it might have been that channel yeah
it might have been
it was really interesting
australia is kind of
[\h__\h] man because you can't use all
that land
[\h__\h]
so weird
anyway
would you like want to live any other
probably not i want to live in if i have
a choice i want i want to live at the
beach
yeah
desserts everywhere yummy hopefully with
vanilla ice cream
okay shut up i'm done see what the funsy
i will now tell you a bit about my trip
because that's what you guys are here
for aren't ya
why are you guys just here to see me of
course you are
of course you are
[Music]
so i think i can say
this
at least because you know it's my first
trip so i want to give at least some
details and i think i can say this
uh
i've been to
[Music]
los angeles
angeles los angeles
[Music]
yes oh
such a
relatively cool city
[Laughter]
for the way of saying
something good about something ah
that's not how you say it i know i know
but every time i see the signs i read
los angeles los angeles do you not even
say it when you speak like spanish
you would say los angeles no
[Music]
because there's only what does that even
mean what does it los angeles even mean
los angeles
is it no
it's pronounced with an h sound
los angeles
the angels
wow city of angels oh that's no surprise
that we met there then
angels okay
i guess yeah it's similar a similar word
kanata city
relatively cool
nobody and no all right okay so the
thing is i didn't
see
much
of los angeles
in the end i didn't see that much even
though i kind of want to see him a
little more but like when i told my
um
my friend
[Music]
when i told my friend that i
was gonna go to los angeles
uh
she told me to
not
under any circumstances
go outside alone
especially not at night but even
you know not
even during the daytime
i i you know i booked
in some time sometimes i booked i stayed
with you know the girls and sometimes i
stayed alone but when i was staying
somewhere alone i was staying in a
downtown
downtown l.a when i booked a hotel i was
like not sure like which area would be
good
um but downtown sounded like it it would
be like
i don't know downtown sounds so cool
so i thought that would be close to you
know where some interesting things are
but apparently downtown was not the best
choice
but i haven't really like seen
anything in particular
okay that's a lie
that looked dangerous that's a lie
that's a lie it did look dangerous
sometimes
i did see
a lot of police
uh and a lot of yes people who don't
have a home they even walked into the
hotel
uh into the lobby and then the
the
hotel bodyguards aka concierges they
kicked them out they were like no no no
not in here
go outside and i was like oh dear oopsie
doodles
um
yeah oh my god the lag holy [\h__\h] my god
be good kiwa be good glad you made it
out of l.a alive no i didn't think it
was that that that dangerous
i mean
they're just people too
so
i don't see how that that itself is
dangerous but i did hear
stories of people being attacked from
them i guess but
that doesn't apply to everybody i don't
know but at least nothing happened to me
because like
uh on the days when i was not with um
the myth girls i was with a friend who
has a car and drives like a maniac so
she kind of adds to the whole
uh la traffic
very nicely
but at least she drives therefore she
drove me everywhere
and
yeah
she drives like a maniac she's so funny
when she drives
oh man and she has these really long ass
nails i don't even know how you drive
like that
uh no i didn't stay for any of my expo
you know um
i think when i originally planned the
trip
[Music]
i think
i may have been aware of ax happening
soon after
but
i think
i didn't want to stay because i think my
stay was like 10 to 11 days
i think 11 i think
um so
i was like you know that's already a lot
of time where i can't do normal content
um especially considering those days
where i was recording i was really busy
and so partially you know just because i
thought i shouldn't be away too long
um
you know
for normal i wanted to do normal content
and originally the plan
was just to go there for recording not
necessarily for an awful lot but then
everything came together like that so
yeah
um but
no no no not kelly my friend my friend
i didn't kelly didn't drive me anywhere
no no no
um
oh what was i gonna say
oh i forgot oh yeah yeah and then you
know afterwards i kind of regretted uh
nothing longer for ax because i thought
i guess at least
experiencing it once would have been
interesting
such a huge convention that i've heard
about so often
but you know
kiwa with the orange hair and the
feathers in her hair in her ears
stands out very much and
i think
i i would have been very nervous and
scared and i don't know you know i don't
know
i don't know it doesn't sound
too safe to go there also i didn't
really have any friends to go i
obviously wouldn't be able to go with
the myth girls because
i
just stand out too much
and i would put them in danger if i had
any other friends that i know that i
knew that would be going there
beforehand
then maybe i would have thought about it
if i had someone to go with you know
um
but you know not really having anyone
and not being able to go with the myth
girls basically just like
i i i wouldn't want to go through that
experience alone
sounds scary overwhelming i heard that
it's like really [\h__\h] busy so
yeah
but maybe one day one day i want to
check it out either ax or any other
uh american big convention
uh i might want to check it out one day
maybe not this year maybe another year
[Music]
but i did see the convention hall from
outside when i was driving by with a car
uh i wasn't driving with someone else my
friend was driving
and i saw that big big big big
[Music]
what's it like not not a poster but this
big advertisement on the building
so be
oh yeah anime expo
um
well whole life will have a booth at
anime expo so if you're going to ax
check out the booth
billboard a banner yeah it was a huge
banner
so bing
hmm
billboard i guess mm-hmm
so anyway you are you guys already know
the story
of
me at the airport
mia diaper yes yes
so i'm not gonna tell that story again
um but you know some people
you guys criticized me for saying
anything in the first place and i was
like yo but i have to tell them
and you were like no no but yes i have
to tell them
maybe if i was american then i could
have been like none of your business
dude but as a foreigner entering they
have the right to
not let me in
if i'm suspicious if i say no i don't
want to tell you
that might that that is my choice but it
also gives me
this suspicious look
that
yeah they would want to question me more
and more and more like why is this lady
not telling me everything the way it is
and then they have the right to reject
me from entering the country which would
have been very troublesome so and they
are you know a foreign authority so i
have to tell them
i have to i looked it up
so it is how it is i have to tell them
and also i think you guys were saying uh
tsa but it wasn't t-s-a uh what was it
called b
border
border something
border border control patrol
border control patrol something like
that border
board or something yeah ah cbp or so
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
uh can i just say one thing
from the end today like oh my god
i flew um
unfortunately i didn't have a direct
flight back so
i have to i had to go for [\h__\h]
chicago airport
uh
and i asked i asked the girls how is
chicago airport like and they were like
oh it's really big and it's nice
and i [\h__\h] regret it
because i did have
not much time
for
changing and i had to go
basically from one side of the airport
to the other and i had to
i had like i think i had like 40 minutes
or so
and i had to go from like terminal one
to terminal
wherever
and so [\h__\h] far away i had to only
first of all you know i was i was
following the signs that said um
terminal one two three four five etc
and at some point
the terminal i was going to
disappeared from the signs even though i
was just normally following them first
of all that's confusing
and then i asked a guy thankfully i
found a help guy a really nice one but
he was so up into my face relatively old
guy really nice but like when i was
talking to him he got so close to me i'm
like why is this dude talking so closely
to me it's not like he's whispering into
my ear he's basically at the distance
where you would whisper to someone but
he's talking loudly so
[Music]
that was weird but he was like really
sweet he was like
oh my dear my dear it's all okay calm
down so you gotta do this okay
there's this uh airport transfer thingy
that has a really fancy name but it's
really not that fancy so you have to go
out here and then and then you gotta go
and stay on this level
and i didn't have to stay on the level
what the [\h__\h] i ended up not staying on
the level but anyway i made it
relatively fast to that thing i had to
exit
i had to exit the the maybe he can't
hear but he's talking to me i'm i wasn't
even saying anything
he did he did 90 of the talking
anyway he was nice though uh close
talker yeah yeah he's close talker
um but i had to exit
once which
is the most obnoxious thing when you're
doing transit and makes me think that
this airport was not planned very well
and that is apparently america's biggest
airport
if it requires you
to leave the airport once
completely
then you're doing something wrong
with the planning and creation of the
airport what the [\h__\h]
yeah so you know
the biggest airports have like dubai for
example
they have like uh trains
inside the airport that bring you from
terminal to terminal really fast
this is one thing i'll
one good thing i'll say about the dubai
airport i don't like big airports but it
you know it's it has trains inside
i think i think uh
the one in paris should have that too if
i remember correctly
[Music]
or any kind of other you know
transportation
whatever so
they don't have that i had to leave once
which means i had to go for the whole
security
uh and passport check again
and that took some time
and i was really stressed because
i saw that my boarding was about to
start in like 10 minutes or so at the
moment where i finally uh
like lined up at the
passport and security control uh
and
in front of me i saw this huge line
and i'm like
oh [\h__\h] hell mate
[\h__\h] helmet
what am i gonna do i'm not gonna make it
but
it moved it ended up moving relatively
fast so
i made it in time for the boarding
but this is now this is this is
something that pisses me off so much
when i travel
i run and i run and i run and i was
already like my legs were [\h__\h]
killing me i don't know i have really
really really really
stiff muscles right now in my calves
um
because i guess because of all the
dancing and traveling i don't know
um
so i was i was holy [\h__\h] i was suffering
when i was on my way to get there in
time
carrying my [\h__\h] insanely heavy
alienware laptop
so i finally arrived and then
i'm like oh [\h__\h] thank god i made it
huffing puffing huffing puffing
and then they made me wait
another like 40 minutes or something
[Music]
it wasn't even delayed they just started
uh um
boarding so [\h__\h] late and i'm like
why
why did i stress myself out so much
every [\h__\h] time i hate when that
happens
[Music]
oh
the doctor's office paradox exactly
you can't be late in five minutes but
they make you wait an hour uh-huh
uh-huh
yeah
but then the rest of the flight was fine
and
i think i know it wasn't fine
it was not [\h__\h] fine
when i booked my flights
i
uh
i did myself a favor and for the first
time did in my life did not book economy
but i also didn't book business because
i thought that's too expensive
it is too [\h__\h] expensive
so i booked a premium economy
yeah
um
which is at least a little bit of an
upgrade
still expensive though
and yeah about premium economy
and i i remember very clearly choosing
window seats
and then when they sent me the email for
online check-in both on my way going
there and on my way going back
um
[Music]
i couldn't do one one second it just
didn't work somehow
so
what happened i lost my window seats
[Music]
on my way to america i fixed it somehow
because i i had relatively enough time
to
um go to the counter and be like yo
uh
where is my window state
so
the lady um tried her best getting me a
window stitch in the end she gave me a
seat that was like blocked for some
reason uh but she said go go there
anyway it might be broken but
i don't know why it's blocked so just go
go ahead and use it if it's free and
yeah so i did get a window seat that way
but then on my way back i didn't get a
window seat so i didn't sleep that well
um
but it was okay uh it was okay
my legs what is it though when like
you're if every flight no matter how
long or how short
i
up up until
from the bottom of my feet up until
right above the knees
i'm constantly in pain
what is that
i mean i know i have like some body
issues
and chronic pain
but why does that always happen to me
when i fly is that the
yeah i was wondering if compression
socks would help
i wonder
poor circulation air pressure um
must be something like that because it
only happens to me when i fly and it
doesn't matter if it's a short or a long
flight no no it doesn't matter if i sat
for a long period it starts immediately
the moment i sit in the airplane and it
takes off
and it's at a certain certain
altitude
it already
hurts
[Music]
even if i've just sat for like half an
hour or an hour
and even if i walk around a little bit
and sit back down
[Music]
do you guys not have that
does anyone else have that
same problem
um air pressure so do the socks sample
them the compression socks i wanted to
buy them but in both of my flights i
didn't have time to check it out in the
store
all altitude allergy is that a thing
yes but with my ears
air pressure make can make your joints
hurt
compression socks do help with it it
doesn't happen right away but yes it
does happen to me
never experienced that ah
i'm jealous good for you
[Music]
i just got um out by all this yeah
why did i start reading that
uh
how many songs did you record you will
see soon next week oh my god next week
is my
birthday what
what that's so soon
next week
i realized oh my god
it's not
it's
it's a week or not even a week away
so i have uh
i guess i'll i'll announce it now this
thing i'll show you um i decided on the
times because genma was like girl you
need to decide the times
quickly please i'm like okay
sorry
uh okay
so here it is
[Music]
nice image right the
chihuahua on the left beautiful cool
although the weapons will not make uh an
entrance in the uh concert
because i'm not fighting anyone um but
yeah uh psd 9am sorry it's early i it
was really hard to choose a time it was
really hard because i want the japanese
fans and everybody korean fans i wanted
them to watch too
um est 12 p.m
i mean it is my my usual streaming time
so gmt 4 pm
uh i think what time is like uh
6 p.m i think
jason
1am
that's 1am guys
[Music]
foreign
and because this is not um
like produced by the company but more
like self-produced
um i have the
permission to go on longer than an hour
so
uh
it might be longer than an hour a little
bit i know
it
[Music]
we recorded it with the
plan of it being an hour but then some
parts the mc parts
ended up being pretty long and i thought
you know cutting it would be kind of
weird uh don't know where where to cut
it so yeah it will be uh probably a
little bit longer
not too much but a little bit um
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
not so much my fault
you know
that's just how it goes we had fun
we had fun
i had fun
ah
yeah
i'm so excited i've seen some previews
um and it's been looking pretty pretty
pretty damn good
um
no total
[Music]
so i think i can say this
or maybe i should wait until afterwards
i'm not sure does it matter
i guess i'll say and i guess i'll say
um
so i recorded everything
uh
my body movements and my singing and all
that obviously
um
but you know
for
reasons
[Music]
several reasons
um
the original plan of having the company
put it together into a concert
failed
so
i
couldn't think of anyone else to
make it happen than kanna ubu
so kana ubu
is putting it all together into a
concert
yeah yeah um this time not music video
but a concert
yeah
so kind of uvu is creating the whole
stage
and camera work and stitching together
the data of me dancing
everything
which
is nice but um see i had to sacrifice
something for that uh i'll tell you
this now because i think i originally
told you that i want to do it and now
you might be wondering when you watch
the concert where it is
so let me tell you there will be no new
song performed during the concert no new
original song
i originally planned it
but
um
you know the thing is i wanted the music
video for that to be made by kana oovoo
as well
and then
when like after i decided that we like
figured oh [\h__\h] i i need to ask someone
else to make my concert into a concert
uh and then we asked kanaluvu and
obviously like that's too much of a
workload so i had to sacrifice my song
um i'm still aiming for it to be like
out sometime at the end of july or so
but yeah currently i don't know
their song is like created but um
i need more time
yeah a bit unfortunate
um but i'll get it out there soon enough
and we'll make a cool music video out of
it
uh in 3d because i want this one to be
in 3d um
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah will there be angling no
that won't be angling because i'm
keeping the egg laying for my 3d debut
this is not a pretty debut although
there will be already a lot of
showcasing of my 3d
um
in relatively good quality i think
but yeah
it's not a pretty debut
yeah
it's something else
no no no this is not afraid
yeah yeah it's just the way that you
know things are
ended up being chrono
chronologically
we will still do a 3d debut
in japan
eventually once we all are able to go to
japan
then we will do a proper 3d debut
in the whole life studio
yeah
so that's at least something to look
forward to but i mean i guess it doesn't
really
make much sense anymore at that point
[Music]
that's why i want didn't want to use my
3d for so long i wanted to wait until
the 3dw
but then it got delayed so often that my
birthday came first and i'm like i'm not
going to miss out on another birthday
that i want to do in 3d so here we are
this is coming first
and
yeah and then actually
um on the previous day
uh
not exactly 24 hours before but like
20 let me see wait a second i wrote it
down
i think it was
28.
so the concert is on the 6th of july
uh
at
let's just use eastern time uh 12 p.m
but the
collins
including
certain birthday merchandise
announcements
will be made
in the separate stream
uh
the kind of a countdown but it's not
even a countdown because it's at 4 pm my
time uh 10 a.m eastern time on the 5th
of july
why
so early i want to do it later but why
so early because if i would do it as a
countdown in my time zone then japanese
members would have a hard time calling
in
they would have a hard time calling in
is what genma told me so i was like uh
you're right
so we're just gonna act
as if it's a countdown it's a countdown
tour
for japanese time zone because it starts
at 11 pm
right
yeah it will be a countdown in some time
zone um
in japanese time zone i guess it would
be a countdown
yeah
do you need them to call in well i want
them to you know if they want to count
uh call in i don't want them to be
effing tired and forcing themselves to
wake up and like open their eyes at 4 00
am
even though some of them might still be
awake still
anyways
uh so
[Music]
this is exciting i'll put this up on on
twitter later
um
and now let me tell you a few more
stories and then i have another
announcement afterwards
i'll tell you some more stories
prime gaming time hell yeah 4am
it would be probably
awake with no problem
but wait there's more yeah
[Music]
where did i stop um
what did what was the last thing i
talked about
i wonder
do you guys remember what was the last
thing i talked about in the last
uh solo stream
[Music]
i told you guys the airport story was
that all i told you
no i mean in the previous in the
previous stream
[Music]
i i did tell you about gura amena
meeting them
holy [\h__\h] there's i have i have so many
notes and they're like
just paragraphs and paragraphs
pretty set up ah i did tell you about
the 3d setup um that it was a pain in
the ass and that it was delayed and all
that yeah yeah yeah yeah
so
or we i repeat originally we had like
three days
that were planned for recording
um because the day before the equipment
was supposed to arrive but then it was
delayed and then some something was
missing that's just a quick recap
so effectively we only had one day of
recording
which was big suffering big big
okay so
woke up inaudible
um went to ami's place
um okay did i tell you about going to
amma's place
i met first thing first thing uh
i did is
obviously give her the double hug the
big big big double hug i charged at her
gave her a big hug i was so happy and
then pyongyang i jumped around and i
gave her another hug
so happy to see emma i love her i love
her i love it so much i will say this
because apparently some people need this
to be extra clear i love her as a friend
but oh my god i love her so much
i feel like out of all of the
um
members like we all you know had a good
time i think but i feel like i bonded
the most with
um
ame
you know
i
[Music]
love me
i love her
[Music]
on the first day
so she gave us a tour of her place and
we met we met her pets oh my god
her
her doggies were obviously very very
um
active and
they always were running after emma that
was that was cute
uh you may have heard that i was not the
biggest fan of bubba
you know i i don't
hate dogs
but i if anything i like like bigger
dogs big fluffy dogs and bubba was
small and
i don't like small dogs so much
i i did give him some pets but always
very reluctantly reluctantly
um
that's yeah
i'm sorry but hey he got he got a lot of
love from
you know ina gouda
[Music]
and fauna
so
yeah yeah he didn't need me i gave all
the love to henry
and i keep on forgetting the name of the
other cat but
yeah the other cat
on the first day i didn't see
him once
at wellington yeah
i didn't see him at all he kept on
hiding
um then on the second day oh man
ah
on the second day
[Music]
i shouldn't say this
on this well at least on the second day
i met uh wellington
at some point and
um you know wellington is like when you
move a little bit he will run away
and hide such a scary cat such a chicken
yeah but but but but
we were like at some point we were like
chilling in the living room
and he finally he was like hiding behind
the tv
and he just didn't didn't get out for
hours
and then finally at some point
he came out from behind the tv and i'm
like oh [\h__\h] i'm i'm i'm i look
and she's like okay be quiet don't move
so he came uh closer to us she he walked
he walked up to me
and i'm like oh [\h__\h] what do i do what
did i want to scare him
i mean it was like reach out your hand
and he will like headbutt it so i
reached out my hand
trying to not not move or make any loud
noises
and then he started aggressively
head-butting me
so much she kept them like
i've never seen a cat headbutt that
aggressively before that fast he would
go like
against my hands so fast from one side
to another turn around
like a car like he's a race car
yeah so cute
and it was really silky really silky so
so soft yeah
very soft but yeah then then after
a while like someone would make a noise
and he would run away again
ah
poor baby no need to be scared um
no
[Music]
ah
oh yeah it was like
one time when inna was like
um
uh horizontally laying on on the sofa uh
and then when wellington was out amen
was like oh you need to put this blanket
on top of yourself
and then you know pet pat pat your
stomach or something and then he will
come and lay on top of you
and when i heard that i was like i wish
i was inna right now
i wish
so she tries it and he's like
on his way to sit on inna
he was about to like
climb on top of her
insert dominance and then somebody or i
think it was even ina made some movement
or some noise and then he ran away again
she was so close to greatness
so close
i wish that was me man i would have
stayed as still as a log
so that i could acquire
the cat laying on top of me because my
cats don't do that
and i wish my cats would do that
i would want them to lay on top of me
all day
even though then you can't really move
i wish they would do that though yeah so
um
oh yeah we we we did record i don't know
if i said but we did record one thing on
the first day
with
the
loki scuffed um
equipment that we had that we used for
the arm wrestling stream
so you may notice
a tiny bit of quality difference
from 1mc
compared to everything else in the
concert because just one mc is recorded
with something else
at least i wasn't dancing so i'm hoping
it won't stand out too much
uh
but that one thing now you if you see it
you may understand why it's so scuffed a
little a little bit scuffed just a
little bit
because i had that scheduled i had this
recording scheduled thinking that the
setup would be done and i couldn't move
it because the the
person who would join me in the mc
had a tight schedule
yeah so there will be some call-ins
during the during the concert yeah and
then we recorded that and i i was like
[\h__\h] we have to record it but we don't
have anything set up and then ahmed
quickly
uh got me into the suit in like 30
minutes everything's set up
wow they in 30 minutes they got me into
the suit took my measurements
yeah uh ina was taking the measurements
took my measurements yeah with the
with the ruler
she went around my wrist and my coughs
and all that
yeah actually i thought she would take
three sizes but it didn't even need
three sizes so so she doesn't have my
free size yeah
just some other weird measurements like
my my shoulder length with and my arm
length and all that
those are not
really
any interesting measurements not really
lewd or anything
but yeah we tried really really really
quickly to get everything done quickly
um
as fast as possible
and then we ended the call
thankfully and
thankfully we made it somewhat in time
and made it safely i thought of a few
games
to do in the mcs
um
one of them
i completely made up
in my brain
and i'm proud of it
[Music]
but yeah uh
you will see
so
and we recorded that
oh yeah might because i was waiting so
long for the equipment to arrive i was
like on the side i was like practicing
my songs that i wasn't too
too
confident in yet choreography wise and
it was freaking hot so
by the time i needed to get into the
suit my t-shirt was already so drenched
so i borrowed one of ana's t-shirts
i bought one of her t-shirts and then i
got into her suit
yeah and then um
uh later later we brainstormed some
ideas for off collabs uh i did that
tweet asking you guys and you guys gave
us some good ideas
um
i feel like basically
pretty sure this is correct
all of the collab
collab ideas that we did
came from
uh
hello lag
[Music]
there she goes
she's gone
did you hear me still
you still hear me right
[Music]
yeah it's because i i'm doing it
differently than usual
nanny the [\h__\h]
oh my god let me restart this
oh
oh come on it's installing an update now
[Music]
there we go are you [\h__\h] kidding me
this timing
okay
well
amazing we have an updated version then
[Music]
why is it doing this
why is it doing this um let me restart
this
too
[Music]
now i'll be back soon
this and this
[Music]
there we go
here i am
here i am once again i turn into pieces
can't deny it can't pretend i thought
you were the one
broken up deep inside you wouldn't see
the tears
okay everything back to normal more or
less
thank you tadama um
[Music]
where did that meal come from what the
[\h__\h]
i'm not done streaming even though i
didn't talk so much
that was a sign because i got kind of
quiet it was a sign for her that i'm
done streaming i'm not
i'm not downstream
[Music]
hi
hello
hello baby
[Laughter]
sorry i got my my cats visiting me
ah indian you need to meet my cats holy
[\h__\h] though smoothie is
losing insane amounts of hair right now
oh my god it's summertime
it's summertime
she said meow
inia sent meow no surprise because i i
always call her inya these days so she's
obviously a cat but i didn't i didn't
tell any of this but i thought of a new
nickname for inya
um i thought it was genius
i have a new nickname for you inya but
i'm not ready to use it yet because
i'm still very much into calling you
inya
i figured
i
have a new name for you it's nina
because ninomaya the n plus ina is nina
it's such a pretty cute name isn't it
nina
actually in in german
language
it's a very common name
nina
yeah but it's currently i'm still very
much into inya
so
not i'm not gonna use it yet
nina hey nina
[Music]
that's so hard to say
is that in indian leave already was she
really here you guys said hi but was she
really here
[Music]
okay so back to my stories
she was oh okay
i was gonna say like basically the ideas
for
pretty much all of the collabs came from
my twitter replies and me
like the pop-tart no the pop-up thing
was a spontaneous idea i had when i was
in walmart
and then
uh
super smash brothers
was partially twitter partially me
because i was like um
this is
this could be fun and then what else did
we do wait what did we do on the
previous day
what did we do before smash
[Music]
what
did we do a stream before smash
on the previous day
no that was pop-tarts okay ah
[Music]
i thought we had another one now we
wanted to do another one i guess and the
the arm wrestling thing we wanted to do
already earlier
but
we didn't have time because then we were
recording all day but thankfully
uh at least by doing it later we were
able to do it with all the girls
together
yeah and the arm wrestling was also
like somewhat requested we suggested
from the twit twitter replies and
partially by me because i saw
oh yeah they just said arm wrestling and
i when i saw that i was like wait a
second i remember seeing
amen doing that thing where she was half
life today and half 3d
so it would be so funny to see
that
with us doing arm wrestling but we ended
up just doing full 3d because
i guess it was somewhat easier actually
but changing the suits because we only
had two
changing the suits in between you know
it takes a lot of like calibration and
[\h__\h] um
and it takes some time so it was kind of
scuffed but at least we got it done it
was fun i'm glad we did it because that
was a very original idea
[Music]
uh
yeah
my show that was very funny um but i
have to say i watched back a little bit
on it
um the part where i was like you know
dancing a little bit
it's not very accurate
i was like dancing way more intensely
like really popping out my chest and all
that
so
yeah
it really um holds back a lot of the
movement
i've noticed
by about
it makes it eighty percent
less movement somehow i feel like
nerfing it a lot damn
you missed that yeah i did some really
intense dancing
[Music]
you had an idea of what i was actually
doing
and then what the [\h__\h] is up with my
butt
[Music]
i saw that screenshot
where
like
that part on top of my skirt above
looks like a butt crack
and then the butt itself is just so flat
that is
not
not so accurate
oh well
[Laughter]
ah it was funny though yeah
anyway so we brainstormed but we didn't
stream on that day so then um
tuesday
wait
oh no that was
tuesday what the [\h__\h] i feel like i got
some things mixed up here isn't it
wednesday
i don't know anymore yeah on one day on
the day when we streamed
we had some yummy thai food
um very tired at the end of the day very
very very tired
we always stayed like super long
and amazed play super super super long
and got
got uh two hours uh our place very very
late like originally i could have like
stayed with um ahmed but then you know
when ina and gouda decided to join
um it was like
okay maybe there's a little bit too many
people to stay
so we should get our own place so we did
get our own place for
the time being uh
me gooda and ina
stayed in
an airbnb
for a few days
and then we separated went our own ways
for a little while and then we got back
together again
yeah
all
all together uh
all myth members
so
yeah that's why i did the the solo
stream there
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah cause like some of the girls wanted
to do their own thing
um
for a few days which is totally fine
yeah yeah okay so let me see um first oh
yeah
did i tell you that like me and ina went
on this hall i think i did scavenger
hunt of finding
some cables that were missing
uh that was a long long long trip
of finding the right things and the
right amount because we needed so many
i didn't tell you
that was so stressful like because when
the uh i think it was like one day we
waited
yeah one day we waited the whole day for
the equipment and didn't come
and then the second day
uh
[Music]
i think yeah the second day we went in
another like almost the whole day but
then it arrived and we thought we could
use it
but then something was missing when we
were setting it up
but it was already late so we couldn't
get anything so
what we did was
on the third day i felt i was so
worried that it wouldn't work out on the
third day which was the last day i could
possibly record something
we
me and ina first before we set out to
ammon's place we went out to get all
these things that were missing
hoping that they would work
then we went to ahmed then we set up
everything
took us quite some time but then finally
we could record
i might be missing mixing up some things
here but in the end you know i only had
one day to record so that's that
[Music]
and then and then and then and then
i told this
i'm gonna take measurements
so one day inna was taking my
measurements but on the other day
for the different equipment we needed
different uh measurements and all that
so amy took my measurements
and then ina was putting you know some
balls on on me
yeah and then they tried like taping my
fingers
uh and and toes
and then
put balls on there too
yeah
and i'm gonna touch basically every body
part of me
[Music]
yeah but they were very gentle
and very efficient
emma wanted to make like pancakes for
lunch i told you this that i regretted
not getting the pancakes because
like
we were so busy setting everything up
and did not have time to take a break
that lunch turned into dinner and then
it was so [\h__\h] late that
you know we were like maybe we should
eat something proper
yeah so no i'm in pancakes
kind of sad
[Music]
i wanted to
get my pancakes she kept on the polishes
yeah how did you know did she say
every time she would like you know touch
me she apologized
i'm like
i know you're just doing your job
or not even your job you're just you
know
trying to get this done but she's so
apologetic she keeps on apologizing for
for you know i'm i know you're touching
me for the reason of putting balls on me
i know
touch sorry touch sorry yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
i don't know why she feels the need to
say sorry it's all good
[Music]
um
yeah so
the day when we set everything up it was
mostly like amen inna
uh big braining the whole thing putting
it all together
yeah
oh and i did i brought everyone
souvenirs by the way i brought everyone
uh austrian
mozart balls chocolate
and
they really really really liked it
i was surprised because i didn't like it
much
but it's a really famous souvenir from
austria so
i got them those balls
and they all liked it yeah
i got the ones that are in a really
fancy violin packaging
and i was
i was doing some funsies i was trying to
be funny when they opened it up in front
of my eyes
i was like
what
why is there no violent in there it was
a violent packaging so i thought there
would be a violent in there absolutely
bamboozled betrayed oh my god the lies
false advertisement
but they didn't laugh for me
[Laughter]
they
they didn't laugh at all
i guess i'm dancing with the funsies i'm
danny with the funny it was danny with
the funny right why am i making it into
dances with the funsies
um
anyway on on uh on thursday
uh ina wasn't there so um we thought oh
oh dear we have to do it only with ahmed
kurani
but
then
fana joined as you know and i didn't
talk too much about meeting fauna but
here you go i will talk about it now
let me put some water
yeah the whole final thing was i think
pretty spontaneous like i didn't even
know she was like actually gonna come
until we met up on that day
i was very yeah
oh my god this movie's on the floor and
and um chunkers is crying in the
distance these girls
so cute
i'm sorry so um
i didn't know that she was gonna be
there so i didn't do my makeup and
then when i saw her i was like [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
the first time she sees me and i look
like this oh [\h__\h] so i was really shy i
didn't want to like look at her too much
because she would see my face
you guys don't understand
for for girls it's like
ah
embarrassing
at least like if you have like some
complex complex complexes
some i'm i'm not so
confident in my face
so yeah i was embarrassed
um
but she was very sweet she was
um she was very um
had to say
she was
she had her makeup on and she was
dressed cutely she did her hair cutely
i was i was
kind of um
fascinated because
the way she did her hair
was
a hairstyle that i used to do all the
time when i was younger
i'm not gonna say what kind of hairstyle
exactly it was but i was like
you know the way you have your hair
right now i did it like that all the
time when i was younger it's so cute
yeah
yeah yeah and a mohawk exactly
and then there was one thing
that i was absolutely shocked about but
later on realized
it might be more or less normal for
america americans
so
i need an explanation from you guys
i um
since it was my first time
uh in america
i
did not have much experience with
american money right
and you guys have like dollar bills even
for the one dollars right that's that's
pretty cool
because for money exchanging purposes uh
they usually don't take coins they only
take um
um the paper money so that is actually
useful that you have one dollar bills
because you can change it even when it's
pretty small but anyway that's not the
thing i want to say so
[Music]
but you guys still do have coins
and
when i looked at them i was like
like for example at a cash cashier
at a cashier
i
um wanted to give him like a more or
less exact
uh payment
so i i looked at the coins and i'm like
i don't know what the [\h__\h] these coins
are
what do i do with these coins like what
what even is a quarter what does it look
like and i was getting stressed out
yeah so a father was next to me and i
was like hey yo
help
and then
she didn't [\h__\h] know
the coins she was like struggling
everybody was i asked good at too and
then she was struggling too and then
later we sat down and i pulled out all
the coins and i was like well what is
this coin what is this coin and what is
this coin and they were like
i don't know what is this
this this uh this maybe is a 50 cent and
then later it turned out it wasn't a 50
cent it was just something else
and then she got it all mixed up and i
didn't [\h__\h] know what it was
and i'm like it i mean i understand that
i didn't know because it was the first
time i was seeing these coins
no they were not trolling i swear to god
they they they don't know freaking no
coins and i'm like why don't they know
the coins is this normal
maybe because you guys even have dollar
bills up to one
dollar and
i guess
then you barely use coins but don't you
sometimes have to use your coins
sometimes
and then
every now and then at cash cashiers i i
wanted to give them my coins so i
wouldn't have too much
uh when i would leave america so
sometimes i would like open my wallet
and i would be like sorry i'm not from
here could you help me like find
like the right coins just take take
whatever
you need to get this to the exact amount
or whatever
and they
i don't know what the problem was
maybe they were hesitating because they
were confused
but like
they wouldn't really help me
so i would take out the coins and i
would put
every single coin i had in my wallet i
would put it down on the red register on
the on the table thingy and i would be
like is this enough is this enough what
is this does this work
and they would just like silently
like stare at the coins and do nothing
i'm
i'm so i'm so confused
and i was getting more and more nervous
and embarrassed and stressed out because
someone would stand next to me or behind
me
uh like waiting to be next and i was
just trying
and then i ended up giving them twenty
dollar bills because they just wouldn't
help me get the right coins
maybe they also didn't know what coins
oh what
they weren't doing anything
oh
[Music]
and that wasn't even the only occasion
later on i remember asking like other
members
or who who did i ask but i asked other
people too to like help me with the
coins and they
they couldn't
and i was like maybe it's a thing for
younger people
maybe the younger people don't know
coins
why would you not know coins like
if you pay in cash you eventually will
get coins back
right
[Music]
i'm so confused
i'm so confused man
uh now now i still have some coins in my
wallet because i didn't really get to
use them much no i didn't mix it with
euros no no no no
but then
one more weird thing was like i was at a
cashier
and and i was trying to pay with coins
and you know i've only been in america
during that time i've never been to
canada before yet
when i pulled out all these coins
one of
the cashier was like one of these
this this one is a canadian one and i'm
like
how is that possible
[Music]
how
how would that even be possible
because i've only been to america that
means someone else
some other cashier must have given me a
canadian coin then
[Laughter]
what
someone slipped me in the
canadian coin it happens it's similar
they looked very similar yeah i guess i
didn't pay attention yeah
how did you mess no it wasn't me messing
up they gave me the wrong change
no it was only one though that was not
the reason why they were all so confused
it was only one out of like 20 coins
that that was maybe maybe canadian
ah they mixed up
very similar exchange rate is closed oh
oh
oh well okay so that was that funner
fana did not know how to deal with coins
i was so shocked i was like
is this normal
and then at some point uh
i had this really embarrassing moment
just right after meeting fauna
you know i wanted to
look cool
and leave a good impression
like a senpai impression and then like
we we took a public transport so i buy a
ticket
and
then
i'm like about to use it
and between buying it and using it there
was like
maybe
three to five minutes
in between
and i i go through my bag in my wallet
and i just can't find it and i start
panicking because they were already you
know passed using the
the ticket
and
it was about to leave
soon
very soon and i started panicking and
then and then i was like oh [\h__\h] i have
to buy a new one
how did i lose it in that five minutes i
didn't even walk that far
and then i had to buy another one so i
went to the ticket counter thingy and
but that one only took a card and i
tried my austrian card but my [\h__\h]
austrian card i'm so mad because it
sometimes worked in america and
sometimes it didn't work and this was a
case where it didn't work and like guna
and fauna were like watching me from
afar
and i'm like come on for me wait for me
i was panicking and i was getting so
nervous and
sweating
so i was like
please help so good i gave me her card
to buy the ticket
and then i get the ticket and i finally
get through and i'm like [\h__\h] this is so
embarrassing i wonder what fauna is
thinking about me now like oh damn this
girl is not cool at all
oh
fauna i'm really cool
this has got me in the right in the
wrong moment man
that was a big panic moment
yeah
thank you gouda for helping me
i gave gooda back the money immediately
in cash
in dollar bills not coins
because no one understands coins
this movie's still there even though i'm
so loud
why are you still right behind me baby
cute
[Music]
did you find the ticket in here no
i must have dropped it somehow
i didn't find it
hmm
i enjoyed watching you panic i don't
know they looked
really normal
they didn't really look like they were
enjoying it just like they were really
confused about what was happening
uh
has kiana wanting to be cool ever worked
well
yes actually
on that day it worked later
because that was the day where i
actually recorded
all of the songs
and fana and gouda were watching
um
is this the right word intently
they were watching and a little bit
helping there was not so much help
necessary because mostly things worked
out on that day uh but they were
watching me suffer and dance and suffer
and dance
every time after a song i would be like
totally overheated and exhausted because
it was really difficult to dance there
um
first of all it was really hot in the
suit and all that the room was hot and
then the floor uh
was not made for dancing i told you this
before i think
but
it was a it was a carpet
a fluffy carpet
and i tried you know several things like
i tried dancing like i'mma had this huge
piece of of cardboard
um but that didn't quite work so well
because i would dance like so
so aggressively that while i was dancing
the cardboard was moving under my feet
and like kept on moving away from me
away from the center
so and but i still had to use it because
for some
dances when i had had to turn around it
was literally impossible to dance
properly on the carpet and it started
making my feet hurt at some point
so
but i was dancing so much of it that at
some point i made holes into the
cardboard
yeah so i couldn't use it anymore at
some point
and we also tried like this big big big
piece of
like
plastic
ground thing
but that ended up like kind of
interfering with the capturing
um because of like reflection and [\h__\h]
even though it didn't even look
reflective you never know like wow we
had to take care of so many things like
even even water bottles were not allowed
to be like in the view of
you know the cameras um
it was really really really complicated
every single thing like we had to look
like sometimes when something wouldn't
work we were like oh what is it this
time what's what is in the room that
causes this problem
um
yeah so i had to give up on that plastic
thing too even though that was really
good to dance on yeah
so mostly i was dancing on fluffy carpet
so
the turns didn't turn out so nice
unfortunately
uh yeah
[Music]
yeah um yeah so i was suffering but
fauna and gouda they looked very
fascinated when they saw me dancing like
that i think fona also said she wants to
take dance lessons or something right
yeah
yeah yeah and gouda kept on like
praising me for working so hard like
when we got when we got closer to the
end they were cheering me on like one
more song two more songs come on
you can do it
bona was inspired by me yeah
apparently
man it's really not easy
even even though you know i have some
like quite some experience with it
um but even for me it's tough to like
i just don't have quite the stamina
anymore that i used to have
so
uh
yeah i i
i had some
problems breathing and uh was very
exhausting but
also the environment of where i was
dancing wasn't the best so
i was like putting so much so much
that was the right word
tenseness
into my legs
so much strength into my legs because of
where i was dancing like trying to
trying to stay
i don't know how to explain it
so much tension tension yeah yeah
in order to
[Music]
have a somewhat clean somewhat clean
dance moves better grip and all that
yeah yeah yeah to make up for the lack
of grip i had on the floor
um i put so much tension into my my
calves that's why they're so [\h__\h]
dead now
they're so so like stone hard
now yeah
it was tough
i want you guys to know that when you
watch the concert and it looks so
amazing you'll be like
wow and she said she was suffering so
much when doing that wow such an idol
amazing
[Music]
yeah but uh guna and fun are giving me
mental support on that day was really
nice yeah thankfully
[Music]
oh i have also this thing where like
when i practice the songs
i wouldn't make mistakes but once i was
recording them
like
like the actual recording i would make
mistakes because i was like probably
again putting too much
too much tension into my body
and the pressure the time pressure too
would make me [\h__\h] up
and
so i want i also originally i wanted to
do like more retakes because
we
we definitely even though we got it to
work we still had some some scuffness
here and there so i wanted to take
retakes for every song but i ended up
like not being able to take
um
retakes properly
yeah because no time
anyway the suit and me
were very sweaty by the end of the day
even the gloves
were like
kind of moist
but er
good al wanted to try it on quickly at
the end of the day so i was like
are you sure like it's really stinky now
but yeah she is she wanted to try it on
so she tried it on she did some stuff
with it
yeah
[Music]
and played around with it oh also one
more thing i did is i took some
countdown videos
so there's some short really short
countdown videos that i will upload
uh
when the days come closer
[Music]
really short ones nothing too long for
twitter and i think i'll upload it on
youtube too probably
uh and some i i recorded like two more
like mimi videos
um for later to upload them later
[Music]
um what else was i gonna say
oh yeah um um um on that day i had some
super yummy uh yakisoba
and i want to say
like i
expected because everybody talks about
it i expected
american food portions to be
much bigger
because everybody tells me they're so
big
but from what i've eaten in my time in
america
i mean most of it was i guess take out
or like ordered
but
it wasn't that insanely big though like
it was pretty normal i mean i'm like in
in austria
uh i
like our normal potion portions are
often also too much for me to eat but
like the pizza that we ordered was
pretty normal size
and then on the other food two
it really depends
um
you know that one day where um you know
after the recording we split up right
and then i was alone in a hotel but then
on the on the last night in the hotel
actually ami joined me
for whatever reason she stayed with me
um
and
uh on the following day before we met up
with the
myth girls again
um
i was like okay i'm a what are we gonna
eat for lunch
and we were looking around like what to
go for what i haven't had yet and kind
of wanted to eat
and
we went to
[Music]
chipotle
right it's chipotle amma kept on
correcting me
i always said
to put what did i always say i think i
always said chipotle chipotle
or
chipotle chipotle
and she kept them correct and said
portal to poddle no i said chipotle i
said the wrong i said it the wrong way
and she corrected me the right way i
think wait wait i don't know anymore
wait what is the right way
listen
it's important
what
chipotle
chipotle now i [\h__\h] out
and anyways any case she kept on
correcting me i don't know which one was
the correct way you guys say she was
patrolling but maybe she wasn't maybe
i'm mixing it up
i don't know anymore
we went there and i know um ami said
this too
it's not the most
um
accurate or like
authentic
mexican food
but i wanted to go because i've i've
heard this name
so often
and i don't know i just i just wanted
some food
yeah whatever it is
it definitely isn't yeah but you guys
like i i heard it's still very popular
and people like to eat it so i was like
okay it seems yummy
so
i got a burrito and i was so again i was
overwhelmed i was like standing at the
counter i'mma already got her stuff so
she went like already away to sit down
and i'm like
i'm like so confused i'm like i don't
know what to put in my burrito i don't
wanna uh
and i couldn't put in anything spicy so
a lot of the choices were already um
like
a no-no
yeah but i put i put in those those
brownish beans not the black ones the
brownish beans
and
chicken
and some salad
and
the sour cream
something else
i think i put something else in there
cheese yeah put cheese in uh pinto beans
i guess it was pinto beans
um um
i think that was about it i didn't put
in guacamole i'm sorry because i
actually don't like avocados
spanish vows is similar to japanese i
see
no i don't think i put in american
cheese no no no it was a choice but i
didn't put in that
i know acorn did that put
i think yeah i think i put in corn
i think i did yeah yeah am i of course i
put in corn
you could get the queso yeah i think i
put in queso
ah corn
but okay now this burrito i have to say
was pretty big
i'll give you that
but i ate quite a lot of it
uh and then i wanted to eat more later
so i didn't eat it all at once but yeah
ame was impressed that i ate so much
because i'm normally a small eater i
don't and and i like to eat like um
in
in small portions and then maybe i would
eat more the rest later but yeah
yeah yeah yeah i need to sneeze i think
no
oh [\h__\h]
i need to sneeze
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] sorry
oh
i forgot in in the hotel um
i got a
in the hotel i got a massage
um
[Music]
i got this
massage deep tissue massage
holy [\h__\h]
i was
in pain
a lot
doing some movements
that the lady would do
and um
i feel like she may have destroyed
something in my body
more or less
i don't know if that's normal that's how
you know it works really it [\h__\h]
hurts so much
like around my neck
like at the um you know where your
hairline is behind the ears
that's the one that hurt the most
yeah she went so [\h__\h] deep and i was
like i was about like i wanted to say um
can you move on or like can you do it a
little bit lighter
but i always like when i'm
um being massaged i get a lot of
massages
most of the time
i'm too
intimidated
or
nervous
to
say something like i want to say yo can
you go stronger or can you go
weaker
but i usually i rarely say anything
because it feels awkward or i don't know
you got to speak up for yourself that's
what i always think because
it costs money so i should say something
but it always takes me so much
courage but also because like when i say
i usually ask if they don't in japan
they always do but then in other
countries they often don't
but when i would say something
um
like do it weaker here just that spot
they would do it weaker everywhere and
then i have to be exact again okay can
you go stronger again it's annoying
like i usually tell them in the
beginning
that um they need to do it stronger
around my shoulders
[Music]
only my shoulders specifically but then
they they forget and they just do
whatever and it's annoying no
don't want to keep on reminding them oh
[\h__\h]
okay good
[Music]
don't want to backstage your massage
you're right i also don't really want to
backseat too much but yeah
anyway so
[Music]
where was i um
oh yeah i think i said this before but
it's in my notes so i'll say it again
ame
never
showed annoyance is that a word
or anything she was always patient and
eager the whole time
always on track and fixing things
super supportive and selfless
and i can't thank her enough i thanked
her so many times
uh
yeah i thanked her so many times i love
her so much
you know
she did so much for me
and you know she's the best you know you
know she's the best
i wasn't i'mma pay you she didn't pay me
at all
she likes the tech
yeah and now we can use it for so many
things
now we basically have something like a
studio
over there we don't have to go to
america but the thing is from uh to
america to japan the thing is for me
though living in austria going to
america and going to
uh japan
for me is basically it takes the same
amount of time basically
[Music]
and the same amount of money
so
well you know if i go to america then
okay i have i have the extra of meeting
amit that's great
but if i go to
japan
i also have the extra of meeting other
like whole life japan members and all
that and
uh
and and
uh more i mean sorry i did a great job
but
in japan
i have a little bit more of like
professional troubleshooting
so
maybe not as much trouble as
you know when when doing it in like our
amateur studio
[Laughter]
yeah but she it was still great and you
know
both both options are definitely an
option for me
it's just like both ways it takes a lot
of time it's not something i can just do
like oh tomorrow i want to record
something
yeah
but i am
kind
of considering
loki considering
getting the same
setup
i'm not too sure about it yet
it kind of i guess depends on
how soon we can go to japan
easily
[Music]
i kind of want it for myself it's pretty
expensive i guess but i feel like
it's less expensive than i thought it
would be
i'm just kind of worried about setting
it up and troubleshooting and all that
[Music]
i mean i'm mature
i
ain't no amateur
no but maybe i could get ammo to like
help me set it up and all that sure sure
but
like handling all it all on my own like
when i when we're done setting it up and
then in the future you know when she's
gone like using it i feel like
i would definitely run into some
problems and then you know being alone
with it is kind of kind of tough worries
me
um
but i'll think about it
i'll think about it
um maybe and then
no
at least i don't always have to travel
so far when i want to have some proper
high quality
3d you know
i don't know i'm still like at some
point getting that that suit that emma
uses every now and then and could i use
it too
for
you know a little bit of a scuffed 3d
which i first thought was great but now
that i have the comparison to
what we did at amis studio
now that i have the comparisons like
such a
obvious
difference
world world
big world size difference
like now that i know
how much it like changes your movements
and all that the the scuffed one
i'm like
i don't think i would be able to do a
concert in that but even though that was
the original plan when i went to amma's
place
we weren't originally planning to use
such a professional setup i was gonna
use her
you know the low quality suit
i thought you know because i didn't ever
wear it before i didn't never test it
before i thought it would be good enough
but i did test it out and i have to say
that is definitely not good enough for a
proper concert
only if i'm like doing a a scuffed
scuffed concert you know
um
yeah so anyway that's some something to
think about i guess yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah on on my way back after that
final recording day
um you know we said goodbye to fauna and
ina wasn't there so it was just me and
gooda
uh
yeah we had a lot of chill talks we
talked about like
uh
like food
and hair salons etc
talked a lot about a lot of stuff and
then
um we had
three day old pizza at 3 a.m let's go
[Laughter]
four or five i don't even know how late
it was anymore but three day old pizza
at 3 a.m sounds pretty good
yeah we ate pizza together kind of a
bonding moment
late night munchies
no it was not in the bathtub
[Music]
yeah it was good it was still very good
i i heated it up in the oven
it ended up being really really good the
american dream
oh boy
yeah in that evening we had some good
talks i would say yeah i don't know
when we discussed things
while we were eating pizza like future
possibilities with the army studio
so yeah then we sat good night and uh
um
then the following day we went our own
ways for a little bit so
i checked into a hotel and
um
yeah then i met my friend and so you
wanna know
these it was i think two days
that i had
uh
where i was able to do some
some sightseeing not much though
so
on one day
my friend took me
to little tokyo
little tokyo in l.a
you guys have little tokyo and it was so
cool you guys had so have so much stuff
there
[Music]
i went to a daiso
i love daiso i got a lot of cool stuff
and daiso
and um
uh we went to an izakaya
and had some yummy food there
what how is it compared to dusseldorf
more spread out
and
uh i guess it had
a bit more stuff than dusseldorf because
it even had a pretty good machine i
didn't use the purikura machine i wanted
to but my feet were already so [\h__\h]
and
i went to japanese supermarket
[Laughter]
where something
funny happened but yeah i went to
japanese supermarket got some
yummy yummy
breakfast for the next day
and
um
what else
what else uh we wanted to go to karaoke
but then we didn't
what's the funny i think i won't say
and then and then i am
oh yeah i got taiyaki
yeah
um
there was like a nice fancy taiyaki
place
i got tanyaki and they had funny taiyaki
because it wasn't the
normal shape it was like a taiyaki with
a big big open mouth
and
inside that mouth was all the ice cream
yummy yummy i love taiyaki with ice
cream
[Music]
yeah
it was yummy
taiyaki i love taiyaki
so
um
something like don
quijote and then
oh
was that on the same day
[Music]
i think on the following day
hi chunky monkey
hi
so fluffy on the fine day i think i went
to target
and now i can tell you
my impression now that i went to both
target and walmart i can tell you target
much better
target much better
walmart
no thank you
no more
i like target yes
target's so much better
yes i think you guys understand
walmart is cheap
yeah yeah but walmart is scary scary
place
target much better
okay so uh the first day that i had off
with my friend was basically like
checking out little tokyo
and then the other day
[Music]
um
we went
to
[Music]
a beach
we went to uh an
l.a beach
i think it was probably somewhere close
to like malibu area
yeah went to the beach which means i
kind of got like a little bit of a
vacation feeling thanks to that yeah
however so she drove us to the beach
which was quite a long drive and
um
i looked at the at the
weather report and it was gonna be
pretty good weather but um when we
arrived
the weather was so [\h__\h] it was so
cloudy
really really cloudy and cold and windy
so we were like getting nervous but
whatever we brought a lot of food we
bought it we brought a cooler my friend
brought the beach towels and all that
and so we were like well we're here so i
guess let's go
and we walked all the way to the beach
was pretty far after we parked the car
uh and then we finally made it to a good
spot we put down our stuff it was still
kind of weirdly cold
uh
yeah um
but then after like an hour or two it
started like clearing up and it never
got to a point where i would say it was
hot
except in my face when i would lie down
for a while
but generally it wasn't really that hot
so i didn't go back for a proper swim
but i did end up going into the water a
little bit
uh like up up to my
under chest
very specific
um
one
terrible thing that happened though
like when we were both like finally okay
let's go into the water yay it's finally
like somewhat warmish so let's go so we
we ran
to the water
you know like a beach episode we ran and
we're like yay
and then
my friend
screams
right before we touch the water
[Music]
i look at her
and she's in pain
she stepped
on a [\h__\h] bee
ma'am
yeah incredible right she stepped for
the bee i know
[Music]
my bro
oh
you guys are getting nervous how you
want to cuddle
yeah
a b it was like on the ground on the
sand and she stabbed on it and
holy [\h__\h] i never got like stung by a
bee before it never happened to me
before so i'm i'm glad it didn't happen
to me but
she was like sitting down on the floor
and like
like suffering and i'm like holy [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] what do we do and then i
like looked at it and she like um
i think she
the the only thing that was left
already was like the the tail the stinky
part um
of of the bee the bee was just like
without its tail on the ground
and
it was in her toe like
ah it looked painful
so she was like
help me help me quit
i don't know so i tried to
she wanted me to help and so i tried to
like pull it out with my fingers it was
a little bit difficult but she was
suffering so i i was like girl are you
okay
should i just just
you should just pull it out quickly and
she's like yeah you're doing it
i know you guys said like we didn't know
yeah we didn't know what was the right
thing to do but yeah i pulled it out and
i got it out properly
the whole tail
thing i had it in my hands
yeah
i got it out properly but it still ended
up being swollen and she was in pain for
quite some time but thankfully it seems
like she wasn't allergic or anything
so she was okay
yeah
uh oh my god but that kind of ruined
the whole magical moment of running to
the water and having fun
then she was like um jumping back to the
beach towel sat down and thankfully we
had an ice pack because we brought the
cooling box
and she yeah she was trying to
you know cool her foot and
oh man i didn't know what to do
she was in pain for pretty long and then
you know
you know i pulled out the the tail right
and i think um
i may or may not have just like wiped it
off on the sand
on the ground
and um a few minutes later
i see this group of
i see this group of people that were
like sitting close to us
um going into the water like there were
like four people or so
and then i i looked at them
i observed them and i see one of the
people
a guy
he
starts like
like lifting his leg and looking at it
at his foot and like
um it seems like he stepped on something
and his friends were like helping him
like holding him and trying to help him
and i'm like
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
yup yup
and i was getting nervous
because they were like basically sitting
right next to me and if they would walk
back to you know try to help themselves
um they would see that my friend was
currently also suffering by something on
her foot
and
then maybe ask us you know about it and
and i was getting really nervous i was
like looking to the side like
i hope he didn't step on the stingy
thing that i left on the floor
but no they were actually i saw more
bees around that wasn't the only bee but
anyway so at some point he jumped back
to his spot and i looked over at me and
my friend looked over and we were like
oh
did you
what what happened to you did you also
step on something
and
uh
he said like yeah
and i'm like oh
on what
because we also my friend stepped on the
on the b
and then
he said
it wasn't the bee
thank god
[Laughter]
coincidentally
even though we were so close to one
another
and he had it literally on the same foot
at on the same spot
it seems like he stepped on a stone or
whatever something else
and was suffering from that for the next
couple of hours
but i was i was so worried that because
of
my
stupidness of leaving the thing on the
floor on the ground
maybe
i got another person
stung by a by a bee
but it wasn't me
it wasn't me thank god
i felt so
worried
i felt so guilty
i got so nervous about it oh thank god
yeah the timing and the position like it
was exactly where my friend stepped on
the beach
literally the same spot
ah
damn i was so nervous
so
anyway so that was a day at the beach i
also got the elotes
not elitos i kept on saying elitas but
it was a lotus but apparently it was not
a lotus when it's not on the club then
it's not elotes i forgot what it was
um
esquitos or something like that
uh
escritas there we go that was it [\h__\h]
i'm getting so [\h__\h] hungry
[Music]
i want to eat pizza
yeah that was yummy um
you know that was at the beach you guys
were wondering where i got it from
um
if i got it from like some kind of uh
street vendor it was a beach vendor guy
thingy who was pushing the cart and was
like ah hello this elitos
muchas
was good
and yeah
yeah yeah and then
yeah my friend was like oh you gotta try
this you gotta try this it's so yummy
and i'm like what are you getting and
then i watch the dude
you know putting all this cord into the
into the cup and then putting all kinds
of extra things on top and i'm like wow
that's a lot of stuff that you're
putting on there
um
and then she mixed it and she was like
try and i tried and it was pretty good
yeah
it was pretty good and later on she got
me
like uh
the the dude came by again and then i
think it was a different dude and this
dude had ice cream and my friend got me
like her favorite ice cream from when
she was younger was some kind of
strawberry
cheesecake
kind of ice cream i don't know if any of
you can imagine which one that is
and i was like when she got it i was
like oh it will probably just be a
normal
no really normal
basic ice cream
but it was so good
it had like this perfect texture yeah
the one with the crumbs outside yeah
yeah yeah
it was wow it tasted like
mmm
so good i love the texture of the the
cookie crumbles
soft really soft cookie crumbles on the
outside yeah strawberry shortcake i
guess that was what it was maybe
she's made some really great choices of
food for me to try
oh now that reminds me and gets me
really angry because
so anyway let's just stop talking about
the beach we had some fun at the beach
it wasn't the hottest but i'm glad i
went
um
because that made it more like a
vacation but anyway we drove back and on
the way i got baskin robbins so that was
also a great success i really wanted to
get baskin robbins they didn't have my
favorite flavor though which i already
knew beforehand because that is a
japanese-only flavor that's not what i'm
angry about though it was still yummy
but anyway we um we were gonna like she
was dropping me off at the hotel to get
ready for dinner because she made a
reservation i was like yeah you gotta
make a reservation at a fancy restaurant
so i can um treat you i want to treat
you to a fancy dinner
so just pick a fancy place you know this
city well so
yeah you do decide so she made a
reservation i was looking forward to it
and i dressed in my fancy dress and she
dressed in her fancy dress and we met
back up again and then she drove us to
the place
and then you know uh parking [\h__\h]
pain in the ass so
we decided okay how about we use valet
parking
and i'm like okay don't worry i'll cover
it
so
um the moment where like the moment i'm
giving him the money
she says oh i gotta get gasto because i
ran out of gas
[Music]
which is okay and she's told she told me
to just go in first
and she'll come later when she gets the
gas and she'll give the car to the valet
so i i paid the dude the valet dude
and then i walk over to the restaurant
and i go in and i'm like yeah i have we
have a reservation under this name
now and she's like
no can't find your name here so i walk
back because my friend was still there
and i'm like yo girl they don't have the
reservation on his name are you sure
and then she checks her phone
and she's like
and this is not what i'm angry about
though she's like oh [\h__\h] i made it for
tomorrow
and i'm like okay
that's okay i guess let's just go
somewhere else then
so i walk over to the valet guy
because he's he's still there and he has
had yet to touch
the [\h__\h] car
i'm like dude we made a reservation for
the wrong day so we're not gonna make
use of the parking we're gonna go
somewhere else
and he's like he smiles at me and he's
like oh yeah sorry but can't refund it
and i'm like what but you didn't even
like park our car or touch our car and
he's like yeah but you're already in the
system and look here it says no refunds
and i'm like what the [\h__\h] do you mean
what system
and he smilingly shows me his phone
where supposedly i didn't even look that
closely but he shows like here you're in
the system because he took our phone
number
and i'm thinking dude there's no [\h__\h]
way that you can't just delete that and
give me yeah i want to say i'm not part
of your [\h__\h] system i'm giving back
the money
and i was so
i was so
i was so astonished
by
the [\h__\h] logic
and the obvious greediness
that the moment he said sorry no refunds
i
i was like i gasped so loudly that it
was like
almost a cough i was so shockingly
and astonishedly gasping
that it was such a loud gasp that i
ended up coughing okay
and
somehow i was so i was angry but i was
also so astonished that i was laughing i
was like
you're not actually
serious
[Music]
and i'm like okay whatever i'm not going
to discuss this
i really wanted to swear at him but i'm
not that type of person i was inside of
my brain i was swearing and and just
this can't be [\h__\h] real you're not
[\h__\h] serious did i really just pay 13
for you not even touching my [\h__\h] car
i was oh oh my god
i'm i did not give a [\h__\h] about the
restaurant being booked on the wrong day
i only gave a [\h__\h] about this [\h__\h]
ballet
so i go in i get into the car and i'm
like yo
girl
she won't give me back the money cause
we're in the system he says
there's no refund and she's like yeah
that's la
and i'm like what do you mean
she says yeah everybody wants your money
in l.a everybody they just want the
money they're so greedy
[Music]
and i'm like i guess that's how it is
what the [\h__\h]
what the actual [\h__\h]
no i'm so mad i'm so mad at this even
now like if he would have already like
touched or be
been inside the car
now even then if he wouldn't have moved
it i wouldn't have understood i'm so mad
i still to this day i'm so [\h__\h] mad
and his his stupid ass smile
his stupid ass smile
made everything so much more
worse
stupid smile you stupid [\h__\h] grin
like ha ha
i got your money and i didn't do
anything for it so smug yeah
so [\h__\h] smoke i'm so mad i'm so mad i
was i was like a [\h__\h] volcano with
anger like meanwhile while i was like
venting and just gasping in the car
how this really just happened
my friend you know she was driving to
get gas and she was just chilling like
as if this is normal
and if it's [\h__\h] normal
i'm so [\h__\h] mad
i can't believe it
so [\h__\h] mad
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i could have gone full karen
on his ass
but you know in even though i i get mad
on stream i can't do it in reality i'm
pretty polite in reality
i can't
i should have gone angry german on him
yeah
dude
give me my skeleton
i don't know
oh
it took me a while to
calm down from that experience that
[\h__\h] really i'm [\h__\h] bullying
[\h__\h]
i'll never forget i will never [\h__\h]
forget one day i'll come back
one day if i ever go back to la
i'll come back and i find i will find
that valet
and i will just walk by and say nothing
[Laughter]
no man
i want revenge though i want revenge
oh man i want to fight him i wanna
[\h__\h] fight him
oh man
anyway
huh
one more thing i noticed maybe it's just
like
maybe i'm not sure if this is an l.a
thing because i noticed that in l.a
[Music]
people dressed uh women specifically
dressed really um
fashionable
and
[Music]
a lot of them stood out very much
because um
a lot of them were like really
tight and tight and short
uh like party dresses even though it was
just during the day
on the street
um yeah that seems to be an l.a thing my
friend told me i was like holy [\h__\h] you
guys are so fashionable in america and
she was like yeah no that's just l.a
um but then another thing i noticed is
like because they were all dressed like
pretty nicely not all of them but a lot
of them um
and my friend and me we were also
dressed nicely
like people would you know
but while walking by
they even we would like my friend would
say to them or they would say to us
first like we would be like oh i like
your dress i like your shoes and they
would be like oh i love your shoes i
love your dress i love your hair and all
that
like
i was like everybody's so
nice and friendly
what the [\h__\h]
what what you know i
i didn't expect that
i thought americans would be more cold
and i don't know not so not so [\h__\h]
friendly
yeah but they were very supportive we
were supportive of them they were
supportive of us looking cute like
everybody's so supportive of each
other's cuteness and prettiness and all
that oh there was this one thing that
was really cute like we were at that um
we were at the restaurant
and
um
[Music]
now maybe i was a little bit jealous
about the situation but i still thought
it was really cute so we were like done
eating we were leaving and
the girl
who like
gave us our table who brought us to our
table
oh
[Music]
the girl who um brought us to the table
she was really cute and we were like
saying that to each other oh she was so
cute isn't she
and then when we left though
she
would
yes scratch that scratch it real good
yeah yeah get it go get it
chunky no i know
ah
sorry i keep on interrupting cause she's
so cute um
she she came up to us
and
she specifically asked my friend so that
was kind of sad but um she asked like yo
i'm kind of new here in l.a i just moved
here i have no friends and you're really
cute so here's my number
maybe we can like hang
and i'm like looking at this situation
and i'm like
i i'm not i'm not jealous or sad or
anything because i don't live here
anyway so it's not like even if she gave
me her number like i could have hung out
with her so i don't care it's not like i
care i don't care but i mean okay so i
was being a little bit like like tunsun
in my mind but i still thought it was
really cute how she was like giving my
friend her number and you know that was
such a cute moment like once again i'm
like everybody's so supportive of each
other's cuteness and
oh hi
just jumped on the table okay well now
you're mine i will cuddle you high
yeah i was really
no i mean i cared a little bit but i
tried to
in my mind be like oh
even if i got her number i wouldn't have
done anything with it you know
yeah is that a normal thing i don't know
is it
you guys probably wouldn't know because
you're not you're not my cute friend
yeah but my cute friend she got like
talked to so often
yeah
it depends on where you live ah i feel
like l.a people were so nice
[Music]
maybe especially
girls
are like
so open
yeah
all about networking
yeah my friend told me that like
so often you see like famous people in
l.a randomly because that's where
everybody is for the music industry and
all that
[Music]
now there's a reason why i'm not saying
who it is but
um
yeah you may know who it was
but she said she doesn't even want to
live in l.a um she just has to live
there for connections and all that
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah that was it was i had a
good time though even though that
[\h__\h] valet guy ruined everything
had a good time um yeah saw some cool
places i wish i had a bit more time to
see a bit more um but it was also really
um nice because like she drove me
everywhere so it was really comfy mostly
except for the parts where
i walked too much
it was nice yeah and then on that night
um after my friend dropped me off at the
hotel a man came to join me in the hotel
and she slept over
with me and and and i had a one double
bed but it was enough space and i i was
like
maybe we should watch something so i
pulled out my ipad
and i i showed her because i thought you
know abe would be interested in that
because we both like to think of like
some projects for you know project
streams exciting project streams uh hi
from alaska hello thank you for watching
i need to go to alaska someday
and um
no no not animal videos no i showed her
the the taskmaster show that my mom
recommended to me
that i was like um binge watching i was
like i'm i'm i need to show you this is
really funny and it kind of inspires me
for like stream ideas so we watched an
episode together and i was like i was so
tired so i was like closing my eyes and
like almost falling asleep i feel like i
partially dozed off and i i hope she
didn't notice because we were supposed
to watch it together
yeah i i dozed off for like at least
five minutes
um
i didn't want her i'mma to notice though
i don't think she noticed
[Music]
but yeah we were cuddling
not really cuddling we were like yeah
together in bed watching taskmaster and
i think she enjoyed it yeah with little
with little alex horn yeah little alex
horn i love the show so much
yeah
yeah yeah
yeah and then yeah and we slept and then
we woke up and then uh we had some
breakfast uh not at the hotel this time
because i thought i know i i tweeted
this out right i
i
had the breakfast buffet
um on the first morning
but
i paid like
bucks
for the breakfast buffet
which wasn't even that
big
it was pretty small i've been to cheaper
buffets that are much bigger
yeah
so
and one orange the orange the juices the
drinks were not even included
that's why it was 40 dollars personally
um
one [\h__\h] small glass of orange juice
nine
dollars
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
yeah and the breakfast was really really
not that special it wasn't even that
good and uh you know it was like a
buffet like i go there and i pick up the
things that i want to eat
but there were there was like a low-key
service like um them bringing me to the
table i guess and giving me the orange
juice that i ordered so that's why i was
so like confused it's a buffet but i
guess i got an orange juice so
but it's also
me
i don't know i know chunky wonky
so i wasn't sure about tipping because
yeah i got your guys's opinion
uh
i did meow yes i know i know i know it's
incredible no don't jump up there you
won't be able to get down
chunky
yeah yeah yeah come down she's she wants
to get on the on the top of the shelf
no chunky monkey
donkey
[Music]
baby
yeah you just stay there on top of the
chair
she's so talkative they both are
oh did i leave for a moment
just for a second right
next
[Music]
okay well at least i came back so
quickly
okay
um
yeah
that was my time in l.a pretty much
because after that
uh after getting breakfast and and
chipotle to portal
um
[Music]
we gathered together
and
at cali's place
and you know i already met at that point
i already met everyone so it was just
like the other girls met cali for the
first time
i guess
um besides gooda who already met kelly
the like the day or so before i don't
know
um
she poodle
chipotle
chia polti
yeah yeah but it was nice finally like
seeing everybody again did you meet mama
mori
yes i did and
i mean
i'm so amazed
she's
meow
no what are you doing
no bad joking
wait i need to get her off the shelf and
then i'll continue one second
[Music]
you're awesome fluffy
yo
he's a good baby
you're good baby you could pay me
no
you
oh baby
oh you you she's purring i don't think
if you hear it but she's purring
the moment i touch you she immediately
purse
donkey wonky
chunky wonky you're so shy
i'll give you a brush later okay you
both need a brush really really really
urgently
they both were shedding like crazy
[Music]
okay
bonkers
no no chunkers would never go bonkers no
no that's that's that's uh bonkers going
bonkers chunkers wouldn't kill blankets
you uh met auntie watson too yes i did
so many unexpected
uh
meetups
yeah
uh i didn't expect to meet like mama
mori and auntie watson and um bay yeah
well very unexpected i'ma set you
embarrassed there yeah i didn't
embarrass it you know when we were
eating in and out uh on the last evening
because i really wanted like actually it
wasn't
it was actually like
i wasn't even insisting on eating in and
out or anything
i might kind of just uh
recommended that we should eat in and
out and i was like yo i'm i'm so [\h__\h]
in because
i
oh my god
[Music]
ah
no so um yeah because i didn't get to it
uh to eat
stop
[Music]
no no no
no
uh
so anyway
uh uh so
um told me that you know you can't oh
you can't uber eats or anything uh in
and out
and um
but then she said she has someone who
can bring us the food and i'm like hey
yo what
what and then she told me yeah her
auntie can bring us the food i'm like
hey yo yo what what why would she do
that
why would she do such a nice thing once
again
american people being exceptionally nice
exceptionally
especially nice so [\h__\h] nice and holy
[\h__\h] she bought like a million burgers a
million fries
and then we sat down to eat it together
and i must say
the burger
was
really good
um
i
originally
didn't go for a double-double because i
thought it would be pretty big even
though ami told me they're relatively
small so i got a single
um
but then
after i ate the single and some of the
fries i was like [\h__\h] this was good i
want more it was relatively small the
burger was relatively small so
uh there were still burgers left because
some people didn't end up eating their
burger
[Music]
and like mama morning i think it was
mama money who was like a
vegetarian i think
i think so there was a leftover burger
and
i was like ah it's never single this is
good single plus single i can do single
plus double i can't
so i ate another single then thankfully
happy happy it was yummy like the patty
is like kind of a little bit crispy
which um
i thought you know maybe that's uh
that would be something that would be
something that you wouldn't like in a
burger but yeah uh
it's actually
actually really good i like the
crispiness and um the sauce really good
they gave us a million sauce packets
though i don't know what if anybody even
used them
i have to settle the fries i got them
animal style
uh but still they were dry
and
[Music]
weirdly
mushy soft
and
the cheese was already so
um
it was dried up so
yeah i tried eating it and then
much later ahmed told me i'm supposed to
mix it i'm like what you tell me that
now but even then when i tried mixing it
unfortunately the fries were not good um
i have to say
maybe they're better like completely
fresh and not like delivered by car or
so
but
yeah they were not okay
they were not good
but the the the burger was really good
yeah
i'm gonna get the fries well done
mm-hmm anyway
[Music]
yummy yummy i'm glad i got to eat in and
out
and uh
oh yeah i didn't
so so so because ahmed was sitting next
to me and uh auntie ami ame aunty was
sitting right next to amen so i was like
um
can i can i say something for a second i
just want to say that like you uh you
did such a great job with ahmed like she
turned out so well she was she's such a
you raised her with the right values and
all that yeah you did such a great job
she's amazing
this is how you embarrass it nah she was
probably happy about it at the same time
flattered flatted is the right word yeah
i may use the wrong word even though you
know she's her first language is english
she can't speak english apparently she
was flattered okay
but no she was just silently sitting
next to me but i was like uh yeah
complimenting and praising her
she i didn't even notice her stare no no
don't didn't notice anything i just
wanted to you know
um make conversation because like you
know um oh i stopped moving oh [\h__\h]
oh my gosh [\h__\h]
battery
i'm having problems with battery even
though it's charging
oh well um
uh don't listen to ami
she said it was embarrassing don't worry
it wasn't
it was just flattering
yeah but what was i gonna say
oh yeah because like
auntie watson i had a you know i i
observed the whole situation like you
know cali was in the corner having fun
and then uh ame me and so on we were in
the corner and not in the corner we were
at the table eating
so
um
i noticed because
i'm a good observer that auntie watson
was
kind of
just quietly sitting there not really
having any conversation with anyone so i
felt like i want to include her in the
conversation so i i told her you know
the whole thing about um
ami
i wanted to you know
let make her feel kind of you know
appreciated and involved yeah
i noticed that she was just you know
quietly sitting there and i wanted to
give her some appreciation for coming
all the way to bring us so much food
what the hell
so nice
yeah and i also told her i really liked
her t-shirt she had a really nice
t-shirt on with a cat
uh i wanted that t-shirt i really liked
her cat t-shirt
she seems to be a cat person
and i like her and amanda money
was um
wow so
sweet like
um
she like worried so much about us and
then she
she would like
say
these really supportive things like oh i
don't i don't know how you do that ah
you're so amazing you girls are just so
amazing for like going through these
things and you know wow i really respect
you girls she was so sweet and and and
charming sweet
like a wow such a doting
maybe doting is a wreck or a doting mom
and when i was listening to cali talk to
her
either like on the phone or like when
she was actually in person there
there was like so much like love there
wow i was i was fascinated i was really
fascinated they were so so sweet to one
another
um
really cute
really really cute you know and mamma
money was also very
fancy and fashionable
yeah
she had like nice makeup nice clothes
nice hair
[Music]
very fresh looking
[Laughter]
no i didn't meet the sister no no
only mama money
such a sweet mom like wow
so sweet
there's nothing for me to approve of
but i'm happy for kelly that she has
such a
sweet loving mom
um
okay okay okay uh so that was that we
had um
yeah you know we had those collabs oh by
the way i was like during the during the
aircraft karaoke
um
you may not have heard me so well but i
i started singing along like after a
couple of songs i stayed quiet because i
was really tired and not in the mood for
singing but then i was like ah
you guys probably want to hear me
so i guess i'll sing a little bit and
then i i started joining in uh
i don't know what song was that what
song was that
what what was that song i joined in
[Music]
some kind of low song so i uh i i
started singing a dancing queen and then
later a aviva la vida
yeah i sang really high there because it
was kind of low i used to rule i can't
sing that
you guys thought it was ame
that was me
that was me yo
but the thing is me and ina um we were
sitting on the couch and cuddling in a
blanket like a piggies in a blanket so
uh we actually didn't hear the music
like they all had like headphones on
we didn't hear the music we just heard
them singing and then tried to follow
along accordingly
and just feel the music in our
imagination
eno was actually singing along the whole
time except for maybe two songs or so
that she didn't know well
[Music]
and the models were
almost on point
it was um actually the other way around
my head resting on her but i thought
that looked so cute
i think i i told abby to uh put me
in the back in 3d sitting
yeah yeah yeah yeah and then she put uh
inna there as well
i joined i joined singing a little bit
was being asleep no babe was already
gone at that time
she was already gone
yeah cause it was [\h__\h] late
mate it was [\h__\h] light night
bloody hell
i mean i feel like we were both clingy
to one another
[Music]
you know was the most receptive i guess
of cuddles like at some point we had
like before the
unarchived karaoke we had this like
kind of like
almost like a business meeting
and uh me and ina were cuddling in a
blanket
at that point too
the whole time
yeah
but at some point
at some point i also got to cuddle with
amma under the blanket it was really
[\h__\h] cold the whole time the air
conditioning was insane
i kept on trying to raise it
but i feel like somebody
lowered it every now and then
but most of us were [\h__\h] freezing the
whole time and i didn't bring any like
warm clothes because i thought it would
be [\h__\h] hot people told me it would
be [\h__\h] hot in la
it wasn't
that hot
yeah
and especially inside with the ac
blasting
um
it was probably cali yeah
yeah oh my god
it's freaking hot ah cold so we we were
at least that was a reason to get us all
cuddled up in blankets
oh actually um i'mma because you know
she said that um she was like sleeping
on the couch right because i think we
didn't have quite enough beds for
everyone to get a single
bed
um but
you know
when i heard that emma was gonna stay on
the couch in the evening i was like okay
i'm gonna be mommy again so
i took like um i took off a blanket off
of my bed and a few pillows and i put it
on the couch for her and i'm like here
there you go you can use my bedding
[Music]
yeah
gotta tell you these moments because the
other girls don't talk about it i was i
feel like it was pretty mommy-like
during this whole thing like um i really
had that you know when we had dinner
like i brought out we had a [\h__\h] ton of
food while everybody was chilling i
brought out all the plates it was like
10 plates or so and lined them up on the
on the table because we were like
sitting outside i lined them all up
nicely i set the table
and then afterwards like everybody
like
slowly scattered and sat somewhere else
after they were done eating so i
brought everything back inside slowly i
was like are you done eating and i take
this and i take that and brought
everything back inside
mommy quinoa
[Music]
no we had way too much food
so that we actually like also ate i at
least ate it for breakfast too
no no no no that was when it was only
myth members
on the first night but we still had like
a [\h__\h] ton of plates of food like
unnecessary amounts of food i was like
how are we ever gonna eat all of that
so i ate some more for breakfast yeah
[Music]
yeah no no i had my own room
yeah i was like um close to close to
amido
relatively close
so
i uh on the
when i when i was about to leave
um
it was like it was really [\h__\h] early
and i got like maybe like
maximum one and a half hours of sleep
um so before i went to sleep um that's
why i also like kind of
didn't want to participate too much in
the karaoke because i really needed to
sleep a little bit
um but yeah afterwards they still were
like talking and chilling and hanging
and having fun
nobody was seemed really tired for some
reason except me and eno
but yeah so i was like okay girls i
can't stay up anymore i need to sleep so
i said goodbye early to
um
good uh
and kelly and ina i was like i'm not
gonna wake you up when i leave so
um just gonna say goodbye now
but then for ame since she was like
relatively close to and in the living
room which i was gonna you know
she was gonna hear me probably i was
like okay i'm in uk if i wake you up
when when i leave and she was like yeah
yeah you can wake me up but then
when i when i was about to leave
i walked over and i looked at her
sleeping so peacefully again and i'm
like i want to say goodbye but
but i woke her up a little bit i was
like touching her
moving her i was like
i'm gonna leave a minute and then she's
like
ah yeah goodbye
and i'm like uh oh wait i mean i'm not
leaving because my uber apparently takes
20 minutes to get here what the [\h__\h]
and she's she just fell asleep again
while i was sitting next to her waiting
for my uber
and 20 minutes later i'm like okay okay
i'm in
i'm leaving for real but then she didn't
wake up anymore and she was back asleep
so i was like okay
i'm not gonna
i'm not gonna wake her up anymore i kind
of wanted to give her a hug but i didn't
want to wake her up too much because you
know she has been lacking sleep for the
past couple days i guess so i was like i
need to let her sleep it's my fault that
she didn't sleep so
so then i left quietly
can't wake up wake me up inside
uh
yeah
but but um i left her some money for
like did some food that she ordered for
me
and um
and
then yeah later later she
messaged me
um when i was like i saw it when i was
waiting in in chicago
and she
she wrote to me
she apologized
if if
i uh for for
maybe bullying and teasing me
and i'm like what
what do you mean
i never felt you know
bullied or teased or anything by ame if
anything i felt
the most supported and loved by amen
and accepted and i love her and i'm
gonna cry
[Music]
i'm gonna cry
yeah she said she likes to tease me but
i didn't feel teased by her at all what
the [\h__\h]
[Music]
and when did she tease me she never
teased me
i didn't feel teased
[Music]
oh
chunky wonky
[Music]
mommy
need to ask
her why are you trolling me about the
chip
i'm so confused i don't know how i said
it anymore originally about the chip
poodle
chipotle
pronunciation
is that what you meant with teasing
[Music]
chipotle
i don't remember
i got brainwashed
chunky monkey
well
i bet amma misses you too you think so i
don't know
i don't think i'm a very miserable
person
you know it's just because like
this whole recording thing
i feel like it made me uh and ame
bond very much and we we talked more
than ever before
yeah
[Laughter]
so
i'm gonna get emotional yeah
no
yeah you guys you guys missed me very
much cause well you're fans so obviously
you're gonna miss me
obviously thank you
that's why i was so eager to immediately
you know stream again even though i just
arrived today
yeah
and um i'm gonna be streaming the next
days too
we're gonna do wind waker last episode
and
so on uh for next week i'll put up a
schedule again for now for now there
won't be a schedule i guess because i'm
not so sure what to do besides wind
waker
um
but here comes an announcement
you wanna hear the other announcement
guys
[Music]
yes you
do just gonna show this now
it's [\h__\h] cute
oh should i really show it like this
yeah [\h__\h] it
okay announcements
you ready
no i didn't really decide yet when
[Music]
maybe tomorrow tomorrow okay so uh hi
close your eyes close your eyes close
your eyes close your eyes close your
eyes
did you close your eyes
i know you're not closing your eyes
because you know there's no way i can
like check anyway but close your [\h__\h]
eyes
[Music]
open
coming out finally
tomorrow
i don't know i could already do it
tomorrow i'm not sure do you want it
tomorrow do you want it on another day
and
the special thing about this is
i had this translated to english
so because you guys want english music
don't you
yeah so i had the whole song translated
to english
and we sang it in english
english animal
ian cover yay
yeah i got permission from from dekosan
and de konina-san to
translate it
and originally i was uh asking callie
but i think she got really busy so
uh we ran out of time and then i had to
ask uh the in-house translation team but
the in-house translation team actually
did
an insanely good job with it like it
turned out so great
so
i might ask them again
for another time yeah
um
it turned out pretty good
i like the
the rhymes and all that they turned out
really fun
[Music]
yeah as we have to do everything very
properly in
um whole life
we i just i can't just you know cover
any song randomly english uh we need
permission beforehand so thank you nina
and
for giving us permission to do this yeah
i might do it more often now yeah
because i know already de konino-san
allows their songs to be turned into
english versions
so oh my hairstyle
oh
i think this was drawn before
zeta's debut actually i didn't that
didn't even notice
yeah i didn't even realize who's that
cover artist uh mono-sun yeah i chose
the artist i chose everything i
organized the cover uh that's why it's
gonna be on my channel
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah i was like
elena lean back i'll take care of it you
just do the singing
it turned out very cute you know you
know how so say senpai and mikko senpai
covered this song
um
i feel like in this case
dana takes the position of suicide
because uh they both you know have like
the more mature voice and i kind of took
the position of mikko senpai because i
i didn't even try to sound too cute but
it just ended up sounding really cute
yeah so look forward to it
now what is it
what is it
[Music]
ah i guess i'll upload it tomorrow i
didn't decide on the time
i kind of wanted to
upload it
and then give it some time
uh but i also want to stream
every day the rest of the week i don't
know what to do
maybe stream first and then upload i
don't know
[\h__\h] i don't know i i i wanted to show
you guys that this like uh show it off
and announce it but i don't i didn't
even really decide what to do with it um
[Music]
do i have a lot of superchats to read
where where the people who monitor that
do you guys know
maybe i could do a superchat reading
tomorrow
for like a couple hours and then and
then upload the cover
i don't have that much is it not worth
doing a super chat reading
a lot
a lot really
really
i finished the alpha reveal yeah so it's
really that much
[Music]
i could do it
because i really want to eat some food
now
and i'm still kind of jet-lagged
and it's hot
hold up
i've never played like the original game
so i don't know like if it's not too
stressful for me to eat read super chats
while doing it i i'm i don't mind like
maybe considering playing hodokiwa
as everyone's playing it right now
but it has whole live characters so kind
of
i don't want to give it a try people
i've been like ego searching in japanese
and a lot of japanese people have been
tweeting that kiana
[Music]
amazing i'm really happy to hear that
like in valkyrie connect as well i was
i'm like mvp all the time because i'm
like the front fighter front line
fighter and really strong
yo i'm always so strong in games what's
up with that let's go
yeah nice good to hear
i might try it out maybe next week maybe
i don't know like
it's kind of intimidating by the looks
of it it's like but i guess you don't
really do much
i guess it's it looks really stressful
but you don't have to do much right you
just like blast
blast blast blast blast
you just walk around right yeah
and then fancy
things pop up on the screen
no i didn't play vampire survivors
that's the
thing i was busy with other games when
everyone was playing that um
[Music]
maybe we'll take a look at it next week
um but i don't think i should be reading
super chats while well
while playing on
i don't know how many super chats do i
have to i finished wait let me let me
kind of like check um
[Music]
let me see
because
if i'm gonna read something today i
should read to like now
um
okay we have the chill talk ones
which
are
not that many
and then the kfb 101 and pop tart her
challenge zelda stanley
yeah it does look like quite a bit
[Music]
but how where is the number of how many
super chats it is
[Music]
that's like nothing
stanley
stanley parable had
[Music]
if i'm gonna do a super chat reading
tomorrow then i might as well just do
nothing today but
and then zelda
[Music]
zelda
what the [\h__\h]
did i turn super chats off for the past
zelda stream
because it shows me one
ah i turned them off that's smart that's
a smart thing to do
[Music]
but i guess the pop-tart stream had
quite a few yeah yeah that one had quite
a few so pop-tart
pop-tart stream
chilling in usa and stanley mostly and
today i guess okay i mean yeah i could
do i'm going to do a super chat reading
stream
[Music]
past q a we're trying to not kill future
very smart smart smart smart
okay so how about tomorrow tomorrow
tomorrow
at um maybe like
4 p.m
4 p.m we do super chat reading and then
at
10 p.m
i release animal
maybe
tomorrow is friday right
[Music]
okay
i want to talk about the song
and normally i like to do it that way
but
nah it's okay i'll talk about it
beforehand
or in in the wind waker stream
really sad about this movie oh no animal
oh no
yeah okay uh
no trailer oh there's a trailer
there is oh thanks for asking
i will upload it as the trailer for the
music video
i guess i can show you
[Music]
okay
it might be loud
uh
it's gonna be loud i'm gonna try to
lower it immediately okay three
[Music]
two
one
[Music]
i mean i warned you
i warned you meow hi donkey monkey
[Music]
yeah i guess then we'll do super chat
reading tomorrow and then on the weekend
we do wind waker probably only one
episode i think that should be enough to
finish it uh sunday i don't know we'll
do something i have no plans right now
maybe we could do a collab i don't know
uh but you guys want someone's james
right because you missed me
understandable okay let's do solo
streams
[Music]
and
announcements isn't it oh my god it's
[\h__\h] time so soon
for my birthday concert i worked so hard
on it
i had a favor when i was practicing the
songs i had like a week to learn it all
while i was sick
and now finally you will see
you will see how my hard work paid off
mine and amaze and inna's especially
the hard work of setting up everything
and yeah dancing all day
yeah
you will see it
and kind of use
i i i've
yo the stage looks so cool already and i
won't show you i won't show you
but the stage looks so cool i didn't
know
that kana oovoo can make stages too
um
yeah
he can create stages pretty amazing
[Music]
sorry i'm so excited
i think i have a few more stories that i
can share during wind waker as well
oh there you are i didn't know either
yeah now you know
surprise the goat
so i'm very excited to show you guys
this um
this whole concert created by basically
a couple of girls and kanna ubu
um
created
by
us
the amateurs
the amateurs we should give ourselves if
we make we should make a company and the
company name will be
the amateurs but with ame
there are matures
it's crazy it is like wow
wow wow
wow
good bad name it is
yeah
all right so i guess i'm gonna go now
and get some food and it was really nice
talking to you guys catching up and yeah
i missed you guys too and i missed my
cats so i will uh chill and hang with my
cats because they're like really [\h__\h]
needy right now
so cute i feel like they're fluffier
than before like when i saw them
holy [\h__\h] it felt like i didn't see them
for months
it was crazy probably i feel like what
partially added to that effect is
i had this before when i met
on a vacation when i met um different
cats and then came back to my cat at
home but that was like when i still
lived with my mom and we had a cat there
um
my actual cat looked so different to me
that was such a weird phenomenon
now my cats didn't look completely
different to me but they looked fluffier
and like so much more magical to me
they had this aura about them as if i
haven't seen them for months yeah
yeah
anyway
hope your trip to america was overall
fun ignoring smog valleys
yeah uh yeah yeah my my conclusion is
um it was worth it
worth it going that far
for a recording of a birthday i'm glad i
didn't give up on the plan i'm glad i
went through with it even though it was
insanely stressful
um
one of the most stressful times in
um or since i joined whole life um but i
think it was worth it and it will pay
off because the result will be so
amazing
um
but now i'm glad that everything's
back to normal and that we can we can
stream like normal again
and chill i just want to chill
it was too much but yeah i'm really
proud of myself
definitely um
so
thank you very much for waiting for me
for being so patient i know you guys you
know missed me
um but you know we had some great
collaborations that just
you know normally
normally we don't have the opportunity
to all meet up together that was a
special occasion so it had to be
celebrated with as many collabs as
possible yeah
so thank you for waiting and supporting
and welcoming me back and i'll see you
again tomorrow rao
tomorrow
uh
at 4 p.m kimono standard time for super
chat reading and then the release oh i
guess i'm dying yeah yeah there she goes
nice i feel like i need to buy
a cable for tomorrow
and
is she gonna come back
yeah okay
[Music]
bye bye bye
bye bye
love you guys
i love you
too wait
no
love you
[Music]
you have something to say
she's like meowing at me 10 times no
she's quiet
[Music]
okay
too quiet it doesn't pick you up baby
just doing some cute me out
mouth brown
wow
well talk to me
she knows that she's unmuted now
[Music]
all right i'll go cuddle you
you