[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] [
Applause] [
Music] [Applause
] [Music] [Applause]
[Music]
patience
patience New SC too 5 minutes 6 minutes
[Music]
hang on, am I too small or not? I think
that's right.
[Music]
eh wait a minute
No it's super w check check check
Ni already when Not yet Bu wow I've been
going for 3 weeks coughing
anyways Nice song okay
anyways your service let me day Welcome
back to my stream finally after
eh a week yeah I don't know
How many weeks have it been?
Same
ho hello oh oh my god
oh Do
dooni dok
dooni ah Are you guys oh you guys up
there I am koci koci
down Watasi koci eh bring it on bring it on
bring it on bring
it on under ooo
[Music]
[Laughs]
practice let's go
okay
it If you have anything to ask just
just ask
her sem are
okay okay okay
[Music]
Yeah what
I
Okay So let's just I'll brief you guys
here BRI
Min mini
games
there yeah the first one
[  Music]
so we ni Al
di
[Music]
ara Hai
m
treurew foruret
i ha ha
ha for theure hunt we don't do it ins we
it outside of
bor
it hai
hai today
Yes have you guys  read the Rul
[Music]
for Simon
sayon ​​says yeah
[Music]
so I'll explain it to Japanese first,
antanantan
[Music]
you pen I'll explain it again in
English at
Bahasaones Indonesia
[Music]
[Applause]
Indonesia S du
t  ye let's
go Indonesia
[Music]
love Hi s 2 t Yeah Yeah I love
you Yeah
just yeah love you love you
dog
dog dog i dog
[Music]
uh
don't
Ha Yes I'm going to practice guys
homework OK follow
[Music]
me ha
of have to
[Music]
the hai
hai
guy have you memorized it yet n memoriz e
those are the words that must be remembered Oh left
right forward and
backwardpat
S Please read
read read read the
word Yon yonde left right forward and backward
Yes jump yeah
one three four five Yes hit hit
squat squat face
face throw throw
[Music]
l
war
war okay j j
okay yeah
I'll Start with the first command Okay
okay Do it after I count down  count
okay okay
ha go one
time two
[Music]
one
k you know you also do the same thing
note but in real games there won't be
anything like that yeah Oh there won't be anything like
Simonu but the problem is that it's
too far gone they'll just follow Simon just
name the title  That's
fine, then if that's the case, this doesn't
mean you just have to follow
everything, it's not because it's difficult for
them, it's
a pity,
so this means there's no Simon
Simon, right?  right, for example, if there's a
Publ game, there's something like Simon or something
like that, just move straight away, but this doesn't exist
because it's hard for you to understand,
don't throw it, yes, yes, you understand, he's okay, let's
go
[Music] let's go,
okay,
let's make people overinking
Ere back once three two
[  Music]
one ha
[Music]
you guys go back to where
you came from diahah
okay okay
okay go back once triple jump
[Music]
Hai
ju j
[Laughs]
ka like G
okay  okay okay okay hint can't give
hinance one more time
okay Atar m yeah I
Okay squat twice cheerfully
[Music]
ST
and next
stage let's
go let's go Man
okay
squat
twice Strike once
cheerfully
[Music]
y
nicece perf
Yes squat twice
Hit
once facing
right Sri
Seang
kah
Oh ma
I think your right is different but it
looks like you are both right right?
look to the right but from my direction I'm
semp
k I why
[Music]
why
naon naon what do I see what I can
see no not you're not supposed to
cheat ha you're not supposed to cheat
ha spare if you cheat then he'll be
disqualified by the committee What do you want to
do?
Lo, what kind of team will we
eat, and there's no profit,
you know, people like this
It's OK, keep cheating,
but it's OK, if you
cheat,
gu cute, okay
[Music]
[Music] The
next SEG is a bit more difficult.
G
[Music]
yeah Just A Minute
fighting Ma
[Music]
fighting so that's
wrong G
[Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
Oh thank you
[Music]
for ITL be too hard to
explain I thought so yeah  It's better if
they can like fight against Somebody
[Music]
You are now Um unoficial staff member oh
yeay I don't get paid right
no okay no problem keep on explaining go
ahead
[Music]
so
Kore Kore apa
[Music]
FR Flo
do you be the
for me, I'm in control
[Music]
I'm Har
I don't know
[Music]
How come you've
picked a color or
just blue?  do you know how to play
[Music]
Oh WR yes this is WR WR Oh wait a minute read it
first I'll just explain it so you
'll see what color you have to
replace the white with  your color is
okay, so above you can just destroy the
white one,
OK? Then you change it to
your color. And then Kade below he will
cut out any color lerally,
but if that means my blue wall
can be cut later with Kana,
don't cut it Oh okay.
[Music]
OK, so don't fall. Because
if you fall, you'll have as much as
that will be in the
pack. If it's on the top, just put your
hands on it.
Oh, for the bottom, we specifically have
cutters, punch punches.  five times i tonjak
li
times Okay it's
understoodund okay okay TJ TJ
ton
okay three two
one
Oh
[Music]
F1 I can't cutry
okay okay
easy no no no no
[Music] [
Laughs]
[Music]
What happens
if  What
happened
fire I
[Music]
thought
Oh so the bottom People Have To F
oNe
yes ce
[Music]
[Applause]
Because it's hard at the bottom Siha
is like us  This could be
killing your own friend Yes
[Music]
and
[Laughs]
guys I do I do top again
only I do top again cuuse I need to
practice top anyway okay
[Music]
you have the shear the shear why do so
sad I am oh wait No I'm not s i happy
Okay
here The Purple one Purple Sil ha Take
Two and hold it like me hold it in both
Hands so that if it Breaks you Switch it
with  you
can
change straight away OK
OK don't forget F1 yeah I oneu
[Music]
okay
uu Hi five f three two
one eh let's go how ah sorry
oh eh
you can ancerin who has an opponent too
ma'am
Yes eh try and
me try and
me k k  wow
mustard Ketchup and mustard Yummy I run
out of Blocks
no Wor we R out of time to
[Music]
we for us to Count Count Count
sat 4 5 6 7  8 10
[Music]
11 7 9
nice nice
Oh God ah it's hard to count from the
bottom 28 for the
yellow so good counting 28 7 10 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17
19 20 21 I think we have 24 on
[  Music]
Oh I think we
do then that means I can count again
but Yeah but I'm not so  sure like Maybe
I'm wrong One Two f f
si
12 now They're gone Now I think They're
gone
but it was close
]
look too much
at yeah so
much
this and then next
[Music]
play uh Ma fight Can you join our Ma
fight Yeah but uh Can i be the Shooter
yeah for sure
Okay
sner She's G to headsot me
[Music]
okay hi
SEG
please come
[Music]
Hi I'm in
what's up
leave
monomo put it in the chest
[Music]
not Temp Ah
okay
[Music]
Buki Bu
Let's try
using ah She Doesn't she doesn't  'don't have
the mod yet What mod What mod
[Music]
let's try out the group vision first,
can't hear yaa
[Music]
k What do you say, I'm confused, I'm confused, you
can make your own group, guys make  own GR
vc as ok
really soce because I want the you so no
if you need to know something let me
know I can Translate I don't want to
like translate for you I don't want to
like make you feel like you're  not
saying it Well you're saying everything
well Oh no if anything I would
[Laughs]
love I'll treat you
me
first explain what it's like
[Music]
F
let me explain it to
you the team has a  fighter and a
navigator and The Key point  of the game
Is that the ter can
[Music]
so the navigator has to help The
Fighter Stay
Alive so the navigator has to
what the navigator has to help The
Fighter to Stay Alive to Stay Alive Okay
by navigating them by navigating
them
yeah yeah if the  fighter dies then the
team is eliminated
but if the navigator dies the team is
still safe but the navigator cannot help
The Fighter if the Who's dies if the
navigator dies the
team will not be eliminated but the
navigator cannot help  The Fighter How
can the navigator
die navigator can die because
NAV will be given
ars so the navigator will light each
other can fight other navigators or They
can navigate the
fighter or They can What they can
navigate the other
navigator can navigate the
Fighters and they can also  fight other
navigators Ok I see will
understand I
understand so basically the navigator
can attack other navigators Yes
heeh but that's like an option
actually you don't need to attack
other navigators like that.
Just navigating the team is fine, Dam
That's no we will fight
navigator
[Music]
origator noigator no Alligator
navigator or Fighter
[Music]
まで残ト
の So actually all the mini games that
you will play later are all
for
this fight  I see. So you guys collect the
Emeralds so you can buy
weapons like that for Ma's fight.
So actually it's all for this,
like that.  for Ma fight
Okay Well Kanade said the pressure is
too big, that's what he said
[Music]
did you tell them about the
emeral don't I don't think told Because
I don't know how in Japanese Can you
tell okay
okay で め雑
[Music]
go to Arrow
Okay okay and
[Music]
fight
SW Yes
hi
[Music]
and
Do you angry
trash trash
trash
[Music]
komidahi Oh
k koore
AMB the food
will come from the botom
[Music]
make a group for your group Ok you know
how to do it I know ok ok
[Music]
yeah you want to make
it Wait do we have a unit name
[Music]
GR group
hilarious group wow join
group let's go Te
Te let's go i Let's
gobobo shider
yes okay OK don't shoot me ok ok yes
okay SH
[Laughs]
[Music]
wait eh yeah wait what
is
[Music]
the kill
everybody Oh okay Hi
haiig Hidari left right
ehig right Hidari
left starting
okay eh oh
purple purp Purple purpleple or Purple
[Music]
or
ha Mir Mir
t t Wah go go  go
go
Oh
forward
forward forward let's go let's
go's
go [ __ ]
man [ __ ] man what the [ __ ] eh not
[Music]
toxica om my Om
my om om om
wow
Heh  eh
eh nice Mamy
nice nice
my yes yes yes
yes nice
Momy I know it she SH ye
[Music]
okay okay want to do it
again do you W to try to be a fighter or
you W
be or you
W yeah yeah to try to  try yeah
koci itu
suodod itu e Kore Kore take
new eh take new teh e
nengendii e how to drop Wi Awah What the
heck I forgot to
drop How to drop item
ha Oh
[Music]
yes
Hi
[Music]
hai sinii ro
Pam Pam one ST one ST okay
yeah oh F1
[Music]
Okay
ready ready
[Music]
Okay pink purple yellow yes yes yes okay pink
Purple
Okay
ready
ready let's
[Music]
go Oh  F1 is for Fighter ah F1
f1ate
F1 for
fighter no F1
F I think I think Fighter F1 because Oh
okay okay
okay
that's pink My PIN is pink okay My
PIN eh Cik Cik  Cik
Ok
y pink
man Yes eh ah cheap sick pink pink pink
cik cik
muras top top near
there anjir
[Applause]
[Music]
No
another f to
F1
Oh
[Music]
kas ya
De fight Fighter
n navigator
n navig navig
[Music]
okay
How
was
you I think is better as Sniper
yeah is definitely better as Fighter
I press F
before but you don't I thought you don't
have to press  F1 in game need to press
F1
[Music]
No great
Even though he's stuck guysal
[Music]
he's spaw camping to Spawn Camping spaw
Camping yeah
yeah Okay I guess there's only left to do
the block like  drawing game thing I
don't know what you Call It What You
call and guess
ah
so to be honest I don't know how both of
Us can participate since we need a
theme best I think this one works if Just
They um like you give  them  a word and
they just try to be as fast as possible
like one of them builds it and one of
them guesses it I think they don't
necessarily need an opponent true oh
wait Who's building in your team
uh Oh then you know Uh I I could Just
You know give a oh wait no we have the
undefined stuffs to
here need me I think this works we can
go
follow follow Let's get
W
just one color
one
stack two stacks
I think one stack is enough but
yeah yeah okay
[Music]
[  Music]
n  that's follow me okay follow you follow
followwa
[Music]
helping
yams you don't need to
ask people
[Music]
[Music] it's
like gamp huh
[Music]
we make buildings according to the theme and then they
wear out like they're already
okay ha yeah
Dar That means we  bakalangun
[Music]
if I ng they still hearakak
that's my victory and
Kanadui is still a
dog like this, that means it has to be and evenen it's
already n okay
okay okay okay okay ready ready set ready Okay three
two one
[Music]
Okay faster faster
faster follow Life Company yes Apple H
What did you say apple no peir Y no
banana No
TV TV Bunny Bunny akarium This is an aquarium
bottle bottle cat
yeah cat
Where I don  't see
the I was just guessing
an I know Big imagination
[Music]
okay that's
okay again
yeah
okay
kuing Mimi Mimi What is mimi mimi in
Indonesian cat only has one ear
like a chimney
[Music]
sucks  Sorry, I'm like drinking per
second G, that's like 13 Lit per second to
stay hydrated and so I don't cough
1 2 3 definitely told to undefend now
Kanade and I are a very
compact pair and one Brain
[Music]
Cell
[ __ ] come  on
okay okay let's
go ya s me
E Okay let's go
Oh
three fork sword sword sword let's
go copying Kara Oh my God it's so it's
so tall
eh What is this vitamin  C Spoon let go
Hormones uh Tri protin
trend pickxe What is this Let's
go
crossbow
no
forest flower flower
Waterfall
waterfall life is it to
H It's very hard I have to say really Oh
my
B janggar it will be easier if the
colors Ah i see  i
seeine say the
v v yeah let's go
yeah Ollie is yeah He's building up like
a Vine and you're you're over there
You're pointing at the Vine vines it's a
Vine Yeah  but that's so difficult Oh My
God I love just makes it so that we look
at the Vine
[Music]
here you made
arscece nice nice
yeah
yesanan m
Jordan You didn't realize like why is
there another here what does this mean
why are they so far apart?  It's
easy, okay,
okay, okay
[Music]
okay, easy, easy, easy, easy, later you will
think it's Aro and
the dog, you'll think it's an arrow,
oh what is undaven
eh let's go
yeah okay okay okay
[ __ ] Hai Jom J
[Music]
Okay Christmas Tree Tree
no pi pi  pi
[Music]
is it okay to answer in Japanese Cuz
like some like pickaxe is a difficult
word to know in English It should be
okay
yeah we might Change The Rules a bit So
don't worry
[Music]
we are Indonesians
and we go back and forth yeah jump 1 3 That's why
you help me yes yes this is it Mak OK
your task here is finished I
don't need it anymore Anjay no
joke Thank you yes that's it
twice thank you thank you
[Music]
ama
things to do in
here Thank you so thank you everyone
only goes to sleep No I I have to Oh
no we
haveal you still have time to sleep
[Music]
Where my
k you you really want  my kiss or do you
want la's kiss
[Music]
or kali kali
my does it hurt does it hurt It Hurts
Mommy it HS in my butt ah you
you you Your butt is something I'm I'm
done touching that you  're out of diapers
Now I don't touch your butt anymore Okay
thank youk
no cheating no cheatingatingating
[Music]
the group the group the group
OK
Kaka follow
OK follow
you Im special lesson for you
Im
sensesense
ha left right  back and
forth no
ja k an
[Music]
Ha
squat J hai squat
Yes
squat squat okay
hai J
OK
jump
[Music]
jump squat jump squat jump
It's OK mom I'm fine here let me play
with my friend no I want  to practice to
come this is Indonesia I'm musuk
give it okay okay
now
eh
[Music]
Indonesian kas
Ind y okay please just here on the Okay
jump  squat squat squat yeah
Hit hit hit Kore hit hit puk
puk OK jump jump jump squat squat
hit
I
run run run run run run
run
[Music]
No
it no
no Walk is
walk walk
[Music]
for Run run run run run
run Run run
run  hi okay okay okay jump jump
squat squat hit puk puk hit
hit run run
OK Hi that
[Music]
eh j
eh
eh 1 2 3  4 l wakar wakariasta s dua
ah Hi i nih San Yong
du EMP l one S two du three
three three four four four five five
five Hi
that's one time wah one time ikai ikai Ik
Hi ah Mami tensai
Hi times times W
okay okay Hi two  times nikai Nik okay okay
three times
w l
[Music]
times one time one time ikempaliah
okay
twice two times four
times F
times seven times
Eh seven
[Music]
times t
times tu nana nana
[Music]
squat squat
squat jump
l
hit run run
it jump twice
jump
twice Hi jump twice
Jik
[Music]
Hi
FR recovering
[Music]
covid three three
weeks What allergies or what I don't
know I already went to go to doctor two
so twice you want door twice
[Laughs]
i i
that I already drink all my medicineu
so
Yeah I think I just I  just need sleep So
it's okay yeah take it easy take it
easy no no no we still need to
learn yeah yeah
okay okay
left
right no wait before that hit
twice hit twice t t OK e squat
five
times
okay okay okay okay
josos okay
left right back and forth okay left right
back and forth
left left Hidari Hidari S Left W Hidari
left Ha okay follow
me left eh cig
cig
[Clapping]
left right
[Music]
back and
forth okay okay
back Hi  Left W Hidari Migi Hidari Mae
usiro right left
forward and
backward
okay
right W
Yes
right right left left forward forward back
backward squat jump
jump hit hit run run hi
okay okay okay tens
t k k k
k okay that's homework homework now
okay okay forward one
time forward sat one
once once D
OK go back once
a
nice triple jump
[Music]
eh
wah m chea
[Clapping]
okay
okay go forward once hit twice
forward forward  one
kaliuk ali nice
nice nice nice
throw
OK throw
[Music]
throw in Japanes m
n face
[Music]
left left
Ha
okay okay jumbi
jumbi one two years forward one right
forward one step eh forward once
forward once
forward once once once backward twice e backward really backwards
backwards backwards backwards ten eh backwards backwards us us
backwards ah twice
so left three times left
left kirit nice  Tia times left three times
strangkai Hai
right twice okay okay okay okay
okay jump one
[Music]
times one time
dak Hi
[Music]
face back eh Heh
back
De I forgot
thatot we don't
thatot I  face left tu right
[Music]
okay face
left left face
right face left
ha he
okay
okay face
Koko that
eh red color
red color red color
[Music]
red color
ak Red color
red color mel
that work to that
[Music]
work yeah
yeah nice nice okay
I
think Thank you for let
[Music]
me
okay maybe we are friends here m we will
fight each other you know Yeah I
guess I go easy on you you
[Music]
know it's just the game It's  just game
it's competitive it's not a game for me
It's a Real
Fight All right All right me and are
J nice Okay
[Music]
after
Maybe I will go go rest
yeah
rest sleep Time It's my sleep time
now Thank
you can I ask why you  why do you call
her
[Laughs]
I don't know I just like it's more it
Sounds
more How to say
besty
best
Oh wow
[Music]
Ok
what are you now not not but to her
[Music]
beat-hit S ka
kira ira ka
no no
nowawa
[Music]
yean thank you Thank you k thank
you
thank you thank you eh k eh what
thank you thank you thank you
thank you J Thank you
[Music]
ha madik
[Laughing]
[Music]
Hi
Thank you Mommy Thank you
Mommy No I mean I'm
fine
I I still can control my C
It's Okay It's just
like it's supposed to be okay I will
read the super chat  after i will
go Thank you mom Thank you for your
concern
[Music]
Ok I
will I think I will read the
superat bye
[Music]