[Music]
do
hello everyone
[Music]
shall we um
did each one of us introduce themselves
and the audience
yeah
shall we go by abc
ah yeah okay okay what
[Music]
you don't use that so often do you no no
it's not is that amazing
i like it i thought it was new yeah
um
yeah yeah
[Music]
i'm next hello this is claire fi mori
from whole live english what's up
hi nice to see you guys welcome
i am recovering i was i was a bit uh
under the very under the weather
yesterday i'm doing a bit better today
though and very excited to play with
some ladies yay anticipating
[Music]
but you're good with your mouse drawing
so
i don't think it will be an issue
actually worse with a tablet believe it
or not
i find that hard to believe
yeah i understand that yeah i really am
when you're not used to it then yeah
well we all have our tools of choices
you know
where did you get them from
[Music]
for introduction iris maybe could also
be enabled according to
this chord is
oh yeah okay discord
[Music]
it's iris
somewhat new um
halloween project hope v singer
they made it uh last month yeah for
those who don't know me hi rice
uh i'm very excited this is my first
time collabing with all my new senpai's
stop laughing
i'm sorry
that sounds
how confident are you in your drawing
skills
ah
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah i'm just saying
that seems to be a mystery
yeah i haven't i haven't drawn yet
actually but i've i've been telling
people my streams that yeah i'm i'm
godly at drawing but that was that's
just that's just me um you know put
giving putting a really um strong face
in front of them
i want to tell you guys the truth now
oh i i i draw with mouse i mean i do
have a tablet too but like girls and my
eye i can't i can't draw with the
tablets
it'll be interesting
yes okay
looking forward to your masterpieces
oh good question are we gonna like when
we play we'll meet everyone else like uh
it kind of been among us
that's a good idea
i think uh well but since it's like the
first
uh hollow full halloween collab since
iris joined i think for the sake of
having conversation we should not
mute okay okay as long as we don't like
give away what we're writing
yeah exactly exactly yeah
all right ina introduction
hello i'm you know my innerness from
home
yeah
i i like to draw
i'm looking forward to drawing a lot
today
yes okay
yes that's it
and
hello
phoenix this uh i've played this game a
lot now today even today i've played it
in a separate stream
and i'm playing it three times this week
so i would like to say i'm the master of
garlic phone um let's freaking go
indisputable
and with this stream i think we would
all like to give a big big warm welcome
to iris welcome to hello english
[Music]
i think we should start it off with
normal and
if we if we wanna we can because which
is six people so the rounds should
probably be pretty short we can try some
other things too but normal i think is
the bestest mm-hmm
three two one
i'm really on the spot now okay i
already thought of this one since i was
a girl
i have mine ready
i feel like like very wide broad
suggestions make for funnier outcomes
when they're open to interpretation
but mine definitely is not
[Music]
okay wait did i just give it away
sorry i don't know what i'm doing i
didn't do anything i didn't say anything
what we heard nothing you didn't do
anything
i heard nothing i really heard nothing
um yeah i was too distracted by my lack
of time
i was talking about my roomba i think i
left my roomba going in the uh
the kitchen
right
hmm
you're using a roomba
i have a roomba
i like to sit on it
[Music]
oh dear
i don't know what i'm doing
i got i can't know what that time is how
much time is that we don't have enough
time
half time
oh sh
um this is the warm-up round right
yeah yes
we have so much time to test so many
different things don't worry about it
right okay
i gotta warm up my
my drying skills what the hell is this
what do you mean what the hell is this
i i lost my drawing brain somewhere i
can't find it
no way you're going to do the best
things anyway come on
this is a hard one
5 000 years since i lost yeah i feel so
awkward drawing this okay
um
what time is taking girls
if you add a little bit of color it will
make it so much easier to recognize who
you're drawing
i hope this is enough
also don't don't write anything to your
drawings writing exactly
okay no
i can't put like an exclamation like oh
no
oh that's amazing
why is there so many of me
oh right
well now i know the rules what is this
okay uh okay this is easy this is
um
what is this
[Music]
oh this is adorable
um this is what i get from death
oh you guys you guys don't get to see
what i wrote here one second we will see
it at the end just kidding i'm excited
why is there so much about me
[Music]
without being
on the right side you have some tools
you can erase and you can also go steps
back
oh steps back okay oh you have a you
have a custom
picture as well that's nice i'm gonna
use this
nevermind oh yeah it does work i'm
by the way today i'm playing christmas
music on live stream i hope you guys
like those i was gonna put music on it
oh no
christmas music is so nice the bells and
everything ah
made me feel so nostalgic because it's
music that i went that i was using
during the christmas time
so nostalgic
usual oh god i don't have time
yeah not a lot of time here huh
not a lot of time
can you zoom in music makes me sleepy uh
no doing i think
okay
[Music]
fan artists love this girl
oh
[Music]
it would look like okay so there would
be fingers okay um
wow this is rough this is rough for you
guys
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yes artiste
i mean uh i forgot what what uh
nice weather today isn't it
it's very dark outside i can barely tell
oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait this this
cereal
now everybody will know who it is right
here can i always oh yes
what the hell
oh my god this is pretty
who throw evident
i mean i like it
i don't have a problem with it
um
you guys can't oh
i have my blocked
[Music]
thank you
no in this mode there's no points no no
oh all right
i am confused
so iris
how how does it feel after one month
until i have english
yeah
getting used to everything yeah
but it's everything still doesn't feel
that real
yeah
this is actually not real it is all a
dream iris wow this is one long
dream
wake up
there we go
testing
don't wake up the dream is so nice i
also don't want to wake up i've decided
to never wake up
[Music]
save me
uh
oh my hair yeah it takes a good
two to three hours styling it get ready
yep i woke up super early
sounds rough i thought that was like so
set in place you don't need to like you
wake up like this i wake up like this oh
it's even it's it's worse when i wake up
oh god it's all over it's like
does it tangle a lot do you have to like
are you straight
yeah
my hair brush my hair brush it gets a
lot yeah a lot of hair just gets wanked
off when i'm brushing it yep oh my god
have you seen those videos where people
clean their hair brushes out after like
two months or so and the water is like
brown
why
[Music]
after two months
please like two weeks
oh my god
well i think i'm done this is a
beautiful island no one will understand
it but yeah oh we're done
before you click
we should do auto so we all see it at
the same time normally i do manual but i
guess other displays okay
then three two
one
[Music]
[Laughter]
i get
you guys can um save save the album if
you click on the button to say that
someone wanna be on save duty or i i
will do it okay okay okay okay shall we
go to the next album
next
oh my god
what is
[Laughter]
i thought i couldn't think of anything
besides t-posing
i wasn't sure if that was even still
about um iris but i just put her in
there
so i guess i was right by putting her in
okay
how did you get started yeah yeah
oh
yeah made me think of christmas and i
was like hmm i guess i'll put iris in
there
because she loves christmas so much she
doesn't see it
for another day right
you will like it much more once you get
to know these five santas
us yeah
yeah become santa
become santa yeah want to go to the next
round
oh no
no you
oh
[Laughter]
that is so cute yeah kelly really
enjoyed that beauty
manga that we write together i liked the
plot and it was very dramatic i enjoyed
it
[Music]
thing and it got messed up
[Laughter]
yes
oh my god i didn't notice
beautiful there's a dolphin there or is
that shy
[Applause]
it's like a dog
next door
surrealism
the banana accident
not bad
oh my god
you wanted the chaos didn't you
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god i love this it's beautiful
everyone beautiful it was really good it
was a nice first round ladies yeah yeah
yeah yeah
super fast we shall do more
yeah
should we do another normal one
i don't know what you said what are the
other moons
well
the others are partially pretty
difficult um for example um i think
maybe sandwich could be interesting
people have been suggesting should just
suggest you
sandwich a lot yummy
tasty wanna do that one we can try it
outside and keep crying until the end
finally describe the last drawing we
will understand when it happens
oh is it going to like layer all of our
drawings on top
so yeah sandwich oh i see
i get it
i guess
[Music]
i think that's good that's a good one i
think it's good
i can't think of anything yeah that's
the problem i have that a lot too
i'm excited for your prompt everyone
yeah
i've got something simple
screw it let's just let's do something
fun let's go wow great that's something
crazy it doesn't have to be okay
oh yeah
i like this ah i see oh god the time the
time is ticking so quickly oh god okay
oh my god
i has idea
okay
[Laughter]
shut up kelly shut up
don't shut it up callie
talk i can't like i can't like remember
i'm crawling
uh-oh
i just feel like making it cursed
cursed is fun do cursed
okay you bet your girl you betcha
so how's this different from the other
one
i think we will see starting from the
next round
oh yeah art skills coming at you
yeah
i'm so
oh yeah
you're good
why doesn't i let you save your color
you should have like a custom color bank
you can save
yeah unfortunately
oh no i'm not gonna make it
i don't know uh
don't worry other people will finish
your drawing maybe
oh
oh that's a good idea so maybe we should
leave room for others
probably yeah i'm not short
okay
uh
oh my god i'm mistaken
okay okay at least it's recognizable i
think but all right
it's not recognizable
yeah
okay okay let's see what happens
oh
oh yeah
okay memorize it recreate it
oh my god everything is gonna happen
here uh this is really cute this is
adorable
thank you thank you
wait what
all right i got it we're going point for
point here
yeah
oh okay
i forgot the whole drawing okay
i think i remember
oh my god i don't remember i already
forgot i have a current brain okay
how am i supposed to remember that
also i don't even know what was going on
there
uh oh
gotta be fast oh oh yeah
[Music]
oh no oh god
um i'm so sorry
i don't want to control z
you can i can't i can't draw so many
people
oh my god i've been doing it
okay thank you
there was some something like that in
between wait one two three one
i don't have space
hey this isn't that bad i think i'm
improving i think we're seeing
improvements
ringing oh
now you wait for me game you wait for me
or i'll be angry
i'll be angry you don't want the no wait
huh
oh what's happening
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh my god what is this
wait does this time count as well oh my
god uh
what
okay okay okay what
all right this is a no-brainer
[Music]
what
okay didn't notice there was a
bucket oh wait no it didn't work
your bucket
um
something like that
this is really difficult
i like this game
i also enjoy this game
simplicity simplicity is the way to go
also there's like someone missing
oh man
oh no i actually still have time damn it
are we supposed to be this like
as accurate as we can
or yeah
yeah yeah much as we can remember right
and your artistic interpretations of
god
i'm so
done um
i captured the essence of it
that's the important
one
i actually had it
in early because there was no no more to
say
i guess the reference was just so simple
oh wait no no no no no
no no no no no i can't do this
i'm pretty sure is it sandwich i think
sandwiches like that
yeah
all right we're we're going we're doing
the best we can with the tools we have
what is this that's adorable i don't
understand what okay okay
it's hard to be able to talk about it
because i just want to make yeah jokes
about what i'm seeing
i think you can make graph jokes about
it
also afterwards we see it anyway so
write it down
remember
oh okay okay
yeah looking good ladies looking good
desire that something
maybe later
was it like this
i don't know what happened here
uh oh yeah
can we get like a pur
a different color
nice
nice oh cute wait
wait
feel like my drawing skills are evolving
through every single round yeah the
person who did that
yeah
doesn't have enough time i can't stop
time
just go back in time and absolutely
that's cheating
oh
okay
wow you're fair you're a fair player
nice
she doesn't use her skills like that i
respect that i always
mind i'm not gonna steal that you know
came up with that it's beautiful that
was a good one that was a really good
one oh
it is pretty accurate no i don't know
what happened
there's one more one more thing to do by
the way five out of the six so
and then then we'll see everything
yeah you're evil
i hope you know that
i love it what
oh
oh god
oh did you hear that oh that was my hip
bone
your hip bone
yeah you can't grandma
yeah grandma yeah
i have the same issues though i really
want that brace that you were talking
about i want a brace for my full body
yeah the shoulder brace to make sure you
don't hunch over like the hunchback
yes that would be nice that's a good
purchase you can get one of those gamer
rigs where you just lay back
should we go manual because it's been so
fast actually wanna go for it slower
let's do display mode manually okay then
you can open it up on your own timing
okay
i see
i was detangling her hair but getting
stuck okay okay
i think i did a pretty good job
wow
that's pretty cute yeah she has a lot of
things stuck in there
a lot of mascots stuck in there
so did we all get the same
the same
problem image i don't think so maybe we
did
some people's images had to memorize it
and then like draw it
yeah
let's let's check out goudas
did you know what was going on when you
saw that image do you have an ipad
i know i just thought it was iris
singing
yes she has that hopeful expression in
her face
all right let's see watsons
you're all going for the singing female
yeah yeah now we're just getting like
the music notes made it look like it
yeah oh
all right and iris draws herself
beautiful
oh my god but
kelly's saying what
i'm doing
dope vocal cords
[Music]
[Applause]
how about for each album uh each person
who led the album says next next next
and we follow that person uh you know
what i mean yes
okay
next is inna
what did i write comments
tomorrow
what shouldn't didn't it just start
today again
you know what happens when taco time
ends what why oh wait no wait only
only i can open it
sorry okay i'll open there we go
nice interpretation
[Laughter]
i see you around all the time there
oh yeah the paint bucket continued to
betray me over and over again
we have an opening i can see them
hey
anymore if it was alive or not so i
ended up drawing it dead
oh no well that makes sense according to
the first one oh
yeah
oh no rest
oh no
anyway
this is what happens when taco time ends
i guess so
okay
[Applause]
would you like to read your prompt
i know it's underneath the detective
desk
is
[Music]
oh yeah very confident i did it
perfectly
oh i'm sure you did
who is that
[Laughter]
he's like a spiderman
and what i thought when i saw that was
good i killed it
a beautiful progression of events she
looks so smug about it
[Laughter]
oh
ready for takeoff
[Laughter]
oh
my god
that's cool
[Music]
why do i look like among us
yeah
[Laughter]
they're
well i kept it very simple
having more input
the whole rocket thing just disappeared
[Music]
pac-man
like an artistic edition of pac-man
oh wow
wow
including amelia
[Laughter]
yeah i love the face on on all of them
oh my god especially the amazing
accurate
[Laughter]
my head
it's okay i think i think i saved you i
think i saved you kind of thank you
apex predator
apex
how am i supposed to follow up with this
i didn't have time
you know
maybe don't make a problem
i mean technically that could be correct
because
what battle
all kinds of battles yeah i have i have
magic powers
how many people have you killed until
now
i have no i hope i don't kill people
just saying
okay
you need to leave that to me ira that's
don't let me catch you killing folks i
will have to get you you guys are the
monsters you're the ones who kill
i don't know
all righty next up iris
please read your prompt you're a suspect
i'm an investigation
[Laughter]
[Music]
all right
[Laughter]
[Music]
i thought somebody would available
um
we have
redstones
a bit more i think we can squeeze in
another normal round yeah normal
okay because the first one was like only
15 minutes yeah
all right
okay
[Music]
um i think
check got any ideas
okay
all right i'm waiting for some
suggestions submissions
i hope i hope
so someone
really good gets that prompt
this is going to turn out amazing thanks
chad
okay
all hydrated
party time
was
[Music]
i like that
oh
oh uh
all right i'm on it
leave it to me
okay
not great i ran out of time my prompt is
possibly
interesting
no problem that's just that just makes
it better you know
okay hey maybe i left it really vague we
have to see what others come up with
oh boy what does this look like
um
so we have this
picture um oh gosh
uh
and then this one
okay to write a letter in this
since this is not background
wait this this is pretty much true
though
beautiful i feel i feel i feel it i feel
it i just feel it it's beautiful
um
[Applause]
[Laughter]
did not think about the composition of
this picture very well before i started
drawing it
um
maybe add some more color to this oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
no
[Music]
yeah well i mean
this is pretty easy
[Music]
this might sound better does this sound
better it sounds better oh that sounds
better
[Laughter]
beautiful all right what is this here we
go
what does that word even mean
what does that mean
oh easy oh
i just described one
oh geez
oh
i need to google someone real quick
uh
what is that
[Music]
no no no i'm googling no no i'm googling
this one
tell me what is that what is that i
don't speak this language of memes
okay i'll draw what i think is happening
okay um
i think i know who this is maybe
and if i could draw this could be really
cute what but i can't
[Music]
i need to try
uh
okay
okay uh
uh
[Music]
this
[Laughter]
are you good you're
are you good
[Laughter]
[Music]
just playing my cards real straight chat
check it out
who is this
this is okay
[Laughter]
is that a sword i don't know what this
says
[Laughter]
my eyes are no i didn't have enough time
oh what does this mean
yeah
oh my god don't make me draw so many
people again
i don't know what this means
oh
yes i do
of course i know what this means
[Music]
um
okay we can do this we can do this we
can do this
[Music]
okay
um
[Music]
i have given up completely
ah
never give up never surrender
this is what this animal looks like i i
don't i lost help even though hope is
right next to me
right next to a girl
did you just say i'm next to you girl
yeah oh wow
that wow that's i don't know that's kind
of charming
why is that charming
i don't know
uh-oh
there everybody's gonna know what this
is right yeah
yeah
yeah oh no
okay
oh my god
well we started out with
that's good
[Laughter]
oh
always dead in these things
[Laughter]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
god
looks like a sesame street character
muppet
going wrong
the
position of the lego was a little weird
to me
um
[Music]
the one where i started dying by crying
no
no no no i also didn't know what tea
bagging meant
this is what happened
what is that
he's putting his teeth
i started laughing when when i was
drawing his face
oh
wow yeah that's very you're going
banging bro
[Laughter]
oh
okay i didn't finish my prompt
this is the one you were talking about
yes i my brain um ah
leave it up to your interpretation
i know it was not much room for
interpretation
i mean that's pretty cut and dry
[Music]
oh it's the name it's the confusion it
is
[Music]
yeah i mean everything looks normal to
me background basically
good stuff
oh
[Music]
oh well you know it went it became so
hot that they melted into one body
i miss interpreting
return to monkey
yeah just so we don't get in trouble
the right person got that one yeah
good job
[Laughter]
wow
anyway
[Music]
oh that's a good one
same thing you understand each other
this is the the telepathy that we have
after almost a
oh
no time to draw
[Music]
i had a blast wow
i will send them to you afterwards
everyone can pick one to upload on
twitter or five or two two how many ever
you want yeah i have a lot of a lot of
gifts gifts about okay by the way how do
you guys
give gif
is
i usually say gif when i speak german i
think and when i speak english i tend to
say jeff
it was it was the pineapple on pizza
before pineapple on pizza was a thing
yeah
[Music]
we have
okay three
okay
who comes down
you want to go count down okay
please here yeah okay three
two
one
ba bum
[Music]
mascot plushies it's almost
it looks like or later today i think um
yeah
very soon like
what's 15 minus nine
uh uh
math wow wow that was fast
mathematical genius
[Laughter]
sorry is taking over
in plaster
well uh the boof and
page is go going up in approximately
five minutes
tweet on hololive english twitter is
coming out in i think 20 minutes if they
don't decide to put it out earlier now
but should be coming out in 20 minutes
right
yeah
[Music]
yes
that's big you guys 35 centimeters
[Music]
do we have a picture of yago holding
them i wonder oh
[Music]
for for imagination
yeah no other reason
we have a picture
some people don't think in centimeters
really i thought you guys were talking
about one no no no no
not yet
you know what these look like they would
fit perfectly in a t-shirt cannon they'd
be really good ammunition i think
they're pretty sure we can have a pillow
with these plushies oh
[Music]
no it does not come with juggle
unfortunately we're sorry but jagger
could honestly like just quit his ceo
job and become a model at this point
um
is that what it's called
i think it's that i'm not really sure
let's kick you
i thought it's like a like a magazine
yeah the models i was thinking
dq like dairy queen dairy queen
i'm craving a milkshake right now
milkshake yummy yeah that's a good point
when uh when we all eventually meet we
need to have a big pillow fight with
these oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah straight up cali
i don't really want to put them into my
luggage because they're gonna be big can
you are you getting all of them are you
gonna yeah they will borrow
your hair probably carry one as a
carry-on but then they'd be questioning
you
yeah they're gonna look inside they're
gonna rip them up and be like what did
you hide the bump
i cannot risk that dissection
oh no no please no um
is there anything else besides cotton in
there i will find it out i guess at the
airport
cotton
beans
i think it's more like the soft like
plushies
yeah they're really soft i've touched
them
[Music]
i have held them and i have touched them
i want to squish the face and distort it
yeah i've touched those as well they're
very soft
very good
all right well iris how how did you like
your first collab with live english it
was a lot of fun i loved like
everyone's art art levels are just out
of the world
i like it thank you
figures have a ton of personality
actually and that's not me being ironic
or sarcastic they actually you did a
very good job
thank you we are so glad to have had you
in this collaboration
thank you we'd like to collab with all
of you guys again yeah
of course it happens let's keep doing it
yeah
yeah i mean some of us just like me have
not done a one-on-one collab with you
yet yeah yeah yeah yeah
today was the first time for me to
collab with you
yeah
half of you guys oh
yeah yeah
let's do it soon
yeah
minecraft i want to play minecraft
minecraft money making i'll give you an
official tour of the en server so you
don't get too loud yet
look at everyone's buildings
we'd love to show you around yeah wow
yeah let me show you phoenixton i think
you might have actually already seen
traveled into phoenix
i think right
isn't it like the restaurant the
restaurant no no that's kfp but i heard
you stumbled into a big village
um
where you died
yeah oh by the way iris the hole that
you fell
into that we're all here um i fell into
that hole uh a few months ago several
times and lost a lot of things and i was
always wondering who made that dug the
hole
wasn't
my view is that no one has any record of
anyone ever digging that hold on
on stream but i kept it open because i
was like well
well i want the person who dug it to
fall into it but then iris smell it
we need to know who the suspect is
yeah who was it
was nothing yeah
they didn't open the baby it was hot
gonna be me she's in the summer
mm-hmm
so maybe once a month who was it i
wonder that hole of death
where was it
out of nowhere
like if you go through kfp back to like
spawn
a different different hole that's like
one block wide but uh five billion
breakdown
yeah it goes straight down it's out in
the middle of nowhere and when you're
just like really hard to get in there
yep
straight down i'll have to do something
straight down
up yeah no it must have been straight
down yeah yeah i am yeah could it be
somebody that got lost and they were
trying to maybe just uh make a landmark
or something or
no it's like really close to my house
what if you did it kiara you don't even
remember
[Music]
yeah it's a memorial it's an important
part of holo en history
does anybody have any like individual
announcements like maybe a stream you're
gonna do or something like that
oh yeah
uh so tomorrow um i have a karaoke
stream with a special guest a guest who
is not in holdo live oh so
you guys
check it out we're doing uh archived and
also unarchived streams so please
exciting
[Music]
thank you that's all i have anyone else
um
i'm gonna play
uh
the police officer officer
next week i'm playing minecraft with my
real mother uh on my channel
and it will it will actually be amazing
because for the people who don't know my
my mother is better at minecraft than
all of us here she's really good and she
will teach me um some stuff and we will
go get neva right together
how the farm never rides it will be fun
so my momma will be on our server for
one day
you girls are welcome to join in for a
minute and introduce yourself to my mom
i want to say hello
i didn't say you guys would want to do
that oh i i didn't think so okay go
ahead please please be welcome
my mom knows about all of you she uh
checked all of your streams out
oh i think of some embarrassing stuff
[Laughter]
no i didn't have many feathers back then
it was naked
thank you
okay anyone else with announcements
[Music]
i'll be streaming subnautica later on
today oh
ring fit finally got my little boy
yeah rejoice
no no not your virus just some healthy
exercise
all right we all need that
i'm looking forward to it
that didn't work out anything anyone
else anyone else
i have a
a morning show that i'm gonna be doing
hopefully week weekly but uh i had the
first one it's gonna be a sunday but
i'll be gone for two weeks after that
and then when i come back i'll do
another one
[Music]
i will be watching it it might be
archived but i will be watching it yeah
orlando this weekend yeah if anybody's
heading out to megacon in orlando
florida in the us of a uh you can meet
or talk to us or uh show up at our panel
i believe um
mine is tomorrow and kiara's is the day
after
yeah i'm on saturday on friday and uh
oh yeah if you if you can't attend it in
person if you have a ticket then you can
actually watch a stream of it so you
don't have to be there in person but you
still need a ticket there is a stream
so everyone we're looking forward to
seeing you that is the first one that
kicks off the halloween in america
conventions american canada conventions
tour
we're doing a tour i can't believe i'm
having a tour guys yeah
yes
it's so cool
okey dokey
okay so we say goodbye yeah okay yeah i
think the boots should be up by now
what's your move
[Music]
is up now thank you check out the prep
we'll post it on twitter
[Music]
see you guys
bye
[Music]
[Applause]
right