[Music]
oh
so
[Music]
foreign
dog
[Music]
hello kitty
hello welcome to
today's stream which is a bit different
than usual
well recently um
you know due to the situation that is
going on on the world i don't know if
this existed previously but there
uh now exists uh like online cream game
services bye
and so i don't know about other
countries but in japan crane games are
really really popular
and um recently it's kind of hard to
get there i guess for some people i
guess it's smarter to just do it from
home and there have been some services
who are offering such a thing and
uh you might have seen some of my
senpai's
doing streams in the past about online
crane games
so
um so for this site especially it's
molly
dot online uh molly.online
yeah molly.online and they actually also
uh they're in japan but they ship
overseas but they're also closing their
shipping overseas services soon so uh
please
check if you want to use this website
i'm telling you right from the beginning
that uh they might not
like if since this is being like um
shipped out
in january what i'm trying to get now
and you probably also want to have
and you might not be able to ship it to
your country but if you have a friend in
japan maybe you can send it to your
friend in japan and then
send it to your country wherever
um but yeah to explain what we're doing
uh recently molly online has had a
collaboration
with her life again and
this time it is so
old
it's like made for me because my
favorite senpai
is decorating five but my second
is marin senpai
sorry i'm not gonna say any other
numbers than number three number four
number five but the
top two my favorite are beccara
and mayan senpai so this is just
absolutely perfect for me
when i saw this i was like
my favorite couple my favorite pairing
my favorite two senpais
nibano
as well but these two these two
and there is like a bunch of things okay
so there's like um i don't know if you
paid i'll get it to reload
uh oopsie yeah
[Music]
okay wait i need to i need to still
understand this side
can i can i go there
okay okay so there's like tapas trees
it's like a wall scroll where it's
loading
with there's one with decorah senpai and
one with
marin senpai and one with both of them
wow what is wrong with my internet maybe
the page is like getting
crashed by all those people can you guys
not go
wait there's no one oh we can get right
into it
and by the way i was going for the
pillows but
um magical it's my first time how do you
make it
i was going for the pillow oh [\h__\h] okay
well
i have to keep on clicking it
i didn't even practice it
but this is okay um i told
i told everyone that um
uh i'm going to spend not more than 8
000 points
but oopsie um i have uh
checked my bank account and my salary
might have come in
my salary might have came into my bank
account so now
it's not 8 000 points it's 30 000 points
that i'm spending today
hi
yes here we go yep yep you didn't hear
me wrong
okay here don't mess up again yep go
over there
pick up some balls take the balls
throw them over there and we have to get
them into the
into the red hole okay
there's this system but there's also
other systems
this one seems more like it depends on
luck
i would say it's more about luck than
about skills
there's other other systems
where you actually have to get the
object to fall down
by the way what do you think about my
cursor i retweeted it on my twitter
so if you want to get that cursor go get
it
go get it so we're just gonna spend
those 30 000 points and see
what we're gonna get out of that i'm
mainly going for the
uh i'm mainly going for the
pillows and for the wall scrolls
foreign
you want the bigger screen what does
this look like on my
on my screen wait a second
oh why is it so small now one second
oh
no one take away my food please don't
take away my boof
oh stare
don't they go in my booth
okay whatever it's just gonna be in the
middle here
okay okay
yes there's apparently nine people
watching me
so by the way um
this is a limited limited merchandise
so go get it now or never
there's uh if you want to get it go get
it now
isn't this more just about like luck
this one though like there's not really
much i can do
but um yeah it's just bouncing around
everywhere
[Music]
they call it takoyaki they call it
takoyaki crane game
because it reminds of uh maybe you guys
know probably you guys know what
takoyaki is right it's those balls
where like there's a nice tentacles
in
dough in small ball form that's what
takoyaki is
ah no but i don't know where my balls
where my balls
i saw um also mario senpai and pekka
rasen by
streaming the other day uh trying to get
all these merchandises and wow pekora
senpai was doing such a good job like
she's really good with these kind of
crane games but she's also
done streams uh with these kind of
online crying games before and i
actually i wanted to do it anyway at
some point
but i did not expect such a
amazing campaign to come just at the
right time
so i had to i had to muk
you can actually ask for help too oh no
no
no no but yeah you can actually get uh
you can actually get help from the staff
they're actually mostly watching anyway
there's like stuff i think 24 hours
per day i think
as far as i know i created the wall of
false
four in a row i won the game i won the
game
i'd always go so far over there stop i
think i need some help
okay
i ever be dm to
quiet no problem i can fix that
i'm filling them all up nicely
thank you the magical hand of the gods
the ancient ones have come upon me
to bless me with more balls so i can
fill it up
[Music]
with
am i doing this right focusing but
because if i did a stream yesterday on
this one i was watching the whole stream
and she completed the whole collection
bee okay i'll go go
she completed the whole collector
so close so close
sometimes you're like you can get really
lucky though
saying oof that's so funny she's
learning so much english
from you guys
sometimes we get really lucky like this
ah so close
oh see come on we're not far away from
getting the wall scroll
oh my god if i'm gonna get the wall
scroll oh my god i'm gonna be so
i'm gonna put i want more than one wall
squat i want to put it i'm gonna
have it like on every side of my of my
house
i want one of those wall scrolls
but okay one should be enough one should
be enough we will we will
try to be um happy with only one more
squirrel
depends on how ah depends on how much
i end up with at the end
this is what i do with my first salary
yes yes yes
my first salary will be spent very
wisely as you can see
it's a very wise investment i must say
what else would i spend it for what else
there's no way a better way to spend it
but oh my god i'm i'm
so far off of the red hole again
please it's kind of lagging it doesn't
exactly
move with uh my my
my mouse movements my clicks
lizzie did
i think there's a leg oh yeah it's in
the hole
i didn't see the moment when it fell in
there
okay so i got it okay and then i what do
i do
how do i get out of the window
oh
one second
this is my first one we got it we got it
that was not cheating though that was
not cheating there's just a leg
there's just a leg we got the face
[Music]
wait wait wait
okay now i want the cushion now i want
the pillow oh nobody's playing this one
but the window is all messed up
and now it looks fine oh
oh they're just watching thank you
oh and there's already some balls in
there so this one is also with the boss
but later there's also some without the
balls
you know
i know that sounds wrong i know i know
thank you for the super chat
i know it sounds wrong i know
this but it's it it's just how it is
it's a pillow
well how else am i supposed to say it
also i'm i'm thinking like if i get all
three pillows because there's one for
piccolo senpai there's one from marin
senpai and there's one where they're
both on it
so i could get one for my for my uh
pc chair
and one for my bed
and one more for my couch
i wonder how big but they must they must
fit
my ass oh my brother is calling me uh oh
my brother
my brother my brother is calling me
sorry
i'm sorry
foreign
i will sit on you
[Laughter]
i will get you and i will sit on you
so you mustn't there's nothing wrong
about that
it's just it's what else am i supposed
to do with the pillow
okay
i already i already got the wall
squirrel so
wow okay i didn't think she would be
watching
i did not think thank you for watching
becca let's say bye thank you
i will get you i will get all your
merchandise
all of it my whole room will be full
with
your merchandise hey i would say
you don't need to
she might think i'm some kind of weird
creepy fan
which i'm not i'm not no no no no no no
no no no amma
i'm i'm her colleague okay oh that was
close close close so close oh my god
it's going well we're getting really
close there
now i'm building a wall on the left side
it's going really well next ball
park
get me that peck or a cushion ah come on
so close though
i have already almost spent
uh oh wait i think i already spent
eight thousand points
8 000 point is like 8 000 yen but you do
get
um a bike am i counting right yeah yeah
yeah but you do get some discount if you
charge
bigger amounts of money
come on please please please please some
people told me they got it like with
only like 2 000 points and some needed a
bit more
so it's really really all about luck you
know
the cocking is real oh yeah yep
yep it's worth it it's worth it
i mean look at those cute faces oh and
by the way
this uh this pillow and the wall scroll
uh were illustrated by the character
designer of shishirobotan senpai
right i'm not getting it wrong right i'm
pretty sure about that information
so it's some really really cute artwork
really cute
i wanted this come on magic ball you're
the one i know you're the one
almost almost come on come on
we gotta get it by the way my mom is
also watching the stream hello mom
mama what'd you
hello mama shout out to my mom
she's very very proud that i'm used
very proud that i'm using my money so
wisely
yay wow
wow we got the fellas
[Laughter]
[Music]
this was the the one i wanted the most
are these like playing being played
right now
no it's free
go get mommy insane bye i think she will
enjoy very much if i sit on her
oops ah i didn't see i only posted one
time
damn it damn it
damn it i do this again and again i keep
on messing up
[Music]
that would have been amazing if that one
would have made it in there that would
have been
legendary that would have been so good
i want the lucky frog that will get into
the
books of whole life gotcha history
whatever that book is going to be
wow this one must be blessed by the by
the gods of
i said no one are you depressed
[Music]
although there is one there is one
strategy
if you have too many balls on the left
side
then you could try
to ins uh to instead of going to the to
this side of the balls
go to the left side of the balls and
then
grab one of those and move them around
and it usually works really well
but that is like the your last resort
when just nothing works anymore
when you already have like 5 million
balls and on the left side you know
i'm grabbing those balls and i'm gonna
put them into the hole where it belongs
to the red hole
for mario senpai
[Music]
itadakimasu
in january i shall sit on my favorite
senpais
just as how i always imagined it to be
oh god the points the points oh i don't
want to know
how how much points photograph i spent
ah this one moved like all around the
place
guys you're confusing everyone with
bottom left
i don't know what you're talking about i
don't know what that even means
i don't know what you're talking about
could i maybe get more than one ball for
once can't be that hard
come on come on
come on actually i'm really glad that i
i'm doing this on this day and not
yesterday because yesterday i think it
was
a bit more waiting time because everyone
got so excited and everyone tried to do
it at the same time so
the booths were kind of busy but now is
the right time
and there's lots of support from the
godly hands off the staff if you
ever like need some more help some more
support
there is a godly staff hands
that will help you and guide you
to victory to cute pillows
and basketballs and keychains and what
else was that
but i think there's like buttons badges
keychains was there anything else those
four items were
[Music]
oh what getting really close i feel it i
feel it
i feel it it must be close the day where
i can sit
on mounting senpai it's close
it's so close i can feel it
um by the way
uh while we are uh
getting closer to sitting on money and
senpai
i might as well share some information
with you
next week
with money senpai
and me and me
and it will be once again
off collab we're meeting up
in real life and end and
and suddenly suddenly i am
staying
over we're having a slumber party so it
will probably be two streams one of hate
on her channel
and one on my channel
so i am currently thinking about what to
do
and by the way it will be a weekday
um yeah
uh i'm a bit nervous about that uh
staying over it is making me a bit
nervous
dropped two balls no
i'm a bit nervous uh i'm the i'm an
outgoing type of person but
staying over and we're meeting for the
first time but she was like we're
talking about collabing for a while now
and um finally we have found the time to
do so
and so cool so close
and we were talking about what we could
do and actually i invited her
um besides talking about collabs i
invited her to to just um
go to i guess
like uh have a date together i invited
her on a date
just to hang out you know it's
and then she was like oh well if we're
gonna go on a date then we might as well
also
stream on that day it was like oh yeah
yeah good idea and then she was like oh
you want to come over to my place you
want to stay
over and i'm like oh okay
how can i turn that offer down
yep it was from her side i invited her
on a date
and then she was like oh yeah let's just
do the collab then let's also
let's also have you stay over at my
place
yeah why it's the first time that i'm
doing um
a collaboration with a japanese senpai
the first time and
the first time that the first collab is
a real life collab and let me tell you
this is not normal
this is not normal no but and and of
course i didn't forget about subaru
senpai
tori hollow birds revival
must happen again sometime during this
year
am i really bad at this for some reason
i'm really bad at this i realize
ah please come on now there's this one
no no no oh
i want the money pillow please i've
spent half
of my um money now
half of my points have been
sent out to molly online thank you
please take my money take all of it i
give it all to you
because you will bless me with the most
comfortable
comfortable pillows ever
[Music]
mohammed
it's okay what are we gonna go for after
this though
um we already have two pillows then if i
get this one
then we have
please come on
no i did it wrong again
but maybe we can do our strategy now
come on
maybe we should do it again should we do
it again
should we do it again
that might actually work no okay let's
go to the right side
please please please
give me sexy marin senpai
please please
bless me with her beautiful face
oh come on come on
paint pickle paint pickle
[Music]
sexy boomer pirate
holy guy please
come on come on come on come on come on
yes yes please assist me please assist
me thank you thank you thank you see
sometimes this happens
oh they're adding balls now
this sometimes happens some money
they're adding balls and now i think
what they want me to do is grab
on the left side i think right
no no okay let's probably still want me
to go to the right side
madame the god's hand
the ancient ones as one would say
i hope maybe this will be helpful
because like it will bounce off no
no okay okay okay come on one more
one more and then i'll try on the left
side one more
one more and then it should be filled up
well enough to go to our desperation
uh strategy
come on come on okay okay okay
okay let's try on the left side
okay will this work
thank you thank you thank you i really
appreciate it
thank you very much thank you
thank you i need a very urgent leak
so again i think now we have to go to
the left that he
they're filling it up very nicely
[Music]
okay okay okay
um to say it stay right there just
go straight into it go straight into it
come on give it to me
there's a lag there's obviously a lag
but
yeah we got two balloons we got two
pillows
and now they're cleaning up all the
balls
yay
okay and now i want a marine wall scroll
[Music]
maybe let's see if this one is open
i did not i did not no problem wait one
moment
one second i don't want to show you
anything weird it's
high any any other copyrighted
things that are on the side because it's
not only whole live goods
it's also many many many other
uh things that you can get here many
many ah
oh what the hell i opened my own stream
for some reason
stupid
uh marine vessel which one is
this is probably gonna probably gonna
use the rest of my money on this one
okay sometimes they leave booths um
not empty but like with a few balls in
there
left in there oh two balls two balls two
balls
thank you for the super chat thank you
for supporting
my simping activities
i'm one of you one of us one of us
i'm one of you guys
but i have a good feeling with this one
the boomer pirate has
blessed me with her blessings
i feel the luck flowing through my
body are you guys looking forward to the
collaboration between
me kiara and the best pirate in the
world marine senpai
is there anything you want us to do i
thought i was thinking one thing that
could be fun like i want to do things
that are like
uh really only possible or like maybe
not only possible that work better
uh if you're doing it like in real life
so
um i was thinking we're gonna play since
we're doing two streams
one on one in the evening one in the uh
morning time i guess
and so i was thinking one of them must
be
ring fit adventure mode
but the other thing i just can't think
twist it
you will not see anything you have to be
realistic my friends
marin senpai might have a 3d body
already but i do not possess
such a magical thing yet has to be
something
that i can also participate in
so what should we do
drunk stream but i don't like alcohol
at all i i am sorry i really don't like
alcohol
although people often think sometimes i
i have a kind of a crazy face going on
and then people think i'm drunk
i am asmr yeah people keep on
recommending that
and um i listened to marine senpai's
asmr
oh my god when she when she let us
listen to her heartbeat
i was falling in love all over again but
generally i'm not a big fan
of asmr i don't know it feels really
awkward to me drawing stream
but that is something that maybe even
works better
over discord with two pcs than as an off
collab because usually you only have one
pen
on a on a pen tablet
only really one person can draw at the
time
i would say okay
that is okay i will actually um maybe
i'll consider that but i just recently
did that with nana senpai and i want
something more original actually
and something more where we can talk
and karaoke would be very busy with
singing all the time so
i'm not too sure about cooking uh so
many people already recommended that in
my members
stream but cooking you will not see
anything
[Music]
chest you guys in your chest test is
something
that me and ame must tackle together
we must do it together it is it is
destined
to be me and ame who play the chess game
it must be me and ami
yeah actually i think that was one of my
ideas too
ah no you lost both
why did you not grab onto it stronger
why
why why
to the leg the leg i didn't see oh [\h__\h]
right in the middle i didn't see such
lag with pork i stand by stream to be
honest i think there's something oh no
oh no oh no
no i think it's something with my
browser or something on my connection
normally it doesn't have such a huge lag
english class you know
um i know madden said by really wants to
learn english and i know that would be
fun
but i am the only hololive english
member
whose first language isn't english so
does it really make sense if i teach her
english
like out of all the members who could
teach her perfect english
why would it be me
oh think about but that again is again
something that could be easily done
in a normal collaboration
horror game might be nice because we can
sit next to each other and i'm like a
real chicken when it comes to horror
games i love phoenix though i'm not a
chicken
i just say it you know because this is
how the english language works
it means i'm scared uh when it comes to
horror games
um i could really use someone sitting
next to me
and like supporting me mentally
foreign that's my name i like
boys love stuff
i'm more into the other one
[Laughter]
she's into that but i want to read girls
love stuff
but i never read such a thing before
okay you guys don't believe me but i
never read
a girl's love dojinshi or anything like
that before
leather okay believe me it is just
something
something i appreciate secretly
no really dude you don't believe me
again you don't believe me
but i think horror game actually might
be a good idea i mean halloween will
already be over by then
but yeah um
yuri versus voice lover oh
and she's mixing them up thank you thank
you thank you because i i keep on going
into the
i know i praise it one second well we
gotta go for it okay let's see
yeah why do i keep doing this but maybe
actually maybe that works huh yeah just
drop it there
they must be thinking wow she's such an
amateur
because i think this site is used by
many professional
game crane game players
and they must be thinking i'm like
really [\h__\h] at this
oh
it's not really what you're supposed to
do
are you winning canada i think i'm
winning i already got
two pillows and one wall scroll
but at what cost kiara
at what cost okay
you guys gotta send me recommendations
on twitter for
a horror game that would be good to play
uh on one pc with two people
yeah but um actually it has to be one
that we have permission to but oh i
think we have
permission to quite a bunch of we have
even got phasmophobia permission
recently
but i don't know that looks very scary
so yeah maybe we'll do that at the
evening stream and then in the
wake up stream we will do the ring fit
adventure
a good day starts with a good workout
done by two people girls with
absolutely zero stamina come on
why you keep on going into every other
hole but the hole that i want
why why come on
yes i i i confess
i have absolutely no stamina
but this is a good opportunity to get
our
sexy bodies moving
and then when we're both drowning in
sweat
we're gonna take a shower
oh thank you for assist
hi hi guys
i'm running out of points please help me
and i didn't say we're going to take the
shower together but madden senpai
probably might even offer it to me
thank you ancient ones for your help
for your gracious help in my quest
of probably not completing this because
i'm too bad at this kind of stuff
it's actually my first time even in game
centers oh free
freedom
um uh
yeah even in game centers i rarely ever
uh try out these screen games
and yeah i don't really have many skills
when it comes to these things
by the way i think you can even change
the camera uh
angle maybe not on this one but on the
other ones oh come on
should we go on the left side hit
there's already a lot of balls on there
wait one more time on the right side and
then we'll go to the left side
muay kai
they must be thinking what the [\h__\h] is
she
doing wasted
what's 250 points probably yep
waste it
i thought that at some point it just
stops moving over there
so it doesn't get out of the range
i thought you can't even go over there
ah
oh no i have so many wasted
tries already i have six
six thousand five hundred points left i
started with um
thirty thousand
yes you get left side i believe in you
come on please drop a ball in there come
on come on
come on come on no no no no
come on assistant
thank you thank you for assisting such a
noob
as me tascarimas arigato
wow wow so many balls
this is it the time has come
for the marine wall squirrel
oh wow i mean i cannot possibly miss
this opportunity now
come on come on come on come on come on
come on come on come on come on boom a
pirate
[Applause]
please
happiness this is how it feels
ah this is beautiful
now we got two pillows two wall scrolls
maybe we should go for something small
uh i think i'm gonna go for a keychain
but maybe since we probably
can only afford one more
because i suck probably we should go for
one that has both in
it see uh they have key chains with each
character and
uh that's that's something else so i
think we're gonna go for that please
please be free
yay another one of these
i promise you there's others as well
let's see this one is a bit cheaper by
the way i think the other ones were 250
yen
and this one is 150 yen per uh
playthrough and by the way if you got
like a lot of merchandise
you can send it together and i think the
it
will be cheaper if you um send a lot of
merchandise together
but again okay you can currently you can
send it overseas as well
but they're closing the overseas
services
very soon so please check the
information on that before
getting right into it unfortunately
they're closing
they should keep it open for you guys
what if
one day maybe there will be a chiara
keychain in there
also have you realized there the the the
arm has
only two is it broken or is it supposed
to be like that it only has like two
two of these red thingies
[Music]
is it broken it's supposed to be like
that
it's broken so moon
okay okay i don't think they would leave
something broken there so
should be fine but interesting
interesting choice of design
maybe it works better
[Music]
it only has two they're all like that
okay okay okay okay okay no problem
we will get it anyway i want this
keychain
give it to me please please please
i want this cute kitchen and put it on
my bag and then everyone will see uh
this is kiara kiara with the
piccolo and modern keychain on her bag
yeah might be easily recognizable
i don't think there's many who actually
put it on their back and go outside like
that
people people have to show it openly
their support
for these beautiful girls i mean what is
there to hide
you have to show it also those fan
t-shirts
i got a peculiar t-shirt i wear it
outside sometimes
so what i have a bakura t-shirt
i'm not ashamed to show it
i'm not ashamed of it
so what show your feelings
show your simp emotions
openly there's no need to hide it
don't be a coward wow that's so bouncy
please i have about 4
800 points left maybe maybe if we're
lucky we could probably because this one
only costs 150 yen
per purple so i might
be able to get another one hmm
the police will fill up the holes for me
dear ancient ones
just kidding gotta do it myself
gotta do it myself
i barely spend anything on this one not
bad
okay we can do one more should i get one
of these badges
but i prefer keychains i don't really
like
using the the buttons the badges
someone is playing one second let me
find the right one
uh but maybe maybe we should at least
get the one
where both are on the on the combat
what's up let's come back to in english
this one this is the chosen one oh and
there's one ball already in there okay
okay
this will be maybe the last one
what is it in english what a bad first
try
oh no oh oh it went in there anyway and
we got actually two balls from that
nice not bad
i already got two pillows two tapestries
right
or am i getting it wrong am i missing
out on something important i think i
already got it
[Music]
i probably don't have enough points to
get the the collaboration the double
tapestry anymore the wall scroll
so i'm just going for the small things
now
yeah i wonder where the the ones are
that are not takoyaki system
i don't i don't know why i keep on going
for the takoyaki ones there's others too
where you like actually have the box the
object
on like uh some some
what what you call them uh
sticks sticks when in doubt
use the word sticks wow so bouncy
holy [\h__\h] stop being so bouncy unless
you wanna
bounce into the red hole i'm welcoming
that very much
please
please please come on why am i why do
why do i keep on going for like right
the middle and i can't even
catch them properly but okay as long as
i'm getting some balls
boing boing boing boing boing boing
boing boing boing
come on make me proud molly online make
me proud
please bless me
bless me with this beautiful merchandise
oh this once i receive them
i'll unpack them maybe i should do an
unpacking
unpacking video if i receive them in the
mail i'm gonna do an
unpacking video for you guys
i mean i already know what i'm getting
but still would be
exciting anyway oh
and then i'll bring it personally to
marin senpai and get her to sign it
yeah this is what i shall do
use my power at least i'm at least okay
at least i'm using my money on my own
money on this
i know but uh
it's okay to get a signature from my
from my senpai right it's okay to do
that
right
[Music]
is that um yeah it's okay
it's okay actually i could get it from
piccolo
as well i guess i was just thinking
because i'm visiting mine in senpai but
that's way before i'm actually getting
the merchandise
this is going so well
asking the japanese viewers if they
already got everything what they wanted
out of molly
online stop eh
tonight tonight
come on japanese bros
try it now i will send my good luck
charm to you
good luck
[Music]
now or never don't wait for it don't let
your dreams be dreams
just do it
so you caught up
i believe in you i believe in you you
can do it
i know you can do it i believe and you
guys are so much better at this than me
i'm pretty sure about that
oh i went quite far no problem
get in there really deep get all those
balls only one again
no problem
oh
what what's bottom left what did i say
again that's bottom left
ah oh balls balls balls
balls thank you
well they're privates all watching my
stream right now
and focusing on my horrible horrible
crying game skills
and they're probably laughing at me
they're probably standing in front of
that crane machine and like
she's horrible at this
anyway it's okay
it's okay i already got a bunch of stuff
i'm happy with what i'm getting
i couldn't be happier
i i didn't expect to get so much anyway
yeah this one is really i would say just
look i
i think but the only thing that i should
maybe improve on
is uh not clicking the buttons
properly and not only for one second
i've spent how many uh uh wasted how
many tries on
doing that stupid mistake
today
[Music]
there we go once again but maybe this
will work actually there's quite a lot
of balls here already
come on no okay oh well we moved it to a
different place to a better place it's a
better place there
the ball will be happier over there
don't worry on the about the ball it has
chosen a different path
it has chosen a different destiny
it is allowed yes yes yes i mean who's
going to stop me from doing that anyway
it is totally allowed though it's a it's
a strategy out of desperation
if it wouldn't be allowed they would
force you to go at least a certain
distance you know
no one can stop me try counter on this
one is already on 20
damn ah
i think soon soon we need some
assistance from the gods i'm down to 2
000 points
see i don't really see how far it goes
because it's laggy
that's a bit difficult
but okay it works
please come on come on come on give me
my button
[Music]
sorry
well we should make it we should make it
before my points ran out i
i hope i hope i hope i hope cookie
oyonde
read the atmosphere please my dear balls
please come on this is the last bow
i believe in it i still have points but
this must be it i i know i feel it this
one is special
this is one of the special boys no
it wasn't i have been deceived
actually this is fun though actually
this is fun
i hope they're gonna do more collabs
with whole alive there has been uh
previously also collaborations with
hollow life and molly online before
so i'm pretty sure there's gonna be more
in the future
but nothing there's nothing in the world
that can top
this collaboration except maybe a
halloween collaboration
except maybe just kidding no there's
nothing better than marine and pecora
by collaboration okay i literally filled
every hole
except the red one
akaitokudo
[Music]
it has no choice but to go into that
hole come on
three balls two balls one ball
[Music]
nice nice guys molly online
son arigato gozaimashita
thank you so much
thank you thank you
so we have uh one
peculiar oxen by pillow one marine scent
by pillow
one peculiar senpai uh wall square
one magnitude empire was grown one
uh piccolo 10 by n martin sent by a key
chain
one and one batch
with both of them as well right i think
that's all we got
i know that in one hour spent
spent my my first
my first paycheck very well invested
this is
what you do with your first paycheck as
a virtual youtuber
spend it on other virtual youtubers
curious
i hope you will all do the same make me
proud of you
make me proud go to molly online
by the way this is not sponsored this is
not sponsored but
use your money wisely
hot security well good to meet you
anyway this was a spontaneous stream
that was not on my schedule but i really
enjoyed it i'm really glad
that i did this gotta be spontaneous
sometimes you know
gotta be spontaneous i'll see you all
tomorrow on the minecraft stream
uh i'll leave the the um super chat
reading
uh on for tomorrow we'll read everything
that came in this stream tomorrow
morning
minecraft stream i'll also be playing my
first ever
horror game tomorrow around this time uh
probably maybe even the same time slot
i'm not sure
i'll be playing i never played the
horror game before and
i really didn't want to but it's
halloween it's spooky time it's
booktober
so what choice do i have right
it's just fits well and it's halloween
night and instead of
sitting at home and watching netflix for
hours and hours i should be playing a
halloween game that uh spooky game
that's what i thought so
yeah we're playing a craven mainer
someone recommended it to me so i'm
gonna play that but also
the holo ian collab oh i will also show
you that the
the the sweet that i got from emilia
uh we will also be playing a spooky game
uh for our holo yen collaboration on
sunday
if everything goes well
this is
sunday one o'clock p.m
now let me uh show you
another one of the sweets before i leave
you which one have i not
shown this one i probably haven't shown
yet
hey another piece of the puzzle is
cali's boobs i think sorry i said it
already but
when i see this i cannot not say it
this i'm so glad i have this piece of
the puzzle
very loot puzzle piece uh um by the way
i did not ask for this
amelia gave this to me and i think she
understands me very well thank you
amelia
i love you i love you thank you for
giving this to me
you understand me just oh too well
thank you amelia watson for the people
who don't understand this
uh amelia and us we together have
been doing some kind of puzzle thing at
the end of every stream of uh
member of everyone's uh streams wow i
can't even speak english at all i can't
explain this
at the end of every stream of every
member from holoyen
this week except the members only
streams and there will be
a piece of a puzzle and at the end it
will be a big picture but we will show
it to you at the end as well but
yeah it's like a scavenger hunt you have
to collect them all gotta catch
thank you for watching today i'll see
you tomorrow and in german
we say
[Music]
i had lots of fun thank you molly online
for letting me
stream your services
i'm looking forward to getting my
goodies
in january and i'll be making and
opening
the package video or something maybe
thank you pee pee
pee pee pee pee pee pee pee
[Music]
[\h__\h]
my
[Music]
do
i know that i'm not here that by the way
this is
[Music]
i love you