[Music]
so
oh i'm gone she's gone
hey guys my name is kalai pimori and
this is my stream now welcome to my
channel i've rebranded with a new color
theme just so you know
teal and orange are my new favorite
colors
um anyway i'm the owner of this stream
uh it looks like there was some
confusion i will be streaming um on my
own
[Music]
some i saw someone saying there's been
one
a probably more than one year since the
last time we met irl oh wow because i
left japan in like february 2021
it's been over a year
what oh god
your water life vest is underneath your
seat exactly wow you're prepared wow
there's actually no swimming invest
under our seats though
there isn't
i just wanted to flex some germans that
i learned
there
was something pretty good i didn't know
you you you waited until now to tell me
that oh unterfelt ha ha
sends and fro
wait where did you get that from you
taught it to me it means reaper it means
the grim reaper lady oh my god sense and
fall yeah
it sounds i feel like it sounds cool in
german yeah i know right hey what's up
this is the sentence brow here to take
your soul yeah
finally
uh takamori is back together in real
life it's been a long time
and because of that i want to make use
of the location to play games that are
local co-op only or
should be played in local co-op and for
that occasion
i downloaded sniper clips yeah i don't
know what this is it's cute also why am
i on obs let's go to sniper cleats yeah
sniffer clubs and we can also play
supermarket streak oh that's the one
where you scream a shit-ton
i played that before with um gooda but
it wasn't local i think it will work
much better with loco
uh and then we might wanna play super
smash brothers too oh i'm down let's do
it yeah i like games yeah we're using
you know the the tiny ass controllers
from the switch both of us have one of
the tiny ones such a baby one yeah not
easy to play super smash brothers with
that i
think it out of it i don't know how to
play super smash bros with that yeah i
don't know how to play the new ones so
it's okay we're pretty much evenly
meshed i think okay
well then i kind of want to start with
snipperclips because it's kind of chill
i think yeah i don't really know at all
what this is so let's do it i'm down
hold on you press
i think you have the a
i'm in control
yes preparing software here we go
snipper glaze yeah
this game has an autosave feature
so you have seen that before no no no i
just see that they're popsicle people
now when i'm looking at the title screen
they're like weird like upside down yeah
like they're cute they're like cylinder
popsicle or cup people
they're clips you know the clips that
you use to hold together the paper
yeah that looks nothing like a [\h__\h]
paperclip
yeah
you'll see you'll see
i guess that's the perfect color uh
i don't know
super clear helped me out with microsoft
1999 back in the day they look very
different when i do a pair of controls
do you have to press a different hold on
a second
up here control
okay eleanor
oh i see how it is okay
oh yeah clippy see chat remembers clippy
mine was acknowledged okay and then oh
and then s oh these are yeah those are
got it yeah okay
slam dunk
and then you have to press a i think
okay
press this button don't press through
when you're ready when we're pressing it
what do you mean press l plus the r uh
i'm even from this perspective oh no
yeah yeah okay okay we gotta turn it
around slam dunk
oh i'm so
yay wow i hardly get to play these kinds
of games yeah i'm always so salty when i
look for co-op games and it's like oh
this one looks cute let's play this one
and then it says local co-op only are
you kidding me
no problem
because here we are now in the same room
yeah i meant chunkers and smoothies yeah
she loves chocolates and smokers she
wants to steal them
no i'm taking them from you i know we're
joking about it but like i am taking
them from you so ah okay okay
no you cannot but you're welcome to uh
join any time again kelly's mike is
picking up bgm no i don't think so but
um no no it's just that i have double
bgm going on oh whoopsies excuse me now
it shouldn't be double anymore yeah
we're sharing a mic
maybe it should be a little bit louder
mike's here no no no no
the microphone is okay
yeah yeah
please hold your joycon as shown
press any button okay
am i pink now oh we should switch we
just wish i'll be yeah we need a yellow
one okay i'm the pinky okay yeah this
makes more sense
[Music]
that's
you had eyebrows for days oh we have to
cut first ah oh okay
yes
yes i got you fan all right here we go
um
let me press and hold it to reform oh
wait press this to cut yeah okay
and i'll cut you yeah give me a little
snip snip snip this down
oh my god did it hurt oh sorry not
necessarily
are you watching that screen i'll make
it bigger for you oh thank you
thank you
hold on we can figure this out press s
rotate yourself rotation what
i see
it makes such strange faces like a mix
of like
pain but then they also kind of like it
lovely
yeah we need a nice shape together
that's so cute we can jump
oh my god what game was that that i
recently played where i couldn't jump
but i uh um
uh stanley's parable i was so sick
and tired of not jumping oh yeah you
should play some earlier souls games
there we go
teamwork this is the way that it should
be
together and you can do anything kiara
hell yeah
i believe you can play the tutorial
again
thank you
we got it down
we're going to the right side we're
super good but now we're
[Music]
okay yes you can play with more than one
we need to meet up with some two players
let's go okay let's do it
noisy notebook the rules don't apply in
this notebook oh
shape match baseball and
make the cook
is this like minigames i just wanna
flicker or is this like is this what
we're supposed to play this is a story
mod
is very did you get do you guys know
you guys know
5 000 years yeah ready go go okay are we
on a time trial oh wait oh no we just
have to fill up as much as possible yeah
let's turn us around gotcha
there we go there we go wow
and what do you want us to do should we
cut
[Music]
that okay here we go now here's what we
here's what we do
i'm gonna get below ya
i'm gonna crouch real oh yeah we have to
turn around too i think to get the
corner yankee all right hold on a sec
here we go i do my little turn spinny
turn spinny spin spin and then i crash
like a like a real yankee yeah
right there and then a little smooth
why did he make that slide also there is
no story mode according to the chat all
right now you uh oh should i cut that
part too
wouldn't you want to cut a bow here and
then true oh fact yeah
you're not even wrong
on your eyes it's so cute
okay that's not quite and i'm still
missing some parts all right hold on no
no no no no no no no no thank you
hold on
oh wait but uh no i'm good i'm good now
you there's like a little part there
oh yeah
almost
wait i can jump right i can jump on yeah
or i can crouch and then yeah yeah yeah
if he crashes
like around here your face looks like
these faces are making better costumes
i love them
okay all right we finally got it if this
is not perfect and i don't know what you
want from me yeah
yes a bird like you nice
we got that down
beautiful that was it took us some time
to figure out but now i think we
understand
baseballing let's go
actually we met
yesterday we had dinner
yeah we had a spa day together yeah
today we had spa day yeah it was dope it
was really really really comfy county
fell asleep like most of the time
i had a little i had a little glass of
sparkle oh i see what we're doing okay
okay okay
and of course tiara wanted the
the juice
which i thought was cute and we talked
about hot goss
what which is gossip
oh yeah the hot glass
depends on what you consider gossip i
want to know how like problems yeah
problems i also asked yeah i'm telling
you about the money showed you that
awesome ritz carlton
plays yeah i have dream places
i don't think this is the best
[Laughter]
oh this should be much easier i'm sure
jump jump jump
dribble dribble the ball if i just get a
little tilted though
okay no problem here's what we do and
then do a little tilt filthy we'll see
oh you can still wait
so press the sr so on the top of your
controller oh i mean when you turn
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah make a little space and
then we just kind of don't let it go
marry the baby
the little baby i love the stumps
[Music]
[Applause]
okay and then i'm gonna jump for the
slam dunk okay yeah okay okay i'll trust
you i'll leave it to you yeah get more
of a baseballer no basketballer yeah i'm
confused about this because i don't know
what sport ball this is it basketball
what is this supposed to be yeah yeah
there we go great words
[Music]
a basketball um
baseball but the ball doesn't look like
a basketball ball fusion oh
sports ball
ball basketball
basketball is always orange
uh yeah exactly which is why i'm
confused as to what sport this is about
hamster
are we helping a hamster we need to help
because it seems to be imprisoned all
right to the rescue chicken
i'm reaper
sorry phoenix
[Music]
and now it's dead
oh we wanted to go up here
up here to the right side
yes you stand like if i stand
here we don't let them go down the
little hamster cube of death where the
monsters go to die
how do we get it
[Music]
to build a ramp oh yeah
well or we can brute force it which is
awesome yeah because that's what you're
supposed to do in this game cut your
shapes and we're just brute forcing it
yeah but that's because we're we're just
good at the game we're hackers
game lets me do it then there's no such
thing as being bad at games sorry no the
game left
there's nothing wrong with that
if 10 million fireflies
you would not believe your eyes
[Music]
i like the screamo version
you would not believe the price wow
million firefly wow
am i gonna get kicked out of no okay i
have pretty fake ones don't worry
what is it with this fly we need to
bring it all together
oh maybe yeah
[Music]
i don't see a need to cut a shape here
hey listen
got him on this side so you will get
inside the ball
you will get the ball
good
[Music]
yeah you will alright i'm gonna keep
we're barricading it
yeah what if we kind of just protest
thank you
got him that's what i'm talking about
again once again brute forcing it but
what else can we do man i mean that's
how we do them this is how we do i don't
know i'm not gonna i'm not gonna take
crits on that for being smart okay
yeah
you can't you can criticize me for a lot
of things it's been a long day okay it's
been a long day
we did a lot of walking but we also did
a lot of ubering let's be real that's
awesome
i showed her some nice spots and i felt
pretty proud of how beautiful austria is
what do you think so far of austria
chicken land is magical
yeah we're all just coming for london i
can't you know what i don't really feel
like
i came from the glorious land of the
greatest
the greatest of britain yeah um which is
cool and all that but we i got kind of
unlucky and was there during the the
queen's jubilee ah you're really is that
her birthday uh no it's like the 70th
anniversary of the queen
something like that oh you
when she became the queen uh i don't
know it's either her 70th birthday or
she's been queen for a second she's i
think she's way past 17. wait no yeah
then maybe is she like 90 now she's been
a queen for 70 years or something i
don't know it's
british 17th year on her friend yeah wow
yeah she's like hundred now you're 96.
yes oh jubilee 18
96.
wow she's
nice wow
i mean long long live i guess like you
didn't see her
no i why the [\h__\h] would i go see this
wait it was really dangerous that you
it's not there i know but it's not time
for her yeah don't don't plus i'm on
hiatus but i will be there one day but
not today that's right i would be the
one to take the queen to the special
place and when i say that i mean when
it's time not now i have no attempts to
plan attempts
i think she was very nervous when she
heard that you were around yeah well i
was gonna say it was kind of a bit loud
and um i kind of compared like central
london to like
it's pretty much just like manhattan
except british flavored which by that i
mean very loud a little on the you know
it could be on the on the cleaner side i
guess people are also not very kind
i mean at least during the queen's
jubilee they weren't very nice to me
which is okay
um however however uh being able to
compare that to chicken land austria
i was like wow this place freaking rules
yeah thank you i'm happy you think so i
didn't get to show you that much today i
feel like but
and tomorrow i'm going to do my best to
show you more and make it leave a good
impression
of my country so far
says chad it's still out yeah
they say just a bit but yeah anyway i'm
sure that it's fine when it's not the
queen's jubilee but that was just kind
of rough
for me
but um yeah i'm really enjoying austria
austria and so far
i've tried to make her eat austrian food
only so we ate um yesterday i made her
eat a dish that's called pappushpitz
it's like a
beef that's boiled for a very long time
basically it was really good yeah and
then uh today um she ate a sweet
which is also very very austrian i would
say it's like um some beef with onions
and
i don't know potatoes and stuff yeah
and i had apple strudel yeah apple
strudel yesterday for the bread and
breakfast now breakfast
dessert and then today for lunch we had
a kaiser monk yeah that thing yeah it's
a dessert that i really really like you
liked it too right yeah a scrambled
pancake exactly it's pretty much
scrambled pancakes with like sweatshirts
this is like plum plum thingy sauce it
was yummy
and then i made her eat uh saka toita
the choc the famous chocolate cake from
austria
out when i made her drink the one and
only famous austrian herbal soft drink
ah
wait i have to do this correctly
you're looking at it it doesn't work
my ghostwater is broken but then can you
do like
can you do my reverb yeah i got you
[Music]
thank you
yeah i'm doing that i'm doodling it's
like a we have a yeah an herbal drink no
i'm not talking about red bull i'm
talking about red bull red bull is also
like kind of from austria
there are discussions
but yeah the the company is
from that's some news to me also i
figured out that austria is like the
like one of the european like capitals
of wine or something yes wait when did
you figure that out they told me on the
plane oh yes we do have people don't
really notice much outside of austria
but our
wine culture is pretty strong we have a
lot of great wines i know i can't wait
to drink more i'm gonna drink more
tomorrow sorry yeah no problem
because i gotta take advantage of it no
problem i'm glad you like it she also
tried to uh like a austrian specialty
apparatus blitz today
i don't know what that really is made of
it's aperol and
i don't know why i know what is that i
thought it was the campari thing
i don't know yeah it's like an orange
orange drink with some alcohol in it
yeah and they had some orange slices i
think it's we or was it the [\h__\h] no
it was spritz
so good i love prosecco no wonder i love
this
[Music]
so so far um food and drink wise you've
enjoyed it yeah it's been amazing i like
the sweets the most but i also you know
i love the my meats and potatoes and
this is the countries
and potatoes yes yes yes yes yes she has
yet to eat a weenish schnitzel i will
make her eat one tomorrow don't worry
i'm good good
so um
i trust your recommendation
now let's play a bit more
so that's me just being a random tourist
walking around like i wonder what this
is
what are we doing oh we're making a
volcano
wait are we filling out the inner the
inner middle part
do the outside maybe
we know hold on if we're inside does it
fill up no if your outside doesn't fill
up no
this is odd i kind of didn't really read
the rule book on this one let's try to
fill out the eyeliners oh wait hold on
we're supposed to get something here oh
what did that do
no it doesn't but there's a cutting side
oh maybe
okay i know what we're supposed to do
i'm supposed to cut one of us we're
supposed to cut one of us to be the
shape of the volcano thingy
let's try it so maybe this ship is good
yeah so
oh it's not perfect it's not perfect
that's weird um let's see you need to
sniff it's a reset button
oh chad says theresa just caught the
purple cut the purple okay let me cut
the purple oh we cut the purple ah
i get it
okay it's so easy why are we so
it's okay we we just we didn't know look
at those smiles god they're so smug or
constipated or both i shall ah this is
easy
does one of us need to get on oh wait
nice nice tada
yes
[Music]
oh we're getting it
i want to play that one now you like
eggs star said you're special in the
first one of each world the exit option
also lets you skip
okay why would we want to skip we're
playing a [\h__\h]
yeah game see phoenix is lay eggs no not
in my world
it depends people in other dimensions
and worlds they like to tell
uh it differently
i see that's cute look at those boobs
clips oh are we supposed to say how do i
get there
are we supposed to do a little jumpy
like yeah look at this guy oh this guy
is swinging
we do something with him maybe he knocks
it down
i'm just trying to think outside the box
he looks weak
yeah i don't think he's going to be able
to help us what
honey where's where's the
oh hang on
[Music]
oh it cuts the others when i cut you oh
whoa oh where does the example oh my god
oh wait that's we can do this oh yeah we
got a really weird part of me
yeah you look silly
okay how do you reach that again oh you
have to yeah oh my god i don't like that
face how about you cut my left side okay
yes
so we get it down this is your right is
this your left side wait i cut this part
oh [\h__\h] that's wrong
refresh please yes ma'am okay yeah yuck
your other side and you cut my my other
side the opposite one okay so we can
make it fall into the middle this one
right here uh oh [\h__\h] now you can't
really cut much huh i don't know what it
is
oh wait but if maybe oh oh wait i could
just turn myself okay it just turns ah
oh that's how we get the yes yeah baby
i'll leave the little baby children
oh wait [\h__\h] oh yeah
okay okay okay no problem you have to um
maybe you have to turn in a little bit
yeah yeah like get it yeah oh yeah but
okay
interesting let's see and what if i just
kind of i should cut you in a certain
way yeah i need to be flattered i think
here let me
crouch and then i do like a little
oh what yeah
it's not much though that's right here i
can make it work
no no no don't do that okay
i need that one part two uh please cut
yes ma'am one second okay uh cut okay
thank you
snicker that's pretty nice okay no uh
i'll take this egg please give me
those
eyes
a little a little momentum
hold up yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and gently gently gently
i like these levels
i'm not sure if i like this one anymore
no problem no problem on boys yeah
[Music]
no this is similar but i like this one
much more
that's cool i need momentum again right
yes
okay
just cut it
okay hold on
[Music]
all right get be ready for the baby when
i swing it over to you okay you ready
okay okay oh am i ready maybe i need to
get rid of all right i need to snip this
last little edge over here yeah i'll
snip it
okay
i did it
yeah we're legendary we're too good at
this game too good for the game sorry
games so cute
good work good job
game zero oh we did it
nice nice
very well done oh we got all these new
levels
because we cleared the the monster stage
retro reboot plus five new stations as
well too oh damn but let's like continue
on this one ah yeah they got
[Music]
what are we doing here should we not pop
it oh we're pumping we're trying to pop
these balloons what if i stuck my little
my little spiky part into you then what
would you do
if i stuck my face oh i see
cut us into like spiky people
wait okay let me let me let me cut you
wait so here there you go you're spiking
now it's time to die oh
[Music]
i don't right here let's just see let's
see what we get
just i'm just going to mess you up
yeah what are you doing yeah look you
look what am i help i don't know if i
can do anything
yes now here jump up on me you can use
me as a as a jumping point i don't think
i'm a good um no i think you're popping
i think you'll be perfect
yeah no no okay
i'm gonna jump
here we gotta get it down oh yeah i
can't grab it
if you turn yourself around and put the
spiky part upward okay this one this one
no no no the the other one that's more
like a knife
the jagged knife one well let's go to
the left again
okay
now here we might have to jump from
above right i think so
what's up
[Music]
i think i trust you to be the better
color with this one
oh yeah i'll have you jump on me oh oh
oh
[Music]
okay i got you all right and then i'm
going to angle myself to beast yeah
weapon of death
wow almost almost dang it okay i felt
like we can do it oh yeah we got this
all right let's go right and oh right
let's go
oh i'm fine
i'm falling inside of you hold on no
wait
i'll recreate myself okay
yeah all right
and wait no hold on i'm getting too high
for myself let me just angle my weapon
of death
maybe there's a way we can hook around
that triangular thingy
all right hold on
you're mine now [\h__\h] oh wait oh
here i think it'll work hmm hold on all
right
oh oh come on get down i bet it goes
back up
that's okay
[Music]
you could stand on top of it i think so
yeah you can kind of
[Applause]
[Music]
okay now don't let it escape oh no i
won't oh he's done for oh
okay yeah here let me jump up on you
again yes
all right yeah this dude done [\h__\h] up
okay here we go it's all over there
again my big knife is aimed for you oh
yeah
hey
all right
yay
[Music]
all right let's do more oh this is a
real basketball this one is an orange
ball
oh that's the one that's right
okey-dokey
such a charming game yeah i wanna
play the whole game
cause like when else am i gonna be able
to continue this in local co-op oh this
is a real b-ball hold on
all right we gotta get oh b-balls away
face all right so we need to actually
it's too deep it's too deep so you need
to cut you okay i'll cook you into
something
nice and long you have something thin
oh wait
[Music]
whatever way you want to do it i'm not
sure
can you go lower yes ma'am
[Music]
how about
here
and no no i'm not done oh okay i'm not
done yet all right barbara i trust you
barbara you're a barber a barber
a haircutting person
i am giving you a nice cute new
hairstyle
speaking of new hairstyles i have a new
outfit review on saturday
but i didn't show her yet though what it
is
can you get up again okay
oh yeah maybe try like that yeah let's
try like this because they're really
thick yes
yes
go dunk it down
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
i think i have a future as a basketball
player now
yeah touchdown that's not the
touchdown what are you talking about
chad yeah touchdown home run
crane game oh this looks interesting are
you good at crane games no i suck i'm
real bad i won't even try to sugarcoat
it yeah i'm only good at crane games not
like online virtual but like the real
life crane games i suck well this is
virtual so let's see
oh so uh that one is amazing go left the
purple one makes it go left get me oh
you think he can grab you up there
i wonder maybe i gotta make a different
shape yeah
because it's more grabbable yeah yeah
yeah that's the that's the way you're
supposed to
[Laughter]
[Music]
come with me
come with me come with me
up again
[Laughter]
that's what you get man hey you know
what you know what i think about that
you know what i think at least
cheetos potato chips
yeah that's what you get now we're good
okay make yourself an interesting shape
it makes you make yourself an
interesting child now
oh yeah i'm so grabbable
yes baby
bye bye
oh you better do a good job up there i
need help
hey
you gotta open with the pencil
oh i didn't
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay makes them come this way okay i'm
in a perfect position
okay when it's come down yeah now let go
okay stay on the purple though okay all
right now
here we go
stay on that purple huh i really like
being carried huh
oh hey let you go
finally yeah we got the prize
oh my god i [\h__\h] love this game it's
teamwork it's so cute that's the
teamwork chance with this game
i love these kind of like
um i had to describe it the poppy
graphics
they're cute
i will say definitely
how about
oh
shape match two oh is this like the next
level of like extra levels of the first
world or so yes
drink hydrate
oh gotta get that drink
okay so we wanna kind of match this
okay so i can easily we can easily fit
like this so what we wanted oh i'll cut
you yeah if you could cut this down yeah
and now i'll cut oh [\h__\h]
okay can you still cut me
that's the problem i think you can still
cut me if you turn like it's the
conundrum isn't it like left yeah
i just have to cut me several times
again yeah i just need to give you a
really good do okay
[Music]
strange hold on i'm dying i'm trying to
figure it out my friends you're messing
up my fringe i'm not i'll make myself
taller than you yeah
dude that's better wait and you say
normal size maybe
okay
and then i'll get down here yeah that's
about right i mean there's a little like
spike
perfect but when are arts and crafts
what do you say about this
are you accepting this
come on wait hold on it's because you
still have a teeny tiny little i got
mine cute i don't think you winky
oh [\h__\h]
maybe this is fine let's take a little
gander
oh looksie accept us huh nobody's
perfect
a little more to the left
[Music]
come on
what if i go like
[Laughter]
oh
okay
we should like kill this whole thing and
as well as much as i want to um play the
whole
game until the end we should then switch
to super magic shriek yeah i wanna i'm
curious about that game yes screaming
it's fun because you have to scream in
order to move
wow must be a dream for the neighbors
more capsules and when you need to fly
this little guy
[Music]
we're trying to free the capsule
and
free the
uh this guy maybe i do have to be like
super sharp
i don't think you can just pop a capsule
yeah
what if we try and get this bad boy oh
[\h__\h] sorry oh no maybe this will work in
our favor oh what happened a new one why
did we get a new one i don't know
what if we just try and bump this bad
boy up to the oh
oh oh oh oh oh
can you cut me like sharp yeah i'm gonna
beat a sharp one this time okay
hold on try to finish this way
there you go that'll do it i don't know
i guess that works yeah it is perfect
okay what does that do um it opens up
the hatch
okay so we want to put here i need to
put the firefly one
oh yes now he's free yeah you're free
buddy get over here
just give him a little gentle
a gentle fatherly
push in the right direction okay okay
listen here we go now listen all right
right this way
[Music]
oh we actually yeah we can reform
ourselves get out there just
[Music]
right now thank you i missed i just told
timothy that he has [\h__\h] grades in
school
if that warrants the blush i'm happy for
you jump on me all right
wait i'm the pink one yeah i forgot
like smash bros all over again every
time i play with someone we all want to
be oh no we hurt
oh life is full of
painful things
i'm just trying to teach life lessons
[\h__\h] is this problem though go there
go
[Music]
timmy you get the belt give me you're
kind of making me mad i'm gonna get the
belt
get these capsules out of here but if he
likes the belt
i want all the capsule points let's go
go push it yeah push him
together kelly i'll be your underground
all right cool
all right hang on all right we got this
we got jump oh [\h__\h] all right we may
need to switch every once in a while
all right [\h__\h] fly sound i want it
out of my ear immediately yeah he buzzed
oh he's on the ground no no no no
go back up
you'll fly you're supposed to fly and
not be on the ground
oh sorry i'll give you a little snooze
yes i'll go up here yeah yeah yeah right
yeah you're not going to escape no more
there is no escape no you cannot leave
this
come on
i'll make a wall yeah yeah yeah
oh
whoopsies wrong
[Music]
oh wow
good the birds
the eggs and the birds yeah eggs
okay so remember they're gonna do what
we're doing
and we want one egg on the left so i
want to go on the right side so maybe
you turn around
oh yeah yeah
ah
oh wait i'll cut you
uh i'll cut you to make this [\h__\h] a
little bit more
how can you turn
um
come in here my my sweet baby child wait
wait stay like that's uh
a bit more yeah this way now come here
my child thank you oh nice oh well uh
did it
fall off is it the wrong color egg it's
the wrong color oh okay
that would be too easy to bring it to
the closest side you have to bring it to
all the way over there
maybe i need to be cut all right
don't worry
i got you oh i might wipe without but
here let's see i can catch it oh cute
all right now i'm going to cut you
here oh [\h__\h] no egg shapes okay again
there we go and one more okay thank you
okay that's good i can work with that
all right
wrong way all right no i just need to
that is a blue one no it needs to go to
the right
all right oh [\h__\h] uh
little baby child eggs
okay so we have to be a little delicate
with this
okay
what we just did oh well you know i mean
our our our i mean our little eggy is
you know a tough one
all right come on come on
maybe maybe we can cut you a little bit
more like yeah yeah like stay like that
yeah
a bit back
um
i'll cut you like this okay i'm a little
more
have a yeshe more stability i think
right uh
i don't have a little push oh this is
difficult
oh yeah okay
yeah yeah
just a little
gentle push it will break
[Music]
what do you want to look like system oh
my battery is oh [\h__\h] it really is i
need to i need to give it a little
battery it's uh this little juice yeah
that's the one this one it's a little
juice yeah
i will cook you okay
[Music]
okay like this
okay i trust you
oh [\h__\h] no that's too much that's so
much
[Music]
you want to stay like that really um
okay well i mean
let's just see if it oh i'm stuck here
this way
i cut you a little bit too short though
that's the problem
refresh yourself okay i'm refreshed
refresh yourself
you're really not good at this wait yes
say like that exactly like that i'll cut
you just like me there you go
i'm like the missing half of you yeah
that's fine let's try it again all right
focus focus focus focus up team okay i
will take your egg here you go
pop it lock it polka dotted oh
you have like a little bit left over
there i know right just a little spiky
whitey
i can't jump up
[Music]
maybe i should reform at that point
yeah you know that could work yeah
oh oh you mean oh midway through yeah i
guess so cause we can do that you know i
never thought about it that way yeah
oh [\h__\h]
yeah
hold on hold on hold on
yes yes i got it okay now what do you
want to look like you're cute um just
like this is fine i can carry him on my
on the top of me okay
all right now hold on let me grab
that is i guess how that would happen
nah that's cool me too [\h__\h] it's really
difficult yeah this is a tuffy
how about this
[Music]
oh it's already on my side i didn't even
notice i was still looking at the upper
side okay
yeah push that bad boy over here to me
and then i just do a quick little a
quick little tap
a little oh wait what if
i'm ready to accept you
yes
and then just a little
positive
reaffirmation maybe i'm not the one that
needs to change maybe it's you
it's not you it's me no it's not me it's
you
it's you
really i think i have a nice shape that
can hold people
all right i'll i'll try something fresh
something new yes something
a new start for you well then turn
around a little bit and cut me okay not
like that
turn around
more
yeah yeah
and
leftover part please oh you don't want
your little spiky
okay uh this is like a spoon now yeah
now you're a spoon okay all right
and now we can both be spoons here we go
okay yes
damn it it's okay it's okay it's okay
let's figure it out
that's the good news so you're still a
spoon okay
yeah grab oh wait hold on what if i turn
around like a little windmill whoa whoa
what if we both were spoons yeah yeah
yeah yeah
if we both were supposed to yes
i feel like it's really hard to do it
with these tiny controllers yeah not
ideal oh my god oh okay
like the the lr buttons are like
basically they don't exist they're like
so tiny about all that
it's just rotating like a wind yeah
exactly that's how it worked last time
what if you cut me into a spoon okay i
think we could with my currency i bet i
can you know if you just kind of do a
little chin
yeah just a little spoony shape
[Music]
oh that one's nice that's a nice spoon
perfect okay it looks actually the same
though yeah which is probably good to be
honest
okay
oh i accidentally pressed for a new one
this wasn't our well that was our fault
that was sound alright all good all good
all good okay yeah yeah yeah all right
now
okay that's fine it's fine it's fine
and then
oh come on take it take it take it take
a second
[Music]
my fingers are getting tired right needs
to oh okay take it take it haney
[Music]
no i was all the way over here all right
hold on get in the middle so that we
can't [\h__\h] up all right okay oh
all right i have it here
i need a little bit of momentum
yeah just yes throw that up
yeah okay now wait for me away from me
i'm accepting i'm accepting here you go
wait hold on oh there we go
now plop that bad boy in oh my gosh the
pressure the pressure give him a throw
just throw them a little
yeah
babies ready
finally
finally we can do this [\h__\h] all over
again
okay
now you start it's just the same stuff
right yeah yeah
the spoons in a different direction now
we might have to change the spoons yeah
yeah so instead of well let's try it
first like this yeah yep it works
[Music]
wait maybe this was always the right
shape this is the way to go maybe we
should just make spoons out of ourselves
yes
[Music]
did they just switch it around there's
just two of us now
oh there's two i didn't
but that's the blue one it needs to go
to the right side okay i'll take it i'll
get it um
flip it over all right and this was fun
okay okay
oh [\h__\h] oh okay that's fine one more
time too much of a gap there okay
hello
all right
i'm gonna give a little momentum and
then
that's all good in the neighborhood
here's for you
here is for you
what if you rolled it out what if you
turn the spoon over ah like this yeah
and then i give you i throw it at you
and then
that is nice
i don't think i want to change my shape
to
no
to the other way around like opposite
spoon oh yeah i don't know we'll try one
more here let's see
i'm just trying to you know use my
momentum power okay
uh what if i did this
uh okay hold on
hear me out yes
no no uh i'm a dummy okay so i'm fine
maybe yeah but um i wanna
can you cut me
i guess the way that
no no um no
no it has to be
a spoon but to the other side so
i can't make a spoon with the way i am
now no if you turn yourself around one
more
like these yeah
and then i
um
[Music]
that doesn't work
yeah it makes you kind of like uh
that doesn't quite work
well just cut me whatever like okay
we'll work with this
yeah this is fine i am a hook now
yeah this still looks similar why am i
not turning black because i can't
[Music]
the first time here it's gonna fly off
of me and then
okay i'll just stay straight you'll have
to kind of find the momentum to throw it
on to me somehow
it will have to be a lot of momentum
okay i got you leave it to me ah
[Music]
[Applause]
a full spin spin spin to win
oh
[Music]
change you into a different shape too
oh yeah what if they both have to change
a bit
i was i yeah that was close yeah that
was very close
i'm gonna do it we're gonna do it okay
row fight to balance
[Music]
is someone counting all the dead eggs
because um i'll have to do inventory for
kfb later no no no just don't worry
about it just take a vacation
i'll just try it yeah there we go
sorry i was like
picking mirrors no we can do that again
we can recreate that what did you do how
did you get over to my side bro no clue
maybe a tip
happy time just have tap pepparoo
oh no okay hold on i got you my shape is
maybe not ideal right now
all right what if i did this
yeah yeah oh wow okay thank you
oh
my shape is very extreme now
but but it works it's a nice shape hold
on
um i shall take that egg here's for you
delivery
ping pong okay well i guess i'll die
pimp on delivery that is why you will
not be my delivery person
i work hard on my delivery skills
sorry drops alright just don't panic
no panics
how do we get i got this oh yes yes yes
i'm not ready for this it's okay just
gotta give it a little a little push
what if i okay okay okay i know my hook
is too big i can help you with this
um
all right i got i got you i got you
i'm scared i'm scared kelly i got you
what do we do you want to cut me off
make your hook yeah a little less
yeah
[Music]
uh
hey you're cutting a lot there oh yeah
hold on
[Music]
stop with this
i swear to go again
i swear to god
[Music]
every freaking time oh wait a second oh
it went to you
[Music]
let's just not do anything yeah it will
come to us
it'll come to you
there we go
go go [\h__\h] go
go
oh this is weird
what if um oh [\h__\h] sorry i couldn't okay
you're fine yes yes yes yes
talking about my fingers there's more i
think that's the last one because last
time we also had three different levels
no i can't handle this anymore oh my god
i'm gonna lose my [\h__\h] body what is
this
okay the blue one okay
okay
what if uh i need to cut all right i got
you
i'll cut you
right here
[Music]
now we need to pick it up all right now
let me do a little roll around
i just kind of roll you around right
now i think i'll cut you wait uh
um
yeah get lower lower okay i'm doing an
aggressive shape no goal okay we're all
spoons again yes
best
weapon of choice
[Music]
yeah they kind of i mean a little bit
i typed too much these days though to
really know how much of a difference
what is this
come on come on get in the hole come on
get in the hole
you're not like you're home enough with
the happy gilmor
stop
go go
oh yeah yeah
sorry sorry i'm so
sorry
wait i'm not ready i'll do it again
and then and again and again and again
and again and again and again there it
is there we go
oh boy that's
okay hold on i got this
responsibility yep i know but don't you
worry i'm yes
[Music]
okay you know what for now that's enough
of that game yeah that was fun
that was funny at least we did it yeah
we'll play some
what do you want superman shrink or
supermarket
that one looks fun i'm curious how it's
gonna go though
yeah you have this is with voice like it
moves with the voice oh
why do their faces look so silly
eh oh
there are so many we're always silly
that's just look at the questions their
faces are silly too
[Music]
i'm sleepy from all the walk-ins but
this will wake me up but does that
voicemain even work on the switch
because this is also a steam game and it
should work is your microphone on there
is your microphone this controller i
don't know how it would
hear us but oh
oh
l to the r here we go uh
yes i'm in yes
let's do it
one more okay
one more one
two players are supported
press this button when you are ready
ready
you've been warned oh no oh no well
that's that's promising
wow beans beans
[Music]
um i'll be the guy
okay yeah because he looks like i don't
know how do i switch it
well the goat's red so maybe
how does it work
just know i don't understand the
controls
right ah
okay uh set settings maybe
you turn it like last time i played this
i played on steam so this is the first
time um
[Music]
money
i thought i pressed settings oh there we
go
[Music]
no this one is
okay we can still scream though every
time we push the
[Music]
acting and scream every time you pursue
it
i'll say go again
i'm gold and so that's just the i think
yeah we have to switch controllers if
you want to be the guy i'll be the guy i
like the way he screams okay
switched
he sounds like he's saying i'm good oh
god
scream a little bit more girl
[Applause]
[Music]
this game is really difficult though it
was really tough
really tough what's the goal um getting
for the supermarket
oh that's it while um because like one
of us
i think controls the left one of us
controls the right and screaming is gas
oh
so okay turn left
like a man
turn left
is that me
oh yeah
and now me
[Music]
wait so
is that the only controls i don't
remember so well so it seems
[Applause]
[Music]
we just have to
i guess
now we have to turn around
[Music]
why is this in a supermarket
okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] wait for it and
guys guys
favorite souls-like game
here we go
super mario trees
[Music]
why wouldn't that just have to be a
[\h__\h]
[Music]
wow beautiful beautiful
harmonizing harmonizing ghosts
this is so much easier in local cause
and on this card we had like a little
bit of a lag oh [\h__\h] yeah
okay okay okay
[Music]
let's go straight first all right
[Applause]
[Music]
you gotta scream at the same time
i wanna go that way you guys
[Music]
okay getting for one level is already a
miracle here yeah i know right yeah
all right i'll let you i'll let you turn
oh yeah
[Music]
where are we going backwards oh i see
four words
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh beautiful curve
not so much
[Music]
excuse me
okay
[Music]
we really have to get straight to this
one okay ready three two one
dinner boys
yeah let's go one star there we go hey
oh
[Applause]
uh
oh
where's that letter grilled shop it's
the thrift shop you know like uh matt
like um is that an option all right
danny okay cool
i'll cut hairs on my nose
[Music]
collaborate and listen maury is back
with a brand new addition hold on
okay we need momentum three two one
[Music]
yeah baby
one go
no wait we gotta get on the red oh
frame fling this one okay three three
two one
oh
[Music]
ah
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
what
[Music]
are you kidding me you have to do all
that in one go that's horrific no way
let's go back in hold on get back
[Music]
all right okay so who is the turner is
it you uh i turn right so yeah i'll i'll
turn okay and then you come back and
speed gosh okay ready here we go three
two one
[Music]
what's this do we go left or down
it both looks like the exit no right
hold left waiting
[Music]
okay i guess we're going there
oh [\h__\h] that works too
probably
yeah
[Music]
uh
[Applause]
we're gods at this game look at that one
star he gave us the star it means that
we're gods oh then we did fine it was
the first time we of course if we did it
more often we could do a record i'm sure
good enough for us we're just going to
buy some stuff synchronized screamers
what did you pick up at the antique
store what'd you buy
uh i got i got
a big coat and it was 99 cents
[Music]
yeah that's the one i'm gonna i bought
the the coat that macklemore wears yo
that's nice cause
it's a nice coat and it's only 99 cents
what [\h__\h] how oh my god who wore that
before i wonder the queen
well let's press a morgan let's do one
more i don't think that we could we
don't want to
kill our voices too much or your
neighbors do
yes
walk up in the club like yo what up i
got a big side
what the what up i got a big sword and
shield we missed that one store there no
we missed a fish bouquet oh let's go
there and then go to the face don't
worry
oh [\h__\h]
oh
so in here in this place i only scream
things in a british accent all right
how do you scream
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
i know right not bad it could be worse
okay wait wait wait wait it's really
straight
all right so again it's you it's you
kiara you're the one that's gotta kind
of let's just try to move until here
first right okay three two one
oh it makes us like oh stick to the
rails okay okay that makes it easier
what's the good timing with this like
around here we're good to go
[Music]
okay we gotta really just time the do we
have to stop there
[Music]
all the kfp freaky ones right ksp
is angry
too early
i don't know why i'm spiking like this
this is not british at all i know
i'm aware
but our favorite british accent is
really hot i think it's great okay
hello stop it
pop it it's it's the term it's a term of
endearment issues
hello hello hello
we've got a girl before he's shut down
go go go go go go
go go go
[Music]
all right
you know people are probably really like
shut the [\h__\h] up you idiots yeah good i
hope so let's go
let's go
[Music]
yes that's right
shoes okay
all right haley doesn't like dying in
the beginning is better than later on
yeah you know it's kind of silly though
it's like it's a fish shop you know who
also is into
fish japanese people oh are we poking at
the britishes because the fish
oh
i turned the wrong way oh we need to
calm down there even though we were
going so smoothly you got pretty close
oh
hello
yes beautiful
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
beautiful beautiful beautiful
u-turn
[Music]
look it
[Applause]
[Music]
up and one minute that's not bad one
minute
so that not bad man not bad
well everybody i think that's enough
gaming for today yeah
um
yeah we did a lot of stuff today
it was really fun though yeah and i'm
excited for tomorrow because we're going
to do lots more tomorrow yeah
no bugger
yeah we're doing one more stream but i
think at the moment we're planning to do
it on what day is it today is it today
tuesday or wednesday it's just i don't
know it's tuesday
oh it is wednesday it's wednesday so
it's not tuesday and it's it's wednesday
it's wednesday night so probably um
tomorrow not before we're not going to
stream right oh maybe we will see i need
to check my my schedule real quick yeah
i had to other the couple
things and that i wanted to see on my
own etc um so
i need to check that sketch but there
will be one more stream and it's going
to be on my channel guys that is true
so it'll be probably going to do karaoke
right yes we're going gonna sing some
songs it might be like a little on the
casual side but that's fine because i
did a casual stream members only
recently and it was way more fun that
way
to just like to see like what we felt
like singing
maybe do some holo songs yeah we're
planning on having his archive so don't
worry if it's a bad time for you we're
we're gonna do archival songs most
likely
yeah so look out for that we're gonna
tweet it out when we decide when to do
it
but besides that i'm really happy to
show callie around some more tomorrow
eat some nice food and touch grass
lots of grass i'm going to roll around
rolling
[Music]
or the following day i don't know i need
to look at my schedule like i said but
but now we're gonna touch some more cats
right yes i'm gonna go play with your
cats forever now and then steal them and
then i mean just kidding haha she's
really so intoxicated like my cats it's
so cute she's so fast i love the little
mouse toys yeah
and elaine's a toy yeah and shonkers is
so sweet
so loud so loud with the purring yeah
right it's just fluffy right but kelly
said that she can really tell them apart
easily now just by seeing them in real
life yeah it's super easy because they
have super different personalities too
you know yes i'm glad you know this and
realized i don't i think so far like
when i had other like friends visiting
who see my cats it took them i think
longer than you
yeah but i mean i have a cat since
and smoothie's just like zooming around
all the time she's like the zoomies all
the time this is very open right too
yeah strangers
so soft very kind cats i do have
all right then guys we'll see you
tomorrow the day after tomorrow yeah
we'll see you guys later thank you for
coming to
a fun reunion stream for us because it's
been too long finally fun games yeah
finally
yeah
more soon and in german we say
a vietnamese thing that's right
peter's name
uh and thank you sean
feeling down feeling down yeah and and
now it's time for our uh house
[Laughter]
airport vocabulary is so useful i didn't
think that i did it i'm going to do
better too i'm learning as i look at
signs thanks everybody
good night bye
good night
guten gutsun yoru good enough
[Music]
to learn german there's like i don't
know it feels like you're easily picking
it up thank you i'm trying my best to
learn yes yes
all right bye-bye bye guys peace peter's
piece of peace in peace
[Music]
peace
bye bye yay
[Music]
do