[Music]
oh
me beding heart
alone no control
e don't you dare
apologize
myen
[Music]
up I'll
C
call think
[Music]
taking the crown now call me
King back it up keep that aim I got
thoughts that will drive you insane come
over if you like we'll have a lot of fun
but I got a
lot what
[Music]
iy
it'sing
over I I'll make you cry
[Music]
[Applause]
up oh you wish I'd stay down but then I
just you're not my
enemy
baby
[Music]
SC
keep call
[Music]
[Applause]
me
K there she goes yeah I I knew you
wouldn't want to be there smoothie she
just jumped up my
table this cat just jumped off my
table and said hi and I was like girl
you're going to jump away right
away K
Kitty
I was just eating some chocolate
M and then the remix finishes are
[Music]
y
look
W it
says flock
yeah hat let's go cute hat I wouldn't I
don't know if I would call it a trucker
hat it's just a really nice
sophisticated
hat um so I'm here in my suitable
attire to go a little bit
Trucking instead of
clucking every
day here blue I don't know where to hang
this but I guess in the middle of the
screen okay well is that the middle of
the gaming
screen um EUR trick EUR trick Euro Truck
Simulator for a long time I had that on
my list of games to play one day as a
one-off
game and today was the day I know some
of you were like M did didn't she say
she was going to play something else
today yes yes I said so I changed my
plans because when I was making the
schedule and I am a woman of my own who
can make her schedules however she wants
even if she already announced something
else I was like I'm not feeling that
other
game that I feel like that will be
boring so I don't know if this will not
be boring but you guys seem to like it
so we're going to play this if that's
okay let's go driving I'm in control
yeah girl boss just girl boss
things do I need to use a controller for
this or is it okay with a keyboard guys
answer my question while I consume my
chocolate a little driving snack h
oh well I don't have a [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
wheel keyboard
okay oh
wa who what the
what it's giving
me eight options to launch
it
why uh it says play your TR Simulator 2
or launch with direct X11 64bit or
launch with open GL what the [\h__\h] is
that 64bit launch in safe mode or 64bit
or play e Che Simulator 2 in 32bit or
all the other previous mentioned options
in
32bit
uh direct what why what I should choose
Direct x60 for bit why I've never seen
this
before what is
this why is this why 64 bit so you can
use your RAM
uhhuh it's a graphics API okay wait it's
on the wrong
screen go no hey my windows doesn't
work help this was a
mistake
oh oh yo ah who think I switched it okay
ah
no wait does does me choosing direct X
force it to go on one specific screen
cuz it's moving something but it's not
the game the
[\h__\h] okay I don't like this I want to
close the
game no
no that's not my main screen I mean I
guess the PC thinks that's my main
screen okay wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait can I
change because it's not moving with the
usual uh combination of keys it does say
my middle screen is number one but all
my all my icons go on the right screen
for some reason yeah I'm using uh the
the left alt tab yeah
yeah why do it go over there maybe
whatever can I change it to window uh
Window
mode if I change it to Window mode I
could probably move it
over I'm restarting the
game la la yeah Windows shift a key
that's what I
[Music]
tried
whoa
English I don't see a window mode
setting right now
wait
[Music]
what
t uh what is this I don't want
that company
name
uh uh pun I need a
pun uh
Kias uh f
uh it has to be with
p uh product parcel Portables
M
packaging parel products
proc
uh Park
Park
parking parking no yeah that's okay what
do cars do they Park seems like pretty
much same thing okay what is
this that's me what what the [\h__\h] Docks
but like uh will I be able to change the
Window
mode whoa where did they get all these
pictures from
iock holy [\h__\h] should um well that's me
obviously oh
orange
oh okay okay why for it being a your
truck simulator there are way more
pictures of
women than there are oh hello then there
are choices of trucks what the hell
company logo that's not wait that comes
really close
Thunder Trucking
ink you're a woman simulator
exactly how does it oh I was going to
ask how does it know I'm a
woman uh uh well I need a more European
sounding name so uh
oopsie Sarah
Gutenberg G Scot
[Music]
now let me move my
window what was that thing that I
unchecked by the way I hope that's okay
yeah meet them elav by the way truck in
German we just say uh an AB abbreviation
an a collaboration of letters we say l
cave l k w but in German uh W is V so
it's l v really easy to say right way
better than LK W it's just
elav we just say elav it stands for
something yeah last wag but we say
l every normal person says I'm driving
an L
Cav yes
a
and
um
yeah you'll be able to browse for k
trailer p w you'll able to BR for the
selection of spectacular images
handpicked from World of trucks for use
in loading screens
uh
sure
okay uh wait I don't know if I
downloaded DLCs was I supposed to
download
DLCs should I
buy should I should should I have bought
DLCs are we good are we going to have
fun without dlc's even if I don't have
DLCs can we drive through Austria
nonetheless you can start without them
okay you should play vanilla first okay
nice
that's exactly what I was planning
yeah so
oh
what whoa okay no I don't want to no go
away why is the mouse so
slow
options
oh
oops
window no wait no window
here oh
ah here
blind okay and then I don't know if
that's too big uh apply
whoa it doesn't look like a window to me
but I can't move it
still how are you a window let me make
you smaller so I can maybe see the top
of
you yeah now I see
it I can't I can't tap out windows just
does not work on this wait wait wait
don't yes yes yes
yes I keep on having to open task
manager for this where's my where's my
there it
is I think it's still a little bit too
big on my middle screen no actually it
fits in perfectly but
no
okay okay okay I guess that's fine wait
when if I do a full screen do you go do
you stay in the screen no it moved to
the other one I'm so sorry
guys
uh no go back
return guys why does it why does it do
this
okay every time I have
[Music]
to let me open chat again and let me
open this
[Music]
again what a thumnail right thank you
maybe in advanc you can choose
monitor
Advanced where where does it say
Advanced see I don't see the Bottom by
the I don't see the writing there I need
to make it a bit
smaller h
h
m wait what's the next
smallest this oh that's so
small no where's my mouse
here okay this girl not fit I'm blind
I'm blind okay this is perfect size
though okay I hear advanced
settings well I already found the screen
where I wanted to be it's okay it's
gonna stay here now it doesn't really
have what I want anyway should I change
something
here being a trucker is hard yeah I mean
you got to always make sure that your
truck is like in the right condition and
everything before you get started you
know it's going to be a long
road so do I need to change something
here probably not right let's get
Trucking or
clucking does it just have is it
normally it has no sound or am I
supposed to hear
something I to
oh am I supposed to hear something at
this
point maybe I have some audio settings
wrong level
zero yeah you got a problem with
that I I I just got my
license there should be a
[Music]
okayed there we go oh it's [\h__\h] loud
Tab out
again change although I could change it
in game yeah let me change it in
[Music]
game uh
options
wow is there going to be radio that's
copyrighted all right you got a
license
for my elave of course I got a license
for my
elav no no no
no I swear to God this is going to drive
me insane but once we're
driving then everything should be set in
place and then we're
good soor I have to move myself a little
bit more I guess
okay um music could be copyright
hopefully not I don't imag this guys
having used licensed music and free
internet radio is available but you can
disable it because of okay so just like
GTA or
so
okay maybe so [\h__\h] loud where's the
music didn't change
sh
why is this mouse so slow how do I is it
says reset to defaults was there an
apply
no make my mouse
faster it's like dragging
across can I control
rolls my M
faster mouse mouse mouse mouse there's
not nothing to do with my
mouse okay I guess I'll die a c
speed that's the best you can do why is
it so draggy
ew God okay start continue game it's my
first
time h
uh uh keyboard mouse ster oh oh Drive
using a keyboard and look around the
world with mouse yeah yeah
yeah oh only the right side of my
keyboard then let me move the
keyboard so
okay no I don't understand
this simp can I do simple
automatic I I
don't the simplest driving method this
this is like the easy medium and hard
and super super super difficult Hell
mode in
games I can do the first one okay for
the keyboard control please press press
forward to drive forward and press back
to break or reverse the gearbox will
handle everything else thank God maybe
later in the future we can use the more
advanced stuff oh oh look this is
German links or and or D for
steering so I can
use okay and what is with the what is
with
enter finish wizard oh my God no more
magic we'll finish the wizard we'll kill
him we'll drive over
him select the city I want to started
okay okay oh there's oh there's more
than just one city in austrial that I
can start Garden oh my
God Austria we're going to
Austria oh we can go to
glat it's quite nice I've been there but
uh I don't know is it's small we can go
to clood I've never been there but
there's a beautiful oh uh a
beautiful Lake and we can go to inbrook
which we have a lot of um issues at kfp
with inbook I have a
um a problem with
them I don't know why they're so popular
we go to sbook which I know like my best
Tasha and we can go to lince what the
[\h__\h] is what did you just say what the
[\h__\h] did you just say k translate that
[\h__\h] uh I I know it like my my my West
pocket
and we can go to the capital Vienna or I
guess can we drive from one city to
another probably right oh oh I've many
times I've done the trip from sburg to
Munich in a
vehicle many times that would be
nostalgic maybe we can do
that over the
Border over the
Border I shall remember the Border do we
actually get to do stuff like that do
you want to walk through the tutorial
yeah I want to drive through it
idiot sussy
Buckle I can drive anywhere on the map
okay but is it just highways I can't
drive through the city right there's no
way that they I mean that that would be
crazy oh yeah yeah I yeah I use to live
uh in this building yeah yeah yeah
welcome to Euro Truck Simulator 2 at
last you have the chance to
experience yeah yeah toally I've been
there experience your dream job driving
a truck wow the graphic is kind of low
is this not how it's supposed to be it
looks nice it looks
nostalgic your own transportation
company is now open for business but
sadly you lock the money to buy a truck
what for now you'll have to work for
other ah okay okay for other
companies you're task is uh to safely
deliver a load of used packaging to RT
log dock in sburg your employer has
provided you with a vehicle and will'll
cover all the expenses don't let anyone
down and arrive on time oh but they're
already down down bad for me in
[Music]
CA it's Monday and we're driving to Sal
book Sals book because SS book is in SS
book yeah oh wow
wait so you guys are saying that
uh Graphics are [\h__\h] can I make it
better whoa it changed the [\h__\h]
window
again oh yeah if was it under low it was
all gray does that mean it was under
Low Max it oh okay
okay I was just being
cautious okay 4080 can handle Ultra you
would hope so wait do I have a 4080 I
don't remember what I
have
okay than
you uh is this how I get out of the menu
I just escaped out of it
again
uh oh
okay okay yeah I mean the
vegetation and stuff the crane yeah that
looks like Austria
yeah that's exactly the sound of kics
how did you know how does the game know
oh my God you can use the phone controls
yeah
okay drive forward a few me in yourself
okay how how much this much
more oh God stop stop ah I'm supposed to
stop H there ah stop
stop no wait how do I stop if I can go
back there we go interior camera
one uh-huh chasing camera oh top down
camera O next camera why is it on nine
not on four h because ah they reserving
for to press during my music video ah
okay okay okay makes sense oh
H switch to chasing camera and look
around to uh around the truck press aab
Orab both the same
okay uh oh wait there's more roof
camera
four lean out camera five bumper camera
six on real camera oh that's a good one
seven
drive by oh cool next
camera try press I okay it's time to
make a delivery use route advisor to see
where you are and where you need to go
press F1 or pause to look
closer dot dot why is that so omnus
ominious
ominous it's time to make a delivery use
R advis see where you are what's what's
rou advisor how do I open that oh wait
press one I guess
oh
oh uh F1 or pause pause or
unpause when the game is paused you can
control route advisor with the mouse you
have a set na called route advisor
available at all times route advisor
displays your current status and helps
you with information about your current
job and points where you need to go or
where to go okay awesome so my
GPS uh there are also shortcut keys
assigned to the most often used
functions which you can use instantly
while driving they available ke are
suggested directly by the r advisor
current
status email indicator oh I get
emails contents of currently selected
page uhhuh page toggle switch between
navigation current jop description truck
Diagnostics and short messages uh okay
sure
whatever uh that's fine I I think I only
need to look at like maybe Fuel and
damage and or fatigue maybe oh okay I
need to sleep
at some
point navigation map shows your current
position as a blue arrow if you're on
the job it also shows the shortest draw
to your destination in red at the bottom
of the page there is an estimation of
the remaining trip time and distance and
you can cycle through different Zoom
Levels by pressing F5 or activating
what's Zoom levels oh ah okay zoom in
and out pressing F5 or activating the
button on the screen I would like it to
be uh
o oh
oh oh maybe okay for now this is okay
but later the other one switch to the
next page uh zero uh okay to
Contin no zero didn't work
F6 the job description page summarizes
what you're carrying and wear it tells
you when you are expected how much time
you have left and how much money you
receive if you arrive on time without
damaging the cargo okay
okay okay we we must arrive anywhere
between this time but now it's already
past that time they want me to arrive in
like 5 hours and a half
Max okay next rest up in 10 oh [\h__\h] so
far okay so we're not resting today
probably on the Diagnostics page you can
see see how badly your truck trailer and
your cargo are damaged the vehicles can
be repaired H at a service station in
any City the D damage to Cargo however
is permanent so be careful if you happen
to get stuck on the road you can also
call road assistance by using service
and
adjustment sure I'll just ask you guys
when I when I'm like lost that's all you
need to
know okay can I drive
now wait show me the wait show me the
show me the the
yeah
okay uh so I already like this because I
like the driving part of
uh
GTA so this is good oh my God but
controlling such a big boy M Mia well
I'm doing good now I'm really too far on
that side though I guess oh God how how
far am I
wait oh oh oh no that's not too
bad okay that's
good right side oh do I have to press
the the blinkink blinkink
blinkink a let's go ah on the
autoban you driving very
fast is is sarcasm your specialty the
blink blink I can't do the blink blink
can I does it do does the game do it for
me well look how
pretty that's not the entrance to the A1
that I know but do I really know where
it starts and where it begins
[Music]
ah sign okay let's go oh left oh okay I
don't know this this entrance oh God
wait am I really allowed to go left here
oh
okay okay we can go 100 oh can I get
stra
tle can I get oh what if we drive
through
there can
I wait am I too big
maybe sh I'm certainly not the only one
who tried that oh my God a track hey
buddy what's up
buddy from go go go go go why is he not
going okay so not there we cannot go
through I'm too big for that now keep
that in mind need to visualize my
size see
SP okay right side ah okay I'm so
slow I'm just getting started
okay
I have some bgm if we get bored later
but for now wow
wow I'm out
U left side is U okay I'm going to teach
you German autoban and car lingo
today yeah not supposed to be on the
left I know I'm a rebel re Rebel I'm a
rebel okay I go here hey my trial damage
went down how's that
work what she said hor it's kind of a
difficult word I guess wait we're
already going off the outan
no are we're delivering within sburg
from sburg to
sburg okay wait uh oh [\h__\h] slow
down just let it oh
no I'm convinced you're American what
what what whip game what do you mean
what are you talking
about I am I am today I will not Flex my
wait I know this yeah I know this I
think I know wait is this where I think
it
is excuse me
oh yeah I think I don't oh is it oh no
yeah no yeah kind of wait did did can it
be could it be that they like shorten
they
combine certain
parts yeah I swear okay can I say this
my school my my
ele School
Assa was
here can I say
that
I mean what you going to do what you
going to do get my yeah every what
that's not how it looks okay but pretty
close oh I know this my school bus it
stopped over there and it started uh
this not doesn't look so much like real
life but it started here yeah yeah yeah
yeah W I'll go to
school wow it wasn't this hilly though
eyes on the yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
wait did I follow the
GPS oh my god let's
go wow oh yeah oh my God guys remember
the story I told you about this uh this
this this this um this this thing where
it was like a like a Showcase of
furniture and I thought that people live
in there and I was like who wants to
live there when your uh living room is
constantly on display it was here on
this
road child w w was thinking that uh that
furniture showcase was somebody's home
and they just had a huge [\h__\h] window
showing you showing everybody their the
life of
them
[Music]
yeah I I didn't crash what are you
talking
about free Hometown yeah although yeah
it really feels like they uh shortened
certain sections and like sticks stick
stocks stick them together wait where am
I supposed to go you got rid of the
thank
you approach the entrance gate to get a
clearance to bring the clock to a
particular spot watch out for animated
Beacon Market
[Music]
okay yeah they simplifying it right they
condense it make it a package deal good
Sho oh good shoes oh my God wait back
back back back back back at the terminal
once you have selected your desired beep
beep parking spot proceed to park to
trailer if you get an another TR you may
also choose to complete the delivery
automatically
oh
[\h__\h] sh how do I how do I
H this is not
good okay got to do it
nicer is this good that looks good
there's something lying there on the
floor but sure okay okay and
now did I go too far am I supposed to
stand there but the dude is waiting over
there should I not park over
there too far okay just just here then
okay I did it a skill truck driver can
deal with maneuvering in a tight space
when dropping off a trailer however
cargo safety is top priority if you do
not fill up to the challenge negotiate
with the dispatcher for a backup place
to park the trail M how nice of them
where do you need
it what does this mean uh
under what does it let's play it safe
sorry I'm in a hurry now
skip
uhhuh uh well try better
skip eat the
cargo
you you always skip it oh so
okay what do you mean it took me an hour
that was uh 30 minutes IRL so even less
in
game that's so exciting seeing my old
[Music]
school I remember like taking the the
like a little um you know when when it
snows and you go down a hill with a
what's it called
again what's it
called sled like a sled but like not a
real sled we would like choose like more
cheaper options like it just looks like
a spoon for example like a plastic spoon
this is my headquarters oh my God looks
really
um
nice no not cardboard no plastic plastic
well sometimes when it was really bad
then maybe a plastic bag actually works
pretty well plastic bag from from the
shop yeah like a giant
spoon it's a pretty basic garage it may
not be much but it's a start uh
unfortunately you haven't got anything
to park there yet so there are no trucks
inside once you've earned enough money
and you bought a truck H you will be
able to move in the world freely and run
your own business from here good luck
good truck you should say good
truck you can say your pro see your
progress okay thank you wow so go next
trip
please I get
high should I just do this one first
because I can't choose the others anyway
okay
um I could choose sbook again what there
SB SB to SB SB to insb SB to CL SB to
insb SB to
insb why is s why so much in what what
SB to Munich can I do SB to Munich SB to
Munich he let's go I'm taking the
job to
Germany
[Music]
torant torant
torant game really wants me to go to in
yeah what the [\h__\h] get out of here
okay from
from where's exit a
there what am I transporting I don't
know doesn't matter we don't ask whether
there's dead bodies in my truck or or
not it does not
matter I'm happy to
transport the dead bodies in your
closet W whoo whoo whoo whoo oh [\h__\h] I'm
stuck a little bit
um
mhm okay come
on it's a this truck is a little bit
late on Reaction
Time whoo W really close one I think
w Wait I see the problem I see why we're
driving so slow do you see those little
little Stoppers
stabilizers you got to you got to get
rid of those otherwise we're constantly
dragging across the the ground
no okay okay let's go it's not
realistic no I don't know what that is
to be
honest ALK to
AO or what is
this that's a a sign for trucks truck
healer do I have to follow the traffic
stuff what if it was red why why can't
he go there and I cannot
unfair I'm driving a gas tank oh
[\h__\h] yes I I
should I have oh cuz he has the
DLC
gatekeeping oh my God he's a
hacker cops are nah cops are not going
to chase me are
they wow oh my god wow it's going wait
oh my God I know this place there's a
McDonald's close
by oh my
God but they're like making it so
compact oh [\h__\h] oh my God I remember I
remember
[Music]
this oh my God ah what the [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh oh okay
okay wait so I think yeah this is
supposed to be the yeah this is the
McDonald's was it's like kind of weirdly
positioned it should be like a few
meters before it's kind of weird but oh
my God yeah I know that tunnel there was
not really a tunnel but you know oh my
God wait I'm supposed to should I go
there I don't understand the navigation
I guess afterwards
okay no no what we drive what we Drive
uh yeah we drive on the
left yeah what what do you mean uh we
drive do we drive on the wait no I guess
we no no we drive on the right I don't
know game too
quiet
really well you're probably thinking of
the UK the UK does not speak for Europe
anymore okay
okay
right wow I know those flowers I
remember those
flowers
okay oh and Sh a a curve is a okay
really easy almost same writing just a k
instead of a
c oh my my truck is making weird sounds
man oh my
God why is it making such weird
sounds oh is it purposefully keeping me
slow or
so
a
no
Co okay let's go I'm just going to
follow the s
in no oh my God my heart wants to go to
in hey hey cutting it kind of close
there my
friend hey don't look down on me just
because I'm a l okay rude yeah why can I
not go faster okay we're going
50 we're ra raising our oh I know that
Hut I used to live in
there yeah yeah oh yeah yeah yeah oh
this looks so
familiar oh my God this is making my
ostran heart go doy doie this is really
nice oh my God this is like way [\h__\h]
better than geog guesser in regards to
showing you my home country because
geoga always brought me to the same
[\h__\h] place no variety this game has
way more variety already oh my God I
know that shadow oh my god let's
go well Bishop's H yeah you
know Vienna guesser so true my God no
respect
for for Austria this yeah the drive to
Munich actually is supposed to be pretty
long how much how long are we going to
drive in
reality are we already what oh wait next
one right yeah yeah not this no no not
next one I was like hey that's kind of
soon no it's just a
curve just a
coolair it's going to tell us when we're
not not in Austria anymore right whoa
whoa whoa hello truck the truck behind
me wants to wants to Uber
Halland he's in the Uber H wait this is
this is the yeah this is this is the
this is this
is this is the
Border let's
go yo hello border I know you oh my God
oh my God God I'm just driving by
they're ignoring me I know this border
looks exactly like
that wa and we don't have to show
anything because we're in [\h__\h] Europe
guys yeah I mean sometimes maybe you
have to show something especially if
you're a truck I guess you have to show
something
yeah oh how
beautiful on the way from sides
spoke Sid spoke to uh Munich oh k k oh
hello we were supposed to see a shopping
center like like the the biggest
shopping center of salburg uh oh no I
guess not we're not really supposed to
see it on this road maybe I don't know
it's kind of on the outskirts of soubor
city or shopping center called or Park
yeah um I used to go there wow is there
is there my cow friend over there I used
to I used to own a cow that's a lie I'm
making up a lot of lies so to confuse
you you don't know anymore what's right
and what's
wrong constant distractions not looking
at the
road whoa whoa what's this wait is this
zono wait does the Dono go through here
I don't know wait what is that Lake OH
help me
guys what the [\h__\h] was
that I know it's a river but I'm asking
if it's the
donow if oh wow beautiful wheat the danu
yeah the Don is danu in English
danu
danu least distracted European dver
yeah the lake where I went oh yeah that
is that is in uh like salsburg uh land
okay so to explain to you um so uh
salsburg is a city that is in the land
area so to say uh of
sburg uh we call it land okay sbur land
uh so I went paragliding on the
Countryside of
sbur for that if you remember my
paragliding
video yeah that's that's where I went oh
oh I can go too fast right they would
they would find me for that right okay
better not go over 90 right it's is it
80 right now but we're in Germany it's
free for
all we're in Germany on the autobound
you can go however much you
want uh it's the in River are you sure
about
[Music]
that not trucks oh
[\h__\h] do you think they'll crash into me
or do the does the AI make them go out
of my
way gas gas gas okay we we are around 80
it's okay it's
okayy
Road R in
German I'm just I'm still very calm they
have to do something waa
that's am I right
here yeah yeah yeah okay we
[Music]
good I think they uh that's what's it
called again I know this Arena it's like
some some company's name isn't it oh
yeah I don't recall was it this far out
instead of instead of doing like little
Japanese uh translations in the middle
of my conversation I'm doing German
today isn't that nice I should I should
play this on my German
Channel maybe I will do another stream
on my German Channel just completely
driving for Germany and Austria speaking
in
German hello aliance
Arena can you drive at night okay house
gets to out fat H out out drive is what
we call this okay I
fat I oh who W
downhill let it
flow fart you're so funny huh so funny
now I've I've arrived in Munich many
times but I never drove myself so I
don't think I really oh it's great
I probably never really paid attention
so I'm probably not going to get as
excited as in s book but uh let's see if
we find something
familiar normally it was road trips to
like uh
convention convention it just happened
this last weekend you know it's not
officially in Munich but it's like in
that I can't see if it goes green
oh wait how do I I change camera again
oh here hello I can't see oh [\h__\h] here
we
go yeah so normally I go to this event
quite
often it was this weekend but this time
I chose not to go because uh of the
Bangkok events that I had had to be
around
for you
know yeah honking means hooping so I
said don't honk at me
[Music]
nien if you honk at me oh you don't know
what will happen then my friend oh what
is this area that doesn't look really
familiar to me I don't think it has
mountains this close around it but okay
oh no actually this looks familiar
oh my God oh my God yeah it does it's
just always like a little bit like
oh like oh a I I I didn't want to stop I
just wanted to slow down y y y y can I
still go yab what's Happ it I couldn't
see I hope I'll still make a good amount
of money am I too late by the way I hope
I'm not to L how much did they expect me
to
take
hoopen yeah hoopen
hoop oh a red red red red red
red [\h__\h] it stops pretty early oh w w w
whoo oh there we go it's gr and
green
oo okay
nice nice nice heckin uh what do you
call
heckin this game is making me forget all
my English holy [\h__\h]
y can't you can't drive too fast over
that [\h__\h] right that's a speed bump
right hedge yeah hedge
sh
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
nice excellent that was a lot of fun
wow wow pretty good driving thank
you wait I just realized this whole time
I had my sparkles
on
oopsie uh what what is this can I ignore
this go away oh I can assign
skills
oh what should I
do long distance
maybe I know I'm just going to put it in
there
email we thought you might like to know
we offer favorable loans to new
businesses you need funding to get your
business AR our local banking
center my favorite
RPG I didn't apply okay so the I'll go
back we excited to announce the opening
of a US truck SE I probably can't afford
one yet
right okay showroom in
Vienna weekly truck road trip on German
a weekly weekly is a bit much maybe
monthly okay so uh
apply probably fine I have 4,000 bucks
I'm sure a truck cost
more okay with a loan maybe oh wait am I
supposed to do that now
already a selection of older trucks is
now available considerable discount and
use truck
offers use
trucks oh
[Music]
uhhuh uh oh that's really
expensive
that's really
expensive thanks for the membership
renewal can I just drive like normal
jobs a little bit more quick
jobs I don't want to think too much so I
want to go to Vienna
please our beautiful beautiful
capital
N what
n
Lind Munich Clen Fort I'd like to see
those
twoo there is no [\h__\h] wi is it too
far do they not do like really long
distances or is this just uh you know
they change and it could be another time
oh it is new back okay I thought
so I'm too low
level
no okay now there's
nothing I need to level up to do longer
oh okay okay okay oh then let's go to a
place I've never been
to ah wait I have to do from Munich now
no no some of these are from
salsburg
so I guess we
could should I go from Munich somewhere
where no I want to
go who the [\h__\h] needs a delivery from
sburg to sbur just [\h__\h] walk or take
a bus or what is wrong with
you it's such a small
City what is wrong with you just walk
have you ever thought of using your own
feet something is wrong something is
wrong in your in your upper head head
yeah just
[\h__\h] carry what is in your arms nothing
nothing in your
arms use your legs use your arms use
your
brain not so difficult no no not so not
so no easy okay let's go [\h__\h] uh okay
let's go to my Arch Enemy Arch en
me the accent is taking over oh you
think so I think uh my English is uh
really good yeah
[Music]
yeah it has no accent what it what what
what what are you talk talk Talking a
boot what okay let's let's go Lo gets um
oh this is a different starting
point oh we we are inide book though as
far as I know uh yeah I know that bridge
yeah no what the [\h__\h] is this what the
[\h__\h] is this as my mother would say my
mother my mother would say what the [\h__\h]
is
this the a
no not like this no oh uh well I am
sorry you have to
wait okay
oh yeah yeah yeah is this the FL C I was
like yo this looks like the Airport
Building oh
our our tiny ass airport yeah man I
haven't been at that airport in ages
because it doesn't really do uh any any
useful
flights our flu h fire oh no the fire
people oh no the fire people the fire
people oh I never went that direction
before oh maybe I have actually yeah you
know what that's that doesn't seem
familiar a little bit yeah normally I
takes the bus and goes the other
way okay let Lo kids but normally I say
it's been many many years
okay
the I'm just making the song
Up by
this is called a in the German
language what do you mean I have a new
I'm driving right now [\h__\h] off call
me this is a here it's a
[Music]
circle
intercourse wa
intercourse around about yeah but in
German it's
Circle inter
course traffic yeah traffic
fa
inter yeah actually wait isn't that how
you directly translate that
word but my song was so nice though I
have an easier time thinking of Rhymes
in German than in English like
spontaneously on the
go so much easier in German holy moly
harly
macaroni
German viewers very very happy today for
understanding what I
say oh let's go let's go those kids L
kids you know you know I always say
Austria looks like a schnitzel you know
what is a schnitzel wait are we at the
are we again
whoa wow uh my dear tourist if you look
on the left side you see it all armed
and if if you look on the right side you
see another Soul armed and a little bit
of a tank Stella yeah it is beautiful it
is one like n none
other and now we are into Germany and I
was about to say you may be wondering
why are we going for Germany W when uh
maybe you're not thinking
that why are why are we going through
Germany deand when we are going to
Austria yeah I think that to myself
every day it's a good
question I've done this
before some
KY the kimy uh it's because Austria is
shaped like aittle uh yeah so if you
want to go around uh that corner of
Austria you know yeah there there's
Bavaria in the way and our our
autoban they go for uh the
Bavaria it's such a funny name for Bayon
I always laugh about H
Bavaria just say Bayan just like you say
col what are you a
puffer I'm
really I'm really enjoying my role play
today what are you
but because cologne is it not a male
puffer
[Laughter]
H so yeah if you go around the corner
you have to make a little Hal Halo in
the
Germany yeah we say C in do we say C
it's the o with the two little thoughts
that you are not capable of reading
because we have the longer
alphabet [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] W whoa it's making
the blink
blink I would not have noticed if not
for the blink blink the the blink blink
saved
me I heard the blink blink thank you I
would have driven further to by Italy
or
Italia yeah
if I if I not uh be more careful I drive
through Italia
yeah
from house
man you like the accent oh than thank
you thank you thank you thank you
than now excuse me I have to concentrate
on uh the
road the road is very empty today it's a
nice day no no ST today St is uh traffic
traffic jam why do you put some Mamet on
the road what is wrong with you again
what what is wrong with you
Americans don't put the maramet why is
my blinker on I don't
know why why put the mamade on the road
of course it's going to be traffic jam
if you put the marmalade on there nobody
can drive on the shitty
[Laughter]
mamed I put the I did not put anything
on you think I put the hazard on what
the [\h__\h] is this what I did not put oh
no how do I put it
off the van blink
UNL and I press the oh no it's wrong
button press F oh there we go okay
normally when when they say press F you
do not press the F because you fall out
of the uh uh was uh uh cou Sher
no hoop shubber hoop shubber you fall
out of the hoop shubber when when you
press the
F
the one moment I forget German now I
said cou shrubber which is the just a
pen instead of a hoop shrubber which
just
helicopter yeah this area I don't really
know I think I mean I probably I've
been on this autoban one time maybe oh
we are it says we are on the
artw I think if I should remember this
correctly I really should is the biggest
mountain of Austria
no I think it's the biggest should be
the biggest close clock now right why
you wipers oh well that must maybe
oh okay I turned it off no I
didn't uh
ah H there we go there we go PE yeah my
finger my wor finger it slipped on on P
when I pressed the o oh it's a bus
behind
me oh thank you for the rest reminds you
of your grandfather's trucker
stories know assistant do what is
this what is this who who excuse
[Music]
me oh there's a control oh oh maybe
speed control maybe I should go
faster I'm legally supposed to honk I
don't know how
to how do you honk parking oh [\h__\h] sorry
sorry sorry sorry I thought that was
maybe the honk sorry for parking on the
autoban oh oh no the traffic jam sorry
for spreading the marade on the floor
sorry oh that is
beautiful please pull in for vehicle
inspection no no I did not I no I did
not do anything oh my God I'm so this
here
sorry sorry for parking on the RO I'm I
I'm am so sorry I apologize oh I know
this wall
H yeah yeah sorry uh I have my wait
where do I where do I go here here is is
here okay
pisot yeah hello what the navigation
didn't even tell me to go here I came
here anyway what so so what now you
going to talk to me
or no can I go is this okay are they
weighing me oh that's very embarrassing
thank you for your cooperation oh no oh
no they know they know I am fat oh
no now say no I was trying on the diet
but you
know food is
amazing okay here we go are we in in
Germany or in Austria right now I'm not
sure I think Austria we're back in
Austria aren't we maybe that's why there
was the
control yeah now oh I'm TR to SL there's
a castle up there is it uh honestly I
don't know what could it
be what Castle is up there oh [\h__\h] stop
stop stop stop stop
wo it must be a castle in
inor
okay this is my most hated city in the
world just
kidding I don't hate it that much wait I
feel like maybe I've been this this
houseat really feels
familiar maybe I've been here once maybe
W oh or not maybe it's just all ASAT
look the
same H in
spook maybe they all look do look the
same I'm not
sure that much
ah it's
red wait no it does look for maybe I've
been here
before whoa whoa whoa [\h__\h] I went too
far to the ah to the
right okay it's scen now we got to go if
we got to go we got to
go it would be better if it disappeared
I don't hate in it would be better if if
it disappeared
though it does look
familiar oh is that a a
hospital now I
remember now I remember just
[Music]
kidding can you call this
wait this does feel
familiar and then
left oh close oh It Feels So Close
a I drive so well thank you it's called
an underpass what really in English it's
called
underpass
w
pretty similar then to uh German
torture okay we have
arrived a street street
train oh this looks exactly like in SS
B
okay
next next
truck oh did I do well I think I did do
well it says
excellent nice it's not so difficult try
parking next
time
maybe and another one oh prattis
lava prattis
lava
let's go a
Vienna VI we got some
vienas this the one that pays better 37
uh
[Music]
3,730 ah this one pays
better oh the best paying jobs at the
top huh
well 4,000 isn't too
bad third is often pay best on your own
L with antire
what excuse
me Austrian wine with anti excuse
me are you trying to ruin my
reputation
reput I'll need fuel soon oh is it not
filled up between my travel
yeah VI sausage now so I had Sana
sausage in my
soup two days ago
remember
good now we are back again back again oh
oh
sh
[Music]
for
okay let's
go if you want to insult a city by
saying it's a h what does c really mean
it means like when there's nothing there
like usually you say it to a small is it
green whatever doesn't
matter it's don't worry it's not too bad
like calling a a whole country a [\h__\h]
hole um it's uh it's just you know it's
like a sweet little tease calling a city
a cuff you wouldn't I I think you
normally wouldn't call a whole country a
cuff you just call like a little city or
Village a cuff if there's like if it's
small and there's not much to offer or
so yeah like a ghost town yeah you could
call that oh [\h__\h] it's it's not good to
go it's not good to
go and now I guess we can go cuz he
go okay so I'm make for
by can big make for me hide now
yeah we're passing the McDonald's I'm
not getting my Big Mac today it's okay I
don't need Big Macs oh we're taking this
one who whoa they're they're oh they're
switching things off we're taking this
one oh [\h__\h] well
well
okay
[Music]
are we going
off not for long not for
long can we go to McDonald's can we stop
by an
an and Ana Ana is a a a a ger Austrian I
think
Bakery yeah
Bakery M caring McDonald can I have a
Happy
Meal
I don't know what I'm saying I'm just
trying to Road R in a really Austrian
ACC accent oh yeah uh uh this this is uh
possibly maybe uh the
Mon oh [\h__\h] hey you little bastard you
[\h__\h]
ass I this
oh yeah we are off the that's what I
thought
the yeah he pushed me are we in the
kindergarten this kindergarten
thiss oh beautiful and maybe it was
really the moon see it's the the the
ocean of the Moon oh ocean of the Moon
yeah okay let me turn on noral waa for a
moment uh yesterday I pranked you guys
so
hard oh I pranked you so hard how did it
feel guys huh so people were like oh you
have no prank oh oh [\h__\h] he got he got
in trouble for the
[Music]
shs no was not him I think I got you
good huh yeah people are saying ah wa oh
cow hello wa you have nothing nothing
prepared for uh April 1st I'm like yeah
no I was [\h__\h] busy with the Easter
stream so no I have nothing but little
did you
know okay no it wasn't really
planned but I did
see like maybe a week or so
before uh I saw
someone
mentioning the eclipse on maybe the
Twitter so
um and I was like a wouldn't it be so
funny if I like organized the coll maybe
it was a little more ago than a
week no I I was like really legit
thinking oh wouldn't it be so funny if I
did
a that street looks holy sh
whoa I think it's different but that
part looks yeah know that looks
extremely familiar holy
[\h__\h] um I was going to say yeah I was
legit thinking oh I should collab with
MAA uh on that day that would be so
funny um
wow
amazing but then I kind of like forgot
about it and I didn't plan it uh
planet
planet and then like the before I guess
I was reminded oh yeah tomorrow is the
eclipse and I was like well now there is
no
time uh and then yeah then then I was
reminded at the very moment when it
happened I was like oh I guess now is
the
eclipse and I was like well maybe I
could at least what if I remember
remember waa when you were thinking you
could collab with her well now it's too
late for that but what if we joke about
it what if we make a joke about it and
so I went on Sat I'm speeding oh
[\h__\h] no oh [\h__\h] it's 80 what my distance
was my speed certainly didn't feel like
uh how fast can I
go I've yet to got a have received a
ticket really is 80 too fast no 80 is
fine right 80 is what they want it gets
red after like 84 or so ho [\h__\h] there a
burning over
there oh my that there's there was a
truck collusion oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] that
could be a gas tank what the [\h__\h] this
is maybe attempt at
murder God damn even better than your
king cover yeah right oh my God I did I
can't believe so many of you guys fell
for it at the Stein hor ah no I I oh my
God we're almost in in
um oh my God so
funny yeah and then I I I it was really
spontaneous and the thing is I was like
not really thinking I was watching the
the stream from
NASA and I saw thanks for the
pinky I saw that it was already
happening but I think the moment I
joined
in it it looked I was like looking a
little bit back on because they have uh
DVR was it DVR on so you can look back a
little bit and it looked like maybe the
part where I joined in was the
first
eclipse on the American
land and then there were many following
right but I somehow thought there was no
more like this is the only one one and
in all of America you see this one but
no so I guess uh it travels Across
America cuz America is pretty big and it
had this path Across America right so
many people could see it that's really
nice but I thought I thought yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah ah I started
with me Mexico yeah I joined I joined in
at something that did sound a little bit
a little bit Mex Mexican I think it
might have been that one might have been
in Mexico
yeah huh but they were talking English
they were speaking English maybe it was
close to the the the city or so sounded
kind of like Mexican mat matatan yeah so
that was the first one right that they
broadcasted there of a totality Eclipse
oh nice what is that I don't know that
one uh so I was like yby yby yby it's
like I'm like halfway through with the
moon so I need to make my thumbnail
really fast I was like speeding I'm like
oh my God I don't have any PNG of moon
and I at Google and like there's really
not many pgs of MAA in Google that are
not like fan I didn't want didn't want
use fan art um cuz then I have to credit
and and I didn't have time for that so I
just like took uh this like PRD PNG of
her which was kind of funny cuz she's
like lying on the ground so I was
thinking maybe I can make myself lie on
top of her but then oh my God the moon
was getting closer and closer and closer
so I was like okay I have no time to
figure out how to how I can make myself
pose uh to lie on top of her so I was
like whatever just anything will do and
then I threw the thumbnail together
really really fast I tried my best
yes and then
yeah I put it up on Twitter I was like
here we are collabing now spontaneously
I can't believe I rarely how how often
do I do a gorilla a real gorilla stream
in a year
once this gorilla maybe
0.5 times per year
cuz there must have been years where I
haven't even done it once you guys
believe it we already talked about how
me and MAA our like unit name shouldn't
be sun moon it should be eclipse and you
guys don't your brain didn't go there
ha
pranked so funny it's so funny you guys
get excited huh call you
off and then I took so many of you guys
into the eclipse yeah and then I tweeted
and I sent the Tweet cuz it was really
spontaneous sent it to MAA and then it
took a while for her to reply uh she was
offline for a
bit and then she saw it and she's like
oh my God like first she was like cuz I
I wrote to her like I sent her a tweet I
was like we're collabing right now MAA
and she's like what what how and then
and then the next message is like oh my
God that's so
funny she's really enjoying the joke The
Jerk yeah it was so so
funny and then I was thinking well okay
then I realized there were more
eclipses there were more coming so I was
like oh wait maybe we could still do but
no I would have liked to do it from the
beginning and then I had an idea
headlight oh [\h__\h] how the [\h__\h] do I turn
them
on how do I turn it on
l oh yeah L I guessed it excuse me
game you didn't teach
me yeah
um would have been would have been cool
but then I ended up watching that stream
from NASA for quite a long time look at
that Sunset behind
us wow The Sky Is Burning The Sky Is
Burning oh no we have to drive away from
the
sky
yeah I was watching for quite a long
time and partially okay maybe because I
never saw a I think or did I maybe it's
a child once maybe I never saw a full
eclipse but
um oh it's raining oh
no oh no but I was like first thinking
like why are these people like [\h__\h]
partying and cheering over the moon
moving over the
Sun and some people like got really
hyped up and then this one woman from
NASA like the she was probably not from
NASA but she was like reacting uh on the
NASA
Channel and reaction
streamer and she oh wait wipers there we
go
nice
faster and she was like once it happened
once the totality happened I don't know
if you guys watched it but she saw she
said something is so funny to me to me
directly she said it to me directly okay
she's like she got really emotional and
she's like oh my God this is like ah
holy [\h__\h] the world is ending it's
burning and
thundering uh that's not what she
said she said like oh my God this is so
amazing like I don't know this is like
not what I expected it's like oh my God
like I'm like I'm just thinking like
what did she expect like what this it's
like not at all what I expected I'm like
what what what what did you what did you
expect I mean you you know what you
signed up for right you were uh
moderating some Eclipse okay what what
where are you expecting
exactly so funny but later on she like
um said the same thing but then added
onto her sentence she wasn't expecting
to feel so emotional about it I'm like
why you guys are emotional but probably
it's very very very different when
you're
actually uh experiencing it yourself but
that really shows how simple we humans
are but that's good because we're
chickens and phoenixes
so wa I'll get it I know I
know how do
I he's just turning the wheel endlessly
and it's not
moving
I'll do a circle then we'll go ooh we'll
go full
circle we're so simple ah I crashed it
to myself [\h__\h] no that was
possible oh [\h__\h]
how where is it where is it Anyway there
it
[Music]
is
okay
uh no no no
[Music]
no go go straight go straight
why you change camera yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
a okay let's just let's just make a big
turn if I can wait this way go back go
back I'm pushing A and S no okay I guess
that's
wrong straight
I guess it's D and S if I want to go
that way okay always think the opposite
way ah it's not really the result I was
hoping
for I [\h__\h] sh
order he doesn't
move am I stuck forever oh here we go
okay
sh oh okay that's get no that's
okay you got it you got it you got it
you got
it we're in the position to leave
immediately it's on
purpose already did to turn around so
that I can turn around and
leave sorry that was really difficult
but we're level two now and and and we
did an excellent job again
yeah
amazing uh I don't know what to
[Music]
do experience bonus finishing in how
about
this yeah sounds good more long distance
for longer trips AO thank you oh I'm so
good at this am I am I doll it's pretty
simple it's pretty
easy okay help out I want to go uh to
Gratz let's go to
Gratz but maybe there's no good paying
job to go to
gr or munic to lince would be pretty
nice
too yeah we don't want to go we don't
want to stray too
far or should we go to
Switzerland
okay I kind of want to see
Switzerland let's go L
kids you know the city grats skiing in
schling oo yeah schling is famous I
didn't realize that was in
grats oh no it's raining man hallelujah
it's raining man oh
yeah I have my lights on at least right
right are those my lights or are those
Daylights okay uh this this is is this
uh the fan L am I on the right side of
the road yeah is this the fan L the far
light that you're not supposed to use
cuz you're going to blind
people the wrong way
no that's
the
am I going to get fined for using the
the the high
beams we'll see I guess cuz you is I
feel like I heard about it before that
there is a find for using
it
irow okay it's for ah there's an extra
button for
that okay wait is it green
ah okay we go we're in Munich right now
huh ooh ooh Munich from Germany we go to
Switzerland man truck dealer discovered
man only for man manly men like
me but I want a truck from maybe
from from
Austria [\h__\h]
oh oh I didn't I didn't get find yet
well the police is over
there
uh what
what oh my God the
game there's something behind me go away
don't go so close I'm trying to go
straight I'm shoting
on my truck is a little bit slow to
react yeah okay here we
go here we go are there any people from
Munich
here or from Germany that no
Munich from
Bavaria then it also must be feel really
feeling really familiar to you German
here yes yeah
I don't think you are very German if you
answer with yeah it has to be
yeah two
letters
stop no freedom of speech no not not in
this
case not in this
case thanks for the membership gifts
I oh and and
track oh this track front has a
DLC gamma
gamma
okay wait am I on the wrong side can I
go right side
uh excuse
me
fuck6 bucks was I allowed to go right
side
there
[\h__\h] you Rose yeah no yeah I kind of
felt something was wrong
there
oopsie I just went where there was
space you know just trying to be space
saving okay here we go we're driving at
night now wow so going to see the stars
yo okay there's one reason why I did
feel like I wanted to be there and see
the eclipse with my own eyes they were
saying like you couldn't see this on the
video
footage as far as I could tell but they
were saying a lot of them were saying
like oh yeah now I can see some Mars or
a Venus or a
Saturn already right side
what and I was like oh my God you can
they were like seeing it apparently oh
the
wipers really
clearly they were seeing other planets
when it was
totality I'm like oh [\h__\h] that's kind of
fascinating oh was it just like dots
like stars like like you could if you
don't know which one is what does it
just look like a normal star like this
to you I guess I don't know I somehow I
know they're [\h__\h] far and you can't
see them no but like for me when they
said that I imagined them to be actually
like seeing them as big as the moon or
so oh they just look like you saw a red
dot but are they just bright
or uh do you see some like the Mars is
red right do you see Red Dot no you
surely only see like white right I guess
they just knew what they were looking at
that's why they were saying oh I can see
this I can see
that oh it is a reddish dot h
wow
damn okay now that I think about it it's
not so fascinating
anymore I can see it right now I see I
see the Mars yeah yeah
yeah
wait there's a orange dot oh and there's
a wait there's a purple and a blue
looking dot do you see the orange dot
it's between like this the corner of
hard to show I need to look on the road
okay what the [\h__\h] what is that orange
dot what they're so colorful all those
stars look so colorful what the hell
that's not
realistic what what are those Christmas
lights take your
meds no for real
can we just look at the stars for a
little
[Music]
while astronoma
trucker yeah so anybody here who saw the
eclipse the totality I think at least
one viewer cuz I saw uh something in the
kfb
hashtag is there somebody
W Nice
Bridge I saw it I did only partial I saw
I mean in person
okay I
did only
85% well so you were like close to the
path of totality the path of totality oh
my God that sounds that sounds really
[\h__\h]
epic sounds like a subtitle of a
game I saw totality I saw oh [\h__\h] let's
go yeah it went through Texas
right uh so I watched like five
six six or even seven of them I was like
shopping uh on internet while I was
watching that on a different
window yeah oh yeah 2017 I mean this
time did you did you guys watch it this
time
I think I was never
in before I was in all police I was in
some kind of some City in Switzerland
before what was it again but not Sur I
think New
[Music]
York what was the second one Al
hav
really famous German
[Music]
songor I don't know how it goes
on I saw that one in 223 there was one
in 2023
[Music]
what
here
I'm why the [\h__\h] do I not know the
lyrics thanks for the membership
welcome wait can I can someone pull me
up the lyrics I didn't Brak my phone oh
no why is it black and white who turned
on the monochrome uh mode what the [\h__\h]
what the actual [\h__\h]
why is it so [\h__\h] monochrome uh what
it's really
weird uh life is not always black and
white excuse
me that one German rap song
Oh you mean from Left
Boy left
boy that's a different song though
different left Bo
song
I forgot what was the other
one I haven't listened to Left Boy songs
for a long long long long time anyway
back back back back back back to Eclipse
so to what the
[\h__\h]
okay okay uh uh calm down it was a ghost
because I saw nobody oh [\h__\h] what [\h__\h]
I'm pressing
buttons I turned off my car on the AO
plan I turned off car on out
theun oh
no oh no slow slow recovery slow
recovery okay uh where was where was I
this is a nice [\h__\h] tunnel
wa wa that must be a famous tunnel it
looks so
nice all yeah so I was thinking oh man
too bad I can't see the eclipse or too
bad I didn't do that idea of me
collabing with Mauna during the eclipse
so I was looking up when is the next
eclipse that I may maybe even one that I
can see and turns out the next one for
America is long long long long long time
to go but the next one Europe is
apparently in
2026 that's considerably
close so I guess I got to stay in h at
least until
2026 um but then I need MAA to stay in
Holo also until
[Laughter]
oh let's see I'll I'll tell her we'll
make a little
commitment don't say
that I don't know man 2026 that's a a
long long long long long time to go
still what we just arrived in
2024 but yeah it would be visible in
Europe
and uh I think probably not in Austria
like the list said a few
European a few European countries but it
didn't say Austria might have to if I
want to see it in person I might have to
travel in
person for it but now I'm kind of like
oh [\h__\h] it was it was yellow [\h__\h]
shis all D
nor it was yellow I actually did not get
fine for that because it was was yellow
huh oh uh this is also yellow for
for we are in Switzerland we I don't
know where the Border was I didn't see a
border or is this the
Border not oh this says will
Common
then why are we in
a maybe it's another you know the thing
where
yeah
yeah yeah we're just driving for now oh
the
whoa who
we're in the [\h__\h] SCH
order L
skits L skids is let's go in German by
the
way whoa that that felt really special
but they didn't even have a border
control like we have between Austria and
Germany
what Switzerland how do you do it you're
not even part of the European Union
[Music]
right I'm not saying something really
embarrassing right
[Music]
now I'm saying I get the sh I totally
understand the
shangan oh they just signed an
association agreement with you oh really
oh so now they want to be associated
with us whoa whoa whoa whoa what was the
problem until now huh maybe it was like
a thing where they they had an awkward
like relationship with uh the UK and
it's like they broke up and
and wait was it for real something like
that and then and now the UK has been
gone for a while you know these kind of
things take a long time obviously so I'm
just making [\h__\h] up right now
guys so they're like okay now they're
gone now the UK is gone out of the
picture I feel comfortable with mingling
with you guys again they're like okay
I'm I I'm over my ex I'm over my ex you
okay
now you
drama okay
yeah and but Association doesn't mean
they're joining so to what
extent how much can I drive how far how
how how
fast where does it
say wait there it is 80 I'm [\h__\h]
blind I got to go faster otherwise I'm
going to get fin for going too
slow money hi money if you hear me speak
in the German accent here and there
little bit B uh please do not laugh at
me I am uh I am playing a long little
role trying to be very uh uh I think
they say authentic
authentic oh my [\h__\h] God can you
[\h__\h] make some
space I'm I'm a oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah on the
table teaching German means on the
table okay sorry I'm I'm not so
funny on on the furry Road what what do
you mean furry Road
I see no fies where are the I the or
CLE iion or some rer from the Santa
Claus
or I see nothing is it included in the
DLC the furry road is included in the
DLC in the furry Road are some uh
animals
or
Oh you mean the fury Rod what is the
fury
Rod I'm just [\h__\h] with you oh my god
what the [\h__\h] I almost bumped it
a okay I learned a lesson never look
behind oh
[\h__\h] okay we go we go into
outat please follow
me I I don't know how to use the miror I
don't want to switch my hands are
busy this is why I'm getting a a diver's
license and not a driver's license guys
this is exactly
why do you understand
now no one day I want to get a driver's
license one
day why why are you standing
still why are you standing still what
the [\h__\h] am I supposed to
do uh what
what what what where can I
go
uh do you want me to go on the left
side but is that is called G in
German pass through what do you mean
pass through I I'm going to hurt them
and they're GNA arrest
me Ram them
huh huh excuse me my navigation says I
have to go through here nobody else is
going through
here the game wants me to
wait how [\h__\h]
long there's no one behind me
either EX excuse me if only I could ask
them my schedule does not allow for this
move or I drive move or I drive you can
talk to my uh to my FMA okay talk talk
to my f
move I drive okay it's so
over excuse me you are blinding me with
your lights turn them off please or I
turn mine
on here we we w we we we we will we will
right back at
you they they do not care okay then I do
not
care uh can you please tur is right over
there I need to
go
here um what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you
yeah of course I
mean well what the
[\h__\h] what is this
normal going to the left but I saw
people driving uh on the left
oh [\h__\h] what was that is
what
oh wa I I made I made the path free
pretty much pretty much it's empty now
okay let me go over the cones you think
I get a fine for driving over the cones
I
think come
on go
St sh s sorry
sorry okay okay stop stop stop stop
stop what is with this
game normal random oh really this is a
thing that just randomly appears in the
game but like
man I have no
choice what's a jack
knife a knife that I'm gonna kill this
dude called Jack with probably
oh wait he's blinking is he planning on
leaving
now whatever I
go wait
[\h__\h] when the T trucks uh turn another
rout
what they will only disappear if I take
a
detour
how the [\h__\h] how the [\h__\h] do they expect
me to do this from
here well bye but if I turn here they're
probably also going to find
me no let me go straight wait the thing
is I really can't I'm trying to I tried
to position myself come on come
on okay this is
good
you are not the boss of
me I am the boss of me this is my my
company yeah I am not a rebel no I am
just the boss of
me oh what oh sh
oh ah this is a
problem
H yeah okay maybe you are the boss of
me
[\h__\h] I'm going to do the best turn of my
life this is my chance to prove myself
to you
guys onwards we go oh wait there's a
nice there's a nice oh perfect perfect
perfect
perfect I mix turn over
there and yeah then Z my na'vi tells me
where to
go I don't know where am I going here is
this like a gas station or is this one
of those truck
places
treat oh it's a tree
place hi sorry for intruding I need to
do a little
[Music]
turn oh they look like salami
sticks
yummy tasty little salami
sticks move oh I get it now I have to
like press the button again in these
cases then it will move okay all right
wait so now oh that was close it looks
close now we can
maybe well they asked me to go left but
I I got to go right but the na'vi
doesn't understand
and the navigation I'm going to go right
I guess you can reroute how do I reroute
is there a button for
that are they gone no they're not gone
yet just go
left huh huh no I cannot there is
something in the way oh [\h__\h] oh oh [\h__\h]
I am the GU
far oh God oh God
press M oh
[Music]
well I'm I'm just
uh how does this work I'm like almost
there there's no there ah I could go
this
way yeah yeah is this how I do
it okay okay okay
okay L
[Music]
skits here we go
yeah that's the only other
way my tank
yeah okay okay I'm going to find my way
I go straight and then I'll go left in a
in
a we do be driving
have you guys been listening to Cima H
we're over 300K now yay so I uploaded my
little short I think
maybe cuz I don't want to in confuse the
algorithm I don't want to risk it wait
did I drive wrong is this how it's
supposed to go yeah I don't want to
confuse the algorithm with me uploading
another video uh I don't want to risk
anything so I
going to wait until maybe 500k to upload
the Acappella but you guys I see have
already been working with it I already
saw some remixes and the one in the
beginning of the stream was by cow
carrot EUR beat
Chima cow carot is literally doing any
everything now cow carrot started with
mixing then added
MMD and also did a little bit of dabbled
in music before that already now
dabbling in music even more damn cow
carrot storytelling directing there's
nothing he can't do oh sh
whoa expected a bit more damage than 4%
from that but noce it's okay oh nice C
that feels good yeah
yeah okay okay this is like playing
Minecraft in third person now does it
feel weird to you guys but we want to
appreciate the the the scenery
right he's great great talent is Inspire
[\h__\h] sh oh [\h__\h] sorry I switched back
to this
camera I think it's a little bit uh
easier cuz I'm used to it
now I usually drive like this that is
very concerning please stop driving and
maybe start diving like
me I wonder where I can do my my diving
lessons you know what I could uh I could
I could to discovered
I could uh probably document oh nice
nice nice
flag I could probably document my my
diving experience I can put my uh my
action
camera on and show you guys so I've
never been to T so I can't really say
this looks familiar at
all I want to go any Switzerland
people any person persons from German
language people like to say persons for
plural people it's funny any
persons I've been to Lugo oh yeah that's
that's in
Switzerland unre not me I'm from really
oh [\h__\h] let's
go my S from Switzerland here have in
let's go
[Music]
it was yellow it is
okay oh [\h__\h]
man being a trucker is rough man
I could find so
much it's not fair
oh oh
[\h__\h] not
[Music]
again I miscalculated again back back
back back oh die oh die oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh can I do this is this allowed can
I do a curve like
this
I don't know can
[Music]
I [\h__\h] I don't know I'm so bad I don't
understand it's like reverse
thinking I can't turn my brain around
like that okay okay
[Music]
stop ah that was not so good what do you
say excellent
still I even got some achievements oh my
God they're so nice
what
excellent are you
sure WOW 7 hours of driving
wow thank you w w man you guys are so
nice for clapping for
me I'm sure truck drivers out there who
who completed like 10 12 hour trips
surely would also appreciate some
Applause
Applause for the truck drivers out there
woo good [\h__\h] job driving through
endless
countrysides with a really tight
schedule
usually
yeah man okay we have
16,000 wow so much
money what do you mean others didn't
even reach their destination who's
others next up Italy you want to go to
Italy oh we can we can go to Milan oh
wow
wa oh that's so
cool and then maybe we can Circle back
to
Austria we can go to seagen food or we
can also can we go from Vienna to CL for
yeah oops oops oops oop I want to
go what does this W that's really far
too holy [\h__\h] you know what let's do
this
one let's go to nen n in
Germany or the can we get
oh uh
uh
what I'd love to give that to
you oh I forgot the melon
[Music]
okay
yeah I don't know you know those times
when you just forget something that you
should
know
yeah I should know I should know it's in
my brain it's there I just uh forgetti
spaghetti little
beam
[Music]
oh
wait where's my
chat
okay was in my
job
okay once we are on the
autoban why why do people think this
fits oh is this that's not the exit is
it oh
[\h__\h] I can't go there can I why do
people think this fits truck
driving can I can I not open the gates
over there for me no game
sound ah
oopsie
[Music]
oopsy did FAA sing it
yeah I know I'm on reverb I'm getting
ready I'm getting in the
mood oh I save
wa I
oh trust in the
process all right cuz she had some kind
of accident right and then maybe people
in the clip put the
the symphony number nine on top of it
okay I think I can imagine seems very
fitting
woo I feel so fast oh my
God okay uh on the
[Music]
aoan fr
for drunen him
[Music]
sh
for
for where
[Music]
hold
should
[Music]
all
menion br
[Music]
I think I got it wrong
there
yeah now this is proper Trucking let's
go W
Exquisite H failed to oh [\h__\h] they asked
me to
weigh while I was singing the European
hmer mama
no
no no not
fair
I'll take it but I'll let's just say it
was not minus 100 what 40 bucks it was
plus because it was a tip for my
performance thank you thank
you fire drunken him sh
[Music]
[\h__\h] is it on
it's not even so dark yet what okay
enough singing I'm I'm I'm losing so
much money I already lost 300 bucks holy
[\h__\h] this is no singing Lane what do you
mean every lane is a singing Lane
especially there the right lane but now
kind of maybe honestly more the left
lane oh
worth
it normally normally just saying German
singing or talking in German doesn't
necessarily mean you have to go so hard
on the R I just did it for you guys for
the
r I'm a
pirate okay you guys want to go on the
left side or
what all right you kind of make me feel
better by staying on the right side I
feel like a strong and fast truck
yeah why are you so fast on the right
lane how do you do
it yeah showing
up showing off and I can roll my RS and
I
can drive while doing so
totally no no more looking at theat the
chat is so far I moved it it's like so
far come closer Chad come closer to me
every time I look at you I make an
accident we have a really toxic
relationship right
now no texting and driver I'm not
texting you guys are texting you
shouldn't be texting me wait I need to
there's a r St St I need to go there
because I need to tank
uh in German we say uh we have to tanken
we have to tank when we put gas in our
vehicle why don't you say that in
English we have to
tank it actually sounds so
good it's time to tank just like finish
same in Finland oh my God I have so many
fins
in my
chat you know one of the places I think
where you can
see the 2026 eclipse is in Finland I
think wouldn't that be so amazing cuz
might even be able to mix it with
looking at some
aoras oh my God I totally want to all
right let's let's
tanken let's
tanken
what do how do I oh oh I got to go on
the on that side oh [\h__\h] oh god
oh oh thank God we're not counting their
damage in the
store
uh are we good to this oh we're good at
this H stop stop stop use the phone key
to stop the engine e
press and hold the phone to fill the
fuel
tank
who we're tanking now we're Trucking and
tanking let's
go tip for a wonderful performance thank
you I lost so much money oh my oh we're
already full oh [\h__\h] a good
goodbye but can I maybe I should go
backwards I'm going to go back SE wait
716 they're covered by my employer oh
that's that's a good thing to not be
Indie I guess Indie truck
driver oh
[\h__\h] how do I make a good turn how do I
how do I go back
uh not like this it's going to rip out
those
cables maybe I should go straight maybe
I should risk it how we doing over
there we good oh apparently I took some
damage
okay wait I I I think I can I can do
it a I don't understand the Logics of
going backwards I don't get
it I don't understand like which way my
brain just cannot comprehend it
man
[\h__\h] save
me this is jack knife okay [\h__\h]
ah oh no oh H my brain my
[Music]
brain two different entity wait wait
this no I keep on making the same
mistake
too oh wait Leave Me This
Way yeah yeah yeah yeah this is the way
thank you w for finally understanding
what you're doing oh my god did we drive
for the whole [\h__\h] night
oh my God where's the exit is there an
exit over
there okay oh I did it
woohoo man this really makes me want to
go on an IR L road trip but I don't
really have time for it honestly this
event on the weekend would have been my
chance for an IRL road
trip but as I said this time this time
no
WWA uh-oh wrong side
yes
sh see
see so much
potential inside
me and a virtual trip yeah
indeed was that Korean writing on that
truck over there we got to we got to Al
in we got to see wait for me what are
you delivering
M don't go so fast I can't go faster
right now I'm only on 50 wait wait wait
wa wait wa wait wait wait wait
wait feel like it was it saying hey hey
you drove it to me why do I have to
pay
[Music]
I would I'm just like I'm not really
that angry I'm just like I think I was
thinking I could make you happy if I'm
angry that surely will make you
happy I just making a voice no I
wasn't no
no
okay I'm getting closer to the track of
my dreams don't go right side no he's
going to break up with me no excuse me
EXC excuse
me I'll never know I have to watch the
VA I
guess oh
man Angry German
B do booer
Baba booer do
wait I need to go like
this this is training me for the future
for the one day I'll I'll
get into a car behind
Z I was
lucky
to actually I've been in an accident
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I was going to
say I've never been in an accident but
there's one accid acent I've been in I
was on the passenger
scene that
um my friend I'm sure I'm sure my friend
learned a lesson from
it
yeah I wonder can we explain it with
this like let's say we're not in an
autoban but like in an actual like a
city I think I explained this before but
uh uh it crash I did not feel a crash
therefore there was no crash
huh they charge me so much money they're
ripping me off this tor alaban is a
[\h__\h]
scam going to sue
him going to sue
you I was I saying
uh what was I saying oh yeah so so so
imagine oh [\h__\h] no [\h__\h] I turned it off
again imagine a a
t-shaped street so there's one big
street and one side street and we're on
the side street and we're going we want
to go into the big
street and it was a case
of our mistake I guess well I didn't
drive but our mistake and uh I guess we
didn't look properly so we went into the
big street and they drove into us this
actually amazing I barely remember this
incident even though it should be so
traumat traumatic for me I only remember
the cuz we were driving to a convention
I only remember all all my
friends uh reprimanding is that the
right word reprimanding when
you're when do shs is that reprimanding
oh this
way yeah they hit no they hit did they
really like I should be remember this
better if they hit us in a serious way
I think they may have just
like no it was
huh must have been like really slightly
I I barely I don't even remember this
much but
yeah yeah no it happened because I
remember all all the friends being like
Oh my God how dare you put uh kiata in
this kind of situation and all you need
to be more careful when driving and the
the funny thing is that you know this is
a a Pizza Pizza friend okay Pizza friend
often is in charge of driving in these
kind of road trips to
conventions and pizza French just gets a
little bit too excited
sometimes and
uh
yeah before
before before Pizza friend got uh his
girlfriend I was able to sit in the
front more often okay because I was then
in charge of the music and this and that
and entertaining I
guess um and I was DJing nowadays I
don't get to sit in the front anymore
man times Chang so unfair wipers there
you
go
but I
remember cuz I was sitting in the front
we were on the aoan we were driving just
like the this and there was a traffic
jam or so ahead of
us and like he was literally about to
drive into the most behind car of the
traffic jam and I thought he's he was
seeing
it but apparently not because he was
still very fast when we were getting so
close and I had to like scream to make
him react and it was really
close it was really close and that
happened like two times or so but as as
as the front passenger I got like really
scared I was like dude you got to be a
little bit more careful I know you're
really
excited but you got to be a bit more
careful he's usually a good driver but
sometimes he gets to
excited no hate though I think he really
got
better yeah also these days I just uh
more often I I fly to save some time oh
[\h__\h] sorry wait is this the right one
yeah is it yeah yeah yeah
yeah then I have passengers on board in
the airplane but surely something like
that will not
happen always drive on the right no I
can drive on the left I was on the U
because I want to U
hole okay if I want to I can do I may
not be very capable of uber hauling but
I have dreams of my own okay you cannot
take those dreams away from
me
no hey don't oh why did oh the na'vi
sent me on the right side but then they
just combine again of the same road oh
that's interesting it was very
Scenic I've never seen a split like that
before it was the same road right they
just
what maybe they were like ah we don't
want to flly the ground too much here
like it's difficult and so they were
like okay like we want a fre lane road
but it's getting too high here and it's
too expensive to flatten the the road
the ground so we make this third lane go
all the way up is that is that what they
did
there you
think it felt
nice no we left and then we went into
the same uh road again I think
H you're in depth how the [\h__\h] did you
buy a truck early with Al
loone what skill issue just drive go
drive so yeah and that oh man can I tell
you that story again you guys already
know but I'm sure maybe there's some
people who don't know but that the story
that I just told you reminds me
of one of the scariest if you think
about it one of the scariest incidents
in my [\h__\h]
life so it was it was uh raining it was
dark and the car I was in parked and I
get out I open the
door and mind you I don't normally
wear lenses but on this day I was
wearing like color
lenses and and I get
out and I'm just I don't know why I'm so
[\h__\h] stupid or how that would even be
now that I think about it I really
wonder what was my position like that I
that this happened to me
but [\h__\h] too fast um I somehow when
closing the door or when going out of
the car I don't [\h__\h] know I it it was
a little bit lower than normal cars
maybe that's why that happened I don't
know I bonked my eyeball against the
corner of the car's
door yeah it went into my eye and the
lens left my eye car into eye door into
eye lens out of eye out of side out of
mind and I
felt I felt the impact in my eye I was
like who what the oh
[\h__\h] but it was okay I did not get any
injury in my eye one might think my
color lens protected me now don't think
don't do this at home don't think that
putting in a lens into your eye will
protect you
from this kind of impact this kind of
accident but
in some way I think at least like I I do
think that a little bit my ey was
protected a little bit by the
lens a little bit cuz if it wasn't there
maybe the top layer of my eye would have
been
injured yeah it did huh so wow that's
actually amazing thank you lens I love
you even though I I used to hate you so
much lens lenses
H you know there were times when I was
like really young n new like
15 I'm I'm 17 now but this is like so
long ago when I was 15 that feels like
oh [\h__\h] it why is the button so
close long time
ago I um I wanted to dress up okay when
I was really really young um but lenses
really scared me putting anything like
eye drops into my eyes or even into my
nose I was scared of nose
drops scared the [\h__\h] out of me and I
remember I bought those lenses because I
like I committed I'm like okay I'm going
to I'm going to learn how to do this
[\h__\h] now I'm going to get over it I want
to level up I want to go to the next
level of
costuming and and I remember we were
like in an Airbnb somewhere in Germany I
think it was for
like or something like that the lapic
book fair or or k or something like that
oh [\h__\h] I got to go ride dude
sorry oh
oh well you have droven into me uh not
my [\h__\h]
problem move [\h__\h] get out the way get
out the way [\h__\h] get out the way I saw
that one coming
though that was his fault no no no
matter what you
say wait I remember it was like night
time I was like in an in an Airbnb with
like my friends we were like four people
or so and I remember it was dark and
night and
and we were all sitting by the couch
table and I was trying to to get it get
the lens into my eye but I don't know if
if you guys ever tried putting lenses
into your eye for the first time maybe
you can
relate how how your eye just does not
want to do it you just your whole brain
you you can't keep your eyes open it's
so
scary and I I just I couldn't do it and
then my friends they wanted to help
me open open oh
sh this way right oh yeah and
like they would
y they would try to keep my eye
open and
also uh try to put the lens fluid into
my
eye but when the drop comes I'm like
immediately closing my eye I'm not
letting that into my eye nowadays I can
do it still kind of
like I'm still scared of eye drops and
and lenses lenses are okay lenses are
okay but when when I sometimes don't do
it on like the first
try uh then it gets all messy and I get
like little hairs and stuff on the lens
and it gets dirty dirty and stuff or it
gets too dry because those onetime used
lenses
they uh I guess you got to like take
them straight out of the fluid that they
come in and then you got to put them
straight in and then they dry up so I'm
like what the [\h__\h] do I do now normally
I don't bring any extra lens fluid cuz
I'm like I have this this one thing I
I'll throw them away afterwards I don't
need to store them so I also don't need
to bring any lens fluid and it gets
really [\h__\h] dry and then it's just
really [\h__\h]
painful and yeah anyway freaking
struggle really freaking
struggle my friend's trying to help me
we gave up on that
night of trying to get those lenses into
my
eyes we gave up wipers uh
whatever I like the
wipers uh how about this I don't
know level three tracker wow I've come
so far I'm just
chilling yay I show you a pain of trying
to put stuff in your eyes I've never
been able to handle eye drops y let's go
M so if eye drops the way I go around it
probably not what you should be doing
but I put the eye drop on my finger and
then I put the finger in my eye because
my eyes are okay cuz it's my own a part
of my own body they're okay with me
putting my finger in my eye and yeah
yeah don't worry I usually wash my
fingers before doing
that don't worry don't worry I I do it
really careful it's not like I'm rubbing
my finger all around my eye and hey so
far I've never gotten an infection or
anything that's actually
surprising but sometimes there's
situations maybe I don't know but I I I
try to be I try to be hygienic with it
and I try to be careful with it also
when I take them out I've seen people
take out their lenses without washing
their hands or anything before I do wash
I try to always like find like a
restroom or so when we're out and about
uh like you know and then I take get out
after washing my hands and then I throw
it away cuz I I still like to use one
time lenses I tried using non- onetime
lenses and I've noticed because I rarely
wear them I they just dry out in the
case and I always forget about adding
more fluid and all that also I'm just
too [\h__\h] B uh lazy to you know after
wearing them like wash them properly and
then put them in the L casape and always
wash the case as well etc etc it's just
so much of a bother so I just do like
one time only
lenses yeah
yeah and then it feels more hygienic to
me cuz I'm I suck at taking care of them
so it's more hygienic for me to do one
time only
lenses you want to get lasered I have
some friends
who uh got their eyes
lasered rmt did that my old
roommate she did that and she's really
happy with it okay we're going to do
let's go to
Italy just because it pays well but
actually it's not even that
good
[Music]
Castle I want to kind of go more like
like uh I want to try going to one of
these we can go from inbook to Lin yeah
let's do that we'll get we'll get around
salsburg again
you might work in Castle in the future I
think Castle is quite nice I think I've
been there before for some
convention wasn't the and castle
on they changed cities
though yeah right mm I didn't really
like
it it was like kind of nice because it
was located by oh
here what the [\h__\h] located by a
river which is kind of refreshing but I
think the reason why I didn't like it is
cuz I was still a real a real hardcore
loner back then didn't have any
ooh oh any convention friends at the
time so I was I was a big
loner how do I do
this this is like
math it's okay it took me only like a
few times of going to German conventions
to
find uh like a group and the funny thing
is do you guys want to know I I guess
you guys don't even know about
this you guys probably don't even know
about this this is like w it's like
really long time ago I shouldn't say how
long because you can do some
math um but I was still I was really
really young and I was at
uh wait not con wait was it no it was
wait I was thinking a different an magic
I was just thinking about the one that
was by a river or was I was I no any
magic no wait I'm mixing everything up
what's the one that's like doam me but
it like in terms of it has a nice park
SL
Garden no it is kichi I'm thinking of
kichi now the other one was something
else uh yo oh thank you for stopping
other people just drive into me and then
blame me thank you you uhoh okay we're
good we're
good H
so it was a a
convention that I used to like to go to
I went there quite a few times back in
the
day quite nice because it has this nice
big big Garden not as big as D me but uh
still back then pretty big nowadays it's
probably too crowded was already crowded
back then nowadays probably worse
and it's by like a quite nice Convention
Center which is I think it and it was
never inside before never oh [\h__\h] bought
a ticket
before I just roam around
outside we do that quite often in the
conventions here we just don't buy
tickets we just chill outside in the
garden or park that is adjacent to it
and we have just as much
fun but yeah
and and I I would is small and
friendless and then uh an
Austrian talked to me and asked to take
a picture of
me and oh it's green go wa no it's red
it just looked
green and uh that austan was pizza
friend and the austan was also also a
loner in German conventions and I oh I
think he said it was his
first German convention I
think
yeah and so we got into talking and like
oh we're both we're both from Austria
we're both loners and then we became
friends and then our whole friend circle
shaped around
us and to this day Pizza friend and
thanks me
deeply saying
that like without me being there it
would probably been would have been his
last convention not just his first but
his last
convention while it was
fun uh like I I made it I made it I
don't
know a nice experience I guess cuz I'm
so
cool and and uh was the
the the how to
say
gave I made it fun I gave him a drive or
so to go more into photography as
well cuz I'm so cute look at
me
yeah yeah and then because of that we
went to a lot of
conventions so funny because there's
there's plenty of conventions in Austria
but they're all small and I just started
out going to German
ones because a friend took me when I was
in that art
school
who I fell
over holy
[\h__\h] that was scary I thought it was
going to
explode whoa nice
Revival yeah so German conventions I
just thought they were kind of cooler
and bigger and that's why they're cooler
more fun so I just usually went to those
and then I ignored the Austrian
conventions for a long time until like
maybe two years later and I finally went
to Austrian
conventions and realized okay they they
might be a lot smaller but they can be
so much fun
too I remember there's this one
convention where I became friends with
my best
friend
and she we we were both still kind of
shy especially she was shy towards me
she oh okay okay this time I'm not going
to miss it she was still new to the
scene pretty
much but
we became friends and wait which side do
I go [\h__\h] sh can I is this okay what do
you mean failed
I
freehanded oh [\h__\h] these
people [\h__\h] them you
[Music]
suck
keep I saying nobody's working there
anyway they're all in there and drinking
coffee did you see anybody outside wait
waiting to weigh me nah they're all
inside drinking coffee and they still
take the [\h__\h] money from me [\h__\h] him
okay back to my best
friend so yeah after we became friends
and I remember there was this one
convention which was kind of kind of
like a five six more like 5 minute
walk from a little small
Lake and uh the first time we went there
we learned of that and its full
potential so the second time we went to
the convention we just we just didn't go
to the convention part at
all we took a picnic
blanket we had ice cream in a freezer
thingy portable freezer and watermelon
and watermelon yes watermelon and all
kinds of nice stuff and I think we even
had a umbrella some sun
umbrella and yeah we put a little Camp
there it's [\h__\h] nice we jumped into
the water
we all wore um a tire that we could swim
with yeah and oh my God it was so much
fun
so my my my my
friend my my best
friend would be in a cosplay and then
she uh at the end at the end of the day
we would all stop giving all our foxs
and so we would jump into the
water and just shoot water at each other
and there was some kids who were there
just because they lived there like
really small kids and they had some
stuff to like make make make some some
sand castles and stuff and we would take
those containers cuz they were just like
lying randomly on the ground we would
take them and make a water fight and
stuff oh my God so much fun this was so
much
[Music]
fun oh my God Good Times the reason this
can't happen anymore is cu that location
had the [\h__\h] audacity to change
location even though that was the best
best chillest convention we ever
had we had so much fun and we weren't
the only ones chilling there by the way
by the water not the only
ones really small cozy convention by the
water most people came over to the water
at least once during the convention hang
out there a little bit maybe also go
into the
water take some photos
there a lot of people were taking
pictures and then there there was a
bridge that it was up pretty high can't
really make an estimate of how many
meters but it was up pretty high and we
um okay not me cuz I'm I was a [\h__\h]
chicken
narissa how early did you stream
girl oh [\h__\h] I got to go ride okay I'm
so sorry I got to
go got to go
right yeah we're making a little little
round around
salsburg I guess are we around that area
now beautiful look at that Austrian
Beauty
landscape so there was a bridge I'm
talking about a convention right now to
all the jail Birds uh little convention
experience of me in the past in
Austria and so so at this little Lake
there was a bridge that was up pretty
high and people would jump from the
bridge into the water
speeding well excuse me
police [\h__\h]
you I was telling a nice story and you
were listening to Don't blame me you are
enjoying
it okay they would jump down the bridge
it was so exciting I I did not have the
gun for that but uh it was really cool
seeing people jump
down wow so
adventurous but the coolest part really
was just like picnicking at a freaking
convention with ice
cream and watermelon and other stuff
like I don't know what we had cakes and
maybe some Savory snacks too but oh
[\h__\h] was a Deep River no it was a little
Lake it wasn't that deep but deep enough
to jump into like the the river
uh the bridge was
over probably the deepest part of the
lake oh do we have to go to the tall
andt we are at the border at the border
beautiful border but we don't have to
go we don't have to go because
shangan I wish it was easy to do that at
us cons I've gone to easy to do what
jump from a bridge into the water what
do you mean
so from what I've seen so far just
by uh like appearing through
Zoom at American conventions cuz I've
never been to one in
person I only appear on the screen right
but from what I could gather most of
them are like in hotels or
so or like big convention Halls they're
just like uh I don't know I'm sure
there's some smaller ones too right that
are in nicer chill locations like what I
just told you where you could do a
picnic are there are there any small
conventions surely there
are but it feels like most of the
conventions are in like mostly inside
people don't chill that much outside
from from
my from my
impression yeah
right most star
hotels so the biggest convention in
Germany I would say is still doomi right
and dami a lot of you guys have
experienced right a lot of you even came
from America before or other countries
to experience it and you guys were
surely
Amazed by what doomi has to offer in
terms of location
that big big big
park next to
the next to the location of the event
itself like right next across the street
it's so big like if you at the furest
part of the park and you want to meet
your friends who are at the other furest
part of the park it's going to take you
like if you don't get interrupted by all
the people you'll meet on the way I
don't know that never happened to me so
I don't know how you how fast you could
get there but it will still take you
like I don't know 20 30 okay maybe 20
minutes if you walk without
interruptions maybe maybe 20 minutes
comfortably 20 minutes maybe I mean you
can probably make it faster but it feels
like really long cuz the park is huge
and you there's so many corners so many
different um paths you can take there's
like a a a Japanese garden which is like
always crowded as [\h__\h] but it has like a
little Pond and this and that and a
little waterf oh wow beautiful Austria
for you guys
Austria wait can I see how do I change
the map
again
um how do I change the map again I want
to see where we
are this is just normal Austrian
scenery F5 m
oh oh well I guess we can look at that
yeah it doesn't say the name of of the
leg it only shows the road but we're
close to sbur so yeah this is still sbur
land so it could be like any of those we
have a we have a cluster of lakes in
this
area my mom would probably know and my
brother would probably
know I guess it's irrelevant yeah but
it's
beautiful okay so what was I saying what
was I just talking about I how amazing
it is so there's this Japanese garden
and then there's like something that
feels like a
Greek ancient garden also with some
water there and there's like this big
huge [\h__\h]
Fountain thingy that is not just a round
Fountain there's a round Fountain but
then you go down and there's like a
really long lengthy lengthy
lengthy uh huh
Fountain H there there's so much stuff
there's a million like different parts
of the
garden could be mat or yeah could be
could
be beautiful beautiful so gorgeous the
weather is so
gorgeous are there any negatives
there honestly
no it's
amazing it's amaz I love it still I
didn't go last year people told me my
friends told me who went there last year
cuz I think I was in Japan or something
but my friends told me yo y y sorry no I
was in America I think I don't know uh
it was really [\h__\h] crowded this year
cuz last year that's the one negative
that even though it was the biggest
convention in the one they only had it
on Saturday Sunday while so many others
even smaller conventions had Friday
Saturday Sunday like they were longer
and thus you can also kind of a little
bit at least spread out the attendance
Saturday will always be the most crowded
but I feel like by extending it to three
days you will at least to some extent be
able to to uh like spread out the
attendance maybe and I just thought it
deserved it as such a great
convention and they wouldn't do it for
years and years and years until last
year and then my friends reported to me
that it don't know if it's because of
that or because of Corona being really
truly over but it was way more crowded
than before and you
couldn't
like I mean I'm sure they could still
move around properly is kind of I think
they oh
god get up get up oh [\h__\h] get
up May used no I don't I'm not in a
difficult
situation no no I'm fine to turn around
before come on turn around
again
no
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] hell can I undo what just
happened uh what do you mean what do I
do oh hey my Cargoes
fine view Okay iin
g i I don't want to tow I want to
continue
driving
829 oh it will be charged by my emplo
covered by my employee okay let's go
let's go oh that's nice I love that
sentence it will be covered by your
employer that's such a oh it's so
beautiful sounding it feels like a
melody in my ear like music in my
ear okay D where the [\h__\h] are
we and they're going to open that up for
me
right hey what do you mean visit service
I've been there can I leave
now how do I get back
to there you
go you can you didn't repair your truck
oh oh why do they make me Spawn
here sorry my my truck is just doing a
little bit of stretching
[Music]
exercise yeah there you go yeah almost
almost almost almost almost m
no wrong side again I just can't
think it's okay this works
right repair
please just do whatever
what
24,000 huh but I'm not paying this
right covered by employer right yeah
repairs are covered oh my oh my
God he are we
done
yeah whoa
T that's a lot of money
shees thank you
employer
wow oh I mean I'm probably going to get
my [\h__\h] butt kicked for
that and they'll never hire me
again but yeah
awesome BR just lost her job and doesn't
realize it that's okay I'll just go to
the next
one
damn damn shock of my life man where the
[\h__\h] are we
[Music]
lint Lo gets
lint I've been to Lin a few
times maybe once or so for maybe a I
think there must have been a convention
but actually I haven't been there so
often I've been there once for sad
reason I only remember this memory
sadly h
Lin is kind of like a it feels
like it's more of an industrial city in
Austria and so there's not much to do
there at least back in the day when I'm
but I'm the story that I'm talking
about so I think I was like again 15 or
so and back in the
day I was really really really
really into Japan I was teaching myself
Japanese right and I was watching some
videos on YouTube Back Then
YouTube well this was many hundred years
ago so YouTube videos weren't so high
quality anymore and Vlogs
were a vlog of someone I think it was an
American girl or
so document ing her experience as
a uh exchange student in Japan was super
special and I watched that and I was
like I I want to do
that and I got really obsessed with the
idea I wanted to live Japanese Student
Life at any cost at all cost
but it was going to be really expensive
Endeavor it would have to be kind of
like one of
those sponsored ones and I think I found
a program at the time
where if you're like special to
them they will sponsor this for
you and for an interview for that I
traveled alone
15year old WWA sorry traveled alone in a
train to lint for first time in her life
took that
interview and was turned down and cried
a lot about it because that was like
pretty much the only option I
had I so sad uh but
then that's when I was like I don't I'm
not going to I'm not going to let this
ruin my
dreams it seemed like the only option
but I'm not going to let this ruin my
dreams and then 15-year-old
Wawa started working on another route to
Japan yeah taught myself
Japanese really
fast and
with
16 actually I think I was still 15 I I
turned
60 during my trip I went to Japan alone
end of 15 it's kind of [\h__\h] crazy
story alone to Japan flying alone to
Japan I was 15 I turned 16 during the
trip and then after that I moved to
Japan and was like I was like what I
mean I went back and forth cuz yeah I
had some opportunities went back and
forth from auster to Japan several times
like I would be 1 month in Austria one
month in Japan two months Austria two
months Japan and so
on I didn't go to a actually I did kind
of kind of go to a school but not like a
normal student would I just took some
dancing and singing
lessons but I had interactions with real
Japanese students and stuff
and yeah that went on for a few years
and uh that's how I
made that dream happen one way or
another what the [\h__\h] is happening
what's in the
way there's nothing there except the
train coming soon maybe oh wait I'm in
the I'm in the wrong
thing
[Music]
wrong shut the mother
I don't know how
to I don't know how to control a truck
this is always the one thing that messes
up
everything
ah so I just want to
say like I think I'm really the prime
example of when things seem oops really
[\h__\h] dire
and you don't think you have any way of
making your dreams come true like it
really seems
impossible in some
way you should be able to do
it of course it's not going to be easy
of course there's like maybe sacrifices
you have to make maybe there some weird
okay and also it's difficult if your
parents like if you're in a situation
like me and your parents wouldn't have
allowed it then you wouldn't have been
able to do
this my my my mom allowed it so I was
able to do it but she could have very
well said nope actually kind of crazy
that she allowed it if you think about
it but if it wasn't for that then I I
wouldn't be here today
probably I think she
just trusted me 15-year-old WWA had the
brain of a 25 no not really but m
I already knew Japanese like fluently by
then I learned it so fast cuz I was like
really pissed off that I didn't make it
maybe I was H I do think I was like
around 15 It All Happened very
fast when I did that interview to get uh
into an exchange program and got turned
down to this
day I I still kind of regret that I
wasn't able to do like a proper exchange
student thing I really would have loved
to get through through that experience
yeah that there was a little bit of
spite really towards the exchange
program uh rejecting me that was
definitely a little bit of spite I'm
like I'm going to do this [\h__\h] myself
then [\h__\h] you
guys I'll make it happen
somehow one way or another I'm going to
do this
yeah yeah
so anything's
possible fine I'll do it myself
spite is a great motivator for real for
real it
is fueled by
Spite just like my truck no I will do
another
job let's see what do we got
whool lber n
Castle so here in lapic is lapic book
fair that I went many times and you have
to imagine I went from here with a train
sometimes with a bus a night bus it
takes so
long
yeah long long time
ago what are these
trips I still want to see CL and
for there is no CL and
fo Clen foot is such a funny name there
is no CL fo stb
oh oh These are so cheap I don't want to
take such cheap
jobs there's
one it's one of the cheapest but I'm
going to take it because I want to see
the beau
Machinery sometimes you shouldn't do it
for the money you should do it because
your heart wants
[Music]
it yeah
yeah I mean usually that's the best way
to do things but sometimes you got to
hustle sometimes you got to do it for
the
money oh nice we got a little back bench
that's
cute is it are people allowed to sit
there or is it just for
sleeping they can't sit there right
there's not even seat
bels okay let's
go VI the capital to
Clen just sleeping right
H for sleeping actually looks kind of
tiny cuz usually there's like most truck
drivers are male I would I would think
surely there's females too but like most
are male so I assume they're probably
really like a lot of them are big on the
bigger side how are you going to sleep
there
sheesh let's get
truing let's get clocking woohoo
actually now now I look at the OBS
screen with the dingly dangly up there
it's adorable oh my God it really looks
like it's hanging up there it should if
if only it was
moving
right talking and
clucking oh should I sell merch like
that but actually that's I guess you
could do that with any kind of keychain
really you could
[Music]
dangle can you not just dangle keychains
down there I don't know what the [\h__\h] W
your car is beautiful
[\h__\h] oh the car looked interesting from
the front
go go
go I do I don't have a car so I don't
really know is there like a specific uh
attachment that you need to dangle
something up
there was that a muscle car no it
definitely was not there there's not
going to be any muscle cars here I
wonder if you drive in America cuz
there's an America truck simulator right
hey your [\h__\h] fault don't say you
didn't see me see me coming I know I
know I'm too far on the side but I was
trying my best to slow down I didn't see
you slowing
down okay all right I'm sorry I'm
sorry okay who here owns a car in the
chat say something wait I went the wrong
way that's okay oh did I actually no all
according to K Kaku me me me me should I
should I
sell um you know those trees that make
it smell
nice I wonder if I can make merch like
that with a chicken or oh a chicken KP
bucket KY bucket
design H but I doubt we could really as
a realistic piece of merch put uh Fried
Chicken smell on that you might have to
do it yourself I'll sell the shape the
dangly and you either just you know go
to some drive-thru and to KFC or so and
get a bucket fried
chicken and then just make your car
smell like
that by itself or or you before you go
on to drive maybe you just rub rub the
thing in some fried chicken at home
you'd be hungry every drive for
real but that would be so cute ah too
bad we can't make things that like SM
why am I going have I not been here
before I guess I did
miss uh the the right
turn Okay this time I turned way
better
H I was here before
over
here okay I was a little bit
distracted yeah I even stopped this
time W hi
wuu how you doing I'm enjoying the game
I guess you you played it before too huh
I think I remember you wearing a trucker
hat oh do I go this way
yeah
okay
we somehow seeing wiu's name makes me
think of something I feel like I dreamt
of wisu
recently outfit soon ah today I saw I
saw they're all getting new
outfits but I didn't see oh was it today
stay stay
stay
today
today I wonder what kind of outfits they
are because the they're all getting
outfits right so is it like like last
time
they're uh last time isn't like I mean
like when they're all getting the same
type of outfit is it going to be like
Indonesian Style again or
who knows I really like those outfits in
the
illustration they had
for the
ID was it
anniversary those illustrations and the
outfit look really really dope and I
feel like
they
uh embod their personalities really
really well in those
illustrations and their sense of style
feel like Rea waya absolutely
nailed she was how to say I can't say
Raina nailed it because she didn't do it
somebody drew it they nailed it they
nailed wa uh they nailed it the way they
embodied her oh man it's difficult
difficult what crash for real what is
this
where where there's no one behind
me what I didn't crash
anybody you want me to crash somebody
what is this land am I [\h__\h] what the
paranoid or what's happening I'm going
to get paranoid I heit a ghost is this
common in this game like some bug it's a
second time they're charging me
money I didn't hit the wall either I was
in the middle of the
road
what oh come
on you guys have to warn me when it's
like time
o when it's time to use the
lights cuz I cannot I cannot judge I
don't have a license you're telling me
do you have to already turn on turn on
lights when it's like this
it seems very bright to me
still comfortably
bright we what did you see
we what are you saying you saw here I'm
losing speed oopsie how fast
80 should I just turn him on all the
time why is my truck making these
noises why is it making these noises
noises like I'm opening some kind of
vent every time I I put my foot on the
gas hello thanks for the
Wade my car is broken again H please
pull okay okay this time this time for
oh no it's on the very very very very
furest right just going in in the middle
it's not good enough for you guys you
suckers you every single one of you you
oh this time you're not drinking your
stupid ass coffee huh I hope you choke
on your coffee I hope you get poisoned
yeah I hope you I hope you get poisoned
and then you choke and then you fall
down and then you wake up again in a
healthy
manner thank you for your cooperation
mhm mhm you know you know what word is
in that word cooperation
Coupe chicken Coupe be careful that is a
sign be careful of the chicken
cop they're going to Cluck You Up
if you try me one more
time I'm going to send my chicken coop
flying right at
you they will learn a very important
lesson a very important life
lesson you
know um I had a
dream last night where it was a
continuation of the live stream I told
you about where I went to school
right so
somehow part of in part it was a tiny
tiny tiny tiny part of the stream for
real is my car broken this normal where
uh I got a phone call that I was
expecting more or less and it was like
telling me about the exam I took which
was a math
exam and it was a really important one
and it was telling me that I failed
it and I cried my eyes out because I
kind of knew it I was getting my hopes
up that maybe this time I wouldn't fail
a math exam for
once but I freaking did once again I
felt so [\h__\h] stupid
felt all dumb but that was just a tiny
part the rest of my dream was more
nightmares attached to each other like
there was
murder there was definitely murder in my
dreams it's kind of [\h__\h]
crazy or attempt at
murder I wasn't murdering and I wasn't
murdered I was kind of like
watching observing at that point of the
dream I just I just wasn't part of it
anymore kind kind of weird I don't I
barely remember this
stuff I was happy to forget
it that was me you focus on math well I
wasn't involved in it so but I was
involved in the
math y bastard where was I supposed to
go eh I'm already on the right side
[Music]
lane isn't even trying to slow down that
bastard
who oh I had I heard the
oh oh wait no no no it's still my
[\h__\h] vent of a
engine on exell I know but I was trying
to get back and the exit Lane is also
the entry
Lane I think that was the case in this
case and then and then what if I just
came from the entry Lane and I wanted to
enter and you're not making space what
am I supposed to
do we are getting closer and closer to
clag and foot clag and foot by the
way I think you would translate that to
like
uh Fort of
worries worries or complaints or I would
say it's more like a worry kind you
could say Clen is complaint but also I
would say when somebody
be they can also be like
sadly uh
fortnite so that's an interesting name
kind of sentimental kind of sad isn't
it maybe I'm translating it wrong okay I
translated it wrong it's Crossing river
crossing okay so River Crossing
of
sentimental uh
complaining okay okay we did not have
the
accident this time for once okay it's
turning
um okay
stop
damn sometimes these these Els these
trucks they just go like boom and then
it goes boom man and when it goes boom
it goes boom really big got to be
careful uh how's it going
okay so many buttons
and we go I want to go there is no one
else come on let me
go I'm scared of the night please I'm
scared hello is somebody operating this
thing oh here we
go break St exist no I Tred I tried but
it was too late wait oh this
is oh oh okay only one lane on this side
or
what but this is good practice for me
for the future but don't worry I'm not
planning to get a license anytime soon
probably not even this year this year
I'm getting my diving license my diver's
license yeah you heard that right my
driver's license all the
snorkeling has enlightened me and I'm I
do not want
to do anything but snorkel all my life
from now
on yay chck
sh it's okay my employer pays for it
wasn't I supposed to go that over there
I think it just thought I already went
over I can still go you want me to go
there
no I'm sure you want want me to go here
come on there we
go is
been in
TB that's all I got to see of the city
that's like
nothing but where is the
city damn I I got to say I was pretty
lucky with salsburg being able to see so
much of
salsburg this is nothing what like what
what what this not that's not even a
City I mean they're just cutting off the
whole city I get it
uh-oh I did it I didn't have to go
backwards let's
go
woohoo gabig
beat but I'm sure there's more than just
gabig beat industrial of um the city I
want to see going to go in person then
thank you
another job well done
good
good wait we're level four now
woohoo nice what do this
do high value job offers on oh [\h__\h] I
should have done that a while
ago y we got 30k now we would be already
over 40K if if they weren't charging me
so much [\h__\h] money for ghost crashes
or whatever and not weighing myself
properly when I was just a lost
child
H H any upgrade what do I mean was that
not an upgrade or you mean I can do
actual like
oh who
oh what uh uh Mercedes Benz I don't know
um I don't know my truck is the one that
I use is this one no no oh
I get better breakes what is which one
is the
break these are not brakes how do I buy
a better break these are not
brakes I don't think can you buy better
brakes yeah maybe after I get my own
truck M okay okay okay
okay uh I think
leave it at that for
today had a lot of fun though I should
do this again hope you guys enjoyed
especially the first half where I was
being German accent
waa telling my child
tangents yay thank you thank you truck
driving very
fun had a good
time hard to control like my biggest
enemy is like turning backwards or like
turning a corner and [\h__\h] that's a good
thing about aaban is that most of the
time you go
straight there just everybody around you
goes straight too amazing concept of a
road autoban I love say
autoban Li
autoban we need to see more of Europe I
want to go around Europe I am the
European of the world the the European
need to play more driving games what do
you mean I was pretty good with a normal
car in GTA you saw me driving in GTA I
was really
good using a truck is just a whole
different level cuz you have way less
like you
know
dynamic uh uh
possibilities for real don't don't be
like this you know I was good in GTA and
I didn't even I wasn't even driving that
carefully and I still was able to
maneuver my way through this the busy
City you know it you just don't want to
admit it yeah honestly we're pretty good
there there you go here oh you mean here
too oh thank you really it's not so
difficult it's not so
difficult can you really play this with
a wheel by the way like a wheel
controller
imagine me buying one and then we have
like a wheel hand
cam yeah of course you can I should have
known I should have known do I have to
save this or we're going to read a
little bit of super chats of course but
a
safe
safe wow I normally don't play Simulator
games but this was a lot of fun I like
driving reminds me I think back in the
my children times I played one like I
think it was also a truck
simulator uh I wonder what game that was
my brother would probably know what we
played it was some kind of truck
simulator I remember playing when I was
really really
young really
young and and uh uh
um
uh uh put the autoban
they was 18 whe of Ste I don't know what
game system I don't even know if it was
a PC or if it was a console I think it
must have been a
PC 18 we of steal my childhood that
doesn't really I mean if anything it
must have had a German title and then I
would know it from the German title
probably cuz back back then small wava
would not play games in English no no
no Mario not Mario car I remember there
were
aoan there were AO ban and I had to stop
at like um um like little gas stations
and
stuff I must ask my brother I will ask
my brother and then I will uh tell you
okay
okay next time I will know and maybe we
really do a German only Euro Truck
Simulator in my German channel one of
these days oh yeah one thing I wanted to
say the member stream tomorrow
unfortunately I can't do the thing just
yet I think because I'm still like
troubleshooting something with
accents for like live streaming I'm not
capable of live streaming yet uh but I'm
hoping that it will resolve soon and
maybe next week member stream I will be
able to do it so for tomorrow I don't
know would you guys be
ready relatively short notice but like
would you be ready to start watching
buck with me or is it still too early I
don't know if it's still too early we
have April
now when is this coming out how long do
we need feel like it might still be too
early but we can start with one season
and
then it's not too
early let's
start uh yeah I guess never mind it's
kind of difficult maybe it should be a
members only stream on the weekend but
I'm currently always always keeping the
weekends for Yakuza streams
so and that will probably take another
while until my weekends are free of
Yakuza I actually no never mind maybe
like
only like next week and maybe we could
finish next week I have a feeling we can
finish next
week but then I probably want to stream
something else like The Witcher it seems
like we're already getting Witcher PC
perms I applied for them it's looking
[Music]
good me of the week is yeah right for
like watching a whole season
I was thinking I would I would want to
do that on the weekend for you
[Music]
guys time for you to pick a movie since
we got the sh last
time
Ah that's so nice of
you the Germans in Discord had a lot of
transl oh what one the Discord why in
the Discord why you not translate in the
chat so everybody can see what is this
discrimination why you not share the
information with everybody in the
classroom eh what's wrong with
you you asked that too I don't know why
they didn't why didn't
they classroom
classroom
[Music]
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm Shook at thanks for
the membership thank
you Discord by okay join join the
Discord join the K fast parking oh now I
realize the irony of what I named my
company in the
game parking was the least fast thing I
did in this game
oh the irony let's say it's on
purpose I just
realized oh
man okay let's go to the
office follow
me follow Z me guys did you get did you
order the froggy Wawa merchandise the
link is in the description also please
please stream Kima my new song it's very
important that you stream it and enjoy
it and melt it into your brain but also
get the froggy while merchandise it's
time
limited
yay link is in the description link is
in the
description I ordered yesterday thank
you I bought two set thank
you nice F those are here thank you just
like the wheels of my truck the wheels
of the truck go round and round round
and round round and round the wheels of
the truck go round and wound wound and
wound can we stream can we doing a
stream of
course second device or second window
usually you should do probably second
device otherwise it's not going to count
it probably maybe even second
account wow and round they go round and
round and
round I have okay yeah I should add it
to my original song section yeah but it
it's okay I think that's really not like
that much of a problem that it's not
there right now I I'll add it though
thanks for the
reminder thank you for the reminder I
will get to it
eventually uh is this a teaser for next
song no I haven't started working on the
next song yet but um I actually had a
meeting today with
staff about um my next musical Endeavors
told them what I want to
do and also asked about you know the
booth outfit thing if I can put outfits
on my model if that's allowed and all
that so I asked that I don't have an
answer yet but just uh laid out my
questions like that
more thumnail like this W then I need
more art like
this fingers crossed yeah I hope they
say yeah yeah but yeah I don't know I
hope so I hope so but I don't know if
it's even compatible if that stuff is
compatible with my model I don't know if
there's something there that might be uh
a problem I don't know how these things
work you have a and swims with Arts yeah
that's the thing I usually keep those
for summer thumbnails like I didn't use
them all summer even if people drew me
in swimsuit because I was like ah I'll
probably need all of those in summer for
summer themed streams and all that so I
keep them I keep them on the side oh
wait why is chat not working by the
way there you
go Okay so
oh this sweaty trucker is now going to
read your sweaty super
chats
salty let's see where did we leave off
last time also I'm going to play some
music actually this whole time I had
music prepared but you guys didn't even
seem like you needed bgm and I kept on
yapping even though I was worried about
yapping well I shared I shared quite
some intimate details with you
I mean literally taking you through my
hometown and saying where my old school
was questionable sharing of information
but it's probably
[Laughter]
fine it's
F you
[Music]
know oh
man so I had actually only I bgms
prepared from Whole
Live Well I have 6 DMS but oh for mommy
some
oh
what
oh oh oh my mom wants to
share
something okay I'll read
this cuz my Mom requested
it oh she even translated with deep
L uh
okay I
quote here are a few thoughts I would
like to share with you after my daughter
told you her story again was the first
time though when she first arrived with
the idea of going to Japan I was
horrified only with time did I realize
that she was already learning Japanese
and could not be dissuaded from this
goal but we didn't have the money to
finance her stay there no was I
sure mommy I'm not going to finish that
sentence that's maybe not good I didn't
think it was a good idea but she was
very good at communicating her beliefs
after she assured me that she had found
a good and promising way to go to Japan
we took her to the airport my heart was
trembling and I had to realize that my
childlike
daughter childlike well I was a child
would now be on the other side of the
world H I wrote to the Austin Embassy in
Tokyo and asked if I could contact them
if any problems arose I was in constant
contact with her and believe me it was
not an easy time for me nevertheless I'm
glad that all the Calamity has led to
you now having a WWA and at the end of
the day I'm her biggest fan of course I
am yeah I think she just wants to say
that or just wants to get the point
across that she did uh not just let me
go without being worried that she didn't
just like look away
and uh did not care or worry she did uh
I think that's what she's trying to
say cuz I was
leaving on a jet
PL
don't know when I'll be back
again oh babe I hate to
go no you're PTSD oh no oh don't cry cry
me
River cry me
River
actually the irony of leaving on the Jet
Plane don't know when I'll be back again
of that less cuz I my flight back was
canceled and I was actually terrified
then no was it canceled or did I miss it
one of those
things and then I was like what the [\h__\h]
do I
do cuz I was still so young right and I
I was like what the [\h__\h] what
what and all of alone didn't know what
to do I made it home one way or another
don't worry I
walked I walked A Thousand Miles and
more across the water like
Jesus I no I didn't swim I
walked now that's when I learned how to
fly yeah no
can't you just fly yeah that's when I
learned how to
fly flap flap
flap okay okay wa I was going to read
Super Chat TOS where where was I going
to where were
we I think I got it the Easter
stream the EAS stream oh oh my God
there's a million cats that this
I haven't seen this since the last time
I coab with
fauna a million cat stickers holy
moly the the the rain of snails is crazy
oh my God the saplings are very very
friendly with their snail
stickers wow
overwhelming okay this is uh the
thumbnail
cute so hard to fit everyone in and then
still fit the logo in without covering
too much of everybody and I still want
to keep everybody like decent
sized it's
difficult everybody looks so
cute
yeah and you see the logo has the
elements of the games the race the the
flag is l
I mean it didn't really I thought it was
going to be more like a race like last
time but it wasn't really a race in the
end so maybe the flag is not so
appropriate and but yeah the the egg
balancing and the the the boxing in the
boxing
ring boxing
eggs what do you mean the invisible egg
is visible here what invisible egg is
visible
here ah I was like what what in what can
I not see that is invisible that you can
see the invisible egg that was supposed
to be visible in the in the game yeah
yeah yeah
true sadly it wasn't visible but it it
it
existed trust me it was there it was not
just
a pigmentation of my
imagination no a
figmentation of my imagination figment
figment of my
imagination we had that
before okay here we go Cruz dun Sky dun
oh my God your Super Chat was sent twice
with the same
text it was both of Pinky I think that
must have been an accident
Sky you'll get a kiss though to make up
for your oopsie wh s pouring some
[Music]
water yeah Skye thank you for the pinky
that is kind of a red because you said
two it's April 1st to me now but this
time I can't think of any tricks so
instead let me just uh wish you a Hy
Easter and April Fool's Day thank
you than you sh if if it wasn't for
Easter I if it wasn't like literally the
next day April Fool's Day I would have
planned something for April Fool but I
forgive you for not thinking of any
trick because I also didn't think of any
trick how could I how could I have
repaid you for fooling me if I had no
way of fooling you but I did prank you
yesterday uh thank you for the sweet
message M hope you had even though well
I think Easter probably means nothing to
you but I still hope you had a nice
Easter with our little
stream you got me
good I sent to almost the
same wait that are you saying there's a
joke in there somewhere cuz yeah I see I
see just the the only thing I think I
see is the the period at the end missing
yeah there there's no joke in
here so there's no there's no
trickery you didn't do that purpose
you're just pretending you did now so
that you can look cool or
so for
sure yeah I'm pretty
sure what the what kind of question is
this this seems like you have some
ulterior mode
Miracle what icons from geometry Das
online icon kit are your favorite I have
no idea what that even
is should I look it
up
Geometry
Dash is that the same thing online icon
kit
icons what what is this how would I
know there's a lot of them
good I played this
game what is what oh how would I even
describe to you which one I
like there's so
many why do you want to know
this why do you even want to know this
what are you doing all this
information uh just one of the cat
ones or I guess maybe there's only one
cat one the other look like a cat too
just do the cat
one I'm confused just a project you had
in mind what are you
doing give me the cat
one is is some elaborate plan to get my
Social Security
[Music]
number have you ever played a RI game
before c so what game was it and how far
did you get in I did I mean even because
just because my my song was included in
one but other than that not much but I
mean I probably did play one or two more
yeah Grove coaster was the one where he
know to was included but I'm really bad
at Rhythm games so it's not really my
forte trombone champ I guess
you Trum I don't know if trombone champ
can be
considered uh yeah I don't know is that
a game that's more like a I don't know
create music
game R heaven for tle music ah did like
could I play that before or somebody in
whole life I wonder if we have perms for
that then if somebody
playak those are pretty difficult
because I want to look at the the video
that they prepared for the visuals and I
want to sing along as well but I got to
focus on the on the rhythm game part
really
difficult I think s was the only Ian to
stream it what we from
Heaven oh really somebody did play it
then Japanese girls play them before
really there you say there's tunka songs
on
there from Hello
project for
real interesting but I generally don't
care much for RI games so okay what do I
do with all these cats am I supposed to
read those all out I guess I will they
probably never hear the Danon but I'll
do
it Katie bcoin or KY B ecoy D Anthony
Teasdale D snip D Wolfhound Wolfhound D
classes
[Music]
d d
Hypno
Hypno these are names that I normally
don't read so I don't know how to read
them moral Tom
kazus
beats what are you doing disguising
yourself is one of the saplings I know
exactly who you
are you're trying to match them oh G Umi
you to Dan thank you misery danan
Splinter Man danan username no Danish or
hey I know that chicken I know for a
fact you have feathers on your body and
many of
them Mis F thanks for the pinky ah
tearing it down just keep calling
[Music]
me such a Miss F Mist
fist such a Mist fist
[Music]
did you did you
notice did you notice your name is in
the
song it's like a motion Mansion but now
it's a Mis fist Mansion just for
you isn't that
fun you're forever engraved into
Kima
yeah
I know that's not how it's spelled but
you can totally say it sounds like that
such a Mis
fist it gets close
enough really freaking close same word
for me same
word happy Easter Happy Frog week and
happy April Fool's Day get
pranked oh how the tables turn don't
they miss fist you wish for me to get
pranked oh oh
oh I hope you were one of the pranked
ones
yesterday oh how the turns table don't
day my friend seems like you are not
even in the chat right now so I don't
know the answer I hope you got pranked
yesterday I wish a prank upon you
R AR man D rain than lunar D yuk Mike
thanks for the pinky happy Easter waa I
just came back from Japan glad I found
the waa plushy there you did you gave it
a new home he said he's on a plane a man
that's too bad I'm kind of tired so I'm
going to be VOD gang for this I really
hope your toe gets better thank you if I
would squeeze the the tip of the toe
then it would hurt but uh I don't
squeeze it does it doesn't hurt
generally so all is
good all is good all is well in my toe
neighborhood Tober
Hood
sadly no it's good it's good I'm glad it
doesn't
hurt thank you you I'm I'm hoping you
give this W plus a great new
home yeah cuz I'm guessing it was like
at a reseller shop or so make her feel
desired and wanted not like oh nobody
wants me like in Toy Story
okay
no she just wants to be someone's
[Music]
plushy zly than out run the win D y'all
are joining in on the snails what the
hell sir k d job 47 d
Evan SC Bishop sword Works K Ranger d r
d TK purple wolf D Mr Obi D lofter and
rage bird d v
faction
Pride High Age Diego
AR you are a kfp member but your icon
and everything says you're more of
sapling so that this makes
sense me
J Spirit v d e d graa d j j d simplon
Dan reconcile dangan
simpleton but you also same case dangan
copper Chef dang sacal dang seven
Channel what this this you're your icon
looks like a silver light blue FAA who
is
this NOA
than king shark dun Raven Nightwing dun
sapling bat dun Aster
dun Viper vipper Viper Vier under the
Lemon Tree than stoned wagon
than can St stoop St
spank St
Stone wagon D again night bearhead
D unknown D
El Paul dang fman mer dang V FR dang the
great Mo dang C dang life dang John T
Dang or tit Stone drag Dragon dun again
Chate D Michael D Yumi Ribbit D Mas D
Foria van Jones d v dun Jackson FB dun
frog G dun my own D Jackson f d py d Mr
v d KY STS d i a beep D AK sf2 Dan thank
you you're welcome Majin d d welcome to
the
membership uh temp to talk thanks to the
pinky frogy is not only my Oshi but the
ultimate Idol I don't use his word too
much but I love frogy Wawa don't confuse
her with kiia that one is
okay tempor
work temp work you little
[\h__\h] usual
room three
months
goodbye
beep pressed the
button door opens you get sucked
in you now is in usual room for three
months you cannot get
out speaks in Aster r
and Obelix what
[Music]
asterisks thank you I can't believe I
won my own game it's
ridiculous and I even didn't I put
myself into
the into the what was it called uh Z
zle Cup first so even if the scores
beforehand would have worked because I
would have still been in zaco I think
but I already was in z i put myself on Z
and I still won but I was also Midway
through I was wondering is this rigged
do the eggs not change their stats uh
after each round cuz we I asked for it
to be like randomized and then Midway
through I was like uh he just just
checking are these eggs for sure because
my egg won like two times in a row and I
just while the others were battling I
wrote a quick Discord message
and the answer was like oh actually I'm
not
sure it should be but actually I'm not
sure because we didn't get to test that
part that properly either no
time so I was also like H yeah wait
let's just let's just uh pretend
everything's fine but then I think I did
see the same matchup go out differently
at a different point of
time uh I think I saw
that I think so cuz yeah I think uh the
froggy waa egg exploded at some
point uh against a different one where I
saw it the other way around before and
you
know yeah and crony lost using my egg
but that could still mean that mine was
one of the stronger ones and then there
was one more stronger one but who knows
but generally the goal was it being
randomized each
round but not really
sure
huh crony did lose so that speaks
against the
rigging uh GL
thankfully oh I was just really [\h__\h]
lucky and I felt bad about it cuz like
already there was so much scuff so I
kind of wanted someone else to win so
that I would be celebrating someone else
someone else would be feeling better
about their experience
here I didn't want to win cuz what's the
point of me
winning that's so weird I wanted to
celebrate
us frog wins and frog week yeah I mean
still cool but like uh so kind of
annoyed that people said rigged someone
I don't know did they really complain
that much about it I think like maybe in
the beginning they were like H this is R
this must be R but then I'm sure people
were also just like laughing at just the
situation with like explosions and stuff
I I don't think it was I didn't see yeah
I think people were just like messing
around I didn't take it uh as like a big
complaint or anything
H the biggest complaints were in my
brain
anyway yeah it's fine yeah yeah yeah
people liked that part the most anyway
so it's all
good yeah later on I was like okay maybe
it's not rigged but in the middle in the
beginning I was really concerned like oh
God maybe it is rigged and I'm going to
get a lot of
complaints if I end up winning by only
using my own egg that's why like one
time I I went for a different egg but
then I saw uh I won anyway so I was like
okay maybe
maybe maybe it's fine to take my own egg
because then I saw someone else lose
with my egg and I was like okay okay
okay I can use my egg
[Music]
again I still won frogy want sleep can't
believe it why why why why why in a
tournament like this where I don't even
want to win but like when it's like
company stuff like Minecraft sports
festival or like Mario Kart uh
tournament and this like this kind of
stuff why why why why why can I not win
in those
situations
why
man man or like Mario Party
even well those all involve scale oh um
who just said
that just another
kfp you should change your name to just
another kfp in the usual
room one month usual room for you yeah
yeah I'm I'm giving those usual Rim
cards out again like I'm a
sheet giving out red cards and yellow
cards on the football field
on the fball
field thanks for taking a
bullet the one that jumped into my eye
stop jumping into my eye my eyes are
sensitive what do you mean I said
correctly soccer is the right
way
I was in German mode that's why I said
football
F yeah my eyeballs are kind of strong I
mean I did block the the corner of a car
door with my eyes
so that's kind of crazy where was
[Music]
I where was I
indeed ah
here J kber D Jacob langland D and PSY
D yay oh yeah right after this I
released my MV
tasar nice teaser did you guys like the
teas
are it has two super chats Psy Danon and
jaob 47
Danon
[Music]
and it's so nice you know when working
with K I don't feel like
um like uncomfortable or so asking if he
can throw a little teaser music
instrumental together because that's
usually I it's usually an afterthought
for me when the song release comes
closer I'm like can you make a little
little teaser thingy and then he last
time for Kima he did it within
like the hour of me asking him and it's
like in some way like he's remixing the
instrumental cuz he's slicing certain
parts together and it's not just like
cutting the instrumental in the like
beginning and in the end no no he's like
splicing some stuff together and making
something specifically for this purpose
cuz the good thing is also he he
understands exactly what I want because
he's also really into
K-pop my producer and he knows all those
K-pop teasers that I'm talking about so
he knows exactly the vibe that I
want and then with the teaser we create
with Kana uu with some scenes that he
already has we create a
fitting uh suitable little video yeah
yeah and for K uh it's so nice to work
with him because I know when I ask him
for this he he he'll gladly do it I
don't have to feel like it's a big
issue this is nice when working with
people you worked with
before now I understand why the idol
outfit was pink in the te who how does
that make you understand that that was
the original plan to have it in the
whole video but uh only after the teaser
even I want to say I did get the teaser
also approved by Ala
management but I guess they didn't
notice the the idle outfit looking
different
there and then for the real M I was like
guys are you sure that I I was the one
to like double down on it and be like
are you guys sure can you make sure for
real for real that I can really uh
change the color of this and then then I
was turned down I was like nope actually
no and that was when the MV was like 95%
done even though recent in between
steps before but I was like yeah be are
you able to change this without too much
trouble and he did it really fast so I
guess it wasn't the big
deal shouldn't have said anything I feel
like I would have gotten in trouble at
some point maybe they would have still
stopped me
but it's good that I asked earlier about
it cuz otherwise it might have been even
more last minute like hey hey hey 5
minute before the video premieres
actually you're not allowed to do
this that would have been terrible so I
think it's better safe than sorry to um
you know go through all the procedures
cuz I know how it works I've been in
this company for fre and a half plus
years I know how things work I know what
to ask for permission for I know how the
rules go and uh I know if I don't follow
them I'm going to be in trouble so it's
not that difficult to go along with the
flow it might be annoying sometimes and
it might stop me from doing some things
completely but it's better than but I'm
getting in trouble I don't want to get
in trouble
H don't want to get sued also by by
external parties you know let's say
let's say cuz in the end the company is
just doing this to protect us from legal
problems let's say we use some assets
that we don't have the proper
permissions
for uh like I don't know music or or I
mean kanu knows what he's doing and he
worked with us many times before but
let's say it's like a MV or like a song
cover MV or anything created by someone
else maybe someone who's working with us
for the first time um maybe they don't
realize you
know how serious we take it with
copyright stuff with having all the
rights everything so better safe than
sorry safety measures
yeah needs to be
taken don't want to strike yeah don't
want like I feel like especially with
big
creators even if it's not like the
intention of the person who's uploading
the content or whatever when when like a
smaller Creator finds out that something
that they created was being used against
their will or
something uh when they see that a big
Creator is doing it then I think I've
seen cases where it blows up like
crazy you want to you want to sometimes
also it doesn't because sadly small
creators don't have to reach sometimes
but Case by case but you don't want to
get into situation like
that yeah but I I wouldn't want to to do
that like intentionally I wouldn't want
to of course I wouldn't want to take
anybody's like Works assets whatever
without their permission
so bigger is much easier Target and much
more to gain from exactly like that's
like you you you could potentially gain
something from that so h i mean as I
said previously today sometimes you got
to
hustle
no but I feel I feel bad like one thing
that really really really annoys me is
when like artists smaller artists when
their art is being used on like from big
fashion
giants like H&M Za whatever like if
companies like that put small artists
art onto their shirts or whatever
without getting
permission that is
devastating although I think it's less
those bigger companies it's more like
small smaller fashion I think I don't
know are those companies do they do
something like that sometimes I feel
like I've seen it more of like smaller
fashion companies or like
random uh random
little
fashion things I don't know but like
especially when they're uh
non
Japanese then they think they don't
really understand they think they can
just take some random anime art and put
it on the clo thing nope dude what the
[\h__\h] think a littleit use your brain a
little bit use your brain just a little
bit huh how about
that somebody drew
that some people are so
delusional some people really are so
delusional they think they can just oh
my God sometimes see the screenshots of
like artists uh showing off the crazy
DMS they get sometimes where people feel
really entitled and delusional and
they're like hey you have to draw this
for free for me no you have to like oh
my God you're so [\h__\h] rude why don't
you draw for free from
me I I always wonder like how what
what's the matter with your
brain yeah you live in a different world
or something this is not how it works
people try to make money from this
they're trying to make a living out of
Art and all that you know you can't
expect people to give everything for
free to you
what
yeah but it's amazing it's it's like a
Wonder of
humanity seeing stuff like that like
w there are sides of humanity that you
thought were
impossible
damn entitlement
um I can understand why Ena shares her
illustration low quality oh yeah she
must have probably had that like had had
her art stolen A lot of times
before oh yeah for sure
H okay reading super chats from the H
break stream which by the way this week
the day after tomorrow I'm having a
collab with
Nisa wow look at this I love this
thumbnail w
no naisa
yeah I told her Nisa and know you didn't
finish the game yet like one round one
playthrough so if you feel like
it maybe maybe you can you know finish
it until then but if not that's also
fine I I guess I'll I might I might have
to carry her like the cool Senai I
am let's
go time to time to make my coolness
shine she gonna be like save me and I'm
gonna be like
ah here I'll carry you hop on my
back I wonder is there like from the new
characters that you uh unlock after you
clear ones is there one that's like
comparable to energy like are they kind
of like
mirrored mirrors of the you
know more or less is there like maybe
like coyote plays like n because she
also heals
herself not at all no other healer no
other healers
[Music]
she I wonder who I should play and who
who narissa should play when we play
together at least one Healer should be
there right one of us should be a heal
ER maybe I should be the healer cuz I
might have a
better eye on it while
fighting and she should just focus on on
fighting fighting
fighting I had fun playing
Chloe feel like laas when I tested her
maybe we should play a little offer
H Maybe
try L was
fun you guys say positive things about
every single one of
them but we don't even have to use one
of the new ones cuz I mean I didn't play
anybody but nii in the first place so I
could also play one of the other ones or
I guess if I'll be the healer then
really it's for narissa to
choose maybe make Anisa heilo so you can
try new characters you UNL yeah that's
also true
H well we'll see maybe we'll try it out
both ways like one try I wonder how easy
it is with two players one try can be
with her as the Healer and one try can
be with me as the
Healer what the good thing is now we can
save in
between I suppose that also applies to
multi player so if you fail we don't
necessarily have to start from the
beginning
right
H say spam healing items H I wonder how
how high our chances are
then we'll see we'll
see either you or Risa will experience
extreme lag
extreme
H would it be avoided if we were in the
same content continent cuz bibu and KY
obviously were also in a different
continent with the distance between you
perhaps Ella said she was really delayed
on playing oh
no oh no not that bad to be
honest ah ah for steam sharing yeah yeah
yeah is that why it's more delayed
H but understand cuz otherwise wouldn't
they have
to put up like their own
servers I trust the EU us data centers
would have a better connection between
the two it probably won't be extreme
yeah we'll see oh by the way I guess it
wouldn't make too much sense to have two
streams so it might just be on one of
our
channels maybe on the we but we'll test
it beforehand see who lags
more well Pro it wouldn't it be usually
automatically the one who hosts it has
less lag or is that not really the
case host has okay that's what I thought
host will have no lag okay
H I don't know I'll I'll ask Nissa if
she wants to have it on her Channel I
wouldn't mind having it having it on her
Channel
M if you're housing you shouldn't have
like okay we'll we'll think about
it please just show up and of course I
will I always show
up I'll show up to my oneon-one collab
don't
worry if you want the other characters
and or hard mod you have to well I'm not
we're not going to play hard mode trust
me you have to host yeah okay that's
true I guess I might have to host if we
want to use the new caus or we could see
it as an O opportunity to help her clear
the game once on her side oh yeah cuz
even if we clear the game together it
will still not count as a clear for her
right no we should just uh play on her
side and let her clear once I'll help
her
clear
yeah then she can get the new
characters yeah get give her the
progress Ah that's that's the one bad
thing about it not for me personally
that it uh is only available through
like
Steam remote play if it was integrated
into the game they could probably give
both players the
progress ask if she has any plan to even
playr I'm not sure if she has maybe I
can make it more fun for
her they're working really they're
working on it wow okay that's cool okay
so7 thank you for the as a tadpole I
kned before froggy W but I knew in my
heart I was wrong and now remember I bow
only to one Queen s Gooden wait that is
not right either I remember I served
takanashi Ki of kfb stand back I'm going
to
chicken hopefully not chicken
out thank you get on me that is really
inspiring and makes me feel
emotional thank you for opening your
eyes and coming back to your true queen
or should I say King
taking the crown now you calling me King
you're going to hear my sing you know
one of my favorite scenes in the MV is
the one closeup of my feet when I walk
and everybody's
kneeling it's a short scene but I love
these kind of scenes it's so
wow wow cinematic and artistic and
impressive the slow-mo walking slow-mo
walking is always dope but the close-up
of my feet walking through those people
is my I think
maybe one of my top three favorite
another one is like in the very
beginning when I'm still like a
silhouette in that like bluish
environment where the camera is like
turning and I'm dancing and like this
the very first one
uh
no in that in that
Melody cuz also with the silhouette you
can
see the body shape is so
beautiful thanks to also the coral and
showing that
off so that looked really
[Music]
nice
okay moving on Golden i d sh thank you
you successfully
chickened F cute Expressions little
hands fooled me but vava is my true Kam
Yoshi thank
you I ask what should the next kfp 101
video be would the origin of your Kiwa
nickname be interesting there's also the
baby or and the baby that is interesting
story but it's really not
um like it never comes up these days
anymore both I mean both if you mean the
baby that always send super chats or the
kfp baby that we had in the
beginning Alo the baby the baby appeared
doing my Tales of arise streams right
once and I was like oh my God you still
exist right or was that I think it
appeared at some point somewhat
recently and I was like over the moon to
see the b
b
yeah sand came back recently didn't he
no not really
no so I don't know if we should make a
video about that kiava
the the where that name the origin comes
from m is that interesting enough I
don't know
[Music]
last
month I guess
yeah they said hi like
once I don't know how how relevant in
general we we barely get updates about
the baby anymore that toddler now we
shouldn't call it the baby
anymore no s and is not in high school
now don't make me feel so
old good started yeah I don't know if
there's really that much to talk about
for that I'm not sure maybe we just
don't need another 101 video for a while
until we can think of something really
good we don't need to force
it can't believe Sander's 80 years old
now
no no
he's not that
old
H Dan zip danar again Nathan for Pinky
it was awful without you T everything
was green there was so little orange now
everything is back to
normal you seem traumatized are you
okay
thank you I'm glad somehow glad that you
were feeling sad and
terrified makes me feel like you you're
a loyal reliable
[Music]
chicken oh I've been looping the same
one this whole time
huh to be fair orange is
better I don't know I think Green is
great
too she likes to see us suffer yes I
love
it uh green is nice I mean right now I'm
wearing a shade of green turquoise is
kind of green it is a little bit of a
contrast color of mine so it's all
right yeah we got to sell that
hoodie
[Music]
didn't you always want to look like you
threw up on your whole body go by my
froggy wa hoodie for yourself right now
you can look like like a life-size
humaniz booger all day let's
go great
Ed thank you we all love Shrek greenia
you guys can use the froggy waa hoodie
for a Shrek
cosplay and
Al Lord space waterful
d pastel shop D thank
you oh nice nice
nice Psy D Edward Villa dang FR dang
FR FR what have you been up to these
days you seem like a little bit less
around than before
angel thank you Mac M jaob
HD she's still around picture of a
telephone unkown d py
d I'm here to are you here okay
all is well all is well
okay just lurking why are you lurking
huh do I need to get into my Euro Truck
and drive all the way to Italy I know
you're not in Italy but you
know I'm going to drive all the way to
Italy and do you have any family in
Italy I'm going to go drive to them and
tell them to spank your
butt
smooy
hi hi oh and she flop oh yeah and she
stand up again short flop oh did you
hear I think you heard what's wrong did
you go to the toilet or something and
you need to let me know
[Music]
or she's such a baby I love her oh my
God I love my
cats
I wish T would threaten to meet my
parents it wasn't
necessarily parents I was thinking of as
more like more distant
family like an aunt or
grand mother or grand
aunt is there such a thing as Grand a
she do a great
Squatch oh all all my cat trees are like
so what's the
word they look very
used honestly I think those kind of
stuff things you can just buy a new rope
and make uh like glue it on get rid of
the old one and you a she she rub
against my
leg I could probably you know uh
renovated so to
say but I never think of
it you know one of their favorite
scratchy things is not one of those
scratchy poles but uh like
a relatively flat it's smell like a
little bit curvy but it's like a a
cardboard thingy on the
ground it's not just like a plain
cardboard though it's made for
scratching so it's like you know when
you look at the card like a cardboard
thing from the side and you see the
inside of the cardboard that's how the
whole surface of this kind of
scratchy thing is they scratch on that
part the whole surface is like
that they love it they love
it but also that one is like so used up
and that one I don't think I can fix I I
just for those I have to buy a new
one your fourth birthday with kfps
tomorrow you're turning 30 oh [\h__\h] final
exam before I can graduate
oh very
eventful good luck and happy
birthday I have one of those but it's
inside a toy with a ball that's yo all
those things were like there's a ball
inside and they're supposed to play with
it or any kind of cat toy where they are
supposed to play on their
own never they always ignored
it
yeah so sad I bought several ones and
none of them they showed interest
towards they the only toy they play with
is like chunkers likes to play with like
bald up trash sometimes like chocolate
papers wrapping papers bowled up in
really tiny balls she loves those and
she will even bring them back to me or
like
a uh like a fishing rod kind of uh cat
toy are you still down there oh she's
still down there on my
PC
oh hi
smoy
I know you don't like to be held like
this snatched her I love her oh my God
she's so
soft oh man oh
man squeezing squeezing her fluff
grocery bags oh yeah yeah yeah they like
to play a little bit of gr grocery bags
although they prefer the paper ones to
like swoosh
into and besides that yeah that's really
mostly what they play
with just yeah
the the fishing rod
mostly also I have to admit I don't play
that much with them I should play more
with
them I'm kind of neglecting Play Time
quite a bit I have to
admit yeah but they're also so lazy
there's only only really really really
specific times where especially chonkers
will allow me to play with her
and then I have this problem where once
once smovie joins in chonas immediately
gets intimidated and yeah she just like
lays down
somewhere she gets
like yeah just
intimidated and doesn't want to play
anymore
so I try to I try to distract smovie a
little bit but still like she it's hard
to hard to hold her back and then
already chunkers will already have lost
interest in
playing it's difficult but I think
they're fine like chonas is generally
just a pretty lazy cat she's just so
happy all the time and she's just happy
existing and fluffing around and being
like
and just getting pets on her
belly
yeah oh yeah one one more way of playing
they really love is me chasing them
around the the
place the hallways and over the bed and
all that like chasing them and they're
like it's a a little bit of a workout
for me too running after them or like
running away from
them sometimes away sometimes
after
depends what's the favorite hiding
[Music]
spot sometimes they would lie in my
closet quite often actually but I got
doors for the closet recently so they
don't choose that
anymore cuz it's
closed besides that they don't
really they don't hide these days at all
they don't feel like they need to
hide they
don't why never see them
hiding maybe it's just I don't have many
hiding
places no they're always out in the open
visible I think they want to keep an eye
on me so that way that's why they are
really visible to me they're observing
me yeah during New Year I more or less
encouraged hiding didn't want them to
feel uncomfortable but they were pretty
chill right under the couch I don't
think they can fit under the couch couch
is pretty low and my bed is also like
touching the ground completely so
there's no
under h
anyway I got to move on I've been
reading so while and then I stopped
reading H where was I where was
I picture of telephone maybe around here
than unknown than p arst t
k golden
gamer
you m d thank you a Bas Gandhi D thank
you happy Bel
birthday thank you for the sweet message
too hope you had a great
birthday
yeah thank
youim thanks for the red super chat
let's go you got this thank you for
being so supportive my cheerleader thank
you and also for a pinky this level has
the op starts playing buff you got this
kiaha the O op op starts playing what's
op starts
playing opening starts playing what
you're just joking right you're not
actually saying something factual though
right
opening oh hey recently my batteries are
like dying on my uh iPhone
interesting still fine though but even
though it's connected it often shows me
like oh low battery
warning
weird uh L and
D 100% orange juice multiplayer board
game has gotten a lot of
Praise well is
it online multiplayer let me
see
[Music]
I see I mean we don't have to forcefully
play an A game that has orange in the
[Music]
name I don't
know it's very fun
H why not just play Mario
Party you used to play with friends in
high school what this
animal game how old is
this 2013 11 years
ago I'm surprised so many of you guys
have like memories with this
what you had fun with that other Mario
produ one that one is so
good there's like violence in it like
legit violence and blood it's so funny
we should play that again I should
organize one again
[Music]
thanks for the pinky the P party yeah
that was so good thanks for the pink and
sticker you're amazing too right screw
Lou Moonlight thanks for another red
super chat I was here s got the gamean
thank
you appreciate it that was really epic
me feeling in in more or less first try
everything only the first
boss what did I even reach the first
boss in the
first yeah right not sure where where I
failed I don't remember but um pretty
epic the next morning or
midday when I was like eating
breakfast I was watching koni
Senai try to clear like she was doing a
clearing endurance it wasn't much of
endurance though was watching and
watching and I was really wanting to
back seat I watched until she cleared it
oh
s that one was not on purpose
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I was going to say I was watching
her and
yeah I was really wanting to back seat
because some things she could have
really used some advice on I think but
then she ended up clearing and I was
like
waa
nice she did it she actually did
it became like you yeah but I I don't
think I wrote anything in the chat even
though I was in there for like two
hours
yeah say by S roll more
no yeah yeah yeah she was never using
power attack but then I was like oh man
her whole chat is telling her haha you
shouldn't use this equipment or so
because you're not using power Texs
anyway and like it it took her literally
until the very end to use a power tag
but I shouldn't be the one criticizing
that because I still don't know how to
use a power tag
no actually I know now after pressing
that I pressed that button several times
a little bit longer but nothing happened
so I was
like but if you press it even longer it
makes this like Melody note on N so it
becomes like a distanced attack honestly
after seeing that I don't think I would
have used it much or needed to use it
didn't seem that good so you it takes
quite a while to charge you
yeah I don't really care for that so no
need for Power
Attack
yeah most of the time you don't really
have time to charge so many things so
often because you're constantly getting
attacked
yeah partex are a trap in my opinion you
until you get the right maybe yeah if if
there's an item that can make you charge
power attacks faster then okay otherwise
I don't
know they now made it so you resist some
attack while charging oh really W okay
that's a a good update I
guess but they shouldn't make things too
easy honestly I really felt like there
being no way of saving until the end was
fine for me like I thought that's just
like just like uh Holo cure now they
added it and I guess I'm going to use it
but it really makes everything a lot
easier yeah but I guess a lot of people
just really wanted the safe
feature and the the shock with from Miki
put a lot of pressure on them
maybe but I thought it made sense to not
have a safe
feature yeah it's like a rogue like mhm
and in the end even if you fail you
still get it still gets easier for you
because you still G gain the experience
from it so it will get
easier I feel like now that you can save
it will feel less of an achievement for
sure I can say I cleared this game
before saving was
possible I was
here when that was a
thing
W let's go
little
Flex yeah protection against game or PC
crashing that's definitely a good
point that's where I would want it
[Music]
to I also cleared it before it saves
let's go high
five true gamer now she won't use magic
and Elder ring well yeah I won't use it
because I'm not going to play Elden ring
haha
ah you're ready for no continues on
arcade
games I'll bring you along when I go to
the arcade
center and where was
I oh yeah py fellow
Sky if you ever want to play another
beat them up game River City girls is a
pretty good one it may feel familiar oh
for you as well
h
beat them up as long as it's not like
the the Holo fan game of a fighting game
that we had cuz that's not really my um
those fighting games are not really my
forte beat them ups are fine I thought
River City was more like
that like a fighting game no it's more
like hole break
o
I see pleas I played it before but it's
not really my thing did you miss the
stream that I did on it then you can go
back and watch the VOD but I don't
really like fighting games like that
unfortunately I've made
my I've made my decision on that more or
less not saying I would never try one
again but I just realized Okay this not
really my
thing
M yeah I think
Callie yeah I think cie wanted to make a
tournament then I don't know she forgot
about it
maybe Street Fighter 6 yeah I I would I
I would play it for the for my friend
but the thing is also like I'm probably
going to play it for one stream only and
I'm going to be really bad at it and I'm
just going to feel pressured and
stressed and how much does it cost 60
bucks should I spend so much money for
something that's just going to
[Music]
be not the best experience for me I
don't
know and now it's been quite a long time
since the release so
yeah it's on
sale how much
eh
[Music]
keep it on the 2 hours and refund
after
smart
smart economically smart brain you got
there simple controls you don't need to
learn comos that much you say that but I
don't
know Evo is coming up the sf6 hype is
real not within
me I'm not riding it off completely but
no not now we have you guys know we have
enough things on my list Super Snake
Mario thanks for the pinky hi Ki glad to
have you back froggy turned me into a
frog and I can't say I enjoyed it much I
much prefer being a chicken this reminds
me of the end of last frog week where I
had an identity crisis and you assured
me that I'm a long
chicken
oh what was it I I remember the identity
crisis happening but what was it were
you like thinking oh my God but I
thought I was a snake or a
frog ah you're long chicken because of
the snake thing long likea you like
really the shape and the length of a
snake but with the feathers and the face
of a chicken but like a cute one not a
realistic looking
one cuz that wouldn't look so cute
anymore you look like a like it was
drawn by Duma all of you
canonically
canonically look like d chickens yeah
you don't look like IRL chickens no D
chickens I mean IR around chickens can
be pretty cute too but yeah if we talk
about a snake shaped chicken that's
going to get a little bit
creepy yeah
so that's how it is that's how it is the
slivering chicken the only chicken Among
Us that's slivers and not
walks must be a
struggle donation to The 100 orange
juice 100% orange
juice I don't know I don't really feel
the same hype that you guys feel about
that game I guess so
um not really interested if you can get
another member interested in that like
an Ian member I know you want me to play
it with uh n originally
but if you have
another member who wants to play it also
we still would need prims
but yeah I Googled it now before when
you told me about I have the window
still open
even
but
it's got that early 2000 charm H yeah
we've asked KY too what did she
say
yeah you can beat up chickens in it I
don't want to beat you
up okay I kind of want to but no I don't
want to want to keep
hug you got the same response as the
fighting tournament
H which
was
what oh no time
what I got a baby chick recently
what you went with Jimmy instead what
the
[\h__\h] okay she forgot
okay how much for the head boss uh
bucks mik voice the character in orang
just
what what but the game is from
2015 like after her off is in the
game
do they still update this game I guess
[Music]
so okay I mean that makes it a little
bit more
interesting maybe if I play it they can
put me into
it orange ju they should do a Oru
sponsorship what the
[\h__\h] but they probably don't know about
Oren's existence Oren's existence has
been kind of faint these past two years
or so and ever since the I guess not two
years ever since the uh after the debut
it became
faint well you know things are just like
that
sometimes yeah nothing happened or so
it's just like I don't
know you
know I still like her I I think she
probably still likes
me it's just I can't I can't always um
and keep up with all my and like I can't
be besties with everybody while always
being in charge of like you know
organizing all the collabs and stuff
between whatever friendship we're
talking
about we're still friends but like
uh there's there's so many people you
you guys would want me to do collab all
the time with but it's hard to balance
it
all it's hard to
balance ah oh yeah we did that you gu C
collab that was
fun
yeah it's hard to
balance unless you're Ana then the only
reason I don't collab with you is just
because I hate you just
kidding no if if it I I never I don't
think I ever turned down a collab from a
whole life member so
I will always be up for something if
somebody hits me up so I'm always always
ready you know I mean except for
Ana except for
Ana obviously do I even have to say that
[Music]
still uh well yeah I mean 3:00 a.m.
collabs are usually just like like those
open invitations like hey who wants to
be part of
this but people inviting me
personally that usually I don't turn
down also doesn't happen often
but I'm usually always the one
inviting so I kind of you know I i' like
to be invited too
sometime why do I hate Ana uh wait are
you taking it seriously I don't hate Ana
I love her okay you should know
better I love
[Music]
Anna I love her she's the
best she's the
best collab when no collab
ever out of
spite for like actually we're just
enjoying it we're just enjoying the
meme I love all the ID Girls this is so
true this is fact I'm going wait
how you're going to Korea tomorrow what
is there an event or what wait I saw I
missed your other super chats I somehow
my brain wasn't registering it but I saw
you send
some what are you doing what where are
you
going what I mean yeah you're going to
Korea why have fun why are you scared
why you
nervous I went there before it was so
nice I want to go again it was just so
hot but I think now it shouldn't be so
hot
yet so I will
be
nicer in terms of weather I'm
sure
[Laughter]
even if you were hating her you'll never
say it because I don't think H live
would like H members hating each other
in public so if you're saying it it it's
obvious that's a
joke no I really don't hate her
though I love
her oh
man I hate you I love
you
sure dot dot
dot love hate all the same if you know
play the
game oh you're invited cras Army at the
lck spring finals
waa let's go that sounds
exciting oh I think I saw your AR
cosplay
before
M let's go enjoy it's going to be nice
but I can
imagine I can imagine cosplaying Ari
being really exhausting cuz of all the
tails that you have to put on your butt
so
heavy I should play a fighting game with
any I should play oh what actually too
bad H break there's no like like
versus each other
multiplayer if
only I would tear her
apart PVP yeah there there
is
for online
multiplayer oh
interesting fighter and
WWE I don't really know how that game
works or how what that is
anyway wait since Han is here I'm
actually getting to her Super Chat uh
from previous stream from this one um
[Music]
G
David and H thank you for free red super
chats it's 5: in the morning now I'm
staying up late just to hear your
wonderful voice and then oh my God me in
your house dope I also buy a kiaha do
too and then I I was trying to sell you
my froggy waa merchandise and you say
please buy K froggy waa merch yes thank
you for the
advertisement I'm looking forward to you
wearing the froggy Wawa
Poncho or hoodie or whatever I guess I I
would say I guess it's a
poncho wait where is
it this
one under poop under poop undertaking of
the
underbob it's a special mission that I'm
sending you
on
puno it will take a while it was it will
be so worth it thank you mwah mwah mwah
mwah Mah mwah mwah 2 e or 2 G what does
that mean is wait your poops SI is holy
[\h__\h] those letters to me don't even mean
anything because they are so far from
reality to
me I was like what the [\h__\h] is is this
like a near ultimata reference
or I don't know what are you asking me
for you should know your own size what
should I should I go and measure them or
do I need to bring measurement
tape
H oh if you're not sure about if it's 2
e or 2G I I can go check I guess if you
need help with that you seem to be
confused should I go to Korea right
now I'm on my way I'm buying tickets
right
now I'm willing to
help oh
man too much lesbian be careful careful
k
too
much just
kidding get them I have it I have it
right
here when I showed this measuring tape
to my brother he laughed at me it's a
it's from
dael it's really
cute someone wear bikini now and say
what what me but mine are not e or
G the pink one I bought what what you
what you know my measuring tape thingy
it's a oh hi chunky it's a it's a bear a
teddy bear a pink teddy bear pear and
the nose is a button so if you push it
it will pull the measuring tape back in
it's pretty small but it's so cute and
it's really convenient and it's the only
only measuring tape I have at
home the only problem I have with it
sometimes is it doesn't stay stiff so
when I need to measure like something
for putting up a a picture frame or
mirror or I don't know anything long I
don't
know then it's it's it's not going it's
not so easy anything where you would
want it to stay stiff basically but
besides that I really like it wait let
me measuring tape ASMR you have the same
Pandora
and it also doubles as a a a nice toy
for the
cats it's so cute I like
[Music]
it oh my God so thank you and the
gamer thank you
thank you Yun Take It Monkey D looking
for the top d moonat d moonat what
happened but why did you go from Moon
frog to Moon cat you're supposed to go
back to moon
dog oh my God
accidental
accidental what happened are you okay
this is not done did you make a mistake
did you get confused but you got the
spirit or now did you forget did you
froget you're supposed to go back to
dog not cat that's not
you but cat is nice I don't mind a
cat I don't mind you being a
cat I forgot who I wait you're still
Moon cat is this in the April Fool
stroke going pretty long because you're
you were waiting for me to read the
Super Chat
py D Sky
D guys it's past midnight what the
[\h__\h] so what do we do
tomorrow should we watch monani or
should we do something else is it too
early serious talk when is that coming
out they didn't give us a date
right
the
h ah you're stuck because of the name
change on Twitter
oh I see makes
sense uh anyway please fall which is
around October that's still so long to
go I feel like we don't have to start it
now I know you guys are excited to do it
but I feel like it's kind of
early
don't ask
questions un not making the Super Chat
real oh wait is is the opposite not
enough lesbian more lesbian please more
lesbian
okay
careful No it should be the opposite of
careful like like less uh what's what's
the opposite word of careful of
more spicy more
spice uh please uh
careless Full Tilt daring yeah Reckless
yeah yeah it should be Reckless that
fits
good by the way did you guys know the
Japanese there is
very it doesn't sound
natural but both the English and the
Japanese doesn't sound natural so I
really wonder where the hell this Super
Chat ever came from why
who wrote
this that's how it sounds just by
reading
it it's like this thing with like when
you learn Japanese there's nothing wrong
with this grammatically or
so but when you learn Japanese in school
they might teach you to like this is how
Japanese works this is how you make a
sentence and this is how you end up
making sentences in the beginning but
like it sounds so
unnatural that's why I'm glad I didn't
learn Japanese from a Japanese school or
so from like a language teacher or so
but through myself on my own that way
yeah this sounds very robotic this
sounds like a machine translation which
it probably is but it's also what some
students who learn Japanese from
teachers sound like sadly sadly sadly I
mean the teachers are just teaching
Japanese correctly but this is how they
turn out yeah they they speak too
properly and starting their sentences a
lot with watashiwa when in reality
Japanese people so fushi and they don't
they
they they barely use they often times
more they will address themselves with
their own name they will be like K that
may sound un natural in like our
language like English German and so on
but it's even more so natural in
Japanese language to speak in your uh in
the third person it will make it
more uh natural also for example you may
have noticed I don't use vachi at all
when I speak Japanese I use II which is
like uh a regional thing kind
of mpie also uses
it uh I'm like one of the few uses which
is actually pretty rare I just started
using it because I I lived in uh Kanai
prefecture Osaka before and I think like
using anything but vashi would also make
it more natural now don't force yourself
to use something like II just
because it's so
special no but these these ways of
addressing yourself will also make it
more
naturalash I feel like when foreigners
are not fluent in Japanese when they use
it it will just sound
forced generally any I guess it will
always sound forced if you still have
like a strong accent and not the best
vocabulary it will always sound forced
anyway in my
opinion yeah often you don't need to
address yourself at all the context
implies it's about exactly so you can
actually most of the time just do not
say your name or the Buu Ori or anything
like
that oh jibun I also use jibun sometimes
yeah
jibun when I refer to
myself jibun is also way more natural I
think
than
[Music]
it's like when you trigger the Twitter
plots the Twitter plots are like always
triggered what the [\h__\h] is wrong with
them go away
those trigger but trigger butts Twigg
buts those those those nudes nudes and B
bio those only showed up like I don't
know a month ago or
so they weren't they weren't an issue
before what the hell go away what
happened why are they here why are these
the aliens that
were that just are these just aliens
visiting us and trying to communicate
with us and we don't realize it and we
need to try to communicate back with
them have they finally come to say hello
and we're completely missing
it cuz we're not
listening but maybe we just need to
listen so okay B back back back back
back I think we're not going to watch
monar tomorrow at
least
should we watch something else or should
I play a game or should I do something
completely different I don't think I can
get the 3D stuff to work tomorrow yet
that's the
thing Diana Jones free huh we
could continue out yeah I guess why not
why would we go to a different movie if
we still want to do the Indiana stuff
did you guys say the third one was
good which which one was the the bad one
so to say out of the bunch you guys were
saying the second one was if anything
kind of weird the third one is better
right oh you do like it
okay the best four is heresy doesn't
exist really then we stop there four and
five are considered the bad ones what
happened oh no okay then we ended at
[Music]
threee at least at least Indiana Jones
was able to count to free
unlike portal
and uh what was it
halflife at least they can count
to
free yeah val dot dot
dot and
GA what should I
eat I still have some of the soup but
it's like
the the
third
day and after making it a love it out
for like 6 7 hours or so which it was
fine I ate it yesterday and it was fine
but do I want to eat it the third day
there's there's like four portions out I
don't understand sometimes it's really
just two portions this time this I made
four portions what the [\h__\h] how so
unbalanced what should I do should I eat
that if it's still good I should
probably eat it would be easier I'll
check if it's still
good I made the pumpkin se you made it
fried chicken with pumpkin seeds uh like
coating or just a salad with pumpkin
seed dressing oil oil dressing both is
great especially
combined I'm glad you're listening to me
and giving it the troll a cereal soup no
but I I've been eating I've been eating
more like cereals for breakfast recently
cuz I figured maybe my quasa diet and
my uh crab
diet maybe it's making
me feel less energetic
and also maybe fat
but
but the cereals that I'm eating are also
like on the sweet side with like
chocolate tea elements to it so it's
probably not the best either but I think
it might be better cuz milk should be
good to consume
milk for oatmeal I don't like
oatmeal I don't like it I don't like
it i' show you on Twitter but I'm Turbo
bonked from the hashtag Turbo
was that me turbo
pun man I love K thank
you so okay I'll think about my
soup otherwise I'll get a uh like
something from my
freezer
and tomorrow we'll watch Indiana Jones
3E tomorrow Members Only only Indiana
Jones
free sorry I couldn't get the I mean
maybe maybe I'll figure it out by
sometime tomorrow but then I still feel
like it's not enough time to
prepare next week I I should make it
work
oh okay
I've been I jumped into third season of
The Witcher by the
way I while keeping in mind that this is
not how it is in the books I am enjoying
it mostly so
far I'm I think I'm only in episode two
or so though at uh I at I'm at episode
two so far I think or episode three
maybe
even I did you like season two
was
okay you know I'm so confused the
beginning of season 3 so cuz you guys
told me they kept on they told me like a
million times a million [\h__\h] times
that Henry left the show because they
didn't follow the books blah blah blah
so you you absolutely bunk that into my
head and I
thought I
thought that he left by season
3 but you guys meant he left after
season 3 so did the did they stop
following the books after season 3 or
what or he just already like it changed
in season 3 but he accepted it or did he
hear that they're changing it more
oh what what was season
3 oh they had they changed the during
okay and then he didn't like it and he
left but I was like oh yeah so I'm going
to start season 3 now I guess it will be
a different actor so I I watch and this
first the first uh scene is geralt
fighting and there's no closeup until a
while later uh no still within the same
scene more or less but like it takes a
few like it takes a minute or so until
they show a proper closeup but I see him
fighting I'm like h i I'm lying like
sideways so I'm watching this whole
thing sideways I'm not looking so
clearly and then I'm like huh actor
still look act this actor that they got
looks really similar to the old one and
I'm like I watch more and he still looks
so similar and I'm like well I guess
they did a really good job in finding a
similar dude and then doing the makeup
and everything right huh weird but then
I'm like oh wait cuz the first line he
says it did sound to me like a different
person but then he talked a bit more and
it did sound like Henry I'm like so I
look up a little bit I get up from my
sideways position I try to look a little
bit better get a better
look and I'm like
huh
that's pretty sure that's the same dude
but I was still doubting myself because
somehow even considering that is him he
looked a little bit different from usual
like they uh I think you know makeup and
Camera everything looked a little bit
different from
usual so I was like
m wait what wait a second it took me a
while until I really was like CH it it
is him it is still him I thought I
thought he was gone by now you guys
Bamboozled me and then I realized nope
and he's still there he's still there
but one thing that you guys may not have
not test if you watched so far even um
one upgrade visual upgrade in season 3
that I really appreciate
is they stopped giving him lenses the
yellow lenses they're not giving them to
him anymore yellow color contacts he's
not wearing them anymore they went for
the effort of post editing coloring his
eyes Hand by
hand by masking it in post edit
which is a lot of uh work I wouldn't say
that that means it has less budget I
would almost say that means it has more
budget because color lenses cost like no
money you can throw them in the actor
will wear it and you have to do no
editing on their
eyes this way I think is more
comfortable for the actor and less
comfortable for the editing staff cuz
they have to oh my God every single
scene and can you imag imagine like they
have to like when they when they blink
or when they turn around and the eyes is
only visible halfway that's difficult I
imagine yeah but it looks so much better
in my opinion opinion I think you can
get good color lenses
but uh you have to look really hard and
especially colors like yellow are pretty
difficult because if you don't want it
to be too crazy intense it would look
too fake but when yellow doesn't look
too crazy intense it will just look like
brown that's the problem not so much the
case for other colors but for yellow
when you don't want it to be like
like wow like looking poisonous yellow
it will just look brown or
orange there's something chaing about
not using
CGI I don't know if for for if you
cannot find good natural looking lenses
then please use
CGI cuz they've been using that for
yenifer uh all the time and for for Siri
I'm honestly like her eyes always look
different to me so I don't know what the
[\h__\h] is going on with
that I mean
look her eyes I feel like sometimes she
wore lenses and some sometimes she
didn't but there oh yeah oh she
definitely did here oh I don't think I
can show you the pictures but yeah
there's there's definitely times
especially in the second season cuz her
eyes creeped me out more in the second
season than in the first
season but then now in the third season
I don't think she's using it again I
have attention to Dil that's just
because I have a lot of experience with
lenses like that and I look for lenses
color lenses that look
natural it's like uh a pet peeve of
mine
yeah as you heard about
today don't open any car doors yeah tell
Siri that'll be the end of her not all
these people chasing Siri the end of her
will be a car
door
he should consult for TV shows I totally
should like in the costume
Department costume costume
Department The
Witcher good things cars don't exist in
our time yeah
exactly Harbor line yeah why must you
hurt
me my eyes no my eyes are naturally
purple I'm not wearing lens
eyes I'm going to go now that was a
tangent that was completely
unnecessary oh hey do Tech when did you
send that righted Super Chat thank
you thank
you what do you mean Arif
Joe I do not
recall anything from you that made me
angry do you have a do you have a
conscious what's the word a
uh a h do you have a do you feel
guilty did you do something a guilty
conscience
huh well should I put you preemptively
into the uh into the usual room I can
put you
there today I'm feeling very
generous I never
remember oh that's why I must act fast
now if I must no you must not what did
you do I don't remember anything it's
okay it's okay now I feel bad I you
you're so you're so ready for it like
saluting and all that I I feel like you
you don't belong
there okay I time to wrap the up wrap it
up
please see a little bit oh you should
apologize for your member count not
being 42 months what's wrong with you
why is it only 41 months you hate
me
disappointing
byebye bye bye she's here look at her
look at her turning like she's in a
roundabout in Euro Truck
Simulator only 14 only 40 you guys are
okay I was just
particularly aiming at Ela pin Ohio
enjoy you're good you're good
guys oh happy belated birthday Mystic
Mark why do you wait so long to tell me
is it all because you notice I'm now
paying
attention thank you for being in my life
thank
you 42 months there you go this this
enish person is the only one who loves
me just
kidding you know I don't mean
it I should feel guilty for not being a
member for wait is 43 was 43 months even
possible what's our maximum right now I
think it's 42
right yeah 42 is Max yeah why what a
skill issue why are y'all not at 43 weak
weak
none of you love me none of you do none
of you 43 is the only way the only
number that will make me happy even
though wasn't 42 the answer to all
questions wasn't that
42 [\h__\h] that number I don't want the
answer because the answer is yes I hate
you
Wawa I don't need that I need 43
only that way I can leave leave live in
live in
Bliss oh thank you guys so much for all
the members
messages thank you but everything looks
very disappointing to me I don't see a
43 and barely any 42 what have you been
doing your whole life ah
43 there we go oh there we
go
that's much
better remember for 40 uh
uhuh can't wait for f Freedom amount of
chicken nuggets are you different day
[Music]
exactly sorry for the disappointment you
are such a disappointment my child
didn't you always want to hear that in
your life until
now oh damn my father joined earlier
well you didn't and what does that tell
me that you that you hate
me okay I'm going to go
now she's just like my real
mom sorry
[Music]
Mommy
ah
have a good sleep tenter thank you I'm
going to GL have a great day what do you
mean it's the it's midnight it's going
to be a great
night oh oh
who are you
guys who are
you where where am I what
happened oh why am I half
naked
who what's going on why is there a frog
turning and spinning in this
bowl
I sneezed my memory
away can I sneeze again to get it back I
don't feel it
tickling I don't know who I am I don't
know where I am I'm going to have
exential
crisis maybe I'll just fake
sneeze
ah hi guys sorry I felt like I just
blacked out for a
moment what was I about to do I was
about to leave
right Ana I hate her what are you
talking about
chy thank you for the Super Chat
though no more yapping bye bye
byee I'm going to get the truck out of
here
[Music]
byebye ah ah in German we say
in
[Music]