K KY it is your beloved wobble claw once
again and welcome back to the Holo Ian
Advent calendar yay this year the layout
is already featuring the full artwork do
you like
it thank you as always you can look
forward to lots of fun and unique little
videos to open each day from our whole
life English members at midnight GMT z
mine being the first
H coincidentally today is also the first
Advent so I went ahead to light a candle
on this pretty Advent rev that I didn't
make mine last year was prettier anyway
right also Advent calendar reception I
have my own with chocolate eggs let's go
do you have one too at home ah you don't
need one we have this one right I opened
the first door already surprise it had
an egg and in the egg there was an egg
and in that egg there was a a a bunny
weird stuff anyway this is just a little
introduction video but if you made it to
this point I have good news for you as
you may have seen I currently have
pre-orders open for collaboration
merchandise with Vite yes yes yes and
they were so kind to say yes to a
giveaway to take place within the Advent
calendar in collaboration yay yay yay we
got a love bite they're awesome and so
we are giving away some insane amount of
things even I feel like they're
overdoing it so let me tell you what we
have to offer for you
guys we have 10 of the kfp ramen yeah
five of The kfp Cutting Boards mhm five
of the knives oh y five of the aprons
five of the cute hats five of the
beautiful ceramic ballls and five sets
of the spoon together with the
Chopsticks yeah that means have you done
the math
H did you now you had time to do the
math those few seconds did you do it
there will be 40 winners in total what
the heck oh my God crazy they were going
to do even more what I said n no no no
no no we going to we're going to make
some real sales
too so you can participate until before
it hits 6th December in GMT Z how well I
want you to write a tweet with the hash
poolen Advent calendar and tell us which
was your favorite video last year
include the link to the website of the
current Advent calendar in it and if you
want to check out and remind yourself of
the videos from last year this is where
you can refresh your memory make sure
you have your DMs open within December
uh Vite will contact you directly if you
are one of the lucky 40 winners by the
way you can't choose what you're winning
it will be at random but all of it is
great you can only win one thing and
almost all countries even the ones who
might not have been able to uh ship to
on the website are able to enter so give
it a try you know only a few countries
are the
exceptions all right
I hope that left you in a festive
holiday mood make sure to check out the
calendar every day look forward to what
we are making for you what we're cooking
for you happy holidays from ental and
yeah thank you for the support make sure
to share this calendar with all of the
other fandoms too I would be very happy
if it reaches everybody yay happy
holidays ho ho ho ho ho