[Music]
feel it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
sry about so emotion
feel it rush through me
[Music]
we
feel it R
me feel it through me
[Music]
oh honey
is
[Music]
K
oh hello
[Music]
tummy
hord it's like still kind of stabbing me
but it's gotten a bit weaker I think and
I think it's better when I stay
still it just started like like right
before the
stream like the stabby feeling
[Music]
oh God I think I will be
okay today isn't really supposed to be a
long stream
anyway
oh
oh oh yeah wait I this was supposed to
be loading screen didn't I already use
it as a loading screen for the outfit
reveal at least that was the plan but I
think maybe I
forgot that pretty
funky you don't remember it then I
probably forgot to use it oh I did you
think I
did huh oh I did okay then I did I
suppose I
did but okay this is not not the right
Vibe right
now
M kind of cool though kind of different
from
usual how
[Music]
about oh I'm vibing to it
now how about
this yeah Jazz
Cafe we like
that okay
so I think I might be mostly alone today
I mean feel free to surprise me
myth feel free to surprise me anytime
cie was going to stream originally today
like about an hour from now okay
actually 40 minutes from now but she
moved it I think she needs
sleep I think she needs to sleep um
that's why she did that and she's doing
a different stream L like a Minecraft
stream at a different time let me just
notify the
girls hey y
[Music]
cuz uh Ena is going to play Elden ring
today right so she's definitely not
joining at least yeah that's what I
[Music]
saw okay okay well well well uh is this
the right window
size there we go I love Minecraft for
making it possible to just move the size
however I want
just oh there it oh
oh it's so easy I don't even have to Tab
out okay so I'm not going to play for
too long today because tummy H since
yesterday um but there's some things I
wanted to do and oh my God if only we
had things to talk about today oh
no wait let me put up the the chat
actually we have some space but what am
I going to do there's absolutely nothing
to tangent about too bad there's just no
topic
whatsoever if only there was more going
on right
now that would be
nice wouldn't that be nice this is
sarcasm by the way m
mhm it's sarcasm
guys okay I want to see if this is
finished if Amma ended up like fixing it
or if she also just gave
up well she fixed it several times you
know but
oh
Shimmy Shimmy as
in like get down she definitely did
something here right looks different
[Music]
shimy yeah this looks like are you
supposed to like stay here or probably
right stay in front of the green blocks
probably oh you don't think I should
squat
okay oh there's witches I
can't ah I can't reach from here
though I can't reach
do you think they'll see me like this if
I go up I think I have to cuz I this is
the closest I can get without like
getting on top of the turquoise block
from the right no but it says collect on
the right
so I don't want
to [\h__\h] anything up but I
think I mean this is like this slit is
so small they will not see me I think
let's
see from here I can do it seems fine
from
[Music]
me those creepers should come closer
though that would be
nice give me that
XP too
far why is it why is he so strong what
the hell
why are you so
strong why am I so weak oh my God what
was
that
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah but as long
as you hit the
creepers uh
properly oh wait was
that that looked like a zombie
villager oh yeah it's going to uh I
think they're already like at like
really low HP because of the Fall so
they should die
instantly oh hey he was really close and
he didn't
explode eji looks good stop jumping well
I'm not even reaching him I guess all
jumping stop
jumping wait that looked like the the
the
default default the Villager that's on
the promotional Minecraft pictures
okay w w w w wonderful wonderful
actually the zombies cloes wait a
second that zombies clothes are
just what I realized that just now
because I was only able to look at their
clothes and not their
faces I never realized this cuz normally
I look at their greenness and not at
their
clothes a yo
hey
stop whoa whoa whoa good job
Amy good job I will still try to stay
kind of you know not too close as I'm
scared I'll still try now let's
[Music]
see what has been what is being
collected can can I reach this one not
okay oh gun powder is pretty cool oh
arrows is
amazing arrows are very oh because we we
might not find another Infinity bow so
arrows are going to be good nice Amy
good job I wonder if she wrote a diary
after she fixed this didn't she log out
though
after like when I logged out like she
must have logged back in again another
time
see oh
M I think she may have wrote something
no no she
didn't and the others already read
yesterday at the end of the stream so
there shouldn't be anything
new
yeah Call's still stuck in day
[Music]
one nothing new
here yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah that's fine that's fine that
makes sense because nothing happened
really since then
okay that's probably uh pretty much
everything that is new since last time
that I streamed it's just that that was
fixed don't think Kelly knows about she
knows but she probably
forgot did you guys
see did you I have to put it up on
Stream So that everybody can appreciate
[Applause]
it okay I have to show you guys a fan
art from do
bang it is just so beautiful because if
you remember from stream yesterday I
showed with my OptiFine Zoom I showed a
beautiful view over the whole island and
it was really pretty and then look at
this fan
eye it's so
beautiful it makes me so
happy it's
us looking down on our Island from the
Mmm Mmm is kind
of doesn't sound as nice as
pppp I still like it
though h
merry myth
[Music]
Minecraft wonderful
beautiful thank you for that come are
the villagers still there okay okay
thank God so my goal for today is give
this dude a job he doesn't have legs
though that's concerning you
too give him a new job him his first job
cuz he doesn't seem to have one
and oh yeah we can breed them now with
bread um this should be safe right
supposedly but we'll keep it there for
now but supposedly they can't walk
out
supposedly you want me to breed them
first before I give them jobs
why they can't go under but the baby's
can ooh the baby can oh that's a
problem maybe I can make a second
door like a second entrance like a fence
maybe but will they walk will a baby
villager walk over a
fence
okay oh okay oh nice let me just make
the fence then uh I think we had
like fence and fence fence
gate oh it's fence gate fence
gate all right like for
[Music]
example
uh
wait w almost fell for the world
again oh wait how do I play you can't do
things diagonally right it's so sad oh
well
wait
huh didn't I have what what just
happened
[Music]
axe [\h__\h]
H you can put just a gate against the
wall
what let me make oh I'll just use these
and an axe
perhaps guess I'll make a stone axe um
do I have what I
need wait a
second creepers can get awarded by
swords AOE damage and explode you should
probably just make a diamond sword for
farming to ensure that you will one shot
they are being one shotted
from what I saw just now and it looks it
looks fine I'm cautious I'm staying away
from them we testing it
now do the other girls beside Kelly
know no everybody lives under a rock no
we don't know any nothing
no we all live under a rock that is
called be she's hovering above all of us
and she's threatening to drop on
us and we'll all
die um but I need
um what kind of stone just cobblestone
was
it for uh
normal yeah Cobblestone and some sticks
I have
sticks
o give me give me more
give me more so I can make a stone
pickaxe too
hey don't eat my
Stones
hey this is hey this is really not the
best cobblestone
generate but it's okay it's better than
nothing
o I'm right here
[Music]
okay now I'm done with that how much
iron do we have currently
wow one
that see yeah probably because she um
she was using it up for
Hoppers
[Laughter]
again oh sad sad sad I'll be working on
that too you'll probably we can like
talk about all these things while I'm
mining
uhhuh but
honestly
how we all not not all of us almost all
of us have one um diamond armor piece
already
I
wonder
how can I not already make armor for
everybody I feel like I feel like I
could but that's not necessarily what I
want to do I might want to you know buy
Enchanted armor with emeralds cuz
emeralds we have you know PL
plenty yeah yeah I'm excited to see what
the villagers will offer me so okay wait
first thing first things
first
[Music]
uno
no I don't know I don't
[Music]
know I should I should use bamboos right
in front of my eyes although one thing
is uh the other thing uh uh what's this
daylight detector
wow probably need yeah at least two okay
while I'm standing right in front of it
let me take the sugar
cane and do some sugar
caning
no
expand my sh sugarcane farm maybe with
paper I think you can also trade a
little bit depending on
the wait with these can I farm the whole
thing or should I keep the lowest one
there what was the most efficient
[Music]
way I don't
remember yeah we finally have sugarcane
like since the end of
yesterday doesn't matter keep the bottom
oh well
oh well wo 58 let's
[Music]
go
oh give me
back didn't know you could plant it on
top of the sugar cane
no sugar cane on sugar cane
is that going to grow because it's not
grass I guess probably fine right cuz it
would even grow on
sand thank you for the
membership thank you
oh uhuh here it doesn't work here it
works so diagonally it really just
doesn't
work
interesting okay
let me sort my
tools more memberships let's go thank
you thank
you oh and there he
goes into the shadow
realm all right am I picking it up yeah
[Music]
okay all alone yeah yeah but that's fine
honestly um it's okay cuz yesterday we
had so much going on and that was
fun yesterday we were all five of us
which I didn't expect to be
honest I'm very satisfied with that
today cie might join me later like she
wanted to join me
earlier but she's going to sleep in a
little bit going to sleep longer than
she originally was going to and that's
totally
valid sleep shall be granted because
she's been also on a grind just like
me uh having a million streams lined
up but if you guys haven't seen I was
part of the jackbox
collab uh with with uh you know it was
basically CI and me and some Advent
members so some myth some
Advent uh and I was on her Channel we
played some a what was it called jackbox
we played some qulash we played some of
that draw a character and then let him
fight game I didn't even do that well
with that like presentation game I think
like I was so nervous about it but with
the cat and the hat it kind of
worked I found like a story in my head
to make it
work I actually was pretty satisfied
with my story
there cuz at least it wasn't like all
over the
place it made sense it flowed it made
sense one of my best ones like until now
in my
life s this n
um wait I have so much
babo
wait wo whoo who who who who what give
me why does the shift not work there we
go now it
works M I'll make one more stack can you
make anything else out of these I don't
remember I feel like you
can't there you go now it works now it
works bamboo grow
fast I'll put some bamboo here it Mercy
bamboo I'll keep these
sticks wasn't there another stack of
sticks in here in my yeah
there
okay what do you mean people quickly
replacing the trash can I was that her
fighter cuz yeah when I saw that I was
like ah what am I going to draw at first
I thought okay I'm going to draw a like
uh what do you call M upu in English the
the the the trash pickup I was just
going to draw that but I was like that's
kind of boring and then and then I had a
a flesh in my brain I was like wait
trash can my butt hello we have a
history it's it's yeah I mean it's oh my
God this is actually such old history
from 2020 actually or almost maybe 2020
2021 no it might have even already still
been 20 20 cuz it was my first collab of
a senpai super Senpai and it was an off
collab and I we streamed from her place
and I sat on her trash can cuz she
didn't have a a a second chair but it
was like a really weak plastic trash can
which was not even like you know it
doesn't have a full wall wall around it
it had just like four really weak
pillars so to say and so I was sitting
on it and like it somehow kind of broke
I
guess and ever since then people you
know call my butt the trash compactor or
something like
that but that's so long ago that I think
a lot of people don't even know it oh my
God but I connected it with four I feel
like those two stories those two memes
have a a good connection
now I'm
drinking power AG AKA gator
great hoping that maybe it will you know
be helpful for how fatigued I feel right
now okay
[Music]
um I I I I no wait
ah let me replace
this how do I do I have to make I want
one diagonal but I guess it just doesn't
doesn't work in this
game
[Music]
um how about just like this hey hey you
know exactly that's not what I
want yeah that this works so this should
protect
oops protect us good enough this is for
the for the kids and this is for the
adults h
so and now we remove
the so sorry I'm scared to push that let
me
actually I'm so scared to push
that I never want to hurt who's in the
boat you know oh he's going to sleep we
can have a sleepover party May I also
sleep in the Airbnb that I built thank
you
probably need more beds too
afterwards that's no problem either but
okay it's breeding time are you guys
[Music]
ready
uh wait why don't they take my
bread stop jumping take my oh wait do I
throw
it oh I forgot that's how you do it okay
I'm not locking them in by making them
have babies right like locking him in
into his job I don't want to do that oh
they're looking at each other it's sexy
time don't worry don't worry don't worry
about
[Music]
me
H aphrodisiac bread coming from the
aphrodisiac
wheat should I should I leave the room
and I'm going to go ahead and find
uh hey oh you can't jump over here right
okay yeah
oh I'm going to make you a workspace or
I'm going to mine because I need iron
for the workspace that I want to give
you oh this so romantic oh my
God
o you really want me out huh good that
there's
Windows
oh oh this is
spicy do they need more bread they're
already looking at each other not enough
hi I'm back sorry I know you were
getting like all hot and sweaty in here
but it's not I feel like he needs some
bread okay I think he picked it
up oh God they're close wao wo whoo whoo
whoo
whoo my stream is
sfw okay
it's pulsating in here y I didn't I want
it to be outside no you're standing at
the door how am I going to
leave oh oh he's
bouncy let me
leave baby ugly ass
baby do do the babies need bread to grow
up I don't remember
B he's like Daddy Daddy happy Father's
Day a
[Music]
a no only time
okay well congratulations everybody
uh breeding is a
success I suppose I shall oh oh
blocks oh dear oh no
oh
no oh
[Music]
no oh no okay
wait oh no sorting chest oh no oh no why
do I even ah I have this because I
wanted to make the blast furnace wait
wait a moment
um let's just put this here what is this
let me make some
space
um what is this stuff doing in
here oh
no no no no
no no
H it's so hard to throw away things in
Minecraft
um ah look by the way I'm wearing my
fever Knight outfit yeah let me take off
the helmet ew ew blocks
ew get out get out it's so hard to get
out of here turn to die it's not like we
need die we're uh we kind of decided on
a stream to end it
oh a stream time we've decided on a
stream
time
so I can tell you that
too in a
[Music]
moment in case you're curious and you
want to be
there sure you all want to be there I'm
sure we'll have no
problems uh
achieving our
Quest our
goals of killing the ender dragon once
sent for
all so he shall
never never bother us ever again this is
such a random chest
now I don't know what I'm doing here
I'll add a little
chest oh yeah this is the powder things
chest and apparently some something else
oh block wait I never saw a block of
coal
before that's also a first
you
um equipment is not that great so maybe
it's a good yeah yeah yeah yeah but
that's that's what I'm doing today and
tomorrow well tomorrow I don't really I
I'm I'm hoping that could that I could
maybe avoid streaming but if I see cie
streaming during the middle of the day
for me I think I will not be able to
[Laughter]
resist uh
streaming uh yeah I'll uh probably
stream anyway let me sort this
too
yeah oh
[Music]
um I
mean I don't know I'm I'm I don't know
how I'll be
feeling I'll probably be fine but
a it's just like I have so much things
to do actually outside of streaming and
I'm not able to catch up at
all it's a bit
um stressful
kind of starting to panic at the
moment kind of losing my
mind well this is a random things chest
but I saw the Soul Sand in there so I'm
just going to throw it in there I guess
wait wood chest here take some more
bamboo and take these
[Music]
sticks how about don't stream for the
whole week for CH what no what are you
talking
about what are you talking
about let me bring this to the chickens
okay chickens feeding
[Music]
time aren't you happy mommy kiaha is
here again today I told you I'm visiting
you every day of
course you guys are so fluffy how can I
not come to see
[Music]
you grow strong grow strong and fluffy
and
plump so that I can make you into lots
and lots of kfp fried chicken
buckets eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs
eggs eggs egg
eggs you want some of this huh you want
some of this oh the adults seem to be
fine
no more no
more no
more
okay let me
out do not try to escape you little
[\h__\h] fattening them up
exactly I have to it's my job heyo who
made this
this I don't remember having something
like
that you think I going made that off
stream cuz I don't remember seeing
anybody with a fancy ass sword like
that CH the oh yeah let's make some
sugar out of
that do we still have some pumpkins
laying
around hell yeah what was it
[Music]
pumpkin
eggs oh oh
[Music]
wait
he perfect I got all the
ingredients making some pumpkin pie
yummy wait give me more I want to make
more I want to make more I want to make
more I want to make more
already getting distracted from my all
of my
goals suddenly I'm becoming a
baker [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] pumpkin pie best pie you mean IRL
or talking
IRL is your favorite pie how can it be a
favorite pie when apple pie exists
how this Edge is kind of dangerous
looking I know I know but there is floor
down there that I think n well might
want to extend a little
bit shiffon pie shiffon
pie NY what are we making we need eggs
uh pump oh I just need more pumpkins
nice some more food options although I
think at this point food options are not
such an issue anymore huh cuz we have
all that chicken too and we're we're
getting we're getting we're working on
those
apples working on them
apples let me do something about this
let me put this away it's disturbing me
[Music]
Apple I know just want to put it
somewhere
else
okay can I put the sand somewhere
putting it back here what was I doing
bread
mhm
okay see it's so difficult to make any
progress
already
[Music]
alone but um I'm I'm constantly working
on it okay all I wanted to make this
into wheat and then make more bread out
of it too when is the ender dragon fight
going to start okay let me tell you
um it's it seems like everybody is
available uh at this time so we're going
to start uh okay
jst 7 a.m. Friday the 21st but F it's
first day for America and so on um
midnight for me midnight between
Thursday and Friday so same time as we
started at jst it's or like Asian times
it's going to be Friday Na and part of
Europe is going to be thur day you know
what I
mean yeah midnight for me shouldn't be
too long of a stream I think we'll
probably you know the the fight itself
will not take long I assume unless we
all die and then we're like
[\h__\h] but that probably won't happen
so I have good feeling shouldn't be too
long okay oh more
eggs let me just empty my inventory so
that I can focus on
mining yeah
[Music]
so this there let me just put this
here don't need them torches right
now I want I'm just going to grow
something with
this wait what about where are the
seeds give me some pumpkin
seeds or are they growing on their own
now from this I'm not
sure wait are they
still are going to use beds to kill the
Ender Dragon I don't think
so well I can't plant them so I guess
there's I don't really understand how
pumpkins work in this game that
much if I so strong they can fight my
depression that is
sweet use hole oh do I need to oh okay
okay
but it needs how much space does it need
like one of these like four patches what
is this doing
here is this was this a
pumpkin one block
free m uh-huh
so can I do it like
this cuz this one's
empty should this should work this goes
like
that probably works
[Music]
right new farm for the pumpkin and melon
nah it's not really I wouldn't say this
is our main food source
anyway h
oh bone meal doesn't work on
them no
no oh
well it does what the hell wasn't
working something things do work today
for me it's weird kind of tired too
[Music]
drinking the blue shark
juice Gator
R okay wait I want I need to finish
sorting no I'm kind of hoping that it
will
just St stack and I'll I'll take the
things in my inventory that don't stack
how about
that okay we have I mean I don't know if
anybody's like wearing anything
still I hope um I hope we lose free
Diamond chest
plates but we probably can make more
anyway it's
okay uh let's
go should check on the Villager baby
soon why
why don't ask me they where they're from
I'm obviously not allowed to tell you
any details at the
moment do not put me in such a difficult
position
please but it's very interesting to
watch you guys make
theories check the villagers to breed
more ah thanks for the pink Super Chat
yeah lots of
interesting oh for a moment I thought
you guys were gone what are you doing is
this some kind of ritual where's your
baby did you lose your
baby wait the baby is
gone did you guys see the
baby did it like Escape
somehow let's see if I can find a little
villager baby somewhere
here what
happened I got 9 this
kle he can't go through the fence right
maybe it clipped
below oh God this place is dangerous do
you think that would still happen if I
connect the bottom floor with the
building like fill it up with
blocks what if I do
that I I'll I think I'll try that cuz
maybe that
helps it might have jumped on on the bed
over the fence bro
yeah
maybe it could be but I designed it so
nicely God damn it here I'll put this
one
here and then another bed can go here
and then there maybe I'll make a I'll
put a block or something there to block
it or I don't want to mess this up too
much
now well uh in any case ah I put the
bread away Che about I'll be back with
bread so you can have a new baby
probably best to remove the trap doors
what I thought those were
helpful wait what the H
bread messing with the
F could just make the fence too high
yeah you can do that right are you stuck
up
there you look stuck let me push
you can I
Oh you mean these trap doors I fought
the one up there oh
no this makes me sad that you guys are
getting stuck there wait the plants can
still kind of float there are you stuck
still
hello why are you so stupid why you
trying to ruin what I made for you guys
h
H
[Music]
H oh well have
fun make another baby
please they don't appreciate my
[Music]
work so yeah
um I don't know if I should fill it up
down there
but in any case I guess we don't need
this so yeah today at the jackbox
collab the jackbox collab was
indeed kind
of for the sake to gather you guys up
for the exciting video
Drop see it had a purpose
[Music]
very unexpected yeah that really came
out of nowhere for you guys
[Music]
huh I saw it coming I've been seeing it
coming for a while now and I felt very
nervous always to not accidentally say
something I will tell you
now I have not uh said anything so you
know sometimes you say I hate i h but
okay so the thing is recently I've been
playing um spring witch R which spring
are
oopsie which spring R and there's a
character there that's called
Justice and I was thinking oh
man while playing it I was like
H why must it be Justice
why must it be
justice but it's okay and then because
Justice kind of reminds me of the word
judgment and me being a rail gun fan I
kept on saying instead of instead of
judgment to the snow I kept on saying
Justice to the
snow normally that character says
judgment to the snow and I just said
just this know the whole time and then I
knew it and I knew that maybe you guys
will afterwards be like oh Ki was
hinting K was hinting but K wasn't
hinting there's a character called
Justice there that led me to say those
things I was not really thinking of them
you
[Music]
know so this
n foreshadowing kind of foreshadowing
but my intention really was just to you
know when I see the word justice I think
of rail
[Music]
gun oh trying to be efficient here but
takes a while to switch between
everything and analyze everything
H yeah so what do you think guys you
already got like a little sneak peek of
the
looks of what they look like what are
you
thinking do they look interesting to
excited huh doll joint violin girl yes
you do be carrying a violin
[Applause]
yo no placing me thank you that's sweet
of you to
say very bloody
excited
uh I said don't ask me about their
whereabouts I will not tell you their
nationalities
whatsoever you know how hard I'll get
bonked you don't want that for your Wawa
you don't want me to get in trouble
right
[Music]
oh wait I thought this was
wood you don't want me to get in
trouble but also the colors the colors
are looking nice don't you think cuz
green M
green I was really happy to see green
because you know
fauna and there's so like
generally we have
so many different colors to kind of go
for but green is seems to be kind of you
know
unpopular Frost walk
oops so I think we were in in dire need
of green and the cool thing is if you go
with
green oh the child took a
job oh you grw up and you went to work
immediately well okay
oh oh clay okay you can maybe keep that
job honestly why not I can get more more
more more so much more out of you like
emeralds we have so much [\h__\h]
clay
yeah he moved out yeah he can he can go
there if he wants to yeah well then let
me immediately trade with you
this guy what does he does he make I
don't remember does he make
armor
Mason no she surely does not make armor
what do you make do you need a bed here
perhaps or did you already choose one of
our beds for yours oh he's leveling up
now oh okay it's just actually this is
perfect we we have all kinds of stones
and stuff and
Clay we can trade it he can just be an
emerald generator basically if we need
even more M that's fine that's fine I
can make more villagers I can make way
way
more can always make
more while him oh yeah maybe I'll make a
fence around
him I'll make a
fence doesn't even need a door we can
just trade with him over it
right uh
and then I'll put a bed oh where did he
go did he go to sleep but I heard
him where'd he go already lost him huh
huh where are you behind
here or did you fall
down why did I hear him he's not in
there am I blind
oh no that's that's
the the the noises was him then then
where is the
dude ah how'd you get in
here
how did he like jump up here up
here well now you're
stuck now you're stuck should I bring
you your workbench in here would that be
convenient for
you I'm fine with
that breaking the workbench is fine
right I'll bring him a bed and I'll
bring him a now I don't have to fence
him
in I'll bring him everything he
needs just you know it's kind of weird
that he's in here but you
know he doesn't need a bed really oh
okay really don't they need it to like
recharge or
so oh
yay oh wait now he
can wait I'll put it in the middle I
don't want you to jump on that and then
escape
again but kind of want to see it can I
put it like
this can you reach sh if it's up
there where is he oh here hey you
leveled up again didn't
you
oh what's the second item that you need
for
that cool cool cool cool cool
cool I don't think he can reach
it does he need to
he can't reach it he will not restock
okay I'll fix
it he doesn't need to he needs to okay
different people say different things so
we'll go the sa the safe
route and put it on the
ground we'll put it on the
ground oh well that might still be a
problem sorry sorry sorry sorry here
there you go where's this carpet here
okay
cool cool
y' wait I still have
clay and wait do we have some stones in
here wow wow wow so much
stuff oh
[Music]
ah m
the animals fear the
[Music]
saw yeah it's but it's okay they always
stay at this side so they'll be
fine hey let's try this why does he what
does he need I don't get
it oh wait maybe nothing nothing I don't
know what I'm doing I'm expecting to put
something wait no he's not giving me
emeralds I he needs 16 oh sorry I'm dumb
I'm
dumb
ooh he wanted like the melted Stone uh
or was it
andesite no I don't think he takes and
theide right yeah know just let's let's
try the
[Music]
let's try the granite
Granite can I put something else in here
uh terra cotta terra cotta terra
cotta terra cotta terra
cotta I'm not going to get very far
today I feel
like actually this doesn't go here it's
it goes into the light colors
chest this goes here goes
here this kind of doesn't go here
either oh well oh
wait yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep m
ah chill break day break it's not break
day not for
me what do you mean break
day break
day I do think on the weekend we could
possibly continue our B watch
along um we could we could watch the
movies and
[Music]
yeah all of them all of
them this cow is such a blessing okay
bro look I got so much so much stuff for
you oh wait I got why I I Tred up the
exact amount let's go I'm happy I'm
happy
woohoo wa I just want to trade all of
the
clay I don't think we'll need it anymore
oh he's already leveling up ooh terra
cotta yay more terra cotta no he's just
here to create
emeralds no restock restock restock
restock
go restock
go go
restock wait so I want to I want to H
what about you guys said for the armor I
need a blast furnace what about for
weapons or wait the I guess the armor
dudes also have two different weapons
usually but there's a real weapon guy
too
right the Anvil will
do I need to set him free to restock eh
what do you
[Music]
mean no you were wrong grindstone for
weapon Smith
grindstone do I
need H iron for that do I need iron for
that so wait I got some
oh oh
cute no iron
grind oh
oh why won't you tell me how to make it
let me look it
up grindstone
Minecraft oh interesting
ah uh two sticks two slab uh not slabs
two two thingies and one slab
of melt Stone
[Music]
things
okay I can do
that that does it have to be the same uh
plank can it be different
planks
Stone different is okay good good good
let me use your workspace for a moment
oh you're talking to the kitty the cat
is protecting
[Music]
you there we go that's the
recipe sick all right there's one in
here that doesn't have a job yet so oh
oh my God two baby
wow wow I hope you guys are not going to
escape you're going to stay here
right okay who wants this job where do I
put it let's put it um oh I got to be
careful cuz I guess they can also jump
like if I put the tool there so let's
put it here for now
[Music]
I want
to reposition the
[Music]
things wait we're not what what villager
uh armor or yeah that's that's the plan
I want someone to make us armor I want
someone to make us tool H tools oh yeah
tools would be good
too okay do I have some bread with me
know okay
but you want to take the job or what
wait oh you did you did ah shre already
changed this job
oh ah let's go iron tools a okay wait
this is a tool Smith or a weapon
Smith oh this is
exciting I'm just going to take an
Axe and pickaxe would be nicer I don't
know I'm going to go bring some coal
[Music]
and
some some bread 15 coals for emeralds
yeah cool cool
cool cool cool
[Music]
cool although maybe I shouldn't I don't
want to over populate this house I don't
want to go too crazy oh I think I heard
some
re stocking over here did I
oh yes yes I
did give me more emeralds thank
you
more
more thank you wow wow is he oh now he's
maximum wow we don't need any of this oh
but he's cheaper now we don't need any
of this we have [\h__\h] ton of
this but this is nice the clay is is
incredible the clay
rates let me put this
[Music]
away
uh oh mama M de
don't even know what I'm looking for
right now brain very very
[Music]
hurt I think you wanted to make a blast
furnace yeah but I'm obviously not ready
for that not yet but I'm going to work
on this villager now
[Music]
oh they're talking to their CH children
that's so cute what a beautiful
family I'll take another one go level up
are you leveling
up oh it's cheaper
now yay yay tools tools tools I can give
these iron axes to cie for her tree
farm
yay burn stones what for whom oh oh
they're making another baby stop I'm in
the room and your children too
you but here have some
bread oh the child the child the child
took it hey you grew up
congratulations
oh wow so cheap
level up think you're ready
yeah oh we we can get the Bell now for
Atlantis oh iron oh I wish it was the
opposite
right yeah this is really cheap I I'll
make some more axes actually it's so
cheap I have more emeralds than I have
coal to
give wait is he not is this is not
moving is it oh it's oh it's
only it's so little it's so
little wait let me get one more Emerald
out I'm going to buy a
bell I think I do you think I have
actually should I I I just want to level
him up uh doio doio see
now or I'll take more of the
coal cuz I did want to go grab
um Lava from the nether smell axes for
nuggets oh okay not all of them
though
[Music]
um can I burn the
Beehive can I burn the
chests this is probably not
right oh the chest works oh oh so like
this we could get rid of all the
unnecessary chests oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
cool cool cool cool
cool
oh
oh with the Bees Still inside no don't
worry there were never any bees
[Music]
inside yeah yeah yeah bamboo oh bamboo
oh I guess I can put put bamboo straight
in there
okay I didn't think about making iron
out of the iron axes but I guess as
desperate as I am might as
well today I learned you could burn
chest yeah normally you wouldn't go out
of your way to do that I
think it's not very efficient it's
okay better than nothing we don't need
that many axes and it was really cheap
really really cheap it's a good
deal desperate times
yeah desperate times call for desperate
measures
D anyway I talked about green being a
color right did you
notice
that did you notice the other colors
did
you
orange
orange orange not yellow
orange orange orange
friend orange friend orange
[Applause]
[Music]
friend yay oh but I don't think I ever
got to my other point with green like in
concerts you know let's say there's a
group song where everybody is on stage
and every if if your Oshi is up there
you're just going to use the penlight
color of your Oshi but then normally you
know there's many pinks there's many
blues and so on so you'll see a lot of
blue you see a lot of pink but then if
you're the only green or so then you
know you won't be as represented in the
crowd of pen LS right so now there's
more green and you know it's easier to
find your fans
maybe also like when they're wearing
like green fan shirts and so on at
conventions that's also like easier like
for orange until now for me you just you
know you have to keep an eye out for
orange people and you you can pretty
safely assume it's a kfp most of the
time in like overseas like I
conventions
yeah yeah yeah yeah
it's free real estate hell
yeah
so oh they're sleeping should I make
them I'll make them a few more beds I'm
sweet I'm
nice let me get some slabs uh not slabs
the
[Music]
thingies yeah more orange wow wow wow I
was surprised guys to be honest I was
like this is the first time where I got
like
a um you know a CO High that has the
same
color so what was I going to do oh yeah
yeah I was like oh oh color up okay this
is how this is how it feels to all the
pink girls and the blue girls who
constantly wait there's more sheep now
what the [\h__\h] when did how did that
happen yeah the others who constantly
get like color
overlap so this is how it
is where where did those sheep come from
I guess the bear was a sheep and they
have indeed been able to make sheep
children Miracle of
Life or am was like yeah like in order
to get even more iron she must have been
mining a lot and
then that means she may have gotten a
sheep or you think the GR has spawned a
ship I know so far I've been hoping for
that to happen and it never happened so
I don't believe it until I see
it life finds a way
exactly isn't also orange true I think
she's orange
yeah but you know it feels more direct
uh like a more direct coai when it's you
know actually Ian
[Music]
wait only five girls what's up eat the
grass eat
it I hear Lady identifies as pink
actually are you making some joke she's
like a you know her design generally
looks like like a pink orange design
right but I think her her image color is
still Orange right
her much color is not
pink wait okay let me go to the Hol life
website if we're having this
discussion okay it's
pink it's pink I'm I'm disappointed I'm
sad I could not be more
that's that's an L for
me [\h__\h] my day is ruined it's so
over I thought we were both orange CEOs
what the
hell what the
hell huh it's fine not like I
care not like I care
yeah n after her redesign she became a
little bit less orange and a little bit
more pink in color uh in like overall
design color but her image color stayed
the
same okay got some more beds for you
guys cuz I felt bad
I guess this was kind of inevitable
anyway hey wait didn't
I
what
I wait
what where's the other bed didn't
I's the other bed they stole a bed from
me
bro why would you do this to
[Music]
me normally I get it back after I click
again you know but this
time
damn I want him to level up but this is
so little
what do you think is best I obviously
not this cuz I want
[Music]
Iron can I go for the
Bell it's uh even that is a bit
rough it's not that much
either buying the newest trades will
level him up more
once you get iron farm it won't matter I
don't think we're going to get an iron
farm I mean I mean one Bell for the sake
of Atlantis I think would just be you
know beautiful but let me let
me let me mine some more cuz did we
actually run out of coal now that's kind
of sad do we have any more coal
[Music]
somewhere wait we had a coal block
somewhere hey what the [\h__\h] get out of
here
h ah wait I have one block of iron ore
hey let's
[Music]
go
clay you know I can always get more
emeralds from the other guy of
[Music]
course see some of these things they
just just don't stack I pick them up
here and for some reason they don't want
to Stack they just go into my
inventory
[Music]
rude let me let me sort I I'll continue
sorting I'm like doing five things at
once that's my
problem I'm doing five things at the
same time
this one this
tool is for what
job for the weapon guy
or yeah I can be present for GA I think
so too
yeah Callie's really important I I need
her I genuinely need her they don't use
anvils at all a damn it okay yeah I feel
like I remember that from
somewhere so what I want
is more iron to make the smithing table
right let me keep an eye out for
[Music]
coal
Coal nice
nice m
I'll buy
one just
one it's a present for
Goa I think up there is where it should
go
yay I want to make it go I can't make it
go ding
dong oh there you
go yay goodbye I'm calling you
it's the gooa call wouldn't it be so
funny if she went online now gooa if
you're watching this do it for the
stream do it for the
entertainment go
online come on I'm calling you
gooa come
on for the content come on let a miracle
happen we want a
miracle sometimes she is watching
without mean knowing it without me
realizing
[Music]
it can we get coal out of this did they
drop
coal hey enemies do coal
[Music]
despawn
oh
H they do drop iron do
they ow you [\h__\h] yeah die how did it
die how did it just
die so the spiders still can attack you
and see you cuz they're you know pretty
lowly low situated low
lives that's
okay I want to go to the Nether and go
get some lava
buckets that's what I'm going to
[Music]
do just let me leave this
here that's exactly what I'm going to
do although we
can smelt this for
now m
[Music]
M what could go wrong I know
right I know right is such a Nissa thing
to say I know right I know right I know
right I know I know
[Music]
WWA sorting should I bring should I
bring an uh a
bow I don't want to lose it I'll bring a
normal bow
maybe this half broken one
M well maybe I need both cuz I I guess
I'll bring even if I now I'll just dig
down because even if I say I want to
make stairs although if I bring sand you
know we wanted to maybe try that with
sand
right concrete powder Falls like sand
does it
or maybe
not should go with normal sand
[Music]
does it work like sand oh
okay um
dirt s does dirt no dirt I don't really
want to waste dirt even though at this
point I feel like we're fine Soul Sand
red
sand concrete
[Music]
powder bring Stone gravel works too
bring
Stone
[Music]
mhm so sand works right like falling
down like sand and filling up the
lava although does it does it
no gravel yeah I guess I'll take
it I can find nothing
better oh wait I got a couple more
sand and white
concrete and a bit more sand maybe
that's enough
H yay fite wa ready to go I
think I'm just going to go fill the
buckets
with lava
M
basically wait stop lagging around where
do we want to drop
[Music]
down oh oh ah that could be good down
there here could be
good here here would be good right so if
I place this here it will fall
[Music]
down and we want it to go all the way up
to
me I
suppose well it's going to take a while
it's all
disappearing well I don't know if it
will go all the way up to
me ever
that is a very deep lava
ocean no I already started I'm going to
commit to this spot
now that's so deep what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah I know I'm totally wasting it
but how could I know how deep it
is how deep is your
lava is it like the
ocean the ocean oh my God what no
[\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
way no don't make waste all my
scent
[Music]
no you think sand doesn't work just
gravel something's wrong
yeah huh
o
close feels very close
[Music]
well I guess that's not
it
yep
that's not
it yep
okay um
okay where's the maybe if I dig through
here
down otherwise I can't really or I make
a a bridge over there could try to make
a
bridge right that might be
good Bridge um I mean I have to make a
straight bridge but I
think cuz I can't make a bridge down I
don't know how people even do that when
there's nothing to build on top
of except maybe with slabs that might
work I know there's lava over there too
but there's lava everywhere I just
didn't really think there was a good
spot there
either I was trying to reach this
one although maybe I can kind of climb
down from there I that might be possible
[Music]
let's check it out shall
we it's so
[Music]
scary for future Wawa
future laa
safety she'll appreciate
it okay yeah I can probably climb
[Music]
down don't look at the Enderman though
oh God I feel like I'm going to look at
him I need to look down so I know where
I'm walking oh I'm freed a good spot
y forget about the sand guys never
[Music]
happened yes n n n n n
n n n shut
up scares
[Music]
me
quiet
quiet oh God don't look at him don't
look at him don't look at look
at don't look at it don't look at
anything I am alone in this world
[Music]
okay I made
it it's literally ghost
cat wandering around like a ghost almost
invisible cuz you hear the the Cries
From The
Ghost and the cries are originally a cat
it's ghost
cat Callie what is your cat doing here
[Music]
pick your cat up it's
scared and I'm scared
too okay so now we've got that covered
we don't need to use coal anymore for a
while y That's one good thing that we
have one problem we have
solved so this now wa let me put back my
helmet
m is there coal um no but why not burn
these super chests as
well good lava
hole I
agree yay one iron ingot
hey we got to celebrate those wins yo we
got to celebrate
item can make this into
one okay four uh I need oh wait can I
make oh wait can I make one wait can I
make
one blast furnace doesn't show me one
more ah yeah right it's like yeah I can
I can uh see it in my
brain um
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay we
just get rid of this out of my mind out
of out of my oh hey bed bed
are you the bed I was looking
for
oopsy you guys are multiplying really
fast huh oh you're letting the child
sleep wait oh because you're stuck
that's fine that's
fine I'm not I don't want to give them
any more bread cuz I feel like I don't I
don't want there to be like I don't want
it to be too cluttered in terms of
people
[Music]
okay here we go
continuation
[Music]
M what can we talk about H how about
Nintendo Direct unless you still have
something well right now we can't say
too much yet
about
justice so I don't know what I should
say I don't want to say anything
that I shouldn't be saying either you
know let scares me have you seen no like
I legit don't have time for [\h__\h] I
didn't see House of the Dragon
yet I didn't finish watching
Shogun I'm
like so out of the loop it's sad
[Music]
no no no okay I already explained the
Justice to this no I already explained
that I'm just a huge fan of rail gun and
I know she says jate no but uh we've
been uh playing a game where there's a
character called Justice so I was like
justice this no and in the back of my
mind I was thinking you guys are going
to bring it up eventually I knew
it Shogun is so good thanks for
recommending it oh you're welcome I'm
glad that for once my recommendations
are not being made fun of although shun
was originally recommendation from you
guys I
probably I probably wouldn't have
watched it if it wasn't for your guys'
recommendation explain your carpenter
joke Mama Mia okay I think the viewers
here mostly should
know oh iron oh my God thank
you but
um H so we played like Final
Fantasy and the drop Carpenter came up
and I was like Oh I thought a carpenter
makes carpets like I really thought it
and then you guys thought it was so
funny and I was like well now my fault
that your language is
stupid and we had this whole discussion
and I I insisted on
Carpenter making carpet because it's
just it just sounds better makes more
sense you guys are acting all like I'm
I'm not making
sense I am making the most
[Music]
sense let me put this somewhere it's
fancy what does an advocate do well
depends on what he's advocating for but
he Advocates right I
mean you're going to laugh at me for
[Music]
that never heard of that before that
though is that a
job
avocados is that supposed to be a
job what does a cobbler do not sure you
probably Cobble Cobblestone does
something with Cobblestone probably
right not
sure how would I
know he cobbles these nuts or so
probably oh that is that what is that
what you were going
for is that what you were going for
actually uh
maybe that was your goal all
[Music]
along cob is ah I heard that before I
think I heard that before yeah that it's
a shoe maker
mhm that is not completely unfamiliar to
me let's put the coal here for now
[Music]
wait I'm thinking I'm
thinking I always open that chest it's
even the one where I put something in
there in the first place and I still
don't know I still never
know pisses me off that I'm like this
wait
wait one piece of glass because I
thought there would be more glass
eventually anyway I was I was just
hoping to pick this
up oh
[Music]
the lava is
cooking yay yay yay
yay we're so close to the to the to the
to the blast furnace we're so close to
it actually wait wait we can already do
it never mind we can already do it let's
go I have five pieces
of iron
[Music]
iron oh but one thing I can tell you
remember remember okay
kfp my dearest kfp you should remember
that recently I was like I have idea I
have idea idea for
stream for new podcast
stream this is some I didn't tell you
what I wanted to do but that was
definitely I was thinking of new
[Laughter]
girls it's uh something I want to do
with some of
them so it's been on my mind
and I actually already asked
them if they want to do it with
me not like immediately but after all
the busyness is over I
think for me all all my busyness
man oh
[Music]
hello hey my internet was
dead
hey thanks for waiting oh that was weird
I was like why are my items in Minecraft
not
placing a fruity egg and the this is
exactly where a fruity egg the egg
crashed my
internet hey what the [\h__\h]
we're so back though so I was actually
in the middle of answering a
question the question
was uh am I going to do a h talk episode
of them I want to yeah but I don't know
when it's going to be [\h__\h] busy I
might be in Japan and all
that yeah
what the [\h__\h] what let me let me let me
look it
up but I do want to I do want to I do
want
to it's in my
mind um uh uh ooh what kind of stones
are
those smooth Stone right iron inget
furnace smooth Stone
[Music]
um I will never [\h__\h]
know I will never [\h__\h]
know does it work like
[Music]
this should work like this I think two
two three pieces three pieces
actually Uno
well let hold talk with
Luna I'm working on it but well the come
the coming weekends are going to
continuously be really bad for me I
think
[Music]
so it will be on hold for a while until
we find a good time
time unfortunately it just seems like
I'm not on a roll anymore I just even
when I try I just just can't seem to be
on a roll it just I'm always like I want
to do more episodes in a row I don't
want to take such a big break anymore
but then you know it just it just do be
like
that it's not my intention I don't do it
on purpose H wait what you are the other
guy right huh wait did you already how
fast did you take that job what the
[\h__\h] did he take that job what else did
he
[Music]
take this might be the first fully solo
no cie should be joining me a little bit
later but I I wouldn't be mad at her if
she doesn't if she just wants to sleep
sleep sleep so you you want coal as well
but at least we can already get some
iron armor wa I I might not trade coal I
might actually trade mostly for Iron
Pants like a few ones a few
ones where's the coal can I make coal by
burning wood against each other I
forgot was that possible well wood with
wood no okay yes logs
well that's charcoal
[\h__\h]
right you will got charcoal
[Music]
H sorting I feel like I'm barely doing
[\h__\h] because I'm like doing five things
at once man
h ah there's some coal
here yeah what's the difference between
charcoal and coal like for real wait
what is the difference IRL like is
there in reality how how is
it charcoal is made from trees coal is
denser
M coal is mind ah yeah okay I can I can
see that I can feel
that wa Where was the
wasn't there purple
things
yeah coal is more energy dense and made
from stuff literally almost a billion
years ago charcoal as wood oh wow thank
you for that
explanation oh I'm almost done sorting
this hm
[Music]
H sorry guys that everything takes so
much
[Music]
time I'm trying to be efficient I'm
trying what the egg doing the egg is
just going to stay there
speaking of eggs did you like my egg
fighter that I
drew I didn't know what to draw most of
the time I was like [\h__\h] what do I draw
what do I draw what do I draw I so
lost was
cute I did think it was pretty good it
was supposed to be like a mix of a
chicken and an egg like an in between
age you
know it's like you're in that you're in
between a child and a teenager or a
teenager and an adult you don't know
what you are you're
confused very very
confused poor
teenagers in uh what's it called
teenagers in their puberty be feeling
like that egg chicken egg chick I saw
one or two of you guys ordered a
t-shirt I'm I'm kind of embarrassed I
don't know if I really want you to make
a t-shirt out of my drawings
today I don't know how to think about
that but it will be funny if I ever like
do a meet and greet in at a convention
and you're wearing that okay I
will I will be embarrassed and I will
find find it very funny
too I I totally forgot about that I
think the other members also forgot
about that possibility
today oh man jackbox is good Jack
jackbox is really cool I hope that we
can
also oh wait was I gone again for a
moment it's oh no I wasn't just this is
still here I hope that we can also play
amus and jackbox and all the kind of
games with the new people and also
because uh
amongus has an update didn't it say like
starting from
today I think it's at starting from
today
yeah it has a a few more rols it's about
[\h__\h] time like
damn like up until now they officially
without Mom only had like those four new
roles I think which is kind of
lame step up your game amus you're such
a popular game you must have made so
much money until
now step up your freaking
game yeah I want to talk about every
little thing that caught my attention in
the in the
direct I do want to talk about it
oops they're using their money to
publish other indie games oh really okay
that's that's smart that's nice there's
that's not a bad thing can I burn
anything is there anything I want to
burn do I have something to
burn anything to burn like cook I mean
anything to
cook this is maybe the salmon
little
C although it would be nice to have it
for cats but I think we're good at this
point
[Music]
M I need to catch up on it I saw bits
and everything else on Twitter yeah me
too I was like getting a little bit
spoilered cuz apparently it was really
hype so people couldn't hold back on
Twitter
uh to report their ex ex excitement I
kind of wanted to do watch along and
like join the jackbox collab after it's
over but then I was like I don't know it
will probably not be that exciting
exciting exciting anyway right and you
guys in preat we're like yeah it's
probably fun turn out it was really
exciting
actually actually pretty hype this
[Music]
the collab was more worth it yeah that
was good
too I woke up so last minute because I
wanted to W wake up a little bit earlier
but I was I woke up so tired I was like
[\h__\h] it let me sleep another
hour and I I got out of bed
like 10 minutes I think before the
stream and I quickly got ate some
breakfast and stuff and yeah I was I was
really BL
but we weren't late with starting the
stream because of me just general setup
and stuff you
know
um going to eat that ah the cooked
salmon that maybe got my tummy H I don't
really believe in it either though I'm
not I I wouldn't blame the salmon
necessarily it's a possibility but I I
wouldn't blame it on the
salmon okay a damn it don't take that
Lev cap get it out of my
face okay and ikim the chest should be
empty yay I can't believe I did
that how long will it take to fill up
again huh
[Music]
any other idea what it could be oh
um I don't know it could be of course it
could be anything it depends like how
fast it's it it has an impact if like
right before the tummy horde I I ate a
sandwich with
uh I made a
sandwich that
was M tomato mozzarella and a really
thin
layer
of like a pesto sauce that I had in my
fridge for a long time but it smelled
fine and those pesto sauces they seem to
generally hold for a long time
and I ate that right before the tummy
hord like really right before the stream
the Minecraft stream I don't know what
do you guys think could it be the pesto
sauce I feel like it it smelled and
tasted as per usual not the one I made
don't know a store bought
one I just spread it on the sandwich
like a really thin layer and then on top
of that I put the uh tomato and the
mozzarella it it it the the container
itself was first opened probably a long
time ago at this point but those kind of
sauces
they they don't expire that fast
[Music]
really so I thought it should be
fine yeah it's just basil and olive oil
and it tasted good all of that tasted
good and then besides that h
M I don't know I I also honestly I feel
like it could also be a mix
of oh
maybe I could be several things
but could also be the way I [\h__\h] up or
purposefully messed up my sleep
schedule for several days
now it's been kind of
crazy wake staying up until 7 8
a.m. I don't think it's really good for
my body I'm feeling it I'm feeling
fatigued and then feeling stressed I
don't know could be having an effect on
my stomach
right and maybe I'm also lactose
intolerant and I just don't know it
because on that day I drank
a lactose
drink maybe maybe maybe I didn't know
that I'm not so good with that thanks
for the Super Chat
a wait stop that I don't have a weapon
right now I
think
hey the poor
dokey can you throw it through
[Music]
here is that funny to you when other
people suffer hey hey you poisoned me ah
ah [\h__\h] you
ah oh wait the sword was in the other
chest should I use the axe okay okay
okay okay okay hey [\h__\h] you my poor
donkey man all because of
you yay sand the sand come back
okay let's talk about all of the things
that I tweeted about uh can we start
from the top can you guys like look at
my tweet
chain and tell me what was the first one
I reacted to I want H Mario and Luigi
okay I was watching not the Nintendo
Direct but a I was watching of course a
watch along of my
Oshi content creator reacting to the
Nintendo
Direct and uh he is he loves you know
all kinds of Nintendo things and he
loves Mario and Luigi he loves all those
Mario RPGs and stuff and so he couldn't
believe his eyes and he's like I don't
really care you know I don't really have
these kind of connection like emotional
connections I don't feel the same way
but he seemed hype so I thought okay oh
this is a hype thing but he wasn't happy
with the graphics what did you guys
think I I did I do think it looked a bit
weird like not bad but like a weird
style choice for how generally the
graphics looked and the faces looked and
all that you know what I mean it looked
a bit odd right like the eyes and the
shading ohm now it's still doing
[Music]
that let me let me go fix it um
I liked it personally yeah I don't think
it look bad but just uh I wouldn't
expect that
either that they would go for that kind
of
style a reference to the older games of
that Series yeah probably that mhm I
don't know what they look
like I really liked how the Super Mario
RPG turned out about the Remake
[Music]
so I'm sure this one will be good too it
looked fine like the animations looked
good and the world looked
good the gameplay looked good but I
never played one of those Mario Luigi
games
before so it's not like I'm like oh my
God oh my God about
it but it looks like you could play
co-op as a collaboration right
that sounds
[Music]
fun oh wait I where did ah where did I
put that I I picked up the thing before
the where did I get it
hm where did I put it I had it I don't
know where I went it's like an RPG party
yeah looks like
it looks like it um yeah the brw stand I
have the brw stand is it am I
[Music]
blind
h a broke no it broke and I picked it up
I remember picking it up and I was like
oh it didn't break let's go mhm and then
what happened with it then
huh
[Music]
H oh this is cute this is pretty wow
that's actually so
pretty h
[Music]
she's placing these things randomly cuz
I don't want to like I don't want to
bother with
it sea pickles everywhere smelly smelly
sea pickles they're not Co-op oh what it
kind of looked like you could play co-op
the
H okay no Co-op that's
okay yeah I'll put ice here ice and
glass cuz they're kind of
similar kind of similar
wait should we oh clay sexy
clay Mario is the a button and Lui is
the B button wait can you not play
locally co- up then with
somebody thanks bro you're the you're
the best you're the
goatest wait I was going to make a blast
furnace no no I did I already
did I already did don't worry wa what am
I making next what's the next thing I
want to
make okay so it's not Co-op okay okay
okay but you could share a controller
physically yeah you could play it like
local co-op like how I played tast of
Symphonia with my brother local co-op
although wait that did have local coop
for the fights yeah it actually
did anyway um
could be a dream
idea could pull it off
yeah they're purely single player okay
okay chill
chill no what what what what
other uh villager do I want to make what
tool would I want to
make tell me what you think is a good
idea tell me
tell
me
[Music]
tell cleric blacksmith didn't I make one
already need arrows for the Ender Dragon
oh I think we have plenty and then we
have some
um you know some bows that uh have the
thingy enchantment for that uh more
Amorous of diamond stuff smithing table
blast Lecter oh yeah I want to make
lecturn but ooh I need like a lot of
books for that
right wait I can make paper I can make
paper I can make a paper yeah let's work
on Lecter next and then a Fletching
table
maybe oh trade villager critics oh
yeah okay let's do one after another
first Lecter do you think I can make
that should be able to right I got I
think I got leather worst case I can
kill some
cows I can make a couple books how many
books for one books book book book
[Music]
thing
free let me look up
Le turn oh it's uh four slabs and one
bookcase so free
books okay easy easy easy easy easy easy
[Music]
easy
um got a couple of
these
and make us a pip
Peppa I know I don't need that much but
eventually maybe I do you never know uh
[Music]
leather feel like we should have more
we'll
[Music]
see two books wait Lea okay I guess I
this is cow killing
time sorry man oh that reminds me of
something like I I genuinely feel tend
to feel pretty bad um like
slaughtering animals in in Minecraft
okay I really do hurts my heart um and
now IRL you may have noticed I have been
getting increasingly bothered
by um
I thought it was
free oh okay increasing boted by flies
right so many flies just pissing me off
and you guys have been telling me wah
wah wah wah wah wah wah wah uh kill
them and I have
purchased
a electric quick fly swatter that looks
like a tennis
racket and it arrived like the day
before yesterday or so and I've been
zapping I've been Dippity tapping and
the the moment I killed my first
fly first of all it's really [\h__\h]
loud it zaps really loudly and I was
ready for it because I I even read an
Amazon review that said even when you're
prepared for loud zapping it's still a
surprise and so I was double prepared I
know that this person was surprised even
though they knew it was coming so you
would think that it wouldn't happen to
me but no I was also surprised I was
like ah and my cats were also like what
the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] was
that
valet yeah that was scary pretty oops no
come
on was really scary
and
then I I saw like okay this the weird
thing
is it's going to yes okay so I've made
several experiences
now
um uh one experience was the first fly
that I dapped it didn't properly
die it's so sad it didn't properly die I
saw it like lost a wing or so maybe it
burnt
off uh it was like lying on the floor
and like we wiggling suffering I was
like oh damn it's man it's half dead oh
I'm like torturing
it I was like why doesn't it Die Why
didn't it die this is always going to be
like this like half dead lies [\h__\h] so I
took it I picked it up on its like
remaining leg or Wing or whatever
whatever that was and I I threw it out
into the garden and then I was like well
I still have a lot of flies Let's test
this out some more cuz then I was I was
kind of scared and I was kind of feeling
bad but I kind of wanted to try some
more so I went on the Fly hunt I tried
to find flies and then zap zap zap zap
zap zap they were actually kind of hard
to catch but damn okay it works it's
really helpful I'm actually really glad
I bought this electric fce water instead
of just a normal fles water because it's
really convenient m m
and then after the first one the first
failure the other ones seemed to
properly die just
fine um but today I swatted one and
normally it's like a a quick zap right
and it falls down but this one somehow
it went like zap zap zap zap zap zap Z
zap zap like it kept on
zapping I don't know what was happening
and then it took longer than the others
and then it fell down
and it was it burnt it it smelled it
smelled really
bad and I thought oh my God is my carpet
going to start burning because it fell
down there I couldn't see it I was like
Y is this
okay smelled really bad it was pretty
brutal I I feel really brutal I do punch
too what the
[\h__\h] bro I I feel like I want more
Lecter because
this already seems like he's not going
to have good stuff how do I roll reset
it
oh how do I roll this again I take it oh
he loses his job oh is that
easy oh okay now he has this do I
actually I think I prefer this right and
then later he gets the
books should we go with this this is
good
okay n take a book okay
okay I wouldn't mind finding something
epic fire aspect one oh okay that
there's several patterns now he had a
book and he had the
paper piercing free
piercing free is like
okay not the best we can get more though
guys we don't have
to I only have one of
them oh now you got the job respiration
free that's breathing on the water
[Music]
right uh uh
okay projectile protection why do you
still have
this
okay I hope that wasn't a good one it
didn't sound good didn't sound like one
of didn't sound like one of the popular
am I cheating right
now wait a
[Music]
moment
um I almost want to test if I can really
purchase from
them
[Music]
H why do you still have the
job
why why why do all three of you share
this
job Hing to the gate
uh uh wait who's the new who who who is
who or can you actually not did I bug
the game you all have jobs now is that
what it
is are we just stuck with
this wait a
second wait wait a sec wait a second you
and T you also have the same job with
one
what he's not I thought it was one
villager
per thing per job
thing that's pretty cool though
sharpness too I mean oh but it's an iron
sword never
mind what the how do I fix this I
already restarted the game how do I
fixed this you guys need to change your
jobs I don't like this
[Music]
maybe it's a yeah a bug with this mod in
particular change job
please oh am I stuck with this do I have
to purge
[Music]
everybody man
Purge is that not the word time for
Purge no ideally not but if I attack
them wait I just realized we can make a
TTT with so many villagers I just don't
have the skills to really do it but at
this point we have so many of
them we
could we could price will go up
oh yeah I can dump lava at their feet
[Music]
no no yeah iron farm iron farm I mean
yeah
yeah well this kind of sucks this is
annoying maybe it'll fix after a while
randomly kind of doubt it try using a
workstation well this one
works I don't know if you can use this
at all as a normal person this one also
works could it be because of the
torch
no time of
[Music]
day try putting a barrel instead of
elron a
barrel
T taking your job away taking your toys
away if you've tried it it will not lose
I we didn't trade though we didn't
trade log out put back replace okay
tle
uh oh
oh
[Music]
oh spooky stuff happening in here
damn
um even if I start purging them now I'm
scared that I will
accidentally kind of um Purge even the
ones that I do
want make babies then
Purge I feel like it'll just get more
and more difficult I could I could uh
put them in a boat and then bring them
out but it's just
annoying use an axe but don't the prices
go
up I do that oh wait one got on
oh
really oh wait ah they reset now okay
okay okay weird maybe it was like server
lag wait are you the one from before
because that's the like the same stuff
are you stuck with getting the same same
things
now nope forn is
different forns is different we don't
want forns free right I don't think
so thank God man okay he's losing his
job
properly channeling mending would be
cool yeah mending and maybe one more
Infinity for example would also be
nice knock
back they heard me talking about The
Purge respiration
ooh tummy
H just small tummy
H lack of the sea one what is that
sounds
fancy is it just
like something on the water some Tre a
fishing h
[Music]
H Quick
Charge better Goa luck when fishing
that's cool
actually
channeling our fishing spot is too small
for
Treasure oh that's why we we were
literally where we were literally only
getting fish
where are
[Music]
we are you so far how are you getting
this job channeling stop getting
channeling come
on curse of Vanishing wow so
[Music]
useful okay what was the next thing I
reacted to after Mario and Lou Luigi let
me look at my
Twitter let's talk to let's talk about
it one after
another me oh I already kind of forgot
ah ah that was the that was the game
that kind of reminded me of like you
know it's like a metroidvania game right
so it reminded me a bit of
Orie that one looks nice I think I was
even considering like playing it when it
comes out out looks pretty
good H the graphics were cool
too wasn't that the one that had kind of
like the the sketchy art style it's been
so long already oh you're doing this
thing again hey s touch oh wow that's
that's pretty
cool do we need though no we don't need
silk
touch we don't really need silk touch
it's nice
though what would we need silk touch for
in one block Minecraft when we end like
in two
days yeah hey is the price also
gotcha cuz I saw one was like 40 for one
book and this one I guess was
17 it is
oh
[Music]
oh okay wait
okay so it
[Music]
was ah no first I was like reacting to
this game from Square Enix right and it
looked like a near character I thought
it was some near related game but it
wasn't it looks okay but I wouldn't play
it I'm not really interested in that one
looks good though looks generally a lot
of games looked W cor for
sure but wouldn't like necessarily play
all them a lot of cute anime looking
games though was
nice then after that was me and after
that was Hello Kitty like a Hello Kitty
game which just come on that was like
Hello Kitty Animal Crossing no way that
the developers were not inspired by
Animal Crossing with that one and wanted
to make their own kind of animal
crossing no way that that was not what
son was going for
there totally and honestly just for the
giggles I feel like it has a chance in
becoming multi
ooh oh oh in becoming a streaming game
for a few at least for like a one one
off or two off
uh stream cuz H does it yeah no I feel
like it has potential don't tendo also
want wanted to play it he was like
actually actually I kind of want to play
it surprisingly good for crossbow okay
but we don't have crossbows
actually why you doubling why you
doubling again HH stop
it am I too fast for you guys
H undo it now he will turn it yeah he
will turn into the one Fortune Too M
fortune
cookie yeah and then was uh uh I mean
the next thing I reacted to was the amus
Edition I'm guess I'm going to leave you
alone for a
moment and mine a little bit until you
fix your
attitude young
men fix your attitude or
[Music]
else
yeah heo sick
not the best books but that's cool
though what was I
saying what was I
saying oh yeah amus amus let's play
[Music]
amus we have a lot of feather falling
that's
[Music]
cool efficiency too is pretty good too
I watched a little bit a little bit of
that fairly recent amus
collab with cor P Senai all all of those
Senai Lami Senai too no Senai too no
maybe no l oh was she
there you know a bunch of them were
there I was watching a little bit of
that it was quite funny
because what sorry chicken can you get
out you can do it you can do it you can
do it come on believe in
yourself
I it was really funny Pai got to be the
impostor like several times in a row
even with the same person I think it was
even the same combination two times in a
row
and and for a moment she was like should
I say something but they just continued
I feel like if it's the same person two
times in a row you should probably say
something but yeah obviously nobody
expected it so they gave her the benefit
of the
doubt that was
[Music]
funny yeah and they were wearing some of
them were wearing those like amus
collaboration whole life collabor
Liberation
items some of them weren't though they
they didn't have anything they were like
grinding for
points but now that it's actually been a
while and there's people who don't have
it I feel very cool for having
it I would like a pickaxe please wait
which one which one does the
tools I want to work on the guy who has
the tools
you not you shre
shre I can buy a few more
axes and bring a bit more
coal tool SMI you don't have one e what
about that guy won't he have pickaxes
keep buying axes I think so too
yeah it's just one Emerald yeah and we
can get more emeralds from the clay guy
or the paper
people
yeah it'll be
fine so amus after amus I reacted to
Dragon Quest I've never been into Dragon
Quest I don't I don't really I don't I
don't think I really grasped what was
happening there can you guys tell
me um
um they first showed a video of an HD
remake
of
uh
wait of the third one but then they said
there there will also be a remake of the
first and the second like they just kind
of lowkey said it or did I misunderstand
something
there but the whole trailer that they
showed was the third one and then
they're like um yeah we're also
releasing a remake of the first and the
second huh
huh why why one and two
later oh cuz free is a
prequel oh so I could if I'm interested
could I play the third one the Remake
first if it's a prequel then it makes a
little bit sense I guess
yeah it looks really pretty and I mean I
always hear about it is this done
burning yeah I always hear about it in
the
Legends the Legends tell
[Music]
me yeah cuz it's really popular in Japan
too I wonder I wonder if I should stream
it you
know I don't know if I would stream it
but I'm I'm generally very interested in
it looks very
beautiful and it's a
classic Lou is a big fan I think like
almost all of the Japanese members are
big fans do you have the perms for it I
think so I think I saw Japanese members
play the other Dragon Quest games
[Music]
oh I'm peeking into their spots yeah
it's cuz I like cut everything in case
they show
up was tweeting
about DQ earlier she's playing DQ right
now OK is so hyped for it as well a good
for them they're like probably as hyped
about it as I would be or I feel like I
would be even hyper if there was a new
tal of
game I feel I would be even hyper about
it if you like yako are like a dragon
you'd like it
oh I feel like those are very different
games in style and
Graphics cuz cuz also Dragon Quest is
like kind of fantasy looking while
Yakuza is modern world
looking not just because of 2D versus 3D
and it's not like
is similar battle systems well okay
that's like the only thing they would
have in common
right
practically ah okay yeah okay because
his idea of a hero comes from drag that
is true yeah he has been kind of
referencing that yeah that okay but that
you can't just say it's like Dragon
Quest like Yakuza just because of that
are you sure it isn't modern day just
like red dead rtion no it's not I played
the games I know it's like actual modern
day okay and then I got really excited
because they announced some more of
those retro games coming to Nintendo
switch
online uh because one of them was T
Rock
oh T Rock I think that looked like the
one that I played when I was a child
I
think I I might want to do a stream on
it you play tour yeah I remember like
when I was a
child I remember those dinosaurs and
shooting them I like years ago I asked
you guys I was like um there's this game
that I feel nostalgic about from my
childhood I wonder what it's called it
had like pew pew pew and bad
graphics and dinosaurs and then you guys
were like two Ro and I'm like yeah [\h__\h]
it's TR Rock I just don't know which one
because it's been a a long time um okay
I'll bring my
axes it's been a
while
oh since when since
when h
did he level up how did he level up he
wasn't there
[Music]
yet huh maybe it lagged
or so
confused
huh huh well I think I'll continue with
these hey you don't want to do it
anymore go restock I'll even give you
your beds
[Music]
back wait let me sleep a let me
sleep this level up was pretty trash
though it is what it is it is what it is
I'm I honestly I don't want to mmax this
I'm happy with pretty much much
whatever I just want some diamond armor
with some kind of Enchantment I don't
care what it is giving us our bed b yeah
I know I know sorry for the
wait restock restock come on come
on come on
go go go do it Go
restock but what about the armor I'm
surprised wait I we wait they still
didn't lose their job either what the
[\h__\h] is wrong with
them and also we should not have two of
the shreds like those two jobs we should
we only should have one what the hell
there's so much wrong with
this okay I'll I'll level you a little
[Music]
bit and see how you can help me
oh
discount level level up level
up I think they lost their job when the
others
restocked ah ah and yeah we slept the
night over it or so I think oh yeah
these also trade for iron ingots which
we don't have which we don't have
have it's not working
[Music]
lag thank you for thank you while for
putting this event up to see all my
together and to see how much you love
them it's been super emotional right
same I was super emotional emotional
yesterday after the stream
ended oh wait I have no more
emeralds yeah me too me
too feels good
good cuz I was also reading I I I I
wanted to sleep
earlier but I was reading so many
comments everything was so tting I was
feeling so
happy you know it was like a never
ending chain of
Happiness let me change the BTM a little
[Music]
bit h
no that that's probably too repetitive
[Music]
couldn't sleep
either yeah yeah things are pretty hype
right now like with concert
announcements and
um with new new members announced as
well now obviously the myth hype with
our projects uh
promise had a new song right with a cool
animation video
[Music]
M 3D incoming yeah
exactly and Convention appearances
announced this and
that we're fing yeah Ian thriving good
times to be an Ian fan yeah I'm glad you
think
so things feel good right now but at the
same time I am terrified U I'm stressed
out I'm stressed out and
terrified
[Music]
ah yo y'all this is somehow working I'm
getting iron I'm getting iron going
although iron now I'm not sure I guess
it's just generally good to have a bit
more iron for tools but now we can also
buy them
[Music]
some questions I cannot answer sorry
guys oh wait I wanted to bring emerals I
think how's your Tommy feeling it's okay
right
now it's okay thank you for asking for
worrying
about
me what about the new yeah okay okay
let's continue let's continue let's go
down my
list so to rock to rock that was
unexpected I think there was one more
game where I didn't tweet about it but
it kind of was looking to me like you
know that
f99 thing uh one game that they showed
gave me the same feeling like it was
like an online mode for
something where it felt
like it had the same like they were
going for the same thing oh yeah the ne
neses Championship yeah that one oh they
lost their jobs good good
[Music]
good oh you didn't restock yet what's
wrong with you I don't want you to keep
that job I will this is your work
station this is his workstation right
looks like
it what was I just saying it does have a
similar mode racing no it just felt like
you know kind of like nostalgic looking
pixelly looking and at the same time it
um seemed like a good game to play with
viewers don't you think
just like FG that was fun that was fun
to play with you
[Music]
guys ah why are you all getting the same
thing come on where's the Phoenix
luck fzero has lobbies now you know can
can could be but I don't care I'm not
playing that anymore
[Music]
and then there was the Mario Party
announcement which was pretty hype
too not expected I mean actually I think
dendo expected it like of the c3e
wow I didn't expect it cuz I did not
know at all what was going to
happen but I'm excited and what did it
say what did it say again when it's
releasing
[Music]
ka
hi uh what September oh yeah that's a
that's oh no mid October I guess the
other thing was September right
what one thing was September one thing
was
October why why what's happening why you
not changing
huh wait who took a different
job
[Music]
H feel like there should be a two no job
people
Callie tell me in the chat if you're
listening to my
stream oh if you want we can do VC but
you don't if you're like
not oh wait oh okay wait she is asking
for
room I actually didn't open
one 1 2 3
four
oh not like you have the ability to get
into my room
anyway at least I'm not using one one
one one I'm using 1 2 3
[Music]
4 and then let me go into VC
just as
bad there was a time where I decided I'm
not going to use 111 anymore from now on
I will use one 12 three there was a
specific reason for
it maybe I can't tell you about the
about my other opinions unless maybe
maybe Kelly doesn't mind oh k I'm free
oh my God no scary key scary sorry I
turned my voice changer back hi hey
what's up oh what's up good morning did
you get some sleep yeah I mean yeah
definitely more than I would have gotten
if I had streamed that's for sure so it
was a good idea to to not I think I'm
joining you got to get that sleep while
you can at times when you are able to
true
yeah I mean I don't they've been they've
been booking me for a lot of recording
so I'm like I'm feeling regrets but I
wanted to stream so you know can't help
wait let me put you in the right
position okay um take your time take
your time I'm just on Apple Duty Apple
Duty yeah if you need um if you need
like a like an axe to chop the trees let
me know because
I have made some trading villagers like
I'm giving them jobs and stuff and axes
are uh pretty easy to get a hold of now
without using our own Iron cool wait did
you did you spawn spawn a bunch of
villagers finally yeah we have like a
lot now I could get a lot more if I
wanted to oh really weren't we wait so
we don't have to just wait for them to
spawn in block or did you get luck more
we have enough now yeah yesterday we got
two in total and then today I started
breeding them you started
breeding they can breed with each other
breeding with
bread wow just like in the real world
yeah bread it's yeah like in power world
the cake you need the cake oh oh yeah I
guess yeah you need the the those carbs
you want to
sleep oh good idea it is pretty dark out
hold I'm lost in the the what is it the
sugarcan feels I'm okay I'm okay I'm
coming the of
love
lovey love ciss who almost hit the
villagers
oopsie okay okay so I'm basically just
uh trying to get useful things from the
villagers and exchanging their jobs for
something new and so on so that's what
I'm up to cool keep working on apples
cuz we're we're doing really well oh
another
Apple I feel pretty good about this you
I feel pretty good did you happen to
watch the Nintendo Direct I haven't
watched it yeto buzy cuz I was like in
the middle of telling the viewers what
my thoughts about it were do you mind if
I continue that yeah yeah you can
spoiler for I I really I'm not really
planning on like trying to keep the
spoilers away from myself to go for okay
you can like basically I'm going to tell
you how it
went okay do it we Midway through but oh
Callie this is good news for you too
there will be a new Mario Party oh let's
go within this year I think I think it
was either October or September for new
Mario
Party nice that's the best news I've
heard from a Nintendo Direct yeah it
looks pretty high all the times I watch
they're like kind of underwhelming M but
for something hype like that that's
awesome and the cool thing is there's
some special modes there's like a 20
player mode online so you can play with
your fans in
theory yeah this isn't working anymore
what the [\h__\h] the heck I make a new lock
turn whatever like a second one um yeah
20 up to 20 players or is it like you up
to it has to be exactly 20 no up to oh
cool so we can get every member of Ian
in there yeah it seems kind of like a
like a how to say like a fall fall guys
kind of situation yeah I get
it it's pretty cool I'm so excited oh
they died oh um yeah and they are uh
using like some old classic maps and
remade them and also like worlds and
also made some new ones so some
completely new ones and some remade ones
that are like fan
favorites from older Mario
parties so chat which one was it
September or October we got to clear
this up okay what was it knows they
always
know I believe they do October okay
October is really not so far away really
not at all
honestly it only seems like that now but
it's not plusz especially a lot of the
announcements were for 2025 which is
like what do you mean 2025 it's so far
away and I don't know which month you
mean compared to that October is nothing
that's good and
then after Mario party I was most
excited
[Music]
about yeah I think it was just uh Zelda
just Mario Zelda was Zelda next because
they announced oh my God it looked like
a remake of a a like another like Link
to the Past kind of thing again you know
cuz it was the same art style and it
looked kind of old and the you know the
the the the dude whose watch along I was
watching a YouTuber that I like he he
was also like oh my God is this a remake
oh is this a
remake oh man it's a
remake but no it was a completely new
game I didn't expect so soon after the
tears of the Kingdom but I feel like we
talked about this kind of before I was
like oh I wonder what's next now that
they've kind of like you know like upped
their game so much of the breath of the
wild and Tok like what are they going to
do how are they going to are they always
going to have to like do open world like
this do they feel like they like
obligated like they have to or will they
like do smaller 2D games again as well
and if they do 2D again
then maybe maybe there's even one being
produced right now who knows maybe
they're was really successful yeah yeah
yeah and then so turns out it's a new
game and oh my God okay okay Kelly Kelly
Kelly you know how it's called The
Legend of Zelda yeah and you always play
as link yeah and that makes some people
think who don't play the games they're
like oh link is Zelda they just think
it's Zelda you get to play as Zelda now
you get to play as Zelda now let's go
now it really is the Legend of Zelda
yeah exactly that's what I
said at long last it's so exciting and
and yeah she like she kind of like
fights differently from link of course
um because she uses some kind of wand
they showed some gameplay and she uses
some kind of w wand wand to like spawn
things and you can like if you find for
example a t a table in the world you can
like like learn how to make that table
anywhere in the world and you can use
that to
overcome obstacles and stuff you
know it's quite interesting chat makes a
really good point they should call it
Legend of Link now exactly that's what
some people were saying yeah no I don't
think so I think it should just be you
know
Zelda oh yeah Legend of really it's for
real this time it's really Zelda's
Legend guys Zelda until now it was a
scam and now it's for real for real yeah
exciting yeah good time to be Legend the
Zelda fan oh by the way oh thank God
you're here I've been trying my best to
sort and uh I I did I really did I've
been sorting if you f like in between
the Apple stuff you you want to like
mine and sort a little bit that would be
amazing too oh sure yeah you got it I'm
a great sorter I'm I'm just going to
finish chopping these trees real quick
and then I'll sort this big old box o
four iron that's pretty
good oh do you think we can make an iron
I mean maybe it's a little too late to
make an iron farm and too much work but
we could but I don't really trust myself
with it if am already struggled so much
with the TTT PPP mmm it would be great
if you know we could work together on it
again yeah that would be cool let me let
me look at how they do it if it's really
that difficult cuz if we have all the
materials then surely there's a
blueprint or something it's if you want
to look it up it would have to be for
this specific version because there
might be oh Ena did it once to
yeah ena's busy playing eldering so I
don't think she'll help us with that a
temporary one yeah I'm curious what that
would look like maybe we can look it up
I don't have anything else to do besides
apples but I'm playing again tonight
so maybe I can make it ooh maybe I can
try and make it but don't you need a
Golem a Golem no this sorry not go not
smle goem Golem sorry it's the big the
big Ogre dude spawn uh on their own um
all you need is the villagers and then
you like kind of build them a thing
where enemies will spawn and then the
Golems will also spawn kind of oh oh
yeah I'm going to look that up after I
gather some apples and do some sorting I
want to see if I can do you do need one
zombie okay we can probably get a zombie
oh we can surely get a zombie we just
got to lure him I guess right yeah
there's zombies spawning over at the mmm
but it was be hard to get him out oh
yeah without dying especially without
destroying
everything but it it would work this
version needs a zombie okay this version
specifically not want zombie free
villagers villagers you going to have as
much as you want Co I can just have them
mhm excellent oh can I have that okay
I'm going to quickly chop down some
trees and then I'll start sorting some
stuff starting with my own inventory
okay and then I'll hop in that box you
basically torture scar free villagers
with a
zombie okay yeah okay and then do they
drop things because they're
scared that must be it no I think I've
never really looked at it closely but
you know when you kill one of those
golems that protect the villagers they
drop iron they're like made out of iron
basically so probably the zombies and
the Golems fight and then I guess that's
how it drops I I'm not sure how it
really works
let's see makes the IR they summon an
iron golem by being scared
Okay cool so villager in danger equals
Golem okay I'm going to oh oh and the
Golems then get dropped into lava so
they do get killed and that's what drops
the iron and then they produce more
because they're continuously scared thus
endless
iron cool we might need some lava I'll
be honest iron is not like as uh dire as
yesterday and so
on um it's not as dire anymore
honestly oh I see you think we'll be
able to make full sets
of full sets of diamond armor cuz if we
can't an iron good iron definitely with
um the the Villager Trader people
Merchants that I've just created mhm um
and Diamond I think it will be possible
too
sounds good if you want to try making it
it it would be cool to have it but it's
not like a like we we really have to
have it kind of thing gotcha okay let's
see this chest is not is not sorted well
I'm sure it's my fault uh let's see let
me take out some of this and then it
would give you probably a huge sense of
accomplishment if
you it really would I think 55 diamonds
that's a lot of diamonds
um yeah our valuables are in here uh
this this diamond sword we'll keep it in
here but we eventually want to maybe use
that for the final fight I
think that would be good yeah yeah yeah
yeah try to keep those diamonds safe oh
yeah
hi you want some
food feeding time
we I was surprised you want to stream
Minecraft tomorrow cuz you also read
that Redemption happening girl I do I do
well that's okay it's just in the
evening I'll stream for a bit and then I
don't know if I'll finish the epilog so
hold let
no bless you yeah I don't know if um I
don't know if I'm going to be able to do
karaoke afterward because they piled up
the recording so much I didn't get to
practice as much as I wanted so either
we'll finish the game another time or
move the karaoke another time I don't
know just look forward to it guys we'll
get it I'm excited I'm singing western
songs real old western songs it'll be
fun in an
accent uh maybe a version of both we'll
see how we feel yeah I'm still laughing
really hard that you thought Red Dead
was just
Texas people found that really funny I'm
glad I'm glad what are you doing in fact
it's not Texas at least not Red Dead
Redemption
2 I haven't played one but I'm going to
oh
yeah a lot of other places in America
though is where it happens but
specifically not
dexas oops oh there songs in the epilog
you want to sing oh gosh then we should
we should play the epilog and then oh
and then I'll give it a couple days and
then we'll do Red Dead
on best
this okay there was a lava Buck okay
yeah wait uh I'm using that instead of
coal because I was like trading the coal
we have for
emeralds and lava we can get endlessly
from the ne another and and it makes
kind of more sense it's more efficient
this way cool it burns longer too yeah
sounds good you still have some of that
kelp stuff also by the way you want to
use that for fueling things we have
quite a
bit sorry kfp sorry it's just getting
really crowded like don't you want more
space
je
Jee oh sorry to the kids sorry sorry
that I'm hurting some of the kids I
don't want to not my
intention
murder murder is great
honestly
yay yeah not normal people do it used to
be shiny on
me please spare spare the children
[Music]
I'm sorry you'll be revived don't worry
you're getting like a one time revive
remember that's how it
works and then you'll revive as a hybrid
with with Phoenix chicken so I'm feeling
hungry so I'm going to kill a couple my
hands my bare hands are strangling what
what's what are you killing you're
you're chicken the ones that are outside
yeah if you're really hungry there's a
lot of uh already grilled chicken in the
food chest great but it's not as good as
like a fresh kill you
know yeah really freshie wait did I tell
you I told you right about the the AI uh
anal
analization of uh my chat that said that
you were the one killing my chickens
even though you weren even there
freaking Liars it wasn't me I know that
look I get it it's my job all right I
understand at the same time though was
me directly me maybe it was you okay I
may have had a hand in the some of the
process afterward but I was not the
initiator so you all are aware had
nothing to do with me it was so funny
because that was an easy way for me to
move the blame from me to someone else
while the chat was
crying for
you I wish I could see the what the AI
is saying I want to see what the chat
says about it I can't seem to see it I
think it's literally only there for
context so if you refresh the stream
it'll show up cuz it's supposed to kind
of like update people on what's going on
in
the in the Stream at that moment right
so if I refresh I wonder if it'll show
up there it is it doesn't I refresh the
chat conversation is about the AI
artificial intelligence chat summary of
a recent live stream the Chatters are
joking around and laughing about how the
a is blaming Cali AK orip for
sacrificing them the chicken
what for KFC well that's 99% accurate
actually that's amazing Finish Line but
that was really quite accurate yeah wow
is it listening to us I don't think so
that would be crazy that people would
make an outrage about that I riots in
the streets yeah I think so so maybe
it's
not did it did it autocorrect kfp to KFC
it did surely it did yeah yeah that's
okay KF FP will be big enough someday
that that it'll overtake any mention of
KFC and then KFC will be corrected to
kfp
yeah I know it got a feeling in my bones
hell yeah
mhm a
kfp see all right I've almost got
everything out of this chest okay that
was it was that wasn't even like I
didn't mine like I made it empty and
then I mined for like 2 minutes and that
was already the result of it yep that
sounds about right
honestly like I feel like you can just
like continue Mining and let some of it
at least stack on itself but it's just
so when it's full it just looks so
unsatisfying I get you needs to be
cleared out needs to be drained so what
I was actually going to do is I would
was going to make more
books right and then I was going to make
another lack
turn this is what I was going for Chad I
had a goal with everything that I was
making I had a
goal
bookshelf a
bookshelf like
oh SL was it
slabs was it
slabs might have been slabs
okay yeah figured it out chat I figured
it
[Music]
out oh two Sher boxes
wow what's going on here we knew that
there wasn't going to be a short
stream well
yeah it was pretty obvious it always is
well it's only been 3 hours this is very
very very short for Wawa so far you're
not going to leave me alone are you K
not yet I'm not satisfied with my
progress today
yet and then tomorrow you the the
current time you have scheduled is
pretty good time for me too and I don't
know how I'm going to resist joining you
when you're playing during my
daytime oh true well don't for
resist you also need rest if I need rest
so do you no but I can't just leave you
alone drink again no I'll be fine I
might die I want to help
you he your tummy still hurt right now
it's okay at the beginning like right
before the stream I was like kind of
suffering it felt like there was an Ana
in my stomach stabbing me no oh my God
saw you saw what you did last night
and the jackbox collab oh that's still
the same day for
me time zones be
like
true it feels so long
ago okay let's let's let's Place let's
continue with my
villagers oh they're sleeping wake
up we almost have enough apples I think
okay do you mind the forest almost mind
sleeping yeah yes I do Kiara I wanted to
stay up all night and watch my apples
fall down can't believe you're making me
do this what are you my mom hi sleepy
time we
go whoa that villager why are you
sleeping in the villager's house um just
because I'm already there I'm working
there all right lect turn time oh I
think the other one reset didn't he cuz
wait this wait you just got the job from
that one over there but this one's also
still
here that's
weird s
gold Genie gamy love
apples shouldn't you be getting that job
now H 25 we have exactly 25 golden
apples
oh okay I think you can stop that for
now if you really want to you could look
up the the iron farm for our version
it's apparently if it's for our version
it has to be one with free villagers and
one zombie so just check that okay gotta
in the in the
guide zombie I'll look it up oh man I
don't think this being stuck is a
problem because they keep on getting
jobs from quite far away but okay I'm
doing the saddest thing of my life now
getting rid of this furniture
[Music]
no sadness got to do what you got to do
though
[Music]
no the chocolate tables
man any more Nintendo Direct reactions
yes I think so wait okay okay okay oh
yeah yeah yeah I'm not done yet cuz I
can't believe Zelda the Zelda
announcement wasn't even the end of the
stream no it was their middle
announcement they had really good
announcements in general this time like
you got to say that was one of the
better Nintendo in a while uh the first
hype thing was the Mario Luigi thing
right right in the beginning the first
thing then in the middle they have they
have freaking Zelda a new Zelda not a
remaker show not a remas not a port no
[\h__\h] it's it's own game so soon after
te of the Kingdom holy [\h__\h] that's so
hype I'm so excited to play it wait and
that's the one that's the wait isn't
that the one that comes out in [\h__\h]
September wait did they say was that the
one that comes out in September cuz I
think Metroid was next year and then
oh was M oh oh my God oh my God
September how can it already come out in
September I'm so [\h__\h] hyped
especially kie looks so
baffled especially cuz I really liked
the link of the past whatever that was
uh remake that was so cute like the the
graphics were so cute I loved it so much
I'm so excited for like a really similar
one and this time let's [\h__\h] go and
Al Link's Awakening that's the one yeah
so that's in the middle yo okay for me
that was the most hype thing but then
they continue with a hobbit game that
was uh looking kind of
mid I
mean yeah exactly Kelly that's exactly
what you are thinking just now mhm yep
nothing
else um but even though it looks mid I I
feel like it might be fun for one stream
maybe they're not resetting their jobs
again it's really
mean really
mean or I guess let me get rid of this
one and then it's Animal Crossing B
Hobbits they say yeah no actually I
would say the hell kitty game that they
showed was Animal Crossing but uh sreo
do you like
sreo yeah I enjoy it that was they
showed a Hello Kitty game that was very
Animal Crossing like cute that sounds
fun yeah check that out oh no more
librarian okay okay okay okay I mean
Hello Kitty one of them is definitely
bugged one of them is not getting any
new
jumps
okay proile Pro projectile protection oh
my God what a word free that's a
mouthful
mhm okay and then they had some what was
it some Saga game I forgot the full name
that looks again very Waba core and
other cool stuff like the dangun rompa
game that look pretty cool
uh BL blah blue but the Saga game Roman
Saga too yeah unfortunately it's not a
series that I'm into but it looks like
it would be worth getting into it's
really really really pretty looking it
looked like a fire emblem game to me
kind
of yeah maybe Shi would like it Shi
might Shi seems like the type who would
like a dangun rompa game oh my god oh
yeah definitely that's very sh core
right h
[Music]
and
then oh okay and then my last reaction
was to the
Metroid game which I already saw on
Twitter that people were saying oh
Metroid Metroid Metroid so I kind of had
a feeling it was coming but I I would
say I wasn't like oh my God crazy crazy
but ever since I played that what was it
the remaster of Metroid Prime from the
GameCube yeah I was playing that and cuz
it was a little bit nostalgic to me from
GameCube
times and I struggled with it a little
bit at the end if you guys remember but
I still overall have good memories with
it at this point so I think I will play
it when it comes out in 2025 and you
guys shook me on Twitter when you told
me I didn't know this but I feel like I
now that I'm thinking about it I feel
like I must have heard about it in
2017 2017
is when they first announced that they
were working on this new Metro Prime
game just showing the logo okay 2017
it's been uh three 7 years s years a
long time yeah s years since the
announcement and apparently they had to
like restart the whole production
development at some point I guess maybe
because they took so much time that
everything was outdated at that point
and I don't know maybe because of the
switch releasing I don't know when it
released
but silk touch again
bro
bro yeah but it looks really good and
it's an orange woman so and yeah I
enjoyed the other one so I want to play
it um oh they they switch developers wow
and apparently it's been 17 years 7
years since the announcement and 17
years since the last such game so must
be really hyp for any Metroid fan really
yeah you guys are eating good M have you
played one
before have I played no wait a long time
ago but I don't even know which one it
was it was one of the one of the older
older ones there's so many what was
it you know know maybe I'm just getting
it mixed up because I was really into
Castlevania and there was a a met a
Metroid Style game version one of the
castle Symphony of Night probably Super
Metroid and then I yeah and then I
looked up then I looked up Metroid after
playing that cuz I was like oh what is
this what is this Metroid yeah for me I
would also generally be more interested
in those 3D metroids which seems to be
from my understanding you usually the
the Metroid Prime games maybe there's
other fredd metroids too but uh that's
some ones I'm interested
in oh oh only the Prime games oh okay so
that's really how it
is prime is 3D Metroid is 2D
oh well Metroid Prime yeah oh now we
have two of them again
interesting channeling [\h__\h] off with
channeling
already whoa there what is that even
supposed to mean it's like one of the
books they're trying to offer me and I
keep on resetting them trying to get a
different book from them like a more
useful one yeah and then they start
bugging around and don't let go of jobs
sometimes even though I'm releasing the
job lect turn a I see hey maybe they
just really like their they really enjoy
their jobs enjoy their job not accept it
why their books are biomi dependent
huh what are you talking
about what are you talking about what
are you maybe if you put him in a
certain area it'll no it's not okay one
guy one one dude not here okay this
version no okay okay good
good okay uh reset guys reset the
spaghetti please let's buy some
[Music]
oh these would bring me more obviously
but these are not bad either uh restock
[Music]
need dirt that was Shrek right no that
was not shre Dre he's the original he's
the OG the OG yeah
OG we had more Flint should I farm some
gravel I feel we should have a bunch but
well I I threw I threw a some gravel and
to an ocean of lava
today oh not because I wanted to throw
it away but because I wanted to fill it
up and it was not
working I
see so I don't know if we have more
might be
somewhere should I level this guy guys I
think I should I think I should I think
I
should I think I should location
uh maybe I don't know if that's enough
space for an iron farm I guess we'll
find
out it's supposed to be really tall
right I think it's t iron farm no not at
all no no oh it doesn't take up a ton of
space does it no it doesn't have to okay
like Ena had one in in thean server in
like her garden so to say that didn't
take up much space they're pretty small
yeah okay cool all right sounds good oh
you're making it there oh you're already
making like a platform for it did you
find the the guide
I did I found a video by I think a
12-year-old um yeah so I'm watching that
yeah adult YouTubers learning from 12
year olds how to play Minecraft I mean
yeah that's this how it goes always how
it goes got to have some humility every
once in a while you know well he better
be teaching it the right way Foss else
I'll I'll tell his
mom yeah exactly
just tell on him get him grounded if you
need any help if you have any questions
I I never built one before but I can try
to help you understand or chat can just
ask the chat and they'll help you out
too they know
yeah oh oh no the color I chose I don't
have enough of it um that's okay choose
a different
design um okay what was I just going to
do oh I think I was going to
I'm need a fence so I don't die cuz that
will happen I will fall
[Music]
off my daughter is your biggest fan
salute us from
um that
is Mexico Mexico
Mexico first I thought it was Italy but
I was like no wait Italy doesn't have
like a thing in the middle doesn't have
that oh that's so sweet wait you're
sending a super chat for your daughter
that's so cute cute
gracias Spanish or vanish
Spanish thank
you
beautiful gracias M
Heros oh they kind of had like a a
German accent in it but it was Spanish
that was cool gracias M uh
M sounds kind of French
[\h__\h] gra I'll try yeah wait what is it
graas what Heros Heros
okay why am I
saying gracias gracias
MOS Hermosa just rolls gra gracias MRE
Hermosa good also can we say mama cuz
sometimes chat calls me Mamita oh
mama
yeah cute cute cute cute cute cute wow
little fan
yay I will make
a armor oh zombie zombie zombie zombie W
okay okay things all right a lot of
things are wait wait that's good zombes
good zom good
get hold on the boat distract him I got
the boat oh boat you got the boat you
got a boat yep uhhuh hold on that
[\h__\h] oh there's another one okay
you and me you and me we got to fight oh
yeah we don't need him yeah we got to
fight him let's go C should s we might
want to sleep cuz they are really
spawning a lot of stuff I did not put
down any torches yeah you probably need
to follow that up with some torches yeah
definitely okay sleepy time sleep really
quick and then I'll go put torches down
you not rest there are monsters nearby
okay well weo Jenkins I guess
[Music]
hold okay hold on um torches torches I
got them I'm going to go lay those bad
boys down wish I had a sword now it's
maybe possible safe oh no there's a lot
lot of spiders a lot
of oh my God uhoh creeper I see creepers
oh
no how did that many
spawn how did that cie [\h__\h] around CI
find I really I really messed up y she
do finding out um okay that's fine it's
fine it's fine it's fine it's fine it's
fine I just need a sword need a sword
found
out no little baby [\h__\h] stay away [\h__\h]
you okay it's okay it's okay we can get
please oh my God why is he able to
they're so walk fast stop why is he so
quick kid getting punched kids getting
punched I'm gonna die I'm gonna die this
kid child killed
me child destroyed me where' he go oh
[\h__\h] all right we're going to have to
Leroy Jenkins this um
I'm going to make a
bow oh my God why are you such a little
[\h__\h]
bow killed by tiny child the the big
strong uh god of death okay there are a
lot of creepers yeah wait I think I can
take bow wasn't there a bow what F there
should have been a bow in the weapons
maybe we can build make one wa I have
one in my hand okay do I have arrows
yeah okay
all right we must protect our
lands a thank God they're not moving
around okay nice oh damn it help I'll
help oh I'm sorry there's an arrow in my
butt now Kiara oopsie roof over the
zombie so it doesn't burn oh yeah yeah
yeah okay okay
okay
um when the day comes the zombie burn so
we're going to roof roof him up sounds
good should we name him uh not yet no I
or I think it's okay for
now
okay see all right bow make a bow make
some
arrows what do we need for
arrows uh we need more arrows wait I
don't have any arrows I was going to
shoot wait don't worry about it I'll
I'll be your Aragon
and not my AR your leg I'll be your leg
my
legless you say oh flint and feather
okay we don't have much Flint I think
there's there's arrows in the chest here
in the um this one this one okay that's
big I'll take
those all right awesome I want to help
you I don't want you to just have to
protect me this was my mistake so it's
okay it's okay wait let take a quick
bite oh sorry C
we're going we going to destroy
them
be get some
food we will kill them
all oh nice do
fine what my God okay I got you I'm
covering you not really
but get away
good job
yeah ah you and me protecting the
base we need to work our way
for just like old times really
quick much
yeah yeah it's just a more risky you
know exp Gathering time oh sun's coming
up yeah Sor sorry sorry okay we're even
now we're even now I'm gonna make a
sword got to grab some
food make a sword stone sword
okay stay away from Kiara this is not
good this is not good not good we need
to get a control over the situation yeah
sun's coming up sun's coming up we're
just defending the fort yeah at least
some of them will burn then there is an
Enderman oh my God he's okay he won't
fight US unless you look in his eyes
there's actually three of them oh don't
worry don't
worry oh God all right I guess we should
probably maybe save arrows
for it's okay I can make more but uh
yeah it's if you get the Infinity bow
from behind the oh yeah true we can fire
it forever yeah yeah we just need to
move
forward oh don't die they're burning
they're burning they're burning just
going to eat some bread
oh my Lord we could actually maybe aim
at the creepers from over there oh yeah
see yeah they're dying oh burn okay okay
okay good good good good good I'm sure
the end I'm surprised so many of them
spawn so fast y'all yeah that was
frightening I really underestimated
creepers
incoming okay that's fine no problem we
can get them we can get them okay I'm
out of arrows uh for now okay um make
some it's all right okay no I got them I
got them I got arrows we
good that Enderman is really zooming
around okay okay now see if I can go
behind the
shed and get the
Infinity
oh odaci
Bow need one Arrow all
right ocious bow time
okay okay okay get a
closer looks almost empty oh yeah you
shooting from there yeah a secret spot
Dam
it okay never
again you learning again I've learned my
lesson I'm humbled that was very stupid
I apologize
the Bas is safe though I'm going to name
the zombie before he despawns thank God
we have another name
tag
yeah making something good out of
it
yay what shall we name him um let's see
oh my God hey Andy what's up I always
afraid I'm going to accidentally look at
it um Chosen One Chosen One
Al doofus but Ollie would be happy if we
name it
Ollie oh yeah she'd like that takoni
names don't be Ollie T sweet okay nice I
hope I hope he'll stay
safe you're not not allowed to burn I
guess if we transport him just for
safety we should transport him while
it's night time yeah good
idea okay for now he's he's chilling
okay thank you so much for a helmet it
will also stop and burn oh interesting
okay I'll give him a helmet wa I think I
okay nice I can give him one of the ones
we have back
there how about this golden
helmet platforms how do you give him
just throw it at him or
what feels like that fell for the world
feels like let me
check
yeah God damn
it Fly chicken fly oh now Sher what the
[\h__\h] Sher when did you
spawn
uh-oh is that a white Sher
it looks white I thought they're only uh
purple by
default
oh
huh
interesting okay it's the mod you think
rip the shells now if it when it spawns
there I can't do anything about it you
take this or
else oh oh take it take take it take it
take it take it he doesn't want it it's
okay we'll just transport him in the
night
maybe
yeah he doesn't want it might be because
bot Ollie doesn't want it does he have
no face he has face
yeah maybe he needs to be out of the
boat ow don't hurt your
rescuer M be grateful there's some
humility yeah whatever I'm going to just
not be bothered with that
anymore
mhm Callie yeah let me give you
something really quick
sure oh she's doing it she's actually oh
my God I can't believe you're like
building such a you know cool structure
already yeah I want to try lifetime if a
12-year-old can do it then so can Mor
that's the way I'm thinking about it
we'll
see see let me put the Bodacious bow
away in case I die oh yeah and here this
and this is thank you wow nice
armor WoW appreciate that I'll pay you
back when we make lots of iron no no no
no no no no need to pay back this is
myth Minecraft we work together we get
strong together and we die together okay
I dig that yeah I dig that
yeah yeah yeah so armor up what is the
Wawa doing Wawa is still trying to get
the jobs right right yeah let's do that
wa is back wa is so
back
T
[Music]
[Applause]
Ming Ming let's go fuing good stuff at
last let's [\h__\h]
go ending
hey mending is amazing mending is good
okay we need a book and 26 diamonds so
we can get a Ming book we should put it
on maybe the diamond pickaxe that we
have yeah and make more of
those nice soon nice
nice one win in the bag more to
come for sure another book book book
[Music]
book I can make one
book I can actually probably buy like
maybe two at least for
now two mending
books coming right up finally someone
gets to keep their job felt bad to be
the evil person to keep on taking you
know your dream
jobs did I run out of oh man he's
expensive he's a bit expensive oh you
got a little little bit
cheaper he knows what he's worth yeah
manding is worth it
mhm maning kind of a waste since ending
soon M okay I'll just put it on one
ax one say going 20 by 20 platform
that's really big oo 20 by 20 that's a
lot of space okay that's fine
maybe we can make it smaller I don't
know any complain see this is chat about
this chat what do you think you think a
20 x 20 platform
is we don't need it
or does that sound
right do it it's bigger than 2 by
two complaints where's my salary call it
Mendy it's called Merry myth mending now
oh that's cute now the cool thing is
that we can just mine with this much
faster and we can just repair it
yay oh man so
good yeah we can repair the mm with the
[Music]
mmm is it the same one looks like the
same one
I need to sort my
inventory ah sorry about that I totally
help with the Sorting it's okay it's my
inventory iron farm hours don't worry I
still feel like I should be in charge of
everyone's
inventory if only we could give you
maybe there's a mod where you can give
others access to your inventory if they
like right click you or so that would be
cool becomes my specialty M like in
bal's Gate you can also look at the
other's
inventory oh yeah
true yeah you can snoop on their stuff
mhm snoop Snoop Dog onone yes
Snoop what am I looking
for oh well there's the there goes the
Cobblestone all I'm going to have to
farm a ton good thing that Goa made
something super helpful for farming
Cobblestone oh yeah but that's so slow
it's so slow yeah it it's slow I wish we
had
more make sure you're actually picking
it up cuz for me it burns in the lava a
lot of the time I
see careful with
it there's a mod that auto organizes but
I think that's it
uh you can make the same thing but four
in a row is so much faster what you mean
the cob Stone generator put a block on
top of the lava so it doesn't go into
the lava as much oh could do could
do
[Music]
Improvement let me transform
this that's over 100 cobbly Stone I
think is that 400 Cobblestone I
need math
[Music]
a
bread
okay cie yeah I was actually in the
beginning of the stream talking a little
bit at least to the extent that I can
about the announcement that was at the
end of the jackbox
stream you got something to
say about it I just I can't believe that
those fugitives have been wanted in
hiding with us but at the same time we
knew I mean we knew but like I can't
believe that they were like being
pursued we all knew yeah yeah I mean if
somebody breaks out of prison you would
think that that is they probably
somebody's chasing them right but yeah
why it take a year though a Year's a
long
time it's like they whoever is chasing
them the police or whatever finally got
off their butts m right finally maybe
they were already off the buts they just
had troubles finding them they had bad
directions or bad GPS
mhm no Wi-Fi connection wherever they
how could they have known that they just
like debuted as vtubers after they left
prison like how could they have known
who would have expected that the first
place true I wouldn't First Look for
criminals there mhm it's a really good
point
yeah I don't know I guess we'll find out
pretty soon right actually really soon
yes just a few hours or so right y yeah
all will be revealed is isn't it like so
crazy like Advent they're almost a year
of us what is it 10 months now but it
feels literally like they joined us like
maybe three or four months ago so it
feel so early that long yeah to already
get a new gen I'm going to get more lava
buckets I think true yeah I mean it's
very much like um well I mean wasn't
that the same amount I mean I will say
that that amount of time that that
you're speaking of right it's it's the
same as it was for us in Council
wouldn't you
say 10 months yeah it was 10 or 11 it
had to have been but then I think
between ccil and Advent I think it took
ages right very long yeah it was 11
months for for apparently for myth to
council yeah 10 for Iris 11 for Council
so not too
unusual this is not bad chat but I
should probably get rid of it right not
bad
though myth is getting arrested for
aiding in a bedding Advent sh we have
nothing to do with that it just still
feels like they're so
new that I'm not like quite ready yet
like they're they're so new still like
they're still feel like babies to me
oh Advent babies yeah little Advent bab
Babas I think that once they get 3D
it'll feel it'll feel more real I don't
know I feel like that's what'll happen
cuz that's when it happened for me with
with Council and Iris they're baby I was
like oh yeah these guys have you know
been here a while is a baby
well she is
small that is
true tiny tiny girl
the myth was yesterday now you stop you
know that we feel like old souls at this
point well if us playing Minecraft right
now it might really feel like yesterday
true enough it is
nostalgic okay K I'm going to go to the
Nether um oh want to grab some lava yeah
I'm grabbing some lava thanks uh where
am I oh yeah
here maybe
I'll make it ah wait one is here okay
one is here that's
good
[Music]
so get in there okay uh W go W go W
bring sword at
least oh this is fine I
have I have axe oh wait I have Shield
also Kelly I realized today you know all
these extra chests the super rare chest
and whatever that we are getting right
turns out cuz like we don't need all of
them right we have so many of them
though just like what the [\h__\h] do we do
with all these chests we can use them as
burning material as well for the
melting really mhm pretty I didn't know
that let's freaking go m
sounds good let's definitely do that cuz
we have way too many yeah I've been
doing that since but I only learned that
today and some of the chat also didn't
know it so that's like yeah amazing I
guess it is wood mhm they wooden
yeah okay on my way into the
hell now at least I already have a path
that works for
me nice
[Music]
wow no stored cobbly Stone that's okay
I'll just find some more I've mined
quite a
bit wobbly
camera wobble wobble wobble wobble
wobble wobble it's probably cuz I have
like almost Quake Pro
yummy looks
yummy looks like some pasta
sauce
laad um probably should put some torches
up
there orange pasta sauce orange
juice
yum I'm already on my way back so fast
sh how's it going how's the building
going you feel confident in what you're
doing oh for sure is the 12year old
explaining it
well yeah it just seems it's it's
obviously for a very old version right
M um so it's kind of you know it's
tedious that's
okay titty us hahaa ha you're very
silly is silly yay
titties my God Yahoo goodness
gracious
you okay I'm going
to what should I trade we're kind of
running out of the emeralds but I can
quickly get more just uh clay would be
nice I'm going to you know what I'm just
going to mine a little bit for now yeah
do some mining if you get any cobbly
stone let me know oh yeah okay cobbly
Stone just kid I have 5 whoa got a ton
of
torches just going to put my things here
for now so I make my inventory very very
empty
light actually we should we should
probably just go mend it really
quickly yeah cuz you got mending now
right yeah let's go
uh I guess I'll use this oh yeah
sweeping Edge oh this actually works
perfectly in combination doesn't
it it mmm mmm is the new
PB yeah and PPP was the new
t
a who doesn't like the TT
exactly so spawn please everybody where
are are you at come
on you know at at the end of my stream
yesterday um am was still there and she
was like finishing up and fixing
actually she came back after a while
when I was alone to fix it cuz like we
kind of gave up on it for a little bit
and then I was streaming alone a little
bit and then Amma showed up again when
you already left to do your stream and I
was like I'm just going to finish up a
few things and then Amy shows up and she
like wants to fix
mmm and oh man that that's why I brought
it up in jackbox today as a prompt dying
for the eighth time when fixing mmm
because she really has been suffering
dying several times when she thought
that it was finished already and it
broke apart a few more times and then
one time when each time you know we had
to farm more iron to get Hoppers again
and again and
again which was really because we were
obviously like so low on iron the whole
[Music]
time and the last time before I was
going to end the stream she fixed it one
more time and she was like okay okay
okay I fixed it and I was like okay
let's check it out and it really looked
proper and there was obsidian around it
so that creepers wouldn't explode it
but um but it again failed
and am rage quitted the moment
everything exploded like she legit left
the
game I mean I can't blame her I can't
that's that's rough I really felt bad I
don't know I don't know how serious she
was in that moment when she raged quit I
hope she didn't take it too serious um
but I mean she did have to fix it
several times she was probably really
frustrated oh for sure seriously a has
been dying for our sins big but then she
came back and I was trying to like say
stuff like oh it's okay because like
it's basically working we just can't get
to close it's okay yeah and then she
fixed it uh or she started trying to fix
it no actually I think she did go
offline when I went offline as well and
then today when I logged in it was all
fixed up now it's really for real for
real fix and you can get as close as you
want um I think so I'm still taking a
little bit of a security
precaution in staying away I think you
can but
don't wouldn't want to risk it cuz you
can still reach them from one or two
steps uh
[Music]
behind all right well I'm certainly
going to be careful if I ever go around
there never again I'm just wondering
when she did it like it must have been
sometime after I left until after I came
back when was she doing
that
curious h am and her
shenanigans am is so strong am is so
mentally strong she has the mental
fortitude of
of of yeah I certainly couldn't do that
to be honest
like she is
aing one and only of a rock of a cane
toad a can toad cane toad
sugar cane let's
go okay let's go mining we o gold
block where are the diamond blocks where
are the emerald block oh iron block okay
hey hey hey
hey
you exploded in water so it's all good
but you heard the chicken how dare
[Music]
you exploting
man all good there's water we had this
before I still got scared a little bit
though the moment you hear a creeper
going off it's like oh
[\h__\h] all
good diamond block hey what's going on
next emerald
block Maybe
Kelly did you eat breakfast h no girl
girl
F no I'll have lunch okay do you never
eat breakfast nope M but you eat you
drink your coffee did you get your
coffee get
coffee coffee bottle where is
my oh there it is sorry both of my
contacts fell out at the same time
time I hand this your eyes are rejecting
them yeah they're like
noap wait you wear
contacts yeah huh
wine wait I don't think I ever notic
that yeah cuz I never wear glasses or
anything it's just contacts all the time
wait I want to see if that do you own
glasses yeah don't tell me you sleep
with the that's in no no that's horrific
are you kidding me one of my biggest
fears is is uh going blind so no I do
not I need to go get a new contact
though I'll be right back
okay sorry sorry sorry we don't need any
more of you
sorry damn wait I don't think I ever
noticed that with her she did mention it
though yeah to you or to me maybe she
did mention it before I don't know but I
feel like I never noticed it like I
never saw her putting them in either I
think even when we stay
together in like
Japan maybe I did she did mention in a
collab oh [\h__\h] then I for I
frog I have
[Music]
frogot her shiny gumy lances she just
also doesn't really cuz I never see her
with glasses I just don't really see her
as a you know glasses or lenses kind of
person now I want to see her with
glasses I'm actually it's so weird that
I have good eyes good eyesight after all
these years of like a using the computer
constantly so close for so many hours
per
day I'm just generally not treating my
eyes very nice I
think it's crazy my mom actually too you
know my mom is like you know my mom is
Mom Ag and uh she's also been using like
computer every day for
hours for her whole life
so she actually also doesn't wear
glasses or lenses Maybe by now her eyes
are not like the best of the best maybe
sometimes she might see a little bit
blurry I don't know but she never
complains about it so I think her eyes
are fine my brother also doesn't
wear any such things my half sister is
the only one who will kind of wear
glasses not constantly I think
though my father also I know I never
talk about my father but he
also is this a thing that can be in your
jeans cuz he also does wear glasses or
so can this be in your
jeans you talking about genetics of
whether like you glasses or not they say
yes okay cuz like my whole family pretty
much uh is like resistant to that stuff
like they have all good
eyes seems like
it you good Kelly w w
what I'm good what are you seeing are
you oh you you put them in just now huh
yeah yeah yeah H yeah it did look like
you were looking
up yeah I yeah I put him in we're
good I'm actually so glad I have good
eyes because I do wear like colored
lenses sometimes and they hurt my eyes
so much I get an immediate headache and
immediate dry eyes even when I put in
um like liquid uh eye drops or whatever
I'm really really really really really
bad with them so thank God for my
genetics oh my God yeah you don't have
to worry about things like contacts or
maybe getting lasic surgery cuz I have
some friends who have done that like Mor
you should get lasc surgery and I'm like
so scary they're like yeah you can smell
your eye burning but no you should do it
anyway I'm like oh no you can smell your
eye burning what the [\h__\h] oh yeah mhm y
I have some friends who have really had
no problem Oh with it and then some
friends who say it's the most painful
thing they've ever felt in their
lives die
monster do you have oh wait now he's
down potato
fries okay good potato
fries yeah one of my U my old roommate
actually got a a laser eye surgery
thingy and she's happy with it she
didn't complain but damn I could never I
could never I'm such a chicken when it
comes to like anything surgery
is yeah I get you I've just heard mixed
reviews about it so I'm kind of like
eh come here come here Kelly look at
what this chest has
inside ooh what's inside the chest let
me
see player head why would why would they
what would that be is it a message or
they trying to tell us something
oh is this like like how in the game of
thrs or whatever they bring someone's
heads to the king or so to show him
[\h__\h] killed him it's a friend and I'm
messing around yeah I killed
him oh my God on Mommy
I'm just going to put that on and then
surprise the others with it tomorrow and
they'll be like what who is this who is
that someone hacked into the
server that'd be pretty
silly but you guys seem to be kind of
excited about the fire aspect
book I guess we could put it on on a
bow fire aspect o it does it make it
flaming yeah we should spread out the
powers amongst the bows maybe M mhm mhm
instead of just making one all powerful
bow oh that's okay um fence on fire oh
oh that's what you meant Oh the fence
was on fire not the book okay now the
book also looks good though
[Music]
no just clicking on things hoping they
will go in but I guess they
won't but zomes we got six diamonds now
that's a lot more than no diamonds yeah
a good for sure it is a good amount
of wait did we have
any yes
yes yes o clay I can exchange the clay
[Music]
wonder if this really needs to be 20 by
20 cuz that's just that's so big we got
69 diamonds now oh okay nice let's
go
vamos
nice okay I have come back with some
clay for the first time in a long time
aren't you
happy yes you are 10 11 12 13 14 we
almost got
it one diary was L it no they're all
here you guys are so dramatic one trying
to one guy me in the chat telling me
things that didn't happen at
all trying to make me worry it's all
good in this neighborhood
[Music]
works really well cuz we can pull the
villagers up there okay no Andy please I
don't want to look at
you I don't want to game's going to make
me look at you
please Sanford and Sun I guess that's
what it is
[Music]
[Laughter]
G
yeah look at this is like this is like
coefficient wearing Fever Night cosplay
look at me I'm
underneath I'm
coefficient yeah intoxicating DJ keep
playing looking good yeah you got that
you got that you got to Str your stuff
yeah Str your stuff I'm ring ining in I
think you look great you look great no
matter what kind of makeup you put on ah
damn it I'm so angry that the chat is
making me do this I lost the challenge
the don't laugh challenge now I have to
wear this oh I'm so
angry believe all of that sounds like a
whole lot of
cap in reality he's happy about doing it
he's all he's happy proba having a good
time he's just pretending that he
doesn't like
it yeah that's what it is
pretending we all know the
truth uh wait I can where oh no it went
there okay sweet Sho it's back
waa
[Music]
yay okay what are these eggs doing
oh okay I'm mining mining mining mining
mining
[Music]
mining I keep on sitting on my foot when
I
stream and then when I finally get off
after the stream my legs are like so
like o I feel like my legs are getting
shorter each day than I'm
streaming sh ah but I do try to switch
and and I do do try to stretch also that
blood
circulation yeah you know someday when I
get to build my own house I want to the
first thing I'm going to do is make sure
my studio has a standing desk oh wa you
can already do that now though I guess I
can but it's it's a little bit small
quarters it's just kind of it's like a
lot to kind of
redo so kind like maybe a desk that I
can lower up and down
like have a like a treadmill under or
something I watched a video um a while
ago like a week or two or so ago where a
guy takes up this challenge of what was
it like a week a full week of not
sitting down will only like so to say
sit down uh when he goes to sleep so he
lies down for sleeping but between going
to bed and waking up again he does not
uh-oh
he does not he's not allowed to uh sit
down so but like it was actually so
rough for him for in the beginning the
challenge the experiment he was kind of
like thriving from it like feeling more
motivated because he bought himself also
a a standing desk instead of his normal
desk so he was working while standing
and saw that he was much much much much
much more productive through
it yeah so
yeah overall he was thriving but then I
mean it's really like Overkill right a
whole week of never sitting obviously
that's unnecessary and going to have
some fatigue effects come with it and
that's what he then
experienced yeah sounds like a Mr of
Beast video Yeah it no no no yeah if
it's with 100 people
yeah people
challenge I Challenge 100 people to to
see who can stand for the longest amount
of time yeah and whoever stands for the
longest period of time gets $5 million
they're all cubicle they're all in the
glass
cubicle MH yeah those it sounds kind of
interesting I would die yeah you would
die someone would die eventually I don't
think a standing desk would have a good
effect on your general poster and
everything M agreed m
oh poor
horsey she says while murdering it oh oh
wait set itself free okay wow okay it's
pretty it may live ooh okay sorry I have
not been organizing whoops you do oh
don't worry only so much you can do I
guess
but so I can do I do try to like pick
those items up and then put them cuz
like they they really don't stack but if
I stack them on top of it myself a lot
of them do end up stacking if you know
what I mean yeah yeah I get what you
[Music]
mean that's a good way to do it
m
[Music]
oh am
I oh yeah bous boat don't want to lose
that it's our treasure away can I burn
the head
you got to use it to scare the girls
yeah and then you can burn it I feel
like the sound I just made sounded like
uh like the potion drinking s spider or
something yeah oh the potion drinking
like
whatever yeah that one blowing up my
notifs what what am I mining for
chat what am I mining
for General materials
to do something about the villagers
right
stuff we're going to need a lot of
villagers for this iron farm I feel cuz
the one the 12-year-old is making has
like 10 villagers or something oh oh
don't worry it's pretty easy to get more
of them really you just throw bread at
them
yeah oh again just like real life
Minecraft's realism really surprises
me yet
[Music]
again okay what it only needs three
apparently only needs three villagers no
we're just going to Let's made a 20 by
20 thanks well actually it's very easy
to get them over because I think there's
um a platform close by maybe from the
farm or you can maybe direct them
through a path around wait yeah cuz like
where do they have to go
because where are they going actually
what does it show in the video I have to
make a fence first cuz if they got to go
up there where the Cobblestone is up
there m then there's a platform up here
though on top of if we made stairs maybe
that would work well I don't I can't uh
well if
it's no I think with the
boat you can't
um go up yeah but we would have to like
make a piston or so but we can lure them
with beds like I can make an extra
amount of villagers and then we'll get
rid of the beds they will sense the beds
wherever we put them we'll put them up
there and if we have uh like stairs then
they walk up there themselves as long as
there's a bed there
that's a good idea
wow W you know all the ways to do the
things or a workstation yeah they're
just really motivated to sleep or to
work oh I
see interesting yeah just get them real
motivated a rail eer yeah I think the
12-year-old sorry I keep calling them
that is using um because they're
obviously not 12 anymore that was 11
years ago um I think they're using like
a mine cart maybe I'm not sure I'll take
a look though not that far in the video
yet we don't have to do that I think we
can just um bring him over with the beds
okay yeah whatever
works but maybe there is a minecart
necessary
for uh like the yeah for like when the
iron
drops possibly I don't know what how
exactly that stuff works sometimes they
do stuff like that with uh iron carts
and mine carts to transport items into
chests and stuff to make it
automatic I see
interesting you can do a lot of
Automation in Minecraft huh
yeah people with huge brains must love
this
game I'm having a good time I love this
game does that mean I have a huge brain
I think so
rain people make computers in this game
oh my
gosh no wonder it's so popular I feel
like you can do so so so
much anything basically except build a
ferris a working Ferris
wheel it's the one thing you can't
do the feris
wheel h
about that you can with mods yeah with
mods though come on that's a little
different
guys all righty looking really
good I think like we
won't need that much more prep tomorrow
I'll think of something perhaps if you
want me to think of something that you
could
do sounds
[Music]
good but
generally now that we have the villagers
and the iron farm and so many diamonds
and stuff and already a couple of good B
bows uh I think we're going to be so fun
cool ouch oh cats what the heck meow
think ghost cat tried to jump on
something out there that was loud oh an
enchantment table set ah true we could
make that because now books are not such
an issue either
M yeah we could do that and then right
before we go to the end we could like
enchant our
things that could be something that's
relatively easy to make that you could
probably do tomorrow if you want to Sure
enchanting stuff yeah like an enchanting
table table basically that's like
surrounded by
bookshelves oh the bookshelves are not
decoration they're they are there to
strengthen the enchantments in the
enchantment table that you can get mhm
the bookshelves really help with that
specifically yeah you can make them you
can make the enchantment table without
the bookshelves but then the
enchantments will be pretty
weak oh I see bookshelves do you get
them for merchants right no no we can
make them oh with the sugar cane and
with the leather from the
cows and some some wood a little bit of
wood that's
big
okay is this new sounds good it looks
NE same no they're all the same number
it's new I found a new
CD nice really collecting all the music
yeah it's like we're trying to 100% this
game uh in terms of
Music yes feels like it like normally
you wouldn't really like when playing
Minecraft normally probably that
wouldn't really be your goal or so and
it's hard to find them but here we find
them so
randomly it's
nice six
more
mhm yeah I want to listen to this one is
it going to be a banger it doesn't even
have a name it's just a number that kind
of concerns me Untitled other ones have
names
[Music]
huh okay it's just church
bells oh little bit a little bit
weird
strange what's the meaning of this
haunted that one that's my jam is that
what you listen to day by
day wake up in the morning and start
playing this
trash gets me motivated wake up in the
morning walk up the church Tower ring
the bell and like ah man this is like my
kind of disco I love it feeling like
Quasimoto I like it it's a good
lifestyle I mean people are into all
kinds of music so who knows maybe that's
really like yeah church I think a world
where everybody
likes Peak Hunchback Vibes I I like a
world where everyone can just enjoy
enjoy what they enjoy is that right I
think generally church bells are good
these are kind of spooky but real life
church bells are not
bad cuz these ones are not great CU
they're scary not the best scary can be
fun though
Kiara tell it this would be a good like
um
what's the word environment track in the
game ambient yeah
ambient yeah like an actual scary place
but our base isn't
scary no no not anymore it was in the
beginning it was in the beginning and
sometimes in between but generally
no just
tting m lots and lots of that speed
[Music]
need two more on both sides then I think
the platform will be
done the first platform or I mean it is
the only platform but it's the main part
making notam with this
one I don't know about
that I don't think so okay I'm going to
go back to the Villager and try
to level them see what they need I how
far do you think you are with finishing
the iron
thing very far away I'm about 2 minutes
into the video and it's a 13-minute
video
what yeah damn well the hard part hasn't
begun there's stuff with water and then
the villagers and we'll
see I'm almost done with the platform
though once that's done then I can
really start cooking
okay got to make a fence after
this
[Music]
okay generally I could trade some a few
of these but I'll have to remake the
bucket with iron once the iron thing is
finished I could do
this I have a few more emeralds I can
just throw those out
you're fine the way you
are so many
dudes they breed really
fast I could breed some more actually
while we're at
it yeah let me breed some
more yeah why not we just need some
dudes to be
scared ask Kelly to check if that's a
Bedrock or Java tutorial that sounds
like a Bedrock I oh does it
say hold on
that it says Minecraft
1.52 don't we have 1.
15.52
oh oh yeah that's a good point here let
me
see if it's 10 years old it's Java oh
because
uh oh e wait we are in Java right we're
not in bedro oh yeah and this is 1.15
5.2
1.15.2 oh okay cuz the one I looked up
was
1.5.2 will that
[Music]
work one seems very complex maybe the
other one is
[Music]
similar most likely not no at least
you're only 2 minutes into the video you
built a nice space for
it
woo let's see I'm not finding a lot on
1.15.2 H
1.5.2 yeah
1.15.2 Chad can you find her a nice one
a good one a lot of
these do not look like the one that we
have in in our server which I guess
makes sense but yeah that one would be
different most likely I don't think we
can build that one nah not possible what
you have so far should still be viable
for other builds yeah probably it's not
that like special so far just a platform
no mechanics probably be fine drop to0
two just oh yeah okay just type in
1.15 1.15 should don't don't add the
two
okay okay
1.15 iron farm Minecraft 1
five
one
farm this one's 35
minutes
wow I guess video tutorials are pretty
long maybe just like a picture tutorial
would probably be
faster if you watch the and you go by
the video then you'll probably make less
mistakes yeah that's the
thing see easiest and smallest iron farm
in Minecraft what oh this seems possible
smaller smaller iron
farm yeah this one's only five minutes
what's what's everything I need what's
the Creator's name maybe chat can check
if it's really like a good one that
works
see look up easiest plus smallest iron
farm in Minecraft 1.15 simple Minecraft
iron farm tutorial what's the YouTube
channel name not Mur don't bother them
by the way not Mur not
mour the 12-year-old's now
25 it's got 5,000 views 5,000 views okay
that helps guys can you find it 5
minutes long and the Minecraft Geniuses
among you can judge if this will work
that would be nice that would be
B let's see you need 35 glass blocks
three villagers one zombie 35 walls one
bucket of lava one bucket of water three
signs five Hoppers ooh five Hoppers yesh
no worries we can make that I'll I'll
get some iron for that okay one chest
three barrels one bed one trapo one
sticky piston o we can make that too I
think shouldn't be a problem redstone
torch Redstone Dust three repeaters any
solid blocks other than wood 29 okay I
think we have everything there not a
hold you need some red stone
gotcha okay you can get all this
together yeah okay I'm going to gather
the materials first and put them in a
chest they said uh maybe seems
excessive that one is too much work do
the one with just a boat zombie don't
even need name tag well give us a video
give us a video yeah give us a video I
know you can't post it in chat but can
you if you post it as a a reply to me on
Twitter I'll look it
up
kist also Kelly can we sleep in in the
game really quickly yeah going to bed
now yeah just oh can drop the video
title in the chat too that's fine too
you may not rest there are mon nearby
why you were just slain by a z or is
this from ages ago it's from a while ago
right you're not dead right now I'm not
dead okay there's one let called Simple
iron farm tutorial here I'll I'll drop
you a message maybe look this up okie
dokie we'll find
it what the
[\h__\h] where do the [\h__\h] why the [\h__\h] what
triggered it's the
[\h__\h] where I a creeper was underground
probably let me look I mean not a lot
was lost or anything but that was weird
he did you see where where it was no not
a
clue nope monsters are nearby it
says let me
random easy efficient
bottles we'll find the aftermath
later yeah surely well it was four there
were four missing four missing spaces in
the ground oh okay okay let's sleepy
time sleepy time this one's got a lot of
glass in it but it's 17 minutes I
wonder
okay yeah this this does seem like if I
make one mistake I'll be in big trouble
though
he make it from the beginning he's
floating in the air and so that's kind
of that is
he why do so blocks in the
air there's another one that doesn't
even need zombies H Glass isn't
necessary I think it's just for
viewing well could be bushes not
Kell can you sleep in the game I'm
trying but it says that there are
monsters nearby oh maybe try logging
out yeah I'll do that oh okay it just
opened up a little hole um in the side
of the myth house but that's it
[Music]
okay so all right um wonder how up I
should be the only thing that I don't
like about creative mode is I don't know
how high up I should
be you're not changing to creative mode
I don't think so no I'm not but like
because they're making it in creative
mode I don't know how many blocks up
they are Etc in the sky oh that's a
creeper why is he there I'm going to
shoot him I can't shoot him I don't have
arrows okay watch
out Arrow Arrow Arrow Arrow height
doesn't matter started High work down
16 blocks above existing
villagers
okay you take your time and watch that
video maybe maybe or maybe in the
description there's some more details or
so about
that
yeah what am I going to
do um he doesn't trade that why does he
not restock what are you guys doing
is it because you're sharing the job of
someone
else could take another
Bell he also doesn't restock why do
these people not restock
chat what I
do you think it's because they're
sharing dony because they don't you mean
no Bell as in don't buy a bell or no
Bell as in put a bell into the
house ah now you're the wrong one why
are you doing
that don't buy okay well well I want to
buy the axes
but I I'll bring this guy some lava
buckets
get rid of my
platform now we have a ton of
cobblestone though
[Applause]
oo who was it was it you was it you oh
yeah it was
you I'll give you
one h
two now let the magic happen
o we got that Unbreaking two projectile
protection that's
good and F oh yeah why not why not okay
and with some discount I'm I think I'm
going to just buy them right away that's
actually good I was going to I mean if
we have Fe falling books I would have
just put it on the shoes
anyway yeah okay we're getting that
armor I'm I'm happy with that I don't
need to like minmax their uh Enchanted
armor things I don't care about
that very good value for emeralds hell
yeah they love
me okay I'm just going to
get enough of
these you ready to wait is he maxed
already no now he's maxed oo okay here's
the gcha the gacha will bring us a
helmet with also projectile protection
okay I mean with the Ender Dragon he
shoots at us right so that's that could
work that could help us and then Fire
Protection One oh okay okay he shoots
fire so fire production you know better
than
nothing sure yeah we got a full set
yay it's not bad Okay
Yahoo okay now I just need to trade more
to get even more
emeralds from you I can make I can make
okay okay okay let's get some paper
going Peppa
Peppa pretty good you can always strip
the entrance it's still diamond armor
yeah y y no I think I'll keep it
projectile protection doesn't do
anything against Dragon
okay okay but
still at least it looks fancy what am I
doing it looks fancy that's what
matters yeah oh I wanted to make a chest
for this armor in
particular I want to make a
set let's take take
this let's put it next to the other
chest over there the Fireballs aren't
projectiles I thought they were but
maybe it's only like smaller
projectiles
so shoes
shoes
helmet
pants should i m these ones we can
enchant of something so let's just buy
threee more chest plates and those two
will
enchant probably like arrows yeah I
guess
so yeah we might have a enchanting table
eventually before all of this ends then
we can do it otherwise anything will
do even unenchanted diamond armor would
be fine
we want to make a couple different sets
though right because we will die yeah
yeah oh I mean yeah maybe one backup set
if
we if I can
manage it would be really cool per
person one back up set maybe maybe yeah
if you have the enchanting table you can
do it or is it the blast furnace uh
Blast Furnace right enchanting T table
just for generally enchanting but the
the traders that I'm raising they
already give us like Loki Enchanted
armor oh yeah it's convenient so you
don't need a blast furnace uh no no
Blast Furnace I already made that's what
I needed for the job for them ah I
see that's
my that's my artist right that's
[Music]
the artist of my newest outfit sent a
super
[Music]
chat you know Callie cuz I I've been you
know always using different artists for
my new outfits so oh oh he sent two
super chats wait it looks like two super
chats is is it is it bugging
they say anything oh
yeah thank you for wearing the new
outfit W bigs w w aerobics thanks for
all the fan art drawn by all of K's fans
there's so
many they must be happy about it I enjoy
watching myth one BL Minecraft
[Applause]
[Music]
y That's So Random I didn't expect
that oh how sweet I wonder if your
Sensei speaks English because
seems to be watching this whole time and
we're not talking any kind of hard to
understand yeah we don't we're not
speaking any as opposed to when I did
the the Whatchamacallit the clubhouse
one where us two English
speakers we don't even have Japanese as
their first language what are we
doing it was a challenge so it's fine
fine myself
[Music]
wow blessed be the
Sensei yes spicy spicy
outfit Chad I don't know you might be
sad about it but I did request to lower
the jigglin by 5%
approximately just because I mean I
think it's nice yeah like it's just just
a
limit oh the outrage it's just 5% just a
tiny bit you're probably not even going
to Noti this unless I tell you which I
now did cuz we have an honest
relationship you and me Chad she's just
going to firm them up firm is also nice
you know but still soft firm basically
yeah they're just getting
firmer yeah it's a good thing it's so
there's nothing wrong with a bit of
fness some he some half oh the outrage I
want to see what the AI summary says
about the current out oh
yeah call can you refresh and see if it
says something I'll read it for you I'll
give you a dramatic reading oh my God
people are reacting to the virtual
YouTuber Wawa reducing the frequency of
revealing her legs during the stream
with some expressing disappointment and
others finding it humorous oh all right
let's try that again a can we try that
again people are reacting with disbelief
frustration disappointment to iris's
announcement that she'll be increasing
the firmness of her character model's
jigle physic
you're talking about the tofu oh my God
Iris who mentioned
Iris probably
chat outrage they're expressing outrage
at iris's decision to increase the
firmness of her character's model gizal
gizal
physics is that what it say sorry that
was no it's not I said it wrong no it's
just that c can't read apparently
despite the AP English beus react to
shock disbelief and dismay over Iris
announcing plans to increase the jiggle
physics firmness of her character
model's legs with many humorous and
exaggerated responses like not the legs
and
tofu oh no not the
[Music]
tofuu not that
t wait how many more do I need I need
like these there's nothing wrong with
some fluidity right but you know they
might have like a bit more like of a
hefty bounce after you reduce it by 5%
be it's really just a tiny amount yeah
just a little bit I I like them to
be at least somewhat realistic I mean
it's I I do think you don't want to be
watery you know yeah but I I do think
it's like it's I've seen like crazier
boobies like not IR I mean like in
YouTubers I've seen crazier ones I don't
think they are completely unrealistic
just a little bit like the way they move
uh I think is okay but just like they
move like even when I like nod like this
kind of crazy so I just want it to be a
a little bit nerfed in the smaller
movements but they can stay the way they
are in the bigger movements is what I
said and I said just go down by 5 to 10%
oh oh oh oh I I know I went up with what
I said just now have I think that's
fairy I think I said like wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait CH don't
go crazy don't go
crazy wait
10% wait wait I you guys want watch
boobies I mean that's fine but you know
it's no I respect your decision you no
wait wait so I said I yeah I said 5% for
the
F and maybe up to 10% for the boobies
but only um only for like the small
movements mostly
[Applause]
chill no she said 20 she said 20 chat I
heard her under her breath say 20 people
are reacting to the vtuber Kiara and a
recent change she made in her model's
physics particularly the amount of
jiggle in her legs her community is
divided on the change many expressing
disappointment and even
unsubscribing don't unsubscribe you
mongs no absolute Rascals you stay loyal
kfp like this enchanted book here come
on
please why must it be like this and from
the future she n did 65%
how wa but it said it said it was
divided I I feel like it wasn't even
divided maybe not I don't
know oh oh Phantom maybe we sleep let's
try
sleeping I'm down I'm down for a quick
nap you're not you're not losing the
jiggly Pi it's just 5% they're still
going to jiggle
she literally said 100% this is
insane 65% that's basically a
rock oh I should have never said
anything
okay oh no noore 300% reduction
reverting back to stick
figure yes I will become like the the
guy that Iris draws oh baby
time irus
oh bab bubble when they have little
babies do they look like baby children H
they look like the same adult model just
sized down it's kind of
creepy no they tried I guess you only
accept 1% okay I'll do 1% but like five
times how about
that you are chickens you can't do that
MAF you can't you can't add it up you're
just
chickens deal okay
deal there you go managed to bargain
with him congrats okay deal okay deal
not enough beds okay I'll go make some
but I wanted to
[Music]
um I think
I wait
why no you are
[Music]
different you're going to have one and
then wait you're already Diamond I guess
I don't need to level you what the [\h__\h]
am I doing ah m m m
a spicy
me sorry my brain is like
so you've been playing for a while don't
worry about it no it's I it's been like
this since the beginning though my
multitasking skills are not working
today especially when uh when you were
not here yet and I was like doing
sorting and Mining and villager stuff
like everything at the same time I was
like running from one corner to another
doing things always forgetting what I
was doing and stuff like that like now
busy like right now I doing what was I
what was my
purpose what was my purpose what was my
purp got
rest no I'll rest when you feel like it
that's all I'm going to say it's only 3
a.m. but yeah I I
I late I feel like it at least if I end
it a little bit
earlier I'm sure everyone will
understand then tomorrow maybe I can
also join for a few hours at least just
bit to try and figure out what the heck
how to do this iron
farm I want to I want to I want to wait
I want to make a little bit more
with the
armor
so eh I only had one helmet so far okay
I want to get let's get let's go get
four helmets and I want to try to
enchant these with some books guys help
me
choose something good from our book
collection we
have impaling two looting two Force Two
fortune two for blah BL channeling blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah this also all all this doesn't seem
suitable ah this one blast protection
could be good maybe although that's for
explosions he good against Dragon let's
[\h__\h] go yeah he kind of blows things
up no with
his fire does feel like he's blowing
things
up Unbreaking one I guess we don't have
such super good
books fire
protection we need blast protection
protection fether
falling hey this is blast
protection does nothing for Dragon
protction for we don't have protection
for okay I really want that book that
that uh that enchanting table now no I
really want
that maybe okay that'll be our mission
tomorrow for sure yeah cuz these books
kind of suck they're never what you
really want it to
be hey well do we have any eggs because
this Tut tutorial requires eggs it seems
it needs eggs yeah Zombie egg and three
villager eggs it says it's your time to
sh no the special eggs not that you guys
aren't special yeah that's different
wait I thought it was your shine no
sadness is there a way to get zombie
eggs I I think that's just for like
creative only when you spawn them um in
our case we're going to actually bring
the real deal there oh God you think
it'll work
M how many did it just how many did you
say oh let's see there's going to be
three villagers and one zombie three
yeah okay that sounds about right name
tag for the
zombie okay who else do we
need oh wait I did it
wrong I forgot how to throw eggs for a
moment even though I've been doing it my
whole life
see what materials we
need M over preparing for five minut
well yeah uh we it's all part of the
journey silly yeah it's also I'm really
just trying to extend install but the
fact that we decided for the I already
told Himi that the ender dragon fight uh
will be like basically the day after
tomorrow um that means we have one more
day to prepare so why don't we you know
use that time to prepare I was going to
take a break cuz I also thought most of
the others were going to take a break
tomorrow I didn't see any reservation uh
or like scheduling from anybody well
then myy moved it yeah then you moved it
so now I'm like damn it what do I do you
don't have to don't worry about it no I
have to I have to it feels like I need
to be
there if you
want Ender
birthday oh well I think wait her
birthday stream it doesn't overlap her
life it does not overlap no she gave a
thumbs up actually I think yeah I'm
pretty sure she
did I think it's like the day after no
wait let me see does she have it in her
schedule
uh no she doesn't have yeah that was I
saw that too I was like I don't know
when the
schedule wait what where
is wa her schedule is kind of gone for
me yeah I can't see it either what
happened I don't know maybe you got
private it or something who could say
he any wool uh a little bit by the
sheepies thank you otherwise you got to
cut some more you making beds mhm I need
three okay
okay what am I doing sorry K where are
the
Sheep they're around your Forest if you
go towards the forest look to your left
oh oh I remember where we put them thank
you oh yes with the Enderman great
awesome
fantastic no shears
though make some
I mean she gave a thumbs up so I should
be fine I think maybe her stream is like
24 hours or like 20 6 hours or so
afterwards or I don't know I can't see
oh there
shears please Andy don't hurt
me 24-hour W stream no no no no no
no I'm too old for that kind of stuff
24hour stream yeah you could totally do
it if you wanted but key word being if
you wanted to
uh I mean I did 12-hour Marathon maybe
once or twice or thice by now but and
that depending on the content it went
quite
smoothly mhm but 24 hours I will
freaking die it's a long period of time
time yeah I'm not I'm not I don't have
that power in me
anymore you know what sleep is important
especially as you get older I
feel I'm too old for this
[\h__\h] yeah but I do like I don't know I I
saw you know Japanese members 24-hour
streams I'm like damn like like they're
preparing so many programs for it and
looks fun oh you want it to be good yeah
but I I just feel like it's it's a
special experience and when you get
through it especially when you're not
doing it alone but you're doing it with
a partner like Miko Senpai and cor
Senpai then
then I kind of would want to do it too
you know if it's like
that right that seems fun I'm kind of
changing shifts a little bit here and
there yeah and like help each other yeah
that seems way way more
doable Callie take the hint oh do you
want to do something like that I don't
know did you didn't you also want to do
something like that oh yeah I've
definitely thought about it before but
wasn't sure if anyone would want to do
that I'm always in though it's just a
matter of you
know if you're if you're down I'm down
so
I don't know it's it's wishful thinking
I think on my
side oh well there would be a lot of
preparation involved that's for
sure yeah we want to make it good that
can take a while and that probably have
to be in Japan for it so that we can
like that might be ideal that's what
they
did I'm not adding that to my PL plate
this summer for sure because my summer
is is uh
rough yeah also I saw P Senai talking
about this and then after that I saw
like
viewers uh Ian viewers still kind of
like um fear Rising about it but
like
uh yeah cuz fubuki Senai said it so like
she kind of said it so maybe it's okay
um like whole life
summer in any case is not happening in
the capacity of like last year if
anything's happening I don't know about
it so it's definitely not happening like
last year like with a concert or
whatever and at this point it's like
almost end of June so it seems like it's
not happening which is so sad I don't
think it's going to because like whole
life summer it was like gone and then it
was back and people were like oh my God
H life summer is back and now it's gone
again don't take it away again
maybe we just got to wait for next year
but I think it's maybe it has I really
don't know the reasons but maybe it has
to do with the fact that you know the
studio is getting used a lot this summer
for all kinds of things oh yeah oh yeah
all kinds of project so maybe it was
really a choice of availability and in
that case I think it was the right
decision um you know to let yeah I think
so us do these other uh projects that
need to be done anyway like 3D debuts
for example you know don't want to delay
that for the sake of whole life summer
now I don't know depends on the person
but like cuz we had to deal with so many
delays of our 3 debut back in the day
that's why I feel like okay that should
take
priority you know yeah I get you yeah so
yeah but maybe it we'll come back next
year and we'll be like super hyped like
oh my God whole life some's back
again it'll be history will repeat
itself right yeah keep I'm coming back
it'll always be back com it'll stop
coming let's see um do we have any
string by the way I just need one more
string uh I keep looking how do
you you have string yes and one string
there's probably string in some chest as
well but here I think I got all of it
thank you so
much okay I have my loom finished almost
got all the materials I need
looms 15 slimes well where are the key
kids why did you not make kids yet huh
what's wrong with
you like
yada you just don't want to make they're
still stuck here yeah I'll free you you
don't want to make you don't want to
M why does the bread wake him up like
this and smoosh him off of the bed funny
let's
z z z z
z z z
z Oh Z oh yeah you're right z z z I'm
sorry it's ZZ
Z can't there are monsters nearby there
are monsters nearby I'm going to
disconnect okay nice can come back
already okay oh lovey Dy okay I'll go
make more beds for them that's probably
what I was going to do anyway ah Chad
I'm sorry I'm so useless oh what you
mean off
useless but I'm I keep on forgetting oh
do you still have the shears in your
inventory by any chance do I'll give
them to you sorry about that I was
holding on to them right now I'm coming
to you I'm right I'm behind you oh take
a moment just sit right there here you
go yeah it feels good the pr sorry I
haven't been writing my diary by the way
ah no worries I I no this like you're
not the only one who forgot and and then
I think I mentioned it and then GAA
wrote her Diaries and I think she wrote
like three days at once oh um and then
am also heard me complaining about it
she also wrote three days at once but
then she only wrote like one word each
like
suffering okay that sounds accurate
though she's not lying well if you want
to write it today I would be happy to
read it tomorrow cool okay yeah I'll do
that sounds good
make more sheep have everything I need
make more
sheep not for you
end this has become a whole like
mishmash mish mash mix Max of animals
here that are not supposed to be here
yeah M
Mash why are why is it chicken a
merchant an Enderman a donkey and a cat
here that's quite the like the group
mhm cute little sheep I can't share you
can I no oh small looks like the chicken
wait did I just call it a chicken or did
I call it a
sheep chicken did I
okay oh oh
no I just see see sheep there's
definitely this sheep
yeah that is a sheep for
sure 65 concrete what's the thing that
looks like a funnel a what it's like an
upside down gnome hat but it's
gray I don't know what you're looking at
oh maybe it's a it's either a hopper
Hopper do you already need
one um yeah I need nine
nine
yeah that's a lot got to spend iron to
make iron I guess hippity hoppity it
better not explode Hopper okay we need I
got my torches I'll light it up that's a
okay that's that's a lot of iron um you
might not be able to make all of them
right away cuz we have 17 now and one
hopper
needs five one hopper needs five
uh so you can make three right
now okay I can make three
Hoppers maybe may be difficult to finish
this project today not sure yeah with
that many Hoppers might need to make it
um should only need one
hopper it says nine though it says nine
in or only need four I guess there's
several different versions you
know just bottles has nine so that's a
big
one botles has nine we don't yeah we
probably don't need such a nine is for
3x3 funnel four is for 2x two
funnel can Si okay well I feel like
could we yeah could we size it
down and you need nine chest well we
have plenty of chests that's not a
problem you can probably work around it
yeah you can place it at the end okay we
can place it at the end then I'm not
going to worry about The Hoppers I'll
just put them in the you can temporarily
other blocks instead of The Hoppers
until you get more iron yeah oh okay
that works sounds good to
[Music]
me W let's prepare the materials and
that'll be what I do today for this and
then we'll build it while I'm getting
weaker W that's okay I'm probably going
to stop in a second too okay we stop
together yeah and then tomorrow we G do
a bit more we finish that we make an
enchanting table maybe am Oro will wake
up and help us with it yeah and then
we're so so so so
prepped oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah got a few more beds for you guys
Yahoo I just need need a lava bucket o I
think there might be one in either the
food or the tools chest Okay lava bucket
lava
bucket and a water bucket
too how much bread do these people
need oh oh baby Time come on come on
make a baby make a baby don't was them
too closely Ki you'll make them nervous
you don't seem to mind honestly you sure
they're used to it that's how they were
raised you say so oh oh so so much love
is in the
air their beautiful green eyes are
meeting each
other go make a baby oh they made one
that looks exactly like them that's how
you know it is from
them nice no one else was involved
except maybe someone else who also looks
exactly the same way yeah you say that
but jeans are funny you know it work
strangely you never know look nothing
like the parents um let's see we have
one bucket and then do you have well
there's no Lava do I have to go to the I
have to go to the nether to get it right
wait wait wait wait wait I I still have
uh one how many do you need there's one
here thank you I need this okay so
that's good that's all I needed and now
I need a water a water B so this is
endless water up here right uh take yeah
take this one where there's no plants
growing in the water plants gotcha okay
thank you and now I have everything I
need how I baby Bor didn't you just
watch the stream you should know by
now this is how it's
done birth was a success well yeah why
we [\h__\h] tired why we got to go I'll
watch you do your last steps and then
we're going to just hit hit the bed oh
yeah hit the hay are you going to go
back to sleep or stuffff to do no I have
a members only stream coming up soon so
I got to girl you're so insane you you
play Jack books you had you had to
stream oh my God the amount of streams
you've done in the past hours on girl I
have to do it noise but I want at the
same time I want to it's
fun I like hanging out with you guys and
this is like you're basically streaming
now so this is not an excuse you know
you you're basically streaming you're in
my stream but it's so much more chill
though I don't
know concrete is a little bit less
stressful when you're not
streaming yeah you need
concrete yeah that's what's recommended
non any non- burning block will work
though maybe not concrete cuz that seems
to take a lot to make you need like
gravel sand and dye and stuff like that
so forget that maybe Cobblestone you
think Cobblestone fine Cobblestone will
do yeah Cobblestone or honestly we have
have so many non burning blocks we might
even have gather all concrete I have
enough nice okay then we have enough
okay all right so I'm done then I think
yeah that's
it all the materials you can see in this
box over here in this
chest all the materials needed except
for a few more Hoppers but we can do it
before we should be able to yeah you
didn't put glass though in the chest and
I see him using glass here so I'm
confused I have to research that we
don't have to use those glass they said
we can do it with like bushes for
example cool oh and then there is
another chest that needs like there's
like a real road with like a mine cart
and a trapo and another loom in a boat
but that seems easy that's easy to get
is that chest over here also materials
for building no it's just stuff I dumped
out of my inventory oh okay cuz there's
a bit more iron here too oh yeah you can
take that yeah okay I'll put it back
into the like a gem gem
gems chest
yeah catch fire from the lava glass
would be helpful to see if it's actually
working out first
a maybe not the full amount though right
yeah glass is pretty easy to make though
I think you know actually I I'll cook
some for while we're
gone yes only cook in your I might have
taken all the sand maybe there's a bit
more from mining uh 11 sand we'll make
it work
make you there's also one one glass
block in we can make glass panes I think
one glass block might make a few more
pains than
one y let's do that sounds good to me
and then maybe there's some more sand
here there's 14 sand in the in the
mining block
Box O Okay that's that's good that's
good 14 sand
iron
okay burn some of
this
okay oh we can use chests right as fuel
yes big chests or the buckets of lava
but you might need them now
so okay I'll just start cooking yeah
cook cook cook
it time I'm so used
so useless you're what do you
mean you're not useless at all you've
done so much stuff I'm tired let's go to
bed then sleepy time no I want to see
you go with me okay I'll leave I'm not
leaving you
behind I don't want I don't want to like
loog out and then you get like blown up
by a creeper cuz I'm not there okay true
enough I want to help you if such a
situation
arises yeah all good see myy left the
game now we're good wait can I be what
can you write the diary I will not read
it now but if you don't write it now
you're going to forget about
it okay all
right if you remember what happened in
the previous days uh feel free to write
that too uh a little even if it's just
like two words or so and I'm going to
let you do that I'm going to log
out disconnect right so that you can
focus on writing that yeah thank you Al
for keeping me company yeah catch you
later okay bye-bye Ka Mor byee see you
later everyone see you kiaha she do be
typing she
[Music]
typing
okay I'm I'm tired earlier than I
thought I would
be it's the the the fatigue of this
shitty sleep
schedule I'm honestly this made me think
I'm glad that I'm not forcing myself to
stream for like na Prime Time generally
just because it's a better time to
stream and just living by a realistic or
like for me comfortable sleeping
sleeping schedule instead of forcing
something is
better I can't I can't live like this
girl you live like this what the
[\h__\h] stop yapping and
[Music]
sleep I really need to do things I also
need to pay my taxes because I missed it
and my tax lady reminded me like weeks
later like hey oh it seems like you
missed paying your taxes so now you have
to pay
700 extra on top of your taxes so make
sure to pay it
now gaps harder
mhm it's not nice I mean she did give me
a reminder that the the payment is
upcoming but that was like weeks before
it was due I would prefer a reminder
more like closer but I guess her job is
not reminding me just like telling me
once and I need to remind myself so
that's okay the tax evasion is
real oh yeah that's that that that that
was funny the the AI summary about tax
evasion I sent that uh screenshot to our
uh uh Discord uh where everybody sees it
all the members and managers and we had
a little laugh about
it justice is coming yeah bye
J I can't believe that's how it ends
with my I was like I I I posted it I was
like okay um thanks so much everybody
had a good run um I hope that future or
other Generations don't make this
mistake as we do uh goodbye myth is out
I wrote it like that it was an obvious
joke
but and then Ena joined in and one
manager I think it was I think it was
HMA was like why didn't you pay your
taxes don't let Justice no well they
probably saw it they saw the they must
have seen it
they saw that I posted that
yeah yeah so this n not like this no so
I I don't know I will decide if I'll
stream or not tomorrow depending on how
I feel when I wake up and when I wake up
the time but I might I might stream
because if I'm going to end up in like
in Minecraft anyway I might as well
stream
it no POV
please but if I do a PO then I I
actually like will have like an everyday
every day one stream like it will be an
actual proper playlist with no days
missing in between no unreamed Wawa
appearances that you have to look for in
vods on other channels it would be like
so nicely completed and
satisfying and I like having my chat at
my
side yeah it would be a full set
so I will do
it yeah I don't think I can resist
playing tomorrow but that means so today
today
is now it's Wednesday so when I wake up
it will still be Wednesday and I I'll be
streaming Thurs day uh night more like
Friday night first day Friday night is
the um
finale
then I
I on
Friday I will do a short
stream to watch Austria versus
Poland and then I'll take Saturday off
of
course they will be chill it'll be chill
we're not even playing a game we're just
watching balls get thrown around
H I'll take Saturday off and if I must
I'll take Sunday off too but ideally on
Sunday we would watch uh some movies
together uh members
only
okay [\h__\h] there's so so much to
do okay if only I could split myself in
half like this for real for
real on Sunday maybe maybe maybe maybe
M okay and thank you for watching today
I'm going to go eat my dinner and
then it was exciting day anyway with
jackbox and Nintendo Direct and Justice
oh what that actually what a what a day
what a [\h__\h]
day
[Music]
czy stream tomorrow probably
might as well already put up a
reservation and turn we say
[Music]
byebye oh
go
[Music]
p
I'm already making the next thumbnail as
we speak
[Music]
okay okay okay I'll end it