[Music]
foreign
and mic check mic check one two three
magic magic one two one two I think I'm
gonna make mattama louder
one more mic take my check one two three
[Music]
thank you
thank you so
much
[Music]
okay okay
aren't you guys hearing like noise from
the microphone don't know what noise
[Music]
and my guest is
um
[Music]
when did I say I wanted to do potato
chip collaboration with bottom Mission
but I think it's a long time ago and now
it's finally
[Music]
I'm gonna translate a little bit I I
oh well but I'm hungry hungry
hungry so hungry so that's why I started
this dream a few two minutes early
um
hungry wow we have many potato chips
today
[Music]
maybe potato chips today uh seven I
think seven seven seven different
choices from each country
[Music]
and we're gonna eat them and compare and
give them points 10 out of 10 or less
and yeah we'll see like which one we
generally liked more at the end science
um
[Music]
then
if you watch your streams you probably
know but if you don't then you probably
don't know she ETS potato chips all the
time
[Music]
um
yeah so you can't even trust my judgment
just trust hers
[Music]
um
we can again
[Music]
so I was saying that like um I feel like
Japan has like all kinds of like
interesting flavors but Austria maybe
not so much but they have like
interesting shapes in my opinion but
then again I feel like I don't need
special flavors because I just like
um salt the most simply Simply Salt and
vitamins if I said she likes uh solves
the most too so
um
[Music]
we don't have any sour cream potato
chips today actually
I forgot about the existence of it when
I was born
[Music]
I
was having a party
hahaha
um
[Music]
so I'm saying that like I want them to
fight and I want mine to win but in the
end it's like an individual thing right
and and like
I grew up eating Japanese potato chips
so she probably likes those the most and
I I probably like my own the most but
we'll see so we start
that though wait
a minute Contender is that the word on
my on my side is
[Music]
um
the shape of tiny potato fries but it's
potato chips
foreign
[Music]
she said that the first the first uh
participant potential should be a simple
or like the classic one yeah um
yes so it's salt versus salt
foreign
[Music]
she's saying uh
okay
[Music]
here we go potato chips are being
scattered on some plates
dinner
[Music]
[Laughter]
did you hear the crunchy
[Music]
I don't know
um
[Music]
she's saying I'm eating my potato chips
so much that there's nothing left for
her but no we have more than enough
[Music]
um
yeah
give our first contenders
knock knock
[Music]
um
I picked up a potato chip that was like
folded and those are like the best
um
we're here
[Music]
no she likes them
um
[Music]
we're eating each other's
um potato chips
[Music]
I don't know
I wonder if they have one of those that
I have you know the potato fry shape in
in Japan too
[Music]
come on
campaign
I know
um
[Music]
mama
we're gonna like you know we're opening
like seven packages actually 14 right so
we're gonna take some home and also
leave some for the staff because we're
in the studio
um
[Music]
yeah I guess it makes it a bit difficult
that they're so small and you want to
eat so many at once tell them
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
I'm 10 points from here
okay first contenders
10 points from both of us for both of
them um
foreign
sleep a lot beforehand yeah
um
she's telling me that
um you know uh I should sleep a lot
right before my showcase but then she
says that because she's nervous when it
happened before that she couldn't sleep
but I said that's probably not the only
reason it's probably because you stream
all night and then you're used to
sleeping like early in the morning and
so that's why you can't get up and she
said yeah that might be true
[Music]
um
okay
she's telling me not to eat too much
beforehand
so that's
it I will dance
[Music]
security
series
I've been saying that you know even
though you know it's been two and a half
years so obviously I've used my model
before for like last year for example
for my birthday concert but that was
under an environment that wasn't as
professional as this one so I'm like
curious to see how much better it will
be how it will look like so looking
forward to that yeah
okay
[Music]
coconut
chicken cake
our next contenders am I actually saying
the word right I still don't know R okay
oh
am I singing right now
is camping uh okay it's right okay it's
um uh from okay I have to explain this
by the way the brands
[Music]
so I recently found out that the Kelly's
brand is from Austria which I didn't
know because most of our things are like
from Germany or like other outside
country companies so I didn't know and I
was so proud
okay so we have good containers that we
both have never eaten before and they're
both chicken related okay
wow
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
chicken wing flavor specifically chicken
wing dough which is very interesting to
me why is it not just chicken flavor
this is chicken wing flavor
connection yeah
chicken
ah I'm thinking
that is
[Laughter]
can you imagine maybe you know it comes
from the area that's called eye Skin So
ice prefecture and you know I was just
maybe you were noticing I was making a
joke maybe when they were thinking about
oh which flavor should we give for our
region
I am a chicken
let's go let's do chicken wings
let's try chicken flavor
three two
one
oh
my um
on her side she's like tasting the
Pepper too
actually I expected a stronger flavor on
mine but I think I'm glad it's not too
strong
um
[Music]
that's going there
so it's like chicken
wow yeah it's shaped like a fried
chicken and it's like hollow inside so
it's like fluffy and crunchy at the same
time
nice sound
okay
oh
ten points
[Music]
just give me 10 points again because
she's she does think that she would like
normally just buy it from now on and eat
it at home while streaming
oh
[Music]
come on
foreign
[Music]
oh
my God
thank you
on me
[Music]
it's such a strong pepper flavor holy
I'm not wrong
[Music]
really strong it's good though
she likes Peppers so she likes this one
too which I'm surprised because first
she was like ah you know salt salt
number one but now she's also on the
pepper team huh
um
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
what's it
Antonio
International
[Music]
foreign
he says that she feels like it's a
little bit like spicy after eating a
couple of them but first it was kind of
like a weak flavor but then it got
stronger because it felt spicy but I'm
saying no way because I am really
sensitive to spiciness and I didn't feel
anything and it's probably the pepper
from before
all right
no um
[Music]
Jonathan
foreign
[Music]
I think
um the pepper flavor
it's so strong so if you like pepper
this will be a 10 out of 10. but I
thought it's like too strong and it
really overpowers the chicken flavor
[Music]
what's up
yeah
[Music]
I would never buy this again even though
it's good but it's just not my thing is
[Music]
Go Get It Go Get It all the ice cream
people is
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
because she's like you know the expert
but she says we could do it together
[Music]
so that was grilled chicken versus
tabasaki flavor
next topic is
why do you love potatoes
and that's something else as a snack
that's it
no
it's good potato chips
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
eat potato chips and then her mom would
get angry at her because obviously you
shouldn't be eating potato chips when
she's making you a nice breakfast in the
morning so yeah it's just it's like a
influence from from long time ago
[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
foreign
come on
[Music]
you guys I thought that if I stream from
the studio there will be no problems but
apparently there will be problems always
instead Ian curse foreign
[Music]
Focus
it's your possible
[Music]
um
okay
we talked about the potato chips love
that she has yeah so actually
foreign
[Laughter]
we have like two supposedly spicy ones
[Music]
[Laughter]
come on
when I bought it I did not think it
would be spicy because all I saw was
paprika but then I realized oh it has
some chili in there
[Music]
but it's kind of
um
ah awesome
[Music]
okay
so uh paprika flavor is very very
popular in Austria and what am I saying
it says hey what's up another long day
just try our yummy spicy caramucho and
say hi
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
videos
[Music]
it's very orange very red uh
probably same uh color but mine are
riffled foreign
[Music]
oh
hold on
[Music]
laughs
yes yes wow so you know you know how
much I hate spicy things this one's not
so bad I I feel some spiciness but it's
totally fine and I think the paprika
flavor is just amazing it's bell pepper
by the way yeah
gonna
no no no
um
oh yeah this is also
um popular
um potato chips brand in Austria and I
think also in Germany probably
um
[Music]
and yeah I will give this
um
[Music]
7.5 oh thank God
um
okay eight out of ten for vitamins
Empire
[Music]
because she doesn't like paprika but I'm
saying like maybe she will like it if
it's from Austria
each
crunch
she's doing a face that's not very happy
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
hmm
my name is
[Laughter]
I feel like it doesn't make me say but
I do I feel like it's like it has an
interesting
Aroma to it once again
it's like opening up in inside my mouth
yeah it feels like
I I I can taste the chili even though
it's not spicy
I've been I've been scammed by this
is
maybe maybe if you on top of these chips
if you put some hot sauce if you pour
some hot sauce then you get what you
want because I think if you buy this
then what you want what you're looking
for is spicy potato chips and then you
eat them and even for me so spicy so
it's not like you're getting scammed so
I'm kind of disappointed
[Music]
thank you
okay so she says it's not like
disgusting but she doesn't like Africa
um
[Music]
yeah
points
[Music]
for me
I mean
it's the disappointment
and the lack of crunchiness
um
five
oh five um
absolutely
mine might be spicier than hers even her
packaging looks more spicy but mine
feels spicier
um
[Laughter]
topic
they must
Senpai wow
[Music]
um
so I'm asking her
um about Japanese traveling because
she's like you know big traveler in
Japan too I think and if she has any
um
spots that she would recommend me to go
to and then I told her where I went
already and I don't it's like too many
what she said that I already went
everywhere is that true
[Music]
in
um
[Music]
what is this place you Flynn it looks
like
it doesn't look like Japan
um
[Music]
I don't know
thank you
[Music]
tonight
I wanna go to Okinawa so Okinawa is like
the like place to go in summer for
Japanese people if they want to go to
the beach
um and I haven't been there and vitamins
but the place she recommended me is in
uh
prefecture and it's called and it looks
really special and she went there for
Onsen because it seems to be focused on
Onsen but we're talking about like how
it feels kind of like
not desirable to go to Onsen in the
hottest region in Japan
in the summer it's like hot hot hot like
how how can you even no no thank you
maybe in winter but soon
[Music]
Okinawa
um
[Music]
oh yeah
so next she's bringing out the potato
chips that she got in the place that we
just talked about uh oh actually I
wanted to change the video
okay and so the place that she went to
recently here she got these potato chips
yeah
[Music]
this might be spicy because it says
um adult spiciness
like a Japanese citrus fruit right
[Music]
special special flavor
um
[Music]
it's not really related at all and not
comparable but we have potato chips in
the shape of onion rings with onion
flavor onion
um
[Music]
oh she likes onions so we might have a
chance to impress her on this one
[Music]
wow very oniony smell onions
okay hers is also smelling very
interestingly
[Music]
I feel like her potato chips you know
they're like pretty big but they're also
really really bright colored so to me
they look like they're sparkling wow
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
okay so I can already I think say what I
think about this
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
I feel like you know when a friend of
mine gets onion rings from the fast food
place then I'll take one but I would
never buy them on my own and also I
don't like texture that much actually
so I'm not that happy with mine I will
say
5 out of 10. I'll stay with that number
it's pretty bad I mean
I mean it's not that bad I think it's
good but I don't like the texture
so I'm like that
[Music]
she's she's unsure about her is
uncertain
seven seven one why why why why
use the skin on that thing oh she likes
you too
so even
[Music]
though
um
[Music]
jacket
she says that the texture of hers is
like surprising so I'll try now with
switching
[Music]
oh
so good
interesting
[Music]
especially I don't know if you can even
call it spices something like
it's not like like chili kind of spicy
that's nice
I mean yeah it's like pepper spiciness
[Music]
yeah
and and the texture the texture is like
fluffy actually um comparable to you
know my favorite ones the the bare ones
that we're gonna bring us don't worry
um but the usual flavor gives it
something like Fruity right but it's
it's surprisingly fitting
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
the spiciness of the pepper is stronger
than the usual but the user is
definitely there
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
cannot handle the adult spiciness
foreign
[Music]
pool because it like gets stuck together
I guess something like that
[Music]
then you will like this
is
[Music]
saying the texture is like making it
lose a lot of points unfortunately
okay okay and let's Skip One topic you
know I don't even think I have that
money so let's go to the next because I
want to be on time so
oh
yeah
fighting
favorite contenders yeah this is um our
both favorites so they're not really
like that similar but they're our
favorite so on my side
it's my favorite you know
foreign
it's so different even though it's like
salt flavored I don't know what it is
but this is just like so much more
addicting than any other salt flavor
chips and it's also the texture which is
so good um
oh
it's a sweet soy sauce flavor from their
Kyushu region and they put it all
um
because she likes it so much and she
also eats these while streaming so these
are her number one let's see if we can
impress each other with our number one
job okay
[Music]
oh
interesting interesting
um
[Laughter]
because we were eating like so many like
weird flavors now strong flavors now it
feels kind of weak but it's so
cool
[Laughter]
right now because we had so many weird
flavors
[Laughter]
it tastes different than we remember it
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
yeah good stuff we're like confused
about the flavors right now but it's so
good
she was she was saying that the first
one actually feels like tastier right
now to her than this one I don't know
it is
even the water we're drinking wine but
um
okay so I mean I'm a bit confused in the
flavor right now but obviously I'm
giving my babies 10 out of 10. what
what now where our hearts lie and that
is with these potato chips so 10 out of
10 of course
[Music]
soy sauce flavor before
thumbs up
[Music]
foreign
it's like good on other things but I
don't think it fits potato chips
oh no
karaoke
um
foreign
[Music]
she's saying the texture is really good
but I'm like you know I'm telling her
that I also think right now these
actually taste different than usual they
taste less salty than usual
and she agrees it's probably also
because we've been like you know trying
so many weird flavors but she says that
this texture would have been good on the
onion rings that we had before yeah
um like they're similar as in like they
have like a puffy texture but the Palm
Bayern are doing it correctly they're
doing it the way it's supposed to mean
[Music]
I told her this one has different
flavors too but this is my favorite but
we I don't think we have sour cream and
I think maybe cheese and probably also
paprika you know paprika is like always
there
[Music]
okay
um
she hates bell peppers very much it's
okay
[Music]
foreign
I know
what's up
okay
next what are your chips But first you
still have time let me ask a question
um
[Music]
when I first met her in the studio a
long time or not that long but a while
ago I've noticed something and I wanted
to ask her about it because that was my
first impression
um
my first impression of her about them
was that her skin is beautiful and I
wanted to ask like how did you do it
[Music]
[Laughter]
tonight
look
[Music]
tell me why you skate carrots girls talk
now wow ah is it because because of the
oil from the potato chips and the potato
chips
they must
[Music]
come on
so she has like you know some stuff that
because we all kind of use like girls
like some
um
hydration stuff for your skin but also
she got like a special cream a while ago
from a special place and it's
interesting because even though it's a
cream uh it's like
you put it on and it but it comes out as
like bubbles like you know like uh
something that you wash your face with
but it comes out as bubbles and you put
it on your skin and then it's a cream
yeah interesting actually I think I
forgot to give uh points to each other's
stuff right
now
okay okay
[Music]
I
thought this does not fit at all
foreign
[Music]
honey
because she says it looks cute
um
[Music]
foreign
rarely
um
[Music]
she's praising my looks now even though
I was praising her
whatever
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
pretty good
[Music]
okay we're going with some cheesy ones
but I never ate this before and I don't
think there will be particularly good
um
foreign
[Music]
but we have some cheesy ones now so mine
is this one that I don't know I just
want to go variety
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
peace
[Music]
she thinks that this one everybody likes
but you know the packaging already looks
incredible
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
come on
Pizza potato versus cheese potato and
mine once again have a weird shape and
they're really bright yellow
it's so bright yellow okay
[Music]
I'm not expecting much
oh
this is terrible wow
it's pretty bad I don't know I don't
like the texture I don't like the flavor
but if you like cheese then you might
like it
um
laughs
I know
[Music]
it's weirdly
hard like in a weird way like you know
they're supposed to be like crispy but
it's like a hard crispiness it's
difficult to explain
um
[Music]
she's saying hers is really good but the
cheese flavor is really strong
wow the cheese on hers is like literally
visible to my eyes not just you know the
flavor the invisible flavor
oh she wants to eat these in the middle
of the night
don't know four
months it's me being kind of
um respect respectful towards my
country's potato chips maker probably
um
okay
switch
I don't think you want more than three I
only have three on her face
[Laughter]
[Music]
she likes cheese that's melted but she
doesn't like non-melted cheese
so that I guess reminds her of the
non-melted cheese that's why she doesn't
like it so much
okay I'll try the pizza one
day
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
come on
cheers
I'm saying that I feel like
you know it's doing a good job at what
it is it was very focused on the cheese
I I wish the other ingredients would
have a chance to shine a bit more in
this product
um because I'm not a big fan of cheese
but that's pretty good it's pretty good
look at me pizza Vibes I guess and it's
better than mine also in terms of
texture
[Music]
um
cheese
apparently there's some different types
of this one
love jingle visit guys
if you guys see it tell me
um
[Music]
I'm telling her to eat more because for
me it also became tastier after eating a
couple of them so I'm forcing her
it's not looking very happy
it's not getting better
[Music]
okay
nothing
sorry
Civic one
much
[Music]
we're going back up yeah okay next topic
I feel like Japanese viewers might be
asking themselves a question by now
um
[Music]
foreign
like very popular here a very popular
flavor would be seaweed salt Nori shield
and they have it everywhere and I
thought she would bring it because this
seems like
standard for Japanese people I don't
know they have it everywhere but she
didn't bring a single one and then I
thought that maybe the Japanese viewers
would be wondering where is
um
[Music]
one more flavor that we're missing here
that's also very popular is
foreign
[Music]
so I made her also by seven or bring
seven so she had to like choose you know
and that's why she left some behind but
I was oh
[Music]
okay
what's your favorite potato chips flavor
I mean
[Music]
foreign
cheese normal salted Kettle soups salt
and pepper salt Rosemary oh I did see
some Rosemary ones I almost bought them
let's have a pretty onions
[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
in the chat but yeah she couldn't and
then I said well speaking of sweet
things she said those sweet we have one
more Contender on each side and hers is
actually sweet yeah
[Music]
potato chips
so this one is a luxury it says
literally luxury chocolate vanilla
flavor
[Music]
time limited and this is probably more
like something like what Cali recently
wanted us to eat on the street
and yeah
it looks so good in the packaging
is
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
because you know there's no potatoes in
there but um you know it's maybe for
people who can't eat potatoes and she's
forgiving me that's the cheapest
and chips
[Music]
something
I never ate this before either
oh
yeah
it's literally how it is on the picture
hers are like you know like lines of
chocolate are covering the potato chips
wow interesting
and then
okay okay
[Music]
um
it doesn't give me much sour cream
flavor though but it feels like potato
chips
have blow chips too
a little bit more healthy
[Music]
she's confused reverse she says they're
good but it's confusing and she can't
even say if it fits if it matches or not
mine I think are good actually
look
no
foreign
[Music]
I will give mine
actually a surprising 10 out of 10 even
though sour cream flavor is not quite
there but it's really good it's like a
good amount of saltiness it's a great
texture and it's just actually pretty
damn good I know
[Music]
um
fat
[Music]
thank you
yeah they're healthy I think I mean
it's perfect 10 to 10 actually surprised
how about the chocolate ones
not so bad
[Music]
um
let's switch I told the story about the
Cali potato chips that she brought the
chocolate ones that were actually not
for their chips at all was kind of like
disappointing but actually good
UMass
oh
it's mysterious
she wanted more of mine nice
I have to say no no
[Music]
um
I don't feel that salt that she has
detected on these chocolate ones at all
so that that might be why I like them a
little a little bit more
um
[Music]
foreign
it's like not too much chocolate and I
don't feel the saltiness so it's not
weird
and I'm oh
I do feel the the vanilla flavor
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
from the beginning but
I will give points oh
how many points for the lens chips
10 points or lentils 10 points
she says it's surprisingly delicious
really good oh potatoes
[Music]
um
so some people are wondering now can we
get this in in Japan but
um
[Music]
please come to Austria and get the
potato chips if you're curious about
them
tonight
[Music]
indoor
um
[Music]
foreign
but otherwise I guess it's just a reason
for you guys to come to Austria and then
hopefully I get some like uh promotion
offer from Austria government
um
no no
no
time
[Music]
yeah okay
so we're done with the potato chips
cure Ichiban
um
[Music]
yeah so we're saying that the ones that
we were positively surprised by is this
one from my side the lentils but
negative surprise was the the soy sauce
one another side it was a Cheesy the
Austrian cheesy ones
[Music]
look at it
thank you
yes uh salt flavor is best in the end
and our favorite ones are still the best
after trying all these ones
um
[Music]
you can be very honest with saying this
but do you feel like in general
um
your your own countries are better or
from Austria
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
you know I was asking her which one she
prefers in general but then I said I
actually don't want her to have an
opinion on that right now because the
ones that I brought like some of them
you know I just brought for the sake of
having different flavors and not because
I think they're good so if I would bring
the ones that I think are good I would
probably bring different ones and she's
like me too me too I
we have to offer we have so many more to
share very varieties
[Music]
no
hello
[Music]
I'm not that hungry anymore either I'm
not feeling quite filled up but I still
have to eat something proper probably
um
[Music]
.
you decided
[Music]
foreign
in the morning and she said well she ate
them morning but not for breakfast it
was before she went to sleep but it was
morning time and I said you know what
what
you could you're not yeah you're not at
fault because that's not breakfast
breakfast is when you wake up and eat
something and she did eat onigiri for
breakfast so I would say that does not
count as breakfast the potato chips yeah
so she grew up
[Laughter]
on a late night snacks
late night snack oh great night snack
later oh sorry
Make That Snack
s
[Laughter]
okay okay
everybody thank you for watching today
we will have to leave the studio
but I hope you guys enjoyed this
[Music]
um
thank you
[Music]
foreign