[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
this is
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
kitty kitty
[Music]
hello there wait
hello
[Music]
yo
yo yo when I wanna introduce introduce
first yes karaoke
[Music]
oh you got it hi Maury's here it is
I'm excited
oh sorry it's okay no problem
no problem more is here hi Jesse
Miss some more clappy death Grim Reaper
I'm here I need to do my best for my
team ID Sports Fest well let's go I
think your brain your brain is still
sleeping huh yeah dude I don't know it's
been a long day
what happened
[Music]
not Lo-Fi but you can't call me your
Brio fee but it's not love I am can I
[Music]
sure I mean like um FYI I'm I think
probably I'm not the only uh I'm the
only one who doesn't open stream so
you're free to watch from whichever is
[Music]
uh
hi hello everyone my name is
wait um okay
um
the black hair from whole life ID third
generation
[Music]
you have to remind yourself about your
introduction
without any introduction in my own
stream
oh my God
so
okay
Indonesia generation one I am
part two in these guys I'm actually NPC
right now
you're doing I can see your forehead
yes
okay calm down calm down
no fighting yet
calm down
next is me hello I'm iron I have I have
been chosen as the produce team leader
this year
leader leader I salute
hi a good good day good morning good
evening everybody uh I am participating
in the soccer match and also in the
badminton with a teaming up with Kaila
so two games I will do my best fighter
routine
[Music]
passion English
very good
no no good English
[Music]
okay
so before we start I actually have a
little bit of uh
[Music]
yes before we start so
um
okay
okay so before we start I have something
to announce that
Uma will not be here but but they are a
really diligent member so they already
practiced
um in the afternoon although there is no
stream and also later on uh one hour
from now uh hopefully sooner Senpai will
be able to join
[Applause]
yeah
what uh I think Mona here tonight will
help us as the mod for several uh some
games nice okay
and also
okay so I will also explain about the
game first uh okay for each game okay
but but maybe it will be better if we go
about the teaming
[Music]
let's go first impactivity team we have
um nine members including me and then
there will be Elfie Kyla Senpai ganas
[Music]
yes so many strong people are we are we
strong anymore we are strong all of you
are great
[Music]
thank you you're great
yeah
pink ladies
ladies
one two three four five games five games
the first the first going to be a a
catch the four third floor capture the
four thank you uh and from our team it's
going to be uh Kyla me uh fauna and Luna
yeah
and what's it called again
two more people to kind of like join
um
because they aren't here
if you want to try the fort you can just
join in okay
and then there will be potato sack race
[Music]
so basically it's a race
uh basically you insert like like you
you go inside of the potato sack and
then you jump
so basically it's not it's not the the
normal race it's like the race while
jumping you have to jump okay yes and
whoever uh complete the three laps uh
within their member
first is the winner
yay okay
the team will be me yay
[Music]
um
foreign
okay
[Music]
you're playing against the blue the big
the big blue yes so basically it's the
pink team against the blue team
[Music]
because it's going to be me coyote and
Cali okay we've got this you have to win
don't give in to the big blue right
[Music]
now
yeah
and then there will be badminton so
badminton will be will have two rounds
basically A and B
a there will be Kyla and Kiana yes
and in badminton B there will be iofi
and Sona Senpai
[Music]
and then last there will be soccer oh
yes soccer is really fun soccer I love
how you're saying soccer and not
football
that'll trigger some people
okay
so
basically
initially it will be me but it's going
to be change yes so the team for soccer
will be eovie
[Music]
and before before we start playing I
would like for everyone to go here
cute
whoa that's amazing
wow amazing
I would like to teach you
I'm looking at the let me look at those
script okay
I have the script I will I will read
everything first from the from the top
to bottom and then we'll practice after
that okay okay
so I will I will give example first
fight fight fight let's go
hoo-ha
okay okay
you got it did you get it guys yeah yeah
yeah I mean there might be some delay in
this chord but yeah it's okay it's okay
I got the yazzo part yeah the Yago part
I got for no problem
to manage the delay I will I will I like
it's okay to to take times to answer so
it will it it's it's okay to not be as
fast as how I did it okay okay
um
okay are you ready yeah yes ready ready
ready
two one
[Music]
tomorrow
[Applause]
yoga
[Music]
[Applause]
we got it
no problem what does it mean
oh okay okay so basically uh that one
is like the the best team
[Music]
on whatever okay like the strongest team
ever okay
foreign
[Music]
yeah it's like yeah
let's go
again right
again I'm ready I'm ready
[Music]
probably uh I wouldn't say it's probably
like most likely
um the MC will tell us to do that before
the game starts later
chill okay if you'd love to practice I
already
put the
the example the audio example for that
there so feel free yeah
kind of you're kind of gone
yes really because
foreign
[Music]
so uh which game do you want to try
first
um
[Music]
soccer Kelly soccer
I'm ready for football let's go Kyla
you're good yeah let's go let's go
soccer
change
who are these people oh my God
these are NPCs that that are copies of
Muna and Kyla they're fake
[Music]
this is the fake
interact so yeah you are not
participating in the next games
should we should we
um split into two teams how many people
here I mean this is
three and three okay
I want to be goalkeeper okay I'm just
gonna be white all right
[Music]
what should I do is roll
what twice I went for white
okay so you're gonna be a keeper or
starter I feel like we should practice
what we will really be in the end okay
so basically who wants to be a keeper
because keeper is the only one position
I'd like to try I I want to try it if
it's okay yeah you go do it keep her
I'll practice the the other one
okay
what is this okay I'm just oh roll okay
I'm just gonna be standard too
um
[Music]
keeper six minutes please oh already
already
[Music]
six minutes
right now why team Striker I have to
explain something first okay
so there is uh like three items uh if
you are on basic there is like two shoes
green and yellow and if you're the
goalkeeper you will holding this
yay oh this one yeah this is for the
goalkeeper so okay for the goalkeeper
um if you want to get the balls you have
to click it so it's gonna be on hold
and
for the
basic one uh there's like two uh green
and yellow the green is like a regular
kick and the yellow is the long cake
and there is uh if you are on the uh
some special occasion
that you have to kick to the goal what
is the name
I forgot your name
it was like a final decisions
shooting
[Laughter]
um
there is there is like uh
you cannot use this one you're gonna use
the yellow so you have to use the
regular the green one uh you mean the
penalty you mean where you stand in the
corner and then shoot or no no no no not
in the corner
in front of the goal in the center
ah where they line up so it is 11 meters
shooting okay okay they line up and they
try to get a goal until yeah they get it
okay okay
okay so that's all uh okay okay
[Music]
thank you
oh my God okay
yes
oh it stopped there oh
at least I can't be out of breath here
in this game
unlike real soccer
where am I ah the Reds okay
[Music]
the ball
team wide let's go oh
[Music]
yay no
no no no no no no no no no no
no let's go
[Laughter]
oh my God I'm gonna get confused by the
colors
let's go
try bro
are we allowed to go past there yes
I think we're allowed though I don't
know because I don't know soccer rules
how close can we get to the goal can we
like walking this is possible is that
allowed
[Music]
don't worry
oh no
I'm not talking about it
where's the ball where's the ball I
don't see it
goes back into the middle
[Music]
yeah it's gonna be like that where is it
no no no
[Music]
okay okay
yo stay out of my goals
nice try nice try ladies okay okay white
team let's go
[Music]
thank you
oh
great
time oh there's a great time great time
okay
so like this is fun I like it
this is crazy
oh so okay I will I will be the back
Kiara we're okay
I will
um
[Laughter]
wow a long kick
I have found my new Talent yes
apparently I don't like the pressure now
no no no no it's okay you just take the
ball I think
[Laughter]
yes yes yes
yes
[Music]
oh oh can I block when someone's
throwing it I guess not
[Music]
no no yes
nope oh the fireworks are giving me lag
oh really oh [\h__\h] I gotta I gotta
quickly open my door BRB
okay
oh
no no no
let's go okay no
okay should we pause back
now
oh it doesn't look like it
referee yeah
you always have King a bit for like a
few seconds
apparently there's no Pals in the game
there was a stop
Kayla I think
is still opening the door right now so
she yes
[Music]
I'm sorry I'm back
sorry Amazon delivery Amazon Amazon
[Music]
is it gonna end in a tie
that was finished
this game is only six minutes as
requested by risu
regular game will be on 20 minutes ah 20
minutes
everything
yeah okay but I'm already I'm already
doing so much better at this than in
Pokemon unite I'm excited
what are you talking about
natural Talent okay
is this again or moving
okay
[Music]
before it keeps the girl oh what is this
please
[Music]
be prepared
what is this my slime
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
we've got a lot of penalties okay I
can't defend the goal right I can't
mean
[Music]
okay really okay
I just fell through the world yes
I also I was flying a second ago
well I think it's because you switch
because it was switched to ilfe so that
she's controlling the goal and then so
it switches back to you yeah
[Music]
let's go okay all right good good
where's the ball I'll do this
and I'm gone
okay yeah me again oh my God
[Music]
I think you're going into spectator mode
amazing
it's gold
here we go Kelly here we go let's go
I'm gonna do a
um
I guess I have to be up closer to it
I can see Cali come on ready you have to
anticipate yes
[Music]
what is going on
let's go that's what we needed
I'll try I'll try
grab it
[Applause]
oh you did it
no no go cocoa
[Music]
yeah
I'm gonna hold the ball
nice song Oh bad
all right I'm gonna hold it
let's go bring it
coin
wait uh
[Laughter]
oopsie oh no oh no holding your feet
hold it
ready ready
can't curve yeah try to curve the ball
but it doesn't work
[Music]
[Applause]
I don't think I should be the goalie
is is elfi
um in the soccer are you in the soccer
game yeah I'm in a soccer game you
should be the goalie I don't want to be
oh yeah you did pretty well too yeah
that's the only way I can we can win all
of us together okay you'll be our goal
keeper
[Music]
more yes yeah I'll always try for this
time next one okay
I wanted to keep white again okay I'll
be team red I like red
I think I get a white again
yeah okay I'm gonna be Striker you'll be
Striker are we good keeper
I'm the best soccer player in all of
Austria because we suck in Austria we
never make it to championships or
anything Striker
who
is who is goalkeeper on red Ella maybe
okay
okay sure sure
okay I think I I think I pick it already
I cannot change it oh can I wait wait
again I think okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay
again
[Music]
okay I'll be helpful this time yeah
well no time wasted
okay
let's go
[Music]
Colleen let's go
are you going
there how is going there
nice nice nice nice
let's kick let's go party yeah leave it
to me
fun okay
no
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no
[Music]
okay oh wait
no no no no
I hate this yeah
[Laughter]
okay
let me go back let me go back okay
no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no
[Laughter]
they're so fast
[Music]
let's go
no no no no
no no no no no no
okay y'all are aggressive
hell yeah gotta be I am we are gonna be
you gotta be aggressive and I'm glad
we're on the same team
nice
nicely yeah yeah yeah
come on
yeah okay okay
let's go
okay here we go
[Music]
oh okay
okay so it's a cracked goalkeeper okay
dead again
[Music]
you must
continue should I started yes
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
oh it's fun
nope nope
yeah
let's freaking go well
you guys are getting stronger yeah
[Music]
no no
foreign
[Music]
okay
oh God oh my God everyone is getting
stronger
because
it's my ball oh I see I see because I
threw it outside over there I see gotcha
all right all right let's party
[Music]
okay cool
oh my God
yeah I wasn't prepared
[Music]
Get Ready Get Ready Get Ready
no no no
no no no no no no
[Music]
come on
yeah I touched
[Music]
it
the goal needs to be counted yes
this game good game
[Music]
so we want to go back go just left click
okay okay
[Music]
what is the next one
okay this one I am with Kyla and then
there's uh iofi and Sola Senpai as a
team
yeah we need we need opponents
foreign
okay can you guys give me a left-handed
uh bat please
[Music]
everyone's good everyone's good
cute it's like a fly catcher
okay okay everyone's good okay
I think it's gonna be easier if you
press F5 okay
you cannot see the shadow come on can we
hit each other yes no no no no there's
gonna be a channel
yay okay ready ready
let's go
let's go okay we should sell make sure
that uh when you want to kick the is it
yeah throw the ball throw the ball uh
make sure you don't go uh don't look up
because when you look up it's gonna be
sword oh
yeah it's gonna be short it's it's gonna
stuck in your place it's not gonna be on
your opponent please okay so look more
straight
yeah it just looks strange because I'm
strange
okay okay
[Music]
how do I know
foreign
[Music]
uh I see I see aim for the red
oh I gotta fly oh my God
[Music]
[Applause]
if you're not playing the game you can
fly don't worry about that
oh no oh because you looked too far up
oh I see
[Music]
I think I understand how long will this
game be in the actual uh tournament
20 minutes
okay
thank you
[Music]
guys are strong
I think I can trust my teeth this is a
real song on every game Kyla I'm sorry
this is difficult I don't know where it
goes
later okay
yeah nice nice
okay
company
no they said this third person is better
Chad they said third person is better
because you see the shadow
really I didn't know that they said So
Right girls you said F5 for third person
is better
it depends on your preference actually
no okay I'll try this one um This Way
live okay I'm trying F5 okay
foreign
I feel like I don't need so much
practice but for this one this one now
yeah okay
yeah
[Music]
you guys got a train we need white one
more
white one who is it no white white
okay okay okay
let's go do
yeah let's party
okay
let's go let's go oh let's go let's go
okay okay
[Music]
okay
nice
one Carla
finish the tournament it's on Sunday
right it was fun Sunday for me
but in the early morning 6 a.m that was
pretty good yeah Saturday for n a okay
oh wait
[Music]
[Applause]
on the left
nice one it's nice nice sweet so you're
okay
nice
[Music]
okay let's go
we can do it oh ball out I think yes
[Music]
very straight ball ready just let it hit
the ground yeah
wow yeah um if they're shooting over to
your side for the first shot you should
just let it fall down to the ground if
they're gonna if they're not gonna hit
the red what's here we'll show you guys
a trick
yeah
very cool okay okay
oh uh you're too far behind good job
come on let's go
where does that go
you did it pretty far yeah felt like it
yeah
and the first person I feel like I see
the ball you can hit it
but I don't see the shadow but at least
I see the ball
that's maybe
okay
that was a good one
hit it hit it
okay
oh okay
okay on the ground for a second it's
still sorry I'll get back with my side I
thought it would already be over at that
point nice okay
because it looked like it was already on
the ground it was it is
just kidding I'll be left it's fine it's
fine just full whatever yeah just follow
just follow them
[Music]
oh no oh
my god oh wow you guys are strong [\h__\h]
that was too high though
yay
go out of the court or was it does it
landed
yeah
fun we have good badminton players
badminton okay let's go next game yes
yes
[Music]
model
um
okay
is our is our potato sack Team all here
oh no I guess not because
but but fauna already practiced right
and Solas Empire is coming at midnight
oh isn't that now midnight none for her
because I already practiced the other
day so I suppose she did okay
so I can try okay
we can all try this one it's okay sure
yes because it's like three versus three
which no you don't still need one
I'll join white the white okay I mean
two versus two is it good though why I
guess so yeah
[Music]
close your eyes
sick from this game
one time just one time
how does this work it's okay it will be
over before
in real life okay it's like a rainbow
yeah
okay
[Music]
oh that's so cute
faster than this yes
oh no oh no there's lava thank God I'm
not participating in this I'm never good
in these races
ah
yeah there's no way okay you're good at
this
it's such a cute idea
what
wait wait
are you are you going the wrong way
Callie yeah
oh my gosh oops I went the wrong way oh
wait um I was pressing Ctrl
you'll be already in her second round
oh cause I thought you were you passed
me already but that was okay because you
were slow
oh
honey
he's the best route why am I so slime
means yeah try it the best fruit
[Music]
determination
you get shot
oh
my God okay the bounciness I can see how
yofi gets sick from this yeah yeah
oh I understand yeah what's that motion
sickness
okay I'm gonna get sick from this too
being stuck in the berry bush
did you get through the berry bushes
there's like no path through them no you
you I had this no I don't like this
oh I'm glad I'm not doing it again
I never have problems with motion
sickness but even this is too much for
me
you can get through the cobwebs that's
about it
bye
just kidding I lied
I'm not in sync with my potato sack
do I have to have to do free laps
you can you can actually just just stand
there waiting for the other team to
finish it okay come back there
why am I flying
I don't know I'm done if everyone has
already gave up just tell me I can just
stop the game
this is really tough okay yeah okay okay
the only one from our team who's here
right now who has to practice this is
Lisa right so yeah I want to finish okay
okay I believe I believe in this video
okay yes
yes
there we go I finished
[Music]
nice huh
it may be making me sick but I have to
say it's a very cute original way to
replace a normal Marathon relay so very
cute
[Music]
let's go let's go
let's go
[Music]
okay okay I need to practice this one
um
[Music]
okay
so you free should be in one team and
we'll be in the opposite
you'll be ready
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
okay yes okay yeah who wants to join my
team I'm in one team no hello you need
one more oh hello yeah we need one more
uh okay
[Music]
um
she just said she's bad at it
thank you
for watching up here
everybody goes up there
okay yes
do
[Music]
ready I'm ready ready okay I'm ready
find out your finger Queen
how do we do this
so basically you're Korean uh you spam
right click you on I click the lever
which lover whatever
whichever oh my God
left click right right right right right
right good it doesn't do anything for me
fun
I have no idea what's going on
the whole game
obviously the room
okay one more
you need to like spam clay the
level with a right click okay
besties unaware
we both didn't know what to do
oh I didn't join now we know now we know
um
I haven't joined yet hold on I'm going
down okay I'm going down
leave it to me
okay okay
let's go holy macaroni
Hannah
the the whole architecture is insane I
know who built this okay Magic
[Laughter]
[Music]
got this one
thank you
[Music]
strong arms no more noodle arms strong
arms no more noodle arms
on my finger
my middle finger
try again again again this is fun
again again
we have to win
let's go let's go
practice practice
we have to win
left side or right side either fine is
okay
I'll see also tips from me you can
actually pick the furthest lever so you
don't really need to like stay on the
front lever okay that's safer
so you don't fall off so early I guess
okay okay
[Music]
right
if you want to focus more we can like uh
divide on different level left or right
yeah
okay and everyone hits a different lever
right yeah yeah
oh no
the most part is
okay okay okay
[Music]
nice let's do it okay
on us
make us feel pain
here we go easy
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
maybe I should be in the team
okay well you know what happened okay
what actually I started doing better
when I changed fingers when I changed
fingers actually
oh man
this time I'm gonna try okay with the
other finger unless you guys never give
up my strong finger yeah yeah basically
and actually I will not lose this first
stick with your
um pointy finger yeah yeah that's what
I'm gonna do yeah I switched Midway
through so that the other one gets a
break but team the current team red
lineup is our homeban lineup a real
lineup so you girls gotta win against
team white go go go go go
okay okay I'm ready
foreign
[Music]
really
bad coolness Empire is not in this
right seriously Beauty
it's ground free
[Music]
also you can you can press shift so you
can you you barely move I think oh that
would be nice
hold on hold on hold on uh I messed up
don't get it still moving I'm still
moving even holding shift yeah me too
yeah it is
not like you have to keep on moving
forward like while you're hitting the
thing I see it's in small steps ah wait
hold on because it because I hit shift
it messed me up
it's okay
[Music]
I'm chilling
I want to see I want to see even more
stats like who who the most pulls each
member I want to see exact stats one one
versus one oh
we're using we were using a game
controller it would be a different
decision
on the button mesh and queen like two
like space bar
no I mean I mean you can do it right I
guess you could yeah I mean you can do
it if you want it okay yeah
[Music]
so we'll start changing language okay
let's just try without Kayla okay
wait two versus three
okay
okay two versus two okay oh okay one
more
she did
[Music]
oh yeah
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
red okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
I mean if you want to one versus one
it's okay though I'm gonna try white
team okay okay so white and Chihuahua
white okay
[Music]
let's go okay that's good that's good
let's do it okay
um
[Music]
you're playing against Kobo you wanna
you wanna teach her a lesson right this
is so true
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
imagine that and then you will be so
much stronger
she's taunting us cool boys touching us
John
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it's so close oh
finger
[Music]
the problem is when we're so close to
the the numbers then it takes so much
longer and our ubis have to hold out
longer
um
we'll go as long as you need me to
my underarm is feeling strange
I may not be as fast as quicker but I
have stamina
please
[Music]
oh yeah
come on
[Music]
[Laughter]
look at those numbers guys oh my God
[Music]
we're equals
equality yes let's go
We Stand equality
we're starting to kind of lose it
let's go let's go
we're leaving we're leaving
I'm gonna break my finger
[Music]
um
but we're still leaning
[Music]
oh my God
oh my God please
oh man my fingers
thank you
[Music]
oh my God
carpal tunnel syndrome
[Music]
is doing well is Fred's still a good
thing for us is it not
[Music]
we tried really hard
laughs
[Applause]
maybe the fight you're alive
I'm never doing this again
except if someone gets sick
[Music]
Kelly is actually really strong as well
yeah
you did my best we held our own against
you
so we played all games already
yeah seems like we played them all looks
like it look at it
the Labyrinth can I take a break because
I'm not in the game anyway yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
let's see I think Mo is actually gonna
have to leave now I gotta go to bed but
that was really fun
good luck to you guys
rest your fingers
I will rest my fingers and I'll fight my
best for the time
[Music]
bye everyone
foreign
[Music]
um
okay
let's download again
[Music]
so thank you foreign
foreign
[Music]
nearest
Metallica
I am watching and on the day who
actually gonna play me reasons and also
there is another thing as you can see
yes
[Music]
okay okay
hands up here I want to tell you guys
that be careful uh if you're on your
opinion land so as you can see this is
the center of the place
the one that I am sitting right now is
the center of the place and this is the
red uh
the Red Land and this is the white land
if you're white and you're going to Red
be careful uh if you meet your opponent
because you if they get you you will go
into jail immediately
okay and it's also vice versa with the
others
your friend can help you to get out of
the jail okay please explain it in
Japanese okay
okay
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
took everything from me thank God I'm
not participating in this game I already
practiced the games that I am
participating in which is um the
badminton and the soccer and the soccer
was I think generally like you know
it's kind of natural thing badminton I
definitely need some practice
uh with like
aiming not not necessarily aiming so
much but catching it but I do realize
like for F5
if you press F5 and you see your
surroundings you could see the shadow
but I feel like when I tested that the
shadow it's like it it looks like it's
so far away
and it changes like you know Direction
like as you see it like over here and
suddenly it's there pretty quickly and I
can't keep up with it I feel like it's
easier to see
um the ball itself in normal first
person so I think I'm gonna go with
first person after all yeah I was more
successful with first person anyway
wasn't I Hi Marissa you too here oh my
God
yeah so kylo says she's available for
practice anytime so I might be like off
stream I'm practicing a bit more
badminton with Kyla or also maybe after
we're done here
yeah because some people are probably
gonna leave early on now when all the
games are over for introducing
introduction so yeah
um
apparently we're practicing today like
eight hours ago or seven eight hours ago
apparently off stream I don't know
I don't know when that happened but they
already did it apparently yeah yeah it
looks crazy right holy moly this is like
next level construction but I wonder I
I'm assuming they got help with it
there's no way right
yeah yeah I heard that some members like
commission plans
uh like designs and all that
from other people I didn't even know
that was a thing
that people commission like people to
make them like Minecraft construction
like plans and then they build it
and you pay for it it's a bit it's a
huge business for real
damn okay
thank you
um
[Music]
I am watching spectating
gambates
[Music]
yeah at least you need to try one
I didn't care but be careful of motion
sick be careful
listen to that I didn't really mentally
listen to the instructions though
it's okay
should I just run what which team so so
if you pick white you see that uh White
laser like two up to the sky yeah yeah
you need to go to the red one okay I'm
if I'm white I gotta go to Red okay yeah
if you're red you need to go try just
try to find a way okay
to the white and then if you see your
opponent just punch
okay okay okay easy easy
yeah I clocked out
all right I'm back in I'm back in again
[Music]
who wants to go with red
let's do
that
yes you you practice
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
oh let's go okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
should we go together
except should we be okay maybe separate
is better because we have higher chances
oh this is closed
do we have HP nope
yeah we have the the in the middle one
red bars items
oh
okay
can't you like remember
to remember you can do it I mean I'm not
in this but can the people who are
actually participating remember the the
pattern
[Music]
then you just gotta remember the pattern
and you win but but there are mobs right
there are mob status yeah I just I just
ran all past all of them they didn't hit
me once pattern
s
mother s okay
get us onto something tell me if you
want to remember it but maybe maybe you
can bamboozle them and just change
before the real match just change put
one door somewhere
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
that was all the games
[Laughter]
[Music]
foreign
she wants to have a pink team
colony was worried but she wants to have
a pink team okay
understandable have a nice day
um
[Laughter]
mm-hmm
[Music]
one thing to ask first
you're okay you're good yeah
should we practice the badminton again
yeah
okay
[Music]
um
your life is okay
okay okay
so three versus three
not two it's all you can play by two
yeah
I mean if you want to play treats it's
fine too it's gone actually yeah Kyla
Kyla
um
yeah because that's our actual members
okay
since uh you guys will no longer need to
practice and soccer then I think uh you
can actually lead this uh start game and
the stop game okay
[Music]
thank you
okay let's go
all right
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go oh Focus
concentration okay
[Music]
okay
okay should I stay more in the front
than you more in the back okay
okay
[Music]
they don't expect such close ones shorts
okay I didn't I didn't think about that
one very much all right that was good
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
too much power
they ain't too much power
[Laughter]
oh
wow
Auto
laughs
[Laughter]
let's go you view minor
I'm doing Japanese
[Music]
okay let's go let's go
on fire hell yeah
let's go let's go
this is fun I like badminton but it's
easier to uh in Minecraft than it is in
real life
[Music]
sweating potential
wow okay okay
Kyla nice backup
hello
gonna protect the front yeah they always
shoot so far
[Applause]
oh my God oh my God
wow
I'm not ready it's fine it's fine it's
me neither
[Music]
ready though it's okay it's okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
we need to run faster yeah yeah all
right I think it's out yeah it's out
inside
Kyla's always there
is actually making me feel very relieved
everybody
[Music]
nice it was fun
that's fun let's practice again hell
yeah of course that was already much
better than before
[Music]
Kyla I'm up for more practice yeah maybe
we can one versus one yeah
foreign
[Music]
what's up
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
makes the Minecraft screen really really
short for the potato sack game because
she normally feels sick for these kind
of games but she just makes it really
tiny and it helps it's actually really
smart life hack
for sure
[Music]
can we have play different games at the
same time
yeah you two go potato sack
okay should we switch voice chat then
maybe into two different ones
we're gonna be talking about different
things okay
where should we go let's go training
oh training training okay yeah okay
we're gonna go training okay okay
hello are you ready oh yeah I guess so
you versus me
hold on hold
on setting up the PNG
one one but either way even like because
we're together in a team so if you were
good and I lose or I'm good and you lose
both ways is fine because it just means
we're good to practice the head box but
he's gonna be fine
yeah do you wanna for the actual real
game also be mostly in the back and I'll
stay in the front yeah sure sure that's
good okay
all right
but practice
like this is kind of hard because the
field is like kind of big yeah it's okay
so far so good yeah yeah it's good it's
good no
no oh my God that was that was almost
out it was on the white line okay ready
ready ready
how was that outcome we need to where is
we need to go to the the opposite side
you cannot go straight if you're passing
the first the first one I didn't even
know that yeah
that's if you saw the Ah that's what the
x is for I didn't know that
so you need to go the more you know wait
not horizontal accent wow realistic
badminton rules
fine red
[Music]
it's so good
you're good we were fine yeah I think
together will be a good team we'll be
fine
this is so fun I want to do this as a
collab stream just badminton and other
games even after the tournament
yeah I didn't even realize I was hitting
it okay okay
[Music]
yay yeah it's kind of funny
are you ready
okay
oh nice nice nice
[Music]
oh it's out oh no hey
so good
new collab game idea but this server is
like disappearing afterwards right man
so sad
can we keep it up I don't know
we'll see about that playing badminton
different server right so yeah
can we move all of this to the two hours
I don't think uh I I will pay for the
server to stay up
it would be such a such a waste of
beautiful buildings
how much time must have been spent to
make this Kayla that was so close to the
net yeah to the net man
but good job
[Music]
oh we can pull such close ones in the
real match then we're gonna bootle them
[Music]
true true
okay
no Kayla it's almost that's all Kyla I
have a question for you yeah in in
Pokemon unite uh-huh did you
you purposely always go for me because
you knew I was weak as [\h__\h]
not really
because hey I don't think Ian Tim is
weak like yeah we were decent but I was
the weakest link and I feel like you
maybe knew that
rain is level even under your level oh
[\h__\h] uh like like the Character level ah
I mean you mean our Pokemons or the
character the character ah yeah but
still like I think because you were you
were looking at the um Japan Ian match
right spectating yeah yeah maybe you saw
oh Kiana's kind of
no I say to the editing that Ian please
so need
yeah yeah of course of course you think
it depends so well yeah
really really
true I really I really saved it too
though
you're too nice too nice no no no I will
literally say that like like when when
we
um analyzed the the match I really I
really say that like not on the stream
but I really say that yeah uh the en
team
strong
yeah I mean you know that was our first
match so we were still really really
nervous but uh I think we were really
careful in the first match
and then it's super good yeah JP one is
super good
um even when we saw that we were losing
we still thought that okay this isn't
this isn't even so bad this is not as
bad as we thought it would be Ian you
[Music]
but yeah I think
uh then in we at the after the first one
even though we lost we thought okay okay
this isn't so bad maybe we can have a
chance against the ID but I was really
scared because I knew a lot of you an
idea also cracked at the game really you
know like um I I and rainy started
practice the Pokemon like four days ago
before and yeah that's literally four
days practice you too but I think I saw
your rank and it was really high
yeah because yeah because my practice
Yeah like crazy like you usually do yeah
yeah but I mean I I literally just
practice just play the game like four
days and I've never but you played MOBA
games before right like leaks on PC and
on mobile so I think I'm you know like I
mean I got the micro macro one I don't
know but you know
um I've never played on switch too so
it's like the controller is kind of hard
for us oh but I saw that you can play it
in on the phone as well apparently we
cannot we cannot I asked already oh for
the tournament we couldn't okay because
generally I saw in the world
championship I was watching the world
championships and they play on the phone
some of them
[Music]
okay can we start and continue talking
well it's chill
but you were so scary with your
especially you and the combination of
you having a scary looking Pokemon it
freaked me out yeah and you always came
out of the bushes suddenly and you're
like
destroyed I did a lot of I did a lot of
blunders here and there yeah no you also
when I was watching the jetpack the
Japan versus ID match we were spectating
all together and I was like constantly
watching ID and I was cheering for you
guys and you were doing so well all of
you it's really cool thank you thank you
you look so organized
right were you guys not really like
organized and well communicating because
to me it looked like you guys must have
been communicating so well
um yeah but I mean we we literally did
um blunders here and there so yeah
um
yeah I wish I could like hear what you
guys were talking about but it's
probably Indonesian anyway
I wanna hear what's going on like it was
somebody giving instructions in your
team
yeah who was giving instructions
um
on the practice most of it gonna be like
Kobo but on the day it's
mostly me because uh yeah because that's
just happened
was Kobo the most experienced right
oh that was Alto actually no I saw it
behind the net wait I think it's wait
it's sure okay okay
yeah I saw it was Chad wasn't it behind
the net and I hit it anyway maybe it's
the hitbox and I shouldn't have hit it I
don't know
that was weird okay
right
[Music]
yeah
all happened I'm just reading chat okay
let's go
ah yeah because I looked up too high
that's what happened yeah I thought you
hit it
was like right next to it
okay
that's so cool again on the top of it I
see
that's very lucky move yeah this week
there's so many exciting things right
this tournament and Pokemon
so many
things to practice for you know Pokemon
unite ends and then suddenly we have to
practice for for days
never ending practice yeah no next week
ending
no more practice next week
well maybe still very very busy yeah oh
yeah yeah oh yeah we have the
Independence Day ah yeah what are you
guys doing for that
uh
um we have the my giant costume review
oh yeah
yours you don't have to say about that
too oh really you don't have to say
anything but you look you're a
silhouette looks really cute to me no
it's gonna be cool
you know
it better be cool we'll see about that
yeah sure
and cobos looks so extra to me again
yummy yeah yeah
yeah as always Kobo always extra always
I'm excited is that on Wednesday or when
was that
um 15th 15 um 15 GST
[Music]
15 15.
but that's that's not the Independence
Day is it no seven things right because
17 we're gonna have something else
where's the ball ah
that's so sweet of you the enemy won't
be waiting for me yeah because we we
have that kind of rules too like we need
to wait for the opponent to be ready
before we hit it oh really yeah yeah we
need to wait okay because like yeah
should we be giving each other like a
like a announcement and oh I'm ready I'm
ready are you ready ready yeah maybe
maybe it's nice to us probably okay
because sometimes it's very sudden like
oh oh okay I just I was still still in
my brain uh thinking about what just
happened at all oh that's all okay okay
oh this is here hi hi we're done that's
fast how did it go
yes we actually
tried twice and Edwin
[Music]
brilliant okay okay we are practicing
really great too yeah yes you guys are
really
[Music]
um
passion passionate yes
[Laughter]
very good very good yeah that's very
good that's very good oh yeah
no one more Kyla okay yeah
I can't believe that you want to stop
this practice you want to go back to
hollow cure don't you no yes
thinking about hello cure all the time
but she's like are we against on the
badminton from the three candy
and tokoyami Totowa
yeah okay sure sure I wonder how good
they are if they're doing a practice
stream I need to watch it yeah yeah they
actually did they did in the morning I
need to watch the pods yeah I need to
check it too we need to know our
opponent right yeah yeah that will help
it's all
I never rely don't rely on the auto
can't rely on the Alcohol oh yes Kylie's
serving Kiara
very close I ran for my life
[Music]
what's wrong
Focus Kyla okay oh
because it's such a big field
I think it's pretty pretty big okay
oh Kyla is catching up oh well it's
ready
okay oh I'll do it
I'm getting a feeling for it when it's
out though nice
already
um yes we practice for that yeah
[Music]
well right here
standing right there
okay
nice nice
wait what yeah I passed through it it
was too close
okay I like the Smashing sounds
my legs are too short both theme are
equally strong apparently which is good
it's good because we're on the same team
yes and it's actually a good thing
yes I love this this is fun
[Music]
I got it got it [\h__\h]
wrong direction
[Music]
five five oh the score is five five for
both things
it's supposed to be out I think I don't
know yeah
I think it's my mistake for still
hitting it even though it would have
been Outdoors
[Music]
okay this is so fun
oh my god oh wait okay I'm ready
oh yeah yeah
what
oh
sometimes it's good to look up and make
short shots so that is good because they
don't expect it
[Music]
okay hi
this is catching up yes
oh
yeah
just one more one word okay one more
um
this time I waited
my last point is this gonna be a
comeback
it's going to be
very tough
I thought it was more in the front than
it really was okay nice nice
fine I don't know if you wanna practice
again
can we uh for soccer we have two three
people is not enough I guess
we can do it oh yeah
like at least four yeah
but you know right you can dribble the
ball so by the time that's the very
important one so you just can walk and I
yeah dribble the ball with short shots
short shots just kick kick kick like
that no you don't need to do that you
can you can actually hit the ball of
your body yeah you can dribble the ball
oh without clicking yeah
can I try that yeah you want it yeah
yeah let's go let's go let's go yeah I
didn't know that that's secret knowledge
[Music]
I thought that was the only way we can
make it move
I will be the white team maybe two
okay nice shoes
okay ready all ready yes
bison
okay I'm ready okay
we will not have goalkeeper okay it's
okay that's fine
hold on don't kick okay don't kick first
don't kick just oh but just walk over it
this first okay just walk over it okay
just walk don't kick
okay okay yeah like that oh yeah
yeah you you just need to like turn left
turn right yeah
how does this not go go in go in
[Music]
I want to try something so now okay uh
let's let me see how far I need to go
until I shoot maybe let's say I'm here
on the line and then ah too far wait to
go back
I think that's yeah that's kind of okay
if I do a long kick from here is it gold
it hits the most I think it hits did it
ah does it also have to do with like if
I'm looking up or down no not really
Landing not really okay yeah so we can
do like this yeah
[Music]
okay
with the ball
oh there
oh that was a score
apparently
was it
there you go but I can't go this far
right
how far am i about to go you can you can
actually go that far like I ask and and
munas be like yeah you can actually just
like go there I guess I've seen that in
soccer before as long as the goalkeeper
doesn't stop you know yeah I think the
goalkeeper gonna it's easier for the
goalkeeper to hold
rather we dribble the ball like I think
the goalkeeper gonna catch the ball okay
I think I wanna finish I I don't think
I'll I'll try the the dribbling but I
want to finish my dribbling off with a
good cake like this yeah okay okay yeah
practice stuff that's right try try yeah
so um can we have like maybe risu in the
goal oh okay try to stop the ball wait
no or maybe or maybe I will be the
goalkeeper okay let's stop first okay
okay our actual goalkeeper is gonna be
who
gonna try to stop the dribble okay
yes do it yeah okay okay
um
okay so one girl the goalkeeper is
either Elfie or Kayla yeah I think yeah
sounds good
I think it's better for me because I
think I can dribble quite okay
so yeah so you you beat the uh the the
striker okay okay okay yeah um so your
face and probably gonna be the
goalkeeper I think
[Music]
yeah maybe white so you can you can be
in the opposite goal yeah yeah we'll try
to get a goal against you
should I be the goalkeeper I'll be the
goalkeeper no no no no no no no you you
need to be the standard so you try to uh
take the ball from Kiara because Kiara
is like trying to practice the dribble
Arena
keeper
wait I will be the goalkeeper for the
white for the whitening do we need a
goalkeeper
oh you have to try to stop oh okay
you're both against me now okay
what am I am I not a goalkeeper or am I
a goalkeeper no right I'm a goalkeeper
you're both okay we both spawned there
wait wait
shouldn't Lisa be spawning over here
it's okay it's okay you can just you can
just try to take the ball but don't hold
the ball
yeah yeah just try to stop the dribble
Chris a girl I'll go around here
I'll go around here I'll be giving okay
[Music]
yeah but you got it right yes
that's right
[Applause]
oh that was I was pretty far and I only
used the normal kick at the end
so that still went in nicely I guess the
problem always was that I would hit the
the top of the goal a lot that's why it
never went in don't use the long cake
yeah just use the normal yeah
oh can I follow her I want to follow her
[Applause]
go by a goalkeeper
[Music]
okay okay
but no one
nice thank you lisue
try to catch up
this makes me want to play Real Soccer
I never actually play Real Soccer uh
what about in school like no I only
played when I was little and I never
really played anymore
how little was little we Sue
which little little baby actually
this is like little little bubble bubble
we do hey
oh
I smacked it back I think when Lisa
smacked it at me I smacked it back
oh yeah nice
okay Lisa
five seconds
okay break time I will talk to my
teammates
I will talk to the ball I'll talk to ASA
both goalkeeper
um balls balls yes pep talk yes
yes okay thank you Kiana I will do my
best Kiara all right thank you maybe try
to go from the side Kiara ah okay only
if you help me look at your gloves do
you have the goalkeeper this is my
gloves okay oh you both have you see
still both have it
and when you're talking to each other no
I am very white I'm wider I'm the widest
person in the room
[Laughter]
I'm a white basic let's listen again yes
okay here we go
[Laughter]
the problem is I have to go around the
ball because I I don't want to shoot it
in the same direction man okay okay okay
so no this is not listen no this is
Well normally I would have someone
behind me to back me up right to help me
no no no no no no no no no no no oh
no I'm gonna keep her now
that's illegal
illegal you're going to goalkeeper
prison oh I stopped it
ah I was pressing the wrong thing I was
scrolling elsewhere okay
you don't need to Skyway you can just
use like one two three
oh okay but my fingers are waste
my fingers are busy being on wasd and
Ctrl I can't use it okay you know you
know you know
Nice Shot back into the middle
not for you this is not for you it's
possible
[Laughter]
it's good I think for the goalkeeper
it's also easier to use the F5 the third
point oh yeah yeah I'm also doing that
oh okay
[Laughter]
nice nice so fun I'm feeling so sweaty
and hot but it's so fun
okay okay
[Applause]
now you can't
okay
no
oh thank you
reason why are you playing the soccer no
right
I changed with elv oh your figure okay
okay wow you're good you're good at it
what's up
Kiara is putting the pressure no
no I was close if I would have angled it
a little bit more to the left and I
would have been a cool
oh it's almost out okay okay
what are you wanna try again do you want
to try anything
um
no I don't play that no stop it wait who
is this is Lisa in tug of war oh yeah
she is yes it's me you could do Kyla
versus Lisa because kylas no we actually
did
a lot I want to see it you have to be
able to
win against Kyla
but I want to see it once how many how
the point differences I want to see it
it's gonna be a long one I want I want
to be in my uh top performance because I
already did it but yeah once I want to
see it
entertain me you must entertain me
that's a request right there
your entertained winners it's your job
we have done like 1 800 before whoa It's
1 800. on your own wow it's like five
minutes ish yeah five minutes and it's
like one on one one thousand oh I don't
want to match
I'm my team
[Music]
see I don't know if I can still do it
but why is wait why is Kyla not in the
tug of war team she could win it
[Music]
man I'm not
I'm not picked by the um style I don't
know why because he would have wanted
it's fine when I wear that clothes so
it's fine okay it's closed yeah
and my my hand feels sore which side is
which side is uh now you're running in
okay
left this is
here
okay
am I right or white
you're red you're red yeah red okay
yeah we're we're actually that close law
yeah yeah we're that close so I mean
it's fine
Oh I thought it would be a big
difference but maybe in the late game
early game
yeah who gets tired
oh my god oh yeah so far it's so pretty
it's pretty much the same
[Music]
I'm sorry I'm already sorry for in
giving you this challenge making you
suffer it's gonna be five minutes like
this but yeah I mean yeah no but
actually it is oh it's leading and and
she's creating a bigger and bigger lead
it's only a matter of time until she
pulls the first wait ah oh yeah she's up
no she's already right because the more
red mouse there's one to her six red and
four uh White So Lisa Goldies I'm red
right I'm red right oh wait no never
mind you read okay sorry mistake mistake
I don't know I don't know which color am
I yeah you are red but it's like the on
the top it's like switched with the what
I'm actually seeing in place right yeah
that's right okay
still doing very very very well yeah I
mean we got the same spit like yeah yeah
pretty much I think this is going to be
like five minutes match and okay you can
end it I think you can end it don't
worry about it
so yeah basically our difference is like
20 to 30 yeah on average yeah
[Music]
oh one one letter tap is like
um
one point or two points or what I don't
know I don't know actually I think it's
three three points every lever
yeah and and I don't really know like
how well they do it like the blue yeah I
don't know I think they're practicing
Copo is definitely a speed clicker I
think because she's a Zoomer she goes
fast
wait
wait she's a speeder I'm pretty sure
yeah is you know a master at Rhythm
games so she clicks everything really
fast and she's not she's she doesn't
just click everything randomly no she's
very coordinated with where she's
clicking at what timing so she should be
pretty fast too with button smashing I
will see the practice after this then
[Music]
you know I saw the clip about
um the um
Polo cure hmm
um yeah Easter egg where the uh grass
for perfectionists oh yeah yeah
completion is completionist
congratulations
I haven't played it yet
yeah one gold yeah I'll play it's not
four wow yeah I mean well I think I'll
play holociro on Monday or so because I
don't have time this week I'm very
focused on on this uh Minecraft and on
the whole time thank you so much thank
you so much for your answer no don't
worry I have this problem this uh starts
for me at 6 00 a.m and the Pokemon
tournament I had to be there at 4 00 am
so yeah it's it's I don't know if I
should stay up or go to sleep super
early or go to sleep
I can't do that normally though
yeah also I have I have hold a talk at
10 pm so that's like I think whole talk
would end at midnight that's six hours
before the Minecraft thing I would be
done with holotalk six hours
so that's not really enough time for me
to sleep because I need one hour at
least to fall asleep but realistically
speaking I'm still excited
ah God damn it what did I do with I
didn't think it through I didn't think
it through
um
now I wanted to do a whole talk on the
Sunday instead but they couldn't do it
yay
yeah I'll take a nap I'll just take like
a free hour nap or so and I'll be fine
okay looks good all these matches
looking good
um I think I think we are ready yeah I
think I'm good I'll practice maybe me
and Kyla can practice tomorrow a little
bit privately you can yeah yeah you can
we can just do it off stream too yeah
it's fine yeah uh just call me anytime
or even before uh you know after Hulu
talk until the actual Minecraft Holo cup
I don't know what to call it
oh yeah between those I have like you
know some time probably so we can play
the ring sure that Gap but I can
actually uh a company too so like
whatever okay thank you definitely make
my
um it's gonna be midnight
no but yeah midnight for me is like
morning time for you girls
yeah
but I I must say you girls are doing a
great job at organizing this and I'm I'm
really impressed at everything that has
been prepared for this turn this ID cup
so good job
good job thank you
okay I'll go read super chats probably
thank you okay
[Music]
thank you
that was some intense practice and and
uh man sweating I sweated I sweated but
only because it's also getting hot again
in my room
that was really cool though holy moly
the stuff they prepared
oh I had bgm on the whole time nice
really quietly though you guys didn't
even hear it did you
I heard it really slightly though I
thought it was coming from the game
I thought it was implemented for a
moment I was thinking to myself wow they
even implemented bgm to this guy now you
hear it right
well well well well
yes so I'm playing with them and these
games are so much fun too like I I feel
like because they used mods and
everything
um the games are just like even more
realistic and easy to play
like this badminton at the soccer game
like wow I had legit a blast playing it
I think you heard how much fun I had
um
yeah
they just like you know you know how
when you look at the whole life Japan
Minecraft world you know it was already
always impressive and then you look over
to the ID world and it's like
so like whoa next level
it's like impressive on a different
level because Japanese uh server is like
you know cute cute dorky weird buildings
and then ID server is like futuristic
modern crazy big huge buildings over the
top buildings
yeah so I think you can compare in the
same way the sports tournaments the
Japanese one and the ID one
Arena and everything and depending on on
the game The Arena changes too and like
what
we could Ian could never I'm
we may have considered before making our
own sports festival but after looking
with Japan and now ID has done
ours would be like Unga Bunga
um
never no no let's leave it to ID and
Japan we don't need to make a sports
festival
caveman Sports
but yeah if you are interested in this
watching the actual uh proper
home I always look for a prop better
word in English for honban in Japanese
it's such a simple short word for an
actual like performance or an actual you
know the real thing you know what I mean
the real tournament or the Real
Performance that's honban hornbun
yeah in English I never you don't have
such a good word for it like a mo one
word
really that's just special game day
game day
um
that works I guess so if you guys want
to watch the actual oh yeah Main Event
game day
that's for me it's on Sunday but if
you're like in Europe or Asia or so it's
Sunday if you're on the other side of
the globe and a or wherever wherever
whatever then it's on Saturday night
for Europe for me it's 6 A.M
I was showing you here a few Graphics
like yeah there is
uh
some participating members in EN so it's
a
the three candy team is Zeta is the
leader whoa I didn't even realize that
and Kubo Anya
um
damn
and that team has the big blue and you
know do you guys remember when I told
you about my blue theory in Wind Waker
when we played Wind Waker and I I told
you guys my my blue theory and and I
think a lot of people were still like
nah I don't know what you're saying I
don't quite agree with you but nowadays
I've heard someone else
she also brought up the blue theory so
there's a there's this thing you know it
can't be a coincidence
so yeah
um that says sorry candy team and the
pet TV team is
um uh Lisa as a leader ilfi Kaila uh
Cali me and fauna we do have some Gamers
on our side too Surah
like the left team already scares me
when I look at some of these
but honestly we got good Gamers too like
fauna is a pro at Minecraft Kyla is a
Pro with Minecraft
I I'm pretty decent and this is not so
much about being a pro at Minecraft
anyway you just gotta you know these
games don't normally you don't you don't
handle this kind of stuff in normal
Minecraft Gameplay anyway but yeah
[Music]
um
the left has bait they're gonna lose
[Laughter]
I'm scared of gouda the most for some
reason
uh apparently she was part of some group
practice already right I wasn't watching
that I was sleeping or whatever
um you guys maybe some of you are
watching it was she doing well
[Music]
you'll win badminton for sure I'm
honestly relieved to be in a team with
uh Kyla for that
at least I'm not playing against her
pickle fell twice in tug of oh yeah I
read that already a few times that
pecora
maybe isn't so good at clicking so fast
foreign
[Music]
but by falling down but then she loses
or you mean good I was distracting the
other team
the strongest ooh I'm going against
Torah in badminton though
[Music]
and then for soccer oh
our team is ilfi Kayla me Cali coyote
and Luna I have no idea how good Luna is
because she wasn't here today and this
time
and then the opponents are Zetta kobul
gouda
and Marine oh my God I don't want to
play against pecoran Malin
[Applause]
just because I don't know they I love
them but at the same time they
intimidate me I don't wanna I'm scared I
have said by respect I don't want a
plague
I have a special respect again for them
towards them
[Music]
I want to face my ocean no
okay
I'm a versus yeah I know I'm going
against so many people that I like like
amen I mean I like them all you know but
yeah I mean that's the problem in
general I guess
because I like them all
but no matter who would be in the team I
guess there would always be an issue
yeah
because generally I think we like each
other
so I could say this and whatever the
team is made out of
I don't want to do this because I like
them
no
yeah so this is uh happening
uh on Sunday uh it says there will be
free streams of different points of view
but I thought they told us we can also
stream I'm not sure this sounds like
there's three point of views
for the sake of keeping it organized
uh then I actually don't know if we're
gonna
I'll have to ask
um
what's what's asked of us because they
even you know what they did
they
prepared assets for us
let me show you because like holy moly
[Music]
this is so
wow
they made an overlay for us
like they commissioned one
and I also prepared like thumbnail
overlay which is just like the logos
um but like you know they have
everything so well organized
um
I thought I was gonna use it on Sunday
so I didn't use it today but I didn't
realize maybe they don't want us to
stream
spoiler no no no no man that's not a
spoiler
I could have used it today
hmm
[Music]
oh but it does say here if you plan to
stream from your own perspective which
implies that it would be okay to stream
from my own on perspective right
if you plan to stream from your own
perspective please feel free to use this
data
[Music]
then yeah I'll ask again
um I genuinely feel like it's good to
have
[Music]
like you know some Main povs
the leaders and all that and the
observersed spectators
but
you want to see right you want to see
wow a POV you want to see why was sweaty
I I did notice though and I don't know
what to do about it
um
that my game lags went or not not my
game only OBS lags when the fireworks go
off in the soccer game
it lacked for you guys right
I saw it on the side of my eye
[Music]
it it may have or did it also lag when
we were just playing at the end there
not a big problem yeah for me it wasn't
a really big problem either
just a tiny bit oh okay maybe it wasn't
as bad as I saw it on obs
[Music]
right now
who's the host of the tournament ID
[Music]
so I still have you know time uh
I will
[Music]
um
I will read some projects since the
Minecraft part wasn't that long
oh an update for everybody who wasn't in
the pre-chat
so last time I wanted to play Minecraft
Minecraft didn't work
uh
but it has naturally resolved itself
which kind of makes me angry
like I didn't even really do anything
um so Minecraft worked without me having
to fix anything in the end
and then my sound problem
more or less seemed to have it resolved
itself I opened GTA last night as well
um without trying to fix anything it was
just working by default but it may have
been connected to me trying out some
other things unrelated to GTA
um but I don't know
um anything everything is working now
basically GTA is working Minecraft is
working GTA sound is working Minecraft
multiplayer is working and my the
problem with you know me not being able
to use the app that has the accessory
function
because when I opened it my sound would
stutter that problem kind of resolved
itself as well apparently because when I
did it last night I'm not using it right
now
but when I did it last night it was
fixed also my roads that was the Amazon
delivery my road just arrived but I I
don't want to like change everything
right now
so
I'll keep it like this for now but I'll
be able to try it out sometime
oh yeah no because yeah yeah we got a
new app
um the app the one that has the
accessories got updated and when I tried
it out it was working so
yeah
they I don't think they like I reported
the problems to them but every time they
update the app they tell they tell us
like what they fixed
and it wasn't like mentioned that they
fixed anything regarding my issue
but they may have like
fixed it without
wanting to fix it yeah and then told me
uh or told also reported an issue like
this a while ago
and so I I told them hey with the new
app
it's working for me
I don't know if they tried it out yet
but
they were excited I I was on the phone
with all of Advent last night
at first I was on the phone for two
hours with uh narissa
and then afterwards I got like an idea
and I I wanted to call all of them
individually to ask them about this idea
uh because I I felt it was easier to
explain so I talked to all of them and
with Bijou with Bijou I talked uh with
her about some jrpg things
yeah
and I told her
um she was aware of blue
protocol
not reflection not a Clapper blue
protocol she was aware of it but she
didn't know that the the English one is
coming out next year
and that the Japanese one is already out
I told her and we promised that we will
play together next year
when it comes out it's like a Bandai
Namco MMORPG that they worked on for
many many many years that has the
graphics of tales of games and me and
Bijou love Tales of games
so that's exciting
and I want someone to play that MMO with
me together it would be sad I mean you
guys can play with us too but I would
like to have a another member playing
with me
um
and and it's just perfect I'm so glad
somebody joined who knows and likes the
tales of games
that's quite rare oh and I talked with
her about adelier a certain someone in
the chat might want to know her stance
on Atelier she likes Atelier she played
two uh older ones
um
not the newest ones she wants to play uh
she wants to try ryza
[Music]
I don't remember uh
it was I think
and another one
yeah because she didn't mention Atelier
in her favorite games list
I was wondering because it kind of fits
her tastes so I asked her Bijou do you
like Adele games too
she was like yeah yeah yeah I actually
no no yeah you actually played
um
and the other one that I forgot the name
of
she's such a bubble bubble
gonna try to impersonate her voice
[Music]
her voice isn't soaked again
Ian Luna
she do be small and color what color
wise she's also kind of there
yeah
thank you for your service you're
welcome
um I don't know if she'll stream it but
um
she definitely wants to play ryza and I
told her about the new one that's gonna
be on the mobile phone
[Music]
oh and it why am I not switching screen
by the way I'm kind of feeling
comfortable here but oh well uh ah we
gotta go here
that's right I have an office for myself
[Music]
there you go huh you guys are kind of
small but oh well
I think she had practice with Alden ring
beforehand hmm
use likes Tales of games too but I meant
I meant I want someone in EN you know
who relates to my feelings about Tales
of games
small to small house small small chat
box why smart smart
[Laughter]
EST mode if you guys don't know I'm
doing a code on a reference
huh
and one of my favorite memes
money
did you say blue protocol en version
remove the short body fat
what how how they didn't even release it
and it's known that they do that
but how can people be accurate in the
game then
[Music]
they removed what do you mean they
removed skirts
why are they censoring so much
like how they censored the the
Archer and Diablo the Amazon
[Music]
because it's Amazon interesting
ah
okay it will still be cute but hey what
do you mean like every skirt they don't
have skirts anymore what do you mean
like what
what Amazon literally sells skirts
and Amazon said salute things how like
how can they be against it
Amazon sells anything they literally
can't be against anything because they
sell anything
well
it's okay can I wear short pants then I
don't wear um in my casual outfit short
pants
hmm
no it makes no sense just because of the
game many games have skirts
that's so weird okay well I still play
it I'm so excited for it it doesn't
matter
doesn't matter I've I've been waiting
for this
since the closed
huh what was I playing the clothes
better or the open Alpha well it was
really [\h__\h] early
it was
yeah it was so long ago
what's that
yeah before how long
[Music]
it might have been I feel like I
remember playing it in that tiny tiny
tiny small smaller smart
one little apartment
uh it was an alpha I think yeah
but I think it was in that small the
smaller apartment that I had in Japan
when I joined Holo but in the beginning
of my trip
[Music]
or or not I don't I don't know anymore
was it maybe it was
yeah 2020 beginning of 2020
um
that must have been
must line up with the alpha then
hmm
suppress your computer back then could
handle it well I mean I wasn't
up
yeah
it wasn't so
I guess it wasn't so resource heavy
[Music]
did you didn't you move the month after
debut so slightly well it was slightly
less nicer as in there was so much more
space
but it was so worn down the house I went
from a one room a typical Japanese
one-room apartment
which was
small but
um
relatively modernized
as in the floors were not like making
sounds when I would walk on them
and then I moved into the house where
Casper was in yeah
uh which was a two two-story house but
like small narrow
um but for me alone it was a lot of
space
um
uh however it was like super super old
the people who moved in after me
uh renovated it
um
and that was really necessary for that
place I hope I hope they were happy with
it
um
yeah it was nice living in a small house
but you know if only if
the whole mouse rat thing was just
freaking me out you know I would always
be on alert I would always be like tense
when I was walking around the house
yeah and when I was trying to sleep I
would hear them all the time I would be
so tense I would be so scared that they
would
like
look around my floor when I was sleeping
[Music]
um
good times though looking back on it
thinking back it's just a funny memory
do you think you try but I'll just get
yeah we have a group
actually
we're probably playing in a four people
group
[Music]
um
Cali Wawa Bijou Arizona
told me a little bit about the game
because no perms no perms yet but we're
just as soon as we get the perms we're
gonna play together
[Music]
that's the plan
hope this lasts longer than Diablo
yeah that's the problem I talked to
Bijou when she asked me you know because
I talked with Kelly about playing
together and then Kelly asked Bijou
apparently and ambija told me that Cali
asked her and Bijou said she also asked
nerissa
and I'm like oh okay so we're full group
now and she said yeah and then I said uh
well that might be a little bit
difficult because then where we have so
many different time zones
and maybe I'll be actually the problem
so maybe I shouldn't maybe you should
replace me and she said no I'll wake
I wake up now I'll wake up for you early
in the morning
she was so ready for it and Marissa is
always awake for me anyway
but then I said no we should just rotate
that's sweet of you but we should just
rotate so one time the n a gang wakes up
early one time I wake up early and one
time Kelly wakes up early
what is his voice I'm trying to channel
my inner Bijou
[Music]
so um
recently I had a lot of streams where
the super chats were off oh but where am
I where am I continuing to read
whoever knows it gets a cookie
[Music]
um pre okay
pretty okay I'm reading pre UK
[Music]
okay you all have to share one cookie
hey
[Music]
I finished off this reveal yeah
yeah corn is okay
I love corn
[Music]
I'm glad you guys are happy with corn
bam
pack pack
um
[Music]
Metal Gear Solid prims if somebody told
me about Luna playing Battle Gear Solid
I'm like so what
she's what oh was it to make me notice
that we have perms for it now I thought
we may have already had perms for it no
I'm not gonna play it no
no
[Music]
I'm not interested pomu has to try to
sell it to me
if she can sell it to me okay but I'm
busy I'm playing I'm having like you
know we're gonna finish GTA soon then I
want to play ff16 and probably maybe if
the Baldur's Gate perms come sooner then
we might be playing it simultaneously
also I need to start playing some Hollow
cure next week but that's not gonna go
on for that long
um
yeah I just have you know
plenty of things to do also I just
realized I have to
record
I oh
well
maybe after the stream I can record a
something
[Music]
um
will they be feeling up to streaming on
Monday after the tournament
I am planning to I think it will be fine
because the plan is I stream Minecraft 6
a.m then I sleep sleep to sleep
and rest the rest of the day so that's
enough rest to stream on Monday
planning two streams on Monday
mm-hmm
don't you have prep for whole talk as
well yeah but this time whole talk is
late at night
um so I have kind of the whole day
Theory
but I'll prep some things after the
Stream
uh and then some more before the stream
but after this stream and some more
before the whole talk stream you know
[Music]
ah man
it's so much going on right now
I feel like I can hardly keep up
but at least I I gave myself
like plenty of leeway
between all these exciting streams to
rest up I really needed it uh
yes yeah so after the unite tournament I
was still even though I was so tired on
the stream at the end I still couldn't
sleep immediately because I was kind of
excited so I was tired and excited you
know
so I want some
reading reading comments and all that
and then
uh uh yeah it took me a bit to finally
sleep I slept so long
no I tried to sleep long
but then I had to wake up at a decent
time right was this is am I remembering
this correctly is this the same day
[Music]
I don't know anymore what day was which
day yesterday I went to the doctor and
then the night before that I you know I
couldn't sleep much so after the doctor
appointment
I I took a super long nap I was knocked
out
um
yeah the doctor's appointment was after
the tournament right like with some
hours in between but yeah
was it
whatever it's so so weird because I
sleep at weird times you know
I don't know where my days start and
where they end
um
[Music]
okay you guys have yeah you guys are
keeping better track than me
was the Pokemon United tournament
yesterday for me it feels like the day
before yesterday
because I stayed up
um
I was watching uh the world championship
I was watching a few of the first
matches and I watched the very last
match of day one
it seems like all European teams are out
but Peru
stayed in
the one that I just randomly mentioned
yeah
this is so funny I just I just joked
about them winning
vamos pero
ah unfortunately in the last match
that's what I caught when I woke up I
woke up and I checked before I went to
this watching the matches then I woke up
after like nine hours or so after I
didn't sleep in nine hours but I I
stopped watching for nine hours and then
I opened YouTube tiredly on in bed and I
see
I see it's still going on so I open it
up and it was the last match of the day
a European team versus
[Music]
uh
uh I think
an Indonesian team
[Music]
I think they were underneath
or mixing something up I think they were
Indian oh
was that before I went just I don't know
anymore but I just know Europe lost
um I I am confused
[Music]
I don't know anymore maybe it was in I
don't know it could be it could be
anyone
yeah team
no team peps was before I went to bed
whatever whatever whatever
not Europe wasn't so weak they did well
they did well
I was cheering for them
um but now I'm cheering for team Peru
ah
it was still ah hype and emotional damn
yeah and um
I might watch some of it today as well
because now that you know I just learned
how to play it it's really interesting
to watch them
watch them play it this big big
tournament
I think after I've watched the
tournament I won't be playing the game
well ever again and I will be watching
any unite content ever again but right
now I'm still riding the wave you know
although all of our team
uh we all agreed and wrote to the
management like hey this was actually a
really good fun collab game collabing
with members but also collabing with the
audience
uh so it would be nice if we keep the
perms
so
for now we're not keeping them but who
knows
hmm
[Music]
if we get perms then I'll play it again
but if not then no
just as like mostly a collab or audience
participation game but I kind of I don't
know I doubt it
I doubt it I don't know
nightclub yeah see we could do that for
example oh well
speaking of volatility I need to ask
Lena
oh
[Music]
okay
because like I was I'm trying I was
trying to find you know a time for
horota collab next week
and so I I asked everybody for their an
impossible dates
and Reina didn't answer for a while
so first it seemed like everybody has in
total only time on the 20th
the 17th
but then yeah
two days later
Dana said 17th might be difficult for
her because of the ID Independence Day
[Music]
yeah
so I'm still getting an update
from Arena if maybe she can do both and
we just
move it so that it's not
um at the same time as whatever whatever
they're doing on Independence Day
um
it's difficult it's so difficult to get
us together
man
but we're trying so I'm asking her for
an update about that
ah anyway anyway
okay so you guys said pre UK yeah
foreign
[Music]
you're all different bird species
yeah we might be all birds but different
species have different schedules is that
what you're saying
[Music]
hahaha
um
[Music]
hello Liza
streaming list
[Music]
uh post pretty okay
and then thumbnail
[Music]
here
pre UK
ketchup.atsu that's me that's me
[Music]
wait
oh
[Music]
I don't understand why does it not match
why is my head so much bigger my body is
matching kind of
why is my head so big huh
because I'm leaning forward a bit more
maybe that's why
what
that's weird
that's so weird what what
[Music]
hmm
oh well
let's stop playing around
big head realization
one of you is fake
yeah the lean
um
oh thank you I'll get to you eventually
[Music]
um
thanks for the pinky and some additional
ones
could not watch the outfit reveal as I
had to sleep early due to her earning
earning morning early morning lecture I
avoided Twitter the whole day to prevent
myself from being spoiled and I just
noticed the notifications of the stream
when you saw the phone well
but it's okay kiwama has always been
given Kiowa love hashtag young and
congrats on the new outfit looks
Magnificent the Exquisite divine
[Music]
did you not anticipate that I would put
up a stream with a thumbnail with this
outfit soon after hmm
could have anticipated that but well
well well eventually you are gonna see
it at some point anyway right
hmm
it it will happen eventually
so thank you Michael
I remember now it wasn't I it was uh
Brazil I was mixing up what I was
watching before I went to sleep it was
Europe versus Brazil okay that you know
what I just remembered that because I
saw senior MC said in the chat and I
remember that you're from Brazil
[Laughter]
I remembered yeah
[Music]
you helped me remember
come to Brazil now
oh is that like it must be a reflex from
you
you had to take that chance to invite me
right you had to I understand
it was inevitable how could you not ask
me to come to Brazil in this moment
it would have been a lost opportunity
yeah I've been there twice
um
[Music]
so thank you open the mic I am sorry I
spoiled you but you know
if you've anticipated it
um
thank you for the rainbow
wow wow
[Music]
he he sent 99.99 to avoid the two for
real what the [\h__\h]
why would you do that
[Music]
okay with the with the wordless rainbow
I haven't seen you around uh for a while
so I'm happy to see you even though it's
worthless and I should be scolding you
I'm happy to see you
thank you for the beautiful rainbow
thank you mwah
Anka
are you even ever in the chat
[Music]
I don't know if I ever saw you in the
chat just in super chats
[Music]
did anybody ever see him in the chat
maybe he's a lurka
my plan failed
why would you lurk why would you do that
why well well thank you Anka hope I'll
See You Again feel free to write in the
chat too I'd like to see you more often
[Music]
also sending a red super chat this
outfit is on fire oh thank you wow
I mean I I don't know I don't feel like
I'm on fire I feel like I'm pretty not
on fire right now
thanks for warning me though
false alarm false alarm don't call the
Fire Department
I am not on fire
um
ice cold
[Music]
it's an expression I know but
you should never joke to a phoenix about
them being on fire
because it could be true and the problem
is when that happens that means I'm
dying because I will go up in flames and
then ashes
so you can't joke to Phoenix about them
being on fire you know
it's insensitive
[Music]
that's not always on fire there's always
a fire in me but on fire is when I'm
dying
laughs
[Music]
ah
that reminded me of something
[Music]
no no no no it does it doesn't matter it
just reminded me of Bijou yesterday on
the phone
I was like oh my God I can't believe
it's Bijou and she's like oh my God I
can't believe it's and I it sounds like
she was about to say
a chicken or so but she said the boss of
kfp
and I was so proud I was so happy I said
okay you passed test
you passed the test
[Music]
I didn't expect that one
proper manners
good good girl
thank you
Jacob's monkey with the pinky thank you
hey Cara you know that chickens only
have one heart right and it's difficult
to get a new one so how could you steal
it from me who have that cool and
beautiful new outfit with amazing
designs now I'm gonna have to steal a
new one from another chicken but then
that one will have to steal a new one
from whenever and that one will have to
steal a new one from another and that
one will have to steal a new one from
another and you know how it goes on and
on and on
maybe you can steal one from not a
chicken but instead
but why are you even pouring out the
chickens only have one heart don't is
there anything that has two hearts
[Music]
maybe some weird ass animal or
what
is there what has a worm okay then still
a heart from a worm
it might be super tiny but
it's a Time Lord
are you making that up
octopus has three Heights what
they have plenty go steal the hearts
from the takodachis
and they might be bigger in size than
the warm as well
why the [\h__\h]
why do all octopus
okay and it even comes up octopus says
have free Hearts which is partly a
consequence of having blue blood
they're two peripheral Hearts pump blood
through the gills where it picks up
oxygen
oh octopuses have gills too
essential heart then circulates the
oxygenated blood to the rest of the body
to provide energy for organs and muscles
wait what what what does it mean
peripheral
sad again
[Music]
Oh I thought so but I couldn't believe
it it's on the outside
can we see it
wait
Oh you mean wait it's not outside but
like on the outside of
where I guess like you know like it's in
the inside but it's on the outside of
the inside I guess you know what I mean
maybe
not really on the outside right like on
the outside of the body
[Music]
yeah like the side okay on the side
okay okay there's a center one and
there's side ones
okay
oh thank you for the knowledge
um
yeah I see a picture it seems to be kind
of in their head right
they have their hearts close to their
brains which might be a good thing
[Music]
how many brains do they have hopefully
only one
how many brains it comes oh must have
been a follow-up question from other
people too if they have free Hearts how
many brains do they have
[Music]
that what
my prince
what do you mean nine brains where in
every tentacle or
[Music]
where are they
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
huh
I'm looking for a picture
[Music]
um
Central brain
oh oh
it seems like the central brain is where
the eyes are
and if I am reading this correctly then
the other ones are kind of one two three
four five six seven eight yeah they're
kind of like at the beginning of each
tentacle
like not the end the beginning that's
still connected to the body
that's what it looks like
so that makes
yeah each each leg can move like super
individually maybe because of the brain
that each one has
holy [\h__\h] we're getting like really
educated right now
[Music]
why do they have so much of everything
what the [\h__\h]
that's like so [\h__\h] overpowered
they're cheating
and they have nine brains but they still
can't like become the strongest
animal race
and overpower humans why are not
octopuses controlling the world or even
alone the ocean I would be fine if they
would just control the ocean on their
own
but they're not
why are they not controlling the ocean
why are they not building cities in the
ocean huh tell me that
you don't need so many brains as you can
see because they seem to be useless
anyway
tears who comes this topic
so I'm gonna watch that later if I find
it octopus brain
you mean the one that says the optimal
number of arms
what's the difference eight versus ten
this one I have actually not watched
that one yet
that one okay I'll watch it afterwards
haven't watched tears do in a while
they uploaded a new video three days ago
America's Secret top tier animal
all right
they have poor memory they can learn to
open a jar but they forget about it the
next day cute
lab would go like this Fun World facts
you think so
I wonder if she can teach me many random
facts
no recently I haven't been
watching tears of videos in a long long
time actually so I haven't been up to
date
um
[Music]
okay let's go back to supercharge how
about that interesting tangent doll
thank you jackets monkey
substitute of substitute thank you
I saw you in Pokemon unite a few times
so interesting happy belated birthday
and I think I mentioned how you guys
should address me right you can say
Empress or
or you're your finest
your time is
[Music]
are you here substitute
I don't see you but
um sorry I'm late to wish you a happy
birthday
ah you saw him
where are you
[Music]
my Royal finest
okay stop calling me finest
Bonito
I think you are yeah I'm busy busy too
busy man
I hope you had a lovely birthday though
congratulations
[Music]
thanks for the pinky finances are a bit
tight at the moment
and you send a pinky but I still wanted
to send a pinky away for 50 out of 10
I'll put the reveal a lot
and what an amazing animation too I knew
night Captain Wawa thank you yay
I'm glad I put the budget my budget my
money into that video
um
it made a good impression I think thank
you so much
yeah I'm glad it popped off on my
channel too when I uploaded it
separately
I checked I checked I checked the ads
income by the word ad revenue and of
course it's like well
Japanese is so [\h__\h]
but still it doesn't matter I'm just
happy that it's been watched a lot
[Music]
um
but I think it had better ad Revenue
than for example like the
um something something videos because
they're too short
they're too short to make any Revenue at
all
[Music]
um
yeah I am
[Music]
animators hate YouTube because the
algorithm hates them
yeah
because even a three minute video like
that is a lot of work
and then YouTube just doesn't really
give you back what you deserve I suppose
oh well
that's just you know ad Revenue tiny
share have to rely on super chatos yeah
mental Jetty donations
for the pinkies watching Dimensions
likely story all the Wawa killed kiwawa
Ivo Vendetta even though Alton Wawa cute
with short hair
was this statement before I told you or
afterwards because you have to you have
to follow the Lord that I tell you you
have no choice
if if she would have killed kiwaba she
wouldn't have been here yesterday
uh-huh
[Music]
yeah we just swapped places whenever
when we you know
[Music]
unfollow it's easy I just brought up a
new piece of lore for the first time in
a year or so yeah
improved spoon
bt4 thank you soon thank you
try sticky toffee pudding
[Music]
hey I didn't see any of those anywhere
where I went sorry thanks for the
recommendation though I urzilot thank
you space wonderful thank you Wiki tunes
and James Jackson thank you for the
recipe chat hello July 15 was my 41st
birthday but I kept encountering
non-monetized streams so I had to wear
to send this anyway would you please
sing the birthday song for me but make
it something silly about me being an
ultimate Carefree oh you're proud of it
you probably tell me your age I respect
that
you are still
uh younger than my mom by far so yes
maybe that makes you feel younger
wait let me find the
let me find it birthday
and birth
there it is
okay
I'll do my best
um
[Music]
happy birthday dance
happy birthday James Jackson happy
birthday to you
your skin is cracking
but you ain't lacking
you're still amazing
[Music]
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday James Jackson
[Music]
[Applause]
remember your key wow wow
you honestly can't say
thank you Dad oh yes
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday in your shoe happy
birthday in your pants too happy
birthday to you
[Music]
instead of sending
me all those red super chats
make sure to save some for your picture
that's coming up
they want me to roast you a little bit
right
be careful you need some money for your
pension
retirement is coming up
soon TM
no but
I liked my rhyme your skin is cracking
but you ain't lacking
the rest it's so hard to rhyme
spontaneously
you're welcome
you're welcome a rotisserie chicken
we get pension no it's like
no
[Music]
crispy roasted and toasted
yummy
well you know what happens to Old
chickens
you're becoming a soup
but
you know I'm not in the soup mood so I'm
gonna let you live for quite a while
longer I think
yeah congratulations
man 43
[Music]
[\h__\h] loud
I'm happy to have viewers from all ages
[Music]
or like a wide range
some we need you know we need some
adults in the chat to make sense of
things and give deep input about
about serious stuff
and to keep the the children in line
right
[Music]
oh
what do you mean like corn
it gives me wisdom and wisdom is sexy
wisdom and intelligence it's sexy
[Music]
what branch manager you mean
that's quite a big job to give to
yourself
ah you can be
the kfp
[Music]
we don't have a kfb dad yet I think
it would be the kfb dad
I haven't heard of a kfb dad yet
[Music]
ah yeah it can be yours take it take it
it's a cool name can't be dead
but you know that you'll automatically
be married whenever I give away the name
kfp mom to someone
[Music]
wait I'm the Carefree Mom right
wait a second where's the um
you know there can be several moms and
dads
laughs
[Music]
and then there can be many
cannot be the dad when he hasn't been
around for
two and a half years
[Music]
yeah he went to get milk I guess that's
very dad-like
[Music]
grumpy old grandpa that's more like it
huh
okay okay uh thank you anyway for the
big red subject
and congratulations I am almost one
month late oh my God
oh [\h__\h]
okay then we have a summer karaoke super
chats
sugiba
natsuno middle Missouri
mm-hmm
[Music]
yeah it was so sweet man 30 minutes home
this whole [\h__\h] it's like nothing
I had a few more songs like ready just
in case
but yeah I should have known
I could have calculated it on my own
I know
but yeah but that yeah yeah summertime
sadness sped up is actually quite fun
[Music]
um
this is seven times Summertime Sadness
this is Summertime Summertime sad names
[Music]
oh yeah we're gonna do Nightcore cuddle
okay
unfortunately there is a maximum of how
fast you can make songs in our
um Kara fun software
but it went pretty fast
[Music]
it was decent
and that was originally a really slow
song If you speed up the middle middle
mid fast song then it's gonna be crazy
[Music]
it's lost all its sadness
you can zoom and still be sad right
all right here we go
all these cat hairs Mamma Mia
BB Busters
blood donation baby why did you change
your name to oh are you like offering is
it like because there's a question mark
are you offering people to consider or
blood donation
because before you wear the poster boy
right
was this already at the end
[Music]
I think next karaoke will be when I
announce
the thing maybe
[Music]
that is I I
I don't know what else to do so I'll be
doing that
I'll bring out my
my scuffed home Freddy
[Music]
suit for that again
haven't worn it in a while
[Music]
yeah we're getting closer and closer I'm
actually getting a little bit stressed
and worried if everything will make it
in time
uh but yeah
[Music]
yeah cause I would want to make it
archived next time and you from Bell
could be archived I assume
[Music]
possibly
um
[Music]
yeah maybe I'll sing her live songs and
some anime songs that haven't sung yet
and you
no because uh it's originally in
Japanese and they covered a song before
and so on so yeah that should be fun
should be fine
[Music]
Young
sounds like a plan
[Music]
oh maybe I'll sing Elena song too yeah
okay yeah I'll be preparing for that
and so anyway
if you want to see more fun karaoke be
there I mean y'all all of you have to be
there
when that happens because it's important
more important than ever
[Music]
don't know at what time I'll be doing it
though
oh it's spanking time
um
[Music]
thank you for the right support
hi pencil I just wanted to let you know
that you look absolutely Stellar in your
swimsuit
[Music]
sorry my my brain was thinking about
some thing because I was singing
Summertime Sadness and I thought the
lyrics said something like I just wanted
you to know and then you start your
sentence with I just wanted to let you
know
my brain was doing things
[Music]
also this is my birthday today
marmalade in my show oh
[Music]
uh okay bye love you my Aussie marmalade
in your shoe okay okay you know what
Paul Gunter
[Music]
boots
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
um
peanut butter
[Music]
Nathan
Foods
he put his leg on top of the peanut
butter jelly sandwich oh no little
mistake
put it back put it back where it was
stick it on there with some some honey
and peanut butter
we don't want chicken foot sandwich
man rhyming is hard I can't rhyme
and get rhyme I tried at least not
honestly in German it might have been a
little bit easier for me I got some
Rhymes in the second verse
um but it's so difficult
it moved you really I don't know what
the [\h__\h] I'm trying to convey
I seemed quicker on my feet in English
really
yeah maybe the German threw me off
but anyway you got your birthday so
for being with kfp still
this is not your first birthday with us
I think
and so it was also kind of late
actually you went it was just only 11
days late or 12. that's not so bad
well I hope you had a lovely birthday I
hope you celebrated hope your healthy
and doing well but as long as you're
with kfp
I think you'll be doing wonderful it's
helping
with your health anybody's health is
improved
by 500 points
if you're with kfp
because of wholesomeness effects
and love
and fulfillment
um
[Music]
nose
fuzzy
I've got mokoko on my nose
the fuzzing one
I'm sniffing my cats too much
Honestly though I think it's also coming
from the microphone because there's many
hairs accumulated on the microphone
no no no no I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine
bow bow
[Music]
they say when you know City you have to
kiss a fool
any fools here oh nerissa is here it's
never said she's a fool for me right
[Music]
where do you see whisa there it is
you know I told this to nerissa but it's
just
so
weird normally until now
I would never
just like call someone up randomly on
this card for a voice call
and just chat with them for hours
I never did that before
I've definitely not regularly that's for
sure but I've been to chatting so much
with nerissa
usually like around
the end of my day
oh
even when I'm just calling to ask her
one thing we end up like talking a lot
and I have to forcefully end the
conversation
after one or two hours so that we can
get back to work
yeah I don't know I just feel so
comfortable talking with her and she
gets it you know
um
she's so sweet and supportive it's just
so nice to have someone who's
so supportive of me
it makes me feel
loved and appreciated
um
somebody who I know I can always talk to
in whole life English
without bothering them or anything no no
worries ever about that
huh
I think I found my nickname for you Wisa
Wisa
are you okay with that
but you gotta say it sweetly and softly
and gently
[Music]
nice
awesome
I watched the cow carrot compilation
of uh you know me being sad about not
having someone like you and then
eventually you joining and all that
maybe you guys watched it too mm-hmm
yeah anyway
s
[Music]
all right
okay next is
the post UK talk that changed me
made me angry
although in this jatsu I talked pretty
much only about the whole
um Lord of the Rings thing
so
it was actually a happy
conversation
yeah if you guys are curious about the
Lord of the Rings musical watch the
Vaude of this stream is
foreign
[Music]
wobbly water
probably water
[Music]
yeah the guy not giving me credit for
copying my
my order in the airplane
why is there so many rents widgets what
the [\h__\h] how come thank you for the rest
of the chat I can finally send this
ponytail Warrior
I didn't think I'd live to see this day
of you getting a proper Warrior outfit
and ponytaily I love this outfit so much
I feel like they're one with this outfit
can't wait to see more of it during
streams yeah you're welcome and you see
I made many people happy about the with
the outfit
I know some of you guys wanted to see a
more Warrior side of me and there you go
there it is
wow
another one checked off the the list
[Music]
mm-hmm thank you guys thank you and I'm
glad you like it so much thank you for
the big support and the generosity it's
very much appreciated
and then we have level
uh We've also a recipe Chad health and
child is my first Uncle spot oh really
it was my 18th birthday on the 26th I
finally become an adult I was also sick
recently so I've been quite behind on
the vods but I'll catch up soon oh have
you caught up yet love you both hope
you're feeling better now
I feel bad if I don't give you a
birthday song too especially because 18
is pretty big at least in my country
because with 18 year your
um adult officially in Austria
but I can't think of words
um
uh
wait
uh okay can I just
[Music]
quickly make some notes
um
[Music]
ah
okay
um I'm cooking I'm cooking
um
[Music]
was there free verses it was free right
or was there two
is it true or free always
I think it was free and two courses
yeah okay
um
[Music]
uh uh wait uh
uh
[Music]
is from the Philippines right
legal age in Philippines
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
child is a person under the age of 18.
okay okay
[Music]
I'm getting weird results
um
uh what was I supposed to type
uh
uh what
I don't understand
what
[Music]
but drinking age
Philippines
[Music]
18. okay so it's the same okay
um uh okay no it's not that's fine uh
and that's fine
um
uh uh
I can't think of anything
so now now I'm forcing myself
[Music]
um
what else what else could you do after
you're 18
besides drinking
maybe ah maybe in take out a loan
vote vote okay
uh
now
[Music]
okay whatever
happy birthday
[Music]
to you
[Applause]
oh my God it's too loud oh no
you are now 18
no longer a small team
we should go drinking
hey happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday
to you
now when you go boating
I hope you're devoting
yourself to me there's only me for you
never been to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
happy birthday to you
now that you are 18
life be really starting
but when you get older don't forget
about KFC
[Music]
we'll be switching man
congratulations
yeah good luck
good luck being 18.
[Music]
18 good times man good times
but honestly 18 year old you're still a
baby
let's be real
[Music]
this little baby I don't think you can
really adult until you're 20 or so
you you feel adult when you're 18 you
think oh I got this I'm so mature
but in hindsight when you're like older
than that
and you look back can you really say
that you were very mature as you were
waiting
um
yeah
and I mean 18 even says teen in the
world oh my God
you're not how can anyone say you're an
adult before 20 when it's in the word
that you're a teen
18 19.
[Music]
you're still a team
the H says it so clearly how can we have
been deceived by the legal system
how can we trust anyone who's under 20.
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
you guys agree I'm happy
I'm making so much sense it's almost as
if like I am so agreeable and genius
then I should be a cult leader
[Music]
ideal for a cult leader don't you think
you know I was watching this you know
Netflix released the series
uh narrated by Peter Dinklage for some
reason I don't know why that was
necessary to have it narrated by him uh
but there's a cult uh series on Netflix
that just explains like it's a
documentation that finally makes it
makes fun of it and like it's it's
ironically telling you how you can
become a great cult leader oh nerissa
aren't you already no no no no no no
but we got good potential to go there
but yeah there's um
there's they they tell you what you need
to do to become a cult leader by showing
you all these like famous Cults and I've
already known about a lot of them
because I already watched like
documentations about a lot of them and
holy [\h__\h] is [\h__\h] terrifying what
these Cults do but there was one that
[Music]
no wait was that the one
that was just like stupid and just
there was one that was like led by some
guy who I think just wanted to be famous
um like he he was like a model or so he
was like buff and he had like I think
Botox in his lips and all over his face
um
was an American cult and
um so the people who would join us
called only were allowed to be pretty
people and you had to have a certain
hairstyle uh only only specific
hairstyles and there was no body hair
allowed all men had to shave their body
hair because it wasn't attractive to be
having like body hair on your chest
because that's his own aesthetic so you
had to follow his aesthetic
yeah and and and you just wanna he
wanted you to follow his aesthetic with
his lifestyle and everything so they
were doing like I don't know yoga [\h__\h]
and and just you know becoming the
perfect human being in his idea
yeah yeah yeah smooth as a candle he
looked like a wannabe candle
mm-hmm
it was interesting the ballet yes
can't
believe a piece
and he made them build a theater for it
from scratch
and then they performed it only once
after months and months of practice and
building this theater when you
and they only performed the two other
cult members this one time they never
performed it for the real people but he
was so serious about it because he loved
ballet beforehand but I guess he never
got like to be a part of big
um uh pieces like never never famous
performer whatever
yeah rejected ballet dancer
who trained his cult to become politics
[Music]
can you believe
that it's just this one cult stands out
so much compared to the other cults
because this one is just for his
personal I mean okay I guess they all
are kind of for personal satisfaction
but but his one is just like about being
pretty
yeah
with the ballet thing wasn't from the
beginning it was like Midway through so
as a cult member you must we must
imagine like you're really committed to
this and suddenly your boss is asking
you to do ballet for real for real
and he gets like really so serious about
it gives you a [\h__\h] tutu to wear
[Music]
freaking hilarious man
ridiculous though hair removal belay
cult
oh man I mean I have no problem with
ballet but it just sounds so
it's like he's just trying to live out
all his dreams
hmm
[Music]
yeah
but going this far to live out your
dreams well
would you guys be open to
making a chicken belay
theater with me
you can't say no
you can't say no to play with me can you
not imagine cute chickens in tutus like
with your with your little legs
prancing around that honestly though the
image of it would be adorable don't you
agree dakuma is currently drawing a
chicken in ballet outfit I can see it I
can sense it
[Music]
chickens coordinated ballet
you did it before I think I
I that's why I can imagine it so easily
because I saw it before
oh
instead of the Black Swan it's the the
black chickens
do we need to pluck our feathers no no
your feathers are your charm
black rooster
that's so cute
is so cute oh my God
Chicken Lake
okay
chicken leg
oh
[Applause]
we gotta bring all of your parents to
watch it
[Music]
I feel I can now relate to the guy
but for me it's not for my own
satisfaction there's more like because I
think it would be super cute to see you
guys dancing around
that's a bit different I feel like we
have different aspirations me and that
guy
[Music]
ah
still myself no no no no no no
[Music]
anyway thank you
soon and Flappy boy thank you for free
red super chats what the [\h__\h]
welcome back to your home base Kiara the
past month of July must have been must
have really drained you is with all its
travels and appointments I really hope
that you can take it a bit easier after
this weekend
anyway in your absence I seem to have
been promoted to many items really
surprised me because despite all the
unforgettable memories it doesn't feel
like I've been here around for a whole
year
what really for me it feels like you've
been around longer than a year
it's been an Incredible Journey For Me
learning to love something unironically
even when I used to mistakenly find it
unbearably cringe you mean they took
this
you found YouTubers cringe first and you
you you didn't just immediately give up
on it but instead you gave it a chance
and fell in love with it
is that what you're saying
that's actually
oh
wow because I think most people would
just like ignore it
hmm
and move on and just look at something
else
[Music]
here I don't see an answer
it's not cringed
she is
[Music]
you know
maybe I'll get an answer another time
[Music]
uh continues essentially turning from a
huge toxic piece of [\h__\h] to just a
little piece of [\h__\h] a little [\h__\h] right
and it's all thanks to your inspiring
influence already I'm determined to rise
again uh as a phoenix and then whatever
comes after that yeah we don't know yet
but wow yeah I think that's a that's a
great change and it just shows how you
may be calling yourself a huge toxic
piece of [\h__\h] but the fact that you even
gave it a chance I think tells tells
that you're a great person who is
open-minded
hmm
I don't know I don't really understand
like how that switch turned for you like
why would you
if you really didn't like it then why
why what made you actually watch it did
somebody Force you that somebody like
put a rope around you on a chair and
then
force you to watch
my streams
you have to watch this and you really
like it
[Music]
water boarding water boarding
you know
whatever it is I'm glad it happened I'm
glad you stayed
for the long run
and I'll see you every day in the future
as well hopefully
[Music]
you have made a commitment
and you must commit
yeah
thank you Flappy boy thank you for
telling me your story too it's really
interesting to hear
some of your guys's stories
first I thought it looks interesting not
for me though then huh I'm seeing the
appeal though I don't have the time for
it and it all spiraled from there whoa
[Music]
cute I'm glad you stayed as well
welcome pack how come I've never heard
this before
what do we come month even yet I'm still
taking a book oh over the sheer Majesty
of key out there so beautiful and just
like you said it's a perfect fit for
games like Tales of Elder Scrolls
battles gate for you Fable Dragon's
Dogma Dragon Age Blue protocol Final
Fantasy Age of Empires Mass Effect
Crusader Kings Fire Emblem Dragon Quest
and 20 others yeah so it works for all
of this it's even got perfect potential
with other members like Luna and Noah
[Music]
I think concept wise yes but style wise
maybe not so much
we do not at least
I adore Ki alter so much and may never
stop Raven about it
he dropped his whole wish list is that
your wish list
wow enough no never enough never
thank you soon for your sweet words and
yeah I think I may not be playing all of
those games in the future but
some of them for sure so I'm excited to
use my outfit for all of them
something very very matching
to immerse ourselves even further into
the atmosphere yeah
[Music]
hi
I was up to all Ian
but then I saw the magic and creativity
from all the streams
it really took my time and I appreciate
the attention took my time because I
love where I am
so much
thank you
I appreciate that you're here
[Music]
glad you're here all of you
are you gonna update your MC skin to
look like this outfit
yeah a moon I don't really care about
the Minecraft skin so much because most
of the time you don't see it anyway
because you play first person anyway all
the time
if someone makes it I'll put it on
[Music]
okay
thanks for the pinky High controls
payday girl hope that London was not too
much of a pain for you
well well you heard the stories
uh yeah
it's not all completely the fault of
London right
blame
London completely for
[Music]
well I saw some pictures today from an
acquaintance
who was in Brighton I think
and those pictures looked amazing
Brighton was beautiful
next time I go
hopefully not to London
but I have to go
at least
one more time probably
[Music]
strange how you got sick before going
there and better once you left
you think it's connected
[Music]
my body was trying to tell me to stay
home
wow wow nah it was okay you know I still
had fun even though there was weird
stuff going on I still had fun
Chinese
for the pinky the travesty that he
didn't thank you for making the ultimate
meal plan
is on par with the people who didn't
thank you for overseeing the emergency
exit that one time
you get it Maple Leaf
thank you
for understanding
how much
these people
just
ignore
the blessing I am bestowing upon them
despite my existence and my presence
ignorant
peasants
[Music]
hahaha
what do you mean I I it's there's alter
Wawa and real Wawa why don't you
understand
you like the movement of my ponytail
thank you it moves nicely
I'm hungry guys
I'm hungry
very hungry
ah
[Music]
offering sacrifice
I have food that I cooked yesterday that
I would eat but
it might be too early for dinner
if I want to keep the same pattern I'm
honestly I don't know but but the fact
is the fact is
that even if
would go to sleep early today in order
to go to sleep early tomorrow I can't
really because whole Talk starts at 10
pm 10 pm my time and then
let's say it takes two hours or ends at
midnight
and even if Minecraft starts at 6am I
probably have to be there at least half
an hour early 5 30.
so the only I can't get a full sleep I I
could take a nap only so
[Music]
so
I'll just continue my current pattern
and fix it after Minecraft
um
foreign
[Music]
I still have all those energy drinks so
I'm quite well prepared more oh
storm ice Kitty Duncan thank you well
I'll see you at the convention in
Toronto then to run out to run towel
Toronto
spanking hand thank you for the rest of
the chat time to build a new Mountain of
bricks
well why Oh you mean the red bricks
welcome back thank you I bet the kid is
an ultra clingy now
I don't think so I don't I think they're
like kind of the same as usual
[Music]
like not much more clingy than usual but
but strongly
chunky wonky has been so
[Music]
so cute because I put
um I put a little box like um an Ikea
box that's not really um
sturdy box it's like a fabric box
that you can
flatten if you want to I put it next to
my pillow because she likes to sleep in
boxes so I thought why not
there was a time where I had a little
cardboard box next to my pillow for a
whole year
uh and she would always sleep in there
it was her favorite spot she was so
happy in there
yeah but no this box isn't so uh small
it's pretty big she's she's got quite
some space in there but she loves it so
sometimes for example after dinner
um when I leave the living room and I
walk over to my bedroom she goes like
you know she makes these these um dove
sounds
and
then she runs over like she sees him
walking towards the bedroom
and then she she makes the dub sounds
and she runs past me really excitedly
and then she jumps like ah she jumps
really like so fast and excitedly on top
of my bed right into the box and then
she immediately flops down and lies down
she's so excited to you know lay down
with me
[\h__\h] you
cute I need to record it sometime
this movie on the other hand is just
being a little [\h__\h]
[Music]
yeah cat thrilling is the cutest thing
so cute
can't I can't handle it
[Music]
honestly I might sleep early today
earlier than to last night
at least
I'm kind of already tired
but still like realistically I'm only
getting a nap in between
whole talk in Minecraft
[Music]
yeah that's fine though
uh so thank you spending time
[Music]
np153 garlics thank you for one two
three super chats
[Music]
ah
thank you my habit's done question thank
you every another call thanks for the
pinky but wouldn't it be worth it to see
the prettiest lady in the world
wait what are we talking about Abby
[Music]
what are we talking about
maybe you need to explain this one to me
so the membership gift to ah you always
gift when I sneeze
okay
[Music]
you talking about me what did I say
though
[Music]
it's been two weeks please explain
Abby are you here
baby
[Music]
he means me let's just say he means me
thank you
oh was it when I was I maybe saying that
it's not worth it to go to Austria or
something like that I don't know ah
it wouldn't be worth it going to to what
to what
the
Lord of the Rings how could I say that I
think it's a
again
what do you mean with the prettiest lady
in the world dude you you meant me right
why would I be there again I don't
understand it anymore but you also are
not sure anymore are you
me
you are too sweet
you are so Charming
the Riz
[Music]
thank you so much
and last but not least thank you a
little Moonlight for the pink Super Chat
I miss you I miss you too
okay
[Music]
we still have to read some chat from the
Chit Chat Story Time stream and that's a
bit much but then Pizza Tower doesn't
have so much GTA no GTA no fauna collab
a little bit GTA no and tournament also
not so much so in total I think it's not
that much I will I will leave now
[Music]
I'll go finish up some preparations
and eat
[Music]
um
it would have been worth going all the
way over there to see you is what I
meant yeah unfortunately I won't be
going to watch it again
but still you should still check it out
if you can
it's what a great streamer while you did
great practicing today the Pokemon
tournament was fun thank you thank you
thank you so much I hope I can get some
stuff done I'm feeling
not very motivated
but I'll I might eat first and
yeah
maybe I'll drink Coca-Cola so that I
don't take a nap now hopefully
hopefully cannot go on a call with
narissa today we saw because I'll be
unproductive if I call Wisa
[Music]
you wanna watch rings of power after
this why
[Music]
but go do it hell yeah
lava needs to sleep yeah nawab needs to
work too mama needs to prepare holotalk
wait let me can I take a look at my
schedule
because I am
I've been
the good thing is this time I don't
really need to translate things
still translate the questions at least
so if some Japanese people are watching
they can at least have a rough idea of
what we're talking about I guess oh yeah
I have all day
I have all day before hola talk to do
everything that I want to do so
quarter top prep
I could sleep early and just do
everything tomorrow
record
songs
yeah I could do that
[Music]
and then some
maybe some MC practice even
yeah I gotta I gotta work on my schedule
sleep schedule for next week
yeah
next week
next week next week
next week I want to play
holocure like one twice at least
I want to do a Korean study stream
because I'm forgetting things already
that'll be like early in the day
[Music]
I'll try my best to stream a lot next
week we're doing also I mean it might be
actually there there might be three days
where I stream twice in a day
because I gotta do a member stream too
right
members foreign
there might not be a day off
unless I unless I put it on the day
where I already have a stream
I could do that too
but let me put this here in here
I want to play that ad game next week
have you seen somebody made an ad game
a game with a funny title with all the
ad games
some Hollow members have been playing it
I want to play that one
and
um well my plan is Saturday GTA
[Music]
and Sunday
GTA as well unless we finish it for some
reason on the day before
then I would play ff16
started but I'm guessing we still need
two streams especially because last GTA
stream was so short
we didn't
get very far
yeah
okay then it's GTA weekend
again
now I have to go to an idle meeting
everything's working fine yeah I I
opened it and it was just magically
working which I think
it's just you know because time passed
and I restarted the PC but I even
restarted it during that stream many
times right but it's just like I don't
know things reset itself I guess
I restarted it several times though
during the Stream
[Music]
stupid but I also fumbled a little bit
with some audio things because I finally
realized one thing do you guys remember
me ever complaining about my audio being
weird like when I go to audio settings
and then an output
in output it would always
uh default to my Elgato
even when I change it it will always
automatically go back to the Elgato and
when I would go to
um
like ah all
um in German it's audio get rid of
you know the right right under the audio
output there should be um
like a output devices
settings where you can deactivate them
and I did that with the Elgato and it
still didn't work you know it still
would always go back to the Elgato there
which both sets have it still worked but
sometimes I felt like maybe that's uh
one thing that causes problems when I
don't get audio in the right
[Music]
um
like outputs you know not the correct
routing and then yesterday I finally
found
where that came from what what was
holding it back from
you know me switching it out
I finally found it and now now I think
that might have fixed my GTA problem
um
yeah it's weird that it doesn't just
work when I
like
deactivated in the audio output devices
settings
I had to go elsewhere to do that
basically
yeah because Elgato when you have this
Elgato it has the the capture software
and it has the audio software
like an audio a sound capture
and you don't really have to use this
um but I only open up this little
software when I hear audio crackling and
then I just switch between there's like
a choice between
some
outputs or or I don't know what this
even is but there's some choices some
icons that you could push and then it
fixes the crackling usually and there
hidden somewhere I found
whoa I just changed something and then
it disappeared uh yeah I just found
a setting
that forced this uh this Elgato output
onto me and I just clicked something
that made the bgm disappear for you guys
it's okay I'm ending it anyway but yeah
uh Gala was in control yeah behind the
scenes pulling all the strings
unbelievable it was manipulating me all
this time it took me years to find this
yeah nothing else to fix now for now
everything
more or less yeah
and that cat always the cats
um
the buzzing the buzzing only really you
guys only complain about it when I don't
have bgm on when you don't hear anything
else
so it's really only an issue when
there's nothing else
Audible
hmm so it's not that important
anyway uh I will leave you guys
tomorrow hold a talk and
I've been cooking to make this
um different from the usual whole talk
so
you know I still add I will still ask
some questions and this and that but
um yeah
please look forward to it I I am
honestly
also a little bit worried about
interviewing five people at the same
time but we'll figure it out
we'll figure it out I will probably you
know ask when I ask a question I will
ask someone specific to answer it and
then ask another one specific person to
answer it to not have everyone like
you know
yeah I wanna replace the speed quiz
because it's not gonna work like that
I think I'll replace it
with something I'm still cooking on that
one
also because a lot of actually a lot of
the speed quiz questions are very Japan
specific like the restaurant question
and the convenience store question
hmm
and the walk one station
or take the train or the taxi or so is
also kind of like big city specific
and I just assume all Japanese members
live in the big city but I don't know
about these girls so I don't know if
it's really if you could apply this to
America because I feel like if you don't
live in a big city then walking one
station could mean you're walking for an
hour or more
hmm
please keep the pants a question
I'll see what I can do
but you already know some of the answers
don't you
[Music]
um
so yeah
foreign
[Music]
taking up a lot of time
it already takes up a lot of time to
translate for one person so
yeah
yeah yeah
okay then uh and in German we saying
guys
it was fun practicing in Minecraft
we'll see how it goes in the honban
um
[Music]
thank you
thanks for watching
raid again oh my God
oh my God
so nice
[Music]
my cool hands are so nice what the [\h__\h]
like all of them braided me at this
point I think
it's like normally uh besides
besides fuomoku I probably won't be
getting raids in the future from them
because they still that was like Pokemon
unite was an exception because I was
streaming at the weirdest time ever
um
but
still I appreciate them doing it when
it's possible
um
so nice of them
[Music]
morning
so far I feel like they rated me every
time
every time when I when I was streaming
or had a stream up
haven't they rated me each time
What Angels
[Music]
so sweet sweet doubles
I will return the favor when I see them
streaming when I end my stream yeah
I told them I want to return the favor
so turn your rating on girls
so they turned it on
um
[Music]
yeah hypochat still doesn't show me
raids either I only noticed it when you
guys tell me
anyway bye bye
[Music]