[Music]
hello everybody this is takanasi Kiara
from Whole Life English and I'm here to
announce that I have been chosen as an
ambassador for advice
yay yay I'm very honored to be in such a
position and I hope that with me and the
other ambassadors power together we can
share by slides all over the world and
we can spread the love and interest for
it to get more and more people to play
it yeah with us here I heard that a
whole life cards are pretty powerful and
oh my cards are specially
so yeah we guys are gonna use them to
play with them and I also want to
practice a lot to get really good if
possible yeah so I'm gonna do my best
let's celebrate the 15 year anniversary
of restaurants together and let's Vice
foreign
[Music]