[Music]
Hmm
Hey
[Music]
Ah, it's ben.
Hmm,
me,
hmm,
me
a hahaha 4
[Music]
Everyone, I bet you're
going to buy a darter, oh
Abakku Malhon!
[Music]
meiko Isoba
naaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaally, I
did it really
well  I wonder if it
was Iko?
[Music]
Nadaze Musical Instrument Shop
ni Come on,
Kurozuka Wool
Hmmm, seriously
[Applause]
Ha ha ha yeah yeah
dme
[Music]
Bach
Day cake is good
Tax accounting tea  k 3 Fund Kitty chikikikikikiki daddy who goes
oh a It's amazing that Japan
mainly wants to abolish , but first I want to explain this room.
There are also people who donate English, so I'm Miss Meister and I'm a civilized 10. There are
two of them, even the media kings are Zaianz mappy. This guy has a wig mountain mother. He's got an
amplifier, and Vienna is also 4
t the.  quiz joint-bai goods
thunder pearl
pink obi day cheap super
papal shotzume bread a naratae wo playzu
t you na na i ha
Today I'm going to talk about that girl's room, which I'm going to talk about later in the series, and book number 7. Well, I think it'll be exciting if you know about it, but this
room bar, that fairy tale
in German, I'm teaching you a fairy tale, which is a
series that I've only done once so far, is
Heiwa.
Um, there's a
new work by Totita,
but this boron is on the mountain. It's
Christmas Eve right now,
so I think it would be nice if I could spend it here. Nao, I'm actually
playing the role of Maa's older sister, Anna,
for the sake of um.
My turn sounds like a fairy tale, but my series was made in a playful way,
but in reality, there wasn't a Christmas tree, but
Chris added one for that purpose. But I'm a little worried.
Why is Subaru-senpai's expression afterward?  I'm a little worried
too Saa d Dawn Akana Win
Meal Apa Paan ana Tokoro Tsuba
Momonatama Ho Ran Mura Pingnu One's Own
4 ab to do Ah
Wow,
what is this?
What is this? I
looked at Twig Din's Twitter, and the
reception pattern is
like iron mesh and other goods. It's
professional specification production 2.
[Music]
Previous  Papa Achisu Sa is a little
rabbit rabbit rabbit rabbit on the left side of the rabbit rabbit.  Don't
worry about hitting, are you okay? The Tower of Koa
is the deputy general manager. The
range of defense is going to be shortened.
Choo, ah, the defense is good. Powder butter, it's
better to hide it.
PM
Is it okay?
[Music]
What,
Mebi Big Bach,
what should I do?  I don't know what to do, but today I passed the marshmallow before the abolition of the Neako.
But
thank you to everyone who sent me the Maruo Neako.
If you'd rather have a delicious papa from the Doncobus,
please
talk to me about that.Bach
a
First, Santa Claus also appeared a little while ago, but everyone, send the aroma of Christmas goods to the heavens.  I
did it.
Oh good Lian
fence with my japanese dusan bergersen
ipm in japan by pa 6 up pony 4
And everyone here,
there are some things that are very easy to understand just by typing.  What does it
mean to be here?
[Music]
Um,
Do you understand?
[Music]
Bach, it's okay, I'm with you. I'm
going to make myself all alone,
everyone who doesn't have a girlfriend or boyfriend.
Congratulations to all of you who haven't had a chance to play.Today
you'll all be spending a lot of time with me.Ahaha, I'm so
lonely.Ah, I
can't buy hair, and I'm agitating for color blue.
Yeah, I'm a little bit excited, so I hit the spot
reapers reba me to do well aaaa day ic early
pointer to do a piaa
andrade team bom se e aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Well, that's what it is, wait, there's nothing to be sad about.  [
Music]
alloy
ae 4 e 4 haha ​​If you're with Chiara, that's one, two, two, ah
, there's something I want you to remember.
First of all, Christmas
wasn't originally meant to be like this, Dad.
It's a day to spend time together, so I guess we
don't have to worry about waking you up here or there, right? Someone?  In 2012, I
guess he decided on his own that it was the day to have a Christmas bar date in Japan, but
the first place was Hodo's keys, which he had the right to do.Why
did he decide to do something like that?
why different  Why
does everyone have to agree with that person? That's why
I want to say one thing.
Well,
I'm also close to the real one, but it's still
the case right now.Everyone feels like they're getting a little closer to each other.We're all the
same, hey.Today, I'll
spend about an hour answering that question.  I would like to go to
Other than that, I felt a little sleepy, right? Dad.
I was a bit stupid and put on too much of that broadcast for Christmas.
Usakki.
Before I put out the newspapers for the children's goods, I prepared them for the Sims.  After that, I
prepared this love,
but I asked Bose, and the fairy tale video of the two and that girl was also recorded on that recording station, and I was
making Aaaaaan's office work 9, but I was still in care, so I haven't finished it yet.
Yeah, I'm a bit busy,
so I guess I can't help it. There's that kid in the egg-laying car, too. I'm
going to go somewhere with a borrowed girl in February, but I
just can't stand it anymore.  Tou: I'll be
leaving Japan once February is over,
so I'm thinking that I'd like to see Atsuko a little more soon,
but it's a little tough because of some things.  It's
been a year and I've only had one good trip, you idiot.I
know your powers are a bit weak, but 22 Japan is asking you to go on a trip.Well,
which one?  I don't think so.
But it's okay. I try to avoid places with lots of people,
but it's been a little over 8 years since the new year started. I
went to the Kansai area with my 200 racket for those three days and watched that broadcast.  I don't think so
But it's
been a long
time since I've been to Kansai, so it's not my first time. It's been a long time since I've been to Kansai. I'm going to show off your sensibilities in sumo. I'm going to
do this.
[Music] Do you
think it's cool
? Do your best. Kansai dialect n appears in the camber.
Someone told me that it does happen sometimes,
but not as often as in the past, and I used to live in Kansai.
Once upon a time, not this year, not long ago, I
knew that something like that would happen in the Kansai region.  I
learned a lot of Kansai dialect, so I didn't ask to learn it,
but there are a lot of good Kansai pitches.If you
were involved in that, you would
have memorized Kansai dialect.After that, everyone was complaining, but you're the one who doesn't speak Kansai dialect.  I do
n't know if it's a big deal or not,
but I just answered, ``Enkido.'' It was strange, but eventually I calmed down a lot and went back to normal,
but even now, I sometimes get told that I don't speak the Kansai dialect.
Baby, it
's a little super, but the baby has only been sent to Subari so far, Kyoto,
but the
baby's first word is Kyoto, oh, it's
not yet, Kyoto.
There's a word that's about the size of a Sunday tying chap.Dah,
canter,
hard version,
sherbet, oh yeah.You
know, in the character broadcasts, that baby
comes in front of me every time.It's a good day to live with the rest of the secret
bath left over.  The
numbers are decreasing.I
wonder why they're disappearing.Or
rather, it's not the first time I've started.It's been 22 years.But I don't want to get divorced for an hour.Why did they
decide to do it for an hour?  I
thought we didn't have much to talk about, so I
rang out the trumpet, but there
it was, and I was at Subaru, and I was like,
oh, what the heck,
but hey, I'm so happy that there are so many people at the Takano store in Japan right now.  I
thought she was gone
. I didn't see the bottom view of Chiara at the beginning. She
was the only owner. It was broadcast to a group at that time.
Thank you.
[Music]
Thank you.  At
that time  bunny on was eating in the grass, but somehow I just slapped her and opened her mouth.Since
then, I've been spending more and more time talking to you, so I've
cut down on my Japanese speaking.
But now, because of that, Japanese people do
n't show up as much for Pat.They
seem to be hiding and watching, but chatlanders don't show up that often.
Color: I don't really speak Japanese anymore,
but now that I
'm watching 5, I'm going to shut up, watch it, and leave a comment. People
will buy it for
me. That's the Japanese language that I've said to you so many times.  I
want you to write about it because you stand out.There's a high chance that you'll be picked up because you stand out.Ah, I
'm commenting on the ball, so I wonder if everyone is like that.Sometimes I try my best to comment in English.
If that's the case, I might not have realized that I
was Japanese. I might not have realized that I was Japanese. Let's go out.
Well, there were both at the station.
Thank you, everyone.  Japanese-only high sumo I was
just worried that Japanese people wouldn't come anymore
Thank you for being awake
Wear wear Bye bye Ibo star in Awakenoyama Crampons are convenient
Abe Pyon Kidney Rally is the only Aggar flashing
Hey, marshmallows are good, and I chose a lot of them.By
the way, the questions I didn't select at Marco in Nakamaka City were between the questions about Mashmaru, but I always
tried to type something with rice, but this one doesn't appear on this screen
right now.  It
said that I didn't want to leave a comment anymore, but
what should I do about this area? It said that I don't know what to do about it,
but I don't know what to do. Live Chat Top
Chat
There are two types of comments, right? And then there's
YouTube. I don't buy it, I put a filter on it, I
reply to comments, etc. Why are the comments
deleted? I don't think they are deleted, or rather, they're not deleted.
Today's tax is about
whether or not it's withstanding. Why isn't it
displayed
and it doesn't say that it's been put into it?
But even so, I don't understand why it's a compliment. I don't know why it's like that.
Hmm, I'm sorry for writing the same comment as everyone else,
but I'm sorry for the inconvenience, but I was just saying that people in English speaking countries
sometimes have this same problem.  Something new
[Music]
Ah,
there were people who said that they were cured by creating a second account, but
if you take a mock test, try it. That's
lame again.
Hey youtube Wow.  If you
could find out more about how it works, I'm
sorry.
[Music]
Well, for now, I guess it's
Tatsuya who's just starting out. My
carp got clogged up, so I went to
Jump and told Zack to my sister.  Sister, is
this or that?
Hey there,
ok,
oh
star r.
I wonder if I can respond to a drink.
Wouldn't it be fun to have Usa Ienaga live in a shared house for the rest of my life? Who would want to live in the same room? That's
interesting. Hey, hey, it's a bit. Well,
that's it.
[Music] I'll
give you money.  I was thinking a little bit about how it would
be to have a 3D in my house.If we all have to come to Japan, we'll have to go south of the station.I'm in Japan right now, but
if I can do a 3D, I'll probably have my own by then.  I'm going back to my country
That's why I have to go to Japan for that purpose.Ah,
but if I stay at a normal hotel or something, I
can't stream from the hotel.The reason is that the internet at the hotel is terrible, and it's
not very stable.Day
That computer.  You don't even have a proper computer,
so there's no way you can come to Japan for a day and buy something right away without wondering how you're going to do it,
because it usually takes 20 hours and 13 hours, like a flight.  It
depends on where you're coming from and if it's good, but I
don't usually think about it because I'm not the staff member, but I thought about it a little bit.
So, for example, I
asked them to stay in Japan for a few days.
I mean, I think it would be good to do as many 3D houses as possible, but
not just for the sake of closure.And in between, there's also regular streaming.In
order to be able to do it, I'd like to
do a monthly apartment or something like that for five months.
I've been thinking deeply about whether I should be able to borrow a computer for everyone and do that.
I guess the manners are perfect, but there's also the thing called privacy.Those colored rooms
may be separate, but it would be nice if we could live in the same room.  I
kind of wish we could live in the same house.
Well, there's nothing left to do. It's Paris, after all.
Carragher has
told me that I can stay at his 5-note home when I return to Japan.
That's what he said.  a That
's why I don't live in that house, I move on with my soul.
Even if I'm sorry, Anu is the
princess who can stay at Kari-chan's house.
I'm the only one who is treated as something special.
So, well, I want to live in the same house as Hikari-chan.
Hmm, you're a Yankee right from the start. I think it's a little
difficult to spot. Could you
please tell me the schedule for Risa's Prism? Hi, hey, it's already today,
Mr. Bachul. I'm
spending it as one day.  I stipulated last year.I
went to the convenience store and got the rice for that breakfast,
so I came back here.It was the hanger over
there.It was the same as the hanger over there.The
rice I had was that same cutlet bowl.
What the hell is that? It's
Christmas.
It's not a fancy meal, it's just too ordinary. I have
n't received any presents from anyone today, so I don't really need them. Ah,
sister, I have
n't met anyone yet.  Not Alone
[Music]
Aichi Chip Norm Rice Powder Water Chure Face with Chris O Line
Juice Isa
Spanish Girls Follow Scrotum Monty Aimed Mr. Ford
Wiener Blanket Manufacturer Minsu and Emirin's right-hand man won a prize,
no, I
don't wear those Christmas decorations or anything anymore.Haha,
but if I buy Christmas decorations, I just throw them away in the morning, is
n't that a big deal?  That's the ideal Christmas burger.For
example,
one year ago, I
had a very peaceful Christmas.I
spent it with my family for the first time in a while.
My brother, sister, Dawn, and sister's boyfriend are also here, and my
mom and I are all at home, and all the other family members are there,
too.
Well, for example, my family lives in Osaka, so I feel like I live in Tokyo,
and everyone came here to visit the garden,
but it wasn't Japan.  Hey,
hey, hey, that's it.
First of all, we all went to Neohiro to fill up Maa. It might have been a little late.
Hmm, anyway, we went to the Christmas Market Wit. It's
really big. I'm sure it's the biggest Christmas market in Ushi Town.  It
was really cold, but we all had something hot to drink.There
are all kinds of things like that at the Christmas market.a
How do you say it?I don't know how to say it in Japanese.I do
n't know, but there are all kinds of things.  We went out
of our way to eat, drink,
eat, and talk about all kinds of things,
and we all talked about things like, ``I'm
going to Japan in a few months, and everyone is coming to see me.''
But in the end it turned out to be a forest Ah,
idiot By Yeah, that kind of brain is so far away Yeah, I don't like that, so
everyone was playing, reading, and drinking, but I was a little relieved and had some chocolate.
And
then there's the junior high school version of mulled wine. Drink and turn. Ah, that's it. We spent a lot of time there. Ah, it's
kind of like Christmas.
Look at the eraser.
Christmas-like music. We drank there, and then we tasted it. We drank it a few
times, so we went home.  I think my mom, my
mom, my big sister, Karsheen from Nezu, and
others were helping out, and there were a lot of people there, and
I was like, Wait a minute, and in the meantime, everyone was decorating a Christmas tree somewhere.
That mother's nature-obsessed boyfriend was a very fancy and
fashionable christmas dinner,
and we ate that at the end.I
felt like I had seen that movie, too.In the end,
at our house, with my mother.  My older brother stopped at my house, my older sister went somewhere else,
but they all stopped at my house, and the
difference between the shots was that the mothers went back to their own place. Well, that's Osaka. I
feel like it's a lot.  I'm
not trying to say anything, but you know what I mean
?
Ah, but that's what I mean.
Wow, last year was so good and ideal, but basically it's been that perfect Christmas for years and years.
I didn't spend a
lot of time there, and there were a lot of times when I couldn't spend time with my family, and there were a lot of times when I was overseas,
so the sounds resonated with me.If it
was a good Christmas, I would talk too much, and it would be a crazy tree.
Yes,
Follow
[Music]
Nya, is Santa going to come? I asked for something, but he's not coming anymore. Ah, I guess I
'm Santa now.
But now I have no choice but to give myself a present.  Well,
thanks to all of you, I've become able
to buy whatever I want, but now that I'm like that, I'm
wondering what I want, and what kind of present should I give myself?  I was wondering if I should buy it or not.  I
can't think of much of a baby anymore, so I'm having a sad run.I
realized that
yesterday was the last day.I won the
Yankee-chan stick from Amazon.This
Yankee candle will arrive tomorrow.I know, it
smells really good.That's
all, but I thought of something else.
Well, I want to give Junon a really luxurious present, but I can't think of any.
Um, I'm going to that Kansai area in a few days, so I'll give it to myself as a present,
yankee.  candle Yes, that name is a bit strange in Japan, but I wonder what it is.I wonder if it's an
American brand.How about a
candle?Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa Well I looked for it a little bit
but I bought a present for Mi-chan as a cat
and it was a
really big present.  I bought it, but I contacted that expensive guy
and asked him what he wanted for Christmas, and he
told me to make a wish list on Amazon, and he wrote a list of what he wanted.  I
made it and got mad at my house, but
during that time I bought a lot of things in the countryside.I bought a Switch and bought two Switch games.I
ran away from something like
Lois Canceling.I could hear the sounds outside.  Well, the
expensive headphones won, so
in the end I paid that big brother
about 100 times that amount on my own. I
wonder if he's happy. He's
just like my big brother. He loves that game.
I love Zelda, too, but I wonder if my brother didn't have the money to buy a Switch for a long time.I
was sad because I couldn't exercise in Selder Breath who the live was.I
think he was worried because he was going to get ballet for a long time.Ah,
but  I also made money on the new Switch and its Zelda,
so I bought it for you.
That's why I'm Santana. I
'm the chanter,
yeah.
Thank you for coming.
Roasted c. Hey.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa but it's really good I
want to protect that house Japan is Japan before startup Japan Japan After I left I have a roommate who I live with now I don't have a
Noh mask or
anything.  I told her I wanted to buy something for her,
but she didn't make it for me. She
couldn't think of anything, so she didn't
make anything for me. I wanted to
pamper her, but oh well, it's
mine, so I don't
need anything else.  Karau
[Music]
Well, for now, I'm going to fall asleep.
Hello Genkicha-san, I'm going on a trip to Germany and Austria next spring, but
if you have any other sights to see other than Win, please let me know. Also, do you
have any recommendations for the amount of rainfall in white ash supermarkets?  Please tell me about this as well.I do
n't know much about it.I'm not an Austrian, but I'm a big believer, so I'm going in here.Dad, I
don't know much about Austria either.Surprisingly, I don't
know.
Japanese viewers don't really understand the current topic.It
's a topic that is often used on broadcasts about abolishment, but
do you get it?  I'm
pretty sure I understand, but
I'm a slow user, and
I'm a slow healer, but that's
true.
However, I
can only recommend tea for Vienna, where it's obvious that you're copying the Queen.Sasalzburg is
a little bit of a wonderful city called Salzburg.Sasalzburg is that Vienna.The
Yorii is
very beautiful, and
although it's small, it's compact and nice, so be sure to check it out.  Please take a look!
Especially in winter, Haruka Honey. This cardigan is also very beautiful for those kinds of people. I
don't know much about Matsu Southern Tsubu Kuzuzu Book, but I don't know.
devin  When you head to that seated chair for the first time after surfing, it might be a
good idea to go to a place called Hallstatt first.Even if you miss it, it's amazing.I've
never been there, but it must be
close to Block 5.It
feels like a fairy tale.
It's a beautiful place, but there are basically a lot of tourists. There's no
one there right now. The startup sound doesn't seem like anyone should be that Austrian. There are
n't any Austrians around, so it's really pretty right now.
There aren't many people there, but the line will probably start next week.
Uchishu: Starting next year, the number of tourists will increase again, and I
feel like it's going to be implemented.When
there are no tourists, the meeting is called Power.The color that that older sister was in was
there.My older sister went there the other day.  There were no tourist interns who sent me this photo. It was
probably the first time in spring in 100 years. It
was really amazing. I googled it and Hallstatt is really beautiful. But to put it in perspective,
Abe, it's not that special, isn't it?Everyone goes there.Even
though it's just as beautiful for generations,
ah, ah,
mama,
yes, the moon, the rice, the Neuroi, that Matthew, why here, why here, why white tomorrow?  I
don't know if it's going to make you hungry, but it's the food of your dreams.But why
don't you call it Shuriken Yapono?Eat the perfect amount, you've got it
right.
In Austria, when you eat shmitsuru, you eat it with that jump, so when you
eat it, sometimes people don't come.
There's poke, but I wonder why.
Please tell me that, I'm
going to turn around. I'm going to
take away Bear from Kaise, so I'm
going to make a recording of this and play it at the restaurant. It's a
sunny day. I'm heading
towards Bear, so please play Rio's song.
This is a certain jam. Please give me a certain berry jam. I
don't know how to say it in Japanese, but it's Bach.
That's what I mean. Also, hurry up and
eat some earth schnitzel. Ah,
ok. Next: Good
evening.  Hell, I'm very shy. I admire Chaa-chan, who can get along with all kinds of people. She
's a character. Bahco Semo 1 Shop Rainbow Do you get nervous
?
What do you do in times like that?I always get a lot of energy from watching Kiya Gacha's distribution, but I'm going to
protect it from now on.The turner to the area is cute.Evapa.This is
cute.beaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
I've been asked this a lot, but you know, I'm really nervous too.For example, when I meet someone in a riad for the first time, I get
really focused.I was
nervous when I met Kiccho Sorio, too.  I wonder if
Apica 7 is playing or there's a scene in Meissen where I was so excited
when I met him. That's right, I was so nervous when I met my great seniors. I'm so
nervous every time. Hmmm. I
was also nervous when I met Cyber ​​Matsui.  I was really nervous when I met Natsui Center.a
But when that happens, you just have to try your best to get over it.Well, most of the time, things turn out okay.Well,
I wouldn't give that advice too much, but it might not be possible.
The truth is, everyone gets nervous when it comes to noises, and
if I get nervous at the invitation name,
that's difficult.
After the super face-to-face meeting, I don't get nervous anymore.
Hmm, I can't say anything.  No.
Start
[Music]
Hey, I
have some advice for all you guys out there.
Ah, the hot springs at the door were nice too. Hey, I don't drink, but
what do you think about drinking at Osaki?  It
takes a long time to get used to it, so it's amazing that it's okay the second time.If we
talk about it, things like that
will work out somehow.You have to
be careful not to be too much of a woman with that mellow brain.Even
if this place doesn't make any sense to me when I meet you face to face...  Well, I'm sorry if we
had a meeting and the person was drunk, but I really want to go home. Well, it's a
little bit.
So if you're feeling nervous, I don't mind having a drink. Hey,
Noi 3.  -4a
No, that's why I do
n't like being drunk, so I'll go ahead and say that.Next, I
'd like to write about Kyacha's favorite story in detail about
Kamina.Ah, that's right, I haven't watched the anime in a few years now.I'm
sorry, Ano.
I don't know, I
used to be really into it, but
now I don't have much time to watch it, but I'm obsessed with
all sorts of things, like Noah Minamike, Kannagi, Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann, Bakemonogatari, etc.  Things
like A Certain Scientific Railgun, Nichijou, Burger King and Color, etc. That's where I came in at number 3. I
loved the
Monogatari series, which is my top number one, so
Elaine Ganger
was at number 2 or 3.  I don't care about the number 2, 3, or 5,
YamadaYamadaHe really wanted to see the body.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa I
loved Zero's Familiar too, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it's been quite a while since Zero no Tsukasa was released.It
was the first anime I ever watched.It was
about the country where that family grew up, and
that group was on that TV.
[Music]
Meanwhile, I didn't see that one that was being played that wasn't as famous as Pokemon. I hadn't
seen Akira, either. One Piece was also on the air.
So then, I watched the star anime for the first time.  Gaa
Uwattsu and good. He
might be a baggy guy. Hey, hey. Hey, I
got into it as a target with the manga, but there's
no manga. Oh, my
sister
, it's a little bit really good. I don't have a good memory of it,
so I don't really like it. Um, I can't remember. It's a really cool Nakabun feeling, but it's the first one.  I'm not sure. I
was on the run and there was a manga at Gosokan, so I saw a little sweaty manga. I
wonder what it was.
There was a selection there, and I picked up Goddess-sama and crossed the valley and
thought, ``I really, really like it.'' My sister said that at the time she was into manga like Killer Character Girl, which was also a
big deal.
No,
why did you suddenly give me the 4th book instead of the 1st?
Then I looked at it and thought, Wow, it's really cute, but then I thought, ``A, it's cute,'' and I was
hooked on that Noah manga that was addicted to Sugar Sugar Rune.  I
don't read manga right now,
but that's when I got interested in it, and at the same time, I was
hooked on Increased Bushin 4, and the middle team was wearing all kinds of clothes, and I could feel a
lot of Japanese influence,
so I started watching anime from there.  But
what's his name if it wasn't for his looks?
For some reason, ah,
you're Bob, yeah,
yeah. The first anime I just watched was the name of Aso, who might be the committee member you want
.  Music]
That's it
That's a
lot.
No, the knitted glasses were pretty safe on the street. Ah, the
kettle was safe. Why, why,
what was that? It was
seriously delicious.  I'm
addicted to the statue's sacred treasure Nyan, I'm
talking about the Middle German edition of the Sinfonia with increasing numbers, and
all of you are gathered together.It
's a bulletin board.  There was a guy I became friends with on that bulletin board, and it
seemed like he was into the kind of movie you wanted, so
maybe we each tried to find out about it on our own.Pun's
masterpiece plan is certainly not available now,
Kosegi.  I don't remember anything about that, I can't remember anything about it. I don't remember anything about it. It was kind of
cute. There was a maid as a character. I mean, a meat maid. There was a
cute girl who worked at Bamisu or something, and I liked her.
But it was kind of sad, wasn't it? He was kind of a sad prime minister.
I feel nostalgic, too old.
[Laughs] I don't know what to do.
Ayuta are you na
running.
[Music] I'm
getting excited. I don't know if I want to
say something, but I used to be a burden to my close friends.  It's kind of
weird, but
that's when I tried to create a [music] fan site.Marmon does
n't exist.Hmm.  I
made 3 sites.I was addicted to the dark stuff.I
made a site where I can teach you how to get the language you want in Nakajo using German sounds.  I've
started seeing a lot of things,
and I still have a lot of memories like that.Even
now,
there may be Amiaki that is as good as ever, but I wish you were as good as ea.  It's
not that bad, but now that I think about it, I want to know if it wasn't that good.I don't
know, but when I say it's that good, it just means that it's a pretty easy-to-understand anime.I wonder if that
Adewo no Ii or Nemii is an ad.I
wonder if it's still available.  I'd
like to know if I'm right, but there are so many Nakane animes out there that I don't know which one I should watch.I don't know which one to watch,
even if
everyone recommends it.  The
number of line lines of Balan and mine are completely different,
and now it's so dark that a girl would fall down and see her panties.If I looked at her
suspiciously, I'd be pissed if I looked at her now.Ah,
back in the day, when I was at the beach, I was like, oh, how cute.  I thought that, but now that I look at it, it seems like something like that is easy,
but I can't pay for it.
It's not interesting,
so it's even more interesting.
There's a good thing that comes along. I
want to watch anime.
Anime that seems to aim too much at the inside is
kind of shallow and superficial. I'm
not interested in morning rules.
I'm sorry, I'm
sorry. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.  If so, please let me know. Yabe
Atsugi is also a bit long. I threw Aisin Hyana, which is a slightly longer Chinese song.
Actually, I only intended to do it for an hour, but I have a lot left
.
I'm talking too much. I
saw Anohana. Oh, I saw it. It was
delicious.
Ah, well, well, I haven't seen Kamido either. I'll send you a better one. I
watched Bull Camp. Angel Beats was really good.
Yeah.  I have
n't watched the trackside beat, I haven't seen it, I
haven't seen it at the end of the day when I'm not suited for it, I can't do that, I've seen Gochiusa.  I
used to enjoy anime like Post Investigation, but if I watch it now, I probably won't enjoy it.My
taste has really changed.
[Music] Is it
just that?
That Strawberry Marshmallow inspired the name of the anime Atke Icchibou Marshmayo.  Yeah, I
know. I
really enjoyed it back then, but if I look at it now, I'll definitely not be able to enjoy it.
Ah, looking back now, I'm thinking, ``Ah, they're aiming for me.''  I
might not enjoy it Ah, I wonder
what it is.100%
No, I don't know if it's not Ichigo Mashimaro.The
maka wave is too deep.It's really a
troublesome otaku.Ah,
it's a monster that wants eyes, just like in the year.It's an
anime with a double story.  I want it, but Bakemonogatari is also okay.It's a bit
cheesy, even though he's showing his panties.Sometimes
it's a bit cheesy, but I can forgive him for the fact that he's a big monster now.  No matter
what you do, I'll forgive you.
Yes, let's read. Thank you for always being the bridge today. Thanks to Kyara-chan, I'm
glad that we were able to interact with en and Japan.
What kind of games did we play with the little one in Kyara-chan's Bokubokokkko?  Taka: If you
have any fun or questions about Japan, please let me know. I
can't pronounce Akiara-chan's "Pop Boots." Do
you already have boots? Haro's original version.
Can Germany do this?
Bokuro PokkokPokPon I'm
happy to see Kya-chan every day, and I actually love studying.Ah
, when I was little, having an older sister was good for me.I
used to pretend that I could use magic.I played around pretending that I could use magic.
Love was really small when I was little, but after that, my mother was the only game.I
was the mother at home, and the mother neon run game was
on.  When I
'm off the soil in Apita, I play a lot of games like Wow Crafty, A Bar Quest II, and stuff
like that,
and I don't even have a home.I
started playing it when I was quite young, and
my mom made sure to get a computer at home as soon as possible.  He did that for me,
and then it was already 6 years early, and he
became a recluse,
and that girl who guessed you was also a
winner, right?
Nowadays, I think my mother is operating on other people, but back in the
day,
everyone used to play a game
called Onna Jekuto.  I used to go there once in a while.I don't
know what else.I was always on the computer.I got hooked
on anime.I got hooked on Japan.
And as a family, the whole family did it together. We were
trying to beat each other and it seemed like we were the worst, so sometimes when we went there, we would just cheat and stand next to each other. But even then, we never won well. Ah,
no. 3  Even though I'm serious about pipes, I'm going to eat a Galavenia sentence.  I
used to use blue cards from time to time, but I had run out of cute cards, so
Neoga-san made a machine using extremely black black and made extremely strong and scary-looking cards.
a horror
Hmmmm Kiritani's dull super bar is a bit of an oddity in the tab
Oh, he doesn't even have a house
[Music]
Well, I guess it's a color Kinone is really small I
never heard of it when I was around.  If it
's Germany, Hirotomoki will be the one.The
performers of 9 Ah Good
are dark, good, good, mama, it's going to be down from now on.I wonder if the
two broadcasters will appear on the broadcast or not.I don't
know.
Even if they do, they
won't do it in German, but I think they'll do it in English.The
reason is that Germany
[music]
Those who are hungry are bold.The people who live in Prefecture No. 5 are all fluent in English,
and
everything else is in English.  I
don't
think Germany can do this because it's just a bar joke.I don't think Germany can do it.Germans are
all fluent in English, so I don't think it makes any sense.Yeah,
that's what it
is.Fishing.  Thank you for your hard work
on the simultaneous Sudo work on the expedition. Everyone was watching. Did Mark
see it? He was watching it. [Music] If he hadn't, why hadn't he? The
other simultaneous director was in a group.
Eren is temporary.  If I wanted to watch it quietly and alone, I would have probably watched it alone if it was worth it.
[Music]
Thank you,
ah,
a I hope we can have a live performance together with the members of Ienoya and Indonesia in the future.
That's right, what kind of song would you like to sing as a unit?
If that's the case, then of course it's my original. I
want to sing Otori. Ah, I
want to perform Inaho no Bo, which was a very long and passionate production.
Fire, I
want to get jealous from the side, and
I'm going to dance to Ken Kurizu, who has a nice pretense, and Bamber's bird turn.
Well, I'm a little good at it, or maybe that's it.
First of all, I'm the youngest and I haven't practiced, but I used to be good at picking up sounds,
and I used to do it a lot as a hobby.Hmm,
that's why I'm so confident in that area, like Bang Bang's bird turn.  I used to be a Hello! Project otaku,
so now I'm a little different.I'm a big fan of the old cabbage, but I guess Ota Ward does
n't really follow it anymore.I
think it would be great if I could cover Hello! Project songs.  someone etc.
For example, I heard that Kanata-senpai also likes Hello!
Project, so it would be great if we could cover something together.I don't know if he has permission from someone, but I'm OK with it.In Hanshin, I'm still lucky.I've gotten permission to sing quite a few Hello!Project songs, so I can sing them live.  I wonder if she can sing.The
sound of the song is really professional.It's
amazing.It's a scene suitable for idol concerts.The
choreography is also pretty good.Well, I've had a
life that I wanted to enter around spring.
Yes, there it is,
so
Page Day, when I
sing a Cal Pro song in front of thousands of people, it doesn't feel like I'm already in Spring Pro.
[Music]
Mini Moni Bakun I wish I
could cover something like that.  I'm
really looking forward to the next one
[Music]
Amelie Queen
On the 2214th, Nihongi Daishi will do Nihongi Daishi to the former governor. As expected, Ara-chan
It's idol Ota Ward, and it's a perfect move to meet Japanese people who aren't happy anymore.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
dad
Eh, that kind of thing, that kind of thing, this is what I was hoping for.
In particular, I would like to receive a bonus message from Mr. Clooney, the manager of the Japan branch of Keifu, who was on shift on Christmas night.Thank
you very much.Actually, I
stopped by at the beginning, but it's
okay.Christmas is
actually a
day to spend with family.  Deah
Spending time with your lover is something that
someone in Japan has decided to ignore and
don't worry about it.It
's baccarat.It's
stupid.What's the point?
There's a perfect excuse for being alone this year.
That monster
is na.
[Music]
If it weren't for that, we'd probably
be going out on a date.
[Music]
If it wasn't for that, we'd be in real trouble
Words like that
[Music]
Because it hurts
4 types of lies It's not like Yasui can't lose now I
can't go out since winter I think Kazune is important
Well, it's my illness.  I don't want to be like that, so I
have to keep my distance from other people.That's why I'm
standing in the government building.I'm
doing everything seriously with Arthur.How many times have I
seen people who are trashing me outside?
Oh, well, there wasn't any kind of announcement asking people not to go out on Christmas.One of
the balls was from Chile last summer, and when I saw it just now, people on Christmas dates were
handing out stuff.
[Music]
Hey.  Hey, it's my own.
Actually, it's a little bit. I
have to be serious.
Hey, I have to be careful about what I say, but I'm going to explode.
Fishing,
Dad. I'm so
sad that my character will change to a country soon.
Hmm.  I
know it's for the sake of the kids, but I guess they have cats too. I wonder if they'll be able to
send occasional messages to Japan after all this,
but even if I write about it, it'll still be a pushover.  I haven't had any, so I've been doing
this for a long time. Yeah, you're listening to me in a guiding tone
.
[Music]
Ah, right. I just
said something.
After that, Inoko, who is also streaming in Japanese, is collaborating with Zenshitsu.
But sometimes there
are scenes where the Japanese is painful, and the marshmallows are like this.If everyone comes, I'd
like to do it, hmm.
Even when I wanted to collaborate with Aoni in Rougami, I would have to go there, and then in Japan.This
year, I actually wanted to go to a general-quality school.That's
why I came here.This year, I
decided to go further north.
But in the end, I didn't come on a trip at all, so I have a lot of things left to do.That's why I
think I'll probably go to Japan a few times next year.If
I can, I'm sure it won't be that bad.I'm
planning to go
sightseeing quite a bit.  I don't want to
go to Okinawa yet. It's
not summer, so I'm going to Okinawa on October 10th next year. Do
n't worry, it won't change much.
Even though the wiring time has changed, I'm still happy about that house
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa The
Tama family's Nanyang bar will remain unchanged That's
why I look
forward
to your continued support. [Music] Same thing [Music] Mr. Jung always enjoys Air Turn.  I
really love Aisin, and I go back to Eastern Europe. I
respect Sahiraku's hard work every time, and I can feel his hard work behind the scenes. ringtone  If you
compare Aiba's Kentucky Fried Chicken and Mark Door Donald's in Japan and other countries, they
're probably smaller in size. Hey,
if you compare them to America, they're probably smaller in Japan, but if you
compare them to Yoroga, they're the same size.  I do
n't think I've noticed that much of a difference.
Thanks to the famous members of PISO,
Haneda, etc.
[Music]
Thank you.
Other manufacturers seriously, members of the scene, etc.
Big,
long, long
canmake the Recommended Queen  The store
manager's height is called Ternate, but
in the heart of the 10 people, the sound and the 23 fan service are great, and the village equipped village is so heavy.I'm
surprised and surprised every time, and I'm going to be the royal mother.  I
'm sure the Japanese viewers will be able to keep up with the translation because Chara himself was his biggest fan, so I think he was very considerate yesterday on the pavement.That's the right type of owner, haha.Well, the red sea bream seems to change, so it's always the case.
Recently, Jazz, who has been talking about masseurs who have come overseas, seems to be saying that he will be taken to his usual room.
What does this mean? He sounds like he has just seen something horrible, but this is
not a white corporate cult.  Is there something like that in Yo's genealogy pin?
[Music]
What
?
No.
Well, just the other day there was a drive with my seniors, and they were in charge of how many characters there were. He's a
male mule from a private school who heals.  Please let me know if there is any scene
Also, why are you making such a fuss about the movement
? Calm down! There's no point in arranging to buy something related. I
wonder if I had a vision of myself standing there after watching Air Ferry and the others live.
Today's a color play, so it's
okay.  Let's eat.
What do you mean?
8 Hey,
there's nothing special about the back woods. It's over right away, so it'll be soon. Even if you take it in one shot,
you'll be aware.  Before the collaboration with my boyfriend, I grabbed my kids for a while, and as
soon as it was over, I grabbed them right away, and then I
remembered the bob car in that room in front of the club.
Thank you so much for the members.A
lot of it was recorded in one shot.I
wonder if that
vision of me standing there in the future has
come to mind.I
don't know if it has come to mind.It may not have come to mind
.
First of all, I
have to wait for my slippery good girl to go up on the deck.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it. If I
can do that, I might be able to imagine it a little, and it'll be spacious. I
wonder if they'll be able to bring their house into the Japanese concert in the first place.  I'd
be happy if you could stay with me. I want to be like everyone
else. I want to dance the same way, sing the same way, and stand on the same star stage. I
want to mix with everyone normally.
Sorry, that's fine.
In the same way, I took a hatch unit and did each one,
but I wonder if I can do it live.Yes, it
seems like it's dialysis.It seems like I'll have trouble if I don't get the Hagi position.  It's
not just me,
everyone, I want to see Dankura-chan and Grachan sing together on stage for 3 d days
Anchor  I
heard Bula -chan's voice there. I really borrowed it after borrowed after borrowed after borrowed ANAP
Performance Tomomi Someone stopped and absolutely cool.
So I'm happy.
[Music] It's a
three-tiered stack of characters. I want to show it to everyone. I
want to dedicate it to my baby. The perfect idol sound. Aizu's steps are
too easy. Don't do them left and right.  I
have a lot of kilos that I can do. That
's too much. Let's
do the star choreography properly. It's what
I can do.
1 Yamamachi
[Laughs]
I'll do it properly.
Hey, Marin-senpai has some really unique movements. He's doing
it, Ayakawa.  I'm
going to keep raising the bar!
Have you ever been to Disneyland or Sea in Japan? I
like the attractions there. I've
been to Disneyland a few times.  I think it was once or three times. I think it
was once as a receiver. It
was quite fun, but the scenes might have been more fun.
But the attractions aren't really moving. Ah, hey, Maeda, whatever. Nice to
meet you.  So in
Europe, I went to Disneyland once in France,
and France was a lot more strange.When
you come to Europe, you don't have to go to Disneyland.If you come to Europe, you do
n't have to go to Disneyland.Japan is
much better.Well,
booth.  Honer: It's
probably easier to see things because there aren't many people,
but
actually, at that time, I went to Disneyland with a Japanese guy named Todate, and
I had a good time.  I do
n't have any business, masa
Hunan province, huh? My
friend is
really disappointed in me.
Hmm, my friend is a coord who has orgasmed over and over and over again at Disneyland in Japan. He's already
like a Disney professional.  Yeah, I
said something to a guy in Paris, and
then he
tweeted
a lot about Japan's Underground Days, and
I was like, Wow, I was a little hurt when I saw that, but yeah, I guess that's true.
Disney in Japan was better, but that hurt a little
. Good luck to me. I guided you there, but it was my first time going to the village.
However, after that, I went to Japan after all. As I
was writing about it, I thought, ``Wow,'' and I
don't say that to the moon.  In the middle of the day, I'm
hurt and
sad,
but suna no, the
feathers were a little bad, and it was raining, and there was
something wrong with someone, but there was something I couldn't give them.Well, maybe it was
because it was a little depopulated, but
first of all, umm...  I
got in around 1:00pm on the 12th of the
day.Well, I got in without lining up at all.First of all, I was hungry.I was
looking for a restaurant inside Disney,
but I couldn't find it.There was
nothing vacant, so I decided not to go there today.  There
was only a small snack that was written there,
so I found just one lesson and found that wrestler who was supposed to be vacant,
but I
didn't feel like there was a key to doing something.
Although it wasn't a solo role, I felt a great sense of freedom.When I
went to the restaurant, I believe it opened 3 hours after middle school,
which was 3 hours longer.It
said it would open at 4 o'clock,
but when I went at 8 o'clock...  It looks
like I'm going to close it and there's no
rice.
If it's not strange, it's not amazing.
[Music] I
went to Disneyland in Tokyo, and I
was having trouble finding food.First
of all, I had to give it to you.I wonder
why the food was so small.I
bought that fried chicken from a food stall.I only ate the small fried chicken.
But there was a
little bit of Bagon imitating Atsuko, a little bit of it,
so yeah,
well, everyone,
if you're going to wrap that up in Europe, I want you to think about what I just said.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaude Do you
have any ideas or advice for how to prepare a cat mom? It
’s an al-addon, isn’t it? There’s something like that. Is that normal now? The palace tomb.
That toilet to prepare, the long-tailed cat tower that you can climb up, etc.  It's
normal to have a rag to put food in that ball, especially
if it's small, especially if you're raising a kitten, you
have to hide all those small things that shouldn't be eaten.  I
really tried to eat everything
this year, so my kitten was a woodcutter at the beginning of the year.On the second day after I bought him, he had an accident with that cat.It
was really difficult.7
days
For example, that toy for cats,
let's put it away when it's done.  Cats will eat things even if they don't seem like they'll fit in their mouths.
Cats are stupid, so
you have to be really careful about that. Hide everything,
even if it's small or not small.  It's
Really Dangerous
[Music]
Next How long did you believe in Santa? Did you have a mother? You
know, no. The
country where I grew up is Post Urariana. Then,
actually, it's
not Santa who teaches the children the third turn. Ah,
Cafe Skins Cut Money Transfer Toiso.  It's a name that sounds like a child, but it's
like Gar is going to give you a present.It
's like an angel, like an angel.
When I was little, my mom would ask me to go out for a while, and I'd go out and
play outside at 10 or 9 p.m., so I'd go
out with my older brother.  I went and played in the snow, and when I came back, I was
told that I had a festival gold coin, and
that angel came down and
left me a present for some reason.I used the
tree bar for some reason.
But it's not worth it
Oh Chris, I heard that and chose it, but the
mother of the cow is a mixed story,
but the mother in the back doesn't believe in eating God, nor is she a Christian.  I gave
birth.It
seems like it's far away.That's why
Christ is in the name, but I
guess Christmas is also in the name.Well, even if it's not Christianity, it's like Japan.  Well, I was born, so yes, that's right.
That's right, I do
n't remember how long I believed this,
but it turned out that there was no such thing as Santa in the first place. Cha-
chan looked at me. Is your stepfather busy today?
What are you planning to eat? Tiara The manager is from the area.  I don't even eat, right? I'm
very busy right now.
There are all of you working hard right now, but I'm slacking off.
Usa Ozawa Come on, it's your job.  My
job is to make everyone feel better,
but I don't go to Mass. I don't go to work.
Papa, the
genealogy of adaptation. Pinault. You know,
that Franfas Black Wrestling Run 22. I
don't sleep when I go out.
Everyone has to work for me.Ah,
I won't be eating chicken today.Bach
at the katsudon shop at the convenience store.Yes, I
came to Paliope-chan, but there's something like "see you."
Please change the menu Fuku and the bunny suit please.
9 That black black bunny suit. It's
black and looks a bit like that
Nanao Nezu leather. I
'm looking forward to the suit between the kanji characters.  I
'm looking forward to a naughty one, not a sexy one.
Good evening, I'd like to ask you a question.
Takamori is getting too attached to me. Is it okay if I draw a circle for l?  If you
submit it and post it, you can tag a tag.  Are you
thinking of a bird of prey?
Hmm, for example, the people at the hot springs of prosperity that the 3 Atata family retweeted the other day
are OK.
[Music] If the
parts
of my private life are not the Emperor, I
would like them to be included in the tab with ordinary fans. Well, it's a little bit retired,
but I already took a scene of Rose 1.
Kanea, don't you dare say that to a Japanese horse?
Even if it's too sweet,
is that so?
[Music]
Hey, I'm
at a loss for words. I wonder if it's
okay to use this word.
[Music]  I
wonder if it's okay to use ah, ah, I guess it's better not to use it.  Hey, more than that, there's a photo of a fellow private parlor 2. Well, I'm
a little curious.
Someone wants to take a look.
Ran, yeah, I'm trying to
suppress everything.  It's
ok to post it after that, but I don't think I'll retweet it.
Because even if I get scolded, I'm still like, ``Oh,
a little bit.'' At the end, that little bit is seriously dangerous. There
are three choices, ah, uh,
where am I not?  It's a little hard to say, but I
don't want to see the Ganchinoya tour.Well, I want to see it a little, but no, right now, I'm free.
Please don't do it to me. It's
a little awkward for me, so I won't come.
That's awkward. I
don't want to know what you guys are imagining.
But mach,
bacio,
uh, some manager is standing there.
Ran, daddy, it's all right.
G, Leather, w, it's okay, up. Big
big big big big big sister line.  I don't know anything about the game.He
just asked me what Taki wanted to say.Ah, the
manager who was listening to me was listening to me.  Not
even, umm,
uhm
[Music] I wonder
what it is,
oh, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, bad, bad, bad. Well, I'd love to see that kissing scene, too. Well, that
someone...
Well,
[Music] You
can give me 4, that turn, I
put it up with the tag.  Okay,
but I wonder what that thing is
true.
Yeah, he's dangerous. Is that what it is? Um, yeah, I
get it, I get it, I get it across. On
to the next part aaa
Kapikachiya's exact gold or not
Hello
Eh 5 Ha I
don't know what to say, but I know what suits you. Do you understand?
Acoustic key It's a
short time with love, but it's a bit too much. Yeah, Tama-kun
is in the dry season, but what do you think?  Do you take care of your skin
? Well, I use an Ospei rice-based face bag before going to bed.Thank you for the skeins.Well, I haven't been taking care of my skin at all lately.  My skin has been
getting really rough lately, and it
has nothing to do with the weather.I
used to take medicine for my vagina, and I used to listen to it a lot,
but
recently I stopped using it
in my home country.  I won't be able to get any more by the time I get home, but if I go with you, I'll be able to get into 8.
But it's
a bit of a pain, so I'll just drink it, and after I finish that, I'll
get rough inside.
But I don't go out for a while, so I thought it would be okay. I only
go out
once a month, so
even when I go out, I usually wear a mask, so it's
okay. That's why
I sometimes try to shoot even if I don't do anything in particular.  Sometimes I wear a
proper pack instead of a sheet mask from the chapter Lush.  I'd be
happy to receive something from Flash's Rush as a present, but I guess
Nash's
is NG in terms of its cover. I'm sure it's a
shame I bought it. I
love it. Ah, it's an
old pattern.
What's this year's kanji?  I've
prepared three things.This is what I've prepared.I was also asked about other magic tricks.Hmm,
I've never performed in a performance before, but I
want to do it in a Japanese-Japanese way.I wonder if it's a little early or early.  Is it
too early?
Why are all women like that, why are they animals?
What do you think? That's how I felt. I
was so proud of myself.
That's how I thought.
My feelings this year are clock-shaped.  Hey,
it's like this on the radio. Oh,
no, it's only 9.
Of course it won't come out. It won't come out. Wait a minute. Let's
put it in here.
Maten Uma
Tei
[Music]
Wait. Now, I
put it in there.  Takara  I wonder
if
Bach walks There are
too many attendants
Ah, why did I go back to the beginning
Stop, ah,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait If you're
about to answer a question, the answer is ah, this is it, ah.
What should I do?
Don what should I do?
Instrument
[Music]
That's my heart.
I was driving this year, and I
found out right away.
[Music]
Hmm, is that
really the case?
[Music]
Um,
just
when I thought that I really
couldn't do anything anymore, I don't know
what I've done. It's definitely even darker, but no matter what I do, it's
not going to work out.
ua What's the point in living?
When I was giving up on books and 2 years from a major company, I lost my job.
Yeah, I'm very serious, but I
want to thank you.
A
Ah, if
everyone couldn't tell us what the wave was
like, we wouldn't be the same without everyone. If there
wasn't a live show, right?
[Music]
But I was like
that.
[Music] I wonder
what it was.
[Music] It would have been great,
but
we...  There are 8 books in there, and
I can't do anything about it. I
want everyone to be a little bit happier.
[Music]
I want everyone to be happy. I do
n't know what I should do.
I can't do anything, but
let me support you, please, thank you.
[Music]
Okita would be the one without Pia-chan. I'm depressed. It's like I'm depressed. Really
. Especially this year, well, everyone is really depressed.  I think it will come out, right?
Hey, hmm.
I also grew up
with Sheena. I want everyone to feel the same way as me.
[Music]
Yeah
[Music] Let's
do our best, everyone. Let's wait for the flavor.
If the salt character is happy, I'll be happy too.  release
[Music]
Everyone, everyone, let
's not shut up. It's like we're in a serious situation. Because this year was so bad, next year will
definitely be better. It'll definitely be better. It'll
be. It'll definitely be.
Come to our lives.  Thank you for everything, everyone, for always seeing me as a good person.What is it?Everyone is really happy.Everyone
[Music] I tend to
stay at home and feel gloomy, but thanks to the original club, I was able to have a good time at the store.  Masu
I'm happy about that, but from next year onwards, let's go out more and more. I love calling this house a good one too, but
next year too. Let's travel around the world a little more, everyone. I'm sure
Mamina won't leave Japan very often, but there are other places.
Let's go on a trip and
enjoy nature. It looks
delicious. Thank you for that.
I like Gyata's nice impression and Forebar's mask, but I like her positive and
assertive personality the most, and I'm surprisingly happy about that.
This marshmallow is perfect because you don't just say everything out loud.It's
just right.It's so nice to be able to get close to your thoughts with AI.This is what I
noticed when Kira usually communicates.If you
have a way of thinking and iron work.  I'd like you to tell me about the
store.Nothing in particular.I have
n't met him, but thank you
very much for being a guard.It's not something I'm thinking about.Well, it's kind of awkward.I don't like
must-listen songs, so I'm
trying to avoid that as much as possible.
I'm trying to talk when no one is there.I
guess it's okay to say something random.This is
delicious.I want to see what you eat.I'll start the episode first.Ah,
yeah, I do
n't really understand.Communication  What I'm conscious of when taking a picture
is not to create a strange atmosphere.The
atmosphere is a loose character, isn't it?Naka Nihonko-san,
there's a word called "reading the atmosphere" in Japanese, but it's also
common in German and English.
If I try to explain it, it probably exists, but I
guess it doesn't exist.
Well, it's Wii, Shake Maker, and Witblo. Oh, please, Dochiho.
Hey,
Tsuboniwa. I don't think it exists anyway.
So,
since I moved to Japan,
p.  Reading is good for dogs.Once
in a while, I was told that Chiara, who ranked number one in the prefecture, was a ky, and I
thought to myself, ``Why?'' and when I thought about it, I realized that this is what makes a ky.
a
Well, I tried my best to
read the atmosphere.I
think if I consciously solved it, my horse would get better.Ah,
money is important when it comes to reading the atmosphere.It's
important to know that people who can't read the atmosphere should seriously give up on me.Body
22  This is going to be important at some point.
ABuilding I
went to the one where Chaa-chan told me to put Nodaya on the Friends Stone Stone and make snow. It was delicious.
However, the first time I bought one, it was a little hard and it was difficult to get it on the bread properly.When I
saw me, I thought, ``This is important, I have to tell this person about Mashima 4th edition.''  Do
you maybe put some nutella
in the refrigerator? You
put some soil in it, so it's hard. I
don't put it in the refrigerator, but I
thought for months that it
's better not to put it in there.  It's a
very ticking when I put it in and I
can't say it. I can't say it, but it doesn't have to be
entered, but it's strange that Edir is strange.  It was a
pancake even without French toast.
Put it in a regular pancake.
Place of application:
Ludia. I
love you so much. O
Bring it on! I'm so happy. I'm stuck in a supermarket. What's
wrong with this place? Overseas.  The
food is sold in supermarkets where you can get it for a while, and
there are scenes of him returning to the cruiser everywhere.Yes, I
feel like he also sells it to his day or Rudy because of the distance and that many calories.
Who would you be if you put the numbers in the box? I
love this coloring, so I guess there aren't many Japanese people out there
who know about Nutella. How much does
it cost?
How many Nutellas did you save?  What's the
point of restarting the chase? A Gay [Music] I don't know about that, but if I put it in the warehouse, it'll be a little bit. All I have to do is do that one. Ah, well, basically, I can't hit the bottom.  If you're going to make me a lover, then make me your sister. If you're going to make me a lover, then make me your sister. Mountain Banana Moonroof.
If you're going to leave me alone, it's difficult.
[Music]
Hmm, I wonder
who it is.
Wait a minute.
Hey.  I'm
thinking too much while looking at my affiliated talent.
But if Umi-chan is a guide, I don't
need a lover.
ua I
don't have
one. Can I do without one? I don't
have one.
[Music]
So I'm pretending to be a younger sister, but my younger
sister is a natural pie.
Let's make Temperature Senpai my younger sister Aider If Anri is
going to do it... Hmm no l Senpai is at the clinic Noel tactics I wonder if she'll be my 3rd sister I like Aro's seniors I
'd like a senior who's there
And I'm going to do it again with wavy line bread,
please.
So, Karima-chan and Tsuki are little sisters.
New hot spring double day. My older
sister is Noru-senpai. A mom is wavy-line bread.
Thank you for your support.
Version is my father.
That ramen-senpai is different.
Isn't that?  The reason is that her voice is calm, and her voice is calm.She
's a kind, wonderful woman.That has nothing to do with her.Nah,
uh,
2021.  There was
something I wanted to try in my personal life. My life now
[Music]
That's right,
Ofu, hey, uh, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa I'm
heading home c Life is here, Bach a Well, I don't think I'll go,
but I'd like to try
cooking once before I cook.  I
want to live a good life.I don't want to say anything, but I go to the convenience store, eat out occasionally,
etc.Next year, I
want to be healthy.That's
why I want to be able to cook more by myself.I'm a mom.Well, I can do a little.
Well, it's
a bit dangerous if we keep taking away money from them,
but it's
not healthy either.Ah, it's
a bit too much.I
want to spend more time cooking so my child can eat as much as possible.
Hmm,
even though it's super early, I'm
currently living in a house in Japan.Oh, I guess
that's it.It depends on the amount of rain and the day.There
are several reasons why it's difficult to cook, and there are
also reasons why I don't have much time and feel lazy afterward.  Opponent's brain waves  The
kitchen is small, and the gas stove in the kitchen makes me a little afraid to use it.Well, my
older brother is more like that, and there's also the
Mouse Street thing.I guess
that's why Ettone High School's 9 colors
touched this barrel.  I'm scared of not having it.Oh,
well, I've been worrying about it for years.I haven't prepared much, but since I haven't, I've been wanting to cook a lot.The
gas stove seems to be strong.Ah,
how many months have it been since I've been here?  I have
n't used it for one month or four months. I'm
scared to leave it on all night even if everyone uses it. I wonder what I'll do if it explodes in the countryside. I wonder
what that other thing is that really stipulates that.  I
heard from someone that I
bought the real one.
I used it once, but when I use it, I don't have any space in the kitchen.
The color is rainwater
[Music]
I1 building. The
dormitory is expensive, but it's not easy. Anyway, I have a gas stove.
Oh, it's strong. It's a
strong day when the gas conditioner is strong.
Ichiraku Phoenix is ​​scared of the mountain tab.
Don't use the header. I'm
not used to gas over there, but it's tens of thousands of dollars and it's strong. The
bus is dangerous. It
's scary.
Well,
that's enough.I like my own voice.I can't help but
admire Chara-chan, or rather, other girls, who are tall and cute.I'm a Chara-chan streamer, so I like my own voice.  I
think you often hear the voices of people like
Lucia, Peko, Senpai,
etc. Hmmmm, I don't really like my own voice either.  I want a voice like that, and I
want a voice like Aper Senpai, too, and a performance like Grand-chan.I
don't really like things like that, so especially when I sing, I
heard Naka Uji's form a few times.  I
gave it away because I was like, Wow,
but that was born out of this voice inside the company.
Well, it's only daytime, so that guy on the inside is using his own coins. But hey, I chatted with him and
said I like Kihara's voice.  There are so many people who care
for you, so you must have someone like that too.It's only human to think that you're not pretty, or that you're a total idiot, or something like that.
But for the most part, I'm the only one who thinks that way. Yeah,
well, I know it's hard to get over that.
I have a job like this, so I can't help it, Barbapapa. I have no choice
but to do it.
I had a girl confess to me the other day because I was on a one-year bond.I
guess I was thinking about it.If I
answered, I said it would be Christmas, and we went to Autumn Bridge, but I was thinking about that coat seller.But I'll
read the answer tomorrow.  It's ok  I can't find the courage to do it. I
'd be happy if you could give me some advice on how to get the courage to do it.
[Music]
happened and I said, ``
Hey, what are you doing with this couple?'' I don't think I'm going to fall in love with the spiritual food hall,
and I don't want to go back. Unno,
this person confessed to me.  I ca
n't understand it a little, but I ca
n't do it.
Winner is angry, Pat
S -shaped moon dadda, so
good, it's okay to answer anything.
You know, seriously, you've got a lot of energy, do
n't you? Papa, who's been assigned Hey, even in the rain, I'll make you do it again, etc. I'll forget about that man. That feeling will be gone. So don't do it again,
really.
[Music]  I do
n't want it to happen again, don't tell me.
This teenage thing is the key.
[Music]
Good, I'm
going to fall in love with you. I'll soon get tired of commercials. It
's Eve's house.
Thank you for watching Dad's lie funeral.
Eh, I'm going to get cold soon. I'm really nervous. If I don't answer right now, I'll
probably go to that other loan guy.
What's the most important purchase you've made? I
was thinking about this, but it's been a while
since I've been here. It's
kind of like making my own. Let's
open it,
brother 22. I
bought that car.
Other than that, e 2.  e
I've never bought something so expensive and so good.
Bach must be surprised. I'm not kidding, I
was living in poverty up until then. I've never
bought anything that expensive in Fuchu before.
[Laughs]
Oh
well, it's me
.
[Music]
Please be my little sister.
Yeah, yeah, I want my sister to be my brother. Big brother, I
want Chiara to be my ex-sister.  I don't care about
who you are, it's not just about cars and self-preservation, brother.
That's what you're aiming for.7 I don't like it. Well,
that's a bit off, is
n't it? It's for your brother's sake. [Music] Uh-huh!  Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
When I search for ``Kiyaa'', all I see are
tweets from FGO's Chiara.Germany
Sometimes I wonder if this is about the house,
but sometimes I don't know for sure.For
example, Beko.  When I streamed War Crime Rank, after that, I did English 3 and it
was all about me, but when I didn't stream it like it was basically a mail-order carver station, I
searched for Chiara and found FGO.
Actually, I like Tarman, who doesn't show any ego at all. I
use Takanashi's character to make him speak English, but sometimes. It's
Kiyo Takahashi. Well, people who
tweet are
good manners. 2-day full bath. They
tweet. Hmm.
What are the people who tweet?  It's just people who have cut out something like that.Ah,
so not so much.Ah, when
you say English in that old, sad, ra, you say it to me.  I ca
n't really get excited because the number of tweets from everyone and my own rear is not showing up.The only thing that comes out is Whip, but it's a sad sentence with a serious name.Damn, I can't do Toei Good.That's why I
sometimes do that.  Hoshino genealogy p I see that in the various tags of Araki Alive,
but well,
if you tweet about proper care, there are those 3 who will look at it
But that's amazing.  When you
write about being a great scorer, it makes me
think that you're really trying to use her full name.It's
obvious, so please go ahead.If
it's Kara-chan, you don't have to use fg.Special
price.Maybe
that's the case.
[Music]  Is
that so? Tanaka
[Music] It's
not going to last for 10 days
[Music]
Ra-chan Kitani Well then,
let's take a look. It's Naeko-
san.
Even if you cut it, it's true that it's just the same as it is, and the
people who use it say that they might be able to see it.I
write with that feeling, but that's
not always the case for people who don't.  I
want to say it, so I want to make it speak English, but
people don't have it.Eh, ah, I
made a mistake.Tiana-
chan
[Music]
ee I was trying to make it sound like I was watching.  It's
true, it's true, it's true, it's
true, it's true, it's true, it's true.
]
Even with this person,
sometimes, sometimes, no,
there are definitely people who praise Kia for being amazing, but when it comes to English, they
don't follow me.
Can you give it to me?  That's
what I think
[Music] I do
n't like it, so what's the point?
[Music] I think
this person has 3 points for abolishing the rate now. Ah
[Music]
This is about us, isn't it? Japan.  She practices regularly, she's cute, her boobs are big,
and I like her
[music]. I
wonder if she'll die because she doesn't follow Plala Naughty. It's
about her house.
Bach. She's
got big boobs. Scenes like that.
Well, I don't know what else to say, but if you search for + Kanane Kiana-chan, you'll
hear what I'm talking about. Almost everyone.
Oh, it's shaking so much tonight too.
What are you doing? Where are you looking?
Dad,
ok,
what are you talking about
? Next time, I'm going to canter and Tsuboya. I'm not going to say anything.
But sometimes, I still talk about F people, and
when they first came out, I was
going to play a role, and after that, it was English.
But seriously, it's in English. It's not really English, so I
searched for Kia's impossible-to-understand tree and bamboo.
Takanashi  Even if I search by character, I can't find anything that won't lead to a miscalculation.
That's why I can only speak English in Japanese.
Stand up, I'm
in trouble. It's
been 2 hours already.  If we
don't make subtitles for that fairy tale video, I wonder how much time I have left to suck it up. I
want to do this. Hey,
let's speed it up just a little bit. Everyone, just a little bit more. Just 10 more minutes.
Let's
eat. Then we can eat. The economy has boomed
since the abolishment of the internet.  I've been tricked and asked questions by the opposition parties, so I'm finally going to talk to them about my worries, but I
'm worried about small mistakes and things I'm a little worried about.  I
know that, so I want to change my mind and live a happy life. Chara-chan, how do you change your mind when something unpleasant
or uneasy happens?
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa from
8 me too.  I'm seriously really worried about Western 8 and Western 4.
Ah, I wonder what that feeling is. I don't think I'm good at it either.
Um, I usually watch Netflix.
Ah, it's over
.  I was thinking of talking too fast right now, but I waited.Dad,
Matsuo is great.Go ahead.I'm sorry for not
being a good anchor.I'm sorry for those who didn't use that spell.That's fine.Even
with your voice, the amount of rain was too much.I
thought I'd just do it for an hour.  Thank you
3 He
said he was waiting for a freaks project
[Music]
Nice to meet you Eine
Meow
What's this cute twitter  It's so cute when it's updated.
Nice Participant Miss wrote this and it's so cute.
Papa
[Music] Dear
Rossi, Tokiko's legs are also a bit sluggish at that supermarket, but her legs are...
no It's due to the abolishment of the riser.  However, I
promised to read it in the 3rd IC. Ah,
today's Aisin no. I'll stop doing both. I
have to make subtitles for the video I'll post in the morning.
8 and bar fever 3rd place company ui say stop chirp person swab soon
chirp to sleepiness 13
hopper event pip wealth 5 a goods full Spain then Prince pronounced pan
a
aime one pucha piled under visor screen beauty f 2  Sapaloma in
my boo to 4
Zazu morning chau beer proline
dog in my moto 4 bottles  Thank you
everyone for speaking with me today, and I feel like things have gotten better in general.My brother
said, ``It was fun.I'll see you again, but I'm sorry again.''  I
'm a fan of Shiun-senpai. I
wonder if there's someone out there who knows a lot about the total loss today. I
asked him a little question at Arkrimaj.
Love, how to write a worthy tweet.
Madsuma, I'm not wrong, but I don't know. Did
you
write about the ocean?
[Music]
Hey,
last time, Sodozo asked questions about the past 10 days. A
Japanese viewer asked a question about Japanese Haru-senpai's previous and upcoming activities.  It's my second time playing
this for fans, so if there's anything Oto-senpai wants me to know about, I'd love to hear about it, so I
changed it to say, but I've gotten a good grip on it, but
most of the time.  I'm
sure there wasn't a book.Rather than asking a question, I've done a lot of things like Shion-chan is cute and serious,
and
so on.I'm
having a bit of a problem with this question, so I'm really surfing.  If you have any questions, please send them to me by asking them to take a look at the moving war criminals and Marin-senpai's Michiko. I
would like to ask you questions about the make-up group and Gidon, who may have had a hard time with that little bit of writing.
Ah, that Melon Minnakan
old episode, for example, if it's about Fubuki-senpai, it's nice to meet you
, or something
about glasses, or something about Sena being locked up last week, etc. That's
what I want to talk about, isn't it
?  [Music]
Someone kindly ask me to please something or something.Dad,
me too, I've seen Shion-senpai's intense performance several times.
After all, I don't know about the old Sky story, so I'm not sure about that. It
would be helpful if you could tell me about it. I'm a
Japanese person. I mean, there's something
about that Shinobu Oshino Naka Fan Discord that everyone uses.  There
are some studies conducted overseas in English-speaking countries, but there are also assertions by Japanese people.If
that's the case, then a
kid from that family called Kitanira asked me, ``That's the best version of the book,'' and I'm having trouble with that question, but I don't know why.  That's
what I mean  I would
appreciate it if you could make that announcement.Ah,
but Mr. Song on the right, there is
one problem.Poroto
Lake is a morning person.Will the
spec seniors be able to
cut it
?It seems that there is a problem, but I don't understand it.
Someone please ask me if I can put it in a cone. Seriously, I went
to that new supermarket this time
when I made that suggestion. I was
wondering if I would accept it.
Hey, I'm wondering if I'll be able to get up in the newspaper or in the orbit,
so why do
n't you just say it yourself?
Pooh, maybe it's far away. It's
okay just for me. I'm
one shot behind for another 11 hours.
Ah, there is a possibility that it will happen Well, that would be fun. Or
maybe it would be really interesting if the bad Fubuki-senpai came. Ah,
on the other hand, it would be more delicious if the senior who died a year later was late. That's the
kind of
nove.
Well, if you oversleep, it will become a trend.
Well, for now, everyone, please ask questions.
Please give me a lip on that tweet. If you dig, please post this question on a certain tweet.
Mr. Blind and the high-voltage line, yay, 5th class of the year.  It's
coming from my sister, but it's
not distributed in Osaka Prefecture. I love you, but I'm ignoring you. A.
Even if you say you took a runty, are you still a little short? Community
posters are also recommended by fans in the authorized cents
japanese  [ __ ] Every time I leave the port, I take da ice dry up supplements Well,
everyone, it took a while, but
thank you everyone.
Andex I hope it's interesting. I'm dressed
in Tokyo. Then, I say hello in German.
Lobby A Ah,
men's  Tomorrow, tomorrow's broadcast, Konano
Karaoke in the archives, Nehora Ikenu at 0:00am,
and the Christmas collaboration, so I'm very busy.Thank you very much.Camera
Bye
Priest Rings Mahler nvidia  The landlady is fuzzy-chan, Kunihejipapa
No, I'm going to force you. d You can speak
Japanese. I was surprised to hear that you speak Japanese. I
was surprised - thank you everyone. You can do it for 5 years. It does
n't look like Mayu, who has been here today for 6 hours.  Kai
nobby Da-in is a bit amazing
Bio Naraha
Project-n-position frontier study appapa
E by Donken-tan mo 2-run par dosuze when is it?
Sleepy Ah Pua Portfolio Nuzo All Pros are also washed It's terrible Bye
Bye Navi 1
Event is far + py Christmas I don't feel like it's Christmas but Merikuri Nekuri Merry
Puttten
Bach
[Music]