it's been a long day will you call me
yeah you got me sleep talking
soing know what to do talking know what
to do you I'm up late already hit
midnight convince myself I'm doing all
right but you know taking one step
taking one back when you text me saying
no way not fair no fair not fair your
eyes they telling me come here now I
can't got me talking breath CU you got
me one oh baby don't you know got me I'm
hooked I go I'm breathing you and I just
can't forget but you got me stressed I'm
just wanting a oh baby that's what you
do you got me swi talking in my dreams
I'm s talking all these nights it's you
no more hiding it n n cut up in your bed
sleep talking in my dreams I'm sleep
talking all these nights it's you you
sleep sleep
talking that you got me all day I'm
sleeping in my dreams I just hear a
voice I ain't got the choice yeah just
like that baby you might never know hey
don't you leave me alone I'm waiting
head on the phone so maybe just going
make the call and I know if you really
oh IM it give it to me now boy you're
ready got me talking breath cuz you got
me warning oh baby don't you know got me
I'm hooked I go I'm breathing you and I
just can't forget but you got me
stressed I'm just running in oh baby
that's what you
do you got me sleep talking in my dream
I'm sleep talking all these nights it's
you no more hiding it n n cut up in your
bed sleep talking in my dreams I'm sleep
talking all these nights it's you you
sleep sleep talking sleep talking in the
night yeah sleep talking all that's
right
yeah Bell you got me feeling so right
sleep fing in the night yeah sleep
talking oh that's right
yeah you can make me sleep talk every
day
hello baby who are you talking to yeah
yeah yeah yeah if you want to say me you
know just what you got to do you know
you want it Just One Look Down so don't
pretend
hello baby who are you talking to ooh
it's the moment I can't escape
I'm I can't deny oh it's
you who maybe this
way you got me slip talking in my dreams
I'm s talking all these nights it's you
no more hiding in not not cut up in your
bed talking in my I'm sleep talking all
these nights it's you you me sleep sleep
talking talking in the night yeah sleep
talking oh that's right
yeah you got me feeling sing in the
night yeah sleep talking oh that's right
yeah bell bell you can make me sleep
talk every day
go