a
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
he
n
[Music]
guys guys where am I I like I hit my
head or
something I can't remember
anything at
all in my whole life who am I
there's all these people I can't hear
them but there's so many people and
there's this
sign I wonder what it is it's like I
finally woke up after like a thousand
years or
something who are these people e r blood
flame I'm green
one Ki beu
what a
bay I'm not really sure what's going
on but I just I just I just woke up here
and now I feel like I feel I feel insane
I I feel very
crazy it's pronounced bi Boo b boo but
it's pronoun it has got a
j excuse me
[Music]
g g g mooding
Shor very
interesting whatever going on I'm not
I'm not really sure what's happening I
I'm kind of scared I feel like I should
be
frightened it it I feel very
[Music]
frightened uh
how goes it are you guys excited for
this whatever it is that clearly I have
no idea about because I just woke up
here who are you I don't know can
someone please tell me what my name
is I can't
see I can't see at
all who's
this Kiara uncore holen what's Hollow
Ian fluffy
fuaa am
Watson
gaura okay that's not I don't think
that's there's fuzzy
mococo
ninoa
laa
Nana
faes Mory
kopine I think did I get everyone did I
I think that's everyone in this
room I
think I'm I'm
terrified I feel
lost uh I I I'm not really
sure I'm not really
sure what to
do um but you
know we're we're going to do it
whatever it
is
uh someone's communicating with
me one sec I have to I have to do
[Music]
something I have to I have to where am I
getting this message from insane H how
are we
doing nura is Pon who's narissa narissa
Nissa
[Music]
why are you
inissac is that my
name is that who I
am is that who I
am nisak yes you are
nisak I guess that's my name now I I
can't do anything about it I I don't
know you surely you guys know you seem
like you know a lot about me
[Music]
you know my name you are aith aith I
like that name it sounds
nice XXX narisa
XXX sounds about right that sounds like
it could be my
name sounds like it could be my name
surely why is everyone on mute I I don't
know I have no control over anything
[Music]
uh one
sec
yeah uh we're
living you are our wife fra you for Gore
your
wife I I don't think that's what this
game is
about pardon me if I'm incorrect but I I
I mean is this a game I don't know this
sounds like real life actually this is
real life I'm trapped in a box though
with these people I've never seen and
don't know anything
about I I don't know these people I've
never seen them before I'm kind of
scared but we must make do I suppose
with any situation bad or good there's
only so many options we have and uh I
guess what what can you
do I have no memories kiss that goth
woman what
I I'm not going to kiss anybody I don't
know who these people
are wow though look at this look at this
room it's so pretty it's like it's like
it's it's radiating its own light
almost maybe we can break
out if we work together maybe
no it looks like something about these
blocks it looks like they just respawn
themselves who is this Oro
cron
huh uh one sec I have to Quick take a
look at something
something kind
of something is is happening and I'm
trying to I'm trying to do
[Music]
something
um
uh uh uh no that's not helpful uh
someone someone I need my memories back
jail bird jail bird jail what's a
jailbird she's so small and cute and
shiny she's like a little gem I'm kind
of
scared oh my God
you're remembering us but a it's a bird
but in the jail what jail are you
referring
to
H
whoa that's
[Music]
uncanny do you see these two here she
they look exactly
alike holy crap they're like twins
I wonder
H I'm not
sure I'm not
[Music]
sure who are you
people huh hello can you say that again
oh oh my God am I where where are we I
don't know St away you guys can talk
yeah I'm kind of scared what's happening
yeah my God who who is one what happened
to my
hands oh are we supposed to lose our
memory
already wait hold on hold on a second I
don't know why my looks like this it's
so Square every you are really am I
square like that
too yeah you you everyone looks like
squar oh my God what what happened I
think I hit my head what happened who
are all of you yeah I that's what I want
to know I think you all have some
explaining to
do what a coincidence I also my head you
hit your head too I hit I just hit my
head I don't see any cracks though are
you sure I'm very durable but it was tra
Dam very durable you do have you look
familiar hello are you guys also heroes
from another hello I look familiar see
the did anyone see the lights I
people here did you see the
lights I I don't
remember am
I am I hurting
you you SM
go
scared bra feels
[Music]
you you guys are talking to each
other do you live in a pineapple under
oh
well what one
sec um I'm I'm just I I don't know what
just
happened I'm I'm just G to see what what
just happened one
sec um
[Laughter]
I I think I think maybe we needed to
talk to you guys a little bit
more
H
uh okay let's try that one more
time am I dead who moang I
guess I don't know moang
[Music]
was
around hello a
human yes I think
so good at that what about you you you
voes are I don't
I'm what what it's so loud here oh my
Lord that's so noising you will have to
sassy Lost Child what is
she yes I've never seen this before have
you I've not seen this I've never seen
it before either I don't know
what 2 hours as I don't remember
enigmatic recollection why is that
capitalize I can't stay as a blank is
that a typo talking to myself I'm not
talking to myself is a typo okay all
right why is excuse
me what's your
name you good with
languages I I'm really not good with
what about you you know your name I
don't even know what I thought that was
spelled correctly no no no the end the
end I don't think that should be calized
is that your superpower you can
recognize
yeah it is my super it must be that must
be my
[Music]
power is that my name I
think status status menu tells me yeah
oh my God you also see names
too it's insane I've never had something
like this happen before
you think we all got superpowers when we
were
s this weird room yeah this weird
box yeah does it mean her crazy is that
why we're
here I don't
know I hope it's okay me B yeah me
too that's a lot for isn't it well good
luck to you on your Are You Adventure
good luck to you as well on getting out
of this
box okay hello hello my name
[Music]
is would you get that impression this is
supposed to be a cute girl
right I don't know have you did you
respons oh then it can be
T
Nissa Nissa fuzzy
Moco you're pretty quiet Nissa amem I do
you know who I am
um remember you
feel
Gander your belly Buton looks
familiar okay I'll try talking thank you
I I thank you too for I feel like I'm
interrupting in I'm
sorry do I you say I smell like a
bird oh I
see yeah I feel I feel sort of scared am
the last thing I remember was like maybe
a big
truck I think I just
died
uh who am I the world I live in what is
the sneak
key more than anything
Crouch
shift the people I hold most
dear faced with Oblivion I feel
empty save your wives what wives I have
a wife
okay
relieved perhaps
distraught I do not
know whoa I much I don't know and yet
and yet oh my God are we all having the
same thoughts so much I don't know and
yet that bright light
it calls to
me oh to
light is anybody else concerned about
this symbolism of going into the bright
light I am I've gone into the light
before I guess it wouldn't hurt to go
again yeah you might be right go to the
light go go to the light to the light
thank you go to the
[Music]
light is
this are we going to shoot up do we
Sho it say do they have
him me up Take Me is This feel to be dad
I don't know why this so many voices do
we go can we go up can we can we go we
don't go up should we go towards the
light oh what's that that looks like an
egg yeah
right big egg it's like a broken egg
octopus egg but what came first the
CH which one around this
is this where we're supposed to
be could it be this
light
[Music]
Sun's what's going
on leest still
Castle you there what are you doing
here you have to look you have the look
of Outsiders about
you wait could it be quick send word to
his majesty the the heroes have arrived
at the
sanctuary right away Heroes I'm not a
hero I'm just a
girl who's that he's kind of cute he's
like a little
plushy wa welcome Heroes this is the
kingdom of liel and I am its king the
guards who brought you here have
informed me that you remember not but
your own names I be I don't even
remember my name
bro one sec one sec I'm just gonna real
quick a side effect of the travel
between worlds no
doubt dot dot
dot this must all come as a surprise to
you but hearken well it was I who
summoned you summoned me from where you
see an unprecedented Calamity now
threatens our world it has swn the Earth
with corruption and driven us from our
homes you seem pretty comfortable this
blight land now gives rise to creatures
of Shadows known as stains the kingdom
of libel and its surroundings are now
the only safe place left to us left to
US
list but should the Calamity be left
unchecked is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire world
oh faced with this Pro Prospect I
scoured the ancient text for a way to
combat the Calamity and therein I found
one the ritual of hero summoning you who
hail from another world have been
summoned here to me by me to become the
saviors of listel all of us only you
have the power to save our world
and so I ask Will
you
um your majesty what is it a great host
of stains has broken through our
defensive line no we are rushing to
mount a defense but the situation is
dire Your Majesty we must get you
somewhere
safe who are these strangers dot dot dot
what say you Heroes will you accept this
Destiny to SA or there's a great power
within you will you use it to save us to
save this world I guess what
option are you giving
[Music]
me oh oh my God Heroes
hello beautiful maid it is so good to
see you I would you like a piece of
bread I would love some bread thank you
I'll take your bread
I like oh would you like some bread too
did you give me bread I don't I don't
feel like I'm G bread I
[Music]
want yeah what a big
Kingdom Ru my name I
[Music]
did you make the king I Fe the king
might have been mistaken you guys the
king I met the king he's met the king
the king is most mistaken if he thinks
that I can become a we bearer of this
SW yeah I don't think he's very smart oh
thank you I hero from another I think
they let's
see hello
[Music]
there I guess I'ma
Nissa apparently that's a a very odd
surname apparently no no surname
sorry just Nissa is
fine just Nissa apparently right I see
and you
madam might be broken this
one little broken this
one Elizabeth my really cuz above your
head it says e are blood flame what does
that all mean
what I guess it's for Elizabeth and
blood flame is my surname of course oh
Lu you I don't know my
[Music]
surname what what's my what's what's it
say above my
head it says raven COC
really who are you I guess that must be
my Sur then I guess I'm Nissa Raven
that's kind of wordy
hello yes seems like a very long name we
both have names maybe we should pair
together are how very forward of
you wow did not realize I'm in the I'm a
I'm very first
and that me I can kill you any moment at
any time can you per okay yes you told
me my name was fair Maiden you are
speaking quite quiet
is there a way that you can raise your
voice I I know we have just met but uh
so many voices around it is quite hard
to I might I might die if I raise it up
much higher but I can I that that's
probably as good as I can do is that any
better H
um one moment I must go look at this
wall and ponder over at the horiz oh yes
please Ponder at the
wall the wall that is
oh my
[Music]
God there is much to ponder about this
wall yeah there's so much to ponder
about this wall honestly what do you see
what do you
see are they speaking to us I I don't
know
honestly oh my goodness they're speaking
to us
what huh who is speaking now that it's
gone I kind of miss
of why does this this using so many
difficult words I don't understand these
words I we come from a land of simple
words is too late to save this
world stop hurting them I'm not hurting
anybody is our duty to defend our King
it's your duty not my dut I sure wish I
knew what they but this world langu me
too I don't defeat the stains oh my
God fight fight fight for the King fight
for the king there's no
choice beat you with my St wood take him
down I on the let's go
[Music]
maybe we have to kill the
uh yeah I think you might be on to
something
scried might a thing maybe we not so
hurt
oh my
God
[Music]
the where is he
gone May believe in yourself believe in
the me who believes in you I'm very
confused and a big heart and I'm a sh
help me I'm
helping thank you we got it thank you
you saved my life anything for you
little shark
girl thank you I will remember
this why do you keep
falling where is he we got to look out
for each
other
help there can we oh there's another one
get oh this
[Applause]
okay I
think shout
Revelation hold your weapon and left
click
Revelation
[Music]
re revelation
Revelation
what
Revelation go closer I can't I don't
know how to tell you guys this I'm kind
of stuck where I am right
now uh let me let me just
um uh um
okay I maybe I screamed too
hard maybe I screamed too
[Music]
hard with more
feeling with more feeling I don't know
how much more feeling I can get give
[Music]
I don't know you're good was I doing
okay the spell worked as intended I
guess I was so strong I crashed the
server whatever that
means I'm not sure maybe your voice is
too powerful I think you might be
[Music]
right the spell destroyed I think I blew
up lielle on
accident what am I supposed to do now
maybe you're the demon of sound demon of
sound what is
that I'm not
sure
well
well maybe try to sing the word
revelation okay once we get back in I'll
give it a
try tell me guys how does my mic sound
am I
peeking or
anything am I
peeking a little sounds good pretty good
you sound fine Mike is fine you're low
apparently I'm low game but if I turn my
mic up anymore I'll be
peeking so I'm not sure what to do
[Music]
scream for us to check absolutely
not H it has to be the game I'm
convinced configure your voice settings
in the game I don't know how to do
that I'm going I'm going to have to look
into it once we get back in it and
aren't trying to kill the stain
King what do you think the stain King is
what do you think stain are exactly cuz
when I think of a stain I think of like
a a stain on my
clothes so are they like dirt like
literal
dirt do you
know I'm not
sure well maybe corruption corrupt
citizens oh that would be rough corrupt
citizens I don't I don't want to hurt
people even if they're in a corrupted
form it's the Ian curse what's the Ian
curse I've never heard of that
before could someone inform
me could someone inform me about what
the Ian curse is exactly
[Music]
the an curs is an ancient evil I see an
ancient evil what does en stand for
could someone tell
me what what does en en mean
scuff
um English it means
English engineer it's like a form of
entertainment
okay so you think that the stains are
this this ancient evil the en en
curse thanks voices in my head that's
really
helpful enig so
enigmatic stands for English so it's
English
sigmatic what does that
mean what does that mean
enchanting eat nuggets
bro I could go for some nuggets right
now not like I've ever had a nugget
because I don't remember anything I
don't remember
anything I have no memories in my
head Dino nuggies what is a
dino you love
Culver do I I must i' believe it
whatever ever that is sounds
delicious you you don't remember I don't
remember
anything head empty must eat
nuggies yeah that's that's generally
where I'm at right
now had some today actually I'm jealous
[Music]
well this is
interesting you don't speak I've
never spoken Japanese ever what do you
mean I don't speak Japanese anymore do
you like to
sing I don't
know do I like to
sing if you told me so I'd probably
believe it you have 93
prayer what's
that you love
[Music]
Idols I'm door dashing cers you guys
want
anything I I could go for some cheese
right
now do you know this lovely lady named
hoso
madin you know that rings a bell
actually I think you guys are Awakening
something in my brain that sounds really
familiar
remember RuneScape it vaguely rings a
bell but when I think about it nothing
comes to mind but it sounds
familiar do you know who is kiata wait
wasn't that the name of someone someone
in the place today leis
still I feel like I feel like I I saw
someone with that
name remember the no
pan No pans like no pans for cook
[Music]
looking
uh Kiara is your rival my rival wait
wait I need I need more information on
this I need more can you guys please
give me more information so I have a
rival you're telling me and her name is
taka her name is
Kiara Kiara is your wife lies
oh oh yes she's your rival she wants to
eat you oh my
[Music]
goodness she's my
Oshi she's my wife no
rival you guys are giving me really
conflicting answers all of these people
there's something about them that feels
Vaguely Familiar to me but at the same
time I just feel like I've never seen
them before and I'm so lost I'm so
confused and I feel like I need
clarification and you guys seem to know
something something shodin is also your
wife you
remember you mean like the shodin Nolla
niela
person who was also I have two wives you
have three wives you have a ton of wives
bro herb is your rival
but we were getting along so well
you were getting along so well what do
you mean we're
Rivals you remember a zombie named olly
I feel like I'd remember but what is
awells oh wait I've been in this place
before this is so de shja Vu oh my God
we're back guys did you know we we
failed to save the world once that was
that was the that was the world
so is this like a different timeline oh
my God for have turned back the time
your yourness maybe we you can go back
and His Highness we finish the proposal
and you can get me out of here that is
very correct
this then we can go
back save the
world C
from your your marriage I'm not going to
call off my marriage we're going to call
off this journey and you're going to go
to your retirement and I
will hail you
Kingdom
I oh yourness I must ref that sounds
like way too much pressure and
responsibility I just
I a
Shar I find it absolutely adorable that
you in the Kake you similar vocabulary
like
May hi
your I will stick by your side
apparently I'm quiet is your
highness I don't know how to fix it
fix you is fine to the B is fine you I
I'd like that can you fix me
please there is a in
there
thank me I will fix B I mean that hot
bab over there yeah that hot babe over
there yeah I need to fix fix her you are
so my sword they've taken a weapon
yourness
as
well who doing this how are they robbing
all of us w w w w w w the crazy red one
everything is under
control you're crazy she called you
crazy crazy break
out
all won't let us out of these walls man
H beautiful
hello the voices in my head told me
you're my
w well I guess I'll tell her some other
time echo of for we've seen this all
before how can I get through it
fast
faster
okay I feel empty
relieved perhaps distraught
I remember this I do not
know so much I don't know and
yet the bright light it calls to me the
fastest to Skipper Skipper I wasn't
skipping I was reading I was thinking
that was my head sure yeah it was all in
our heads I was yeah it was all in our
heads there's no first let's go let's go
to the light slow down you are cheating
you cheating
oh
wait oh you can't walk on this hole
that's
crazy whoa give me a heart
attack does that
mean whoa make you baby bro
what what who are you I don't know who
who who are you yeah who are you the
voices in my head told me to call you be
boo I I does that ring a bell able to
distinguish it but it's
disting yeah I don't know what a b boo
is either I have no idea where they got
that from don't know I'm uhhuh that's
what I thought too they said that you
were my wife I don't like that at all
apparently but I've never seen you
before in my life I see a ring on it I
don't see a ring on you either block
yeah me too maybe you guys happening
over
okay I don't know it's a first meeting
I'm not ready I don't know who she
is don't
know we didn't finish our
conversation the voices on my head said
that you my
wife that might be uh because I find you
very attractive you you do I find you
very attractive too like let's go look
at that behind
[Music]
yeah yes you know they say we have to
save yes but I think what they really
mean is we have to save the
[Music]
lesbians I think they might be right
let's save them together let's do it
okay for the lesbians we're the lesbians
save you
guys save
[Music]
you I'm
sure Lou I need privacy hello
[Laughter]
privacy Li Estel Castle
I remember I remember this so I think we
can safely we can
um I I I can fast forward because to
totally I that is something I'm capable
of doing it's fast
[Music]
forwarding Skipper
Skipper Skipper Skipper Skipper skipper
[Music]
okay
okay John John
Watson hello what I told the king of
your of your plan no you didn't D I
didn't but I was thinking about it I
forgot your name cuz you didn't you
sound like a crazy person so I don't
think you took any of it seriously back
to
the why are we
back I thought her hardness was
going here everyone wait I know what
happened you know what happen en how do
you know how do you know I
remember remember there was a battle
right here am I crazy no I remember too
yes you cra are we in an endless loop
I'm going to follow her how do we break
it doors I thought out I thought I
cracked the code thought we could get in
here in there yeah that would be nice I
I don't really feel like fighting
again you're quite Cav like your voice
texture yeah we can hide texture of your
voice
yeah can we destroy this green stuff
[Music]
not with such a dull sword yeah how do
they expect us to fight with these I
[Music]
know come on no one will ever didn't we
have this
before my days in peace well goodbye Le
why do you guys look to same I
put I don't know I'm leaving
I don't I don't need this I'm not a hero
I'm just a
girls oh my where did you come from
there I've been here all along I I'm
leaving leave Estel I'm not meant to be
a hero you see oh I've already tried
trust me this is the Fest we can go oh
my God we're TR PR I'm pretty sure we're
or something there they just took our
will from us that's not
fair I know they gave us bread and a
sword and expect us to fight no wonder
they're dying from the
stains I helped people as a Reaper right
that's an important job you're a
Reaper help help get behind me beautiful
help there two dogs two dogs are
attacking me for no reason do
and it's good when she prays uh well it
though h i i i don't think I have heard
it but I think you should leave her
alone whoever you are leave her
alone yeah don't be a
bully I'm not bullying her I'm bully I
just want to hear the pring do do you
look like you might be a dog so do you
bark do you bark yeah yeah yeah bark for
me yeah bark for me yeah bark for me
come
come on puppy yeah for me you have dog
ears in a
tail bar for me too yeah for me B but I
don't think that's Bing it's cute though
Bow Bow Bow Bow yeah she is barking yeah
that's why you hate me I don't hate
you can you per us I want to hear too
I'm a little
curious wait big guys are talking here's
danger of this okay
oh oh you're right it is
nice Follow The
Queen all
right my father you mother you look
awfully out of water to be honest
daughter you're not say
that grandmother's
[Music]
who's this little
guy
please I think you hit your head pretty
I I all I know is that my name and and
now I have family this is glorious I
know how they move
[Music]
must I will for you father
cousin oh my God
[Music]
I feel
[Applause]
bading hit him from the
back after all really I don't think he
has I don't think he has a weak point is
he taking damage doing
anything well looks like Australia joed
here what's up
Australia
Australia oh thank you sharp girl a stby
little
tail she me has a for the last time
line Kill The King The King The
[Music]
don't hurt my wife don't hurt my wife oh
what we're on a mission to save
the stop that he's
like for each Lo yeah I'm scared we
better not lose this Loop then
[Applause]
R this is
fabulous look at the
hero
okay are we here
again revelation
Revelation the stain host has been
routed
[Music]
what what's happening
what's going
[Music]
on
what what was that thing that came out
of nowhere it looked like a tuning
fork I heard the news though we called
upon you suddenly you Rose to the
occasion you have my deepest gratitude
where is he
uh what interests me most however is the
strange power you manifested during the
battle with which you were able to
defeat the stains the power May well be
the key to saving our world from
Annihilation me my
power my
power can I take the
throne since he's not here
[Music]
here here so Heroes I ask you once more
will you lend us your on behalf of all
libon I thank
you
[Music]
what okay
okay okay okay I'm moving I'm I'm
moving you're in jail
why step on the platform and receive the
will of the
ancestor
[Music]
whoa okay the will of the
ancestors so begin a journey to find who
I
am Scarlet
wand
wait Dawn the
cloak how do how do
I armed with an unwavering will seek to
defeat the soul of
Jade okay enigmatic recollection
whoa speak to your Guild's Guild
Master how why do I have so many things
in my inventory all of a
[Music]
sudden
um don't kill the guy I'm not trying to
uh
[Music]
H
okay
um I'm right
clicking I'm right clicking
[Music]
but
oh don't you also feel like opening
every chest you
see
okay every every other person I'm
clicking to will talk to
me but the Guild Master doesn't want to
go inside
[Music]
where is the entrance maybe
here
whoa terribly sorry but we're still
cleaning up the mass after the stain
attack do stop by some other
time maybe I'm I don't know he looks
like the The Guild Master don't you
think look an
axi Scarlet people you're here
too
yeah what's up we have to talk to the
Guild Master I I don't know honestly oh
what's there's a radio you think we can
jam T Tunes maybe oh what's what's this
maybe like a take after oh hey what's
upti lady hello oh what do you have an
apple an apple Golden Apple I have
whatever this is wor on it you got this
giant weapon and I just got a gold Fork
you just got a what do I have I have a
feather I'm going to tickle you guys oh
no tickle tickle is the most dangerous
of all I know no one ever suspect think
I just used it I just used it fa can you
click on this guy here and tell me what
happens click on him yeah right right
click on him click or right click yeah
we don't understand the language without
the power of privacy settings oh a good
morrow welcome to the humble Guild Hall
of the Scarlet wand I Am The Guild
Master
rubius um I think that's all he has to
say oh oh no he's got more thank you for
joining the battle to save Lial so soon
after your summoning that you will
henceforth be working with us to mount
resistance against the stains and save
this world hey oh my gosh hi are you
also Scarlet W
people you get that feather cool feather
man I like your Trident that's
sick thank you I like
your I like your wooden sword yeah it's
not it's great I have something cool too
I have this this cool
thing your oh
cool welcome you have a what oh hi oh
hey what's what do you
have I have a cloak I have um red a
cloak I got a cloak a cloak a I've got
one more thing hold on guys oh you got a
giant like uh
Christmas I got a feather I'm going to
tickle everyone's death
no oh that was short I
thought you're not going to like it yeah
this guy right here
rubius rubius
rubius cuz he's red like a ruby we all
red are we all together I'm so
stupid here we're all on the same team
it looks like yeah my
bad we're going to crush it says I'm in
a party with how do I oh yeah for sure
speak to your guils master should I keep
reading yeah you got to right click him
yeah just go through all all of it but
first would behoove you to learn more
sorry I miss now going to town and you
should find a quest
board why don't you go there and speak
with the quest Master it would be a
prime opportunity to explore the town as
well
okay yay thank you so much okay we got
to go to the quest
board we have to be in a party or is
this fine oh maybe we should make a
party a okay how do we do that um I
think oh wait are you two able to join a
party I I let's try it can you attempt
to invite us to your
party yeah can it be I need to look at
the tutorial cool enough to join your
party he you may forming parties right
click on who you want
invite and then just press the blue one
okay I'm going to invite you guys I I
can't anything actually okay oh well we
can always be
unari how do you accept yeah I guess I
guess I could
solo let me let me solo it you know yeah
how do you kind of sad but how do I
accept the party um
accept I can't press accept accept uh
let me see
except oh wait you click on you click on
oh hey I'm in the party wa I'm in the
party wa wait wait how did you join how
did you join some I I didn't I I didn't
do anything I just pressed random
buttons please please invite me
again wait is it is it the back I good
about this Guild something about
[Laughter]
it does anyone know where the social
menu is wait why is B in the party
because she's been we B and I were in
the party from the beginning but how do
I like it says click um on the right it
says when the person if you click on the
person you party with again the right of
the oh I have to find B in order to kick
her
oh there there goes she oh
no okay it's fine we don't have to be in
the party in the beginning I'm sure it's
fine yeah I guess I'll just we can
introduce ourselves I'll just follow you
guys how about that you guys is my horse
tired do you guys want to okay do you
guys want to you like my horse yeah
where's the quest
board how do I actually I don't know we
have a map but sh is it this way I don't
know what did he say did anybody
remember what he said he said good job
go to the quest board to the quest
Master see where is the quest board this
looks so
[Music]
cute are are we just
I don't know where we're going
guy um we're trying to find a quest
[Music]
board somebody completed it let's
go to the oh wait
no oh speak to Quest Master how you
speak to him
uh to the right click oh okay yeah yeah
I think you actually to just Spam it
next
uh it on the
map it's like somewhere over here follow
me into
town our new leader yeah I used the
map good good reading skills thank you
it's my
talent we might have to go through this
big
building or go around it
yeah is this like all the Scarlet area
or is like over there that that maybe
that's the yellow yeah eventually we'll
I think we'll cross into other areas I
think we lost two
people should should we go back for them
we we probably should oh okay let's
let's go grab
[Music]
them all
right oh hey hey is that town this way
yeah yeah yeah we're we're all heading
this way it looks like the The Guild
Master is or the quest Master's here so
I I'm leading the way but we we lost you
two so we're heading
back I see you my bad no no problem dire
I I would have done the same
thingi yeah where is
shiori she took off towards the Middle
where are you did she uh well do you
think she made it to the
I Quest area let's just go without her
she'll catch up okay okay this
[Music]
[Laughter]
way to
us what's
up is it the front of this giant thing
no it's it's going to be further in the
corner it it looks like it's kind of far
away I I'm looking at it on my map it's
marked oh I see it is Mark yeah you do
have a
[Music]
talent thank goodness I need to have
something
okay somewhere in this house maybe no no
no no no sorry
[Music]
around around the house this is the long
way I'm so sorry I am not being a very
good Navigator I trust you completely
I'm so sorry I could not even manage to
see the text on the
map
okay somewhere back
here oh my my God it's that red Lady
Elizabeth
yeah yes that is
I okay Quest board Acquired and we found
Shori
too it's a wonderful stallion hey what's
up girls complete the side quest what
is where is the side quest we need to go
to
[Music]
can help
usaly I'm The
[Music]
Apprentice I've
aced
Masters May right cck understand your
main is to erate the stain but I hope
you'll have the time for some citizens
in need how about we get
started best of luck off you go we go
now
where is the Smithy wait what quest we
have to complete the
quest this looks like the perfect
job the M we can go to the Smithy yeah
let's go
wait my friends at Scarlet
one were we able to kick out that that
General can I join the party
yet going on a quest you to join us I'll
join you of course we are gu the same
Quest join
us let's go to the with side
quest do know side I the only one
available yeah materials needed at the
Smithy I'm The Apprentice at the Smithy
and my master says we're running low on
Raw materal if you can help us gather
some please stop by the
[Music]
Smith come to the quest board please I
think is there a way we can fix our
group chat because it would be a lot
less chaotic if we were the only ones we
can
here I don't I think apart from just
turning everyone else down probably
not isn't it a radio and a party
there she is okay okay okay okay okay
okay fre stand still do not move I shall
free you I will take you from my
party how do I get off the
horse how do I accept
on it
I
I click on it I spent time with my
please show me the
master helpa accept the quest I have
invited you to my party I have to talk
to the Guild Master I skipped them we'll
wait until wait wait wait this is I just
my head I hit my head real hard this is
a lot to take in all that once holy moly
sh do you really not remember what you
clicked to join how to accept the
invitation I don't know since I've only
invited my it happened automatically for
me I don't I don't know I'm so sorry I
missed what you have
said you maybe f f maybe oh yeah maybe
fun us F I don't know where fun went
[Music]
though I think maybe she's helping she
to get to the quest master I see I see I
see the guy in the beginning so I guess
we just
wait you wait wait wait wait wait t uh T
and then so open your chat and then you
click accept um I can't open my chat
going use our to get there can you do
that nice idea let us ride oh mine it
won't
open Perhaps Perhaps not oh
I think maybe she's muted n are you
muted I'm not muted no I'm not muted
wait wait sorry I didn't mean to mute I
can't open my
chat okay but earlier sh said the same
problem yeah me and shy have the same
problem but she got in somehow so she
probably got in so let's just wait until
she comes back and then you'll know how
to be and right now no one's close to us
so it's not that big of yeah I mean she
afterwards we can be in a group chat
yeah she she said she just clicked
random buttons I tried to spam all of
mine but nothing
happened up here yeah if
youa the right click on the
board it opens up Social menu for
[Music]
trade so I'm not okay
particularly uh we know we know how to
do it I'm in the party guys no worries
we know how to do it it's just
um we
go has some bug with the check thingy
[Music]
yeah
um uh
see wait successfully joined party okay
okay okay okay we're so we're so in
we're so we're SE okay we're in the
quest
woo thanks for waiting I'm so
sorry good
question we need they need materials at
the Smithy so I think we need to
go find the Smithy maybe it's marked on
the map let me pull up my map again and
see if it says anything
how do you zoom out on this thing uh I
don't think we can which is
not particularly
helpful but you know Green oh it is wait
wait bottom Green Oh you see it okay see
it Cecilia onward let's go following the
gura okay this yes this way way yes
thank goodness
trust
me it's so cute I think I do believe I
trust I
hear but I want to
usey hello excuse me people scare me a
of big
crows
oh
okay the blacksmith the required
materials we need Oak
from up yonder hath Fallen to their
death hath Fallen poor
girl this two Scarlet wand member oh
great we saw the quest they posted while
start could you bring 10 okay it looks
like we need
wood to purchase we are missing four
five 10 10 oak logs I think that's very
easy my
friend I
think we
got completed
exactly completed sneak the just that
easy my
friends o all s of tools
easy interesting I have an
axe I think need
coins
M Master see did you say we needed
collect 10 cobblestones
all
right I guess we have
to okay somehow I had the wood and gave
it to him I'm I think I'm confused I
think maybe we need wood wood 10 Oak cuz
yeah let's go find some want to craft
some
stuff is anywhere
good is this can't time to chop down a
tree in the
I'm sure they would notice if we take a
little
bit
oh what about that big tree do you see
that
there the Town Center Tree the giant
tree surely surely we can destroy since
the conception of Li Li style don't
worry they w't notice yeah I don't think
they'll notice either a little bit of it
yeah just a we just need 10 just a
little the tree that fed this Village
for centuries
ah it is now a quest item is this
Oak
H where are we supposed to get
wood well what about here this looks
like a did you randomly get 100 coins by
clicking on him again and again no I
have 100 coins and I think it said that
I successfully completed the quest but I
didn't do anything
you hacking me I guess he's hacking I
must be where do you guys where do you
guys see the quest sorry uh I don't I
just still see the materials needed at
the Smithy but it doesn't tell me what's
needed because for me it just says
complete the side
quest it doesn't say like oh a child oh
we can't cut this
tree oh God oh God I didn't accept it
Quest yes I did no did I not maybe maybe
the map will tell us
again uh
no that's
great H what you guys mind if
we did did you not can we go back to the
quest Master do you still need to pick
up the
quest yeah but I think if it's just wood
then it doesn't matter if I get the wood
first I can I can go yeah yeah I mean we
can't get wood from here anyway so yeah
all right where are you oh we're right
here
where are
you we're right
here I got fun on the phone I don't know
where you sure we are that's true where
are you guys yeah where are they
hiding B I don't know oh okay we're
coming back to you so stay
there
okay
okay I made a loud noise now they'll be
able to find us is there a way to change
to group so that we hear the other five
despite proximity I don't think so
yeah how do I hang up the
phone private call
oh calling ring ring ring ring ring guys
use pick up a phone wait who are you
calling I'm calling the party oh not you
was talking I I got to figure out how to
hang on the phone
okay bye we'll just go back to the quest
Master it's nearby like at the
blacksmith oh they're at the blacksmith
okay we're closer to the quest master so
we'll we'll go there first so she can
pick up the quest properly and then
we'll head back to the black Smith
sounds good okay so CC did you talk here
and then accept the quest on the board
wait she's going okay okay oh
[Music]
CeCe there she is hello yay hi I'm just
going to The Question Master real quick
yeah yeah you just need to you need to
talk to him and then you need to click
here to accept the quest on the actual
born hey this looks like the perfect job
for you B of look off goce at the
smothie and my master says running ra
material stop
by okay why can't I speak to this Quest
master I thought this did you finish the
quest was I did oh I have now finished
farewell where do you where do you wait
farewell maidens oh yes yes would you
like to um where did you get wood from
could you tell
meide outside where head forward to the
to the city gate and
exit yes towards The City Gate there
will be an or I will lead you outwards
outside the city game we prank do we
have to go to the city first can we just
go out I I think we can get the wood
first and then go to the smiy obtain you
can do whichever okay so you said this
way is out you said can we the wood and
then the
Smithy can we can we
yeah construction I'm going to see
accepting oh I'm going to go get some
wood do you want to come with or do you
want to go to the Smithy
I was going to go to the
smth let's go get him cuz I just want to
make sure cuz I others is this the way
yes this is the way this is the
way this is this is also the way I think
up you correct it's this building right
here oh I see I see I see somebody else
just did
the all
right you bring over 10 oak logs there's
a bunch of trees not far out outside the
town that you can
chop okay let's try going outside how
you outside of town okay uh I think uh
maybe here this way this way to the
right do we got
everybody we are three ah well let's go
the giant gate maybe yeah I think the
giant gate might be where we need to go
Scarlet wand of
three don't where are the other two I'm
going to make you know what this feels
like this feels
like like we need matching shirts
yeah we need hat something where okay
hello okay where are you guys
now okay we got to click this orm oh
okay we we'll meet you there we're going
outside now
too okay
okay okay good talk okay oh by the
way
oh okay we're
here now we can get
[Music]
wood let's
go okay 10 10 logs of
[Music]
Oak please tell me this is Oak
no this is
Spruce what about
this are you Oak you look like
Oak yes
[Music]
okay I got
some bro what what's
[Music]
happening bro what
bro pick on somebody else I'm just a
girl bro what I'm just trying to get
[Music]
wood why are there so many attacking
specifically
[Music]
me worry I got
you please I'm just trying to get some
wood
I got
you
[Music]
maybe owie these things are strong man
oh y they are a bit
strong mayhaps who oh we should probably
run I think they after us uhoh
Revelation
[Music]
Revelation okay okay okay okay okay it's
okay it's fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm
fine I'm fine I'll protect you fair
Maiden it's okay it's okay I'm fine
we're
good get
lost you have all the ls that you need I
have 14 do we have enough for everyone
to have 10 we do we do okay let's
go
woo make haste team how does one summon
the
gate
okay did she get stuck we're good I bre
though please say yes we're back
together
again yay what's up hooray okay let us
go back to the blacksmith yes we can
have horses if we use a summoning seed
egg that is
true you have a pretty horse pretty
brown I must do it myself you she has to
hurt the very thing she does not want
to
okay oh the more things to be able to
make we completed thank you so much see
my master over there if you bring the
raw materials can s all the tools and
items for you made it
Cobblestone too many people are speaking
to him at
once all of our money am I am I using
all 10 cob okay think money has not
decreased I think that's your
money I have your wood how much money do
you have a wooden pickaxe at the SM TR
I'm richer than three ha to purchase you
don't have the required
materials completed collect 10 o speak
to the black Smith appr create a
Wen that I can make whatever I want if I
just put in the heart of it wow what am
I my hands are moving on its
own yeah wooden pickaxe did not
work the pickaxe did not work why did
the pickaxe not work needs sticks oh he
needs sticks yeah he needs sticks did I
did I do it wrong
[Music]
coins
money hey how do you make a a
pickaxe it's not letting me got to make
the silly items
this okay okay okay
I've created the wooden
pickaxe great from now on when you find
new materials stop by here and talk to
my master the more different materials
you find the more things he'll be able
to
make see my master okay IAL to then
speak to the black okay can you bring us
10 Cobblestone nexts you can probably
find some lying around in the same place
you chopped the
wood so you do the and then you turn it
into oak plants and then you make sticks
I think you need like four or four and
then you talk to the guy with a glass
yeah wow I don't feel like a hero I feel
more like a okay I I think I think I
understand let me let me try let me
try yeah right he going to ask us
for quite
fou I don't
really they're right Superior way to
travel
yes okay
why just need 10 right oh this is this
is
unusual well I guess I'll wing it
oh that's very
weird yeah this is
different for what oh
you dearest Nissa yes where are you uh
I I'm I'm getting
Cobblestone oh okay Nissa is outside
getting cob I'm going to get enough for
both of
you so just wait she's getting enough
for both of you should we go still or I
was thinking why if we take all the
Cobblestone so no one else can do it
yeah we should prevent the other
team yeah okay let's just to the by
byebye yeah let's let's Rush was she on
the phone
oh yeah they call me they asked where I
went I was talking to you like you were
talking I'm so
sorry okay do I've got I've got 31 so
let's head back oh
hi hi I got enough for you too oh
response darn thank you I got hit by a
orse how do I throw them an orse an orse
yeah I think you have to trade to left
and right click at the same time wait I
have to trade so you're done you
normally oh my God okay I'm sorry I
can't share with you after all maybe
here I I have some I'm sorry I hit trade
oh never mind you're trading with
someone else I'm sorry Who Who Are You
trading with I'm sorry trade with Nissa
oh no wow I see how it is here no one
want to chaed me I see right click oh
right
click no that doesn't do anything a
trade okay wait noises you can only have
one trade active what do you
mean me into
a maybe if I go here s it'll it'll leave
maybe it'll cancel
sorry collect
cobone I don't know is
happening I'm just going to I'm just
going to go the trade has expired okay
thank goodness will you buy it from
him the he now you brought some cob talk
to my mouse you should be able to make
you stone tools give it a try talk to
him
[Music]
yeah to him Cobblestone and sticks okay
I will talk to them the blacksmith's
Apprentice oh I see okay now I can talk
to you oh I see now it makes sense from
now on you okay I think I finished
complete the
quest I think the quest is done I think
we finished the
quest successfully I don't want to talk
to him then you bright as we were losing
hope uhuh okay I wonder what would suit
you best bring Cobblestone next and
probably find some
[Music]
around yes
Rock okay I shop I I have seem to have
lost my way shop is the
shop I see that in the corner of my
vision for some reason what do you see
oh crap the quest master's like so far I
know if only we had something to move
faster wait um know I got the same Quest
though okay theard I see yet to finish
the quest oh yeah there are many we're
close enough for sure I know you but I
hope you stop board you pressed for time
I don't have a look around
[Music]
town talk to the
shopkeeper all ready let's go get
cobblestone
onwards oh I'm going the wrong
[Music]
way
sneak
sneak I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
just thank you for saving the town all
our lives welcome to the humble little
shop all you have to do is talk to me
and see what I've gotten stuck then
select what you want is that
easy make sure you have enough coins
okay just stop by if you ever need
anything sure you fight stains all day
not know these memories they trying to
Guild halls for instance each of them
has activity you can participate in many
of my customers are regulars at the
arena for instance when you're tired
from adventuring or simply looking for a
little diversion maybe give some of
these activities to try take your mind
off your quest now and then it'll do
good you have some time why not visit
the Gardens children are attending them
I sure you'd be overjoyed to meet a real
hero such as
yourself speak to a a
[Music]
child I don't want to speak to a random
child in the garden
didn't I see this child
before
yes oh
no oh no it's another one of those
[Music]
situations server broke it's just
it's since we're alone it seems like
it's just me and shiori who are having
this problem because our thing wasn't
turned on and even though we've gone and
turned it on
now it has it's cuz you see how it says
this we've already gone and we've
corrected the problem but apparently it
takes a few hours to to make itself
work and it it won't fix
itself
um
uh um yeah a few a few hours so I can't
talk to this
child meaning quite literally I am lost
uh I'm going to try
something real quick I'm going to turn
off I'm going to turn off uh that's
incorrect okay going to turn this off
I'm going to try something all
right it might take me a minute okay
quit um cuz I would
like I would like this to
work I would really like this to
work I really want to be involved
too I want to have a good time with
everyone so give me one
second but it's it's a bit unfortunate
because admittedly I have to go in about
20 minutes anyway due to
some preparation
stuff but I'm going to do what I can so
I can at least play until
then okay let me see if this helps at
[Music]
all
um
um okay
have a it should be ready it should be
ready next time the issue is that we've
already turned everything on but it just
takes apparently a few hours or
something to integrate the changes for
some reason
so we're trying we're trying our our
best okay it's loading it's
[Music]
loading it's loading back in at least
you have this nice music to listen to am
I
[Music]
right
okay yeah the bgm is great we feel like
we're on an adventure
hello Nissa
hello where are you I'm by I'm trying to
fix my
game okay but I'm by the LI best in
child in the Gardens at the moment oh
okay okay we were about to head there
I'm here I'm talking to the child I
think my issues might be fixed maybe
okay we'll we'll meet you by the child
okay okay thank you I love you bye
right this is the hero's Garden you're
free to come and use them whenever you'd
like pretty Aces isn't it pretty Aces a
it myob to keep an eye on them scare
away birds and stuff if you don't like
gardening you can also try building
there's an emptied lot just past you
Heroes can build whatever you like you
and your g ma can work together to make
a right spiffy place to stay let me turn
on the screen that that might be a good
idea that might be helpful actually it
might take a moment to come back in
sorry
stop by anytime if you want to do any
building or
[Music]
gardening
bye-bye okay I've talked to the child so
can
I oh say can I tell you a secret did you
know there's a place in town called the
pit mom says kids aren't allowed to go
but I he you can play a really fun game
there yeah here so bet they'll let you
in maybe you can go and check it out
tell me what it's like anyway hope to
see you
again wow wow hi FAA yeah look at this
child he sounds like a cockney
person oh yeah I can certainly voice act
that please do
yay want we found the child must be my
lucky
all right well this year over to come
and use whatever you
like is
it keep an eye on them tin stare away
the birds and stuff if you don't like
gardening you can also try
building there's an empty lot just past
here where you arrows can build whatever
you like
[Laughter]
arrows you and your guild mates could
work together to make a voice place to
stay stop by any time if you want to do
some building or
gardening you AET did you know there's a
place in town called the pit the pit
says us kids aren't allowed to go but I
hear you can play a really fun game
there sounds why would terrible way to
advertise towards children it's so fun
but you can't go you're a hero sorry but
maybe you could go check it out and tell
me what it's like anyway let's Rush
there what a charismatic child able to
loudly talk in front of five people very
impressive okay did we rescue him oh
finally he's finally talking to me oh
thank gosh oh thank
goodness just skip through it it's okay
FAA read it for you let's run cute it is
to the pit L to the pit
oh oh hello
hi you think they finished all their
Quest other honestly I want to
know oh are horses allowed in here I
don't think they
are
okay lucky lady lucky lady I've got a
game for you oh says your new face don't
tell me you're one of those Heroes who
save the town aren't you you want to get
rich I know it could make you a fortune
wait don't gu promise it ain't nothing
Shady look about how I tell she
something useful see I used to run with
the Jade show for I join the Amber
coin the master took out the some I
don't know what he's saying I can't read
this what is
just just point yourself at your m right
click on her from there you can select
whatever to invite her to your party a
trade with
her now you can aveng it together swap
items and coins say told you it was
useful didn't I you'll thank me for when
you're
adventuring uh I know you're very
important Mission World C on you it be a
lot easier if you add some extra coins
know what I'm
saying give us the money then your
pockets have feel too light or too heavy
maybe come down here to the play around
too Shake him Shake him bro I don't
care ju just stop talking to me
bro bro quite simply I don't care yeah
bro quite simply shut up yeah
literally let's beat him up and take his
wallet okay does he have one I take his
bow tie in hit him hit him excuse me
wait we're
crit pause
standing I think I
do we got to speak to
Bri
way oh no there and the Amber coin it's
okay you guys can go ahead without me
just hit just hit shift a
lot sword fin yay I got it Okay Jade
sword come this way is that where it is
that's where it is yeah yeah it
is it's
that the one who looked at
funny veridus where are you hiding
oops okay we got to get in here
[Music]
maybe I can jump from a high I'm not
sure where I'm going and I don't know
why I'm pretty sure he's not up
[Music]
here yeah he's not up here
um okay that was not correct listen to
your heart I tried and it was the wrong
decision
for a
show I'm missing I'm missing the the
context I'm missing everything
important I don't know how to get to him
oh cuz they're the like they're the fry
ones
yeah they're The Feisty ones they're
feral we don't know about here he is
MERS see you returned Brave hero
[Music]
prettyy you don't want to get in between
them they all the
same can't say
[Music]
that I am not familiarized myself with
town at all yeah
same must be
shaking
join H oh oh you were calling me the
Calamity I was like what the
sound hey you just got to you know you
just got to follow like why can't I talk
to you but the flames right it's
horrible
okay okay well got the biggest
hat Mumble
Mumble what's the mission after this um
exit the Town Gate head to the Plains
and speak to a Hostess of the Jade sword
I'll keeping
here
okay two
Hostess maybe maybe one of you
lead let's haste into hustus
hustus with
[Music]
haste follow that shark
is
work this GPS is kind of bad it doesn't
update very quickly yeah it's
okay at least we have each
other I hope we're all I hope we're all
gathered yeah
same we have one
two
well um
let's
well I think we lost him hey there's a
bunny over
here there's bunny too far I think we
went too far I think we back inside he
he's in here he's he's um he's
here oh
[Music]
pry Co yeah he's he's across the
bridge
see
oh there she is he's right
here oh hello H hero you are arrived we
have been expecting you our initial Fay
have determined that the portal into the
runes is yet sealed with no way to enter
the runes we are at a loss for for how
to proceed some have reported hearing a
strange voice but we know not what to
make of it the voice seemed to be saying
The Souls of stains open the way uh what
might it mean by
that uh all
right he is this hus yeah H ow it's hus
hero you are
arrived 1 2 3 4 5
The Souls of open the
way
okay okay we have to kill we have to
kill 10 stains I okay
okay I think so
sadly all right I killed I killed one I
killed
[Music]
two oh this one sounds like a sad little
dog now I feel
bad yeah we reached
it oh okay so I'm going to read for you
now
surely I should um maybe I bought this
sword so maybe I should use
[Music]
it yeah not not the sad
whimper I'm not I'm not built for that
[Music]
die and scares me every time oh
it's it's it's the slow in my
head this one just sounds so SC I know
it makes me sad I'm not sure we're the
heroes after all yeahoo
have I not killed 10 yet excuse me I'm
not
[Music]
counting it should normally count each
St man I have no idea how many I've
killed but definitely not
enough I've got to be
close was someone counting in chat
anyone know how many of these things
I've killed
[Music]
huh
okay five enough soon seven five or four
I feel like it's been more than
that objective completed K
hers then she doesn't get
anys okay
wait okay
so what does everybody else's weapons do
I don't know your
tickles so we have a Healer we have a
Tickler we have a a mop
Revelation investigate the underworld
dungeon then speak to the Jade swword
Guild
Master I wonder how long this will
take because huh bird girl we must
attend to a meeting I know in our heads
I know yes I'm
aware I am man you and I have great
minds but I I really want to keep
playing I mean I really want to
enter oh yeah probably says that it's
complete do do the three of you think
that you will be fine without me and
lady
shiori I think we will be we can do it
we won't let you down Scarlet wand we'll
be we'll be back we'll be back for the
next one
okay okay we're sorry okay thank you
guys we can't wait to play again or I
mean to fight together again are you
leaving my wife we must we must
away yes we have Advent the fireball man
yeah holy CRA me the Phoenix of the
fires and the oranges hello lady of
water Lady of water I can put out your
flame in an instant with try it then put
out my flame you're on cool down a do
Scarlet good luck thank you goodby at
least I can swim
un at least I can swim unlike you oh all
right
jilberts thank you so much for coming
I'm sorry for having to dip out early I
really wanted to keep playing but I
think due to some unforeseen issues it
ended up going a little bit longer than
expected but uh let me quick I want to
Quick um show you before I
go my coat one sec cuz this is this is
slick can we just take a moment to enjoy
like look at
that look at that so as you guys may
know I am appearing in anime impulse
tomorrow in some panels and a meet and
greet so sadly I will not be streaming
tomorrow but just to let you guys know
this whole week is going to be playing
andreco enigmatic Recollections so
please tune in Lots after tomorrow
because uh I I I might not be around
Monday too we we'll have to wait and see
but uh please tune in
lots for more and Reco I'm looking
forward to playing and thank you all so
much for coming and for joining and I
look forward to the rest of our
adventure here with you guys and with
Team Scarlet wand so uh where uh one
sec where's I'm missing
something I'm missing something really
important huh I'm missing my end screen
there it is that's
weird all right
well thank you guys so much for coming
uh again look at this cool
Cape super excited to be playing the
rest of this uh next time we play
probably me and the rest of Advent will
try and play at the same time and go
into the underworld dungeon together so
please do keep an eye out I know all the
other Sunfire are going to be going
through it uh themselves let's go ahead
and raid into one of them one sec let's
go ahead and raid into fou into
fa so you guys can see the rest of
what's Happening from Scarlet wand's
perspective go Scarlet wand so all right
thank you guys so much again for coming
and I'll see you all next time bye
Darlings
[Music]