[Music]
wait wait wa wait that's not how I want
it to
appear guys I I I swear this is not
clickbait I I have a really really
really really really really
really important thing to talk about I I
am in shock and I really needed to talk
about
it I can never recover from
this holy
[\h__\h] please
listen
um I don't even know where to start this
I don't even know I don't even know what
to do I was I was walking outside for
like 20 minutes 30 30 minutes I was
walking outside for 30
minutes I will never go outside again or
we have to go through other measures
[Music]
but I was going to just tweet this but I
realized if I just tweet this you guys
will need a an explanation
so
uh I have a hole in my
ass
[Music]
[Laughter]
I walked outside for 30 minutes with a
hole in
my
I can't I can't I can't and the thing is
this is not the warn State when I was
wearing it it was stretched out because
my ass is too big my ass is too
big
[\h__\h] I noticed in in the in the mirror
of the elevator when I came back after a
30 minute
walk
outside
help I was like what the [\h__\h] this is
much bigger when I'm actually wearing it
my whole ass crack would be seen if I
wasn't wearing
underwear but I was wearing underwear
but I have hole in my
ass I can't I can't I can't I I can't
believe it I cannot this is the I think
this is the
inside can you this is I don't
understand like the last time I wore
these
pants I
would I would think they were not like
this I haven't worn them in a while but
holy [\h__\h] I think it's because I have a
lot of moths in my in in my closet I
have a moth
[Laughter]
problem y this is like so much bigger
when I
wear does I think I have
only one last
thing left to
do
Ben
[Music]
Prince